foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
I'm using everything
do you feel my music
[Music]
I I can't do this Night books for me
because I can't open the box
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
and my secret weapon
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
okay okay
oh my God
[Laughter]
[Music]
ah
kick it
oh my God no go away
cat you know I just woke up which means
we just woke up so
you know my cats are they also just woke
up and now they're really active I'm
tired but they're really active
now they're on on the place where I'm
supposed to show things
they're in the way and they're like when
I push them away they jump back up
now when I close the door then they're
like
meow meow
endlessly oh now she jumped on the chair
oh my god
um
hmm
laughs
she needs maybe some time to calm down
uh gosh I'm so hungry I can't wait to
eat these snacks I haven't had breakfast
I'm tired
[Music]
ah but today I'll be revealing the snack
box from
um uh bales
are sure now she said she really wants
to call in and she's gonna try but so
far I haven't gotten a message back on
my on Minecraft on Discord however Santa
is on standby don't do anything stupid
Santa is on standby to give me uh her
comments instead of Wales
because Santa yeah Santa is actually
awake right now
then maybe Santa can do a Bales
impression no but before
uh we start with oh gosh I'm so hungry
before we start with the actual review
of the snacks that
um
Bales sent me from Australia
let me put the flag here wow wow
yeah before we do that uh she sent she
put in a gift
Osama in the chat
the chats goals Austria yeah Austria
totally Austria
gosh I'm so [\h__\h] hungry ah no junkers
no junkies go away go away chunkers no
go away go away go away go away go away
[Laughter]
[Music]
uh Cat is being a cat yeah oh my God I
love her so much but
did you hear that
uh I think she's angry because I didn't
give her snacks in the morning she's
demanding it a bit more nowadays as well
yeah
um let me find some
bgm
um
can you not be so noisy what is this
I like it
I like it I hope it doesn't make you
guys crazy apparently I'm choosing music
now that makes you guys crazy I'm so
scared to turn on the camera
oh yeah I don't know that's not really
maybe it's not really Australian what is
Australian music
um
[Music]
I like the flutes too yeah tweet um
wait okay
uh
oh iris is one year anniversary is
tomorrow tomorrow
oh my God
saw it on Twitter
oh yeah that makes sense because
three days after my birthday right oh
yeah that I should remember that
okay okay starting
okay
I put it up on Twitter
tomorrow
to Pink
apparently yeah okay so anyway hello
everybody do I have some people here who
usually don't watch my streams because
of the time zone because today is really
unusually early for me
where are the newbies or the unusualies
Mimi
oh hello hello welcome wow
and probably also a lot of people
suffering because they stayed up later
woke up in the middle of the night for
me Queensland oh so we do have a lot of
Australians here right now
a lot of mates
oy mate hello hello
what Australians
I'm so hungry I hope you guys have good
snacks
oh from Sydney
Queensland Melbourne cool
that's so cool
I don't know usually have so many
Australians in my
um stream but it's nice to have some
people from my home country
here with me uh it feels more like home
that's so nice I feel so cozy and warm
welcome my home people
yeah it's so nice to see familiar faces
your shop okay I think my cats may have
calmed down a little bit
welcome welcome everybody from SCA and
everybody from the rest of the world
welcome everybody
okay we could try to start by looking at
the gift that Bales put in the box
for my birthday I'm guessing it's this
oh there seems to be a drink too
delicious okay
oh let's go okay it's immediately
noticeable what it is
no no no no jonker says she she jumped
up to the challenge
she knows she knows I'm about to turn on
the webcam
well
here you go you can see what it is
how does she know I like Lush
how does she know how does she know what
how does she know did you guys tell her
um wow I love lunch it's a huge lunch
box
oh it smells so good
oh even before
it smells so good
yeah I buy a lot of bath bombs but then
I don't end up using them that much but
I love Lush
I love them now I should take more bath
bombs baths it's just I don't really
have even though I love it I love you
know bath bombs and all that but like I
just when I when I go into a bathtub
um and get and get really impatient
and I don't want to stay too long oh
well maybe the smell the strong scent
will make uh chunkers go away
okay let me open this
I wonder what bath bombs we're gonna get
so hungry I wonder if I can eat them huh
no even when I turn on like Netflix or
something to watch it while I'm in the
bathtub I still I don't know I don't
have the patience to stay in there
oh wow there's like you know the the
bath bomb sand in some places outside
the box
oh my God whoa
drunk scent oh wow Mamma Mia
oh oh
I'm gonna give me morning sickness or
something like that oh
okay let me put this here
okay and then let me open this and so we
can see some fancy
bath bombs
uh where do I open this what is it with
Australian boxes
that can't open them this is just a
normal thing though
okay there you go
what the [\h__\h] a street Australia wait I
opened it from upside down
Australia Australia please Australia
no no
[\h__\h]
hell mate
okay
looks like this now it looks like a mess
maybe before that it wouldn't have
looked so much like a mess let me see
like a I think that's like a oh dear I'm
not sure if it was supposed to shape or
be shaped like that this one looks a
little bit sad
oh no my gloves
and oh
that's a nice bath bomb doesn't say
which one it is but it's purple and
sparkly
and we have another like purpley purpley
one and then I have I think I've tried
this one before
and then we have oh
dream cream body lotion
allow your skin into calm Terraces
dreamed up in soothing chamomile blue
and lavender nice and another one oh
[Music]
I've never bought one of their shower
scrubs oh
rub bra wait is Lush Australia
is lunch Australia
I think that's uh
that looks like something I could eat
looks like a
um like a mochi
Japanese mochi
it's British oh okay
I thought maybe there was a specific
reason why she got me this one
okay let's turn off the camera
chonkers is literally sitting right next
to it
okay I will be taking a bath tonight I
suppose
and
bells for this sweet birthday gift
okay and now and now we eat sheep
more snacks into the snack box than uh
is usually in my snack boxes
but yeah let's go do we want I think I
want Sana already here
I'll turn off the PGM I think oh my god
oh hello
hey hi I'll make it louder
could this be possible actually our
first proper one-on-one collab now
all of it that it will be nice to Vegas
it comes because this is her box nah
it's okay this is the first one-on-one
um one-on-one on stream it is so yeah
and it might be I don't I don't know how
much time you have but this could take a
while because there's a lot of snacks to
try
oh no I'm just multitasking so all right
all right
you told me it was huge
cute Australian snacks I don't really
think about anything else but tim tams
there I already saw him down there's
there's definitely tim tams in here
but I'm I wonder what the rest is gonna
be and I would like your comments on
every snack your personal opinions
Roger okay so this is dangerous this
time I'll have to turn on my oh wait I
think chonkers is gone
has left the chat guys my cat is you
know kind of like she's a rogue sniper
so gotta be careful
what's your favorite snack from
Australia
tim tams when I think of a favorite
snack from Australia nothing actually
comes up
it's like it's like if I'd rather have a
snack or else I have like
um one from someone else really
[Music]
[Laughter]
I don't know
[Music]
I mean like have you ever tried Vegemite
okay have you ever tried Vegemite I
think I have not
okay yes sir um
she loves Vegemite but I absolutely
loathe it oh he called me a fake
Australian for that but
if you actually ever tried Vegemite I I
feel like I won't be alone on this
it seems to be a 50 50 kind of thing
I think it's worse than natto honestly
wait wait
but someone in the chat said the same
thing so maybe I did not miss here did
you actually call me koala
oh I called you kiwawa but okay you want
to be called koala
does the Australian accent I don't know
koala Chihuahua koala I thought there
were no yeah Austria
okay this doesn't look like something to
eat this does yay time
that's not something to eat what's this
ah okay that's something to eat okay
well I don't know if this is really like
um
edible that sounds too good to be put in
the box
it did it did look like it could be
edible yeah um
[Music]
yeah especially especially if it's from
Lush yeah whatever yeah whatever bath
whenever bath products always smell so
good I always get really really hungry
like I salivate yeah now it's foreign
because it has amazing ingredients that
will be really good for your body um
anyway I have the first snack so look at
this
you know these oh shapes yeah oh they're
okay they're okay it says the original
flavors okay all of them
um Pizza barbecue and chicken crisp
cream what cream I never tried the
chicken one yet actually well I think
you'll be able to judge like is that
Australian word is that an Australian
word crimpy
crimpy I feel like it is I would never
really thought of it on Australian wood
because I never heard of it before
oh is that is it is it crimpy doll
chicken crimpy is so good these are just
okay
like like it's like crimpy it's just
like it's just like crispy but crimpy
it's like it's like barbecuey uh-huh
what happened okay well okay so we have
all these apparently classic important
flavors
well I'm opening the package now
if he seems to be a favorite and pizza
too barbecue seems to be the oh god oh
I've never tried the chicken on there
they're all mixed
inside wow this is what it looks like
crackers so it's like salt crackers I
suppose kind of with an extra flavor
it's kind of meaty oh now I don't know
but it's Biscuits okay I'm taking one I
wonder which one is this
by the smell
um
by the smell I'm not so sure it could be
pizza maybe okay
um
[Music]
I think it's quite addictive
it is pretty good which one is it do you
think
um
I would say the taste was a little bit
weak so it's hard to tell but I think
it's Pizza
[Music]
so all the flavors are going to mix into
each other so it's just like a paste
of like Savory and Umami yeah yeah yeah
yeah I can see that but I'll take
another one maybe that one will taste
different it looks the same though wait
oh bless you just
smell different shapes oh they might be
different shapes
okay yeah this one looks a little bit
more narrow okay let me try
hmm
um
I don't know
you don't know it doesn't take us
exactly the same
and the shapes look so similar though
um
I mean yeah there's some that are more
why there's some that are more narrow I
guess
um
this one looks like a pizza
it can't
it can't all barbecue it's one the Box
said
the original flavors meow you love oh so
it shouldn't it just be a mix a green
box is barbecue oh yeah yeah green box
is that yeah
the boxes are colored I bet you are
reading an ABS Amusement you have to
come back you have to come back to
Australia to try the rest I guess
Australia I was looking at the back side
of the package this barbecue
I like the barbecue one better than the
pizza one to be honest I'm curious about
the creepy one
[Laughter]
Jewel like to hold the big box
we need like super we need we need we
like train each other's we we train each
other with
um you know really hard to open boxes so
when the wildlife is going to uh come
after us we're ready
that is very smart yeah otherwise we're
not going to be any
um otherwise we're not going to be put
up a fight with all the Kangaroos and
koalas
[Music]
interesting tactics
well I usually always raise my snacks at
the end when after I tried them and I
will give this
[Music]
um
I will give it up
seven out of ten I'm starting off a
little bit you think so I feel like I'm
a bit that's pretty high it's like I
don't know maybe it doesn't really like
a snack I go for because I've always had
it like I've always just seen it around
like as a just a cheap snack or rather
like cheese chips or something
but is this is this actually like uh and
a snack that originates from Australia
I'm assuming yeah
because I've never seen it in that in
the other snack boxes ever
oh okay I was just like yeah I've always
seen it around and it's always when
um when I was growing up in dinosaur
dinosaur school
lunch boxes
see I see what you're getting at that's
nice
[Music]
did you get along with the other
dinosaurs
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
um it's a it's a it's a shame that all
of them died out but yeah
tell me you couldn't have stopped it you
say it's a shame but wasn't it kind of
like something you started
think Santa think
oh at least at least you guys are still
around
okay
I did a pretty good job with the humans
right right so you were probably like oh
man these dinosaurs are too dumb let me
get something more intelligent on this
world that I can actually have a
conversation with okay I get it I get it
okay you know what I'm gonna go for the
next snack
um there's so much
okay I think I I liked I really like
this
oh you know I heard it for a moment like
you screamed because I was a spider and
not because you were excited
[Music]
spider in here
now the next thing I I think I heard
about someone like I think on Twitter is
still writing this name and I was like
there's no way does this exists you're
kidding me right
foreign Golden Gate and gate and popcorn
really
it's golden gay time
oh wait is this from Essence
it originally you're from uh really
popular ice Lolly
um wait wait I remember I remember from
the Christmas collab you guys don't call
it isolis isolates ice cream
wait how what do you what do you call
the company that uh made this
uh over there
this oh this logo
the logo on the top
oh streets what okay I think yeah I
think it has a very different name in
Austria
okay but I think it's not a good name
anyway I think it's an offensive name in
Australia okay I'm confused okay let me
anyway eat the popcorn because I Love
Popcorn
oh sure
I can't open it
[Applause]
um I'll use a I'll use a scissor
grips marbles
Griffin's what what Griffin Griffin's
Marvels
that the thing that it says on top of
the package wait maybe it's like a
collaboration
Marvels uh oh I think like probably
um you know it is a collaboration with
probably a Popcorn Company because
modern gay time is supposed to be just
an ice cream ah
and then like it's just so popular that
they decide to capitalize it it's kind
of like what you're doing with kfp going
ice cream flavor yeah yeah daytime is
originally an ice cream streets um I
think like streets makes a lot of
different ice creams oh yeah it's an ice
cream company like really really yeah
they're really iconic one but did I did
I am I crazy let me Google
ah let me let me see it am I going crazy
golden daytime wonderful ice cream yeah
I just looked up the
ice cream company yeah yeah it used to
be
called I think
something or it still is called that
yeah yeah
something that yeah I think is
I'm looking it out now it's called it's
called streets right
I don't know is it I don't know if it's
so okay I don't know no no
so that's why that's why it's probably
called streets
aha okay no it's called Eskimo in German
uh-huh and I've been I was told before I
think that that's offensive oh is it
someone in the chat said it's not
yeah we call it Eskimo for some reason
because I guess ice cold
oh yeah yeah maybe it's Pizza is already
taken by somewhere else
could be I don't like how in Australia
um Burger King is not called Burger King
[Music]
what is it called
it's called Hungry Jacks Hungry Jacks no
way no it's a different company no
no it's like if you
um like it being called Burger King is
kind of maybe
um less than uh lesson people like
unless people look it up they probably
don't know or honestly unless they know
about like they've gone over to other
countries and stuff they probably don't
know that hungry Jackson Burger King are
the same thing yeah I love Burger King
when I didn't know that I I'm married to
Burger King
Jack lost his crown they're now he's
hungry for me I need to have a talk with
them afterwards oh my God and also
it does seem to be uh offensive
apparently so I'm very sorry the company
is called Dad in Austria and I always
thought there was something wrong with
that sorry about that okay I'm gonna eat
this popcorn now
it smells amazing already there's like
some
chocolaty ones and some golden ones oh
oh they're sticking together let me show
you yes come out sticky and caramelly
the popcorn I think I think the caramel
popcorn over here you definitely should
try the ice cream because
um I think golden gay time has spread to
a lot of different things so overall the
ice cream is the best
okay I'm biting in now oh yeah it's like
honeycomb
um
vanilla chocolate
[Music]
it's good right oh I love it
yeah it tastes like a thing it tastes
like ice cream and popcorn yeah
[Music]
ah
it's so good I actually have some in my
pantry right now do you think I can I
actually want to get something
go get it
let's share
yeah it tastes really good
um
it's a little bit sticky
and on my teeth
oh a little bit is pretty sticky
hmm
that's really good and yummy
I like the packaging too
the packaging looks really um
[Music]
hard to say like someone someone who
whose passion is graphic design no that
sounds like a [\h__\h] it's actually really
good wait what was that that looked like
that it had some actual information
there was already a company called
Burger King
here in omzi when the American one
started
um here they had to change the name
oh
so now there's there's Burger King's
still there that's not Burger King so
people will try to go for Burger King
look it up on Google go there and find
out it's not a real Burger King
so that could happen to me probably when
if I would go to like I don't know
Sydney to visit someday and I'm like I'm
really hungry I don't know what to eat I
just want to go to the Burger King right
now okay yeah eat a crispy chicken and I
look it up on Google and then turns out
when I go there it's on the Burger King
apparently Santa
apparently uh before the real Burger
King came to Australia there was already
a company called Burger King that's why
they went for Hungry Jack's was that it
that's such a weird difference
quiet the ring to it I mean it has a
ring to it it's not quite the ring to it
I don't think but I also I didn't even
know that Burger King was a thing I
always knew of Hungry Jack's before
before I learned about that wow wow so
you got them
you got this so good right it is
I'm giving it a 10 out of 10. yay
yeah we don't have 10 out of 10s that
often in my snack box reviews
so this is quite yeah that's just like I
really wish I really wish
um we could take you out and show you
the ice cream I already put ice cream
together because it's so good I will put
this on my bucket list now it's on my
bucket list hell yeah I'm gonna drink
some water though because it's really
sticky
yummy you have some good stuff in your
pantry huh
yeah I'm surprised
yummy yummy yummy okay while you're
snacking on the Golden Gate 10 popcorn I
will bring it out
I will bring out the
neck that I'm not gonna actually
immediately
um taste but in the following coming
streams uh because it will take some
time to make this the next one is
uh twinings Australian afternoon tea oh
oh
yeah
there's like a kind of
um Earl Gray oh it's similar it says but
I actually haven't oh it says uh excite
your taste buds with our Australian
afternoon blend this brisk full-bodied
blend was created with Australians for
Australians like me uh it's the perfect
pick-me-up and it's sure to living up
your day we think you'll agree it is so
vibrant and wonderful as this beautiful
country wow
interesting I want to smell at least I'm
gonna open to snap smell
I haven't tried this one I've only had
one in a different company that names
like something with Australians yeah
there's Australians in here
oh yeah it smells really good
yeah you can make a cup of tea I
will um as I said a cream not a cup of
tea a cup of tea a cup a cup of tea yeah
well soon and then I'll give my rating a
little bit delayed but not now so next
we go to
what is this oh
[Music]
oh price you say the only thing you can
think of is tim tams because this also
seems like something legit oh this is
actually good for breakfast I think
[Music]
lcms split sticks yogurti
you know that I'll say I'm not quite
good there you go
the jack is excited
oh
awesome oh my good it's um if you like
folding gay time Pop I think you'll like
lcms I've loved them for that long time
there should be golden gaytime lcms then
oh my God
what happened
nice would you be good yeah
yeah oh my God okay so they're uh
they're packaged individually like this
I like the packaging I like the the
simple blue LCM you can put in your
lunchbox yeah I can totally see that
that yeah the parents of Australia would
do that yeah okay let's go I like your
goodness I don't need anything else in
The Lunchbox just lcms
that seems to be an Australian thing
then cute okay so it's like a it's like
a like a double double bar like this
although the bottom is like this yogurt
chocolate thing whatever and it's more
like oh you haven't seen it before
no the one when I went last time I had
lcms it wasn't a double bows just like a
straight ball oh
interesting although it's been a very
long time
there's also apparently unicorn lcms
you would love them wouldn't you
what yeah oh this smells really good
go get them
let's go new run activation for Sana
right now
okay I'm digging it
unicorn and purple and blue and white
and pink sprinkles on it wow
oh oh
my God these are really good
hmm they're good right oh I really like
the texture
um and how it's after you after you bite
in how it becomes one mass in your in
your mouth I like what it turns into
Just Like Rice Krispies with like
um like I remember I used to just sort
of make them make them like as a snack
like the Rice Krispies crispy coated in
something sweet and yeah that's what
lcms pretty much is oh my God I love
them they're so good oh my god um
this is what I call emergency breakfast
thank you so much bells oh my God
oh I love the chewiness yeah
and the yogurt flavor I love yogurt
flavored things
like ironically I don't like
um the basic basic basic
no none non-flavored
um yogurt
I will have to like put some flavor or
some cereal or some some fruit into a
non-flavored yogurt because just plain
yogurt I I don't really like eating it
just like that yeah it's like I could I
could deal with like maybe vanilla and
sugar just plain yogurt no yeah
um I definitely would rather I
definitely would rather fruit yogurt
exactly
this is so good oh my God I'm gonna eat
the whole thing
oh wow yeah off the top of my head I
don't really think of anything I really
snack anymore but I just like this stuff
is yeah I don't even know how good I had
it no there you go appreciate Australian
snacks some more come on
it's not like a snack it's more like
just like just like just like food like
like this is food
it could be yeah I have them
um a warning um chonkers has once again
positioned herself right next to the
camera
she's waiting to hijack the camera once
again she's just chilling there now
cute oh my God I will give the snack
a solid
well-deserved 10 out of 10. it might oh
my goodness apparently second yeah no no
no 10 out of 10.
yes the second the second it's the
second I would like to even give it more
points I think it's surprising because I
feel like snacks that um are kind of
made for kids and and are mostly
consumed by kids don't hold up so well
as an adult most of the time but this
one I don't even feel this
um when I eat it I don't I don't feel
like oh this should be for a child I
just feel like this is this is amazing
this is amazing as an adult or as a
child or as a teenager for all energy
definitely because like there's a sort
of um lunchbox snack like a crackers and
cheese or you just get sick of but then
like lcms is just like a good memory if
you grow up on them
I totally grew up on this because I'm
Australian yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah and never win for real what do you
mean real estate you wanna fight you
wanna fight mate wait
the thing is by the way he's trained
with a heart to open boxes now you won't
want to mess with her yeah I have a
chainsaw right now here with me in here
you heard that that's my chainsaw
oh I did not hear it I wonder if it's
Discord
yeah I think in the Stream maybe I can
hear it because when I opened your
stream I heard I was like what was that
noise yes that little gift card I can't
hear it it's not a favorite
anyway what was I gonna say oh yeah
um Bales asked me if she should send
Vegemite with this box and I said no
because I could probably get Vegemite if
I wanted to in Austria
um no no I didn't take the time to
actually get it because I probably
wouldn't like it anyway
but honestly yeah it's like
it's kind of a meme maybe it's in here
anyway I doubt it though I told her it's
not worth putting it in anyway that was
amazing 10 out of 10 so far really good
snacks
yeah
The Taste sort of stays in your mouth so
it's gonna ruin your taste of the other
snacks oh yeah
horrible
oh wow next next snack um Tom Cruise is
reaching out for it oh we have something
similar
oh more breakfast snacks I guess
interesting
Nutri grain original Kellogg's cereal
bar thingies with some chocolate on them
sorry I should show it to you on Discord
so it's faster uh let me show you on
Discord actually turn on the oh
screen sharing
um
there you go now you should be seeing
the screen on Discord and I will show
you again the Box
foreign
[Music]
my opinion on this was like
um they tried to make an LCM clone with
their own sort of cereal yeah I think
it's still good but it's not as good ah
okay okay well some people are saying
like it's their favorite though so much
sugar they say it's very sugary
oh that's nostalgic not Nutri grain is
out okay I need like
um it kind of has a name it shows me
like to me nature game is kind of like
the be strong
um grow up strong grow very muscles kind
of cereal I would hope so because it
says nutrients grains on there should be
nutrient nutritions to be grained uh so
this is the bar
okay sorry the camera is turning off a
lot today because I'm scared that my cat
will jump in
so yeah let me oh John Christ is now
trying she's sniffing the ground where
the snacks were on
cute okay I see it everybody muscle
master
do you have muscles like like legit
muscles
oh no no no oh um I already have big
but donkas
that's what you're saying right but
don't gonna say it I'm just big I'm just
looking like you know like destroy
everything because you said
you're so big it's like as if you wanted
me to end the sentence
[Music]
all right I'm digging in oh cat has left
the chat so let me show you uh oh oh it
looks beautiful oh wow really um chunky
cereals on here
I'll take a bite
um
oh
oh wow yeah it's not as soft as LCM it's
like crunch oh
um
why did the chat say it's sugary
it needs more sugar
Mom isn't I do I remember it's not as
sweet as the LCM so I was like I tried
it a couple of times I was like give me
back my lcm's mom
well me too give me back my lcms I don't
like this one that much
it's like
um it tastes a bit too healthy
it needs more chocolate covering or I
don't know but I guess then it wouldn't
be what it is so
um
it's on the Nutty side The Nutty flavor
overpowers the chocolate so much that
it's basically non-existent I think it's
like the Nutri grain I don't think it's
nutty it's just like the cereal kind of
um
[Music]
no I'm not really happy with this yeah
it tastes too healthy
so
um I'll give it um
I'll give this one um
ah a full I'm gonna be honest it's a
four out of ten for me
sorry yeah sorry not impressed no no
don't don't be sorry we're we're on the
same we're on the same standing in this
eyes I have quite the sweet tooth that's
the thing I really like sweet things so
much
sweet but it's not it's just low-key
sweet not not even mid case sweets then
that's not good enough for me there's
something missing there
ah it's like um I like really really
sweet stuff if it's maybe moderation
nothing like I also like
um sub subtle sweet stuff like Japanese
snacks as well oh well depending on like
the Japanese snacks like Japanese cakes
I like Japanese cakes like the amount of
sugar it has compared to American cakes
oh I don't think I had any cakes while I
was in America I don't like Japanese
cakes too
they I guess they are different I never
really thought too much about it but hmm
okay have you tried like New York baked
cheesecake
I
I don't think I've tried specifically
New York baked cheesecake yeah but just
like just like uh she's like like if you
compare a Japanese cheesecake to a to a
western cheesecake
um it's very different than the
sweetness I rather the Japanese
cheesecake
I think that's just right and I'll still
I'll still eat the I'll still eat the
American cheesecake I still think it's
really good
[Music]
I had eggs in Japan and are really
really good I've definitely had
cheesecakes in Japan before and and they
are they are pretty good
um
so good
hack let's get it on ah okay
I have a bad feeling about this
uh
mint ties or minties
oh
[Music]
oh I've had I probably like tried once
and then I was like
um I'll have the other lollies in the
back
ground if this is my flavored I'll
probably not really like it I don't
really like mint flavored snacks I only
like mint to be in my toothpaste
what do you think about mint flavored
things do not bite okay okay good what
do you think about mint I feel like
um I like mint chocolate ice cream I
feel like that's just the right amount
of I feel like that's just the right
amount of balance but mint and other
stuff it's like uh maybe not be careful
everyone's I don't need to be careful
yeah it's like it's like a rock
wait but if it's really mint flavored
maybe I should eat this one at the end
after everything else
you know because it will clear my mouth
okay
let's go with something else first oh
wait
[Music]
wait shapes
she sent me the pizza shapes too the
pizza one oh let's go I think look at
Tawana is actually the one better than
about I don't remember
yeah it's been so long since I have
shapes but um you can try it you can
like compare which one I guess yeah I
shall
I'll tell him I also feel kind of bad
about opening another big package that
uh
I don't want it to go bad too fast with
all these openings
but they said
I should have some I guess okay all
right all right I'll do it for science
science for science the whole science
okay
the Legendary Pizza
oh oh okay oh that smells nice
oh I think yeah the pizza one I don't
remember
it's just like oh yeah shapes is also
kind of like this is food
no it's really good
I I can definitely taste the pizza now
originally when I was eating barbecue I
thought that was pizza but this is
definitely Pizza
[Music]
okay
um previously I think I gave the
barbecue one a seven out of 10.
I think I'll give this one a 7.5 out of
10.
um
yeah that sounds right wow that's good
tasty tasty I'll take another one
how about Golden Gate time shapes
modern daytime shapes I'm not sure a
rather golden gaytime LCM still but like
shapes is always like a a Savory kind of
it's every kind of biscuit oh yeah so I
wonder I don't know
like chicken waffles maybe you like
chicken
um
I remember you were talking about it but
it's kind of like that kind of feeling
where like it's sweet and then like you
wasn't separate
you want it separate yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah I'd rather like eat shaves and then
have golden gay time as a dessert oh
yeah yeah yeah okay get that I get
that's only 100 oh I see we're very
similar Sana oh my god oh what happened
we talk more like Australia
oh really
floors Mamma Mia why am I saying Mama
Mia
I wasn't
back let's go next snack this looks
interesting
violet crumble
it's the way it shatters that matters
what look at my gloves oh blush the Lush
bath bombs made them so colored oh it's
the way
[Music]
I didn't even notice like that's a
that's a that's like a phrase I just I
just think I do like this but I can't
eat the whole bar myself it's a long bar
yeah
what is this it looks um
interesting
does it shatter in your mouth
it's like At first it's like really rock
hard but it also kind of melts in your
mouth as well it's like it's like it
matters
honeycomb oh it's like with honey
yeah honeycomb
okay I'm not sure if this has taken this
kind of texture because it may have like
melted once during the time
I don't know this looks like it has kind
of melted and now it's back in on the
inside the inside would probably still
be good the chocolate probably melted a
little bit yeah yeah yeah I just wonder
what it looks like originally and anyway
I'm digging in
oh oh yeah this is quite hard and then
like it's kind of like oh my God it's
kind of like a good texture yeah
that is interesting that is very
interesting
interesting extra the inside it reminds
me of
[Music]
um
oh yeah
yeah yeah
in German is in English
um
uh cream pops cream pops
[Music]
cream puffs
all cream puffs
cream box is like very soft and
um oh it's like a soft cake in Maya then
they translated wrong I'm thinking of
something hard
[Music]
oh my God
but wait for the wind boilers the stiff
one the hard one the [\h__\h] is it is it
not maybe not using your following
chat's like meringue
I think like meringue might yeah it's
like a meringue but a bit like maybe
yeah yeah wait aha
yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah
yeah the hardened version of merange
meringue and it's honey as well
yeah it's it's really interesting let me
take another bite oh
oh wow
Cutters and it matters oh my God
wow
I don't know how to describe this other
than women
you look at it so it matters is that the
saying
yeah it looks like this right and then
like At first it's like hard but then
like once once it melts it sort of melts
in your mouth it's like meringue come on
camera you can do it
that's on the important parts
oh I was there for a second okay
whatever
[Laughter]
thing well the honey taste is strong and
I don't I don't dislike honey but I
wouldn't like normally go for a snack
that's like
focused on the honey flavor so kind of
um mixed feelings about that but it is
good for what it is so I will give this
um
six out of ten
oh it's lower than the shapes
interesting yeah it's like I think I
think it's quite good but I can only eat
like a bite or two until I'm like yeah
I'm done
but I do like the the concept because
it's very original I have not have had
something like this before so very
original I give it original points
therefore all right
[Music]
these oh
oh what is this what is this is for
children this is for children
not what
is this
okay we have tiny Teddy hundred
thousands
why did I look so crazy it was like so
innocent back in the day and now they
look like they've lost their minds what
happened to these teddies what the heck
is really excited
a mean snack in Australia or what
oh they didn't always look this like
this they have I have attitude
attitude now maybe because yeah
open up the tiny teddies and like what
they look like and they're like that's
what it used to be it looked used to be
like kind of like that but now now they
have attitude like it's about like
rebellious probably the fame that grew
up
over there over their head no what's the
right word I don't know
okay so it's a it's it's a a box like
this with snacks inside like this
interesting
uh
all right have you had them before when
you were younger but you remember what
what they tasted like
it's kind of um it is kind of like a
honey cookie I don't know in your
country do they do they sell um cookies
and Marcus
[Music]
I guess they sell like chocolate chunky
chocolate chip cookies big ones I think
okay no that's probably not the same
kind of cook either Marcus all in yeah
but yeah the cookies
like whenever I had it I was like this
tastes like tiny titties it's kind of
like yeah okay let's see hungry hastily
hunted for every last hundred and
thousand he could find
Hungry is that your name
but I like the chocolate I like the
chocolate ones I think
chocolate ones
okay let me try to open oh are there
like tiny ones in here
um do you know sprinkles that's really
cool spring yeah that's what we call
Sprinkles hundreds and thousands what
that's such a long name so unnecessarily
it's hard to say what I don't even know
why because like sprinkles sprinkles I
feel like yeah personally sprinkles has
a bit more
call them hundreds of thousands
so it's a bear like this cute cute doll
very cute I'm digging in
[Music]
more
oh
it's very hard
but once you take everything apart in
your mouth
then you get to the sprinkles
um
oh
yeah
well it's um
also not very sweet huh
are these all the same flavors I guess
so they all look um like they all have
sprinkles
on them I think yeah it's not really
sweet it's not really that sweet I like
the chocolate ones I think I think like
the chocolate ones they taste a bit like
brownie so that's why I like
chocolate ones yeah I've had the
original ones
um I don't like honey ish and I was like
I like the chocolate ones better it's
like brownie
I think I would like them more too these
are okay but as I said before I have a
sweet tooth and things that are just
low-key sweet are not sweet enough
um and somebody in the chat said I
should have bitten off their arms all
right all right wait a second I haven't
done like since they're in the shape of
a bear you kind of like disembody them
ah they're they're too small to properly
disembody
I don't know it's like don't they don't
have Expressions can you show you like
chat like the like the different kind of
bears maybe like I bit some limbs off of
one now
there you go
thank you he's missing his arms now are
you happy now he's suffering are you
happy
this is the content that um chat came
here for
okay
I like the questions black
you slack on your kfb degrees
exactly yeah
okay I like the crunchiness it could use
like more more sweetness though
I'll give it a
little six out of ten
I think
I feel like to be honest I feel like the
the honeycomb bar is probably a bit
higher than six out of ten than like
tiny teddies but yeah
could be um okay well then 5.5 out of
10.
yeah
I don't think the chocolate ones are in
here unfortunately
but let's go next oh
next up we have twisties cheese flavored
twisties
oh I think it's good I think so
um it's a bit strong there the
cheeseburger is quite strong I see it
this is the thing with
um cheese flavored food I I can eat them
but and I like cheese but I don't know
I'm not a huge cheese fan like most
people seem to be a bit babe but baby
these yeah they won't see it they
probably won't see to like these all
right so inside they're like I feel like
I've had a snack like this before in the
different snack box streams I feel like
I've had it yeah I feel like other
countries probably had similar um
definitely
I feel like yeah like what Chad says I
like the chicken ones better than the
cheese ones because the cheese is kind
of strong but I really feel like I had
these before
okay the shape really gives me a deja vu
all right I'm digging in
people say like it looks like Cheetos
it's kind of a bit more kind of like has
a different texture of Cheetos cheaters
is like um breaks easily foxies you have
the foxes were maybe similar oh yeah I
suppose it's not the same texture as
Cheetos even though I don't remember how
Cheetos were have I even had Cheetos
before I'm not sure at this point
they're good they're not actually too
cheesy when when biting into them it's
more than the looks and the the scent
that's really crazy cheesy oh
they're pretty good
pretty good oh it's like I think
um people is compared to his seasoned
cheers but I like twisties better than
cheaters it's like you can you can like
play with cheaters on your fingers and
like
the sort of like make rings and stuff
um
model I like this I actually even though
I'm not the biggest cheese fan oh
[Music]
I won't get the mom I'll give them a 7
out of 10.
I have a seven out of ten yeah I think
that's quite the next one next time you
should try the chicken one though I do
like the chicken one because
um I don't know
of course yes
when when is the kfp or twisties collab
good question good question I I
take your lab come on companies come at
me
I'm waiting I'm waiting
all right next snack
um
what are we gonna go for
um well this one really confuses me
because it's not a snack I think it's
just a joke a joke from Belle's uh
directed at me
[Music]
oh how funny is this
joke
[Music]
it's just salt though
what you need to put it you need to put
it on your chip on my on like your
Savory food to taste it though put on
your kfp but okay if being charged
double what people are eating up wow oh
is that so popular in Australia there's
this one specific flavor oh my God
I'm just so good we can capitalize this
um
Chicken Salt what if I put it on chicken
and it's double chicken chicken chicken
Salt
it's like salt but it has like a it has
like a different Umami to it it's like
One Direction once you put chicken salt
on like a fresh hot chips no it will
never like you'll never mean I mean
potato fries it'll change your world
yeah like like fries okay fries oh
and oh I'm curious you guys are so
excited about this wow I guess I guess
Bales really made a pretty good snack
box for me wow I'm I'm honored I thought
this was a joke but maybe when I thought
of what you can send to Kiara I was like
um Chicken Salt
all right I'm gonna try this next time I
cook I cook a lot you know so next time
I make potato fries or any kind of
potatoes I'll put it on those and I'll
report back to you as I can currently
not really judge them so
next we will what is this by the way
this is just a big
she opened this one didn't she or did
she just open it for the sake of making
it smaller one two three
four five
no no yeah she just opened it for you
know that it's smaller oh that looks
good though the packaging so I mean I
have this big
package
five generous packs of Honey soy chicken
it's like I don't have any other brand
of um chips than Deli Rock and this is
the best flavor they have no I see oh
but it's it feels it feels like it has
been kind of flattened so I wonder how
the chips are doing inside oh no I hope
it's good because like the reason why
um this this brand of chips is so good
is because it's just so
crunchy ah I don't know it's like um
it's very different to you very
different to you it's it's just such
good quality I don't know how they do it
oh yeah I'm excited I love potato chips
but normally I just go for the basic ass
salt flavor potato chips just a normal
one and this one is like the sweet and
salty oh this is sweet and salty okay
this chip company in my opinion oh it
just to the side actually still look
pretty fun
oh the smell is nice it's not too
overwhelmingly strong so it's not so
much inside because they're small
packages but they're five of them so
let's go uh I'm taking up oh don't you
love it when a potato chip is like you
know a big one folded together like this
oh I love that
chips
has a lot of those in a big packet so
love oh they call them foldies
holies fold it they're so good ah you
guys are something I love that we're
bonding over folded potato chips let's
go all right I'm digging I'm digging in
wow
[Music]
um
yeah
mm-hmm
[Music]
10 of the 10 10 out of 10 10 out of 10.
yeah yeah that's right
there's like um this is when the first
time I bite into it the first second the
first half second I get this this
feeling the scent and uh
it's like as if I'm biting into a
chicken leg Yeah
I see people in chat like saying other
chip companies like kettle and stuff I'm
like no you guys have more cases you
guys have not tasted chips until you've
tried Deli chips especially honey soy
chicken ones that's the best flavor they
have my God I need to pay bills for this
but actually I'm sending her an Austrian
snack box instead
um so I hope that's um
sufficing for the great stuff you can't
stop me no
thanks for the fight with me
I'm taking another one ah okay it's so
good right it's damn good
hmm
I'm surprised they survived the trip
like this
rock rock hard potato chips but in a
good way
um
[Music]
it's good that they're not
overwhelmingly flavored like
um like chicken
I feel like there's definitely the
flavor is definitely there
but it's not crazy overwhelming so
that's probably why I like it and that's
why it's addictive
mmm
ah okay okay oh there's we are emptying
the Box
there's that oh I'm getting closer to
the oh what is this oh there this must
have uh melted a little bit on the trip
but I still want to try this there's one
one lonely single snack in here just one
simple bar of cherry ripe double dipped
oh oh I think I don't really like cherry
flavor myself so I never really found I
never really liked this
now it's my that was Bonkers my raccoon
[Music]
nah
you little [\h__\h] no she heard the noise
you know this plastic wrapping noise
unless she likes that yeah yeah
ah she comes out of nowhere and suddenly
jumps up here all right so let me try
this I love cherries
[Music]
for me it's like oh that's okay just
okay
the inside is kind of messy I don't know
if it's because
of I think it's gooey I think it's a
gooey
very
um
ah my vocabulary don't go very do you
like coconut yeah because I don't
remember I have I don't know okay I
remember like Cherry ripe whenever
um there's like there's a bag of lollies
of different types of lollies I always
avoided the Cherry right because it
reminded me of it's not for some reason
it doesn't say
something about coconut ah lunches
cherries and coconut double dipped in
old gold rich dark chocolate yeah the
rates that's the one I was looking for
the the smell of the chocolate is very
rich
so there is coconut in there oh well
let's see if I like it anyway
maybe the Cherry overpowers it I'm
digging in
I don't know because I
yeah my memory of it was always coconut
[Music]
oh yeah
interesting
[Music]
a coconut is there
but
thanks to the rich chocolate flavor
um
it doesn't bother me too much
the Cherry could be stronger it's barely
noticeable even though inside it's all
like red
I can't show you guys right now because
there's a cat in front of the camera
oh we're cool
there's a raccoon in front of the camera
no misspoke
no no it's good it's good oh no no
no
um I think the hurricane was speaking
that was a cat in the in the back that
was not the raccoon
the cat in the back is staying away from
the camera what
can get Bonkers huh move your move your
fat ass hmm
cute so cute
move
no she's
stupid is the ass soft yes very soft
very soft and fluffy would you like to
leave or do you want to be held like a
baby
okay holding raccoon like a baby now to
keep her in control
how are you doing
pokers or she wants to be held oh oh
[Music]
I will send you pictures of my raccoon
later Sana
please
yeah cheeky cheeky cheeky cheeky raccoon
bye bye bye bye that's how you get her
to leave
by annoying her there we go
okay thank God we don't have many snacks
left now we're uh gonna try oh wait I
didn't rate the the bar um
I'll give it a five out of ten uh
probably a lot of it is dragged down by
the coconut
[Music]
um
and the lack of cherry but it's not bad
like it's actually tasty
but there's just something misses them
up
I feel like Turkish delight the Turkish
delight bar would have been nicer oh
dude have you ever tried
uh but I may have Turkish delight I feel
like
maybe it's like it might not be
Australian but yeah well rather that for
a similar or for a similar taste oh yeah
the turkey is just so much better oh
well next up we have
uh what is this example
Zappo this is Australian is it
um I think this is like really sour
it I I know it's a mate in Korea
made in Korea but yeah but imported to
Australia that stands here
is it isn't it Australian snack it says
incredibly sour it's like
[Music]
play around with
um but the Koreans are confusing
stuff my childhood is ruined
but maybe just because it's made in
Korea doesn't mean that maybe not not
necessarily mean that it's supposed to
be considered a Korean snack I don't
know I don't know maybe that's just like
where they make it because I don't know
it's cheaper maybe yeah just because
it's made in Korea doesn't mean it's
Korean
oh yeah because the Korean fans say oh I
couldn't see it at all they have never
seen it before
it's Australian Oh I thought it was I
thought it was like American snack or
something
oh okay well well oh
feel like a child again the way I'm
opening this like
oh
this gives me a childhood vibes
okay I haven't had a shower snack in a
while oh they're like they're like
they're they're in the shape and size of
malams
I think Malamute is a German name for
the snack maybe there's a non-german
named Mounds I love mauams oh my God I
need to send malams to Bales when I sent
her the snack box my lumps
you guys know malam's some people know
melons
yeah Mom
s
how do you spell it
o a m yeah
oh so it's the same name
[Music]
now I want to eat some melons
all right all right let's go so this one
is Cherry and strawberry flavored
it looks like a MAO um but it's sour
really
okay let me try to oh
wow
it's not sour but it's so chewy
[Music]
oh it's so good
it's good it's all chewing so good
I think like a lot of watermelon one
I have grape I have oh wait
this one says it says sour strawberry
where's the sourness
oh wow
it's coming it's coming a little bit
[Applause]
I thought they would be extremely sour
okay I haven't had yeah to be honest I
haven't had this very much but uh oh
it's like the advertisers and stuff was
like this is sour and stuff there I
don't know
it's not sour yeah
it's just low-key sour Loki
um
all right
um but they are good they really remind
me of malam's in chewiness
um
it will take a while
tell me something Sana
tell me some story
what's on the story
um
laughs
[Music]
okay did you know and
um have you ever had
um
have you ever had hot cross buns
what crushed bun have you ever heard of
Hot Cross Buns yeah
Penny Hot Cross Buns where's Dad
um it's a it's a it's a it's a bridge
right oh brick is sold around it's sold
around Easter time in Australia oh
hardcore sponge oh that's quite good
originally it's like uh raisins and
stuff I'm not into raisins but
um nowadays hot cross buns they come in
like all sorts of flavors and fillings
and stuff they look yummy
it's so popular that even Marcus has
them oh why
and Easters like um yeah around Easter
time uh
I just have I just stuck on a lot of hot
cross buns because after Easter it's
just nowhere anymore it's not the top
the cross is that the sugar sugar glaze
thingy
the cross because I see it like uh it
looks
yeah
I remember it when I saw it it looked
like a sugar glazed but I think it's not
sugar glaze it isn't that part isn't
sweet unless like this it's just like
chicken yeah it comes in
everything I think it's a bit
[Music]
generally it's not glazed uh maybe
that's just some versions
oh I think it's cinnamony yeah oh yummy
yummy yummy I wanna try
you know what I I'm quite
quite the the bread familiar myself
I love bread we love bread so much in in
Europe like oh I love eating bread for
breakfast so much
um
you know what the best one that is but
then like when I think of Bakery it has
a sort of European image to it yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah we
have good bread here very good bread
would you like to come to eat some bread
in Europe come on a trip for breakfast
yes yes bread a little paper taking the
best bread is of course garlic garlic
baguette garlic bread garlic bread
yeah
I wonder why garlic bread is so
addictive it's just the garlic
how did garlic bread with like cheese on
top what what's your opinion on that
nah I quite like it nah I want to focus
I want to focus on the on the Soggy
drenched and garlic parts of the of the
baguette so I just wanted to be garlic
especially when it's like just fresh and
like the butter has just melted into the
bread yeah yeah that's pretty good but I
also like it with peas on top
[Music]
if you're ordering it in the menu if
you're ordering like garlic bread in the
menu and like you've got garlic bread
and cheesy garlic bread so she's a
garlic bread oh yeah yeah
[Laughter]
the Zappos um they were I think falsely
advertised so I'm quite Bamboozled I I I
came in with different this uh different
um expectations so
quite Bamboozled I must say therefore I
must take away some points
um
I will give it uh a 5 out of 10 because
it's just a basic chewy it's like chewy
Lolly yeah yeah yeah it's good but it's
[Music]
gonna advertise so what the hell so
maybe that's why I really remember it
yeah yeah it didn't stay in your brain
it would have stayed in everybody's
brains a bit more people show me the
shoes fall down like that that that's
all you know
all right so I'm sorry it's not bad but
it's just I need to give it a bunk so
that it learns from its mistakes yeah
all right we're getting closer to the
tim tams I've been deliberately staying
away from the tim tams until the end
[Laughter]
but next time
well you will see well next we have this
what is this Fredo oh
it's a great war of us Australians um
I I like the caramel corn
since
it's a caramel the caramel koala and
it's like chocolate it's a chocolate bar
filled with caramel inside and if you're
a sweet cheese like me I think you'll
like it the freddo is just a just a
chocolate bar shaped as a
frogs
in here there's um oh
Bonkers welcome back Bonkers thank God I
really I already showed the snack but
okay I have Fred dough with milky top I
have Fredo milk chocolate and I have
Caramelo koala
I think that's it so free flavors which
one should I try
first
um there's some milk Fritter the caramel
koala and what was the sad one milk
chocolate milky top and then caramel
koala
okay so chemical
um it's my favorite one out of the three
then milky top then the normal Alfredo
is just like normal chocolate in my
opinion okay okay
I'll try the milk the noble one first
then and then it might get better and
better each time
ah damn
it dad looks like oh dear yeah it melted
once definitely uh oh
Frog's face like gone oh and they're
supposed to be crossbones uh it looks
terrible but it's like supposed to be in
the shape of a frog frog koala it looks
terrible wait let me push away the
bunkers bunkers go away please
sure it's I don't know anymore what this
is
foreign
ER
[Music]
what it's supposed to look like but it
doesn't look like this is how it's
supposed to look like it makes me look
like a smiling frog I think I see
something like a frog leg I think so let
me bite into that
oh my God
[Music]
oh God
oh
well
you know what it's it's just normal good
um milk chocolate chocolate and since
it's chocolate yeah yeah since it's
already melted like this what we should
do is throw all of these mounted
chocolate frogs
into a chocolate fondue fountain
melt it and then dip strawberries in the
melted frogs
[Music]
[Laughter]
I think that's a good use for it now
yeah I said the chocolate though
chocolate
just just milk chocolate I love simple
milk chocolate sometimes that's all I
want sometimes
so now we try the Fredo milky top which
probably uh oh I see it I wonder if it's
melted I wonder if it's melted does that
mean like all the milk chocolate and the
light chocolate just sort of melted into
each other
um but like not fritters no Freddy's
um head is like melted into his pants
um I I definitely once again don't see
any frogs here
um wait chocolate and focus is on the
top again
go away go go away
sorry sorry
I pushed her down so this is what it
currently is oopsie
okay it says
it isn't melted into almost bottom part
don't know what this is man it's also
thicker on one side than on the other is
that normal
I feel like what happened was like it
sort of melted and stated and like
except in a yeah yeah
in an angle that's the back yeah well
the other side doesn't look any
different no it's not the back though
that the part that I showed you is where
his face was on the packaging originally
so
let me try it nonetheless
um
[Music]
in my opinion because you get birth it's
very good
it's very good very good okay okay okay
good chocolate
I like both of them but these ones so
far are simple chocolate so this is the
chocolate yeah and you don't even get to
see the Frog oh sad
maybe it would have made a stronger
impression if it was still a frog now
the koala I'm opening it right now
um oh dear okay oh dear
um oh the inside's like everywhere I see
some of the insides and I think
I see something that could have once
been a koala indeed yeah
[Music]
um oh no I I need to push uh Bonkers
away one more time why do you keep on
keep on here
why go down
I just had a flashback
actually heavy yeah
um that's quite there's a similar
there's a summer alone here oh my God
that's cool you can kind of see a koala
shape maybe doesn't like yeah it's not
as bad as a frog
[Laughter]
[Music]
I can see it
ah all right and now there's a bunch of
cat hair on it
yeah that's all um there's a lolly
that's similar to The Taste of caramel
koala but I used to send over to
um overseas friends no because like um
it had like a really strange name oh the
name of it was like camel balls camel
balls
yeah and it's like it's like a bowl
okay look it up yeah it's just I used to
remember that now I'm curious no
Bonkers is sniffing the camera she's
back once again oh thank God we're
almost done she's like really obnoxious
right now let me try the melted caramel
koala ah yeah
mm-hmm
[Music]
I see
I will tell you something
you know out of all these free
maybe maybe this is just my current mood
but but my favorite is actually the
first one the simple normal chocolate
one
sometimes simple is best
yeah yeah sorry this one's good too and
I do love caramel
um but now not that I compared all of
them plain oh yeah also you're not
playing I wouldn't know how to rank them
I would say for me it's it's the normal
one first and then the Milky top second
and then the caramel one third
amazingly
[Music]
oh I think like in order you need to be
in the meatball maybe yeah something
really really sweet and nothing else oh
apparently there's strawberry fraddle as
well
strawberry is quite good
have you ever had strawberry Pocky but
uh but the job but the not the like
there's two types of Japanese
um there's two types of strawberry Pocky
right there's one that's really cute and
then like this one that's kind of like
lighter pink oh oh I haven't compared
them so consciously before
does it taste like that though
oh wait wait no no strawberry photo is
all it's like caramel koala but the
inside is strawberry I don't I think you
have something else oh
strawberry like coming out of it
I want to eat that too all right well
well well it looks like we have finally
reach the bottom
of the tim tams and two times yes
same time I got two different ones
two different ones let me show you
we have
Tim Tam original and Tim Tam Deluxe
salted caramel brownie flavor oh my God
you like them which one do you like more
um I have to say I like The Salted
Caramel one but since since it's uh
since it's 10 times you gotta try the
original one as well ah okay okay it's
like if it's like Photo where like
original is best maybe you'll like it
but yeah ah actually sorry I forgot to
rate the the previous ones I will give
the caramel one
um
four out of ten I got the Milky top
five out of ten and I'll give the normal
one uh a 5.5 out of 10.
um it's great chocolate though so if I
just would be like you know looking for
normal chocolates it's actually pretty
high but yeah if you're going for normal
chocolate just like in a small portion
then I guess like you'll just grab a
grab a photo or grab a caramel koala
yeah yeah yeah yeah all right so
um I will uh go ahead and take the
normal tim tams first
it says apparently find the golden tip
Jam win three wishes were a hundred
thousand dollars what
maybe I have a golden temple oh
I have no [\h__\h] way that I'll get the
golden Tim Tam there's no way
yeah it wouldn't that be interesting
oh by the way
um so Bales we met her in America right
she came by we didn't have much time to
talk but she did bring a lot of tim tams
and then a lot of 10 times yes I was
talking about how it works I like it was
so heavy in a luck
you didn't bring a [\h__\h] to the Tim Sands
and then the others were eating them but
I purposefully did not take one because
I was like you probably put tim tams in
the snack box they didn't share so I
want my first um impression of the 10
times to be on camera
that is dedication yes that is
dedication
um kfp should be grateful yeah I saw oh
oh okay there was some some melting
going on here apparently
but not too much and oh
it smell yeah I don't think it doesn't
melt too much because there's cookie in
it
okay oh
very very uh cacao e flavor uh scent I
like the scent I wanna I wanna smell
this before I go to sleep
[Music]
that's good oh yeah oh let's go all
right
um uh so it's it's melted a little bit
on the top here
as you can see on the packaging Emily
has melted but I think it was fine
because it's created in it's chocolate
hey it's chocolate cake
[Music]
one glove so I can I won't get too much
chocolate on them let me take one
what's the best way to eat a Tim Tam
I feel like just on its own honestly
okay I don't know
um like for orders there's a there's
like people say you gotta dunk it in
milk and stuff for 10 times just on its
own maybe with some tea oh yeah the
Australian tea all right I'm digging in
oh
whoa
[Music]
I did not expect it to be crunchy
and then like in the middle of the
cookies sandwiches are like the filling
is
oh it's really good yeah I love the
cookie the the ratio
of cookie version chocolate and cream
yeah yeah it's really good ratio oh let
me take one more bite
[Music]
no no no
what's the temp time slam
Santa what's the Tim Tam slam
what is a Tim time slam
um
is it what is it
[Music]
him time slam
you know
[Music]
ah you bite you bite diagonal corners
and drink through it
you bite the ends up and use it as a
straw to drink your milk
what how would you do that
bite the ends off and use it as a straw
huh but it's a flat object
it's like the inside of it
the inside of it is like on the feeling
right yeah and so it just kind of like
suck it sucks
this doesn't look like very idly thing
to do
it they say probably doesn't work
because it's melted a bit
you need unmelted ones
I mean it's not that badly melted though
but I don't see an opening where I could
I could drink milk through
oh
[Music]
that's very interesting though is that
something Australians do
with your Tim Thomas to be honest to be
honest I don't know I don't know
hesitate maybe yeah
they came up with this
an Australian I'm like oh okay that
makes sense
are they really good I like the
chocolate flavor of the Australian
snacks so far in general like depending
on the on the country or the continent
even
um chocolate will will taste really
different
I've I've tried chocolate from America
I've tried chocolate from Japan I've
tried chocolate from Europe now I'm
trying chocolate from Australia and I've
tried uh England and they're all all
pretty different but Australia is quite
close in flavor to European chocolate I
would say oh interesting I think it
makes sense because
um probably the milk I don't like the
beans and everything
um it changes the flavor like you know
Hokkaido milk what kind of milk for
um like Hokkaido kind of snacks and
organic kind of snacks and chocolate
definitely tastes different to yeah
other chocolate for example well my
favorite and probably just because
that's where I grew up and that's what
my taste buds are used to is European
chocolate and that's why I might like
this Australian chocolate because it's
kind of similar yeah yeah so now that I
tried the normal tim tams let's move on
to the
salted caramel brownie tim tams oh the
packaging looks very exciting
um oh by the way the normal tim tams I
will give them oh
a nine out of ten
very good rating I feel like I feel like
um
that's not good
ah I can't open I'm too too but
stupid night I still have that um Emoji
all right let me see you
solve the caramel brownie okay so it's
packaged the same way they look from the
outside the same they're on there kind
of like a tiny bit less melted than the
other one oh
to down to town
it looked normal
[Music]
okay I think lightning this one it's
like the inside of it
um it's like the the chocolate filling
and then probably caramel filling and
then a chocolate filling again
in the middle okay you can probably slam
those
you still use them for slamming
you want to try it I don't I don't have
milk in my fridge right now but maybe
I'll get some later
hey guys still told me about the
Toontown slam I don't think I want to
try it now you're still you should try
it
you have to try it you have to become
the real YouTuber if I try it before you
then I'm more Australian than you
hey I'll become it's Australia please
understand please the dinosaurs did not
do this
maybe they did it behind your back they
were trying to hide something from you
yeah
all right I'm digging in itadakimasu
oh
wow it took a big bite
[Music]
how is it it's very good
I think I might actually prefer the
normal 10 times though these are really
good though I feel like um
many of them maybe they should um make
the brownie taste a bit stronger
oh
but yeah same oh same really yeah I
think I prefer the normal ones uh not
that I dislike them or any anyway uh I
like them I think that's not bad I've
actually never had the brownie ones
they have like another soda card oh wait
there's black forest
I love black forest cake
I feel like there's like some other 10
times like uh
3D ones but they're not as good banana
feet jams oh
try all the tim tams
damn oh oh I have black forest I love
black forest cake
I love that I love it so much yummy now
I want to have black forest cake oh I'm
I feel like I'm exhausted from all the
sugar
um but wow you're not you're not having
a sugar rush
oh no I don't know I'm I'm getting tired
exhausted maybe you can like just have a
relaxing bath yes with the um uh
Australian tea that I was sent as well
that'll be good
yeah sugar crash all right so I'll rate
this one
um
8 out of ten eight out of ten so pre the
number one nine out of ten and this one
eight out of ten
oh man
that's it that's the end of the Box
there's nothing else in here I think but
yeah that was that was the end but it
was more failed than the other snack
boxes thank you so much males who's
currently sleeping uh for sending me
such a huge stack box
very good job yes here's a here's a
heart a dirty dirty heart because my
gloves are [\h__\h] dirty it's a heart
for Bales and the heart for sanana for
joining me to give me some you know
thoughts some deep thoughts but you know
what sadana usually
um during my snack box streams
um they send like some facts and stuff
about Australia uh oh and the quiz
actually too normally a quiz yeah now I
I didn't get any any sort of those
things with the Australian snack box
because it's the sauce
do you have some facts about Australia
for me
talks about Australia yeah have you ever
heard of that the one
drop there drop bear drop bear
is it a bear that
um drops everything because they're so
clumsy cute
um I don't think it's very cute it's
kind of like a koala but it just kind of
um yeah it just kind of drops what kind
of drops and if you look at that attacks
you yeah it attacks you job
bear also I'm gonna eat the big teeth
now I think I could put a Vegemite in
your head wait when you look up drop
bear there's some crazy scary pictures
of koalas oh my God
[Music]
it's like um Australian museum has a
slide up and everything what isn't it
just a koala
[Music]
vampire koalas
real
maybe almost fake ew oh my God okay
it doesn't it doesn't take because like
there's a Wikipedia and like the museum
side and everything
it will show up in my dreams
[Music]
well uh well you asked for well you
asked for Australian facts
I've been more happy or I don't know
fascinating while I eat the minties okay
did you
um did you know that Australia had an
emu War along with the enes a what uh-uh
[Music]
is we only like kind of war with the
birds
I
mean yeah
and the humans lost right I saw a
documentation
[Applause]
you guys are losers you can't even win
against Birds
[Music]
um a good example for kfb like it says a
good example and it should Inspire us
for the future that we can indeed win
against humans just look at Australia
and we can understand we can see yeah a
good example this is just what happens
if you [\h__\h] with birds yo
yeah
maybe we should buy this version we
should team up with the emos
I'll get you in touch with it oh please
do yes
please okay okay let me try the the
minties
[Music]
ew it's like it's like toothpaste ew
zero out of ten
[Laughter]
Two-Face what the [\h__\h] but now my mouth
is fresher just by having it in my mouth
for five seconds
[Laughter]
do you like peppermint tea maybe no I
don't like I don't like mint tea no no
that's right
okay that that well that's just ate was
um something we've shown before it was
these and I'm giving them zero out of
ten I'm sending them straight back in
the Austrian snack box uh straight back
to Bales
you can have those back Bales I don't
need them but but thank you though
but overall I give this whole snack box
uh
an upside down 10 out of 10 which is
it looks it will look like one out of
ten
yeah does it look like no does it look
like one other one
if I say it is
10 out of ten oh or one out of four it's
New Year's Day and one other one that's
still full points
[Applause]
yay
nice so it's still hundred percent yeah
oh good job good job I think Sana is
also probably
um impressed and surprised that there
was so much that you could put in
Australian strip clubs yeah yeah the
only thing I could think of is ten
thousand chicken saltfish I guess we
have a pretty good here
yeah something like chicken Salt I
probably would have never gotten out of
like a company made snack box because
they in my experience so far they always
put in so many like random ass things
really random things into those snack
boxes that they sent me random things
yeah really really good things no no
snacks but really random snacks that
aren't even that popular in the country
while they often let out the most
popular things that would be so
obviously necessary in a snack box for
that country so it's been kind of weird
salt itself is not a snack but it's just
like a staple of like
um you need to get this out of Australia
yeah all right then now I got it without
even going to Australia but I still want
to go
um
yes I thought it was a joke dad dad
's name I thought it was a joke I I went
everybody so I when I read that first
when somebody wrote that on Twitter I
I thought of something I didn't get it
I'm not gonna say that what but I
thought of something else so anyway
um I thank you very much Sana for
spending your time with me I have to
prepare for the next stream uh that's
with Elena on my channel I'll have to
take a little break in between yeah I
kind of wanted to read some super chats
but I don't think I'm gonna really uh I
think I need some normal breakfast
just like just like
um yeah take it easy that's a lot of
sugar no no I know I know I know it
means happy I know but I you know I
follow some other things
yeah but yes so then I'm very very
I'm very
um I'm very gay that you were here today
Sana
oh same it was a golden gay time it was
indeed a Golden Gate sign that we had
together hello
yeah
thank you so much thank you thank you
thank you thank you thank you for all
the all the Stellar choices yeah
yeah
maybe maybe one day you can show me
around in Australia When I visit of
course of course
and stuff that's pretty beaches yeah
yeah and dinosaurs right that's yeah
yeah oh no no no no no no
oh no they'll be dropping down in my
streams in my dreams now on you yeah I'm
scared but thank you for um
thank you for your commentary it was
nice having someone uh chill with me
while I'm eating snacks it was really
nice I usually I'm doing this alone I'm
glad you let me yay
yeah and yeah with that I say and and
enjoy when we say if we dozen I will I
guess have to change the description
where I wrote uh where I linked uh Bales
um I'm Gonna Change it to Sana because
Santa was the one who was actually here
yes everybody check out sana's channel
if you haven't yet and
[Music]
um
check out my channel
[Music]
um
I'm one of you guys thank you
I want Australian
not anymore I don't really do that joke
anymore but yeah totally Australian just
for today
okay shout outs to bae yeah thank you so
thank you so much for putting together
this huge and yummy high quality uh
snack box uh I I I'm glad I'm glad that
I asked Bales to do this now sometime in
the future she will get the Austrian
snack box in exchange so keep an eye out
for Dad yeah yeah all right everybody
thank you and in German we say Alf
[Music]
bye bye
yeah
[Music]
bye bye
foreign
[Music]