The octopus is flying so high, and I'm
telling you, ``The rug
of the octopus is all about you.''  I
felt a relaxed and fashionable feeling, and my heart was so wet that it fell apart,
and I kept it there again,
waiting for the gaze that said love to me.  It's
a little fun to look out on the dark night, like I want to check the length of the comb. If the same morning sun rises tomorrow too,
[Music] I do
n't need anything else. It's a starry sky that shines blue.
[Music]
Shine on me, shine on the earth.
Let's dance all night [Music] The beginning is just a battle,
and even if I run out of space, it's okay to take a different
path If I go all the way to the end, I'm sure a
new world will come into view for me.
Until then [Music] [Music] Well, thank you, Loki,
I'm the only one who has the nerves to witness it. I want to
deliver the first part of Salo Nohaya's reading, too.
Meredy, it's
time to take a break. It's still going on like this, and my heart is rising.  It's so
high that it's
flying all the way, and I can tell you that the little love that you're whispering will make
you smile and tune out.  I've been
walking and watching this
girl in front of me for a long time now, and I realized that I
couldn't help it.The
stylish wind was so
wet that my father was falling apart.I
put my determined heart there again and fell in love.
[Music]
[Music] The
screen is
pitch black and there's
no BGM. Why isn't there any BGM?
[Music] It's
from a game, after all. BGM  I
didn't set it up, wait
[Music]
Thank you, wait.
Thank you, thank you.
Open
[Music]
Masuata.
Hello everyone. Hello, I didn't
open it. I
'm surprised. It's so different.
When I do that, I try to go to that loading screen, and
then it always starts again.I forgot to
put in the loading screen and started streaming right away, and
then it was pitch black.
Ah, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's
okay. We're all here. We're all here.
Today, those squirrels and Ori are
going to explain the rules and guide us around. Today, that
team that's practicing is Ioffi,
Sorane-san, and that Chiara.  I wonder if that's true. I
'll do it without Team Unra and Pabo.
Oh,
I can't move. I can't move. Yes, it's true. That's a
bug.
Restart once. Restart.
Yeah, it's Japanese. It's set to
Japanese. I see. That's wrong. If it's set to Japanese,
wait, everyone's volume is adjusted here.
Yeah,
that's the setting. If you press the escape button MOD, something will come out.  The only thing I
did was set the voice level to 300%, so it was a mess.The
only person I thought was too loud
got an extra 300.I
just don't understand why.  That's
right, it was just too big.
300 is that voice chat. It's the one I
used in the previous Hodoke. Yeah, that's right.
Maybe it's from that time.
Oh yeah, that's right. And then I added 300. That's
right, I participated.  I didn't do it, so I don't know. I
didn't do that at that time. Yeah,
yeah, should I sleep? Maybe I should
have doubled the sound. Maybe, no, but in my frame of mind.  It's
perfect. Who are you drinking? I do
n't have a bed. You can log out. It's
okay. Just use the waterfall here and
sleep. Good night. Good
night.
[Music] That's
right.
Hey, Bole.
[Music] I
'll show you around.
Thank you very much. Thank you. Please
come.
[Music]
[Music] I'll
put in the [Music] that I made.
[Music] That's
fast.  Oh, I
put it in.
[Music]
And
from
[Music]
Dada yo Oh
yeah yeah
[Music]
Yes
Tori yes
Here we go one more time
[Music] There
are 5 other games
[Music]
In H at first  There's a game called
Pleasure, which I haven't finished yet,
but I'll explain the rules, and let
players
compete to find emeralds hidden by the society.
Yes Teams collect emeralds and exchange them for final
game essentials Yes
Yes Events include challenging gimmicky
platformers,
brain-damaged ones and tasks that require teamwork
Yes
Yes beHi
Male For now  There
's a lot of stuff in the blocks and stuff
like that. That's right. It's a treasure.
[Music] I
want Indonesia. I want it. I want
it. I want it.
Thank you, Papa
. [Music]
[Music]
Eh, I'll explain the next game.
It's coming.
[Music] I've been
making this for about MON months. It's amazing. It's
moving inside the moon. It's
moving. And then there
's the maze. Ah, the maze is moving. I don't even know.
But,
oh, I don't know.
[Laughs] It's
safe, it's
safe, it's okay. It's because
of the ID members who are using this, so I'll
stop and introduce it to you.
This
is [music] [music]
But no.
Everyone is doing well, but let me explain a little bit.beexplalittle
BOh, each pair will stand on stage and
follow the instructions of the introduction.The instructions will
be held on the Indonesian ship, so all the
talents will be given a simple Indonesia 5 in advance.
Yes, it's
still going to take a little bit more time.
I don't remember it yet. No, it's okay, it's
okay, it's okay.
Teams will earn emeralds based on how well they follow the
[Music]
Yeah
Wait, where is this written? Oh
yeah,
everyone remember this.
I'll teach you the words Kiri
Kiri Kiri Kiri Kiri Kiri Kiri Kiri Kiri Kiri Kiri Kiri Kiri Kiri Kiri Kiri Kiri Kiri Kiri Kiri Kiri Kiri Kiri Kiri Kiri Kiri Kiri kana
Canaan
right right
[Music] Is it
behind the Babak word
?  [Music]
Janjan Num
from
Sadoor Door
Tigaa12345 dakore oh yeah
[Music]
Empa
Enen
Mari Marima
Rima and Po
[Music]
Hit
PUNCH
ter
sayhaveashave
particularhavejust
needI can do it somehow
[Music]
Out Shamu Shamu is Crow
Shamu
Jinko Jinko Jungkook Ga Crunch Jonko
Jinko Yeah Hada
Facti is Jonko
Ki Turn to the left Turn to the right
When it says Fang fasting to kill, pick up to the left.  That's right, that's right,
that's difficult. So
when you say "Hahapukiri", do you have to go to the left? Oh yeah, that's right.  That's
right, when I was told "Happ", I could have gone to the right,
right? That's what I see. Oh,
oh,
olepa. Oh, oh, oh, throw. It says
throw, throw. That's right, throw, that's right, throw. It's
like, if you
remember to run, it'll be bad, right?
Jonko.  Crouching, crouching, crouching, what else do you
do?
It's
okay to throw [Music] It's okay to
throw something, but um, I'll give you something in the real game.
[Music] I'm
sorry for not letting you know.
[Music] It seems like there's
going to be a wall later. Oh, there's going to be a wall
. There's a left corner of the
Times, or something like that.  It's like
2 times, 2 times, 2 times, 2 times, 2 times, 2 times, 2 times, 2 times, 2 times, 2 times, 2 times, 2 times,
2 times, 2 times, 2 times, 2 times, 2 times, 2 times, 2 times, 2 times, 2 times, 2 times, 2
times, right.
If someone says 5 karinrima, it's
like saying 5 times.That's
right.If that's the case, you
can say it while doing it.I
think it's easier to remember that way.
Ooh, oh, yo,
just stand here, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, I get it, I get it, I don't know who that person is, I don't know, I don't know who that person is.  I'm leaving, so I'm
going to make sure that I can stand in the first place.
[Music]
Oh, you're right. I wonder
if you're in the second place?
Oh yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah,
oh yeah, are you ready? Yes, it's starting.  Yo
[Music] I'm
going with Sulis. Hey,
EX will will have
will
on that stage. O3
[Music] There's a
countdown for 3 seconds after ``Yes'' appears, so
when the countdown is over, we move on
. [  [Music]
Oh, look at the squirrel, look at the squirrel, look at the squirrel, look at the squirrel, look at the squirrel, look
at the squirrel, look at the squirrel, look at the squirrel.
Oh, I see.
Next, it's
really long.
It's so long. It's so
long. It's the same pa. It's a good ending. Good luck.
[Music] Um
Lopa.
Sakamaji
Saka
Hakiri.  I'm here. I
want to see Rene and Kia next time.
[Music] It's
Ohana time so you don't have to.
[Music]
I see.
Red Red
[Music]
OKspeSlowlySlowlyOK
Slowlyokok
Let
1 Kan
[Music]
3TRUSTtrustyou I
see. I see.
ST2
[Music]
Sui
ofalAG
yesok
[Music]
STAGEONE
[Music] I
think I'd like to go like this for now
[Music]
[  [Music]
Yeah, I see.
[Music]
Ira
no Teji How much does it cost to have 10 stages? 3
Stage Well, there were 3 stages earlier, but there
were about 10 stages.I see, the
number keeps increasing.In
the beginning, there were only jumps, jumps,
running jumps, jumps, running back,
jumps, running, going back to the left, increasing like the left.  Is that
okay?
It's okay. It's
Oanstar, so there are about 10 stages,
so please do your best. For now,
about half of it is worth it.  If I
guess it right, I can do something. Yeah, yeah, yeah. No, let's go to the next mini-game. Oh, no. Uh, next time, uh, go, go. My poor memory will come out. Make sure you remember it. It
's okay, it's okay. Looks like it's going to be fun. It's okay, it's fun. Just go.  That's
fine, that's right, that's right, yes, yes, that's
right, right
here,
white,
a little, oh,
it's here,
nono,
nono, all safe, safe, safe
[Music] It's
safe, uh, first of all, I'd like to explain it in Japanese.Be
jaan Yes, yes, then the team will sell
and Formen will be synthesized.Yes
Formen is colorful wool and
will
cut off the wool from the top in the world.  You must make sure to fill it with the color of that team.
By destroying the upper layer, you can drop the opponent's four men
to the lower level.
The wool is still there, and the chim is standing up.
Hmm, I'm going to take it. It's an ult. There
may be a lower part at the top as well.
[Music]
I'll learn it while doing it, but it's a game. There's
another moth at the bottom, and it's divided into a bottom and a top.
Well, this is what the person at the bottom says, and the
person at the top goes, and the
person at the top can fetch the wool, and
what does the person at the bottom do
?For example, I said,  I'll cut it  My older
sister is above me, and when she paints the
wool of her team's color, she
becomes empty, and if she
changes her team's color, I
wonder if the more colors there are, the more the color wool will look like.  Yeah, yeah, it
's somewhere.
Oh, and that person is that person, Chizu, for example,
Kia-chan is that lucky girl, and
Kiara is on the left. When I heard that, it was me.
If I cut it, that Chiara will drop it,
and if that character drops it, I think we'll win. I
see. I see. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, let's take a look. So,
from here, from here,
from here, too.  It's
okay, it's going to be, so the
squirrel is going to be [Music] I'll cut from the bottom and it's going to be at the top
[Music] That's the language, right? For example, yeah [Music] I
see.
[Music]
What's going on in the lower part?
[Music] I
guess I'll cut it. I
guess I'll support the team above me. I
want to be able to open the game quickly. If I press green and red, then if I
press yes, the game is over.  It feels like it's
over, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, the more there are, the more I feel, so ok, ok, for now, let's try our best not to fall.  Which
one do you prefer? Just cut off the top and
put it in. Yes, yes, you
can cut off the top, but whichever you choose.
The one on top is also the white wool. You
can destroy it yourself, but the other person's color is  I
can't destroy it, but the team below me, the
members below me, can
also destroy the colors of the other teams.Oh, I see.
So if I'm on top, I can't do anything but
add white and myself.  It's
easier to understand the other person's chimuru at the top, so
why don't you give me a smile?  Me and my sister, what color
should we choose? Well, I guess green is okay. There's a lot of green,
so the people below me won't
be able to wear that wool.
[Music]
[Music] I
can break the dolls with those hands.  It's
only possible to break it, right?
[Music] It's
only possible to break it. It's
okay. It's okay. I
see.
Sora-senpai is better than me. It
seemed difficult, so I put it on top.
Either one is fine.
[Music] Have you been able to
do it without thinking a little? If you're on
top, then yes
[Music] I'm sleeping,
okay, okay
[Music] Do your best,
do your best, I'm
waiting for you
How many Stark blocks should I have?
Hmm,
I don't know. I don't have it either. Where did you
get it from?
Oh, how many stacks should I bring?
[Music]
Range:
Um, I think 2 Stacks is fine. 2
Stacks,
Stacks. I wonder if that's okay.  It's pretty
down, isn't it?
[Music] I
really remember
[Music]
Teru
Kiri
[Music]
O
Kirika
[Music]
Kirika  I
only do sharp and kana kana?
Majimaju maju
majudo
mundo
[Music]
Maji
Mundo I think I can learn it, oh majima
[Music]
Majichi Maji
wa
[Music]
Kanakana okay
Aa
adashi
[Music] Let's
try it  I'll try it. Let's
try it. I
heard it was a book. It's not me. That's right. That's nice.
Japanese is okay.
Oh, it's okay.
[Music]
Thank you very much.
L
[Music]
It's about to start. The reading is starting now. Ah, I
'm here on the left side.
Look at the missing wool. I see the
wool.
[Music]  It
's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's
dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's
dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's
dangerous, it's dangerous, it's
dangerous
[Music]
That's terrible.
Oh, oh, oh.
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh, that's a shame. I see. I see. It's
no good if we fall.
[Music] I
see. Wow. If we
fall once, it's
even more chaotic if there are 3 losing teams.
Well, this is
it. Ah, senpai. Yes, I made a mistake.
When I put something like this, the staff
seems to erase it behind the scenes, so I don't have to worry about the date and time
.
[Music] I
want to do it, so I'm going to try it. Let's try it. Yeah, yeah, I
guess I do
n't have to jump. I can do it without jumping. I can do it. I just did it, so I can
go. Now,
press F1 for the knife.  The
name of my new partner is
Waka. I have to press F1. Yeah, I don't
care where it is. I see.
Yeah, yeah, if I do that first,
something like that might happen.
If you put that color down, maybe I can figure out where it is.
Yeah, it's like this.
Yeah, if it's broken, then Shia breaks it, press F,
and it's a new Shia.
[Music]
Suo,
uh,
press F.
[Music]
F is ready.
[Music] I'm
ready.
[Music]
wor Here it is, finally, finally, finally, finally, it feels
good, it feels good, it feels
good, it
feels good, it feels good, it feels good, it feels good, it feels good, it feels
okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's
dropped
[Applause]
[Music]
Teruoto
[Music]  [
Music]
[Music] That's
left over, White
[Music]
Well, how was it? I want to do it again. It
's difficult. It's difficult. I'm below.
Thank you 4
Chim, let's play 4 all at once.  There are
44 people instead of 22. I do
n't know. That
's dangerous. If there's a hole in the top,
then you can hit other people. You can hit someone so that they fall. You
can hit someone on top.  It's
okay to fall. It's
okay to do it. It's going to be a battle. It's going to be a battle.
[Music]
[Music] I
see.
Or maybe three people at the same time. Let's
win that one. Let's do it. It's the
final
tournament.
[Music]
[Laughs]
That's right, I'm getting too lazy with 6
[Music]
has
Turnwill
6 people 6
people
Terunaku
[Music] Okay, so we're going to
play 3 games, right? 3 games Oh no,
no no  I'm so nervous,
everyone's going to fall all at once, I'm sure.
Later, when I reach that green color, I'll be fine.
Don't stay here. I'll
do my best. That's why that white, white
[Music]
Me
It's not the number, it's not the number left, it's just the
number left. It's not the number, it's the number left. That's right, it's important. It's
important. At first, I thought that if the color
goes up, I'll win. I thought so too, but
no, I stayed at the top.  That's because the one who wins is the one who wins.
[Music]
Wait a minute,
oramneedthereway
OK
[Music]
Yeah, no, no, I heard that 6 teams will
be participating at the same time.  Let's
try one round and we're all here Let's
all do it Let's do it together It's a bit
chaotic Oh yeah I want to see it a little more I
want to experience it
6 up and down 6 pi
[Music] [
Music]
Male
[Music]
instrumentreally
MAK
HORNlooklike
HORN
hearSound I
hear a banging sound
[Music] Do it
now
[Music]
Oh no, I
have a have2 stack right now I have one,
but that's enough, right?
[Music]
GoingLet
meGoing
beBLBL
[Music]
BLONE
yo,
drop your breasts [Applause] Lua, I made a mistake [Music] I
can do that, I'm
sorry, Senpai, it's okay, I think I'm going to do it one more time, one more time,
okay
[Music]
Okay, I see.  I see,
I don't really want to come here.
[Music] I'm sorry.
That's how it is. Hit me,
hit me, hit me.
Wa Punch Punch Punch Punch Punch Punch
[Music]
Para-senpai
neverVIIMANDVIIwas
afes
[Music]
[Music] It's
been going on for a while,
right? It's a vibration, isn't it? It's a
smartphone vibration, right?
[Music]
[Music]  ]
[Laughter] Are you
ready?
[Music]
[Music] I'm
sorry I made a mistake.
Alright, alright, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok
[Music]
Okay, 35
seconds, 30 seconds I'm going to put it in a strange place. Okay
, can't you forgive me for the range
orange? It's orange-green. It's green, green, green, green. It's full of weird places.
[Music]
Oh no, no, no, no.  If you don't bury it,
bury it, bury it if you don't, bury it, put it in a strange place.Pus
stop stop stop stop stop stop stack It's
stacking Toro
Mashimi is still alive
[Music] Is it
something like that? Apparently,
if you put it in the wrong place, Nesa-san
will pick it up right away,
so it'll disappear on its own.
[Music]
No, it's delicious, it's delicious, it's delicious, it's
delicious.  It's not a good idea to keep hitting them.There
is a
possibility that they will remain.I've tried both.
It might be filled up right away, so there
might not be any holes. Yeah, yeah, that's right. So,
do you want to give priority to filling the holes? Well, that
might be better. If there are a lot of people,
there will be people who will go there to fill them right away. Yeah, yeah,
yeah.  But when it spreads out, I'll hit it really hard.
[Music]
The first treasure Treasure
does the same movement as before.
[Music]
Hey, it's okay, it's okay. This, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this.  I'm so tired, let's play the
next game,
okay?
[Music]
Well, we don't have time, so let's play the last game. Please
put it in.
[Music]
Put everything in there. Rice and bread. Food is okay.
Food is okay.  I
need some rice-like rice,
uhm, what kind of rice do you have, senpai?
Well, let's have the same rice for now.
No,
senpai, please use this.
Well then, potatoes, I have a status,
but what should I do? So I'll give you some rice and potatoes.
Potatoes. Potatoes. Other rice.
Recovery. It's strong, so for now, everyone's a
potato. Everyone's a potato. Yeah,
yeah, that's right. And after this, be.
After this,
eh.  I'm going to use a VC group, so I'm
going to use a group voice just for practice, so I'm not sure if I need it.
Even if it's a chat group chat, it's a
group.Well
, it's a group in Mac where someone makes it.You
see, it's a create
group.Who makes it?I'll
make it.Okay, then I'll wait and let you know when it's done.I'll
probably do it on my own.  Since it doesn't come in, what's the type? Oh, it's a
group type after all, noror noma.
IS
[Music]
IS password
What power password
people
[Music] I
see, it's about 1111 Yeah, it's
about 11
Okay, maybe I'll change the password for Ade Maa in Toy.
Anyway, it's 1111.
Yeah, right now, that voice, that group. I
can't hear the voices of other teams because it's in the chat. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's why I
can meet them in the chat
.
Don't go with Lady Lady, OoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOo...  Is
n't there a normal group chat? Let's
get out of the group chat. Everyone
does it. How to use groups.
[Music]
Oh, play Elmen.
No, I'm already playing it. Next game.
Um, I want to explain.  Yes,
yes, this is the last game, but there's a
maze called Maze Fy,
and the team
consists of a fighter and a navigator. Oh, I see. The
navigator has a maze at the top that transforms into one.
And guide the fighters Yeah Yeah Yeah
Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah The
Navigator's job
is to help the fighters defeat the other fighters Yeah Yeah
Yeah And the fighters are standing The
team advances to the final round Yeah
[Music]
[Music] I think I'd better move properly. I'm probably going to die. I'm going to die. [Music] I
'm here.
[Music]
[Music] I'm
getting an email from a fighter,
right?
This is the last game, so I'm going to use the
winnings I've won so far to turn into a vessel,
so if I
win a lot of games...  I guess it's like putting it in a good weapon type.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, the
weapon changes depending on the number of emeralds.
Yeah, yeah, that's right. If it doesn't happen soon, it'll be a
fighter
in its bare form. If you can do something with your spirit, you
can do something.
music]
Kasan, here, here, here, let's
go, let's go.
Hey, there's no weapon here. There's no weapon here. Here, yes, I say, yes, for now,
everyone uses the same weapon. This is a panda. Yes, this is a panda.
Yes, this is practice. The weapon is that. It's
not a weapon.  Sorry, that's not a weapon. The
yellow one. The yellow one. Oh, and
the weapon that that lady ended up with is
[Music]
Here, the
weapon. Did Navi Navigator explain it to you
?
Ao Eh, the navigator is also a little bit, and I
have a bubble,
oh, wow,
wow
stow stack, and navigator navigator like
fighters
, two people here
[Music]
Den.  What's
going on?
Petit Petit
[Music]
Phifabes Oh, okay, this is the
base, so as far as I can see, it's probably purple, pink,
and green.For now, that's what I can see right now.  I'll
try to
stay out of this purple as much as possible, so I won't get on
it.  It's good to get on top of it and
look at it like this, look at it like that, look at it like that,
look at it right now, look at the group chat, but right now, uh, I'm in the
pink-pink room, but it
feels like there's someone there, and there's
no sister there, and there's an enemy over there.  or other teams  Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, it's warm,
maybe my sister, that, that, that, I can hit that, so I'm going to try to
stay in this range of purple, pink, yellow, and here, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right, that's right,
that's right, right here.  Is it
easy to be targeted if you're standing there?
That's why I'm begging you
[Music] I
dropped Haru, but
if I address them separately, I'll go over here and
join the group chat.
Eh, what is it?
Group
Hey, I guess the password is 5555. Are you going
home? Gogogogo Hey, I changed it. Okay, it's changed. It's changed. I'm all about that. I made it Gogo. We'll start soon. Okay, so let's go down here.  I'm in
position O, but I can see it properly. I
can see your name, so you can see it. I wonder if
I'm off to a bad start. Startin', I wonder if it's a
countdown.
Ritsuwao, I don't know if it's Rene or Chiara, but I can't
see anyone. I can
see it right now. I can't see anyone. I can't see anyone.
Well, for now, Yuppi's
going to go to Pink. Okay.
For now, I'm not going to be in Pink.
Ai, there's one person on the pink side. There's a pink person in the back.
Who
is it? It's somewhere I can't see. Oh, there it is.
Right now, it's pretty pink, I can see
it, I can see it, I can see it, I can see it, I can see it,
it's in the back, it's there, it's really shot, it's really
shot, wait a minute, it's
dangerous, it's really shot, uh, I'm
right now.  And I'm in purple. I'm trying
not to let it go too far from the base. I can hear it so loudly.
Pan and my sister are being shot so hard.
Who are you
? Let's go over there. It's dangerous, it's dangerous, me too.
If I was there,
someone would say I'm downstairs.Wait a minute, I
can't see my power in pink right now.Ah, it hurts.I'm going to get shot.If I'm in pink, I'm going to
get shot.  It's pink, I'm aiming for it right now. It's going to attack me
from the back. Where should I go? I
can't go, I can't go anywhere. It might be
better to go back to the purple that's in the bag.
Maybe the pink side will fly. What's this?
What is this? What is this? Oh, what are they really aiming for? Oh,
yellow, yellow, purple, Renee, behind,
behind, chasing me from behind.
Um, hey, hey, there's no path. Why, now, so
close, so close.  I'm here, Reine, I'm hitting you, you're right, I
'm next to you right now, and I can shoot, I
can see, I can see, I can see, I can see, I can crawl, I can
shoot, I can shoot, I can shoot, I'm aiming, but it seems
like I forgot to eat, regularly.
If I don't eat, I'll get killed. That's right. I
forgot. Okay, ok, ok.
Congratulations on your arrival. [Music] The road will be closed, right? What's that? It's amazing. I'll be chased from behind and chased
around.  It's
been a long time since I've been in the middle of a
long time, but I haven't been able to go to the other side,
so I'm
going to leave the voice chat.  Well, it
feels like there's a group of all, uh, all open, um, all, um,
tantal, uh, going to all, right,
going to all, oh,
yeah, I see, yeah, yeah, but the
punch hurt, the punch, the sword.  Gapa, sword,
hamabro, sorry, senpai, sorry,
everything. I couldn't see where he was at all.
Seriously, where was he hitting me? Where was he coming from?  I
thought it was in the red part of the red temple.
Yeah, that's
right.
Honestly, when Ioffi and Eunwoo were fighting,
they both had white hair and were so far away
from me that I couldn't tell which was Ioffi and which was
Una, so yeah, me.
Well, I didn't know.I really don't care.There
are two white challengers.I can't read them.I ca
n't read them because their names are too small.No, I don't know, but I
want to switch it up like this.Do you want to
do it again?Oh, I see, I
guess it's okay.  I understand the content.
Oh, I understand the content. I understand the content at all. Yeah, I
understand. Oh, I understand. Oh,
okay, rules. Do you want to switch? It's okay with Fighter.
Question: Eh,
I also have a question, oh, by the way, I understand.
As for the people below, do I
need to press that F1? No, it's
fine. Thank you very much. I do
n't know, because Kiara hasn't been shot in any way, but if she gets shot in some way, she'll
die someday.  Suka
Ah navigator yeah navigator ah die
yo oh die I
need a bed touch from Karaga Sata Is
Senpai dead? It was barely okay
But that was terrible and I almost shot him.
If Shigeta dies, I feel like I'm going to die for the second time.No, there
won't be a second time.If the navigator comes back to life,
I'll
live again.
If it dies, that's all there is to it.Then the
navigator will come back to life.The
navigator is the navigator.The navigator is Phoenix.It
feels like Navigator Phoenix.Yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, that's
it.
[Music]
ReallyLikeIsThe
thingonmyrightSide
thebighouseisalso
kindofinthewayand
meringare
SorrycommunwithST wasthelikeWhereI
standIfILooktomy
righttherelikeBIG
HOUSEmeringwith
AnotherEnemyAREA
likeIs
ThatHowdoIseeit
thereFTOWERSjust
likeoneachSideofthe
MA
Goingbe3
think
TurnTurn
[Music]  Let's do
our best to make sure it doesn't happen. Then there's no way it'll come back.
[Music]
ThereyousaythereF
TOWERSIGUoneachSide
themiddlelikemyview
tothetofrommy
blockedbytheistheo
GAMENotheogameThe
woolGameisBlocking
My
Shall we do it one more time? The
man and the squirrel will participate
.  Music]
Akaya
Fai I'll do my best so I don't die Let's
go to Group BC
BC
[Music]
Oh yeah, we're not Kia.
Well, let's try our best not to die. Let's do our best. Let's go. Let's do our best. If we get hit, we'll have to
eat some bread or some fries, or we'll be in trouble. That's right, we
don't have any fries.  Yes, no, no, no, no, I just
left my baggage in the place where I died,
so I don't know. Well, I'm
practicing raw potatoes, so I'm practicing. It's
okay, it's practice, it's practice, so it's okay.
Oh, it's already long enough. I don't
know where everyone is. I can't see
this. Come back, it's gone. Even if I keep jumping, if no
one is there, I can't see anything anymore. Hey, it's
me, so I shouldn't go.  I'm
being targeted from here, yeah, that's right, I'm being
targeted. I was also targeted a while ago, and
where am I now? I'm not in Pink.
Pink, that's right. I'm in Pink right now. So,
uh, I
can see where I am right now.
[Music]
Hey, Chiara, I can't see it at all. It's
moving so
tiny. It's so moving. I can't reach it.
Lady, lady, lady, I
want a telescope. I want a telescope. I wonder if I
can't do that. It's a telescope. I can't see it
while I'm using the telescope.  I can't do that, that's too bad, I
can't hit it, I'm ready, I'm
ready, I'm ready, I'll try not to stray too far from the base.For
now,
[Music]
Bye, then,
wa,
where are we going?  I
'm messing up. Oh, I wonder if I'm
right. Anyway, I'm
still in purple.
Oh yeah, that's Ioffe. Oh yeah, there
's someone there. There's
someone in pink, so wait a
minute.  There's purple, there's yellow, there's yellow too,
so I'm going to invite you to this purple for the time being. My
sister hit the person under there that way.  I'm
typing now I'm typing Thank you Thank you The
yellow side is amazing, it's so far back It
's in the back, but I
couldn't close the road for a while
Well, uh, everyone's in yellow
Everyone's in yellow So I'm going to yellow too
Or where are you? I hear there's Rene and Rhys on the left and right right now,
right? They're all there, I guess. I do
n't know how to get there. I do
n't know where to go. I don't know where to go. Airiru
[Music]
Okay,
now I'm in purple now, whichever I am,
but I'm next to you, I know, I know, I'm
wearing protective gear,
right? It's scary, I'm laughing so hard, I'm laughing so hard, I'm laughing so
hard.  That's scary,
bro. I can't believe it.
That squirrel's laughter is scary. No
one has been found by the endermen. I don't know. Maybe it's me.  I do
n't know. Oh, go, Lilith, there's a squirrel. It's
dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous. I'm
aiming for it, but it's up, up, up, up,
but what should I do? It's true.
Get off, get off, get off, get off, go purple.  Hey, I
went to purple. I guess it's purple. I wonder
if it's a hit. It's a hit. I'm aiming for a potato,
but I feel like eating and eating. Maybe now.
Hey, Kane is going to break soon, so
what should I do? Oh, it's purple,
it's here, it's purple, it's purple, it's purple, it's purple, it's purple, it's purple, it's
purple, it's purple, it's purple, it's purple.  That
wall is in the way. I have to climb up here at this time.
I
see. I see. It's warm,
but it feels good.
Well, the swords break quite a bit, so this is the case.If I
get a lot of money, I wonder
if I'll change the swords a lot.I
think I'll change a certain amount of the emerald, so for example, how many
strong swords should I have?How many weak swords should I have?  Do you
have one? Yes, yes, then I'll
ask you something. Yes, that's
fine. I turned into Bol Bol just now,
so yes, you can easily get that item from the person you defeated earlier.
Yeah, that's it, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I can't
tell you where it's
going. Yeah, yeah, yeah, everyone, where is it? I wonder if it's in the voice all,
right? It's like a group, right? That's
all for going to all, I see.
So let's go to All, let's go to All
Yes
[Music] Yes, come back Ao [Music]
Peko welcome back Peko I just heard that.
No, I wonder if Peko-senpai is there.
Thank you
[Music]
Um, questions,
questions, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what,
how many swords can you buy,
but it feels like there's only one sword.  It's
a bit worn out. It's a waste
of money. If I had a lot of money, I could
buy many books. Maybe one. But I recommend it.
[Laughs]
HELLi
cber
haryduanyberkita
bisabeliaDongSWORD
akutengahudahrusak
lagi
[Music]
ChatRat
lagisalah
lagi
Navigator
OverNavigatorigate
So, uh, the rules have changed again, uh,
uh, when the navigator dies, he
comes back to life, but it's like he
can't navigate anymore But the game  I'm
not going to end it. Oh, I'm
just looking. I'm just watching.
You can't use that one either. I have it. I'm
just going to support you. Just do your best.
[Laughs]
Emi, time is
okay. Tomorrow, my time is okay
. I see.
Well, it's okay
. Need [  [Music] I'm
here.
Thank you. I'm chasing him.
Who is that Enderman
? There's an Enderman here.
[Music]
Kaja
Kira, where is this?
Should I pick this up?
No, I'll pick it up, because I can't hold anything
[Music] Don't
chase me now, don't chase me, don't chase me, don't chase me,
this too
[Music]
Which? Which? [Music]  [
Music] I'm
sorry
[Music]
Here it
is, here it is
[Music]
Next game,
then one person in the pair is given a name for the stage.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, they are part
of it, but one
player tries to guess what it is, and the
pair responds with an emerald.
Baby, all colors are
green,
then I'm yellow
.
And who's in the building?
Who's going to start?
Which way will we start
?
[Music]
Okay, okay, I have a hand, everyone,
please do your best. It's about to start. I'll do my best. Um
, just earlier, earlier,
oh,
321. I
feel like it was like this. Emuzu emmuzu, it's really difficult.
Wall
Okay,
uh, hey, oh, that's it, uh, that's it,
uh, no, no, no, no,
that's it.
[Music]
Question Mark Question
Mark
Oh, it
's not grape No,
uh, that color doesn't matter Color is
color-related Ha heart is different But it's buu waaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
I wonder if colors are related.What do I think?If it's me, it's related to colors.
[Music]
Maybe it's pondering, like a snake.I like animals.I like
that.That's right.
Ah, I shouldn't have read the real chat,
probably. Yeah, I wish I liked
something like that. I don't know if it's just round, so yeah. I
imagined all kinds of things with Nemaru. I
like balls and things like that.
Oh, oh, senpai.  Toki-senpai, let's try it
. Let's do it.
[Music]
Then, I'll give you the title. Oh yeah.
Well
then, uh, Risu-senpai, let's do it. The theme
is the key, oh-
oh.
[Music]
Oh, it's difficult, I think it's a little difficult,
but it's difficult, okay, so are you ready? Yes, it's
321, what is it, what is it?  It's
a hit, it's a
hit, it's amazing, so I can understand why. Somehow, I can get to the top with just one shot. I thought it was a coincidence, and I feel like I'm a genius. It's
so good, so I guess I'll get another one.  Shall we do it
again? Let's do it again. Let's do it again. Let's do it again. Let's
do it one more time. Let's
do it one more time. Will we change hands during the actual performance?
Change Dared
[Music] It's
like how many rounds do you change
? I wonder which one it is. That's
what I heard. We're talking about squirrels and how
many times we do it.  I
heard it's not, right? If it's 3rd or 4th round, I'm sure we'll release it to the public, right? Yes, it seems like it would be more fun to switch places. It would be fun.
Well, there's nothing wrong with that. It doesn't matter if one of you
writes twice and one of you answers twice.  When I was
told "Janki," I
started to get excited, and then with one stick, I got a pop on top of the sako.
So I did a pop, and then I went down once,
and it became fluffy and round.
Let's put it on top of the top.  That's what I thought, and
before that, please answer. It's
good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's
good. The octopus's gentle voice [laughing] It's soothing, it's soothing. It's like those bonds and bonds in that beautiful sky.
Telepathy, telepathy, yay, yay,
nice. I wonder if someday we'll climb a tree together.
Climb, climb, climb, climb, climb
. At that time, I'll go to help you. Yes, you'll
fly away. Yes, you'll give me a ride.
Yes, yes.  I can climb up, but I can't get down. I ca
n't get down. Maybe that's why I thought so,
but that's why I'm going to help you. I
'll burn that tree. I won't
burn it. If I let it burn, then we'll be burned too.
That's right, no, don't burn it. Don't burn it, put it down and do it on the stairs. Stairs and stairs are a bit difficult. Faa. I'll call a fighter. Faafafa.  No matter how you look at it, she's a little girl, but Rei,
Rei
, Seriously, I've been wearing my sister's face for the past two months,
and somehow I've been hearing Renee's voice.  I
thought Anya was there,
right?
[Music]
[Music] I'm not sure if I'll
change it or not. I do
n't know yet, so maybe tomorrow
[Music]
Oh, but if you still want to practice,
let's practice. No, let's practice one more time. Do you want to
try it? Oh, let's try it again.
Oh, let's try it again. Who's Bill?
Ah, who am I? I got it right in one shot,
so I guess I'll try again. [Music] You're imitating Raco too much. Listen to the question. Leave it to me.
sayes
japaneses
Ah, I see.
Kiara and Seo-senpai, yes,
yes. Well, now it's time for flowers. It's
easy, isn't it?
[Music]
Yeah, yeah, have you made it already? No, you're making it
. There's still more to do. I'm asking you questions, and uh, beer.
Or is it okay to use the original? Both are fine.
If the floor looks easier, I'd
look at it from above and think, ``This is it?'' I
think it's probably easier to do it horizontally than vertically.
It's better on the side
Oh, look from above here Oh yeah
yeah Oh yeah are you ready Are you ready?
Yes yes yes I'm ready [Music] Tae, let's go 321 What is it? Sorry, change the place
Maze
[Music]
What
It's a flower
and a
flower.The bond is too strong.I can
see it in the sky.I can't see it.It's this.It's a cat.I was
wondering if I should make this shape.I
wanted to make it.
Well, it's
a little bit, I
think it might be better to separate the places, but I realized that we're going to bump into each other, so
there's a little space, but on the floor,
if you want to do it, it's fine, but it's a little space.
Yeah, yeah, this is true, I see.
Yeah, yeah, I'll leave it to Eunwoo, so I'll probably leave it to Eunwoo. I probably
won't make it on the floor. Let's do it
one more time. Let's do it one more time. Let's do it one more time.
Please, please, please.
Feeling, it's easy.
Banana is easy
. It's easy. I'll
do my best. I'll do my best. I
'm Rio
. Color doesn't matter from this point on, but it does.
1 What's wrong with me? I'm so bad. NoNoNo. I'm
better than me. What
's wrong with this? I'm a big snake, uh, chicken, chicken is no good. [Music] Hanaaah, nice. I don't think it's bad, but it's not bad.
Yo, what is this, what is this?  It's probably
easier to understand if you look up. Hey,
where, where, where do you look at this, this is it, this
is it, this is it, it's [music], what, what, banana, yeah,
okay, okay, this is a banana.
Well
then, I thought it was pretty good,
but I was glad to see the big banana. I
thought it was Yaru-chan's mark,
but this time I guess the older sister guessed it a little.
Let's try it then Aja
[Music]
HaveImeanyoudoFFWay
notalltopickafter
KNOWKNOW
Pi Yeah Ok I do
n't understand that because it's said in Indonesian No, there's no need to do that
Yes, I'm ready Nyaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa lady
deo
[Music]
Daaaaah
No, no, no, no, no,
what should I do? Spoon did it. Is it a
tennis racket or a spoon?  I
thought it was one or the other.Ah, I
did it diagonally.When I looked at both of them, I thought, ``I see, I'm sorry, sorry.  It's so fast,
it's so fast, it's so
good, it's so good.
[Applause] We
're on good terms with each other. It feels like we can't get along.
[Music]
[Music]  The
rules may or may not change during the actual performance. It's
a little bit possible. There
's a possibility. So,
yeah, I guess I've played all the games for the time being.
Hey, it's okay, it's
okay, it's nice than [Music] [Music] Shall we go out to the US? Jake, it's nice, it's nice, it's nice, it's
nice. I think it's nice.
Where is it?
[Music]
From where?
Kara Rishi
[Music]
Excuse me, but someone's going to have a real show tomorrow,
right? I heard it's going to be tomorrow, so I
thought I'd use the picture from today's practice session as the thumbnail for tomorrow. Oh, I
wonder
if it's here.
[Music]
Where?  Miko went.
Climb up. How do you climb up? This,
this, this, this, sister, this is here.
[Music]
Where's too high?
Chaooooooooo
It's night, it
's night.
Where do I want to take a photo
? Let's go, but
here. The back of the back is cute, so I might as well do it here.
Wawa, wow, where is this the end
? Tell me, this is the entrance. The entrance. Yes, the entrance, so it's
okay here too.  I wonder if it's okay for me to stay here, senpai.
Where is it? It looks like a nice place, but maybe this is the best place because it's
pedo.
[Music]
Yeah, it's funny, but I want you to send me a photo.  Do
all the seniors want to take it? Or yes, it's a
fit, but I want to take it too. Really
okay
cheese. I wonder if we can get close. Maybe closer.
Usu ah, Usu is not here. We are also masked.
Thumbnails of 6 of the 66 members of Kamen practice session. You
can use them.  It's good for thumbnails.
Wa-cheese [Music] I
can't get too close to you. When I get closer,
everyone gets bigger
[Music]  I'm
going to take a photo, I'm finally going to take it.
Thank you very much for this kind of thing. Please
send it to me. I'll send it to you.
[Music] Ta-
in
[Music] Good
luck! Good luck!
[Music]
Good luck!
Honjinemi  Moja Neji Neji Nene
Wow
OK I wonder
if he's talking to me when I open the book.
Thank you Pipi. No, I thought he was saying something.  I
saw you here, so you're talking, okay?
See you tomorrow, see you tomorrow, see you tomorrow, tomorrow, tomorrow, let's
do our best, let's do our best, let's do our best, let's do our
best, then I'll take a break first, I'll take a rest too
See you, see you, babye
.  Okay, so thank you very much for today. I was so
busy thinking, ``It's finally time.'' We
only had one practice and then it
was time for the real thing, but I understood the rules,
so it was fun. So today too.  I
worked hard, so let's enjoy tomorrow to the fullest.That's not going to
happen again.Let's do our best tomorrow.So, I'll
see you again on tomorrow's broadcast.I'm
sure there will be some tonight, too, but I'll remember the words ``Good luck.''
Zo
Maji
[Music] Maji Zubai
Bailogau
Chachichi Senkyu Tamakusa Gracias Malum Ka
Danda
Arika Graba It's fun I wish I could practice more
[Laughs]
I really wanted to practice a lot more every day.
But I'm glad I was able to do it today. I'm glad it wasn't a one-shot performance.
It was a day that proved my artistic talent.