AhDET
Let's start
No, no, different Button-chan, different broadcast.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, the broadcast has just started.
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, the broadcast has started.
only started broadcasting
Sorry, sorry, sorry, it's not Ramen
Sorry, sorry, sorry, the broadcast has just started
It just started Yeah, yeah, sorry, sorry
I'm sorry for confusing you, I say yes.
By the way, today is also hardcore
I would like to have a little pillow
For now, let's get rid of that fake trial.
Can you wait until the court deadline?
Nae, it just opens at 7pm, wait a minute.
Give it to me, it's dangerous, I have to go to Aqua's trial.
I can still go, I'm sorry, that big voice is so loud
Can I still go to trial?
I went to cut that tree with Hajime.
That's the guy my senior was trying to make.
Hunt the shins from the trees needed for the machine
Because of that, there's a house called Momori next to Ririka's house.
There was a big forest and I went there to crawl.
But just the day before that
I wonder if I can use it for something
I thought I'd try making it myself. It's amazing.
Automatic yes yes yes yes but a little bit
How do I use it since I'm a total beginner?
Even though I don't understand, I just look at that body
I tried making it, but I have it already.
Yes, the manager came with me.
Since the timing is precious, let's use it.
I was just about to use it.
I didn't know how to use it, so I made it myself.
Caught up in the equipment and unable to get out, submerged in water
This means that there was an incident where
yes
I was wondering if it was okay to enter this.
There was a recording of her, but she ran away from the trap.
In order to run away, a record like this is being played.
Is this correct? Yes, that's right.
Lyrica is 500% just me.
Trying to save the Bancho just by closing his own neck
Then, I'm just going to commit more sins.
I can't afford it, I don't know if I hung it or not.
Looks like I won't be able to go tomorrow.
Please stop me, I don't want to sin any more
Just having it
Invading enemy
I feel rushed
Gadakema
Show me what you did
I got it, just a little tea.
I had just lost consciousness.
At first I was trying to help that climber.
Did you do it? I stopped trying to help you.
It was really fun up until that point.
We had so much fun hanging out in the grass until then.
reflected
I probably said something about A-chan, the best defense attorney.
Have you ever heard of this? Yes, yes, Azuki, the lawyer.
However, I will watch the resurrection of the accused.
What is that? Yes, what is that? Business.
There's something inside.
Exactly what I was watching
Ei is with Ah and this Lyrica Hajimeko team.
The machine is moving and there is a defective machine inside it.
It's going to be an accident. It looks like there's going to be another one.
hey
Please leave your picture books at the Maru-sho where we keep them.
I'm here
I would like to read it out loud.Yes.
Will be distributed on May 15th, although Subaru will also be included.
Ririka-chan died
1 square of the automatic fishing machine at Ririka's house
I apologized to the water and swam into it and suffocated.
It seems that he died at that time.
Chan tried to break down the iron door to help.
Kuhaji-chan's log is slippery due to the reaction from the punch.
Tsuka-chan died while trying to escape from
Log No, this is definitely Hajime-chan
Didn't kill Ririka-chan yesterday
Ririka-chan has great knowledge just before the end
I would be happy if you could revive it.
Hajime-chan is also true, so there is no sound.
I would appreciate it if you could do this.
It means Masune
Well, I was really interested, so here's the first one.
Can I check? Yes, please.
I was abandoned, but it doesn't mean I abandoned you.
There's no way I can play drumsticks, right?
There's something a little weird about suddenly being guilty.
Is there such a thing? I don't like Lili.
I just thought I'd check it out just to be sure
Are you okay, Azuki-san, that friend of mine?
But if you give me a little doubt, I won't lie.
Let's make it clear here that you can't.
Yes, you're not here, Banchou Akonene.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, that's right, someone is in the drama.
Everyone, listen to this story and bring back Ririka-chan.
I would like to request a ruling on whether or not to allow
I think it's okay to let him come back.
Please raise your hand to chat.
If there are more than 1, please let me return.
I would like to have some. Please.
Please do it like this backstage
I'm going to work, this is Subaru, please hit this.
It's good, it's not squeaky.
Please, what should I do with that shield and sword?
There are so many different things happening next door.
If you let me eat my limit, I'll do it.
of course
It is a beautiful alert meal that can be made endlessly.
I made a mistake
I made the mistake of hitting Taayabai Iru-chan.
People who have died twice have brains.
You're really helping me out with this.
Ririka-chan will be revived in Ma1.
Looks like it's okay, Ririka-chan.
you from today
Thank you for the revival
Good luck and work hard
Necho-na, why did I forget to bring the diamonds?
Please use the diamond block only.
I don't know what to do with that terrible thing later.
I forgot to bring the diamonds.
Thank you very much for the diamond.
I forgot to come, so thank you and welcome back.
[music]
Good luck on your way back, Senpai
Good luck with the smell
Is there anyone who can protect my clothes?
Maybe not, it's your fault
I don't know what happened because I lost.
Not a bit
The cat people saw that, so they're witnesses.
Well, as a witness, I'm not defending you, I'm witnessing it.
I hope you can ask me some questions.
I think there is some damage to the back and legs.
There are people who have had various experiences.
In this life up until now, oh no no
No way, my wife will be pushed down.
thank you
Sorry, that's not right.
I'm a little older than you.
I'm the most senior among all of you, so please take care of me.
It looks a little bad, but it's okay.
I want to check the circumstances of the death, so what is it?
Can I ask you to tell me if it was warm? Yes.
that
Well, yesterday, while I was working on that case.
That's right, I fell from that TT Tower.
I slipped and fell and continued forward.
Since that is true, it seems like a bad accident.
Does it feel like that? Yes, I lost my foot in a bad accident.
But he slipped up and the witnesses said it was true.
Is that true?Actually, we weren't witnesses.
do
It's the same as saying, "What's this?"
It is true that he worked in prison for
The three of us were having lunch together.It was expensive.
By the way, it's true that I worked in a prison.
But then I woke up and heard Aqua's voice.
suddenly stopped and I was in the middle of a conversation.
When it disappeared, I looked at the log and found Aqua.
I fell from a high place and looked down.
Somehow Aa's belongings are scattered about and she died.
That's why we, like Aqua, did it too.
At that moment, I see you, I see.
I fell silently. I want to ask you something.
There are things like that.
But it could just be a slip and fall accident.
Yes, when I was wearing that carpet, there was a
I wasn't watching and I fell. Yes, yes.
Yes, all you have to do is press the shift button.
Hey, you're an enemy, you're a friend, the atmosphere is an enemy, twice, twice.
I'm dead, thank you
Thank you, thank you!
Sorry
Nea-san was like yesterday and Pecola was
Are you saying that Arata is at fault?
It was an accident because
It's sad that it's gone
That's true, but I don't want elephants.
I was just thinking about it and went to the guard seat once.
How much a little bit to Aqua-senpai
How many people have you ever been subjected to that kind of evil?
Can I count you? I feel bad for you.
I'm sorry, but please say goodbye.
That's good
No, I don't think there's anyone here.
You have Raki Lucky, Lucky and Rawa.
Do your best, there's one chin
Good luck, what did each of those three people do?
Can I just confirm what happened to you?
Yes, I went to Aka's house for a while.
I'm going to go and bother you a little.
Just a little bit closer
I thought so, so I want to talk to you.
That's what I thought, but magma was poured on me.
[applause]
It's too bad, it's too bad, I can't do it.
Can't do it
Sorry, I can't say anything.
I'm sorry I burnt that water.
It's not me, but my wife and family are
Well, I have a family called Ramy-chan.
But that Lamy-tan is on that leg.
From behind in a very deep hole in the house
She was crying because she was pushed off and dropped.
Is this a bit dangerous?Is this a little dangerous?
This is dangerous, I can't use it anymore, I'm pushed down too
fruit
I was pushed off
It's bad, you're dangerous, so it's dangerous and quiet.
Why are you so quiet?
There are so many things that make you wonder why
You're guilty of this.
Yes, I see. Can I say something to the court?
Okay, that's it, that's it, that's it.
I'm waiting for something like that.
Is it okay if I do that? Please, please.
Let me just say one thing.
Well, it's not really a term, but that
TTT Tower would be without the power of Aqua.
I see it was seriously not completed.
I see, so just keep that in mind.
I hope you keep it.I'll do my best.
So, are there any seats left?
Oh, it's totally fine, sorry, hey leader.
I want to say something too, after all, ah, Noe.
Atty, I would like to say a few words as Nene's bond.
I'd like to, but yeah, that's true for us.
On the first day, we had a bond with the group leader, Kanete-chan.
I was scammed out of two diamonds.
At that time, when the leader said that he had been deceived,
I'm like that without any hesitation.
I started burning Kin-chan with flint.
That's dangerous, that's dangerous
I'm a child with a strong sense of friendship, even though it's just my body.
So please give me that chance
Please, just make a little noise
It's difficult, but that's right, humanity is
It's a carrot and a whip, right?
Candy Candy, listen to the story so far.
For those who are okay with being revived, please
Reject it
Please, please, please, really
Um, please, please, just Endora
If I were to go, everyone would have wanted it.
That's right, I want the front, right?
You don't have the right to vote.
Subaru's worst idea is this microphone.
What do you mean by giving me the cod of memories?
What is this? This is so amazing. This is so important.
While saying that it's an item,
It was so kind of you to give it to me.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
I was told that if I didn't give it, I would be cursed.
It seems like you don't have any memories.
I'm more than half way there, wait, who is who?
Not doing it 12345 Who, who, who, who's hand
I haven't raised it, on the contrary, it's dangerous.
On the other hand, there's a possibility that he might break down with this.
Well then, I received a starting move of more than half.
So this time I'm going to revive it.
But unlike Ka-chan, I feel a little guilty.
I don't think it's a good idea, but the new one is coming
Tashinten Yes, I'm not innocent.
It seems like it's a problem from yesterday.
Yesterday's problem is also a little sin.
I just want it to hang properly.
So, now that I've added more, it will be permanent from now on.
The management, please be my little servant.
I'll ask you to help me too, and for you
Participate in the hell project organized by Pecola.
I want to go there, so please and the people around me.
Improve your daily behavior so that you can give back to others.
Please continue to feel it, today too.
I can't do it anymore. Is it already too bad?
It was really good.
Just say goodbye
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
There's a meeting starting today, so there are people who want to go to the Nether.
Let's make that gate in the Nether.
Well done!
It was so hot, the temperature of Nezha was so hot.
I can get it. Let's all make that.
I want Pekola, Licca-chan Nether Warm
Nice to meet you. Thank you very much.
I know how to do things in the Nether, I know, I know.
I understand, but why don't you make Peko-chan first?
Peko-chan is over there. Something is wrong.
It seems like you're busy, so I'm like, oh, that's me.
As long as it's that close place where I can leave it to you, I'll do anything.
Okay, I'll tell everyone today.
There will be divine punishment, so do your best with all your equipment.
Damn it, divine punishment, what, what, gone somewhere?
Why did it start so suddenly? I'm going to sleep, sleep, sleep.
Once I go to bed, I'm worried about Paco's throat.
Let's all do it together.
Let's go to sleep, okay?
He talks really fast whether he's going to sleep or not.
I don't know what to say, I'm sure I'm punishing you.
God's punishment is too scary right now I wonder what kind of punishment it is.
Even if there's something wrong with the timing, it's okay.
Don't let your body be torn apart
What if my arms and legs were torn apart?
There is a possibility that it will become a good thing.
Nowadays, the courts don't even use it.
Let's make it a distance game from now on.
Okay, so let's make the Nether.
What's going on with the gate?
Well, water and
You Obsidian, umm, magma magma water is fine.
Not mama bear and water
If it was Yoishi, it would be where Nene died.
But if you have a diamond ice ax, you can do it.
But we all have diamond ice axes.
I wonder if I can make a heavenly Daya pickaxe.
Is there 99 Mastellas? No, it's 9. If there are 99,
I can go with 9 okay yes can I go with 9?
101 or 10
I have to remove a little bit from the bottom of the foundation.
It's about 15 Miko's things we want to do once.
Ririka-chan outfit
Can't we do something like that?
Looks like something like diamond equipment.
Well, let's go back one step at a time, see you soon
I'll be back soon, equipped again.
Masuhai
123456789 Eh 10 At least 10.
The minimum is 10, but if you're going to do this, it's 14.
I think I need about 15.
Set aside a little more than the whole lot.
It might be better to have a diamond
Please bring about 15 and make a base.
Pour in the magma and pour in the water
stone 20
It's a good size, water and water.
There is a perfectly good water bucket, but there is also earth, earth, fire, and stone.
If I don't have one, I'll bring it.
Well, I'll bring it to you. It's already gone.
I got Subaru for Aqua.
Is Nosako's revival a good thing?
What's wrong with Sasa-chan, I forgot?
No, it's nothing, it's a button.
It's okay
Scary Pika-chan
You forgot to take the money. This is a diamond.
I forgot to get the diamonds, but now
I've calmed down
Nabakacho, wait, Peko-chan isn't there.
I'll be your servant instead.
We have to be self-governing here.
I think I'll put this in. My heart has already changed.
I stood on the management side, on the management side.
I stood up
I was left in charge, but you guys are going crazy.
It's fine
I get it, calm down, calm down.
Calm down, Aqua, you're seriously going to die once more.
What will happen to you, servant?
Zero, no, I can't revive it anymore.
That's right, I'm just like that.
Although it has been revived, Pico-chan's
Pico-chan is having a bit of a hard time.
I see, I'll tell you a little bit about it.Yes, yes.
Ah, yes, then I don't care if I die
If I were Peko-chan's servant, I would die.
If so, that's what it means, Peko-chan.
It wouldn't be a problem if the target disappeared.
Thank you for being Pecola's dog.
Thank you very much, you
I'll go get some weird obsidian.
No, at first we surrounded it with this earth, that earth.
Isn't it okay to just drain the magma?
Well, Aa-senpai's resurrection money is from the house of beginnings.
Please keep it in your cento.
is
Hey, seriously, Peko-chan, watch that broadcast.
I'm looking at this, Peko-chan, it's not like that.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, that's fine
Something like that
It's not a mask
I'm not sleeping, right? It's dangerous, it's dangerous, I wonder what it's like?
I don't know what to think
Hey, today for Aqua, by the way, it's super
I dug diamonds, so it seems like it's true
That sound yeah, this is also really dead in that nether
If you don't want it, then yeah, that flame regime or something.
It might be better to keep it on, sure.
Yeah, it might be better to enchant it.
If you want to be enchanted, I've made a gate.
I'll save some time and go as the closest group.
But it's okay, people who already watch it can watch it.
Okay, really, really, I'm definitely going to die.
If you think it's okay, maybe
That might be better, that's for sure
Well, for now, let's leave it as is.
The obsidian on the foundation under there in Suizi is probably
By the way, Subaru is really good.
I know where the obsidian is, but I'm looking for it.
You can go get it, but everyone has come.
But everyone is here, so I wonder if they brought it.
Thank you for bringing it with me.
It's a house stone, so the frame is a little
Arisukako Today Subaru Meccha Diamond
I found this super obsidian while digging.
If you fold it into a square shape inside here,
It's okay, I guess so.
That's tall, isn't it?
It might be a bad idea to remove the huff from the bottom one.
Is this the wrong place?
If that increases, it will be 14, so this seems to be enough.
It looks like that's enough, so I need some flint.
There are so many things that need to be said.
Senkyu, this is good too, please break it down.
a
Okay hey hey hey hey hey hey
Hey hey hey hey
Hey oh
It's okay. You can go. It's okay.
Just hanging out
Ah, what is this?
Ta
Yes, those who want to go should go now.
Chimauoi nene techimi let's us here
It's dangerous to go
There are people who don't seem to be able to keep their logs long.
Wait a minute, what if?
It's coming soon
But even though I had gold equipment, the location was not good at all.
Looks okay
By the way, let's put the bed down.
But when you come out, there's something like a cliff on the left.
But I'm not a match for you, let's get this.
First, the gate was surrounded by that gate.
First, go a little bit to make sure it doesn't get damaged.
I think I'll go too, will it be okay?
Sui-chan and Aki were able to gate this one too.
What time is chan coming?
Wait a minute then
Shall we go then? Well, that's right now.
It seems like a safe place.
Let's surround this place for now.
Drill a little hole
Masu Gusto
So for now, I'll take that or a stone from Rin.
Come
Let's go get some stones today
A mission while collecting diamonds
I would like to do this while also
For now, Subaru's house is ready.
I want to show it to everyone
Masue, this is Subaru's house, by the way.
I'll take a moment here and add some equipment for hanging metal.
I also have a rock
So I've collected quite a lot of diamonds today.
I'll do it too
I showed you that house. I should have shown you that.
Where and how do you look at the house?
I can't believe I collected super diamonds just by looking at it.
This is the diamond that's coming back.
I collected a lot
I'll give this to Aqua later.
I think I should go to
If I keep going at this pace
I wonder if I'll be able to make it in time for Sunday?
What should I do if I can't pay it back?
By the way, it's scary, but what about repayment?
If you can't do it, wait a minute, hat.
It's strange that she's doing that
No, what if I can't pay it back?
[music]
Even though the project is already over, I'm dying.
cat
Be careful, be careful, be careful
Everyone, be careful
Oh come on, everything is already covered.
It's well maintained, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous
It's dangerous, my cousin, my cousin, it's dangerous.
It's dangerous here, it's dangerous, you're so dangerous
go for a ride
It's dangerous
Chan down
Can I ask you a favor? Yes, please.
hand
I have to get the stone from Masuairuka.
Pyo
Hey, let's connect this like this.
Is it okay?
Well, this is it
Teya
I don't have anything to help you with, so I'm a real servant.
Wow, you're going to fall down there, so it's like this
thing
I'm sorry I couldn't save you.
This is it
But when I put up the sakoresako, it was a bit
I wonder if I can get diamonds with the new update?
I have money now
Or this or that.
Is it a Subaru that's open, no matter who gets it?
Quickly
Hey, I was thinking about putting on that armor.
That's right, wait a minute
This is okay
I'm here, I'm going, I'm going, the vine soul
Look at the diamonds
Please, are you okay? You're really, really okay, aren't you?
Seriously, we built a house and then we moved in together.
There's a house, there's a house, there's already that house
I wonder if it can't be changed to
By the way, I may have used it today.
You can use this here. It's a lie.
Let's try to make this better. Come on in.
Hey you, you're going to win, isn't that awesome?
Don't call this home, it's home so make fun of me
If this person was here, this would be zero.
That's why I'm being graded differently.
I can't tell you everything, so please wait.
There's one in another place. It's over there.
I thought there was a possibility of that being plagiarized.
Hello, hello, hello, hello, hello
Hello, hello, hello, ah-kun, kaosan-san
Hello Kocchibeko, nice to meet you.
My wishes have changed, please eat and wait.
That's what I've been told, so please excuse me.
hand
Ah, I'm going, you can't eat yet.
I'm sorry, I wasn't hungry.
You've changed, Minato, you're like that.
Where is Atikiri?
He's gone. Say hello to that girl inside.
Please, please give me a book too.
Hurry up, why did you hit me like that?
I've changed, I've changed
Wait a minute, Subaru is also a bit okay.
Since there is, it's 14 for now.
Okay, okay
Yes, thank you
Yes, thank you very much.
But wait, what is Aqua's debt?
About a little later
teeth
It wasn't 1633 or something, it was 16, give it back right away.
Yeah, that's a lie, I have 14 more on hand.
This is not the chest plate.
Even if you enchant only the armor, you won't die.
I don't want to die even if it's a joke
If Chan falls, he'll die, so either way.
I'm going to make that potion or something.
Maybe it's good flame potion Sotara flame
If you drink the potion, you won't die.
I understand that flame potions are high level 35.
Apparently there are only 21 left. It's not enough at all.
Well, you
It's not enough at all. I understand. Today,
Are you going to the Nether? Let's go to the Nether today.
As long as Kanapeko-chan has no work to do,
Okay, then what about Subaru?
Attacks that increase experience points
I can do it, just look at the attack and attack.
Well, today I'll do whatever I want and set a diamond.
If you go to the nether while collecting it, it's definitely
Requires gold equipment
That's why I have gold equipment, I have money.
Water that can be exchanged for gold and diamonds
There are no more sociable people
mosquito
Well, what should I do? For now, it's Nether.
But I went quite quickly, so for the experience points
Go and make equipment
Are you going to the Nether?
I wonder if it's true? There's this.
mission
is the mission
Ganeneda mission is aayo mission
let's do this today
teeth
In this mission, the first thing I do is go to the Nether.
If I find something, that's good enough.
So that's it
Let's wait for today's mission.
This is a one-shot reversal in the check mission.
Become the first discoverer for the Nether, damn it.
It's big, so wait a minute, but I'm alone
I can't go, so someone should go to Nether with me.
I say do you want to go?
circle
Who?
together
30 years old fortress
The fortress is terrible, the difficulty level is extremely high, it's underground
Which is the temple?
good
The management really looks like it's going to die.
It's dangerous
So for now
Then diamond
I'm going to have fun with the diamond equipment.
Mom Yahoo
Yay, I don't want you to do that.
Eh, I'll do anything to Subaru-senpai.
I just started today too.
Yes, I don't have that diamond equipment at all.
I got it from chan, yes yes yes
Yes, honestly, that diamond ice ax and that sword.
Or something
I don't want it enough.By the way, I'm going to the Nether.
I have plans so I want to go to the Nether today.
If you go, you need gold equipment, but if you have it.
I think it's good, but there are certain things.
Are there any bumps? Yes, there are already.
No, what would happen if I received some diamonds?
But I feel like I'm going to do it, sorry.
On the road
Oh, Dice-senpai wants diamonds.
Subaru wants diamonds, so
I can't give you a diamond sword or something, but what?
But it's that diamond that will do it for you
Age
If I get a diamond, I'll call it a Subaru.
I'll do anything, but I guess it's a diamond
I want it, but if you give me the diamond sword, it will be plamize.
I can't do it, so please help me
I thought you would help me.
I wish it was something other than diamond.
I would do anything other than that.
Even if it's difficult, it's necessary this time.
So if I had a lot of diamonds
I'll call out to you again, oh well, see you again, blue.
Neaeshi Senpai Diamond Minus 120
yes yes
Yes, it's Japanese Ginbo.
This is what happens with Gimbo Japanese Gimbo
I understand, I understand, that's what happened.
Please do your best. Good luck.
Let me just say that En's child also has Subaru.
I'll do it even if it costs diamonds. See you again.
Hello Ao-kun, what are you doing?
I don't want anything, all I want is diamonds
If I can get it, no matter what happens,
It's dangerous but I'll do it. I only have one diamond.
is
Thank you, but if you need anything
If something happens, just say yes, but I'll give you one diamond.
But there's nothing I want you to do, it's a trap
I would like you to guide me to the tower. 1 diamond.
Is that okay?
Well then, I'll guide you to Trap Tower.
By the way, even the traptor that did it
It's quite dangerous, so if you die on the way, you'll be responsible.
No, but are you okay? I have food.
Okay, let's get a bed.
I don't have a bed, I'll bring my bed too.
Here, here, here, we did it.
Ao-kun, no, just now
I was thinking of going, so I'm glad you helped me.
Subaru was just thinking of going too.
Help me, help me
Hey, I'll take a bed here and have a free bed.
I did it because I wanted to do it.
Rice too
Some fish, rice, and rice are already cooked.
Bring it with you, it will recover a lot of your health.
If I get about 15, I'll do this.
I guess it's a little scary, but the night is coming soon.
That's right, so it looks like it's going to be a bit difficult on the way.
So once you get a little weak
Okay, we'll meet here. See you soon.
Let's meet here before then. Yes, I understand.
See you soon, good morning everyone, good morning today.
Good morning too
Good morning everyone, good morning, yes that iron.
Where can I get iron? It's over here.
Thank you, Tetsu this way.
Hey, you don't need a diamond, right? This is a diamond.
It's so-so and it's so-so.
Toko
I'll put it in my notebook, so don't worry about it.
That feeling that I never said I would give up.
I don't feel like it yet, but I've already got it
It's okay when you enter, it's dangerous here so be careful.
Oh, wait a minute, it's okay when you already have it.
Seriously, when I got my hands on a diamond
If you think about it, ask Subaru-senpai to show you around.
It's like I got it, but that's it.
Minus If it's minus 120 now, yeah that's different.
About 3 days after Nimako this and that.
It'll end, right? It'll end, but Subaru...
I don't want to go to hell, so please tell me the truth.
circle
I hope everyone will forget about Kia.
Is that so? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Pecola is not the kind of woman who forgets things like that.
She's a woman who remembers well
Falling down
Hey, it's in front of you, yes, yes, over there.
Underground office in a gray building Thank you Aja
Hey, I'll do my best to make you feel good, so please feel good.
So
After all, it's just how you feel.
Oh okay uhm
first
Well, after I get all the iron, I'll wait a little while.
Is it okay to wait?
So I told Chiara to sit down and take it from there.
I'll tell you it's okay.
I'm fine with your feelings, so please take me with you.
1 large
Let's go, let's go, baby.
Ze
Oh it's blue
Hey, blue boy, please wait.
Good evening, please give me some guidance.
Looks like it's this way
Hey, is it in such a dangerous place?
No, it's a little far away, wait a minute.
Nahohoho, wait, give me the coordinates.
It's 16600. Wow 1600.
I'll go all the way to blue in case Subaru dies.
I'll give you the coordinates, okay?
000 Wait a minute, here are the coordinates.
Yes, I'll take notes.
1638 Noe
366366 I understand, it's there.
If Subaru dies from something, you
I'll get there, whatever you say, I'll protect you.
This way, this way, this way, this way
I'll do it. It's no good. It's a little tree.
Should I bring this?
I have 30 keys, I'm a genius
Okay, wait a minute, here it is.
Thanks to this, Ah, and Swaru-senpai's diamonds.
I was able to revive Ririka-chan safely.
I was able to do it, it was like that.
Good, good, I have debt too.
No, really, you're such a kind senior.
Please tell Lyrica.
That kind of thing, that kind of thing
Well, I guess it's just a little bit.
Well, Subaru is also having trouble with diamonds.
If you tell me what you want me to do, I'll give you a diamond
Just tell me I'll do anything
Tell Aka
It's okay. It's really hard to say something like this.
I feel bad, but yeah, that Subaru.
Moa, live properly this hardcore
There's a place I want to go back to.
I see, that's right, so it's not Mamasu.
But wait, is this place dangerous?
Are you okay
That's quite true, so that's how I feel.
I would be happy if you could let me know
Wait a minute, what's the blue color?
Sometimes my voice becomes distant and I wonder if he died.
What would I do if I died without making a sound?
amazing
I'm not good at running, wait a second, Aoko.
It's full of potholes so be really careful.
That's what I mean. I have to be careful.
There are things like that that aren't there.
That kind of thing suddenly made me feel like a real hole-boko boner.
It's open, so it's okay, Subaru.
I'm walking behind my senior, so wait a minute.
That's a big responsibility, my scary senior fell down.
If I do that
Are you going to see me off, Mio-kun, or are you going to fall too?
Isn't it?
How to laugh, haha, I guess I'll just make a boat.
I'll make a boat. Leave it to me to make a blue boat.
Subaru makes and builds a two-seater boat
2-seater, 2-seater, 1 diamond
Will you even do that?
Well, I don't like it, but I'll accept it with 1 diamond.
But it's more like a feeling.
If I could feel more gratitude,
Yes in the future
Yes, I understand, please ride.
I'm sorry, but the blue one was in front of me once.
It's okay if I get off, it's true.
It's down, shift, shift, okay
It's okay, I got on board.
There's still more to come, let's go!
It looks like it's going to be a wonderful cruise, really.
Let's make it to this date before night comes
I wonder if it's Yahoo Date?
Sensenpai rowing under his armpit Little bear under his armpit
I'm looking at it from a different perspective, but no matter how I look at it, it's beside the point.
It's growing from under my armpit.
This is not true
That's not really true, you're fine.
It's too much trouble for a little girl.
I thought it would be rude to talk about my armpits.
It took my breath away, I see. Thank you.
Oh, there's a bee. There's a bee.
I see, I guess I'll go down once more.
Yes, getting off and getting off is perfect, perfect
Oh, and here, this is still half way.
or
Ao Ao, you're so scared of running, you're a little slow.
Yeah, that's it, just press space.
I'm pressing the space button for some reason
Sometimes something feels a little better.
Okay, you're a real horse, but there you are.
There's a hole in it so be careful.
Apparently that's the enemy's house. Enemy's house is dangerous.
I'll wait from here for a moment.
Just like the crazy Ishida-san.
If I were to die without a voice, the blue would be alive, alive.
I'm glad I'm still alive.
At least when you die, scream and die.
Even if you say leave it to me, I won't die
Who did I swear to?
It's the last day to eat pigs and pigs.
Survive until the Ender Dragon
I swore to repay you, I see.
That's good, that's what you want
Yes, I don't usually eat pork, but I usually eat pork.
No, don't eat cake with pigs in Minecraft
I'm the type of person who lives by eating, so what's that?
Kind of like Marie Antoinette
It's kind of dangerous here.
It's dangerous and expensive, please be careful.
Poyoung, it's okay, Poyoung, Poyoung, Poyoung.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Oh no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
I got on board
Why did I ride by mistake?
I'm riding, it's dangerous, it's dangerous
It's fashionable, on the contrary, these days, these days.
I hear you ride a boat on land. Travel by boat.
Until we move on land
It's nice to be here
Wow, I'm not sure I can go home now.
I'm sure
Return to
I can send it for just one day. I see, it's a debt.
Is it okay? I can borrow money.
You're a really good junior. Normally things like this happen.
If I say that, I won't be able to get called out even though I'm a senior.
No, but will you lend me a loan?
Of course, but I'm sure that's it.
Tomorrow I will do some kind of mission 1
I should be able to earn about diamonds, so yeah
I'm sure you're doing a mission.
Masuyo-chan and E were the most recommended.
The mission is easy to collect doses.
Oh, it's okay to collect the doses. Pile up the flowers.
If you mix it into a squishy shape, you can create a color.
That's right. It was fun. That's nice.
It is true that Subaru also collects 10 different colors.
That one is the easiest and heartwarming.
It was fun. That looks like fun.
It's like a day spent by Subaru.
I think I'm having a different day
I'm pretty peaceful. Peace is so innocent.
Chinchiroyannattan did it
I won big. I won big.
It's okay for my JFT to get off the train.
Oh, please listen to me, my home's JFT is the place.
So I borrowed 30 yen for diamonds.
I lent it to you, so come on.
is
If you give me the yen back, I have 30 yen.
It's going to be all pure wind boats.
It's a debt war, right now, it's a red pumpkin.
You can take the pumpkin. It's okay.
It's going to be night soon so hurry up, hurry up
Be careful of holes too.
I'm already a little worried, Mom.
You're quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, idiot.
Let's get it quickly
I'll get this already, so hurry up and get it.
I'll do it for you, so you don't have to take everything.
It seems like you don't have to take everything.
Come here
Is there a time when we have limited resources?
Say you can't take it all
If you're going to take it, don't sleep here for a while.
Wait a minute, don't sleep, no, no
I'm going to sleep now
Please take a look at the beautiful stars as soon as possible.
It's over quickly
It's okay, what are you in such a hurry for?
I'm going to die, you're going to die, I'm going to live my life after all
What do you do until you die instead of living for
I'm sorry about the feeling of living.
I don't know what you're talking about, I tend to enjoy it.
That's it, let's go happy
Okay, I'm happy and the inn is the best
It's death, this guy is enjoying life too much
You're so cute, you're so cute
Dolphins are cute, of course.
Subaru-senpai is also cute and annoying.
It's so annoying and embarrassing.
I'm so scared, yes, yes, yes, already.
Let's go home right away or get some beans and go home.
I want to make cookies. I can't make cookies with red beans.
You can make chocolate chip cookies.
But I'm sure if birds eat it they will die.
I'm going to die, I'm going to die 360
oh
This one is really beautiful green.
The sea is probably warm around here, isn't it?
It's tropical, and the dolphins are following me all the time.
Yes, dolphins are really nice around here.
It's cute, it's cute. Is this around here?
Yes, I know what a trap tower is.
I'm not there, but I went to the trap tower.
I thought I was going to collect weapons, so I went to the trap tower.
Go to and collect weapons bow and arrow arrows ah yes
Yes, let's gather now, shall we? Arrows of bows and arrows
I want to dive into the Nether because I want it.
But I'm confident in my weapons, so yes, yes, yes
Wow, this is so exciting
I was excited about this
I said poop, wait, wait, wait.
Wait a minute I said wait wait wait wait
No, I said I was a junior.
Why did you say that? I was a junior.
That's not a total thing.
Well, if you find that, it's not that.
Isn't it true that Esono was a junior?
Is that red one? Red one, right?
It's further to the right once you get off here.
I think you understand, this is where the sea is.
Ah, the sea
Do you want to get off here?
It's okay, but it's already like this
If it's nearby, it's probably found.
certain
What is it that made you a junior?
I thought so, but is it not?
That Aqua made it, right?
Ah, let's go. It's the population.
That's good
Oh I made a mistake
Yes, I'm going
Okay
Yeah, wow, here it is, Subaru also accumulates experience points.
Yes, you can. Apparently you can accumulate experience points.
I see, because you will be able to have sex.
That's natural, did you make it?
I thought it was natural.
Yes, come up
Amazing, it's on top of this
This is it, what a shame, what a shame
If Tetsu-senpai wore a skirt, she would be sexy now.
It's a shot
Hey, it bothers me when you say you look so cheerful.
That's okay, I'm sorry for letting you down.
It's okay to be a samurai, what's the point?
It's so sexy thank you thank you
You're so sexy, I'm glad you're doing well today too.
Blue is always cheerful.It's true that blue is always cheerful.
But today's thumbnail is me with a big smile on my face
Even if it's a lie, the thumbnail always looks good
Hi, my hobby is making thumbnails.
There's a sword here, so yes.
Yes, it's true. This is the enemy that fell here with a sword.
I'm going to hit you, I'm going to hit you
Ah, then there's the bow and arrow.
There are 64 of them. I think I should probably get them.
I think I did it
I see, from here towards those feet
It doesn't seem to fall at all. When I attack it, it's at night.
Then it'll fall, oh, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming
Octopus, yes, yes, that's it.
You can collect experience points and enchant them.
I guess that's the case.
It's dangerous, but it won't explode, so it's okay.
That's right, it won't explode like that.
It's so fun, it's some kind of weapon
If you receive it and accumulate experience points, then go to that sailor.
I see how much I can go back.
I can't seem to get enough of it.
Is it about 20 levels per 1 yen?
That's why I need this so much
It's better to be around 20.
It's 9 now, so you'd better save up a lot.
Since you came all the way here, you might as well save up.
Would you like that? Yes, it's 30330.
Ah 30 Ah, there are quite a few.
Clouds that seem to exist. Wow, clouds, clouds, real ones.
Hey, zombies are here!
Zombie Zombie is here. Zombie is here.
Don't fall, don't fall
And now that's it, it's because I log in a lot.
Yes, she is a witch, and witches have many enemies too.
I just realized that I have to be careful.
But
Sorry I have all the experience
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm fine.
But of course you brought me that experience.
I'm sorry that I sucked up my value. I'm sorry. That was before that.
do not give
Wow, that's helpful, thank you very much
Thank you
Please go ahead and save up to 30.
But will you wait for this too?
You don't have to wait, if someone calls you
You can come and pick me up.
Isn't that kind of difficult?
Even the coordinates of the village are now blue.
It would be a shame if I died because I couldn't find the coordinates.
Shina, I'm seriously disgusted, it's all my fault.
Blue brought me here, Blue couldn't go back and died.
I'm so sick of this
A bird that doesn't die that easily. A bird riding on a bird.
I'm on board
cute
Wow, now that's a little blue.
I'll call you and come over, okay, okay.
You can use the bed here, cat.
Please leave Aqua's grave in charge too.
If it's okay then I'll go back once.
mosquito
Wow
[applause]
Wow this is great TTT
It's good to start a business with luck until TT.
The Nether is so dangerous.
I might die if I do this, don't worry
Looks like I can go to something.
Hey 1000, is it the other way around?
Subaru is dead
Yeah, wait for 1600 in the Nether, minus.
[music]
100 Which direction is this?
This will be the last time I see Auku off.
That's dangerous
It's too much but that's it. It's a bit of a nether.
If you defeat Gust in Let's Go, you'll get diamonds.
I'll do it from
mosquito
Looks like I can go somewhere
Cat
What's this? I wonder if it's a junior gate
This is this, this is Subaru, this is this.
It's not the one Aqua found.
hey
Then take a screenshot of this too.
Wait, this road is connected.
Hey, maybe it's just growing sideways or something.
The one I received
I wonder if there's some kind of treasure here.
There is something
There's nothing wrong with this, I'm sure I'll find it.
It will definitely be collected
For now, let's do this
Return to Amamura
go back to village
It's terribly packed
It's taken away, isn't it?
[music]
Is this okay? I'm worried about him.
I won't die in a weird way.
Na
This is this
All the stars are beautiful
What should I do if I die from this?
Subaru, wait a minute, I was worried about Blue.
What if Subaru had simply died from this?
Let's do this in Ohara, no one knows.
at the right time
If I die, I'll be in serious trouble.
It's really dangerous, isn't it?
First
I can't see anything, I'm really scared
But please, open the night quickly
Coming from land
Wait a minute, land at night isn't dangerous.
everyone
Please sleep, everyone sleep.
It's a little scary on land at night, so wait.
temuramuramumura
Sechi Hoshizora Surua I can come back here
I see. This is the village.
Janko is also a village
Karama transportation will be here soon.
That's right, Kara
In the back of this corner is Kara's attack base.
from
I should be able to go back to the village from here. Well, there are a lot of things going on.
I'm here
But for now
Then go to the Nether and attack the ghasts.
Also take a look at the enchantments depending on the place.
Kou attack point
is here
My 1600 is different and I know something strange about it.
Teru village
No, what should we do? Can't we all go home?
Wait, minus 1600 is strange.
Because
I have to go to minus 175.
is
This is a different village
Wait a minute
I'm in trouble, I'm going to die
This is another village too.
I'm bad, I'm dead
Goodbye
Subaru, no, I can't wait and die here.
I can't die
Sorry, I might not be able to come pick you up.
Not about you
I can't die here.
turtle
hey
Toma Minus 100, where is this really?
I don't know
But 1 diamond
This happens for one diamond
Isn't that what you call it?
If you connect to the Nether, close the portal over there.
We were talking like it's okay.
Why don't you just draw a portal from
Well, that's it, so I can pull the portal
Damn, I'm going to fall into a hole and die.
to
Hey, wouldn't it be better to do that?
How can I draw a portal today?
I'll wait and find out.
That's the best thing
Hey, I need to calculate the coordinates.
Daeane is about to go, wait a minute.
hand
Well, let's follow Nene for a bit.
Kaenene is trying to pull the portal.
I can't help it, please help me a little.
What about portal?
Let's listen. Create a portal on TTT.
Ah, I made a portal on TTT.
I just need to open a connection with the Nether.
Things like that
Hey, wait a minute
For now
I'll go back to the village, but first I'll go home.
Let's go home. It's a bit too much, but that's it.
So we need a portal to
Should I draw a portal on the TTT side?
Subaru broke that Aqua.
Subaru claims that Teru Aqua made it.
That place I thought
I'm sure Ao-kun has already become quite muscular.
Hey, another
Since it is not separated, I have obsidian and blue one.
Just go back there and make a hole there.
I know there's some obsidian in the village.
It's from here.
I'm looking at the coordinates with Nechan. They should match.
Oh wait, it's 1740.
terrible
That's too bad 1740 That's too bad, wait a second
There must be 63 people with 175 mana.
Even though 63 people had to die, I returned to Japan.
It's okay, it's okay, it's gone a little too far
I went too far
Maybe there is
There might be a serious underwater temple. There's a serious underwater temple.
What shape is it?
Even if you come here, no one will say it's impossible without moving.
You can't come and have me come.
I feel nostalgic today about the Subaru accident.
Early Subaru Minecraft were always like this.
It felt like
Wow, I can see it
By the way, if you can find it, you'll be lucky.
That means
Well, let's all be popo positive.
Wait a minute, this isn't snow, I found ice.
But I decided to go with Ao.
Wait a minute, I found some ice.
But I decided to go there with Ao.
Good
It's impossible unless it's naughty
No sig touch
It's over
Well, it's over.
this
Well, if you go here, you should be able to return to the village.
absolutely
The TTT I can go home to is
So in order to go to TTT, first do that.
I have to bring it to the village
I have to bring that here and there.
I know where there is obsidian in that obsidian.
It's okay, Aoe, where are you waiting?
It's okay here, this terrain is fine, it's a village
seen near
Terrain, this is getting closer Ah, I'm back
[music]
Look, this is 100,000,000% back.
I've never seen this before
Yes it's true
It's so bad, I don't have an impression of this place.
Wait a minute, I'm not impressed.
This is a bit scary and I can't go home.
Wait a minute
Even if I don't like it, it's in the right direction.
Wait, what kind of path is it taking?
of
This is a big adventure
has the coordinates
Look backwards
It's okay
This way, the right side
No, I can't go home. Oh wait, I know this magma.
I know where Terune said she saw it.
Near Kokone's house
Maybe it's not this mountain, maybe it's not this mountain.
What a beautiful scenery
Subaru is different, the opposite is true.
against
It's really true, the opposite
JanX
but
No, this is definitely
It's Nicocchi
Why are you looking so hard in this direction?
It's all nature
But I don't want to die
cormorant
I don't want to die a dangerous death
wants to go back to the village
Wait a minute, go to mina 175 first.
let's go
Is it okay to leave?
I'm going to Nakocchine Maina 175.
But I'm so tired today that I can't do it anymore.
I thought it was Mario, but I'll post something.
I'm feeling better so I can go.
a little bit
Distribution has only just begun today
At night
Narucho digs a hole once
Prepare for camp
I'm getting ready for Sueganoshuku.
Okay, let's put a bed. Why put a bed?
year
Yakoya
Na
Okay, well, it's 1000 people, so I'm used to it.
Mons
That's strange, I was planning to go today.
After all, it's a jack-of-all-trades
Quit it, this is not the time to be a jack-of-all-trades.
I did
walk from here
When I got back to the village, I couldn't sleep the next night.
The next night I'm asking if it's okay.
I can't open it, it's tasteless everyone, next night is coming
I want to go home by then, but I can go this way.
This way
Too bad they can't open the next night.
This is seriously dangerous
but
Where do you go up to 175?
The z-axis is pretty calm, that is, one by one.
Because I can only do
1000 people wait a minute and get Minecraft
Uncle calm down
I tried to calm down and calm down.
It's not time to panic yet. It's still night.
Let's do it
No where to calm down
I've never been here before
No, wait a minute, I've never been here before.
Somewhere
Here, here, here, here, you can go now.
It's okay, I'll walk and swim away
Is this a bit dangerous? Is it possible to escape from the soles of your feet?
Subaru is going to die too soon.
Driving technique
What do you know?
do not have
Yaba
terrible
Seriously bad
It's really bad, it's really bad, it's really bad
terrible
Sorry, you can dig a hole once.
Sorry for a little bit
Dig a hole once
Iicho once
What should I do?
[Laughter]
wait a minute
Let's all open the night tonight
I don't know
Minus wait now 63 people want to go
But now there are 1,205 people.
screw z axis
It's on the side, so the side is off.
That's what it is
I don't have that, so I'm going to take a boat.
Let's make it. I seriously thought I was dead.
A dream fill created by an overwhelming sense of direction.
Harmony, I'm sorry, what are you talking about?
I don't know
This is what Minecraft streaming looks like.
Can you imagine anything like yesterday?
I can't find a different dangerous ship, everyone.
I can't see it. Wait a minute.
ship
Where is the night?
Where is it?
This is not what I want to do.
a
Where is this?
1700 ah shrunk
I'm sorry I died
[Laughter]
It's a little white and dangerous
It's so white it's dangerous
It's here, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's here
This way, this way.
This is a bit of a bear
too much
Amachi
First, make sure its white, its a white bear.
Get off
This way
Hey, why is Minecraft so tense?
Wait, it's turning green
blood green
Mr. Fuji has appeared
Datsu-san, what are you doing now in the village?
I want to go home.
I want to go back to my village
But I can't go home
It's dangerous, it's dangerous
When I saw the dangerous coordinates, I fired a shot, but it didn't work.
I haven't done it yet because there are only 000 people.
This way
is green later
Everyone is saying that if they see the coordinates, they'll shoot.
But if I can do that, I'll be fine.
There aren't 1000 people doing it.
Wakocchidakocchiseya
Well, you're finally back
green land
It came, it came, it came, it came
It's this way
This way, this way
Wait, it's not a bear, it's a sheep.
There is also a frog
Wait, first of all
picture
Oh, don't go diagonally.
If you go diagonally, various coordinates will increase.
Because it's not
When moving coordinates, you must go straight
No
Learn about it
That's too bad Mami, that's what it is.
I'm getting lost
Wait a minute, I'm learning too much, but that's normal.
It's obvious, no, no, no, everyone
Hey, people who saw Subaru Ozora's Minecraft from this time onwards.
It might be Hanama-ish.
However, those who have seen Subaru's Minecraft
It's like this
hey
That scary smartphone freedom and Subaru's Minecraft
All the reasons why I didn't do it are packed here.
That kind of thing
Hey, Naru Midori is back.
blood
Haha, I thought I was dead.
I was surprised
I thought it was a polar bear
It's too bad that the night won't open even after waiting.
Wait a minute, the night won't open
Too dangerous fire
Wait, the sun is setting, it's scary
Right, wait a minute
Well,
Howl
Blue
Blue Subaru says, wait, go to sleep.
entrust the message of heaven to the blue
If I have to do something blue
Bamboo of my dreams
Tell them
I have to
Blue: I have already accumulated experience points.
Subaru for a while
I don't think I'll be able to go there.
There's a sense of tension
It's not too tense.
Right, I'll definitely stay there for a while.
I want to go back and open the portal.
Just have feelings
Masue
Oh, it's terrible at night
Wait a minute, a future with really scary people
I'm from. Something good will happen today.
[laughter]
Hey, some people in the future are already going crazy.
What should I do about the comments section of Sachoto Zuba?
It's okay, I'm seriously not going to open tonight.
What should I do to imitate it?
It's not good to sleep in
Dadou
But please open it
Attack event occurs after 9pm
Wait a minute.
It arrived just 30 minutes later.
That's right
I don't think so. Wait a minute, everyone.
30 minutes later
That's terrible
This is dangerous, wait a minute
Wait a minute, wait a minute
contact neti one time at a time
A little bit
right now
Bustling around
Wait a minute.
Sorry, where are you now?
It's supposed to be like this
It's not supposed to be like this now.
Oh wait, wait, it's okay
mosquito
H
To heal
It's okay if it's dancing
Honestly, it's better to sit down than to lie down.
terrible
I see you built a boat.
Hey okay?
Ta
You can come the other way, but I can come here.
mosquito
Even if you come
[Laughter]
nice frog
is crying
Now
where
It's far away
minus
400 Wait a minute
hand
555 Kokoya
Hey, it's okay to sleep now, I see.
I'm saying something, but the frog is crying.
Because it is
Yes, I'll give you the diamonds in return.
This is the code for a crying frog.
Negomen
I'm crying simply, this is okay
[music]
Is this okay?
Yeah
shaft
Ah, wait 400 minutes and go with XYZ.
Wow
66 Ao please help me, Subaru is in that village
It's like I'm not coming out
often
I went all the way there by myself this afternoon.
I was able to go
Nayabakune, I was able to go all the way there by myself.
Right?
Why did you go with Subaru?
Ah, the night is opening
Teru
where
What if two people caught a frog together?
You got a diamond, right?
There's no frog today, everyone.
The creeper
There is
kill kill
Not fit to kill
Ao come quickly
Kureshishank's Sky
to
Oh, come quickly.
[applause]
What's wrong with the sky of the lost city?
Oh me
I am
The weak sky is crying
I want to cry here at home
Let's go home. Let's make it easier to see. Let's light lots of torches.
Stand upright
Chao Hansel and Gretel-like
Nekoko desu SOS
SOS Ao Subaru looks at the sky from here
I can only do this
It's not a grave. It's not a grave.
Hey tower
Too many towers to build
[Laughter]
Aaah help me
There's a frog! It's getting dark at night.
I have to go home
Wow, so scary, so scary
Yo
How scary
Let's go blue. It's not blue, it's today's weather.
It's bad though
Everyone who can sleep
I'm sure I'll expand the room I'm going to sleep in
Subaru will also contribute to
Let's build a tower
Subaru, I want to see the attack event too, wait 9
It's still okay because it's time
I wonder if I can live here.
newly
Everyone seems like they don't sleep
I just stay home and sleep
Hey, there's a raid event going on. I'm back now.
I'm a lost child, I'm a lost child
This is so bad.
Waiting for the smell of a skeleton
Please give it to me
a
What about this?
It's sunny now. Looks like the rain has stopped.
Will I run out of food and die?
That kind of thing
A hole in the hole
I've been seen, I've been seen, I've been seen
Teruoi wait, there are too many creepers
It's better to stay at home after all.
Ta
Wait, find out how to defeat him
It's a lie that's dying
Wait, don't die, you're going to die, after all
Blue is dangerous. Wait a minute, blue.
Oh well, I guess I'll just go back to the village.
Let's get it, wait a minute.
Yeah, I thought it was really over now.
But it's seriously over now. Wait a minute.
hand
Blue is almost here
Terue, what should we do now?
Edesa wait, Takumi has to make eye contact
I can go
Let's make an escape route just in case.
That's true, if the craftsman doesn't see eye to eye with you.
Doesn't explode
It's supposed to be, so I guess you can just break the bottom part.
It's different
Is it dangerous?
No, wait, this is the sound of walking.
What about this? What about this?
here this
and
picture
ah
It's over there
hot water
kill that guy
First 1
body
I wonder if Ayuko can't do this anymore.
Erase it
or nearby
TD and Nezha
Thank you for the opening
Thank you Nene-chan for connecting me.
Blue is safe here
crackle until
Too much
Hey, Subaru, what did you do to guide me? You can't go home now.
It's from 9pm.
The frog
There's a frog
Ta
There was a blue-blue frog
Was there a frog?
Is it close?
It seems very likely that there was a frog.
That's right
I sent you the coordinates a while ago, so I'll send them again.
virtue
Kakorekoshi
Tee this is X
Just X and Z are fine, right?-461
556 is fine.
Hey, that's right, I don't need Y.
This is this
After all, I don't need Y.
This is it
I'll do something a little expensive
or from a high place
Looking down
Ao must be somewhere, wait, something's on fire
Teru, it's not the blue that was burning just now.
It's scary, but it's the blue that was burning over there right now.
There isn't.
Are you okay
Looks like an idiot
Aobuta
It must be nearby. I love the blue pig. Ouch, ouch ....
pain pain
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, I died
I thought I was dead. Thank you. It was good.
How could a lost child know the coordinates?
Well, I came exactly as per the coordinates, what should I do?
Thank you so much for this place
I wanted to go back to here, even the coordinates.
If I can figure it out, I can go home. Amazing, here are the coordinates of the village.
tell me
Please, here are the coordinates of the village.
Is this a disco? Leave it to me.
Please leave it to Minor17563
You're really cool, you're cool
Are you a cool blue parenthesis who is good at numbers?
Too bad, I'll be the prince now.
It's the one who is the one who is the one who is the one who is the one who is the best
The one time it ended, I saw a polar bear in the middle.
There it is
Seriously, it's not a frog.
Yes, there was a white bear. By the time I got here, there was a white bear.
I haven't even been to that kind of place.
Wait a minute, where did you come through?
It looks like you had a big adventure.
The polar bear was too scary
But it was dangerous, blue.
Well, it's too negative. What was the negative?
Um, memo, maina
1751756
63 Now we have to go for the one that decreases.
Of course not.
It's going to decrease, but I have to go towards increasing it.
Hey, you're here, you can manage Helluel.
He's a genius, hehehehe, he's amazing, but that's okay.
Yoishoa Goda attack field I think I can go there too.
Right, I'll go there.
mosquito
Oh wait, there's a hole there.
I wonder where it is, it seems like it's here.
I feel like the point is over there, great.
Hey, I'm too reliable, please leave it to me.
It stinks, it's a little blue, I can't see the front.
Here I am, raking through the grass like this
I guess that's why he came. On the way.
Blue once while being attacked by zombies
I'm so sad to hear that he's dying.
Blue is because of Subaru who couldn't stop.
I'm the type of prince who can fight even if I think I'm going to die
So I'm glad I'm the type who can fight.
Leave it to me, leave it to me, here
I feel like it's right, it's decreasing here.
Both are decreasing, so this one is decreasing and this one is increasing.
It's okay because it's here.This is blue.
The moment I arrived, it was here, there, near the village.
I don't understand anymore. Wait a minute, Subaru.
I'll stop moving on my own, I'd better sleep.
Well, I guess I'll just sleep here.
That's over there
Is it true? It's over there, it's home.
Wow, this is scary.
mosquito
At least I won't sleep even if I hole up
Well, I can't sleep. Maybe I won't sleep.
It's like everyone's not sleeping, they're fighting
Because there is an attack
Ah, but there's definitely someone shining over there.
The zombies are coming. I'm going to someone's house.
It's not someone's magma.
I saw the window, right?
It doesn't matter what it looks like, it's probably a server.
It's good to be back. It's good to be back.
I'm glad I was able to return this.It's great.
Good, good, Ji seems to be sleeping quite a bit.
Let me sleep in this whole place
Hello, I'm intruding on someone's house.
I don't want to die, so please lend me your house.
Koa Koko Ati House, no more at all
It's just a village, isn't it? I'm glad I did a little more.
I thought I was dead
Thank you, that was great, that was great
Give this back to you
I don't need to pay it back because Tsuru-senpai has a debt.
There are a lot of them, and I'm definitely getting them.
Please, thank you very much.
That's it, Ashikamosu attack event
Yes, there is one diamond that is very important.
It seems okay. I want to go to the raid event. Raid.
I'm going to an event. I have a blue diamond sword.
I don't have one, so a diamond sword.
Let's give it to you
[music]
Takocchi
Okay, that's good, go home. Don't go home at all.
This was great, but I had never seen a frog before.
I was so happy to see the frog.
Subaru is also seriously finished, white.
I thought to myself, ``What the heck is going on here?'' It's really over.
I thought
I'm not saying that, but the polar bear doesn't suit me.
I wonder if it didn't match. It's a lie, it's totally a polar bear.
There was no place to die, it was always a jungle
It was so white it must have hurt.
I wonder if it was a lie, right?
Now, let's start now.
I don't think I'll go, but I'll go.
So, is that iron sword enough?
Wait, Subaru maybe 3 diamonds
Maybe I can make about
Well, I lost a lot of diamonds.
Nene helped me today
This is it
dekoko
[music]
Is this a lot of bows?
Oh, I feel like I can make it, I feel like I can make it.
I can make it! Hello, I think I can make it. I think I can make it.
Good morning Ho-chan, I'm seriously lost.
I thought I was going to die, but I was born right now.
It's all about me, I've just been born.
There's a gathering event, it's okay right now.
I'm going to die, I'm going to die, Ani-san.
I'll give you this too, it's amazing
Wait a minute, Aki-chan, this is coming.
I'll give you a little gift
Let's throw this a little bit
hey
[music]
Diamond
Thank you, I'm already in awe of the spirit now.
I have that crafting thing.
This is a crafting table
Please go to the crafting table
It must have been a little old, so I bought it as a souvenir.
There is also, wait what?
It's expensive, it's expensive, it's expensive.
I was saved by blue
Should I leave everything somewhere around here?
Ha, I'm so glad to be back.
[music]
So what are you imitating now, Subaru?
[laughter]
come without
I failed like a popopo and died.
a little bit
A heavy event starts in 3 minutes!
I've been entrusted with it so I can go.
Well then, Ma96, who is making me a shield.
12 I didn't get clicked so let's go.
96 I did it 96 Now I can too
I've gotten stronger. Let's go. I've gotten stronger. 96 and
Azamashoma
96 My 12 becomes impossible, impossible, impossible, impossible.
Don't force yourself to wait, blue is strong, so it's times like this
Ah, Maina 96 is here.
Wait, what about the x-axis?
He said something like that at the iron station.
I thought it was around here, so maybe it's around here.
It's the other way around, but it's minus 96.
Because it's not here, it's ABCs.
It's not me, I saw you attacking.
This is where Iroha is attacking.
Yes, here, here, here
Even here
Location Location Even here it's not blue here
Is that the blue one? Maina96a
Over there
Rashiage-chan guides Subaru.
What happened because there was a lost child tag?
It's dangerous that you're doing it right away.
That was me a while ago. I was also that Minecraft.
I'm a beginner. Yeah, I'm a beginner.
Yes, yes, let's go, let's go, Aka-senpai, it's time for the bow and arrow.
Are the arrows gathered?
Wow, there's so much left there.
I feel like I made this terrible thing, but there's no connection here.
Good morning, good morning, Suichan is here.
Chandayo Suichan also has an attack event
That's right, let's do our best together.
Gathered hard work first day attack event
I wonder if I should bring some food.
I'll be here in a minute, but I'll run away
I wonder if it's true if I'm about to die
If you die, it's over, so even if you run away,
It should be fine, right? It's fine, but using other people as an excuse
The spirit of survival
I guess it's fine if you don't have it.
Chanimaku saves Suba who is about to die.
I gave it to you. It's really cool.
That's right, I've seen some cool places already.
I'm in trouble, I'm in trouble, I feel like I'm in trouble.
I haven't seen it yet, so that's where I get beat up.
What should I do now that blue is dead?
Daraa, that's Nedonmadonmaima.
Once it's gone, you can run away
Looks like it's not coming. How can I get this?
I swore on that day that I would do this on my own.
Moja
Good luck and understand
But I don't have a bow
If it's a bow, leave it to me. I'll help you. It's better to go to the top.
It's okay, that's the only way to do it, so it's a bow motion body.
This sword is special, even Subaru is special.
Ze
A golem looking for how to make a legolem.
Somehow, someone just took the iron block.
I did it Golem
There is a lock, and if you put it together in a shape
It's going to be a golem, right? Wait a minute.
The golem assembled in the shape looks like a cross.
I'm going to do this on my workbench with the letters Ruett TT.
You don't have to worry about it, just go ahead and do it.
I can do it here. I can do it here.
A place where you can leave it behind and fight like never before.
I want it, don't put it here, baby
Let's put it on and bow
Ah, you can try it out, Izu-chan.
I'm sorry, you can try it.
I'd like someone to leave this to me, please.
I may be able to do other things, but this
You might be able to do it, Tsubo-chan is amazing.
Yes, I'm doing it too, but it's a little boring.
There are 2 blocks that are giving me that kind of thing.
I have no choice but to wait for you
Thank you, thank you, thank you
Thank you, thank you, I can make another one.
Iron block that can make one
Pumpkin on the block
The pumpkin ride is so full.
It says that an attack is coming, and it's serious.
It's already started and we're heading there soon.
I wonder if one of this or that is on its way. It's coming now.
Therefore, there is one more Mejikoresa block.
effect
Ah, the whistle rang
This is enough
Can't you get used to it?
I can't do that, why?
can't do it
So why not just put it somewhere else?
The wrong chair is in the way
Teru T Oh wait, no, that wasn't that face.
Well, this is it, isn't it?
It's getting in the way that I can't do with this.
So here it comes
Was it Nanaimatsu?
yes o
I can't say ok
I haven't been able to keep up with consecutive failures.
It's been a long time. The attacker has come. Maybe he hasn't.
I just came, I'm coming
Teru Ako was coming from this side.
The flowers I came to plant and the flowers were saved.
I don't want to plant flowers because it's so clean.
I think they planted it because it's so pretty.
You can be happy and happy.
I'm happy, I'm happy
[laughter]
Aki-chan
Baaki-chan is in high spirits, but she was born now.
I'm so fresh and cheerful that I'm at my most energetic.
I'm going to go upstairs with the best energy, so I'm going to sleep this and that night.
Ah, come, come, come, come, sleep
I'd better go here. I don't have a place to sleep.
Eh, they're coming everywhere, they're coming, but there's nothing at all
I can't see
It's amazing that there were two enemies who looked like they were murderous.
The book that came to me
Even Dae is defeated somehow.
You're here like this now
I'm now
It's in the opposite direction, it's true, it's over there
It's coming next time next time next time next time next time next time next time next time next time next time next time next time next time
This is what I want. I want a crossbow.
Get lost
I want to give it to someone who uses Tasubo.
Nama-chan is bad
He's a scary person, but he's scary.
Let's push the stairs
It's coming, it's coming, it's coming, it hurts, it's coming
Teru is coming, nice nice golem
I'm scared that he's going to attack me, but I'm sure he's doing it.
The golems are amazing golem group
What you're doing is burning.
It's burning, it's burning
Teruta nice ahare
That's so nice, it was on fire
The fire is over and the bow and arrows are on fire.
It's really strong
Hey, I feel like I can win with just Golem 3.
Golem too common pick
I'm coming. I'm in the back. I'm in the back. I'm coming.
It's teruene, but somehow it makes sense.
Too bad
Wait strong
weird food food
[applause]
dead
The firepower and the fire will quickly die.
Yeah, I think I'll die in about 2 shots. Are you okay? Polka.
Po
cow milk
Back, milk, milk, milk, where is that?
I've got it, I've got it, I've got it
Teruburn
Riding on a cow
What is Teruba?
That guy yeah what what what nice nice
No way
A little golem
Tsueeee
Polka polka is dead Polka is dead
There it is, flying, hey, hey, nice
Oh no, Polka is dead.
Go
I'm a polka hero. I've become a hero.
Polka He became a hero, Polka.
That's it
I was just looking, dead, dead.
polka polka died
Pol was killed and turned into a mex.
Becks, the person holding it open, open it a little.
It's open, it's open, it's a little bit
Chan's uhhh polka is dead.
Bye bye
[laughter]
Polka is so simple, Pol.
There's no such thing as a porn product, but maybe
This milk jacket looks like a polka.
That might be the one Polka was drinking.
[music]
Let's make a grave for Po-chan!
Farewell, let's return farewell, farewell party
Pol-chan is around here for a while
I died because I'm used to making things okay.
To Namatsu
There is also one signboard
Let's all have a farewell party together.
Shall we have a farewell party?
Polka is a game that tells you when you died.
let's sleep let's sleep
Good morning 21:07
Apparently he died at 21:07.
Where to put the big signboard
[applause]
Ne5
month 16
Sun 21:07
I got it, I already made the potty soot
Click here to find the speed
Niniru is a little longer
Longer limbs are better
Don't act like that plus alpha element.
Yoohanabetokimasuaohana
That's a relief, it's so long, Pol-chan, throw it at 9pm
7 minutes
Touch the length of the hand
touch
a
[music]
I quit
If you don't do it, it's amazing. It's amazing.
Became
Rutte
Because it was Kayapano, because it was sad, so my face was
I want it. There's no trial anymore, so it won't come back.
I can only do Darue once at most once.
I loved this one.
Hey, you liked this. You liked this.
I'll definitely say it
Everyone, let's take a photo because
last
[applause]
[music]
none
[applause]
Because I'm in Yoichi.
[laughter]
I
[music]
Takonore
It's unscrupulous
is
That's too good, then we'll disband, thank you
Thank you very much for your help.
Thank you everyone for your help
Thank you for your help
Mashigozan
sad sad sad pol
Kapol
[music]
Is it because of someone who said this or that?
So hello ahmikochijanimiko
I don't know anything about this, what's going on?
It's all over now. Polka died, everything.
I guess the polka just died after it was over.
When it was over, Poloka died, yes, Poloka died.
Hello, you're dead. That's crazy.
There was just an attack event there.
That's right, that's right, it was scary, it was dangerous, Emiko
I'm naked but that's crazy. I'm seriously so well equipped.
Miko Shisugi is seriously going to die
It would be better to equip all of them.
It seems to be something like this
That's what it feels like, I have to be careful
No, wait, maybe this will happen.
I'm going to go make Mikotetsu equipment. I got it first.
Hey, what kind of locker is Miko's locker?
Temiko's locker is Arami's locker path
locker
What kind of locker do you have in your locker?
I just came here today, so I can make it here.
I think it's probably a good idea.
Please make me a locker.
Miko-chan's picture
Rocker This is the rocker's exposed neck
It looks like it's going to explode. I guess you could call it a real exposed neck.
I've always had a Subaru.
Yeah, this is really exposed.
Sleep
This is this, this is this, this is what happens when you die
Anya-san, this is what will be written.
So this is probably Subaru's senior.
There's some kind of ice block in the chest.
This is the ice Subaru-senpai was holding when he died.
I don't know if it's not a block, but definitely this
The diamond block is different, but this is that.
Well, I have to get that money here.
Isn't it terrible that everyone is like that?
There's an ice block in this diamond.
It's a block, it's a diamond. It's a block, it's a diamond.
It's a block, not an ice block. That's scary.
No diamond block, no debt at all
I can't finish paying back the debt. How many more to go?
Do you have any money left?
I received a diamond sword from someone who helped me.
Since it's all over the place, let's go to Zaa or something.
No, maybe 120
120 First of all, I want to be with someone.
It's okay, I think it's time for that phase to take over.
Masu me
Hey
I was talking to you over there right now.
What, what, what, what are the rules?
I told them to start by regulating and getting equipment.
Are you parasitic because you got it, like Subaru?
Miko-senpai everyone ah nya nya punnies
Somehow, Senpai, I already hit you, so I won't give it to you.
It's okay, Menjano-chan is big.
I'll give you something nice.Yes.
Ah, it's an iron sword. Thank you.
Can I give you something?
Because I came late
It's okay, it's okay, that's bad.
I returned it and got this one in blue.
Here's a dandelion with a hangnail.
Red poppy miko looks good on you
Hey hey
I'll tell you where the iron is.
Wait, you told me this rulebook.
Ah, read the rulebook first.
I want a rulebook or something like that.
Oh, you didn't read the rules.
Tell that Peko-chan about the rule book.
This is the only rulebook I received.
Thank you. There have been some changes to the rules.
But please stop reading this.
Peko-chan will explain what's going on.
I made it easy for you, but here it is.
Shima
I read that and wrote it on that server.
That one
There's no way it would come as 0 like that.
I called the person written on that server.
in
Well, this is it.
It's better to turn this pumpkin upside down.
Hmm?
Wait a minute, there's a lot of rule books.
that's why
Ne-senpai is in debt, so let's go here.
go home
or here
Something delicious right now
Hmm, I have to give this back.
I can't take it. Wait a minute.
Well then, read it and return it. I have money.
gold
No, this is Sol Shiba's house. I read it. I read it.
This is a house
I thought he was in a hurry and didn't know anything about it.
Tarae family
I already know
It's English
Can you return this to me?
Hey, wait a minute, Diamond.
I hope you can recover anything
It was distorted when Fuchichi's Chichinori was formed.
Mushroom Hohou
You are free to make your own
You can go to Mononie Glowstone.
This is Ano's signboard glow stone
You can definitely go
Let's go to Glowstone. I feel like we can go.
Let's go to the Nether.
death
Negust is like that without a bow, so a bow?
Can something be fixed?
Cloth Tone needs Silk Touch
Is it glow stone silk touch?
Okay, let's do Silk Touch first.
some food for a while
Please collect the food once.
How about making a diamond Tsuruha?
I made a diamond trumpet
Tede
Um, enchanted silk touch.
That's what it means
Hey, we can have sex, no, definitely.
You can use your sword to bounce back from the ghast days.
That's right
Wait a minute, let's start with the diamond.
Pickaxe
Silk touch seems to exist Silk touch is
I found it earlier, but I still have 7 diamonds.
From this
I can do it if I try, wait for this, this is a diary, right?
That's what that guy over there is doing.
what
Let's go over there, go to the attack base.
Just go to the attack point and do it.
So I'm going to sleep like this here and spend the night
and here
First, make a diamond tsuruha
And made a diamond vine
Ah, I have to make a stick. Make a stick.
Turn it into a Tsuruha
Here comes Tsuruha and the enchantment book
Go and collect it
This is the Tedegozaru
go here
This place is definitely an attack point, right?
I received a really nice baggage rack.
Lever
Place
First of all, there are 5 books about Tekusig and the others.
Book
There is a heroo heroo
Hello Diamond, I see so much here.
iron iron
Gae iron
Or this?
Oh, I see. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
It's dangerous, my brain is confused, first of all, silk.
Because of Touch, there are 5 emerald books.
Oh, my senpai says there are 5 books, yes that color.
Chan's Silk Touch
You can get a lot for free
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Is there a difference between that and another?
Chan also made a place like this, and there
I already got that silk touch in the box for free.
Please, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, please.
where
Well, let's go home.
Go me
TR There are many other things besides that, wait.
When I got home, where was the sill that was being distributed for free?
Wait a minute
It seems so
If it's not distributed, it's serious, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ah, uh, uh, I understand. I don't know the direction.
It's going to disappear, right?
What does "mending" mean in Japanese?
I can fix that with mending.
It's about repairs, yes, that's also true.
That's it
Yes, yes, yes, wait a minute
Look at that screenshot
Coordination A14 Bonds and anything
be
Subaru is also a difficult guy who came out with 140.
That's so difficult
negative minus
100 sorry sorry mana 140
Where are you? Go home.
I understand that feeling, Subaru too, now.
I'll take a look, I'll take a look.
What is it?
If it's a minor 140, it's probably a minor 140.
Well, no, but that's what Chat said just now.
I don't know if that's correct or not.
Oh, I see.
-140 and ma
420 I can't believe it
But is it true that it's minus 140?
40e
4204120420 Oh, but it's true
That's right, that's right, I remember, I remember
There's something right over there.
Octopus
It looks like they're giving it away for free from now on.
I guess everyone doesn't know, I definitely don't know
If you see it being given away for free, you'll lose your temper.
absolute
You can tell me, I'll give it away for free when I get home.
Apparently
enchant this
I'm still in the back, around here.
Oh
Here, here, here, I wonder if that's what happened once.
Somewhere?
Nado
I'm sure something happened around here.
I feel like I can see it, I can see it, I can see it
I saw it. It was near the tree.
Oh yeah here
I see.
That's right
[music]
There is also a waa-chan who is reading.
Nanamo get free enchantment here
Subaru, this is really take-free.
too much
[applause]
This is too bad
Even if it's gone, it might come again
Maybe I'll come again
Is there anything else you want? Repairs
Just a moment, is it okay if I get this book?
It would be nice to receive something like Najahon 5.
Seriously?
Say it's okay
This is how it is
That's it
oh
Subaru Subaru let's make it Alex
It's Ax, Alex
Ax ax oh, it's scary, it's scary.
It was done
Nice, it's a little scary now in the comment section
I found something really scary, I should resell it.
Jan
It's so scary here Minecraft's hair
It seems like it's going to be sold, right? No, it's resale.
It's a good thing, it's a good thing
It's not good.
yeah
I had a crazy listener. I'm in a crazy head right now.
good
Genius, there it is
[music]
Durability
I want it, I want more drops. Excuse me for leaving.
I will
Oh no, wait a minute
Even though it's a free take, it's still a take.
Even though it's take-free, it's Maa-chan.
It's okay, it's like that.
Too bad
It's locked in
That's terrible, that's not enough
emerald
[applause]
is emerald
Yeah, I don't have enough emeralds.
But
Well, I'll go collect some emeralds.
Na
Thank you God, I think I'll go back there.
Thank you very much
It's close, it's not close, it's not close, it's not close, it's not close
No, maybe emeralds, but that's it.
You can get that ABC attack over there.
with iron in place
Can we get a lot of iron out there?
There's a place where you can get it, right now.
It's empty, isn't it?
I have a little bit of iron.
Shall I give you something? I want something like this.
When making TTT, I collected various things.
When I collected dead people, the number increased.
Wait a minute, do this now.
I started it today so I'll do a little digging.
I thought so and dug and collected iron, but
Wait a minute, this doesn't have any direction.
I guess I should just go back to zero zero now.
I see.170
I'm going from 175 to 63.
Oh, I'll follow you next time.
It's a bit in line with what Senpai is thinking.
terrible
at 175
60 different
It's here, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's here.
Here, here, here
Oh, this is different
It's different
This way, right?
What is this?
It's this way
Is this true?
It's over here, over here now.
Good to see
Don't worry, the numbers are over!
[music]
It's really difficult. It's really hard.
It's really difficult to play with the iron a little bit.
Oh, wait a minute, now here.
I'll hand over the iron.Here you go.
Hey please thank you Wow seriously
No, seriously, thank you. Originally with that TTT.
I took it with me somewhere, so it's a big deal.
Thank you very much
[music]
Neaah
Wow, this is the first time I've seen the ABCs
Now you can turn iron into emerald.
Daoi
Are you sleeping here?
Wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up
Yeah, it's emerald
where
What put this guy to bed and why is he waking him up now?
I'm awake, but emeralds aren't for sale right now.
I'm not selling this person's house right now.
All
The saw that I took
That's why I don't sell emeralds.
I guess I'll have to wait a little while.
I have to wait, where is that?
Where are you hitting Emerald Eko?
I think the two of them and, uh, this guy were hitting it too.
I wonder if the two people on the right and these people are selling it first.
Did you buy it?
Really true
Wait, wait, wait
yes
Yes, this, this, this, which one?
Thank you for giving me one diamond.
I'm Fuyu, I forgive everything. I forgive everything.
Thank you, just a little while
Yeah, that's going to come back, yeah, let's do that.
I'm sorry, I've always called Subarkia Kara.
The book that seemed to be calling me I understood the whole time on my way home
's return has been running through my mind for a long time.
I know you're back, I understand, I understand, Chiara.
Sorry, I also call myself home sometimes.
That's definitely not the case
By the way, I lied today.
Hasakiara, what are you doing, especially that much?
It's not decided yet.
I want to go. Thank you for your hard work, Mikochi.
Is it okay with Yasako's equipment? That's for sure.
I think it's dangerous. Am I dangerous too? No, a.
Why did my whole body go off when I started?
Even Subaru wants to make money with Nether Monsters.
But hey, hey!
Rival Iya Mikokoresa Nezashii together
Let's find it and pile it up. Divide it into piles.
I'm going to kill all the gusts while I'm at it.
I'm sure everyone will divide the pile.
Let's do it. By the way, there's one.
If I defeat it, that's right, maybe one person.
I'd like a team like the one I want to defeat.
Or something like that, all together
Even if I clear the mission and walk away
It's okay, this is probably not good at all
If you wait and find it, it will be 30330
Isn't it 150 for 30330?
That's not true. Isn't that bad? It's poisonous.
Please leave it to me, but I'm good at begging.
That's why I've been living on words, I've been living on words
Since it's here, Subaru also made it yesterday.
I rolled it up, and by the way, I'm sure it's okay.
Everyone who can play a little or play a little.
30 Eh, it doesn't say there's only one person.
In other words, we are one team.
Can you get 50 yen from the snow gathering?
It's been too long
But snow is snow
Momo Yuki is also going
Let's go snow, let's go snow, let's go snow
Snow is like snow, so it's okay.
It's a little dangerous. It's a little dangerous. Snow genius.
Well then, I'll wait a little while and go back to sleep.
For now, 1 time 1 time 1
After all, when I say I'm staying over, I talk about it.
Let's do that. What if I get 30 yen?
Let's talk about what we'll do to repay our debts
It's already been decided, right? I'm going to pay off my debt. I'm going to pay off my debt.
That's right, I got zero plastic yesterday.
A little surprising
I'm picking up Toa
[ __ ], don't sell it yet.
Well, we haven't won right now, we haven't won.
Okay, look at me, I'll go get some stones.
I also brought some stones to observe the age.
Wrapped
Round stones, I'll give you round stones. Oh, wait a minute.
I didn't have enough round stones to last me.
Wait a minute, I have a lot at home too.
I'm digging it a lot, so I'm sure it's there.
That's what I thought, but the round stone looks like Subaru
It's just my imagination that I feel like I was holding it like garbage
I guess I ended up using it.
I also have a lot of cobblestones at home.
It's really closed over there.
It's my own place, so make fun of me
I can't let you get caught here
It's a Subaru because everything is included.
That's how I use it; all I have is a diary.
That's a lie
I'm keeping it at home with Shoko-chan.
I see, I also have a Nema Subaru at home.
Wait a minute, there's something Subaru at home.
It looks like my senior's half block, so it's from my house.
Should I go get it? Stop, stop, stop.
What is that, half block roku?
Haha, this is a book, right? Wait a minute.
I'm sure there's more. I'm going to Ayacho's house.
Right here
Yes, there are quite a few, but not that many.
say
I wonder how long there will be Hodoe3
Stack Asenkyu Yes this is cobblestone
Is 64 enough? No, just a little more.
I don't have it, I might really need it.
To be honest, today's mission is difficult.
That's enough for Subaru, I can give it to you.
This is about it. There are still more if you change it.
Yo
I'm not sure if it's mine, so I'll bring it with me just in case.
Well, I guess I should bring my blue one too.
It feels good, I understand. I huff for a moment.
Shouldn't Miku be huffing too Subaru?
No-chan, let's go, no-chan, just like that.
I just took a quick look, I was too scared.
But it was too crazy, everyone.
Everyone explores defeating enemies in the Nether.
I found the exploration fortress for 30 diamonds.
I'm sure the diamond is clear and everyone will find it.
If I say I got it, I wonder if I can get everyone?
This is definitely true, the first discoverer is 30.
Noani-senpai disappeared, what happened to Noani? Where is he?
Where are you talking about?
It's the first house, everyone is in the Nether
Don't dig like that if you've been there.
So let's get the diamond.
I went because I already passed something.
It's like I'm like, yeah, yeah, this is me.
It's scary having to paste it.
Well, today, the diamond equipment is a little protective.
Where is the spa-chan Miko equipped today?
Come on, let me lend you some diamonds.
I have one. Should I lend it to you? Is that okay?
I can't lend it to you for free, sorry, but what are the conditions?
I can't lend it to you for free, but now
Do you have 5 diamonds? Yes, this is it.
It's already the final diamond, isn't it?
Fire is the last final fire
Hey me final
Firefox is this, so it's ok
There's a little bit of interest involved, but that's okay.
But if you say it's okay
I got 5 of them, but now I have 1.
That's right, the one thing I found was a little
Do you want to make equipment? I made equipment, right?
Sure.
Okay then, Lissy is fine.
How much does Chinami look like?
Well, even if it's just for one day, Subaru today is an hour.
I dug it up and found about 10 pieces.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
If I try hard for one day, I'll probably get about 10 pieces.
I can't take it, I'll definitely give it to you.
1 and 1 and 1
and 1 and
That's right, what's wrong with the moon? It's blue, isn't it?
I don't think there's anyone here who can go there alone.
I'm so sorry that I might have gone tomorrow.
Unina-chan also joins us in that Nether.
Oh, let's go, let's go, okay, okay.
Let's go okay okay okay
Okay, Hina-chan, maybe go back home.
Just a little bit because
Thank you for having this
Thank you, Senkyuo, its okay Miko-senpai.
Subaru-senpai isn't being bullied at all, no no.
Maybe Miko isn't right. Ani-san, I'm going to lend it to you now.
Let's lend it to Nemikochinami.
About how much
About
No, now Miko, by the way, that unknown person.
It's in a hard state, by the way.
The core is experienced people, so yeah yeah
I think my dependable cat will survive.
Well, I don't know when it will be in the next 4 days.
Well then, is it okay? It lasted all day.
Ajakore
Ready to go home
Tamo welcome home
Here, here, here, here, here
Let's go to Watanabe too, okay?
Mikorea Senkyu Senkyu
thank you
Thank you, don't die
You're an experienced person, you're an experienced person.
It has become
How did you get so excited about this guy who rolled up?
I'm thinking maybe I should make a joke of it.
Shall I put it in there? You're rolling it up. You're rolling it up.
As a dog, it's really that tough.
This girl is Zapecola's dog now.
Is it too harsh or did you just come and tell me? It's okay.
This is where Pecola told me to roll up.
If you want to join the baseball team, it's like that.
It's like Maruno doesn't play baseball.
Wait a minute, it's okay to be evil.
Wait a minute
[music]
point
No, it's cute, no, it's impossible.
I guess he has a nice face, but he's not a shaved head.
Because it's teasing
Everyone is nice
It's nice here
How did you come to the corner?
Let's go out, everyone.
So how are you doing?
Ukai how did you do it?
voice hat
If you remove the skin from Nosusu's hat, it will look like this
Different different settings
Maybe it's Minecraft's Setsui Chamaru.
It's not rounded, it's rounded
Let's all curl up. Maybe this is also true.
Just a little
[applause]
What did you do? How did you do it?
What happened to that setting?
[music]
customization
from
a little bit
Da-chan black hair is really Gerardon-san
I want to
Masu
Yo-san, I'm going.
I'm going to Zaza
What is this a option option baby
Looks like I'm the only one who's getting tired
Tel
That's scary, but wait a minute.
attitude
Well, it's a little after all.
After all, this is that.
Karami-chan and Mi-chan, do it now too.
I'm risking my life, Nezha.
Amazing baby baby baby too
Kaikai
Well, everyone, take a group photo, take a group photo, get together.
By the time the photo comes back, the photographer is gone.
There is a possibility that this will be the last gathering.
There is a possibility that it will become a photo. I am the only one with bangs.
I don't want it to happen in the future.
Jandao
Ote wait wait wait wait
hand
[music]
This might be the last time. I wonder if this is the last time.
I can't do it because I've been waiting for a while
It's like I'm looking at you somehow
Teruo's name is included
Teru
It's too much, let's all go to Koen.
Let's go to the kindergarten, let's do our best, my summer Koshien
let's go
Well, I don't know where to go, so I walk.
[music]
Oh, wait, what's going on? Anji-san, Ina is coming.
Wasn't it? Oh yeah, I'm coming.
Ina is coming, Ina-chan is coming too, Ina is coming.
Why don't you go ahead and make your senior feel bad?
What should I do here? What should I do now?
I'm going to go to Nezha now and explore.
I'm going to explore, I'm going to search for a fortress.
It seems they haven't found it yet, so let's all take a look.
If we all did that, we could all become the first people.
That's right. I didn't write "only one person" here.
Look, it's not
Why don't you stop that dog? Come over here.
I don't have work at the moment either so it's a bit
Is it okay if I interrupt you?
It's a big deal, so everyone's eja
Sakoko, everyone, saano
Dadaya, if I get two more, I'll get a plate too.
You can get it. There is definitely something.
Just to be sure
I don't care if my senior doesn't come to chat.
That's not it. Good morning.
Good morning, wait a moment
The mission is real.Create a potion.
Make a potion, watch the bed once and see the ad
Please give me one day. Please give me one day.
Oh no, I'm out of diamonds
What are you going to use that equipment for?
I thought it might be a bit like that, so Tsuma-chan
I got 6 diamonds and now I have 1 more.
Nate got it
I can go to Mario Gili from 11pm.
Minecraft, time flies in the blink of an eye
I'm going to go there, but it's just before 11pm.
Is it possible to go?
I'm sorry, No-chan, No-chan, I can go.
I wonder if he'll come or not. No one has Daigo.
What happened? Why, I only have one piece of equipment left.
I can make it.What equipment can I use with this diamond?
It's a plate, so it's a bit weird if it's a plate.
Hey here
Hihihi thank you, how do you laugh?
I'm sleeping too, but Su and Suru also followed me a while ago.
I took it
It's true, it's just one. That's so sweet.
That's true, isn't it? One more thing is true. It's true.
Yo, there are seven now, so there are seven.
Well, that's it, Omiko, starting today.
Yeah, yeah, then from today onwards, we'll get back to it.
That's right, grow up and repay the favor. That's enough.
I wonder if Mama, Suba-chan, and Noel are there.
He's such a good boy
Yaaaa, that's Suwa-chan's tele-tele
Noel is a good boy
[music]
No, I didn't have that kind of heart.
Zasu Subaru now has 128 debts.
If you have money, you can say it's dangerous, men and women
I want to take your place.
I learned a lot about whether it's serious or not.
It's okay
You're learning so well. Also, we're similar.
Just take the food.
[music]
I came here
No, someone has too much food.
I just want to get some food
Let's go, 13 might not be enough.
There is
Take a little more
I wonder if I can find the Nether, but this number of people
Then, absolutely, absolutely, why would I die?
Probably scary
Scary
I feel like Yomo will somehow survive.
But I'm not dead yet.
Can I get you some food?
What if it's just the Survey Corps?
Let's try and fall into magma
yes
Wow, I'm getting scared
That's the polka from earlier.
die in the nether
People's polka was an accident.
I wonder if everyone has already left.
I'm going
Ah, I'm going to the Nether. No, not the Nether.
No, it's not the Nether, it's the Nether.
I can go even if I don't want to go soon.
I can do it, I'll do it. It's better to take it in TT.
Look, it might even be possible without a bow.
I don't even have a bow, I have a sword.
Big
It's okay, it's okay
Good job, what's going on when you come back?
Right?
Oh my god, are you seriously going to tree at that distance?
open your eyes and look closely
This is definitely something like Kaname's
No, it's okay to look at this.
I'm sure your head hasn't turned into a blue pumpkin.
Even if I meet that guy's eyes when I'm wearing this,
Hey, what are you looking at?
I'm sure, but Anya-san is no good, Anya.
When you look at it, it's like, oh yeah, I'm a pumpkin right now.
Why is everyone facing the ground?
What are you doing? It's dangerous. It's dangerous.
Let's go
[music]
The go bed is scary so I'll leave it there.
What is this?
is
I think someone who has something good can use this strategy.
Should I leave some supplies or gunpowder?
The popi holder I received from Nana-chan
Let's go, let's go.
let's go let's go let's go
There are too many people so I can't go let's go.
Let's go Let's go
It's too much, let's go in order, order in order, Mr.
Go ahead, let's go let's
Let's go, wait.
That's bad
Block: Oh, this is dangerous. I thought it was a fire.
It was a half block, so leave everything behind.
The shitty Senkyu comment section is seriously dangerous.
in
Mamoto
That's it
This is a really helpful bed.
trap
Yarokocchi? Sankokga
You can go from here
Yes, then which way should I go first?
What's going on here hasn't been fully explored yet?
However, this is definitely a good thing.
It's scary, everything is a wall, it's scary here, press
Please don't push me and go. Too many people.
Sugimokocchi is really exploring
Well then, dig in the opposite direction or go up.
I'll dig here, here, or there.
What's wrong? Gust's voice is so loud.
It's hot if I don't kill it, and I'm sure I'll kill the gust.
Because it becomes a tire, Gust's voice is so loud
But somehow
I went inside and did one row, and I loaded everything too.
Miko-senpai will help Miko do her best, Matsu.
I asked Matsu to do his best.Yes, Matsu is coming.
Please help me, wait, Mi is the least equipped.
But it's okay
Anyway, my feet are fine.
I've got money, that's the entrance
What kind of entrance is that? That's a lot of magma.
make a sound
Where is my fortress?
What kind of road is that?
That's different, isn't it? That's different, isn't it?
Yes, this is different, isn't it?
No, no, no, it's like a different Rega.
It's like a brick. I understand, I understand.
Don't be scared, magma won't fall so it's okay Kanami
My senior is Hosbal, and my senior is playing Matsu.
Oh no, no, no, no, stop.
Pupup dangerous stop stop stop
Stop, I'll make a road. Okay, that's good.
It's a good word game, this is that shift shift.
Goshi Button Shift Let's Go Shift
Let's Go Shift Button Let's Go Shift
Button Push Let's Go Let's Go Dangerous
It's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous
Senkyu is saved, saved, Senkyu is in danger
Dangerous
Dangerous please dangerous
Dangerous Dangerous
Jealous message game
The only job I have is to talk about bad games.
What should I do? I have to do something.
I'm dancing. It's a help. It's a help. I'll collect this.
Collect it and let it go. Oh wait, it's a pig.
Hear my voice, what? Pink pick pick danger
pic deja pic deja pic deja
Japikja
Piku Piku Ja Pig Dangerous
Big Holbig opened the pick.
Hol Big Hole Big Hole
let's go let's go
shift shift shift let's
Goshi Goshi
[music]
Schiff, wait a minute, if you don't press gold equipment, it's gold.
It's okay gold equipment go go
Glow Stone Hey Glow Stone
There was something I wanted to get, Glow.
Stone Ru Glow Stone Ah on top
Is that dangerous? That's a bit gross.
Is that what it is?
That's all I can do, even if it's just a little bit.
I'm trying my best to figure out what's going on.
Is the one in front of me a pickney?
Nino's Fortress Jump Pick Ninoe
That's it.
Let's get this fortress point.
Would you like to have it?
I saw this point, even Pikmin.
I wonder if it's okay to use it as a fortress. Make this place really strong.
Awesome
If you rub this too, I think you'll get something out of it.
Isn't it Sayabess? This is also some kind of photo.
If you do, I'll definitely take a screenshot.
Let's all be together, let's all be together, everyone
So we all saw it, so we all took a photo.
Let's Go Photo Let's
I saw the goal
Even if it's just a matter of time, it might cost you money and space later.
If you understand
There are some really good ones too, that [ __ ] over there.
I wonder if I can go to Stone?
Looks like it's a little higher up
But it feels a little dangerous, I'm sure.
You can go to Nima.
You were Pecola's dog just now, weren't you?
Tell me it's okay to try it now or at all.
I understand that you can look at it.
It makes me sleepy
This too
I said, ``I haven't heard of a fortress.''
Well, I'm pretty sure I haven't heard of the type of fortress.
I find a lot of poisonous things one by one.
It's 30, so one person definitely has 3 cars.
Looks like it's going to go a little further
I want to go to the other side where I want to kill Gust.
Gusto Madoka is a bit scary as expected.
That's the one on the left, that's the one on the left.
It's close, let's go to the left, let's take the left glow
I'll get a stone diamond, so there's a hole at the top.
So be careful everyone.
Hey, do your best to fill in the stone holes, Senpai.
If this happens, it's going to be dangerous here, too much of a trap.
Falling senkyu is good
Na
It's okay, let's go
Why are you so scared? Come across!
I'm not scared, I'm not scared.
There's no one like that
I'm going to push Miko with the trick that scares me the most
But it's really scary.
It's dangerous, it's dangerous, I'm afraid to press it.
I'm the one who says
It's too gross over there, but it's red.
It's kind of a block book.
Red mushrooms are too expensive or distorted.
I should have gotten a diamond, but a distorted mushroom too
That's a kino with distorted red mushrooms.
The red elephant isn't careful, it's dangerous.
Right?
That's right, the red mushroom slightly above is distorted.
Is it Kino? It wasn't a distorted Kino.
Kino is blue, are you going to abandon him and go to high school?
Listen, you're ignoring me, you're ignoring me, you're ignoring me.
I was shocked when I called it a sudden blue that wasn't there.
Are you able to afford it?
I've checked it properly
Is it okay to collect blocks in this area where I die?
scary scary
Naa Mikochi is one-chan Miko is always the only one
Did you go upstairs? Someone went up.
I have it, so I can go with it.Here, this is it.
I'll collect it and go up, I see, I'll go up, red
Going to the forest
Collect the glow stones.
Maybe it's given to me
oh
Nmichido
Those four glow stones become one.
Masu
Don't die from the soldering, thank you very much
That's amazing
[music]
It's okay and here's a glow stone
Thank you very much
4 things
But Naruyokimasu Le Touch wasn't there.
I wonder if I can go if I get the raw stone
It's only written that way, so make it that way.
It's okay, just bring it back in powder form.
So I just need to make a block.
Well, maybe I can make it now.
O
I'll go and see if I can climb it.
I also need sole sand Sole sand ah
The food I came here is amazing, I can make it with great feeling.
Please make it.Yes, yes, I will take it.
Does that mean I can go? I'm going to go get Mito Sanato.
Does that mean it's even better than this?
4 things you can make on hand
I was able to pick up something that was falling.This is this.This is this.
That's what it's like. It's raining.
Yes, there are, I think I have 15 of them.
It's done, it's done, it's done
People who don't have a Glostone
I want to make it Ina Glowston Okay
Yes, I'll give you this.
It's alright, it's a certain glow
It's a bit of a waste.
So is this okay for everyone?
It's okay, everyone got it, everyone got it.
I also need chimuah sole sand.
Speaking of easy things, Lund is fine.
[applause]
Where did it come from?
I'm alive I'm alive I'm alive I'm alive
I forgot that the thing that fell off was bent.
Ge
[laughter]
What if my life wasn't made of diamonds?
He was dead. Even though I made a dangerous diamond, I recovered it.
I think it would be better to have this and that, Miko-chan.
It is better to have
If this is that bad, drink it.
Please, have a drink. Let's move on.
Hey, right? It's better to go through this red forest.
It might be good, red.
Even if you cut the red forest, it's still magma
It's dangerous, this side is fine, the right side
It's right, it's safe.
Oh, right side, right here?
I'm going
Is it safe?
What did I say? What's the truth? This is the right place.
There isn't one
Left, it's okay, right and left, it's red.
This way
Let's go here, let's go, let's go
Well, it's impossible, but what is the Red Forest?
It may be true that people will definitely die.
I can't beat Eino.
I think you can defeat it while watching, everyone.
The only way to do it is
hey
Oh no, wait a minute, Ina, what is Ina fighting?
I'm fighting with you because you're a mushroom in the sink.
We're fighting a different kind of war, the distorted mushroom is the green one.
It's okay, it's over there. Is it true?
It's true, it's a blue mushroom, let's go, let's go
It's true, it's better to pick up those things as you grow your path.
That's right
I'm sure it will make money
I'm going to stretch it out, you're stretching me out.
I'd like to connect them, but if I make stairs there
Maybe it's okay, let's make these stairs here.
Maybe it would be nice to go over here.
Yes, but no, Kamidori is over there.
That's right, that's right.
The pigs are really strong, so I'm going to put them here as well.
I'm going to make a pig. It's true that there's a pig.
There's a really wild boar, it's scary!
From here
It might be better to go from here.
There's a stage, there's a stage, there's a stage
I have a pretty strong pig and a bow.
Then I, wait a minute, Ina cleans up a lot.
I'm sorry, God, I'm sorry.
stomach
Nae
There's some lag right now. Maybe it's me.
I don't want to get shot again and again due to the lag when I throw it.
Wait a moment, I'm here.
Wobbly
Gura lag is alive, it's alive, it's a little lag
The rag that is stuck in the rug's butt.
Rag lag rag rag, you did it, A-senpai.
Maybe what I just did was a lag.It's a lag.
this
Don't press the lag, don't press the button that will kill you
Don't press it and let it fall, please wait a moment.
Yes, I did it very quickly.
It's too dangerous
The top of the floor will turn into magma.
This is scary
Scary green mushrooms over there
discovery
Wow, I'll be that damn pig next time.
I'll kill you
Okay, that's not true. Wait a minute.
I'm too scared of Ina being alone downstairs.
If I do this, I won't get it right.I got it right.
Hit
I'm coming down, I'm going there.
I can win
I can get off here for a bit.
Karahasa-san is waiting for you
It stinks, okay, okay, okay, okay here.
What should I do? It's all over there.
There's one green mushroom, it's over there.
There's one over there, it's true.
I have to collect enough for everyone.
Can we go up this tree?
I can go from here as you stretch out.
Where is everyone? Wait, I hear Gust's voice, I'll kill you.
Do you want to kill Gust? Gust's voice
One ghast for all
Is it enough to just kill them? But how many bodies should I write for each person?
That's because I don't have it.
If you can go to Chan, it seems that one body at a time is enough.
Hey, just one is enough
It's okay to defeat it
Kamikochi is scary, Subaru is scary too, who is he?
The one who said we should go to the red forest, Aqua.
aqua
So, if you connect it with a mushroom, it becomes a mushroom.
I see.
If you want to pick mushrooms, just pick some mushrooms.
Leave it to me and I'll go.
I'll connect it with the mushroom and get it.
bread
Hishiya
I'll wait until I come back blue
It's okay
the best
top position
Kunekore Satsuki, can you cut straight through this?
It's pretty red, it's red all the time, it's a mushroom.
I have no choice but to go slowly as I pass by.
There's one more. Another one is stopping.
The cat's life is too light, don't jump.
It's dangerous
No, this is not the way to get to the Nether.
is
I'm grateful to my seniors for their hard work.
So please give it to Pico.
I'll give it to you, let's run away to our senior.
Thank you. I'm a little scared.
I'll drop it somewhere.If I drop it, it's already there.
I have to pick it up once. I'm a little scared here.
There was one more Nitsuge Tokuka.
It's okay, but the magma around here is pretty dangerous.
I want a little more depth.5
5 It's better not to do this. 5
Oh it's there too It's better not to be there
There was one in there too, so I'll go get some.
So I'm going to go get it with the glue I want to use.
It's not a place you can go to like that.
I'm glad to see that momentum here.
There's still a long way to go
Yeah, it might still be a forest.
The sound of something like that is scary
But
Right, it's okay, blue, blue, blue. Is it okay?
It's okay, Ao-kun, you fell. Well, Ao-kun fell.
No, I'm still there, I'm going home
What are you going to tell me when you're back?
Hmm, pork pig, this is so straight forward
It's probably better to just go through with it and ask for something like that.
I feel like it
I'll hit you straight here once, straight again
It's better to go and cross it.
No, okay, it's straight this way.
I think it would be good to build a fortress.
Is there a fortress to find first?
Believe me there is
What kind of place is the fortress near?
It's hard to find one nearby.
That's right, what's that pillar scary?
The voice of the shifter detours, that's helpful.
I'm saved, but there's a wall over there, and the wall came again.
It's almost here
Yo everyone okay?
It's coming!
Please follow me and rely on me
I'm sure it's Naru Kinoko's first day.
Isn't that what you do on your first day?
What to do on the first day
No, it's okay, it's good, it's good, I think I'll go
There's no sole sand, soul sand.
A certain soul sand was subject to collection.
It's not just that, but it's in quite a lot of places.
TT Tower elevator and water flow
The elevator is definitely okay.
Everyone come
Should I put out the fire or should I put out the fire?
Just barely enough distance
Hey, oh, that's the time to turn on the timer.
I'm not sure if I'll be able to go home properly.
Is there anyone who has the coordinates? It's okay, but
I'm sure I can go because I took a screenshot.
As expected, I forgot about Miko-chan.
Sorry, I've been called around here for a while.
It's gone, so I'm going. Atan, I'll come over.
Tene dog
Please do your best with the fortress I entrusted to you.
Please go look for me, don't die.
The little finger that is shifting is dangerous, a little bit of a step back
The fishing is going to be amazing, please do your best.
Please do your best, it's fragile.
Takinoko-san, it's okay, I don't need it, it's okay
Ah, mushrooms, are you okay? Are you okay?
Please do your best and do your best.
Apparently it's a dog. He's a dog.
Hey, pig. I heard the pig is on the bridge.
It's okay, I'll kill you, I'll kill you, I'll kill you.
Kill, kill, kill, die
Thank you for that. That's crazy.
As a senior, I think it's okay to have as many sole sandwiches as you like.
Why should I get soul sand?
Maybe, what is the mission target?
The mission target is soul sand
Yes, that's right, there's only one.
It's okay to collect just1
It's scary because it wasn't bad.
It's dangerous, you fall so boldly
I'm worried that it's too much, but I don't want to die today.
Who is going to die today? What's going on?
Predictions about who will die today
hey
Even if you take as much as you want, blue won't die unexpectedly.
I think
Looks like there will be some left
It's okay now
Right?
Most of the Kentaippu
At the end, wait a minute, I was surprised.
Make a water flow elevator with this
If you do, you will get points for making it more convenient.
That's right
Sorry, there's a wild boar, hurry up!
Let's go home. It's okay. We'll all go.
Ah, where are you going?
Mani, are you okay? Mom, are you okay? Are you okay?
[laughter]
It's totally fine. I'm here.
Oh, let's go. It looks really open.
Don't pick it up
Wow that's amazing
Tokoyabe, go up!
It's scary, but the back is less scary.
Well, on the contrary, the situation is better at the back.
I don't know and I'm scared, wait, wait, I'm scared
Seriously scary Seriously scary By the way, what?
but
Yes, Rusomi is really scary.
of
Intuitively, the magma above is falling.
If you think about it, the land over there is a little curved.
is green song
What's going on? The soil over there is a little green.
I guess that's it, green, red terrain and green.
There was a terrain that looked green. Green terrain is no good.
What's this? It's not even in the green area.
So you really should avoid this area.
I see
It's red, it's a little close, close, close, it's important.
It's important, it's important, I'm sure I'll close it.
Open the large windows a little.
Kamada is important
I hope the cats and mushrooms are also included.
It's okay, it's okay, I was waiting for Bar-senpai.
Thank you for that.
Okay, this is a pig in my stomach, yes, in the back.
No, what's so scary about not looking behind me?
There's a senior behind me, a senior, and I ended up using that iron.
I thought I changed the emerald, but I didn't change it.
Go home, everyone has gone.
[laughter]
I don't like it, which means the buff is gone.
No, that's right, it's gone.
Yo
What do you think, what do you think?
Should be
Noiko left red forest
Even if I go straight, there won't be anything.
No, it's scary
Probably not, but it's a little far away.
No, I can't see the future, so I'm not going.
In that case, it would be better to go left and go straight.
You can definitely see something on the left side once.
Well, if you have the courage, just go straight
My pinky finger is holding my pinky finger
I'm sure you're holding it down with your little finger.
I'll take a look at the half block.
Okay, then we'll all go.
I think it's going to happen, Miko.
Yeah, if you say that, I'll follow you.
When you die
We're in Dangerous Bridge together.
Dangerous Bridge is nothing at all.
No, no, I'm going home.
Return return, go home, there's no Talita
So, shall I go left? The tip of the left is a little
I can see the shadow, so there's a forest here
There's something just beyond that forest.
That person on the right probably has the forest on his back.
If you go straight, there's a shadow that looks like there's something there
It looks like there's something real on the other side
Maybe there is, go there.
I'm sorry, wait a minute.
Let's prepare the block Mikochi block
There are quite a few out there now, I'm digging around.
Are you sure you're digging over there?
I just don't know the way home, I already know the way home
Let's follow this
Looks like I have no choice but to look away
I'll leave this behind.
Also, I can usually get home without getting lost.
Eh, blue is seriously strong on terrain, it's strong, super
It's so intense, I don't want it, it's serious, it's serious
Blue is blue after all, it's really blue
It's amazing, so please change my personality a little bit.
Please leave it to me, don't leave it to me.
Take a break, take a break, take a break, do this, do this, do this, do this
I hear the voice of Koei Gust, but it's not there.
That's right, it's about time we have to fight.
Maybe it's coming, so be prepared
Maybe I'm not good at reading stairs.
I wonder if I went out. I'm scared of pigs.
Hey pig, open it up a little or open up here.
Is there anything to be afraid of?
Oh wrong
Let's open it. Come on. Come on.
Hey, be scared
Understood, it's near Glowstone.
But when Green Kino was discovered, Ao-Mori said that green was enough.
Looks like we'll have to have one mushroom per person.
That's right, I only have 4 of them yet.
They are working hard to collect them.
Isn't the mushroom far away?
It's far. This may be a bit far.
Let's wait a moment and take a look.Here we are.
Gather for that red man who isn't there yet.
It's not likely, it's scary, scary, scary.
Scary, so likely, so likely
5 How many people are here now?
Eh, 7 is better, then 3.
There shouldn't be any, so if you find 5 of them, you'll definitely be there.
Are you okay
Very top
Pig Pig Pig that hadn't made any strange noises until now.
Hold on, the pig is making noises, the pig is making noises, the pig is making noises
The pig is singing, the pig is singing, the pig is singing
Pok pok small one pok is dangerous pok
absolute
Hey wait, I'm shooting something, I'm shooting something
Yo
I'm so glad you found it so well!
Nice, nice, I died waiting for you.
dead
or die
is
[music]
Death is too close to home here.
is short
Let's come home properly
Go home properly
Let's pig, ...
It's coming
Wait a minute, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous
dead dead dead dead open
Death confirmation confirmation confirmation I thought I was going to die
[music]
live well, live well
Terumada
I don't know if he's alive, but he's alive.
I got really scared.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay
That's great, who?
[music]
Better
Ta
It's so serious
vinegar
It was too much Magic Panic.
There are quite a lot of them, so it's true that there are a lot of them.
It's amazing that I'm still alive for some reason, even though there are so many of them.
I'm glad to be alive, I'm glad to be alive
This is like an infinite bow. I want one, infinitely.
I can shoot it. I want a bow. I have an infinite bow.
It's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's a dangerous bow
What do I have: Chiara, Ina, and I?
I also have a lot of bows.
What should I do with it? Is the magma broken?
It's just a dream, but there's another magma here
Magma Bear and Hey Magma
This place seems like a danger zone
Danger Zone Danger Zone Danger
I'm going straight to the zone Miko Kaede
You can go straight
Yes, if there is a block, I can do it.
There are blocks, there are blocks, oh Subaru
Shall we take the road? It's a little late here.
If your bow and arrow is a little broken, there is another one available.
It's even better because I actually have a sword.
That's right, when you're dead it's already time to die.
I'm sure it's already Gusto's time.
It would be better to give it to him at that dangerous time.
When the time comes, it's time for me to gust.
Maybe all I can do is run away
Maybe all I can do is throw back the fire
No, if I could hit back the fire, I would be strong and perfect.
It's going to be dangerous if you come here.
It's definitely dangerous if you come in here.
kara nice nice
Thank you, thank you, thank you very much.
Thank you!
Before I knew it, I was in Netherrack.
It's getting crowded now
Hey, it's okay, you won't get lost.
Hey, I remember a little bit of this too.
and
I keep saying no, but I somehow understand.
Hey, it's probably okay. I guess things will turn out okay.
Somehow, somehow, it seems to be true.
I might be a little worried about the fortress.
It really sounds like a pig
I have money, money, money, pigs, pigs!
Thank you, thank you.
I don't know where I'm going
For now, it's Ghost Rate, Ghost.
I'm sure you said that
But what should I do with this? Drill a hole and fill it with magma or something.
Ah
If that happens, let's run away right away.
Block it right away, okay?
Hey, but it's because I'm cutting through a wall.
Yes, there is a bit. This is connected to something.
Yeah, I don't think it's connected somehow.
[music]
This sounds kind of strange.
It's true, it's making a strange sound.
mysterious sound
I understand, what kind of strange sound does it make?
Maybe it's open, wait.
stop
My voice is so loud that I laugh. Everyone is so loud.
No ina attack ina attack now ina
attack attack
It's like that flight that happens too often lol
But something like caviar
Please leave it to the attendant.Speak loudly.
Attention please, it's helpful.
Even with a big voice, it's still a forest, it's still a forest, the forest is too deep.
It's red, right? Red, red. Is it still red? Too much red.
It's like this bubbly light flying around
When it's red, it seems like it's that red thing.
Right?
There are a lot of Wakamori who can't get away from this.
It's so spacious!
Hey, have you ever found a fortress? Yes, it's a fortress.
Yes, that service
It's amazing that I have all subjects. I say all subjects. All subjects are
No, you say you can rely on this and that.
That's what I wanted.
Red Red Forest Red Forest
red
[laughter]
Reto voice and snarky voice Ahonmaya Red
Frestlet Oh, there's a mushroom. It's a mushroom.
Wait 1
Is there ever a time? I think I can go get this.
Isn't that so?
Hey, you have too much momentum.
Apparently the equipment was very durable.
It's okay to jump in like that.
No way, diamond equipment
I'm coming back, I'm coming back
[laughter]
It's amazing, it's okay.
Yeah, I guess I'll just put up a torch just in case.
Thank you little by little
If you need more pine, we have some.
Thank you Unkochi too
There are still lots, so that's helpful.
That's helpful, that's helpful
Okay, are there 7 people? Wait a minute, that's scary.
It's scary. It seems like things were different at first.
Now the number of mushrooms is 1234
It's okay Kia, I have mine.
Well, now we have enough mushrooms for all of them.
Mushrooms are perfect!
Clear If no one dies, it's perfect
Hey, stop it, Ani-san, don't say scary things.
Ah, but there's something amazing about the stairs.
Looks like it's wide, this is in danger
I'm sure someone will look at me
Uchida and Aone are back.
It's coming back, it's coming back
That's Subaru and the others. I'll be back. Comment
Well, I guess you're back.
I can't go home, it's coming back
come back
Terue, what should I do once I return?
The only thing I found was mushrooms.
I wish the mushrooms were dead.
I don't want to make a joke so just some mushrooms
I also went to the glow stone that I was about to deliver.
It's Gusto, I'm sure I can go there.
Gusto Looks like Gusto around here.
Emiko-san, let's go just now.
It's the road I was thinking of, so let's take a look.
That straight one.This one is so straight.
I'll probably go with just Ghasts and Fortresses.
Well, if that's okay for the fortress, it's Gust.
Just what?
If you don't want to send it out, it's a one-shot deal.
It's not because I saw a fortress, it's because I saw it.
It's okay. I'm reading the chat.
I was reading the chat and something interesting is happening.
I can't just go away, so now is my first priority.
If you want to be the discoverer, here it is.
Dangerous, I'm surprised, ah, I'm surprised, ah
You'll be surprised. You'll be surprised.
Surprise, surprise, it's really gust
just beat it
So it seems like Gust is a normal place.
thinkfromother
I hope you find a cute gust
Hey, pollen, yes, maybe hay fever, but Subaru today.
I've been playing Minecraft since noon, so it's okay.
It's true that I have to finish it soon too.
It's already time to go to sleep
Is that what you're looking for? Well then, the blue one fell down.
Good people fall here or there
Either way, Yomiko will go first.
It's okay, people who are going home, it's quite early.
It's not a Karanema Nether Fortress, but it's a fortress.
I'm sorry to say that, but I see.
Okay, let's go blue, let's do it here.
I wonder if I should do it, but there's a gust one chan.
Well, I guess I'm back then.
I heard Gust's voice, so I thought for sure.
I just need to defeat Wanchan Gust.
I'm sure that's all you can do in the Nether.
Where did you go? It's okay
Yeah, it's okay, this is worse than this, pig's voice.
Here, here, here, the voice of a scary pig is scary, here
There's a match. Wait, it's a match.
It may be different, but what is this path?
This isn't it, what is this road?
That's probably Miko-senpai right now.
It's a path that I'm trying to grow, right?
That's right, if you go down to the left here.
Neko here, pop around here, are you okay?
Wait, the pigs are coming. The pigs are coming. The pigs are coming. The pigs are coming.
Wait, wait
Wait, wait, wait, wait, once, once, once.
I'm coming to Kuni, I'm coming to Kuni
Terukocchi
I'll come back, I'll come back, I'll do it, I'll do it.
I'm back, I'm back, I'm back, I'm here, I'm here
to
Is it okay too?
[applause]
I'm glad you made it this far alive.
Good, really good, thank you very much.
Thank you, you did your best today.
Because it's tendakara
But it's okay, I have a bow and arrow, so if you feel like it.
If you could just open the top where I can kill you.
If you aim like this from here and here
Can you go? Come on pig, go to the left. Go to the left.
Wait, you can see it from there.Drill a hole here.
I can't see, I can't see from here
I'm going buhi buhi
There's definitely one, wait, there's only one.
There's a gorilla who said, "I'm not going to run out of this."
Maybe it's not a gorilla, it's a forest.
Wait a minute, then I'll go out for a while.
Look, everyone should step back a little!
The cod started digging a hole.
show me
On top of Kuruko
is
On top of this, on top of this, on top of this?
Okay, okay, let's do this with a bow.
It's okay, this is true
Are you grinning? Wait a minute, where are you?
here here
I can't go here
mosquito
Shishi nice nice nice
Nice nice nice I thought it was over
I thought it was seriously over
Wait a minute, it's dangerous here.
It's seriously dangerous. I'm glad I have scary fingers.
I'm really not here. Maybe we're separated.
I'm separated, I'm separated, but over there
I want to grow it, right, right.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's dangerous, it's coming
It's coming, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming back
Go back, hi, this guy is okay.
Hello, it's okay, dear.
It's okay. Hello. Excuse me. I'm scared.
I thought it was really huge
Maybe that's what we are
When I got there, I waited and they disappeared.
but
Seriously, Imi-senpai and the others are in front.
It's just one trip back and forth. It's really just one trip.
I don't think I'll push it to the limit at this point.
It's going to be this, right?
The people who went first and said they wanted to grow
It's true that they're not there, but there's no point in getting separated.
Wait a minute, this is a half block
It's better to stretch it out in half.
It's better, but we'll have to wait a little while.
Wait a minute, are you completely separated?
Eh, I'll just wait a little longer and chit.
Miko
where
Separated
I'm getting separated from my destination.
Is it okay? Where is that?
I went back even further with this feeling
This is where I was stretching, right? The destination is here.
I'll come pick you up
Can you come and pick me up?
Eh, I'm coming to pick you up. I'm already home. I wonder if this is the road.
is not here
About the half block
But now, it wasn't that far.
It's not here. Maybe it's here.
That's right, I thought Suru was talking about this too.
Eh, I thought it was here too, but I was looking over here again.
No matter where you are, you can't come.
It's magma, but it's too far away.
No, I'm glad the pig is too scary.
It seems that Suginomaki Emikochi is very far ahead.
Good reason
Apparently it's not here, the destination isn't here.
I thought it was definitely here.
Wait, are you going to go further than I thought?
It's a green forest, it's a green forest, it's a green forest
Did you find it?1
times
I didn't notice it. It's a green forest. It's green.
If you stretch it out over here, you'll get it
Is there one?
Looks like it's on the left
It's true, have you ever found a green forest?
It was a red forest, it was always red.
I didn't notice it either.
It wasn't there, I didn't notice it.
It's just that, this is a one-chan green forest
come out and say
Tell me the coordinates of where the green forest is.
It's not okay, this or that is blue
Hey, I found my first gust.
Oh really, I found Gusto
It's at the beginning. Coordinates. Let's go. Coordinates.
Yes, it's the coordinates.
372 Wait, come to Gusto here too.
I didn't drop it. I might be waiting. Wait a minute.
Wait a minute, let's go back to the hole here.
Okay, I'm waiting. Where should I go?
Looks like I'll go inside this hole at least once.Wait.
Hey, are you taking that?
Yes, there is a gust, right?
I hear the sound of dying, dying, I want to go home
Niruru is here. Wait a minute, wait a minute.
I hit 34 with a blueness of 302.
I can take it 302, yeah 302
But please let me know
I'm in Iisai.
However, the gust is here and here too.
Ghast to defeat Ghast
And Ma-kun has a bow, so the three of us defeated him.
do
With this, there are 3 people and 1 more item.
from
Ekocchi de
I decided to hand over the bow for the subjugation.
Take a look here
Do a different code over here. Do a different code over here.
It seems like a different code would be fine here.
That eye contact with a bit of a Yankee Yankee
That's right, that's right.
That's there, there's that
No, I'm wearing a pumpkin, but I'm too far away.
I want to
Then I'm wearing a hat too, oh no.
If the future is too far away, than where I just went
The future ahead is too far away. The future is dangerous.
The future is too far away, Amiko is on the way
I quit
There is a half block where there is a half block.
The future is too far away for Block, isn't it?
The future is certainly too far away, but the future is green.
It's scary, but Gust's voice is where we parted earlier.
It's not a place we broke up, it's not a place we left.
Half block extension
I can hear a loud voice somewhere far away.
Yankee is dangerous
It's about 2 years tall. It's a little on the right.
Our place was higher than the Yankees.
The guy on the right is so cute
There are so many of them, they're so scary, seriously
There are about two of them, no, they live in the green forest.
I'm sure more of them will come inside, just wait.
Wait, wait, it's scary, it's following me
Oh, oh, you're following me even though I can't see you.
Oh oh oh
If it seems tough, come here first.
I have gas here as well, but will Mikochi come?
Senior, wait, I'm lost.
What do you mean, Miko-senpai? What is this all about?
It means that we are separated into 3 people, and we are divided into 3 groups.
Teru Emiko-senpai is coming towards me
I wonder if Kikiara and I are giving it to me.
That's probably what Chiara and I said.
Stay Together
I thought he was with Ira and cousin, but that's it.
Koto oh, I get it, I get it, so this is all torn apart
I'll find a way back here or there, just in case.
That's right. This is nice.
Go this way
Tee
Miko is okay
Ekore
to be confused
Sweet but close to home, but pigs
Ah, once Gusto is now that, maybe Miko-chan.
Are you in the forest over there? Where?
Where are they saying that the pigs are probably dangerous?
Miko is not in the forest.
In the forest
I'm Gusto from the Green Forest. Gusto, I understand. Gusto.
Understood, Gust is here.Wait a minute, Gust is here.
There was a faint sound when I said "bogi"
Just then, the gas I was aiming for disappeared?
Well, if that's the case, let's break up now.
It would be better if each of them returned alive.
Is that so? Will I make it home alive? I can't join you anymore.
Well, now that we've met up, let's have a gust.
Where did the big last bogey come from when I went to defeat it?
I bet you heard me, where is Ciara heading now?
I'm on my way now. I'm on my way now.
When Jamiko-senpai waits for Gusto to be discovered, it turns white for a moment.
was reflected
Aja Mikoto has an upward voice and voice.
Join me and meet up with Mikochi and Chiara.
When I heard what happened, I said goodbye to Kiara and I.
Let me first ask you what happened after we broke up.
I'd like to hear what you do next.
No, it's better to decide
And so Nemiko is here now.
Well, it's probably not moving because it's trying to merge.
Isn't it better? I understand. Yes.
I'm about to kill you once
That's how I feel. Gas is coming right in front of me.
I feel like I'll hit it if I want to.
Gusto's voice is so loud now.
It's over there, right?
I heard a voice from the right.
Someone from the right below, someone from the top right
I'm sure you're on top of me.
Right in front of Gust. Right in front of Gust.
It's right in front of me. I understand the gas, it's dangerous.
a
No, Gust is right in front of that.
It's so far away that I can't really see your face, and on top of that
Seriously, there was a name that sounded like Miko-senpai's.
Mikochi is probably on that floating island. I'm on that floating island.
There is at least someone on the island.
Miko Senpai Michie Yabamiko
Both of my seniors are probably targeted by Gust.
Maybe it's on the right, on the right, on the right
If you don't turn, that Ender is on your right.
Ender is on the right and in front of him
Gust
Yeah, you're a senior.
I went up there. Look, there it is. Wait a sec.
Wait, wait, no, no, no, here, here
It's coming here every now and then
My eyes met yours for a moment
Yosuyaba
It's too dangerous, but it's Yankee.
It's too serious, Yankee, what are you going to do?
Yankee One Chan Koko's Yankee
Give it something or give it to Yankee to Yankee.
Give something to a Yankee, give something to a Yankee.
Wait a moment, I wonder where it is now?
Endermen cannot enter areas 2 meters high.
It seems safe to stay here.
What's that? If the worst happens, I'm here.
Come in and kick that guy, yeah yeah
Sounds like you're saying that, Miko, I hear you're okay.
circle
I've reached half
I'm halfway there now I'm on my way, but I'm halfway there now
There's a half on the way, and there's a fly on top.
Who is the one on top?
I can see you, I can see you up there.
314735 I can see it
I don't have one, but I saw something.
35 units that are not at the rendering distance that is
Diamond clothes diamond clothes man
I thought it was Miko-senpai because her head looked like gold.
But Miko-senpai's head is made of money.
It's not gone. Who is that? It's Emiko money.
I don't think it's Kia or anything.
Oh, my senpai isn't money, so it's probably someone else.
It's not like I'm in there.
go here
Naimiko
It's blocked by pigs and ghasts.
It seems that Subaru and the others are going to Mikono.
Do you want me to pick you up? Tell me the coordinates.
Shall we go to
Let's kick this too, it's the worst
I understand, I wonder if I can kick it. I'll pick you up.
Emiko is here, but her senior has broken up with her now.
Ah, Kirakira-senpai is also looking for Mikochi.
I see, everyone should look for Miko.
It seems like we're together
Once everyone gathers at the first place
Miko returns to the beginning and end of the episode.
I'm so tired, but here's Miko.
I said I'll be back
It's about to fall apart, yeah yeah
Please come back and come over there once.
That's okay, I'd like you to type it in English.
If it's okay, Mikochi can come.
do
I noticed the entrance when I got separated.
The place where we got separated is somewhere down the road.
It's okay to meet up with Ami Kochi Ina.
Thank you so much
Tae then what should we do for the first time?
It's better to go back to
Yeah, it's better to be here first than to be here.
The place where we split up at the end was like that.
I guess it was the exit.
If you go this way, the exit is okay.
Okay, let's start with the first one, and finally, everyone.
It was in the fortress of the dead egg, right?
But we found you first.
It's sad, but I just found that one.
I said I was there, but I found my house in a different place.
Maybe someone on our team will say it.
That's what he said. That's amazing.
It seems like it's going to go somewhere.
It's true that it's a little far away.
I'll probably go there once and Ina and the others will be there too.
Right, three of us, yeah, yeah, three of us won't die.
It seems that she is going. Amiko is coming. Let's go back.
mosquito
It's too scary, it's okay
Blue is blue and I've become accustomed to it.
Opipi okay okay okay let's go back let's go back
I died
The octopus is dangerous, there's a pig in here, it's scary.
Wait a moment, be quiet, be quiet, what should we do, right, right?
Let's do it right and left. There are so many things we can do 2
There are two of them. Stop it. Turn blue. Turn back.
go back 1 time go back 2 times 2 times 2 times 2 times
It's found, it's found, it's found
I found it. I went home. I went home.
It's really dangerous to go in and go home and go in and go in.
No, now that I've come this far, I can kill you.
But I'm sure it's all the way here. Come on, it's 1 ma here.
Blue Subaru will be my bait, so I'll leave it to you.
Okay, wait for the future, wait.
Please wait, I'm using a bow and arrow.
They'll run in here with a bow and arrow, so I'll use a bow and arrow.
I don't have it so I'm really asking for it
Please, if you die here, we'll die too.
First of all, come here, I'm nearby.
Come in here and come here.
Terakuso runs away when he knows it's no good or no good.
It's coming, it's coming, I know it's coming.
It's coming, it's coming, it's coming here here here here
Squat down for a little while
I think I'm going to win, so I'm with you.
You can ask me to come down, yes, yes.
Suba-senpai is like, how painful is this?
It's stinging, it's stinging, it's stinging
It's got a blue sting. It's probably stinging.
More earlier, earlier, earlier, more
Before this this this this okay this
Are you okay
Dangerous nice nice nice nice nice
Hey okay, nice, there's another one.
Okay, I'll bring you some.
I'm going far so I'm facing my butt
Hey, can I go now? Can I go now? Is it next to me?
I'm scared. If I guessed it, it would be dangerous.
That's dangerous, wait a minute, that's dangerous.
I'm really coming to you, I'm really coming to you
Looks like it's dangerous. There are two of them, but they're still here.
Like that
There are so many people out there.
I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts
Ahaikekeke
Oh yes, there's one more. There's another one.
Please wait for another one to stink.
Oh, let's go, I'll bring you with me.
Please
Oh, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming
It's so delicious I'll definitely die
Ah wait, this hurts. Hold on a second, I'll hang up.
More le
Gao
Nice senpai, senpai, you should never touch him.
Like a cupid stuck in a place
Wait, what's going on?
that
Teru, Chiara, and I somehow returned to the portal.
Well, okay, let's go back.
Then we'll go back too. Then we'll go back.
Let's go back, doesn't that mean it's an exit?
That's the exit, right over there?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, we got together, maybe that.
On the way home, it's not here, it's here
On the way home, this is the way home, right?
If I built a staircase just a moment over there
Shall I follow this path until I can't get down?
It's scary, right? It's scary, so go to the safe place.
This is a good gust.
Oh my god, I'm aiming, I'm aiming, it's scary
It's too bad, I have no choice but to go from this side.
Wait a minute, let's go back once more Gust
Let's kill it, let's do it, let's kill Gust.
Let's kill Ghast, wait a minute, here.
Is the field too small? Bridge or go back?
Go back, go back, understand, understand, understand.
Understood, what, what, what did you say?
I was surprised when he said "pogigya"
Well, that field is a little too small.
Isn't it just one gust? I'm sure I'll go now.
Then we have no choice but to cross and fight in a wide field.
No way, that means Subaru goes first.
go parenthesis
Okay, I'll go to that hole once for you.
from
eat a nice meal
Hole, hole, be careful, hole, hole, be careful, back to the wall
Yankee with wall Yankee
Yan, wait a minute, where's the gas?
It would be better to contact Samiko and the others just once.
Listen, that blue Subaru Subaru and the others are fighting.
If you're going to break up then just go ahead and be done with it.
I hope Subaru and the others don't come back.
Tell me, I'll make some water.
Thank you very much.
Let's keep it wide, yes, it would be dangerous if something happened.
Karasu
Hey, it's too scary, Nether. Wait a minute.
I don't have it anymore, it's about to disappear by now
I guess it's a good idea.
It won't disappear soon
He's not there
Hey, what's your name, Kill?
I heard a voice saying "ru"
It's a little far, maybe it's a little far, I'll go home
Maybe he ran away.
I heard a sound from a little far away, so I was scared.
Well, I'll be heading back soon.
We can't see each other anymore. It's true.
I said, let's go home.Let's go home now.
Somehow I turned down the sound.He just made the sound.
I'll never come this way, let's go home
Let's go, let's go, yeah
Kopkop
Hey
First of all, Mr. Sado and all the fun mushrooms.
I guess I should definitely give the mushrooms to everyone.
I can't die because I have to
Well, maybe we should change it to that book.
That sounds terrible. Yes, it's dangerous here.
dangerous
It's dangerous here, we're meeting in the dark.
Teteruko
That's right, I made this road so I wonder if I can get home
Dangerous, dangerous, it's not too dangerous here.
Ta
dangerous scary
Yo
dangerous
Oh, it's too scary. I'm not scared on the way home.
Well, I've come a long way, I'll say it.
Wait, we can't go there, it's a bit of a wall
I might want you to make one.
It's too late, don't wait a moment
Wait a minute, yes, yes, yes, yes.
I wish there was a wall to keep me from falling.
It's a wall you can't fall on. Wait a minute. It's dangerous.
Block me, wait a minute.
It's okay to have it, leather rack 64a
That would be helpful, yes, if there was a wall, I made a mistake.
I threw the wrong diamond hair
It's like a wall. Okay, wait a minute.
I thought of a damn good thing here.
Why don't you try making something like this?
It would be dangerous if I shot from here.
I can shoot, but the side walls are scary so I'll just shoot here.
I'm going to build a wall, ooh, I'm going to build a house here.
It's too slow, it's normal
On the way home, I asked him why he was waiting here.
Teru
It's dangerous here
Can I hit it now? You want to hit it already, right?
Yes, it's getting worse now
Tara
I can go here
Is this okay? I heard everyone asking.
I fell down, I fell down, go!
Isn't that so? Go, go, go, go, fall.
Oops, I crashed. I was looking at the chat log.
Is it okay? Wait, I'm at the block.
It's over there, in the half block.
I got it too wrong over there.
da half block
Got it, back and forth, back and forth.
We were able to meet up even so
I'm so glad. I'll never be able to join you again.
I thought so
Ah, I guess it's near the entrance.
I made stairs
Did you come up and wait for me?
No, it was really good
I'm glad it was somehow like that.
Zeairu Senpai Mikochi Atataitaitaitaita
Mikochi
where were you
Wait, wait, I'm glad I met you.
It's dangerous here, it's dangerous
It's dangerous here, it's dangerous here, it's dangerous here
It's dangerous here, it's dangerous, it's dangerous here
Where is the dangerous Emiko? Really Emiko?
Miko used to go to other places, but nothing at all.
It was a passing communication, right?
Seriously, we just passed each other.
Gust ran away because it was scary
I guess we're going to be Nesane Gusto after all.
I reached the goal and at the very end
The place where we parted seems to be empty, so we move forward through the unexplored land.
There are so many things that can only be done
Teruru onion is attached for now
Hey Ao, let me just deliver the mushrooms for now.
Can you please do it for me? I'm sure.
You're not going to change, Saul, go home now.
sadoooooo
or
Okay, there's a pig over there too. It's dangerous here, no, it's a pig.
That was terrible, seriously, but Miko and Miko both died.
I thought Airu Shiba-chan was there.
No, let's do it, please do it, please
You guys please
lie
character
Hey, that's a lie
[applause]
No, it's a lie, I'm serious.
Teru
Hey, hey
Well then, let's go Mario.
Let's do it
[laughter]
Haaji Mario, let's go, how about this?
By the way, he died
Thank you for your hard work. Don't ask me too much.
ask your tired body
Zekorechika
Nine Peko-chan Peko-chan This is by the way
But I haven't been able to pay back my debts yet. What should I do?
It will be
This is too real, no, no, it's too real
What is real?
What is real? What is real?
Is there one?100How many are there?
12,051,250,000 is amazing
hey
I was really surprised.
There are 125 of them.
But there are 125
I just want to say thank you for your hard work.
Just tell me how to repay the debt
I'll contact you later
Please, Ayabe chat has disappeared
Tamou chat also came, came, came, came
debt
How to repay
Please pay other than cash
Mario
So I'm going Subaru's hardcore
Thank you very much Minecraft
Let's talk
If you understand, please wait a moment, everyone.
Subaru's Hardcore Minecraft
Thank you very much
Ta
Ha, what will happen to the debt?
It's okay, but it was fun
I thought we could have fun and adventure like this.
It was really fun because there wasn't any.
It was a very short and rich life.
Finally, fat bear, I wish everyone a lot.
I'm sorry, but I had a hard time meeting up with you.
That was it, but thank you for your hard work.
So thank you everyone.
Seed
Well, after this, from around midnight
Do you want to play Yuru Yuru Mario? Maybe Yuru Yuru and
Subaru, but there is no resurrection trial, so Minecraft
This is the end of this
Wow, what an amazing two days.
Minecraft won't be playing for a while now.
I think so
Everyone who farts will be cut off once from 24:00.
mario
Hey everyone, Peko-chan is also planning a project.
thank you
See you soon bye
Bai Otsuru