[Music]
[Applause]
hi made Hello we made Hello h H hi
CH wow all right thank you guys for
joining my the valve collab Marathon
thank you for playing
[Music]
to2 a lot of you guys are new to the
game right oh yeah yeah never played
before yeah so we're going to learn play
the tutorial you don't need it you don't
need it it's
easy we skip the tutorial yeah we'll
skip a skip a yeah
yeah all right I don't know if we need
introductions there's a lot of us here
so that might take like five or 10
minutes but just maybe for audio check
for the
balancing all right we'll go down the
Discord list I'll go first hello
everybody I'm milia Watson a number one
detective from Hall of English smth
W thank
you hello everyone
[Music]
[Applause]
leader
just
here I'm I guess hello different on my
list okay
it
[Laughter]
[Music]
yay so good M uh who's
next y
[Music]
[Applause]
hiina
okay I zoron from H English promise who
know sorry I couldn't people
it's
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah wa here I'm going to play
Pyro fire good to know got a fire today
yeah oh yeah
true all right so we are going to split
up into different teams uh I I randomly
what oh
what nothing so just killed me oh wait
how am I dead why am I not why am I
looking at people I think someone's
cheating what oh
maybe you can cheat in this game no no
you can't you can't ah are are we
starting uh yeah yeah yeah okay if
you're on Blue Team we'll go into the
other voice
chat okay oh all right and then it's
Capture the Flag yeah any questions
where's the flag somebody kill us
where's the flag should we all go
together hold on hold on let's all meet
up in the bridge meet up in the bridge
bridge no I want to be a red come
on yes no no fighting I don't trust the
robot I think you'll kill us no fighting
no no no it's okay it's okay no fighting
this where is every I'm about to die
wait so blue team wait so red team stays
here or no no red team and blue team
everybody go to the bridge just go
inside uh the middle outside in the
middle yeah wait where's the bridge okay
outside it's yeah just find your way
[Laughter]
outside all maybe I can destroy my oh
that's GG oh crap I found a map no wait
that's to try
no fighting no fighting no
fighting they're all in a different cor
they left already okay I was going to
show you guys I think we should just
start all right start just kill them
just kill
[Music]
them I'll heal you is this working thank
you get out of
here that's cool I like
that not ready all right guys never fear
is
here dead are you healed
yet uh I'm okay for now I think
I'm I'll heal everybody else then oh God
you need healing oh my
gosh all right I'm going to go with you
guys you I'll kill you I
me we die we going to die we going tell
you Run keep running keep
running nice oh it's not easy to kill
somebody as medic nice job nice job you
guys oh there you are all right so we
have to try to sneak into their base and
in the basement of their base there's
like a suitcase careful careful
SP I
stand who was
that heing I think everybody's healing
no yeah AR nice I don't think the other
team has a medic do
they there's there's somebody coming as
good as us
though all right oh yeah you guys are
medic at GTA too I will heal you is this
a spy there's on Fire's on fire okay all
right I'm I'm going into the base we can
do this so we go together okay let's
go just ignore the heavy go through the
bridge go through the bridge go through
the bridge the bridge is d this way it's
okay go inside that's true I'll show you
guys how to get to the base inside yeah
yeah I heal you a gun oh thank you for
the he so if we oh we got to kill this
guy we got to kill this guy kill kill
kill kill I'm
healing no Artic Oh's in our base our
base all right CeCe come with me wait
wait wait I'm going into I'm going to
grab the I'm going to grab the suitcase
run respawn 7 Seconds okay I'll be back
we won we got bed a I thought we
won the the one guy oh it's shorty
shorty is still here by the way I have
taken their
intelligence I'll hear you is our is our
briefcase okay is that our briefcase in
there building right now I I'm taking
their briefcase wait you're on our team
right I'm on red
I dropped their briefcase like in the
top floor and it has a cool down if you
guys go up there okay you could grab it
I'm trying to figure out where button do
you us to grab stuff uh it should just
pick up automatically yeah you guys if
you go up the stair The
Heavy no nice try nice try there
everybody down I'll heal you let's
regroup cuz they're they're all there
waiting I killed somebody oh nice good
job I saw it I'm on fire I'm on fire I'm
fire jump in the water jump in the water
water it's down here yeah yeah yeah if
you're on fire the water will help
there's also a secret tunnel down there
to go into their base they probably
don't know I just found it okay let's go
anyone down down in the tunnel I can
heal you I think elz went down there
right oh yeah I'm in that base I'm with
you I'm with you so sorry I I'm s so do
we do we do we have their flag or should
we go get it uh I had it but it went
back to their base yeah it's like in the
basement in the
basement I killed him they got our
intelligence okay I'm going to go back
to yeah toat
defend
okay oh it's the little square that's oh
it's the little blue square yeah yeah
yeah you can see it through the map keep
on going I'm going I'm going
behind just in case I have the I have
the nice nice they're trying to CR
they're in the water underneath the
tunnel they're going in oh they're
almost tunnel yeah if you guys see them
in the tunnel kill them kill them I'm so
confused which way to go I'm too
slow out I'm out of there I'm out of
there I'm
backing I don't know where to put it
where do I put it how do got them so
slow
oh make sure you get a weapon you see an
enemy I them get a weapon I have the
weapon yeah you have other ones though
Li you got this I don't
to I'm not sure wait I forgot where
where do we take the intelligence is it
back to the basement do I take it back I
oh we did it
Yay good
job intelligence with it's yeah they got
ours I was trying to catch up go go go
you're one one one
one try to heal you oh shoot oh
shoot all right where we going all we're
tired now I'm going in the water again
goodbye okay I'm going to try going in
again somebody I I'll stay behind for
defense yeah I'm
healing are we doing the thing huh
you're doing it
uhoh uhoh uhoh there's a guy behind
you him
grab your gun grab your gun that's
behind you GG got him wa you guys are
killing him nice that way go that way
I'm in their base I don't know what I'm
doing I don't know what I'm doing either
where do I go all right let's get the
briefcase go go go the briefcase or
defend our briefcase oh there we
go is also if anyone's a sniper yeah
there's like a really got theef nice
nice let's go let's go for okay I'm
really slow cuz I'm
heavy got him well moo if you guys use
your Uber he has kind of like an ability
let's go you get invincible boy o there
foko behind you guys remember you I'm
out let's go this
way I'll he you okay back to base oh
that was easy where are they you guys
just killed them all ni I haven't seen
them I
think I have no idea where to
go if you right click with Uber with
your charge as medic you'll get him I
don't know if it's up up up okay okay
it's okay how do I hand the suitcase to
somebody else can I drop
it sure I think you have to take it all
the way down let's be careful oh there
we go I know the way now G is coming
downstairs they're here they're here go
Medics here I got killed by the
medic
get put yay nice one all right let's go
back outside nice nice okay I have my
gun okay uh are some characters base
speat faster than others yeah like the
Scout character I think he's a bit
faster see okay what I'm playing is real
fast okay
sh yeah dead get
him nice nice all right I'm I'm going to
watch cuz I didn't realize it's a 6V
five so I'm going to just spay some more
are we bullying them a little bit but I
mean it's I haven't been doing much
pretty well they're doing pretty well
for Sho shoot I'm going over into their
base again under
water I did it oh there's someone coming
okay I have my gun they're going on the
bridge there's two Scouts
a I'll just
watch yeah
yeah it you're doing it you're doing it
go go go go go go a there's a heavy
going up
fire I'm hearing I'm he oh thank you ah
this way oh you guys killed them nice
got to he we're still danger we're dang
can't myself the same as I heal everyone
else I don't know I feel like we heal
fast if we heal others I think
[Music]
nice okay we got to
guard I shoot I shoot I
shoot nice so C got
rolled I'm so good at this
I I'm behind you I have the briefcase
let's go oh nice Dam I don't know where
to go though uh we need to go up I
behind I behind right
now oh
nice snip nice nice
nice oh yeah this way this way this way
I remember now you got this I'm you
thank
you this
[Music]
way okay where could they be coming they
too quiet let's go let's go let's go
wait they're here okay here where
they're in they're our suitcase they
have
suitc okay oh I'm dead somebody needs to
get
them which way are they going they're
coming out of the
base is not basement G has it g has it
is she under the under the
tunnel's let
let's oh the back stab
[Music]
nice I see somebody I see somebody I see
somebody thanks for you got ready to
go into the water battle I'm so confused
with the
map it takes a while toar yeah so I'm in
the intelligence but there's nothing
here
so you wait are you in their
intelligence or are you in our you'll
see the you'll see the blue uh kind of
highlight of the intelligence I think oh
it respawned okay I got
it together my job is to
heal all right okay we got we got a
guard we stick together M that's the
best part of my job do they have your
guys'
suitcase not
where they are oh do they have
it has a
suitcase uhoh um I'm just wandering
around their
base I am
too where is H where am I I'm in the
eny
get oh no they're
going shoot shot shoot
shoot me he going with the oh nice nice
gra it grab it you got it you got it you
got it see that oh you guys really
good how do we do we have to pick it up
oh I think you just have to guard it up
again okay yeah there's there a
timer okay okay okay it'll go back
automatically okay we got this we got
this okay we just prot we got it we got
it
yeah I'm going to heal s do you need
heal no thank you oh okay somebody
behind
nice where's the rest she ran into like
a bunch of us up
here yeah oh maybe
not okay they're guarding the suitcase o
oh that's suitcas
okay I'm lost again there's this we just
got to make sure we guard this okay it's
been
returned the let's go with the little
blue Mark is on the map on the map and
let's try getting it yeah up here this
way I'm on push I'm on push to talk chat
so now I can cast properly I was
watching oh they're on our base it's G
I'm spectating cuz it's not an even
fight right now are they this is really
fun anyways how I think some people
aren't
streaming ni but you guys are just
camping their base
huh we should get the
suitcase how many
people but I don't know where everybody
else
is he crony killed me oh crony's a
freaking Scout
too guarding CE needs heels wait do you
that is so cute running around is
heavye up I'm go our place andc see if
she like a big cat they on a
base it's been on the on the they were
too quiet get
their oh oh oh I need
help's one HP she dropped a
case with her
shotgun she has another gun nice
she our intelligence now is it in their
face there one guy here oh go oh go oh
go I'm out of ammo I'm out of ammo
healing is eg okay let's get out of here
about to get off
suitcase I think she's running with it
noav withcase it's
okay let's go underground under it
is
help that is thato there is this Elmo
gra that R's sneaky cat you pick up you
picked up nice nice let's go through the
I think's she's going the WR way thank
you she's going to take it back get the
one with us
I think yeah you the way that way which
way I do go this way doesn't know where
to
go oh she Stills Okay Okay g taking what
that is what does it do how do we use
it they're all guarding I don't
know
yeah wait what is it what do you guys
need to help with they cute what is oh
Uber yeah yeah so you you click on
somebody and then you right click while
healing them and it gives them inin
ility for a
while let's get close let's get close
down to to the right way it's really
good in a big
fight oh nice oh they just delivered
their
suitcas nice
GG all right um you guys want to play
this one again or do you want to play on
a new map this one's
cool God used to it I'm going to switch
teams and that I'm going to go to the
other voice chat and see how they're
doing yeah
am okay okay we got this let's do it I
knowy hates
humans hi I'm here to check out you guys
I'm just spectating
oh
okay you guys did good now I saw you
running around what the the case for a
long
time she tried her best I was trying to
find the intelligence room but I fa yeah
it's kind of it's hard I was going to
show you guys but then very
confusing yeah at least I picked it up
and it killed someone which is better
than
nothing if you guys need any help or
questions I can
[Music]
help not sure where am I I don't know
where I think this game is very simple
yeah
[Music]
yeah I'm infiltrating enemies they have
our intelligence again we shall take
theirs okay what if I just Camp here oh
yeah just Camp their spawn get out of
here what they have another spawn too
there's one on the other side where's
the intelligence okay we'll we'll camp
out at one of them you guys are all
going nice nice yes see oh it's easier
together
strong yeah oh where is it C come back I
don't know where it is I found it I
think we should stick
together run run run run we'll protect
you we'll protect you I'll
defend oh they can come back down and
take that yeah the cas okay never mind
ow oh if you're carrying intelligence
you should stay back so you can defend
okay yeah stay back stay back I'm just
going to keep you make around oh no oh
no
no I kill it I kill it I think I got it
got it
got oh shoot oh shoot I dropped it don't
give up no no now you going to run no
good good good nice nice I don't know
where anywhere is
oh dropped it kind of by their spawn
area oh thank you a I don't even know
where I like how G's just standing there
I'm making sure no one takes this
intelligence yeah I think I forgot about
it oh the brain cells are dropping thank
God they forgot about it they forgot
about it no she came back but it's gone
full oh I see the red what do you guys
people there I'm trying to figure out a
better setup for voice chat you guys
think it' be good if we use like we sat
inord and sometimes we talk inord but we
use like iname voice chat or something I
got you my buddy I got you
ra thank you I want to go grab the yep
yep intelligence I refreshed the Tim oh
let's go is that good oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh no no nice try oh there's too many
of them yeah they're they're not even
going for yeah that's good they're going
on the Deep
defense game boy shot might be good oh
maybe they're using it to I don't know
if everybody has it set up though so it
might be a problem they're exped by how
good we are what are you do there yeah
we let them win the last
round what are you down there swimming
you can go through the tunnel here I
don't know yeah I think if everybody's
in one VC it would be it' be funny but
it would be a lot this is fine but it's
stinking there's rats
where where oh oops
sorry you guys need a medic they have a
medic
[Music]
yes Che you got revenge I'm not good at
it
though don't die don't
die why you everywhere y I'm killing
myself no all right I'm medic now who
needs healing going to stay here though
we have payload we could do play payload
um which payload map do you guys
recommend is easy if just standing there
then follow me he me okay I
gotcha uh where's everybody else at now
see what shor's up to uh I think you you
got to like pick up those little
packages on the ground is that M really
big like this one I think we what about
uh no no no what about dust with your
healing we can do it maybe oh maybe I'm
thinking of high tower what's the one
intelligence
too it's
upward was fried not DUS not
D yeah maybe it is upward you know the
one that
has shoot oh I'm thinking of control
points put in a random area then okay I
know they can't hear me I'm not talking
in chat where are we going someone has
our intelligence too oh you guys traded
you guys traded it's okay here oh
returned oh
no does someone have ours where they
head
to I such like this game yeah good
good okay I'm going to join you guys and
I'm going to help healer yes please help
us we're losers no no no
no and now this pretty strong I'm like
trying to describe the specific TF2 map
but then as I try to describe it I
realized that uh
it kind of they kind of all sound the
same when you describe
it wait that barely did anything get
another to the battle it's like the
one I even describe it heck
yeah we need to see some fire all right
I'm protecting this side of the map so
they might try to go
underneath the centuries I hate
the my
follow are they inside at the entrance
they're inside could be really mean and
put it I could put a Sentry on the
intelligence
case that would be mess up let me see
where are we going oh I think they did
they already take the
case oh not yet not
[Music]
yet okay this is super messed up but
uh that's not messed up it's
I'll just I'll I'll just leave it at the
middle upgrade uh the small one
appreciate the help thank you ow
ow nice
nice you should you should you could go
with the the other team into the base
and then it'll help them a lot I think
wherever they're going as a medic make
sure you're not a
spy
oh I'll try where where' to go where
where where are them
is it not can I not to pick up weapons
for like ammo not ammo but for you
know no you going with the Enemy oh no
no no I meant like if anyone's going in
I just can hear people I'm running can
maybe I can't with the heavy gun oh you
haven't been able to for a long time
they changed it oh shoot that's how long
I've been oh everyone has died Prett
fast
[Music]
I'm going to build a t for their
intelligence I'm going to put a Teleport
into their base let me see if I can
sneak in and put a Teleport seems like
she had some practice as an engineer I
can build teleports so I'm going to put
a Teleport into their base from our
spawn okay wow just give me like a few
minutes and it'll be
up KY no KY no no K don't die no
KY no no
okay I'm okay okay I hope they the the
water I got it's okay ra thank you
they're in our base they're in our base
it's okay I got a Sentry down
there they're still in our base rage
swap a they ran away on the Xbox my mama
said I'm not supposed to be here oh crap
oh no I got sniped help help help
they don't know they don't know they
don't know all right where can I put it
where they're not going to see
it so
tanky
yay is that friend or
fo I just shoot them
anyway they're underg
ground we'll figure it out
later let's go get used to this I didn't
even see anybody on the way here I don't
understand this yet
all I'm going back put a teleporter if
you guys Gather in Fr of the
spawn where where is it I'm I'm L think
this way idea intelligence to drop it
off
yeah all the way to the desk again yeah
you know the architect of this place
kind of sucks cuz they put two enemy
factions near each other hey guys I put
a teleporter by the main spawn and if
you go into teleporter it'll take you
into their
base who are you can I trust you okay I
can you can trust me I'm
friend okay oh f is in our face our
intelligence kill her hey take yeah take
that how do I take this oh hey there's a
bit of a cool down thank
you I got their intelligence I on my way
back
no it's okay it's
okay yeah yeah I think they know they
know they know I'm here they know I'm
here watch out spy Spy bye gole he right
behind
you I sense your
present it's just like my fan fictions
where are them all right I'm now without
protection I must stay with someone okay
where are you where are you where are
you wor you not lady oh you need you
yeah hey if you go into this teleporter
down take you right to their base all
right guess we're going together it
takes a cool down there's like a cool
down it's like a minute what the
charging okay all right don't die a
minute to not die the Spy start a spy
it's not me but it's them but they're
acting as
me it's
charged some
here yeah I'm just healing everyone
byebye byebye where are you pyro
anymore behind you I saw spy behind the
scout who's the Scout on the bridge turn
around have nice we got it we got
it oh it's you okay all right I'm going
back into uhor mode now that I've
balanced it a little bit making sure
that it's not a spy gra the
intelligence can we even teleport back
from here I don't think so has taken oh
no no it's only one way
sorry okay be safe everyone he me heal
me I'm healing I'm healing you have Uber
if you have Uber you can right click
going to turn you to a kfp don't worry
don't worry it's me it's
[Laughter]
me all right oh my god let's
[Music]
go everyone else crazy
girl oh
we have to go back have to go Frozen
sorry you guys can watch somebody else's
uh thing I'm looking for the commands to
change
[Music]
it I don't know just make a this way
this way okay this way's this okay oh
crap wait wait fall this way I'm healing
I'm
healing literally Unstoppable all right
I found
it MVP I hear the scream from the damn
ins what's the map I'm thinking of it's
I think it's control point it's like a
control point one and it starts like
where there's like a hill and house
shoulders like a little railroad thing I
was stuck not Sawmill not sawm what is
the intelligence oh my gosh you keep
losing I I don't know I'm not
intelligent enough to that
process sake water
maybe even if look like us at this
point oh yeah bad water basin yeah yeah
yeah I feel like this one will be easier
than now ask later cuz that this one has
like less verticality I guess less yeah
yeah yeah it was bad water it's bad
water it's bad
water all right wait nice let's go into
the all voice chat really quick okay
we'll all go back
okay YY
we have tide all right we're changing
Maps Okay we do random teams again this
time
[Applause]
sure did you guys have
fun it's
chaotic yeah yeah so fun what why you
buling
H you're the easiest Target you were
just walking
around random you walked into my bullets
yeah random Rand you want us to hit
random yeah yeah yeah random let's go
yeah random move the
car
hi what's this you want give
us tutorial yeah so this one uh one side
pushes the cart the other side tries to
stop the
cart die I had a heart attack don't
know or the defending team uh red is
defending blue is pushing okay I cannot
open okay okay do you want us to move in
a different voice uh yeah yeah okay uh
blue team or red team go into the other
voice chat
okay
goodbye f is in my team so she can't
kill me anymore
wait you I I I I left the room by
mistake I mean they k out I don't know
what happened I'm trying to we can wait
for you I just to come
back I guess we should uh memorize the
map really quick oh true straight
forward we just push oh it's not letting
us through this
one set up 20 seconds oh no okay but
seems like is kicked
out yeah I'm trying to play we need
another person to make the team even by
the way anybody can join really I just I
can give you the info if you wanted
[Music]
say
okay wait am I in the right
party uh red team moved red team moved
red team is
in moving I'm pushing I'm
pushing should we wait for
moving no moving Ferrara help someone's
here wait now is it even sniper me
double
check the Blue
Team Auto
balance oh is that I'll spectate for now
I don't mind never don't mind yeah yeah
okay I'm in I'm in I'm in are we red oh
we blue M it's sorry sorry sorry uh
eared in order to speed up the the card
I think more people are closer to the
isn't there somebody in this Discord
chat that isn't supposed to be here 1 2
3 4 5 we connecting wait I don't know
where to go I'm so confused being blue
now because we were red the entire time
oh my God so confusing okay okay so we
blue who's on the team who's not
supposed to be
here got this what I I'm I put put on a
different team
what wow okay sorry I guess it's
confusing switching colors okay where're
this is everybody's on our team nice
blue team right oh yeah okay okay push
push push push P I see it I see it she
got Auto
balance
please please the happiest day of my
life push push ah he's laughing it's
close almost just a little bit more I
can see it does the payload heal hold
their hands out what do you mean it's
beautiful life is beautiful it's life is
so
beautiful two Heavies oh my God yeah the
payload will heal you guys a little bit
so it's good to stay kind of by it yeah
okay
I think the other team has to try
explosives or something right if they
had a demo man forever to come back to
the
train yeah because we're pushing when
you get it to a certain point the the
spawn will
update oh yeah it'll change
mhm Man is Hard kind I mean kind of
yeah yeah payload on offense pay I don't
have a good shot
here see what C see I'm so useless let's
go I think I should switch I feel like
spy you really well though it does doing
good like they you're doing really good
yeah stop stop stop uh what do you to
push
it automatically yeah okay
oh God oh God Is there a way to spectate
in first person you guys know oh wait it
says switch camera mode ah there we go
updated please please update please
we're doing it oh you sniped by
Ena oh my gosh that was
impressive I don't know which way to go
thisa right now no no I think going the
wrong way wrong way I think it's this
there's there's arrows there's arrows
they point which way I see them it's
blue wait okay okay we're good I think
they're waiting for you guys I found
everyone sniper
M oh my
God we almost had GG versus Ena sniper
match
yay so fast right okay I need a
Healer oh you just have to be close to
the train in order to heal so head
shotting heavy is so easy know dang it
yeah you got
sniped oh nice kill Nice kill help
they're all on me oh I have another gun
I forgot I just Arrow okay
I'm nice try nice try my bad there's
also like for these tight Corners
explosive characters are good there's
like a soldier
man I'm pulling out the rocket launcher
let's
go oh it's dead I just tried to double
tap forward to Sprint like it's
Minecraft life is Minecraft behind you
behind you guys behind the
c not even
healing oh no it's so
were they stuck there let go let go nice
youit you guys are almost going to get
it this if you get this it you'll win
this is the end we got this oh the
end final
frch
nice absolutely
destroyed good job right now now it
switches now you guys have to defend
okay okay okay we got this now we're
defense now we're doomed I'm going to go
to the other check look okay okay so
maybe should only use it when we really
need to so let's focus on healing okay
yes yes from what you said just a moment
ago
hello saw I see aive Target so we need
to respond
aggressively moo just battle medic
get healed let us let us
through you got 30
seconds let's just think about our
family probably there's no how do you
look at what all the the do hickeys do
on each nobody streaming on Blue Button
to click we have no PS for the other
team oh red team ah okay okay we'll
spectate red team do I have to press the
Uber and then attach to someone begin 10
seconds 10 seconds oh what was that oh
you got to be attached to someone and
then Uber
yeah how do you changed character how do
you look at what the character does uh
period and then do numbers just keep
holding
thei oh wait what okay always telling me
to kind of get out jump jump jump go for
it go for it I shoot them from here I
think it's freaking I'm just going to
focus on pushing yeah push push push I'm
we dying dying we're dying oh so it's
comma and then if you hover over the
characters uh it'll say what they
do did my weapon change wow I really
like those G Guns we should heal
everybody we getting weting wrong way
wrong
way hold oh I still shooting all right
I'll go I'll go back to the other voice
chat since you guys said there's no
there I'm going back to other voice chat
good luck wait do you guys have any
other questions did you figure it out
Liz
thank
you all right they're in the tunnel
right now I think she figured it out
maybe maybe she tone Oh that's hurt my
feelings though oh
noing hold then just moving Gigi over
uhoh okay I'm died I'm scared I'm scared
fixing this okay got
this can't I fix my whatever all
okay they're pushing they're pushing no
they've killed
me's back no more Sentry they're in a
tunnel
no oh was too
Exposed on heavy do they have they're
making the first
checkpoint oh there's another oh wait
are they blue oh they're
blue wait what got a defend up
top no medic Let's see we have two
Heavies my ankles
Soldier I'm lost a sniper and a SC
follow the
tracks how about you followed the
tracks already is
depending how shoot
blue all
right I keep forgetting about that I
thought they
we're struggling with colors a little
bit over here color blind you switch
sides really often in this game so you
can press tab so then you always see
what color you are it helps I think oh
yeah yeah if you press tab it pulls up
the scoreboard and you see all the other
names as well I completely forgot
about hey you guys don't have a medic so
it's kind of hard with without healing
yeah who needs who needs heals who needs
healing I'm healing healing healer if
you press E I think it says medic can
you give me a 10 seconds medic rundown
uh yeah you just hold Mouse one and you
build up your Uber charge which if you
right click while healing somebody it's
invincibility charge okay okay okay guys
we have a Healer and you have a gun so
yeah and you also have a melee weapon go
fla go thank you very much go fla go
what's the best way to kill the really
tanky guys head shot head
shot you can just have yeah
head if they have Heavies on their team
if you guys have a sniper sniper is
really good at headshotting heavy cuz
his head is so
big what a big lad
okay I'm a sniper at the moment so I'll
try okay
okay no problem Oh GG on Demo Man
missing for eight more minutes more
minutes minutes we got this guys we have
we we have a hea now it's it's easy easy
healing healing I need healing healer
you you had half Health go get somewhere
else wait are we're you're
you're I
forgot oh do you know how
to uh what is it called [\h__\h] DET help
help help no I have no I got it you got
it okay I didn't know you had
detonate yeah those are the sticky ones
there's another uh launcher you can use
instead but you have to equip
it nice you guys are getting of it wait
wait careful
sniper
uh-oh I feel it in my joints heal or
healing where is the medic
I found some
oh okay I see I see the body be healer
healing healer healing
healer I
died healers you
say fun you can speak for my heels right
no green I'll speak for
her I'm out of ammo on my gun
you can pick up other people's gun or or
see there's like a little box on the
ground and there's also like Med packs
and ammo randomly throughout the
map
spots kill the heal up healing
healing all right nice
yeah it seems like they're doing good I
feel like I help the red
team here you go g eat it thank you m
oh my
[Music]
gosh oh the two
Heavies I got
you where is
crony go oh two Medics let's
go B melted the the melee does a lot of
damage though when you can get to
it oh really cool
oh I ran right into
them who's the fake Cecilia immigr
that's me that's me she who's the fake
Cecilia immigr over
there wait is there another one I don't
think the other team has a
SP that F have two Med and two
Heavies the Cecilia immigr I know yeah
yeah yeah I think you can get back into
spawn and heal you can always go back
into spawn to heal kill it kill it kill
it oh no
meds
uhoh guys I'm not sure we've got like 7
minutes left eight wait did it go up did
the timer go up how is it still at 8
minutes it I think oh so when they get
it to a certain point in the map it adds
time oh help guys help help there's so
many of them like a five I'm healing I'm
healing I'm healing everyone that's
messed up they have like two Medics and
two Heavies they're about to get the
meta you guys can stall you can stall
I'm healing I'm
healing the noob Mana the noob
men noobs oh it's a lot of
damage I'm healing we're healing each
other we're all healing
we're oh only one's alive kill kill him
no it's tie nice try yeah hey it's a tie
defense is really hard yeah that's fun I
I think we can do one more uh different
game mode so hold on if you guys want to
go into all chat or something for this
round and then I'm going to I got to
find the command so okay okie
dokie they should come to
us yeah oh true I'll go tell
them hey
uh
hello I'm going to change the game mode
one more time but if you guys want to go
into the other chat for this round and
then just you know do whatever oh sure
okay
chaos all right what you guys
think I want to do control Point M
what's a good control Point M have a
party good game good game Harvest a cute
one Harvest is
good how to defend
successfully I'm overcharged wait let me
just watch one hour video real quick saw
for cont I looked up like a guide and I
was like how to play this one is a
really big map
though kind of scared I mean that one
would be good aage team foress no I
didn't watch it I mean
it's Shing that's a try hard I cannot
believe good
small really I
remember Sawmill
yeah can can you emote in this game gu
switching game oh yeah there there is
emotes each other
[Music]
magic let's
go take him down I don't know where I am
come out guys come on Blue Team all
right I'll let them play for like 4
minutes and then I'll switch
team death match
I'm do of course you oh let me fix the
gift
sorry oh I don't know where I am team
death match we am
lost I'm a little bit
lost might go the other way by the way
they die
already hey I love these sounds oh
there's a sniper
where I did it
now
wow di how could this happen you've been
revenged by
shooting I don't have enough Amo for
this actually can
we you shoot through people like your
teammates all my teammates eat my
missiles the
bullet the block
oh I don't think so okay run run run run
we're oh wait is this the
new no no no it's not yet oh
it's oh playing okay oops all right I'll
switch it I'll switch get out of
[Music]
here I thought you were my
friends what you guys prefer to stay all
in voice chat or still separating for
teams I think separa Sear
okay okay okay yeah otherwise it be too
chaotic and we
[Music]
would but every once in a while getting
together is fun
too in between you down we going to be
in a team
again oh my god well where's the
video
fun it's raining I don't like this oh
we're free of the same uh character mine
oh is it always raining in Sawmill oh no
wait how can I
change we can go over there oh hi
shorty
losers on the same team now
stop so what up Withers yeah all red
team voice CH yeah red team go into the
second voice chat red te go okay okay
yeah oh to
okay not bad ttic is nice sometimes I
could be so what's what's this game
again what's this game oh yeah sorry
this is King of the Hill rather blue
team this is what this kill the hill
King of the Hill King of the Hill yeah
yes so whoever it's like a control Point
type of map ah I see I see
okay where's the hill I'm on a hill uh I
think you should be able to see it in
the map oh I see that the map uh I mean
like through through the oh you gave me
a sorry you gave me this you gave me a
fry what the frak Yeah I'm sorry I was
on the
[Laughter]
hill I think tell the other team what
the objective is I'll be right back
suddenly appeared out of nowhere hey
hello sorry I forgot to tell you guys
it's um it's a king of the hill
objective so you want to get the control
Point yeah yeah oh okay so we have to
stay there
okay everybody hit the the all right CC
needs healing I
died start a fire there so many
fire such fire wait I want that
persective of the razor blades no got I
know interesting here we go better not
walk into the razor
blades careful with
those we
learn we live and we learn ow we live
and learn GJ on and we die and we learn
I feel like I learned most from dying
here we go better
perspective all right they just have to
capture for 3 minutes right and then the
next one
unlocks whoa I'm on
fire fire light the
fire fire fire I need healing do we have
a
bive nice
not he you it does you have to go to the
cabinet in the base there's like a
medicine cabinet yeah yeah wait is this
the wrong
room
fire I need healing they're still on the
May the enemies will heal
me you guys don't have a medic huh I
tell you is a medic yeah yeah I am oh
okay
C I tell you what they're on the hill
does that mean good job on killing the
medic is that a slang for this
game nice medic oh GG versus Liz trying
to Bonk me hey hey I Medics
are
oh good
job no you should heal yourself you're
dying heal myself I don't know probably
you have to find there's Med packs like
on the map in certain places you see
like a little
a med kit thing good job D you was
beefy say you guys can take the point
nice nice where's where are we wait
where's the pool keep going that way and
then if you make a left into the
building I didn't see anything
crony ah yes exactly yeah if you turn
left in there is the is the control
point oh you guys are going towards
their
spawn their spawn are we camping spawn
camping are we not on purpose is going
the right way watch out wrong way no
you're going the right way going the
right way there's somebody right behind
me I
see you got
[Music]
saw I guess you didn't see that I'm on
fire some we're on fire nice got the
point healing thank
you can you heal me me too yeah yeah
yeah AOE heel
when turn on your AOE
heel no AOE
heals there is if for engineer he has
like a little kit he can put down that
does AOE healing I'm going to
get
nice got him fall
get the sniper SP he's running he's
running he's running don't forgive him
are we controlling it any damage uh if
you look at the top yet so if the
timer's going down oh that we're
not oh so now they they're getting it
they're getting it oh you guys still
have it you still have it if it's blue
you guys got
it we the to go
right now they're my friend GG always
kills Scout V
Scout roasted Phoenix
down
yummy right all of them need more
seconds nice know that they have a
minute left until
yeah oh CeCe with the sniper shot so are
they in control of it now or yeah yeah
they are they are they have to hold it
for another 50 seconds a we only need 16
seconds yeah yeah if you guys get it and
you hold it for 16 seconds and you win
that
one GG is dead
nice all my
kills oh we're watching cl to the base
so that we can secure it faster Mission
ends in seconds yes wait it's not going
down got it you guys have to capture it
it's going it's going trying to come up
behind us let's go 10 seconds watch out
theal get theal get the fireal
aun wait that's our teammate whoops G's
back G's back okay she's dead it's
fine
nice oh yeah we
won this one I'll let you guys do best
of three see who wins and then yeah
that'll be the last one ice work I'm
going to go
good luck
one thank you we won once we will win
again have a second chance second chance
at Li Second Chance stay behind you okay
I okay so all right now we actually know
the objective so is the objective so I
don't know all right to to the center do
you guys see the numbers at the top
where it says 3 minutes yeah yeah so if
you guys hold one point that point for 3
minutes then you win we're we're D run
away run away run away
wait we're dying we're dying we're Dy
trying to get but it's like the Shar
points right a Shar Point yeah yeah yeah
Whoever has it makes the time go down
okay okay okay got it
Nows all right we should
coord I don't understand oh right click
the
desate okay I set them on fire surely it
helps it does it does do damage over
time Nice kill we red we want to kill
blue yeah nobody's captured the point
yet
so I think this is working well just
stay
down they know they no they don't know
they don't know they don't know I'm here
they don't know I'm here if you're in
the house come behind the the
wood you floor
okay oh two
Med it does no damage it's actually I
don't really like
it stay behind the go away go
away yeah good job good job going
away go he go here maybe maybe I go
heal ah there's too many of them I have
too many
heav yeah there's to many heav all right
I'm gonna I'm tapping in I'm gonna help
you guys a little bit
okay mom's
coming who wants a Pockets uh you are
damaged here you
gode the hide
theast [\h__\h] I thought I could I hav a
rocket jumped really I don't
know I tried go go go
oh that's you
help sorry I'm trying to kill I'm I hit
him
once no sa
sa they're so big come
here that was nice wait am I in the
wrong
team no the te team don't worry
wow
nice we hi we hi it I
died oh the lag oh what oh yeah lagging
oh
okay oh God the I guess I'll uh I'll I
actually can't move now yeah I keep
rubber banding no the saw the did you
run into it now no never
mind going to the wa for I think I see a
little bit oh yeah I I can't move at all
wait did I also die to the saw
yeah oh yeah guys come here I'm also
being clipped through
walls
no it's okay the game is trying to Nerf
us because feel better yeah they know
we're going to
win yeah a little bit better
now so are we losing or we got get the
point we're winning quote unquote
yeah they're feeling the lag too it's
okay okay we can we can get the point
here just don't run into the saw
hopefully
move second
no as long as we're on the point it's
going to be delayed
okay okay over time overtime is anybody
on the point I'm trying I was not
letting me up ah ah wait Ed out okay
it's okay we still have somebody on the
point it's okaya watch out I'm walking
I'm walking there what
overtime we got we got it we got it we
got it we can if we keep on it I'm
trying wait am I did I get Auto doing so
good go go you are the single letter oh
uhoh where are you guys I'm like a I'm
coming but I'm like I'm like rubber
banding oh my God at least
worked for the first little
bit oh this is what it feels like to
fast forward in
time should we wait until the server is
responding
then oh I think it's back it's fine it's
going good yeah it feels better now okay
for me it's like rubber bending still so
like I don't know if that's the way turn
but like yeah yeah I'm a little ball
sorry weird you weird weird that you are
little
ball you guys just need
to all right they don't have it yet but
oh they're getting it they're getting it
here we go still some time
no I don't knowed te I think they got it
they're capturing it I'm get it back
touch it touch it it's not about
it's not too
L what what if I change teams WR this
instant all right uh we can go back into
all chat and then uh I think there's
like a sandbox mode we could do and then
we'll just um yeah and we'll stop from
there all right thank you thank
you actually I don't know if there's
like a sand g guys GG GG's
yeah oh that was
laggy high tower teleporting G how do I
what's the command change gravity okay
weirdo yeah never too late never too
late never too late never too late is it
still isn't it still lagging should we
like maybe I can't move at all yeah it's
lagging yeah the lag has been really
bad can we restart gravity yeah but is
not lagging it's just stopped yeah oh it
stopped the server
stopped before it kicked us out it
disconnected and now now it's just
nothing's going yeah yeah crony also got
kicked out and for me and 's just like
moving yeah I can't move right now
same I see okay yeah um I think I could
reset the server or also I mean we
pretty much played for the amount of
time we were going to play oh true time
CL that was so fast it was so fun
I'm glad you guys have
funun thanks
of if anything we learned how to
differentiate colors which
is did we
learn you guys got better about it yeah
yeah that was
[Applause]
fun thank you I'm looking forward to
Gary's Mod thank you thank
yeah thank you so
much you still got so many games up
ahead see you thank you for
[Music]
playing byebye
byebye byebye
byebye everybody left oh do you want do
should we should I come back and like
okay you can stay oh I can stay okay the
others left I know I know I know wait
who is playing I let me check who else
is playing uh the next game with us hold
on
yes for this one I also read a guide um
oh oh nice it was a two two minute video
and it was like this is what you do so
yeah this TF2 is like a good segue into
CS cuz you know shooting and it's kind
of similar a little bit less movement
though kind of reminds me of uh I guess
OverWatch is like reminds me of it just
because of the maybe it's the aesthetic
no oh Team
Fortress Yeah no never mind it doesn't
remind me of Cs go because of the
because of the all the different classes
and stuff you know like all the skills I
don't know maybe it's like the original
the original fun one it's very colorful
yeah OverWatch is definitely inspired by
Team Fortress that it stream yeah
probably
another one is it still active do people
still play it a lot Team Fortress de I
think so yeah I I know a few people that
will just play just almost every
day must be really fun because some of
the classes are really cool I think yeah
people get really into it and there's
different game modes uh I mean we've
played a few now but there's a ton of
maps and they do like event Stuff for
holidays yeah that's really cool I think
spy was the best one it was really fun
yeah you did really good at spy in my
opinion that's the hardest class to play
it was a fun to infiltrate but it's it's
I couldn't figure out the invisibility
cloak thingy like it I didn't know how
to use it properly but it was fun it's
really cool you can unlock different
items for spy and they each do like
pretty different stuff oh yeah I saw I
saw one thing and it was like a guy had
a water a milk jar or something like as
one of the other characters is that an
item um I think there is milk but
there's also a PE jar uh oh and yeah so
the sniper has an item it's called
J and he throws this jar of yellow
liquid on himself to uh put out fire or
you can throw on other people and it
does damage
oh
ew yeah it's it's yeah oh it's nice okay
um I will jump I think oh it's people we
we don't know if she'll be back yeah and
then okay um I got to go rewind real
quick I'll be back in minutes okay no
problem by
byebye okay oh sh she's on fire I forgot
I have
that uh let me see who else was going to
join see yeah we're going to play a game
but uh some people might not be able to
that's okay
yeah yeah let me
see okay let me figure out something
else really quick if you guys could wait
one
moment hold on
[Music]
sorry typing ASR
one moment I need to count something
really quick
I'm back hello oh I'm also going to be
right back really quick okay can you
entertain the chat wait are you
streaming oh no but I can entertain your
chat thank you thank you okay all right
take my place one
second wait let me open your thingy
where are you one gu one second guys I
can't see you I can't I can't see you oh
there you are hi everyone it's me uh
little little body on top of 's
head hi did you see our laser focused um
high quality color blind Team Fortress
play hello hello oh you can even say it
with the letters cute um yeah it was fun
I really lik the game actually I was
very positiv to surprised I don't know
why I think T punes 2 is like one of
those that kind of like flew over my
head U because it I I didn't have a PC
for a really long time but but I've
always wanted to check it out and uh
yeah it was really fun I like the Spy
the most can we get some ice cream no
Shop's closed it's what day is it oh
it's Friday Shop's still
closed um Team part still very popular
to this day yeah maybe maybe maybe we
can like I'll check it out some more in
the future um and now we're going to be
playing another game uh for this one I
actually played the tutorial which was
like 12 super fast
matches um this one I started it in I
was like oh oh no this is hard this is
actually hard but it but we'll we'll
figure it out we'll manage I don't know
are we going to play against real people
or Bots I'm not 100% sure but I'm sure
it'll be fun um but yeah I really like I
really like the uh Team Fortress 2 at
least that was really fun oh
hello oh oh sh it's it's the
duck duck of we all know and love it the
dock
Froman hello wait cuz of the cuz of the
overlay
is I was trying to be sneaky oh you
thought I wouldn't know who it was or
Chad wouldn't
know you know it could be it could be
could told be you oh if only there was
someone else here um but it's just me
and
oh wait hold on hold on
it's it's me Ena it's Ina I her Ena hia
did you have fun yeah that was a lot of
fun are you going to join us I never
played before but uh oh no I just I just
I just wanted to quack
oh sorry yeah I was really fun what was
your favorite
class um sniper sniper is pretty fun
it's hard but it's hard yeah I feel like
it was difficult because you had no way
of running
away like if if they were close to you I
think the controls were kind of uh
confusing too cuz like after after you
shoot with with the scope on it like you
UNS scope and then you scop in
automatically so that if if you're used
to like other yeah yeah so instead of
like the toggle you just like you change
that maybe in but yeah it was definitely
I kept clicking it twice and I was like
ah no no stop it or when he reloads he
immediately goes into scope again even
if you haven't anything yeah but that
was really fun
too um well we weren't although we W in
the same team in the beginning oh yeah
[Music]
hello Counter
Strike no you have to quack okay there
we go oh who could it be
[Music]
oh wait that's an actual
duck that's it's a real
duck you have a
duck yeah it's me why
yes what that sound like dud stop that's
animal abuse stop it stop it rip
no let the dock be this messed up
someone call the Duck Police I'm calling
the Duck Police um hello 911 someone's
abusing ducks in here yes how many ducks
are at the crime scene please 70 70 oh
sorry we did we're not equipped for that
that uh scale you have to call the duck
FBI instead thank
you uh I useless I don't have number
duck FBI I have one for duck CIA but can
you call CIA for me I don't I don't know
if it's uh it's going to work out should
we should we try
[Music]
Okay
um how did you know that there was a
death
already there's been a murder is it cuz
you're CIA you already know there's a
death yeah we know everything uh we have
eyes everywhere in fact you're your eyes
are my
eyes what what does that mean think
about it if you really think about it
you'll figure it out okay what am I
looking at right now what am I looking
at right now your
screen that's not exactly what I'm what
am I what am I looking at what oh look
look are you looking at it I'm looking
at it you're looking at Ena I'm looking
at
Ena don't
look I'm on
pajamas sorry you're so cute I can't
stop looks at you looks at you harder
you blushing oh my God blush there
there's an emergency help help HR sexual
harassment that's a sexual harassment at
the work space help HR HR HR help help
this person won't stop harassing the
goddess stop um who would we
call Ghostbusters
B yeah I think that would help us b b
bston bust bust bust bust b mean by that
b b bust bust bust collaborate you never
seen it before no bust makes me feel
good busting busting makes me feel you
never heard seen it before I'll link
it everyone can watch it I'll put it in
uh the chat the voice chat oh hello I'm
back I don't if I'm ready welcome back
thank
you all right so we're just waiting for
oh be was here and Iris Oh yay okay well
I shall not take my Lea my job here is
done want to say hi oh hi hi hi hi oh is
your internet still
struggling yeah I'm on my
phone I mean it's 2024 can you place
your score on your phone now no I don't
think Ste
yeah maybe on like a hot spot like for
your computer if you do that that sounds
complicated imagine doesn't have a
wifi
yeah could you be oh it's not made in
this WiFi list it doesn't
work good try try W Wess W
Wess never mind
anyway I shall now take my leave my job
here is done I'll see you guys at
deadlock byebye
[Music]
byee so
cute so that's a real duck huh bust and
busting busting busting we busting where
what busting makes me feel good someone
about yeah feel good you know brought up
Ghostbusters and then CeCe say she's
never seen this video before oh I've
never seen Ghostbusters
oh wait there's a video Yeah Mei there
I've never seen Ghostbusters either I've
only seen right now vision of it you
know those uh edits where it's like a
lot of the Rings but every time they
take a step it speeds up by 5% and it
ends like a really short
video a really short movie people like
embed a whole movie like in Discord
video or something and then it yeah
they'll speed it up a ton yeah yeah yeah
I mean that's how you suppos to to to
consume those type of movies right
straight into the bra for legal purposes
I'm going to say
no yeah I would never watch something
like that you disgusting
fiend yeah I only read about that I
don't have eyes I can't watch it's okay
I don't even have Discord to be honest
so I wouldn't be able to it's forcing me
into a tutorial yeah it might be good to
do one
yeah what I st the was just dust
too uh I mean there is dust too we
probably yeah we we're going to play UND
do too that be good
practice okay let me start the game as
well too oh what I hope your your
problems are
fixed all of your problems I so many
problems I hope all of your problems get
fixed every thank you
let us know if it comes
back okay I'm going to go have fun love
you bye bye
[Music]
quack She's Gone Gone she'll be back I
hope yeah I hope so well that sucks M
internet's issues are Fe I get them all
the time so annoying
so annoying especially considering if
you think about it right you pay you pay
for like you pay for in the internet and
you pay a lot depending on where it is
and then it still doesn't work so
frustrating yeah
annoying it's kind of like uh Space
Magic so I can understand if it breaks
sometimes yeah the internet's not real
yeah how does it work anyways I still
don't understand there's giant wires
under the ocean It's Magic it's what it
is Scandal sitting somewhere all the
children run awwards out I'm making the
internet work I think yeah that's what
happens when they graduate they get uh
sent into the satellites to operate them
that's why they never learn math or like
anything else because they just have to
sit in the satellite forever I makes
sense have you seen the image of the
shark eating the cables and like M Fiber
Optic Cables M so good fiber
optic someone should make that make that
but we SC
I found it it's the most decrepit photo
of all
time for optic
cable no it's a real
picture it's a real shark oh my God I
thought it was like a meme or
something oh
man are you doing the tutorial J yeah I
don't know how to get out of it I don't
think you can actually I had to do it
too you have to complete it I can't
believe this the Bots are owning me they
don't let scrubs in this game you have
to be like a certain level you have to
know how to install and then how to like
run the tutorial why are my bots better
than their Bots it's not fair did you
turn down your mouse sensitivity maybe
that'll
help I'll do it they're spawn camping me
though I alt Tab and then they killed me
oh yeah the bot's be kind of mean I
think they would do that
is this my areio okay by the
way yes I think so oh I turn it up a
little
bit hi guys
oh yeah sounds good
okay I could I could keep going
sure no stop it you could keep going if
you'd like no no no okay thank
you okay oh yeah this game I I I learned
that that you run faster when you have
the knife apparently Lally yes yes so
that's all right how do I bunny H can
you yeah you you kind of can I think
they changed it so it's a little more
difficult now
Dam people will bind the space bar like
jump key to a scroll wheel and then
they'll just
like
oh that's a good idea let me do that no
well I mean if you
[Laughter]
want uh here I'll send you guys the code
each uh in DM to join my thingy
okay just whenever you're done with the
tutorial okay
this real
quick yeah you have to buy armor uh when
you get money so like a huge thing
people talk about this game is uh um the
economy in
game uh you don't have to buy skins or
anything like that that's what I'm
talking about but when you're in like a
match when you kill people and you win
rounds you get money right and then you
just have to spend that money
wisely um for me the private matchmaking
says game mode locked complete matches
in other game modes to unlock this one
ah we have to complete the Uber
tutorial okay but I did the tutorial
though so have to play a real game uh we
can always jump right
into maybe yeah gu we can I don't mind
jumping in we can uh at least until I
mean I guess we have to go through this
entire thing with uh Iris as well well
if she comes if when she comes yeah so
it's up to you all right here just join
my party I'll send you guys invite okay
okay I'm trying to get out of this
tutorial as fast as I can no problem
problem you just have to click on the
heads and then them all I I spiked the
plant I planted the spike I spiked the
bomb and I won the round I'm still going
how many rounds is this 12 really really
the tutorial is 12 rounds yeah
go wait I don't see the
invite oh there it is
request oh that's Spike the
plant plant the
spike trying to figure out how I can
play like private lobby type of thing
but I can't do private
matchmaking tws looking to play
[Music]
I don't know why but I always thought
this like the game looks a lot better
than I expected than I remembered well
it's didn't it get a remake with like
the
two oh is this the second one yeah it
wasn't it CS go for a really long maybe
it's fine I just want to make sure it's
like friends only type
thing so this is why it looks so much
better I don't know how make sure it's I
think I joined you this session is no
longer available never mind I see I see
you in my party I'm pretty or maybe not
here I'll send you another one in game
there okay thank you oh I see it I see
it oh oh you look nice with that shirt
wow what oh you guys wait what oh thank
you it's like you you you ready to like
chop some
wood me yeah look at your little CH wood
choer yeah it's like a flannel yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah oh I don't like how he
holds that gun towards his neck like
that you can change I think yeah your gu
is holding a little gun you can change
it oh where is it oh this little setting
thing in the bottom right corner do you
see that it says show change weapon
change weapon okay and I can change what
you have in your
thingy that's what I want can I change
my outfit too change show equipped real
AG there are skins but you have to pay
for them like real money no I won't do
it I haven't paid for Roblox I won't pay
for this you can't get me never but with
these skins you can always resell them
on the steam market for a profit yeah
that's what people do guys you know what
I know what I'm going to do for the next
hours I know some people that actually
got into skin trading and funded lots of
their stuff when they had no income I
thought you were going to say and funded
the game well yeah funded their own life
gets intense it's like real stock market
yeah it's true yeah you can make a
living off of it really yeah people will
they'll cuz you get steam money back
from it so you can buy like Steam games
and yeah and then gift that to people
for money I guess um kind of there's
like third party sites where people sell
their knives for $20,000 or like $40,000
$20,000 be right back guys I'm going to
is it is it random is it like yeah it's
like gambling right
yeah cuz you get cases but it costs like
I think
$2.50 to open each
case is that
illegal oh I don't know I think it might
be illegal in some countries
maybe
oops but I've opened cases on stream and
it was fine yeah I'm joking I'm joking
is said do you get cases normally by
just playing as well or is it only once
a week though you get like two cases
like two free cases or something a Crump
a crumb crumb yeah a crumb a Crum that's
dance M A
crumb buty crumping if you play this
game and then once a week and then you
do get lucky and you just get something
for like 20,000 that's amazing can you
get that or do you have to pay for those
really crazy ones uh you can get lucky
at ooh that's the that's you draw right
did I get one the chances are really low
though I think it's like 0 point
something chance of getting one of those
items this is just like cookie
[Laughter]
RH you guys know that what the Yeah I I
guess it's like you know it's it's it's
like those um yeah Loop books loot book
stuff I didn't know it was that much
like I know you could sell them but I
didn't know it was for that much that's
pretty
impressive yeah people get crazy with it
crazy have we played this game a
lot you going to carry us hard yeah I
have like almost 2,000 hours in this
game but I'm not that good I'm not that
good I just can play sometimes you know
no no no I I I I bet you just like
selling yourself short we're going to
get carried Chi get ready okay I'm still
in this
[Laughter]
tutorial do we um the only thing that
I'm confused about is like the money
thing in the game in the game where you
like buy weapons
do you have to do you share that money
or can you just buy or is it like your
own load out
money
uh yeah you can you do share we uh
weapon money though with the rest of
your team I think right I'm pretty sure
but you're talking about in game right
yeah yeah yeah in like once you're in
and then you you open the bag and you
can buy armor and stuff oh yeah yeah in
the in the match right yeah in the match
yeah yeah yeah yeah I think chat is
confused it's shared isn't it shared
money hold on I'm looking hold on
they're saying chat is said chat is
saying it's individual I always thought
it was shared cuz when you went around
everybody gets money
yeah but yeah it's your own bank pretty
much you're pulling from your own pocket
yeah okay okay would be kind of funny if
you had like joke items and then you
just grief it's like okay but what I'm
saying chat is that you get shared money
in terms of like when you win around
right
can you win just with a knife yeah yes
I've been in games where people are like
Knife Only Knife Only down mid
especially if the other team is like
losing really bad then that's their only
chance to have fun ooh that's so nice of
them to go with along with
it oh so like if the other group is
losing really hard then the the the ones
that are winning go Knife Only to dunk
on
them yeah
yeah all right it seems we'll have to
play without Iris for now cuz she's
still figuring out her thingy so uh G
are you still doing that
tutorial don't worry I I'm
at 10 Rounds out of 12 look what I
posted in the in the channel check that
link apparently you can skip the
tutorial if you just put in like a few
cheat
codes let me see if I can do it while
I'm here because at the rate this is
going I'm 3 minutes away from being done
oh okay
nice let's see but we should tell that
to Iris later then so she knows yeah
yeah I put it there it seems like really
easy to just skip it but just a few
steps I tried
play it wouldn't open the console thingy
for me ah you have to enable developer
console in the settings
somewhere I see I see
win the game with this easy cheat code
oh so it's like slash
Win slash Win no no it's a it's a little
more difficult than that I
think to win the
game did you at least winning in the
tutorial no I'm AFK oh but if you go in
it'll be faster
no I walk in and then I die and then I
AFK no oh okay so yeah if you go into
game settings uh then it shows it's like
the first option enable developer
console oh oh yeah that was off okay my
bad okay now we know thank
you I won I mean I lost but I'm out but
you beat the tutorial yay y
let me out let me
[Music]
out oh is it random who gets the bomb
yeah but you can drop it and somebody
else can pick it up oh okay that's good
cuz in the tutorial you you you kept
getting it because it's obviously the
others are Bots and it was a lot of
pressure yeah I think it's just to teach
the player you know like how to play it
yeah okay okay that's good then can I
get a
rein
yes oh I can't invite you for some
reason you don't show up as in the game
can you try join Do You See Me online
maybe you might be able to join me I am
unable to join you I am online let me
see if I I'm hiding it I cannot join you
either can you invite me can can
you me
see invite okay I sent you an invite oh
I got
it oh she's in yippee wait you also look
cool what is this I don't know messed up
default look like this something really
quick why do I look like this when did I
change that I mean you look cool too you
have full body armor and everything you
just saying that you just are you just
saying
okay you don't look cool you look like
[\h__\h]
actually you're fit disgusting W you're
very rude I can't believe it I look like
like I look like I'm about to jump off a
like a helicopter or something like
you're going to parachute your way down
yeah like this is just like a way out
this is just like fortnite this is just
like for where are we
dropping okay sorry Amy we're ready okay
we're going to start out with uh arms
race this is a good way to learn the
multiple weapons mhm I think it's a
private match but honestly I'm not sure
so we might get some random people that
join so I think I have my voice chat is
on really low you guys aren't streaming
though right I'm not streaming okay okay
it's fine then turn off voice chat
though I don't want to hear them yeah if
I get someone I don't want to hear a
person speak to me okay okay they
muted mute all but okay mute enemy team
okay okay
hold on let me fix one more thing I got
to fix something in my settings really
quick wait so will will we play against
real people against bots yeah we will
eventually but now we're just going to
go against bots it's they're easy Bots
oh oh you on two different
teams oh yeah should we we can be on the
same team so we don't have to kill each
other oh how do I leave it's okay I'll
join I'll join a different team I forgot
what the
wait now you left
me Noob no come back okay I'll stay
here I click on the
head yes so this this game mode you
start out with like the easiest
guns
sorry sniper I can't snipe this bot
that's standing still
I'm confused no we are in the same team
okay sorry sorry I misunderstood oh we
are I'm not on the same team as you am I
I'm on yellow team how do I swap you are
the bad one wait maybe I'm not allowed
to swap there is I don't remember the
key though it's like a weird button my
chat is there it goes there's a chicken
m they're saying m m oh I killed the
chicken on accident yeah you get a point
if you kill a chicken or actually not in
here but wait my my weapon is gone my my
sniper is gone what happened oh yeah so
it's Armory so when you get enough kills
you switch to next I was standing next
to a bot and it was really friendly they
crouched next to me and I thought it was
one of you guys and then they killed me
and it was a
bot I think I'm blocking the heal let me
move I mean how do I get sniper back
it's gone oh cuz it's arms race you only
get you only get one weapon for a little
bit until you get a kill and then you
upgrade to the next weapon oh okay
thanks
[Music]
yeah I love team death match uh yeah it
kind of is
yeah oh there's a chicken yeah you can
kill them and also if you throw like a
Fire Grenade at them they'll be cooked
they'll come out as like little
rotisserie chickens do you get HP from
it when you eat it
no you can get there like HP in this
game but only in um I think Death Match
oh
okay uh the Bots are kind of
mean I know why are the bot so
mean owie a bot is winning when when I
was doing a test match in Team Fortress
2 earlier a bot killed me and then it
emoted on me or
something a
it must have been did like a salute or
something I think the bots in TF2 can do
that yeah they start the BM
young got to ingrain it early it's mess
up is what it is owie oh
sorry Falls over for I forgot you're on
the other team um if you press M you can
switch teams but you might lose your
score okay I'm swapping okay come to us
now we're going to lose to these Bots
for sure only one person can win so oh
okay this bot is winning
yeah I like how small the map is
actually it's kind of fun yeah there's
also under part uh but just be careful
cuz there's fall damage and you can die
really
easily okay
okay so I guess this game is a lot about
like cover yeah you don't want to you
don't want to die but there's also it's
it's hard because there's some positions
where like your head is peeking out and
if your head is peeking out even just a
little bit you can also get kind of shot
through walls depending on where you are
uh one thing that's really important is
for the guns is like when you pull down
or here if you guys want to meet at like
our spawn it can show you something okay
I'm coming to spawn okay it's like where
the airplane is okay sensei teach us
Sensei hello well then let's wait okay
I'm here uh okay so you see if you shoot
in one area it starts to go up right
like try try that try shooting and see
it goes up naturally so then usually
what you're supposed to do is like burst
you can burst see it doesn't move that
much if you just burst but then if
you're shooting if you're going to hold
it you can burst and pull down to like
uh counteract the fire rate oh the like
spray yeah yeah the spray yeah oh oh
yeah the the the the what is it called
cross thingy goes opens up when you
start shooting yeah oh so because of the
recoil you want to pull it down and
different guns you have to like pull
down and like a little bit to the left
or things like that or pull down a
little bit to the right but we don't we
don't you don't have to learn that today
that's a lot killed the bot nice I mean
it's a real player what if we like lie
how's how's chck going to know how will
chat know it's a real player how they
know it's a real player oh they just put
the name as bot because they want to you
know they want to act as if they're a
bot but they're actually real players I
swear I feel like I've seen Bots or
people do that they just they're like oh
yeah I'm a bot and then it makes you
feel bad cuz you died to
them this is the type of game where the
player base would do that I think
actually can you sprint or is this the
fastest um no you can if you pull out
your knife you go faster but only by a
little
bit okay
okay and then also you want to pretty
much stop moving when you're shooting
you can kind of do it sometimes
depending on what gun you have but you
kind of have to stop and stand still
still sorry move while shooting no no no
don't move while shooting don't move the
exact opposite of that oh oh okay and
then people will also Crouch and shoot
at the same time that's supposed to help
your Crosshair not go so crazy I I have
little I have a little card on the
bottom of my screen it says six oh maybe
that's your kill streak ooh
OWI I'm killing
here Bots yeah Bots foolish stupid Bots
oh I got killed oh
no oh I got a new weapon no it's same
weapon these Bots have crazy aim oh GG
you're
winning I can't let these Bots win
you're winning you're winning you have
12 kills
[Music]
yay owie oh I died to the same bot a
chicken
back off
bot would be fun to like make an anime
or Manga or something about a bot
chicken oh no not a chicken not a
chicken I'm sure there is an anime oh
mang there has to be yeah yeah we born
in another video game like this and
their life circle and then just like
conly I that's at least a light novel or
something yeah it's got to be a light
novel My Life as a bot in
CS2 uh
I'm being used as Cannon
F life is hard something like that oh I
I read it that's kind of the it i' read
it what is it ground I'm being shot feel
like there's an anime that's airing this
season that's vaguely similar to that
really oh really a bu but it's not like
a bot they're just like you know the
hero and the villain animes but then the
villains are like Bots a they keep
killing them and they come back
oh but it's in their
POV what do you know the name maybe ch's
name chat probably knows the name hen I
think it's henchman
oh not free guy free guy with ran
Reynolds looking it up that's that
that's the
anime yeah I remember I remember he a
he's a big eyes probably he could be an
enemy
character Romancing NPC honestly if you
wear an MC in a show like that would be
really difficult though probably would
be nicer to be a side character because
the MC's they just have too much going
on seems yeah stressful you can just
chill respawn whatever
yeah I think if I was in in isai I would
want to be like a cook or something a
what cook cook oh oh oh my maybe a
doctor something that they need to rely
on yeah wait that's just like real life
wait a
minute wait so I have a place in
society so I have money to feed my
children I had to go deep into my mind
Palace it's called um go go loser
Ranger oh oh just like free guy yeah
just like Ryan
Reynolds Oh you mean Ryan goling Ryan
goling Ryan what what are we talking
about Ryan Ryan Reynolds Ryan
Reynolds why would you bring him up have
to get a nice kill cuz it's the same guy
be careful if you see a bot with a knife
uh that's the last weapon in whoever
gets the last kill with the knife
wins oh that's how it oh
owie okay it's all G up on the the The
Knife Guy well don't get too close to
him no we lost two Bots the bot is so
good oh nice you're on the leaderboard
though nice yeah we're on the board wait
how do you get you get most kills but
you didn't win what the heck I don't
know it wasn't swapping my weapons I
guess ah maybe
yeah well uh we should probably try
playing a casual match I
think oh are we going to play with
randoms or is it three is it three team
possible might be a bad idea to play
casual match with
randoms why we really good what do you
mean you guys against the butts let me
see if there a private lobby I can do
one second
you guys can keep playing for a moment
okay I'm trying to I got to find a way
to do I want to show them like dust too
but well it's okay we can just mute the
we can do practice casual what if we do
practice competitive you're going to
type mean words to me I know it I've
seen them before I've seen mean words I
I know what you but but you can just
answer you you should just like you know
copy paste what they're saying but
putting it ination Mar and then in
Brackets but in a dumb voice I don't
think I don't want to repeat what
they're saying though what if they're
saying a really bad
word wow you're really bad at this game
wow you're really bad at this game okay
should be stop repeating what I'm saying
stop repeating what I'm saying this only
works if we in good faith believe that
they won't say an even worse word than
we oh oh oh we can't repeat okay okay
then s invite
okay I accepted it yay that's true oh we
just replace the evil words with like
really cute
ones so true there's only cute words you
can you can you can fight hatred with
love
Yeah Peace Love on the planet Earth
peace love and
CS2 all right love let me know you guys
oh pick uh we'll do Seaside terrorist
terrorist first terrorist okay okay all
right and then there should be Bots that
fill up the rest of the lobby I
think
nice yeah so okay let me show you I'll
give you guys a tour here follow me yes
all right so this way if we go this way
this is a site that over there is spawn
so you just spawned right there this
this goes into a long we're not going to
go all the way down there but there's
two doors here now here come back mhm
and then over here this is m middle this
is the middle area uh and sometimes if
you jump down from Spawn you can snipe
people through there like through this
door cuz their spawn is over
there oh okay and this call out this one
is called cat like catwalk but people
always say this is cat this is cat and
then it goes around here continues to
asight right and this is where we put
down the bump in the red circle square
uh yeah right here Circle okay okay okay
yeah and then this one is called ramp
cuz you know it's yeah it goes down and
that one over there is called pit and
that's the other side of where the door
is the cat in front of a ramp pit what
was the one with the long door not long
just long long okay okay yeah and this
is their spawn so this is where they're
going to
start I think I think more Bots will
fill up the rest of the team I'm not
sure all right right this way this
way okay all right so here was the other
end of mid doors like if you go if you
look through the door you can see where
I was shooting before so they can snipe
you and you can snipe them yeah yeah
okay mhm and then over here this is B
site um and this is the other site to
plant the bomb yeah how do we know which
one they're on do we see them on the map
uh no no well we're attacking so we're
going to you know pick a site to go to
and plant the bomb okay yeah I think we
might be going against only one
guy a real guy or
we're one guying him I don't I don't
know
Spirit he this is good practice we we'll
practice and then we'll play a real
match against probably real people SC
can we have a team name okay sure let's
follow
GT um I'm going a I'm going a everyone
yeah going long doors going long doors
I'm going straight into there I clear
clear I'm going a sight don't worry he's
not he's not anywhere who the bomb I
have I have the bomb cuz it just
W he's he's nowhere
here don't worry guys I'm watching I'm
watching oh yeah so that's cat I'm
watching cat watching cat at the
internet cyber cafe okay oh yeah I'm
going to go to the other side then I'm
going to watch ramp no I'm going to
watch the D oh he's there he's in spawn
he's not moving C
CT isn't he supposed to be doing
something lazy bot I killed him what a
lazy bot okay well we're going to play a
real match on this map the same map so
it's good to learn it anyways oh okay
pretend yeah keep pretending it's a real
game okay yeah you have to buy so if you
yeah open up the buy menu I can show you
guys like some smoke there's like
specific places you can throw the
smokes okay I purchased a smoke oh wait
H why am I not with you guys where'd you
go oh I'm on the other team oh you got
did you get Auto balanced oh my God but
I'm all alone I don't even have a I
don't even have a bot oh no it's over
wait am I defending I'm defending okay
okay I have a I'm going to Smoker okay
Chad snip for me no I'm
kidding I'll do the call thr a smoke out
this door because it kind of blocks off
their visibility oh like if there's if
there's people we're going be you're
wondering you okay I'm going to go b as
well I feel like that seems reasonable
now Gigi has the bomb she might plant it
can you hear me when I'm running yeah
yeah so if I'm if you're close by yeah
if you hold shift you walk and that's
people are do that all the time you just
walk uh when you think the enemy team
can hear you wait you actually went B I
hate you why would I lie to you what you
mean I thought said it on
purp did you go to a yeah of course I
went
well I planted at be you're
wondering ah
ow okay hey I got her I got one person
nice nice we
traded okay is there I guess it wouldn't
be possible for you to switch to the
other team huh no this is okay if you
press M you can switch and
then hold on there might be a command to
add Bots let me see chat what's the
command something I can type in chat for
if I press M it just lets me like
select I
don't count to terrorist Okay Okay g
which one are you going this
time um I'm looking right at a
site let me or is it B you guys can One
V one I'm trying to pick something I
didn't buy anything I forgot to buy well
let me go back there there's a little
bit of by time so you have you have some
time oh it says it has expired by
I forgot to okay GG it's pistol versus
pistol let's up on the catwalk let's
knife knife only knife only only wait
how do I change okay Knife Only okay I I
don't have the bomb either so
oh well let's
just first one to knife winds sorry you
guys can't watch
chat the one who knifed first knif last
oh no okay okay now we have weapons
let's do
this
okay did that
work hold on you're going down you're
going down you're smaller than me you're
going down M taught me where to smoke so
if you're not careful I'm going to smoke
you did you remember to buy it yeah I
bought the smoke I'm going to smoke
exactly where she told me to smoke
[Music]
bot I'm smoking ow I
took my knees oh it's hard sorry being
here what it command again bot wait bot
ad where the heck did you go it just
says it kicks player left game kick play
server but it doesn't actually kick
anybody oh was the fall damage was the
fall damage I have to put in a number
oh you have to buy it again cuz you died
wait do you keep your stuff because yeah
cuz I
lived my Eon is higher than yours oh
[Music]
no wait the person that's talking in my
walkie-talkie has like an accent I can't
understand them he's like these boys
have a walkie talk it's like a Scottish
accent they have cool an
Arsenal do do you I have an Arsenal
where are you not sure it's not working
um uh I'm at the long disable auto
balance why are you long I'm long I am
long I have did I hit you I tried
flashbang it hit like the corner of my
eye yeah all right well it hit me a
little bit okay now I have to find oh I
don't want to play a real G I didn't
have the
B now I have to find out I'm she's going
to kill you if you're not careful she's
going to get you I'm back from doing
what I was doing okay nice yeah I I
killed her well she killed me twice and
I killed her once but I have to find you
and I don't know where you are um I'm
going
along
no oh you had a grenade you could have
thrown this I didn't have one I didn't
have enough money I think you picked up
GG's usually you'll pick up like one
enemy item oh really yeah that's cool I
dropped my C4 on accident oh yeah you
can drop stuff by pressing
g g
G's all all right um I'll show you guys
um let me buy some smokes and
stuff all right we're going to meet
we're going to be friendly smooth yeah
yeah that's really cool I remember this
game being so crunchy but now it's so
smooth why she that's probably your
PC my PC you're is right I always had
terrible terrible PC when I tried
playing this once oh I knew it all we
meet friendly friendly meet friendly
meet up here I'm going to show you guys
something over here in Long in long okay
I'm in long I think oh this might not be
long you're not I heard you're not there
she is oh here I
am I guess I'm
I flashed myself yeah you have to look
away if you look away you don't get
flashed all right I'm going to show you
guys the smoke this might be important
cuz we're going to play a match okay so
you see look look over there there's a
gold tooth on the building do you see
that yeah yeah so if you make your smoke
hit that
watch look how it bounces and now say
you're pushing from long and now look
the CT spawn area is smoked off and you
can get to sight oh
wait wait wait I want to try is it g uh
yeah oh no uh you just have to press
whatever number your nade is on and then
you just throw with mouse one okay okay
do I have to stand in a specific spot or
uh no just wherever you think you you
have to you have to overshoot it a
little bit so put it a little bit above
I missed you have did I can't see the
truth aim higher aim higher I count see
the to
now okay wait let's wait a little bit
there only 5 Seconds
try oh that was close that was close
this would do I mean you could run
through the smoke I mean it's a little
dangerous but that's good try good try I
won the
round you would have made it if you if
you saw the the tooth so it was my bad
no it's
okay uh let's see next time there's
other smokes that are really complicated
but I don't know how to I don't know
them and I don't know how to show them
so I guess we'll just practice shooting
uh yeah practice shooting for now and
then we'll join after a few rounds a
real match
nice wait I'm
smoking I can't believe you're not even
going to let me try the BM you're going
to em me am said we were practicing
shooting I was
friend oh it looks like you were about
to box
someone look and now you're an [\h__\h]
after I ran by you friendly with the
nade you won't even let Abby kill
you sorry sorry yeah you always got to
check your Corners GG you could have
gone out the doors and you know turned
left I made direct eye contact with her
I just didn't think she'd kill me sorry
okay I won't kill you this
time let's go way I looked her in the
eyes and she killed me when I looked her
in the eyes it's cold blooded killer
cold blooded killer Steve CC CC
I I won't do it again I'm sorry I'm
flash Bing you this
time wait I'm going to flashbang you you
can't you can't do it no yeah I can I me
can I flashbang her yeah you can y we're
we're on B site though GG planted the
bomb you're not careful I'm going to
flash you no don't flash me don't want
that I'm going to flash you where are
you so I can Flash
you terrorist win oh nice head shot I
heard her I heard her footsteps yeah
listening is really important in this
game oops didn't mean a ping
pinging I lost all my stuff this is
messed up so this is what happens when
you die huh yeah go go go this was an e
guy they moled me who threw that
Molly Molly on side a I know in spawn
Molly in
spawn I'm going to go
cat she's here she's here she has a
sniper don't worry I'll flashbang her
and then she won't know that you're
there yeah keep going that way I think
you'll see
her I hear her I blinded
myself where are you where are you come
get flashed I I pinged her I pinged
her can you P
again I see I I see I see I
see ah help oh I I'm flashing
myself okay okay okay she's not going to
see this coming and not only that I'm
going to do this too
flash I can't see oh my God that is
bright like in real life that flashbang
to
me I have no this no
way no she got me nice shot
thank you I was Smoked by my own
smoke you don't know this but she's
planting
has
damn how much time do I have now uh 40
30 seconds yeah something like that
30ish 30ish now
damn no she hit you like 10 times and I
don't think you should fire a shot at
her I did yeah it's hard you have to
zoom in right oh you were sniping her
yeah yeah yeah she had the all right how
about you snipe this here here uh use
this
one sorry cat my internet is [\h__\h]
okay I'm going to snipe you next here if
you jump down here you can it has a skin
too thank you for the
[Laughter]
skin okay meow meow thank you for this
skin first you need a special Discord
roll oh yeah yeah no worri is my Discord
kitten okay okay okay snip snipe battle
snipe battle snipe battle snipe battle
snipe battle snipe battle no
it's cuz you Peak the corner if you go
to Mid doors you know like uh CCE like
to the right when you spawn mhm yeah GG
will peek there I think that'll be good
yeah oh this way you guys can learn how
to peing well I
mean
like okay okay I'm peeking I'm peeking
the left one or the top one the big in
the middle like where you see here look
down the doors look down the doors oh
you smoked
I'm peeking I'm peeking oh okay okay I
see it thanks you see it you see it
she's she's she's not going to play by
the
rules oh she got me the smoke
nice did you hear her
land uh I saw her walking out of the
smoke oh I couldn't see anything cuz I
was still smok no sorry oh you were up
there okay okay
that's fun I like the snipe it's really
hard but it's oh sorry yeah it's super
satisfying
yeah okay
okay there's also uh if you guys want to
practice with the P90 the SMG is that's
like the spray and prey people use it a
lot it's like running gun that's the one
I was using before yeah it's not really
long range though it's kind of like like
mid to mid-range
yeah okay I switch I switched to it
P90 has a
sniper it's okay I'll just how do you
there's no way if you're not careful I'm
planting on
B you going to B I'm planting on B ah
they mollied me they moled me I got
moled there is no enemies other than me
so you're just shooting yourself she
moled me
how do I take away the bumb now oh you
have to diffuse it I don't have a
diffuse thing oh you don't need one try
diffusing it try diffusing it okay okay
okay I I won't shoot you let me
see yeah you just press e on it oh it's
over here it
[Laughter]
is oh I'm doing it
hello I'm
here oh welcome back I
feeling feel well I'm not going to let
you
win people please help me they're
ganking on me 2v one is
unfair now's the moment of truth did you
play the tutorial no that's okay there's
a guide on how to skip it yeah I'm going
to use the guy to skip I'm Starry okay
okay nice nice Skipper Skipper Skipper
Skipper oh now we switch sides this is
half
oh now you have to I'm not going to
interfere I'm not going to
interfere until I die oh hi no when I
when you die I'll die oh hi hi oh hi oh
hi oh hi oh hi okay what are you
planting what are you planting what are
you planning on planting B are you
planting B planting on uh
ay I the problem is I don't know who's
am and who's gigg so if I shoot one of
you I'm sorry oh I'm just standing still
so if I'm standing still it's me uh if
I'm I'm standing still so I'm standing
still it's it's yeah did you probably
just stand still and is that you em me
I'm standing in the
corner I didn't
shoot can't believe
it is this a bad
timeit what the
tutorial you're
a we're just playing against each other
oh wait uh is it too late for us to join
no time yeah join how do I
join also your your Reverb is on you
sound so holy and beautiful sing pardon
me
sorry oh wait did you
play um I did I did the skipper Skipper
okay nice nice yeah okay I'll send you
Skipper Skipper right now to so I don't
know how to play that's okay okay we're
learning the
just a two of us I don't think I can
invite you unless you're in game huh I'm
I'm in the game oh see if you can join
me it says I can invite you ah I can
also trade with you uh no that's okay
let me see don't want to give me your
stuff all right we're going to go back
to the lobby okay you guys can leave the
game after you kill each
other wow I can't believe it would say
that oh it just it it kicked me out so
I don't have to kill her okay but you
totally could I'm going to restart my
game cuz sometimes he does that I can't
see people
online am I offline I might be offline I
don't think so I think it's just a steam
bug or
CS2 you seem to be offline on my end as
well am I I might just be offline yeah
maybe oh wait I see you I can invite you
oh I'm invisible
yay okay people I can also invite nice
yeah so if you just at the top like
there's a thing that says uh wait hold
on let me look at the thing again since
you're going to be the lobby leader so
you have to do it oh sorry should I good
okay okay
okay just uh if you click on play it
says
practice are we together we're together
MH I see it
oh and then yeah just click on Dust two
and make sure the part's closed you see
that little
thingy play practice dust two open Party
Clos okay okay but bibo isn't in yet
yeah we can wait we can wait okay I
think I did
it okay I did it nice yeah you killed
them all
yay full
Squad all right yeah we could start and
then uh this will be good practice yeah
okay so I go play Dust open party is
turned off what are we practicing for
are we going to play against real people
um maybe yeah I think we can hold on
where you know where it says uh casual
so it says practice and then oh I
already press oh that's okay this is
death match so there's no planting and
we're just killing each other we're
killing each other should I just go back
uh we can kill each other for a little
bit that'll be good to get a hang of the
gun oh my sensitivity oh the chickens
explode hey hey
hey okay so we all a bot killed me damn
that bot I need my settings can you not
adjust settings in the game oh you you
can yeah I must adjust please please
don't kill me oh it's
restarting oh my gosh why is it so why
is it so hard oh so this is the same as
earlier ow ow bot how I didn't know the
bot would spawn there
never know what these Bots yeah I never
know what can you get I think it's
random oh yeah just SP was a random you
a friend you're not a friend oh sorry
there's no friends in Death Match I
missed
you you can you can still buy as soon as
you spawn if you don't want random
weapons
sorry I'm baby I'm learning I'm sorry
I'm sorry I didn't know is
you like I look like a bot didn't
I we all look the same
fin all right I I'll jump when I see one
of you guys and then I won't shoot you I
missed sniper
rough this is my Hill I can't ads with
this I he with my yeah some weapons you
can't a SC B
slingshot you can switch
gun
no I'm always scared of jumping down and
taking fall damage my knees they're not
how they used to
be crunch sound this a football I don't
think there's anywhere on this map where
you could jump and die I'm pretty sure
maybe the pit and long oh my
Crosshair bot me bot
me this you see
this killed bot May for
you thank
you oh what the
heck ooh this is a cool gun I think I
haven't gotot it yet
i r the corner got shotgun
apologies me thank you I think I just
saw you spawn in again did I I don't
know get away from me with your
shotgun give me a rifle there's so many
chickens yeah death mat if you shoot the
chickens you do get like a little some
points oh iris is
on do we want Iris I can di out
wait actually no wait wait I I just
skipped the tutorial but wait wait wait
a sec like how do how do I join the
thing you to get invited in that was
powerful wait wait replay training show
almost ready to play on I don't think we
can do 33 yet cuz we can't do private
matching don't start searching do a
Lobby start searching don't join the
random one don't join the
random leave Lobby okay ow
apologies you got revenge I don't think
you're actually
sorry oh yeah you killed me I did that
was that was Revenge getting good head
bot me c me I'll get bot me for you I'm
going back to bot me you're going to one
I got bot me for you thank
you oh when you move oh this makes sense
help I just spawned all right let me fix
something this sniper's so heavy those
down shot you in the leg sorry is it
possible an invite Iris mid game uh I
until next game try try try inviting her
she might be able to kick a bot
out oh okay I'll do that who's doing
that who's doing that wait let me hide
and then try inviting her thank
you uh I don't think we're friends hey
oh we might not be friends I don't
think wait a sec
um wait wait are we
friends I should be friends with one of
you at least wait letom me check oh no I
don't think we're friends I want to be
friends too I see you I see see okay
okay yes we're friends we're friends I
was can you invite her did you get it I
got it I got it I got it yeah okay nice
we're friends yay friend
yay I was tabbed out excuse me
you oh no hi ah stop
it
o it's tell me it failed to join game I
think I might have to wait until you
guys finish we're we get off yeah yeah
we can start a new Lobby I I think the
lobby Max might be five people but uh
I'll leave oh I don't mind oh no don't
worry I'm playing deadlock after too so
I'll get some food okay okay okay all
right I'll leave the game goodness okay
okay me too exit to main menu oh wait
are we leaving yes yes let see if I can
invite you guys maybe cuz then we can do
uh quick practice we'll do one online
game against real people after we
practice one
[Music]
more
bye real
people this we're going to kill real
people in game in Minecraft I haven't
played this game at all let's go wa can
anybody invite M I don't see her online
on mine I should I don't see online NE M
I got her I I why does c Cil has always
got me I got got my
back
W oh my gosh wait that look it on made
it looks like you what that what me yeah
your person oh my my tea guy yeah it
looks like you a the the shirt is that
it no the eyes oh right the eyes and and
arms got really pretty eyes oh wow thank
you yeah I've been working out wow wow
man he didn't the chip and the
shoes all right we're going to try this
hopefully it works I hope the controls
are like regular FPS games yeah it is
yeah it is okay I hope it puts us know
how to sh I don't
know practice against
spots Carry Me team carry me no you
carry me
B all right this is just a practice I
don't know how to do like a five stack
against bots maybe we might have we CH
counter Terror or try try joining my
team I'm on CT yeah try Jo okay
okay for me it says there are too many
CTS so it seems like I can't join you so
I'm going to join terrorists okay okay
oh I'm also we got I'll give them the
same TR hold on we'll meet up in Middle
okay I'm going to show you guys let's
create Terror all right IR follow me
this is mid doors so down here through
those doors I get that gun oh shoot can
you choose doors okay yeah oh wa can
join the tour as well since she wasn't
there earlier oop no shoo
shooting all right stand still don't
move I got her
gun oh my God she's stabbing you
punishment are you not dying please
punish me for wait would you like me you
oh yes please oh that actually me o that
the mark use a knife how do you use the
knife scroll to it yeah oh apologies I
deserve part of the
lesson okay who want to there's no
Friendly Fire uh there is in in like the
real game that we're going to play but
there's not oh they respawn okay that's
good I we warm up okay okay we'll meet
up over
here use different guns is that possible
oh to buy like back where we spawned
in I see okay so this is the tea spawn
that's what it's called here okay this
is where the terrorists are going to
spawn and they can go three ways right
if you go this way that means you go mid
you're going middle and then there's
long so we'll go down long first down
this way oh we're going to warm up uh
the warm Up's ending the scenic route
yeah okay we'll uh meet up again we win
okay no we don't no this was the warm up
that was the warm up wait are we
actually starting are we actually no go
go down long go down long we'll do a
tour of the map and then we can play a
few rounds and then don't shoot each
other okay don't shoot each other don't
shoot each other how can you tell wait
is it friendly fire on in this I got my
KN it's it's not I have a
bomb don't play it okay let's meet up
let's meet up okay so this is long doors
see this is the other side of where we
going yeah it's like the uh it's like a
mirror of the other side right I have a
bomb careful be nice be nice to me I
have a bomb all right so there's also
this pit area this is what it's called
the pit the pit yeah if you jump from up
there down you'll take some fall damage
don't do that oops oops I didn't mean to
drop my gun oh you can just walk over it
or press e on it yeah oh okay okay all
right now we go back down long this way
oh I should have bought a smoke to show
you guys that's okay usually people will
smoke this area right here that way you
can cross over cuz the CTS can see you
like say tside they're attacking they're
going to plant the bomb on a site over
here right this is a site so wh would
plant the bomb try plant it and then
scroll away now scroll off of it what's
the bomb but wait scroll off of it yeah
yeah yeah I'm just saying that so you
don't actually plant it oh oh I see you
don't want me to actually okay I'll hold
if you have the bomb you just press
Mouse one and it'll plant I'm pretty
sure or no is it e it's it's I hold
Mouse yeah it's just Mouse one yeah
Mouse one okay
now uh let's continue on to the tour the
number key but it said it was working is
it not was I about to like detonate it
on myself what no you can't you can't
okay so this like goes to Mid this is
like they call this cat oh this is on
cat on cat Okay on Cat and then it goes
to Mid doors and this goes to like where
the CT spawn right this is where we
started oh
this okay okay okay wa and we'll go this
way and this is the other site there's
only two sites so this is the so main
goal is just to kill the enemy team as
much as possible or yeah and also we
want to plant the bomb I'll let you guys
play a few rounds no don't don't don't
don't don't not yet not yet we'll do it
we'll do it okay counter terrorists win
[Music]
wait this is tunnel this is tunnels all
right you guys can play for real now
watch I'm planting this bomb can I buy a
gun yeah press B and then it'll open up
the buy menu you want to buy armor if
you can afford oh okay you can never AFF
armor in the first round usually yeah oh
I don't have any money oh my gosh this
game is like
valerant okay okay let's let's not too
close together we got to figure out
which way they're going they're might
going A or B those are the options we
got to be sneaky
sneaky sneaky oh yeah so usually if
you're on CT side it'll be like oh let's
send two people to a site and send two
people to B site
magic it puts out the fire
thanks I I got her kill kill nice nice
no there's another
one
got I thought you were I thought you
were I killed them nice job thank you I
thought you I like saw you then I peaked
away that grenade was like a one time
used thing okay yeah yeah grenades one
time yeah
and you can throw it really far you can
throw it like over the map got M do you
uh okay okay nice I'll just watch they
came from the left for this time maybe
they'll come from the other side the
next time maybe bio should go be B for
Boo and Iris go a okay where's a again
yeah this is a so like you go over here
way and then if you see an enemy you're
going to want to call it out or you can
also ping like that like middle Mouse
button okay I can like the middle Mouse
right that one
yeah on
beable IR saved
me it's okay it's okay oh I
can't the P90
sucks so does bib have the bomb now
since she
didn't only I think it's just yeah only
te can pick up the bomb drop it I didn't
have it oh hey we're looking for
somebody the
El uh you can't I hear
Tyler didn't you see her no she was
behind me no no no is absolutely
murdering
us
w Wait okay I'm going to switch guns
what gun do you guys
like I like the usually uh on T side
people always buy the AK and on the CT
side people buy the M4 what does the CT
side mean oh CT counter counter
terrorist yeah that's the one we
are I did like stick together and
there's also snip totally STI together
okay let's completely 100% stick
together yes let's do that I'm going to
stick together I'm going to stick to bio
Like Glue wait wait actually we should
stick together they're banging up come
okay let's stick together let's actually
stick
together I don't see him I see some one
I see some
one why don't you
die oh my go turn okay I've learned I've
learned my lesson that turning around is
not
good I think you guys are almost ready
we'll play a few more rounds turning
around slows you down a little yeah a
little bit if you're getting shot you
also get slowed
down but when you do shoot it's good to
kind of you can Crouch while shooting
and stop walking and you're aim will be
uh it helps with the recoil crouching
helps with recoil I to buy and and not
walking while she you can still buy H
right you can't walk that's what I'm not
used to uh freaking
OverWatch what oh and Iris so if you if
you use that gun if you keep shooting it
you want to pull down with it cuz the
recoil makes it go up right pull down
okay it like do burst like do you have
the bump
okay oh Dam they're they're on people
they're on
a side on
be wait wait wa wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait oh it's you is everyone
huh wait was it you on yes yes okay sto
don't mind me I'm not going to shoot
you oh that's still you no that's not me
that's not me that's not me ow who is
that oh that's
that oh here I you can jump up this you
got to press Crouch and jump at the same
time ow okay okay you mhm and we're
supposed to go find I'm planting the
bomb find people to kill never wait I I
messed up I'm
not
it kill
me terrorist
yay I have been jumped nice oh can we do
one practice run we're going to let them
plant on asite and then have Iris and
biu try diffusing uh that way we get an
idea of how to diffuse you guys like a
button that shows up on the screen when
you're in the diffuse zone or uh yeah I
think e will show up but it should say
like diffuse but just so you know yeah
this good practice you have to hold it
for cuz we're counter we're supposed to
diffuse okay that makes sense come to as
site and plant what gun do you have CC I
have just now I don't actually
accidentally brought a different one uh
MP SD no shooting when I'm here oh yeah
hold on they got to plant the bomb first
hold on oh yeah okay oh yeah don't shoot
us we're here to plant bom
us we welcome we welcome this is a
tutorial please we come in peace we come
in peace you may be planting bomb but we
come in peace we come in peace peace try
but then don't finish it what what is
the buttton yeah try maybe okay now if
you scroll or walk away it'll stop oh
okay got it okay let me try there we go
now you have to hold it for oh I have to
hold it oh yeah so if you hold it for 10
seconds then you get successfully
diffused am I going to make it in time
like five four three two oh no oh no I'm
going
to no that's the yeah the beeping will
get really fast if it's going to explode
it'll be like get him get him get him
the moment we're done all right I'll let
you guys play another round for real two
more rounds for real for real for real
okay I like this weapon which one is it
it's the MP5 SD I'm going to try that
one it's like very accurate like it
doesn't spray I feel at least I might be
wrong don't listen to
me he what are we doing this time we're
planting the bomb and then they they'll
try to diffuse oh we're going to do that
again okay no no noing for real we're
playing for real this time oh we're
playing for the real this time
okay okay and then if you guys press
shift you can walk around and you walk
really quietly you got to be sneaky
otherwise they can hear you sneaky cat
hear our footsteps cat cat if you don't
hear beeping on one site that means it's
on the other site I see them oh you see
them both no
oh they're on a site they're on
aite are we on a side no you have to
come to
a yay they are on or they on they're on
a side uh does it bomb kill me I'm too
close yeah I think you you lose your
weapon I think it's like valerant so you
lose your weapon I think terrorist you
don't have to walk
everywhere like where was the bomb again
uh yeah yeah so you were on B site
before so because there's only two sites
then if you don't hear the beeping there
you got to go to the other site oh okay
yeah one more
round
[Music]
okay thank God
wait is there a fire I don't know I
don't want to test in the game in the
real game there will be a oh okay okay M
don't shoot me
okay sh quiet quiet quiet they'll never
they'll never know
quiet oh
I'm so not used to shooting and standing
still sorry I was trying not to get in
the
way go mama you can do it who did I kill
oh I killed
CeCe I'm
scared what gun do you have
fo she will not answer
what am I up against the secrets wait oh
it's timed of course it
is shoot I don't remember where it is uh
CE I don't remember it'll be on the map
it'll you'll see on the map the map I
see the oh I see go to a I'm going to
make it no
don't I she it's okay wait oh I thought
30 seconds 30 second go go run run run
oh no you got it it's okay is it yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah keep going keep
going it's not
okay they're going to kill me oh why is
it working keep holding it nice nice
nice nice nice bomb has planted and now
run wait but they're here too bad too
bad it's going to go off oh wait they're
diffusing
it she diffuse it wait
wait how long is it
I think it's like 30 something seconds
seconds I thought I was
good so on CT side you can also buy a
diffuse kit which instead of 10 seconds
it'll take 5 Seconds nice okay okay one
one more round last round last round for
real I thought I was set I want to
survive you almost did it I shouldn't
have said where you were going she would
have not known I shouldn't have said
wait defuse it I have known anyone I was
wasn't do so I was like okay got to ate
that we almost got
her it's okay we got
this is that is that such a thing as
like a a letter bias like do people
always go to one letter first yeah yeah
on T side people always are like oh B
Rush B Rush oh oh that's the song Rush B
yeah yeah Rush B Rush B ding dinging
bomb has been
planted I got I got cat
walk I got nothing it's kind of hard to
infiltrate a sights cuz if you go
underneath they'll be able to see you
right so uh you could go around or you
could go this way yeah but just be
ready I'm in the open I should not you
can only jump on the other side
oh finally my revenge they're on a
hurry oh
it's damn it
y
Flash oh dang that still reaches me over
here oh yeah the the radius is really
big wa all right so we're are you guys
kind of ready we're going to let real
game we'll figure it out we
got exit and then I'll buy you guys
again
[Music]
okay oh
boy it'll be find
over oh boy I'm going to I'm just going
to be running around like a
chicken I can't wait to find Chicken In
the game so you maybe you can like blend
in I can blend in with the
chicken you'll see people will wait on
corners and just kind of so it's good to
just kind of hide a little bit you know
explode if you shoot them
M please poor chickens okay I'll invite
her come here M join
us we need a chicken take me take me I
took you put you
there
okay I like how I they kind of posing I
also like how with five people we could
be like it says I have to yeah I see
this I forgot we can't play uh one
second let me see something
what is there a is there a code hacked
for this too I don't think so okay we're
going to we're going to play a casual
game but just uh make sure you have
voice chat off how do you do that how do
you you turn that off in the settings uh
you can there's like a little search
thing in settings you can do that yeah I
want to play competitive voice I
realized that you have to be it says
must unlock this game mode by completing
Vol zero yeah zero and make sure your
own voice chat is off too how do you
turn that off dis go to disable like
audio
your uh voice microphone mode and then
just disable it voice microphone mod ah
push yeah it's push to talk so it should
be fine unless I I'll just disable it
just in case okay I disabled it yeah I
disabled it okay I'm going I do not want
to talk to people
no okay I disabled it as well is there a
text chat uh yes communication never can
we be toxic like yeah I'm going to block
the chat so it's okay
okay oh oh I'm ready yeah I'm ready
to your mom so your
mom that's too far I'm sorry I should
have I shouldn't have what what did his
mom do they're why is it always the mom
what about the dad what about the dad
dad sucks that's messed up your
grandparents Su your grandad sucks I
I've W better how about you suck your
whole family tree sucks and that's
that's something you can know for
sure yeah that's true you shouldn't have
descendants cuz they're all going to be
born
stupid what about what about what about
I hope that your pillow is always warm
no matter how many times you flip it
some people I hope your pillow is always
wet okay with what what with tears with
tears all let's join T tside first T
side okay okay this is good we're going
against bots okay we pretend it's a real
game is it a real game is it a real game
or is it not a real game it's kind of
like a real game we'll treat it like a
real game how do you how do you use text
chat uh oh y is for all and you is for
team only oh oh I see them why is for
all I see I see oh shoot oh oh wait I
turn being toxic well we're just warming
up this isn't the real game yet yeah
okay okay I can't hear my game at all
wait what I do what did I do did you
turn off all yeah there's no way I did
that what the heck that would be
silly
ooh what
is oh apologies
I tip Ted you there's so many oh are
they just the same ones wait is that
no can't hear anything I know what oh
when you have a sniper and you zoomed in
when you move the cross yeah get fuzzy
oh fuzzy get
dizzy be okay okay I want to adjust this
now or later
we're spawn capping them uh oh we have
somebody oh this is their spawn oh
absolutely bullying them wait here I
want to adjust this why can't I hear
anything
anymore I miss what I do oh that's what
I
did all right it's kind of we might I
hope it's not Auto balance one of us
might get uh Auto balance have the bomb
Auto balance next
round where do I go where' I put it
where' I put it you put in b or a let's
go to B wait there's a real person
who's
jodler real person there's a real person
in the enemy team can actually actually
say he's playing with bot who is Jo
Jer don't their name that's he's
probably him he's probably Joe oh no
wait oh wait it's different for me is it
oh is it a bot
then this guy's name is Rob for me the B
I can't shoot I got
you I'm going protect the bomb against
my
baby oh there's so many oh I do ape
we're winning we're winning nice nice
wait is it uh is it so friendly fire is
on now uh on this game mode no on this
game I think head keep going friend it
made a Splat noise when I hit you in the
leg apologies
yeah oh you can go under the floor it
sounded like they're on the
what terrorist y oh nice Iris
nice just standing there all right some
one of us might get switched the other
team I hope it's
me it's oh no oh oh they switched okay
we're
good oh wait I do see a Joe all right
where do you guys want to go um sorry uh
wherever let's go long let's go long
wherever the wind takes us
already got around
nice what are they shooting
at themselves I can hear them shooting
already wait who has the bomb I have the
bomb I messed up the
smoke a distraction it's a distraction
all good okay I I have catwalk they're
not even here I'm going to look out I'm
going to
look I am bom protect the bomb I am bomb
where they all go are they are they
they're shooting each other I don't see
anyone maybe they all went B for they're
up
here where's
here there they they're on b side
they're coming from b
side oh long long long long I got it oh
nice other there how' you guys already
have four nice guns what the heck uh I
think we had money
do they were born with a run I'm want to
[Music]
die did that does is that hurting you it
it hurt me it did hurt me oh it doesn't
it doesn't okay oh oh you weren't
talking to me I thought you were
concerned about the bomb hurting me the
bomb can hurt you you can die to it yeah
it did hurt I'm sorry to that let's go
be Rush B Rush B I'm so embarrassed I
thought you cared about me no I do I do
it was a misunderstanding I was about to
ask actually but no sorry she cared
about there's somebody here there's
somebody here watch out there's one in
the tunnel one in the tunnel one in the
tunnel I I actually okay where's B again
just saw they ran oh they're here
expected okay okay let's plant bomb
plant I got the bomb I got the bomb nice
nice
nice oh so usually somebody will watch
tunnels cuz they'll probably come from
this direction if somebody wants to
watch tunnels okay why do people get mad
when you compare this to B they're here
they're here they're here this one first
is it it is pretty different I would say
but not that I've
ever they're on the tunnel there's two
on the
tunnel
T she's trying to I have such
bad nice only one guy left I'm getting
away the real person
left the real person's
strong run I killed the real person in
myc are we sure this is a real person I
think so yeah I can tell cuz they're of
course yeah their name is different from
the bot one
what what if the AI is just advancing I
got they're try to trick us you can go
wherever you want we'll go split some
people can be distraction I'm going to a
let's go unle be protect me
please go back where the help they're
all here have it they're all
a should we go should we go see I can't
see I can't see I
see I ran I think they're behind us yes
protect are they still coming the same
way I got a a smoke I got some I'm
protecting I have a flash a flashy
thingy can Flash them nice yeah flash
them just don't flash your
teammates okay okay careful bio I don't
want to flash you I'm looking away don't
flash me oh where's the house oh wait
there's a lot
of oh I think I think they're over here
no oh oh they they are up
there terrorist nice nice okay
nice oh are we oh yeah the random joined
our side so we might get Auto balanced
oh they got balanced back oh I think cuz
we're in a party maybe it won't Auto
balance us out that's good the game lets
us stick together yeah that's nice like
Bros
together okay let's go a w they're close
mid
mid nice oh my good she got the sniper
you got the bar it's bot bot how they're
down in the door door go go I protect
you I help who has the bomb Oh there's
one guy there I got him I'll plant I'll
planted I hate you random are they
behind or were they through the door
they were through the door it's the real
person they under the tunnel is the real
person guys careful they're going cat
they're going cat what's cat oh they're
going they're going they're in they're
in sush spawn they're in sushi spawn
underneath you CeCe okay
okay oh there was a bot
I forgot that there's
Bots I was focused on the real person
they were they were
there that's okay wait we're we're still
winning yeah we got this he's diffusing
the bomb he is diffusing the bomb
J Jer don't say the
name I can't I can't see their name on
stream anyways so it's
okay oh guys how about we
rush
okay I got my AK-47 I don't know how to
use it but the AK it's good with a tap
like if you one tap their heads and
while you're not walking or anything you
can get get them really good there's no
the crossair is huge on the AK huh I
think it's it's the person it's the real
no it's not lit
where oh no another person I dropped the
bomb different person you dropped you
have a smoke M you smoke the site I have
a smoke I have smoke too I have a smoke
yeah you can smoke the doors the doors
would be good I don't want to I don't is
this it come from tunnels so watch out
and then you want to plant the bomb I
see I see them I see them they're
they're standing right want me to throw
the throw the smoke that's a flash watch
out okay okay the bomb plant the bomb
plant the bomb plant the bomb wait where
where is where is the thing oh it's over
there I apologize we're at the we are
here it's okay careful you might come
out that window so CeCe watch the window
yeah window which window oh this one
yeah yeah that's the window you can hide
in tunnels that might be good or yeah
tunnel careful guys I see jodler there
just hide just hide you can hide or
shoot if you want where is he where is
he check the might come out the window
big door the window he he's camping at
the door he's going to kill you
no he's diffusing now yeah so when you
have the bomb planted you can hide until
you hear the diffuse sound and then you
want to go out but he sniped
me why is it that I can see the enemy
team okay yeah when you die you're
supposed to not be able to talk really
in game oh oh yeah oh that's so you got
the okay I was sorry I was cheating then
okay it's okay it's
okay oh why are there's so many people
on our on our game now yeah oh what
happened oh God they found our lobby oh
dear how did they do that
you is there Friendly Fire have we
established if there's Friendly Fire not
there's not there there's no Friendly
Fire here but there will be later yeah
if you play a real game there would be
okay okay nice nice I can just okay I
can shoot them all why is this more than
like five people yeah there's no limit
on casual oh oh there's no limit like
absolutely no limit there is a limit I'm
sure but it's really big you can have
like 11 people on a team or something or
10 people on a team be careful there's
one guy there there's a there's a guy be
careful be careful wait what do you see
what do you see what do you see on cat
on cat what do you see that I don't
see oh my gosh The Recoil is
wild oh dear they're shooting
Me I'm Scared kind you can have that
many people though that's kind of cool
yeah we still have we have the advantage
kind of cuz we still I think we have
more people on our team
right they killed a lot of us just
now yeah oh no I have the bomb I don't
like the
responsibility you can drop it if you
want press G on it yeah when you have it
out when I have it out okay someone
please take care of my baby oh wait wait
got here I'll take it over here oh what
I'm pressing B it's not working g g G
G I guess we'll go this way I see o i
saw someone I saw somebody too I saw
someone oh they saw you they baited they
baited it's not a
ghost right we're all chilling yeah I'll
I'll smoke the stairs that way we can
push blood
splatters oh
oh okay that was a bad smoke it's okay
we we have time we have a minute we can
we can back up too oh no how did they
see through the smoke you can you can
just Spam
it I feel like they just did like one
good
shot
wait I like it though it's fun I like
how smooth everything is
yeah and it feel it seems like the type
of game where it's really satisfying if
you if you pull off like a clutch yeah
it is it's it it's a huge Adrenaline
Rush yeah I don't know any other game
like
that let go may I just clarify that I
don't play
[Laughter]
valerin valer valer is literally like
it's l with superpowers right well it
has like skills right nice watch out
watch out watch out watch out oh up
there up there he's watching me I see
you they're watching me yeah they're you
giv you like a little like a
popup em hey let me do that how dare you
pity
me uh teapot you're not P me she got the
clutch
uh come on come on let's go is it okay I
have a grenade we're back yeah sorry my
internet drops like just a little tiny
bit you know I do like that there's
unimited
ammo okay at least it's not like
Apex you can run out of ammo hey this
game is just a game hey this game's
just it has guns it's just a game it has
gun you buy gun instead of loting it has
Minecraft oh yeah it has pixels
now he hurt
me but isn't that wait wasn't it like
wait I I always forget the order was CS
made from halflife or was half lifee
made from
CS uh oh yeah was was one of them was
like a mod for one of the other games
and then they made it like a real game
that's so cool it's like a child that
becomes its own person you know careful
careful oh killed by someone with a
genin ion
yeah it says halflife was first and then
CS was like a mod for it and then it
became like a real game that's cool
yeah oh wait the music sounds like the
Halo theme oh yeah yeah there's like a
music kit you can get uh it's also part
of like the gacha opening a case thing
and yeah you can get cool music to play
when you
win he got like there's huge gacha in
this game it's a whole industry
yeah there's some yeah $40,000 knives
you can win oh I have the ,000 knives
yeah careful one's in the tunnels if
anyone goes over there I saw some guy
cross okay I'm close to a I have the
bomb someone should go in front of me
I'm scared okay I'll I'll be your I'll
be your bait okay they're they're in the
tunnels she said so they're going to be
here someone's in someone's
shopping I got I got him I got one of
them oh both are dead oh one is still
alive I'm going to go and plant yeah you
guys got this
smes I thought I could save the day you
got the plant that means where's
everyone else we
allbody I'm de two it's
over I try I TR sorry I should have not
done that I thought I thought we were
more wait 40,000 as in you can actually
spend $40,000 in game on data they they
so you can buy cases and it costs like
$2.50 to open each case right but then
it's completely random and the odds are
really low but you could get a really
expensive knife that people sell for
like 20,000 or like 1,000 I don't know
how the SK Market works it's like how do
gun skins be so no ni skins be so
expensive yeah you can sell skins for
you can trade you can trade stock market
yeah there's different patterns so some
of them are more expensive than others
have like a little special
image but is it the type of thing where
it's become its own Market where only
people that are trying to sell it are
actually buying it or is it actually
still has end
consumer uh is healing not possible at
all no no healing no healing you can you
can in Deathmatch but not in this
one oh I'm
screwed nice try nice try I think they
have more people on their team now don't
they are
we I'm going to pretend or I'm going to
assume that they have um one person is
really good with a
snip this dude was like killed killed
everyone and then I look at his screen
cuz I'm dead and he's just like
literally vibing and I'm just I'm so
pissed we should just n them because I
think they're going to if you buy
okay I'm going to try doing the nobody
has the bomb no no somebody somebody got
to pick the bomb oh wait no oh my pick
up the bomb I don't want
to wait someone take the bomb Oh wait
wait sorry that was my gun careful
coming from this way coming from this
way no one Iris watch out oh where
where they're all there they're all
there they're in our spawn they in our
spa oh my gosh they are oh my God this
dude has a t your veteran
coin
sweaty I
know I hope no one who plays this game
regularly as being killed by us that'd
be
embarrassing yeah St sh yeah I hope
everyone that we shoot is also playing
for the first time today headed by B
here just wait for them cuz they're
going to
push wait for them yeah they'll either
push through mid or they'll push through
tunnels so okay there's a good chance
they're listening to us but
yeah I mean those are the two only
options so like
they they're coming from this way coming
from this
way yeah or is that what they want us to
think no they're watching from
tunnels I only have a small weapon
W this might not be the best gun for
this Dam it they're closing it on us let
me snipe you yeah
snipers oh they're behind us uhoh uhoh
you're
everywhere nice try nice try nice
try all right that was fun no we did we
did it wi that was fun we what level are
you guys or it should tell you after
this thingy goes away uh let's
see how do you tell how can you tell
what level it is
uh hold on we'll see in a
moment oh it's going back into casual
all right here let's leave this Lobby
and then I'll invite you guys again y
we're going to win exit to me how do I
how do I exit actually joined another
press escape and then like exit men menu
how do you see
[Music]
level uh it's should uh when you're
level let me see I not even level
one I actually don't know where to see
level yeah where is the level maybe the
little oh never mind it's just the
amount of friends that online I was like
oh that yeah 5v5 versus bot like load
out can I go to an idol meeting yeah
yeah are you sure no you're not allowed
to go to an idol meeting did you get a
deadlock invite I got conflicting
answers I don't know what to do I
already thank you
can I you can go yeah I'll forgive you
yes we'll give you the pass mhm I'll
give you that pass just one use a use a
bottle we're yeah use yeah we're gaming
you use a bottle okay what is what is
that have to do with meetings all you
got you got to see have to talk to the
bottle you need you need to you need to
drink water right that's ex the whole
point of the idol meeting yeah goodbye
bye bye wait yeah I don't know how to
make a private lobby with Bots sorry
guys I don't know it is private
matchmaking it used to be easier you
used to be able to do it super easily
competitive absolute
silence that that was like very
satisfying I'm sorry for breaking it not
sure it's kind of like when you have
when you go for food and then everyone's
just s they made it harder it used to be
a lot easier in CS go to make a Lobby
it's when you know we just all I'm sorry
I'm reading up on a a guide so that we
can that's how you know your comfort
with each other is if you can like sit
in silence and be okay with it yeah
that's so true actually okay wait let's
be silent instead sorry oh yeah yeah
sure
okay all right I'm going to look it up
let's see CS2 Lobby private match with
Bots
create a private match invite your
friends Bots will automatically fill any
empty slots I tried to make a private
match wait wait wait I we should stay
silent till momy comes back no can you
guys try joining my uh matchmaking code
I want to see if it works now that we
play a few games okay let's see let's
try that uh did you send it I'm going to
send it the channel okay
okay
wait aren't we already yeah
I just want to test to see really quick
what you play like when I try when I
when I press play for me it like shows
me your code ah yeah it does show me
your code too oh okay already in there
yeah but the I can't click anything I
can't like join
privatech okay or maybe we have to leave
the party and then try hold on maybe if
we're in a party ah we can't okay it's
the same thing yeah you have to play
other game modes that's okay I think
it's we might have it might be time for
deadlock anyways
now oh okay
okay who else is playing deadlock
people uh I can't play I was thinking
but then I think I needed an invite so
yeah it was bio
[Music]
F yeah
yeah hi wait uh we might have time for
something I feel bad cuz Iris just got
in kind of
sorry about that I I left my game on
download before I went to sleep but it
didn't for some reason it didn't go
through Workshop Lobby I thought I
couldn't be here but I'm
here back from your meeting hi here
I'm hi bi boo I'm here
hio
hi we do a quick casual of what we just
did maybe okay
casual
casual I go again I wonder if there's a
fancier way to say casual what if be is
there any mode we can do where it's just
less five or is it not possible um it
it's possible but it would be like us
versus each other kind of oh okay never
mind maybe never want to fight against
you let me see something we could do a
quick 3v3 if we get GiGi back oh
let's ping
her bother her I don't know cuz the
lobby you can only have five people so
I'm not sure how she could join usually
it has to be like private a private like
a Lobby thing wait who what who GG
oh okay sorry sorry we can just do what
you wanted to do sorry I didn't mean to
derail all right let's do a one V4 you
guys can verse me oh oh oh okay we're
going to gang on you
yeah can you handle us oh yeah
maybe I I think she'll be fine okay you
guys can join uh okay you guys join
tside I'll be uh CT only okay okay we
join tside okay okay okay there okay it
says there are too many Terrors I'm Jo
I'm joining you okay ah okay shoot it
doesn't let me okay
I I I wonder why I guess it's trying to
balance so it's not unfair yeah I think
there's a way to turn it off I is so
cool Hello I cank if you want me to I
don't
Hello n
n when I tried the dev consoles chat it
didn't the dev consoles didn't
work oh n n
oh I don't want to kise she looks not
moving wait should I kill you or not
wait I didn't know if I should kill
leave me alone I'm not trying to kill
you I love you I love you oh really yes
because I wasn't sure if we were
shooting or what we were waiting for I'm
very confused love overcomes murder
intense intent it doesn't let me change
any of the auto balp on the floor what
if we just hung out at the at the uh at
the bomb
site what if we just kidding how does
that song go again what if we held hands
at the at the B site at the B site wait
where are we where at the B side I see
someone Comm it's I don't want to kill
her I feel bad what do you think there x
marks
standing of fate into twines it Mars the
start of our oh 10 seconds can I kill
her in 10 seconds go ahead don't kill me
don't kill me no scared I don't want to
die
yay yeah it has to be private
matchmaking it says on Google okay now
this time if we cross path it's going to
be really sad for some reason they
changed it I got Romeo and Juliet
sad yeah I've never seen or read Romeo
Juliet to be honest is it sad I've only
saw seen Leonardo DiCaprio one it's
pretty dramatic it's um isn't it kind of
stupid everyone everyone misunderstand
each other or something like that it's
yeah stupid it's like a giant like If
Only They communicated with each other
if only they knew how to do healthy
communication also I have the bomb seen
the original but I have read a web tune
spin-off that is about the other girl
Roseline or whatever her name is and
apparently Romeo was with her like 2
weeks before and
then said yeah it's a good one it's not
that good actually it's it's a good one
it's not that good actually wait wait
what happened who killed you not
me oh nice try nice
try that was very sad little girl that
filled me with such sadness such
sorrow you know be fun okay sorry 5v5 in
house okay what's the plan um okay uh
you go be and then I'll go a okay I have
I stole am's gun that is called ticket
to
hell has a name on it oh it says ticket
to hell I'm like wow Amy she has a
ticket to hell all right boys what we
doing we going we're going I I'm going
call the shots then we're going this way
okay we'll go this way okay in the this
way Direction in the this way Direction
yeah tippy toes tippy toes everybody oh
yeah tippy toes to Tippy to Tipp toes
tippy tippy toes ooh ooh I'm rubber
banding what the heck oh I'm good I'm
good let me know if they if you spot
them I haven't seen them yet I haven't
se oh they on on
on what do you mean you haven't seen
them mys
here well at least Iris wasn't be they
might have split up I'm not sure I don't
hear them
ah okay people killed
me ow nice
[Music]
sorry oh no your
knees okay who's
left m
m she's not AFK right no no no she's
probably super sneaky I bet
she's they split up is it on a though
no you can jump
there
yes
[Music]
cool stop it I rard on that bomb stop it
shoot I don't have a kit stop it I I'm
it
[Music]
no I had a
kit don't be a loser buy a
[Music]
diffuser okay wait I'll buy one too yeah
it's good to have
okay okay I I got to
okay and shield okay okay why do I
always not have enough
money I go going this way now oh wait
who has it you want us to split I do not
have the bomb that's fine yeah you guys
should split oh I have it
okay that way if they plant you know
then we'll we'll go together someone
stay in front of me I don't want no you
have to go in front I have the
ball I I got your back I got your back
you got do you really got my back I see
someone threw a Molotov over there oh no
I have not your back see a Molotov
that's interesting I see some saw
someone throw a Molotov and I'm
scared know
was oh she got sorry oh I see the bomb I
have the bomb here no no no the bomb no
you the bomb no you don't oh they took
it they took it I'm going to run I oh
that scared me scar
my run run run tactical
Retreat maybe I shouldn't say every
single thing I'm
doing no use more words descriptive
please
[Music]
descriptive hurry Iris protect me I'm
right behind
you no
sorry I protecting
me sorry nice I don't want man I stopped
diffusing for a second I should have
just kept going yeah you got to stick it
you were going to let me weren't you
yeah yeah and I stopped and I looked up
ran and you ran into my Crosshair yeah
hesitation I gave you the bomb okay I
gave you the bomb m
huh oh okay I gave you the bomb M cuz I
didn't want it cuz I'm the bomb cuz
you're the bomb yes that's so true she's
the bomb the
bomb Oh yes tippy toes tippy toes I'm
going to let you guys do that if we say
tippy toes while I walk really loud
maybe they'll think it's not us she's
going
rogue they're at he they're going cat
they're going cat
I'm scared dang it you have a sniper
it's not fair ah you can buy one too
that's they dropped the bomb okay they
they were on the left side okay you
shouldn't you shouldn't be allowed to
have a sniper
what yeah I was cheating okay I think
they ran away there're still long doors
oh they're still
[Music]
there ah I got nice okay okay nice nice
but I got Iris did I get you I'm not
sure I think you did get me you did get
me and wait where's the bomb what the
hell wait who has the bomb Oh I don't
know where it is I did I had the bomb
you have to go find my body wait I'm the
only one oh yeah that way that way surv
no not that way not that way other way
other way that way this way no other way
that the other way that no yeah no no
yeah yeah no yeah
it's too late just kill just kill her
[Laughter]
what be
ready I think I'll just run and hide she
she's through the door she's through the
door there's only 3 seconds spray and
pre I see the
method the
MVP
yay y
[Music]
this time I will buy a diffuse kit what
sniper do you guys like the the last one
I like the last one I don't like the SSG
yeah that one's not as
[Music]
good well that's the one I have then
it's it it can be good it just doesn't
like kill in one shot like the other one
wait shoot we all have snip do all of us
have
snipers I feel like that's the meta
we how are we going to play this one
care has the bomb
nobody no nobody I got I got the
bomb look at them trying to intimidate
us I have no idea where you guys are I'm
confused
ah
well oh go want to go like that
sniper okay there's still one more
person I don't know who it is um but I'm
scared since they have sniper are they
just waiting s it's like it's like the
it's like the I think this is the tunnel
you know the the stairs the stairs oh
[\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] there in tunnel's going be
kind
of yeah where you were that's called
Lower tunnels
what
the wait does that mean I can pick up
her weapon yeah you
can that one that sniper it's okay okay
no no I'll stick with my gun uh are they
b or a I think it's be yeah you hear the
beep oh I missed oh nice shot nice
[Music]
nice I didn't even know you were alive
nice you thought you were just solo
it you're so
strong oh you you hit her through the
door IR cooperate called the wall bang
oh really did I yeah yeah oh you didn't
even know yeah I thought I
[Laughter]
missed I I it's it's difficult to like
know when to you know walk and when to
when to peek I feel like I always just
walk and get just unaware uh they they
at the outside of the tunnels two of
them oh middle
okay uh-oh my animal's not
happy uhoh she's not happy that I'm
playing video
game oh they're shooting me okay they're
just standing there though so I'm just
standing she's not she's not advancing
and I'm watching their their
exit okay she's uh almost at B I think
it's
Iris who could it be ah what how did you
me I saw your arm peeking out so I shot
your
arm sh
she's too strong Iris
nice I planted it on a yeah I
figured I'll never do it again too
strong Hot Potato Hot Potato Hot
Potato I'll take it we should probably
this might be the last round cuz
probably need to yeah
okay anal has no more after this for me
this is the
one I got this good Lu Good
Luck Good Luck let's have a good game
everybody good luck have fun I feel like
for some reason I always aim down on the
floor but I don't know why yeah that's
really normal for first time for
beginner players it's kind of like a bad
habit have to get rid of it but it's
weird what do you mean by down you
always want your Crosshair
floor but I should be aiming at like
yeah but it's like automatically when I
start yeah when I start walking I
immediately look down for some
reason wrong I
got she has the bomb you got you got me
where's that where it's in a tunnel of
Lowa right at the exit of Lowa
[Music]
I was trying to be sneaky I said I
wouldn't do it again oh yeah there's a
countdown where are you guys if you guys
just kill each other like does the team
with everyone dead just what sorry uhoh
it's up to you IR person is in our spawn
CT spawn is so cool where
where so so cool oh please don't raise
any
Flags oh jumping shot
nice all right GG's GG's
G that's fine we won fun yeah thank you
guys for playing with
me fun I want to play this more now it's
pry this is way better than valerin
thank you see see there's no
abilities yeah this is way better
valerin M here Knife
Down have you never played it before I
played it I played it a little bit I
don't like it though it's not it's not
for me I only like the the death match
part yeah literally just a mini game
okay I'm off too bad thank you very much
for playing thank you Amy for watching I
was a lot of
[Music]
fun I'm glad you had fun thank you thank
you
byebye oh wait that killed you oh shoot
yeah
oh apologies I thought I did not want
that byebye I walk animal byebye byebye
later on me thank you oh is this B yeah
who's playing with us again sorry GG and
then Callie you know I will I will do
the call hey and then thank you thank
you hey and
then hey and also
hello thanks for answering the call I
have answered look
backo hello again hello oh
hi hi you guys ready to dead Lock in
when she lock some dead I'm excited I
love
moas yeah that's good it's it's a I mean
you you've seen it right it's like third
person yeah yeah okay okay
yeah we'll do around in the sandbox ni
yes I've never played a third person mob
floor I guess Smite yeah I was just say
Smite warning graphic drivers out of
date P me too and I
IGN it still works not my
problem oh my God I like the little blob
man
oh else going to play the BL man you can
play the block man it's okay I can play
something else will be fun I feel like
you know you we get like a Dynamo he's
this big big kind of round fella he's a
robot and he does heals but he also does
like sub
damage yeah robot Gigi I feel like you'd
be good at um lash it's he he jumps
around a lot and he's really good at
killing people yeah oh he has fist I'm
going he does he
does you don't know this but humans have
two fists
what what wait look look at your hands
also okay I what I want you to do is I
want you to put out your hand right in
front of you and then what happens when
you close it it
closed you have that right there that's
a fist what about my tentacles oh true
um tenta fist ooh
we can curl up
too but I only have eight
tentacles eight tent fist there's a guy
with a katana I'm play the guy with a
katana but it's a 10 10 fist 10 10 10
fist you have 10 of them eight I count o
octop fist oh cool
all right I'm inviting you guys
okay
[Music]
okay oh man all right almost full Lobby
nice
nice oh it's a
6v6 yeah
oh I think CI might still be resting
herself so we'll probably start without
her
first okay you guys I know how to play
yeah we're going to go to sandbox we're
going to go to stbx okay and then we'll
is it a 2v2 V2 per Lane kind of game or
yeah well there there's four lanes so I
think some of them have only one person
yeah it's like one two two one
right does it matter which one you put
the twos
in I don't know some people I've seen
people just switch like whenever you
know they're like I'm going to with my
friend
instead so the the way the system works
like if you guys click on the if you
right click wait what is
it ah okay sorry when you queue for a
game though usually you can uh select
your favorite and then select your like
second favorite and then select your
backup ones right uh so for sandbox just
pick whoever for
now
okay uh I'm going to pick
scien dyn kind of reminds me
of another robot in another game what uh
which that pulls people in and stuff oh
I see what you're
saying hi all right we can learn
together so here's this shop right you
press B on it that for
you oh we have to buy items yeah so
there's in the top right says browse
builds and if you look at like different
builds you can click one and set that uh
under public tab you can see what other
people different languages
yeah trending trending build
[Music]
popular yeah so you can just find one
that you think looks good I mean it's
you're kind of guessing cuz you don't
really know like at first you know just
pick one to try I I mostly just pick
like one of the top ones right and then
if you favorite it and then make sure
you click it in your favorites Tab and
then if you exit browse it should be
like your main buy
menu I think burn them all best DPS plus
survival build what what is everybody
play okay bio's playing Yamato okay G's
on lash B's in
furnace Ina Dynamo and we have a bot
spot I'm playing motus okay yeah you
guys can experiment with your abilities
and
stuff and yeah I'll show you guys some
more stuff when you finish buying some
upgrades oh do we have infinite dollars
right now yeah but usually in game you
have to earn the souls
yeah
W I'm so Nimble need oh I guess you need
stamina to do
oh M yeah oh and you guys see the slots
on the bottom left part uhhuh when you
first start like a real game a lot of
them are locked until you kill the
enemies uh it's kind of like their
towers right and once you kill the
enemy's Towers then you get more slots
so you can get more
upgrades oh
M where's the mini
map uh there's no mini map on this mode
I don't know why but in game there will
be a mini map we'll do a match against
bots after you guys get used to your
abilities and stuff
okay
[Music]
ohas is this a jungle Camp what is this
thing where are you
guys I'm fighting a big guy oh maybe
it's the boss
oh yeah the the jungle is like these
little tiny dudes oh oh so this is the
the uh the guard Guardian so this is
kind of like their Tower and yeah yeah
in early game when you kill one of these
uh there's one on each lane yeah you
unlock a
slot ow ow ow and so the goal you know
it's like a lot of moas you just finish
off the minions and you get souls and
you do like some little tiny camps and
you get as many Souls as you can cuz the
more souls you have the more upgrades
you're going to get right and then the
more damage you'll do and
stuff oh see
I got you
y
nice there's a lot going on
so there's a lot to get used to with the
UI the N creeps too right yeah yeah
those little red
guys you got toy much going on so when
when they're shooting your creeps
there's like a little orange soul that
will fly out of it it's like a little
orb and you have to shoot it and then
you get to deny them Souls yeah yeah
that's like Duda oh yeah yeah yeah I
think so yeah just like
that oh that's also Val games you can
say I think yeah that's fine okay that's
good
okay you see the little green orbs that
fly out when you kill them the other
team can shoot those and then deny your
souls can we also steal from each other
uh I don't think so I think it's shared
it's shared is it shared wow you're
trying to take ours no no I mean yes I'm
I'm the DPS give me all your
farm oh so also your abilities right now
cuz we're in sandbox mode they're all
unlocked but you only get to start with
one ability and then you get to unlock
them as you get more just yeah yeah it's
pretty
common T to upgr Ability not do you guys
know in chat if there's a way to switch
Heroes like now or whatever not Heroes
uh Champions whatever they called
Legends Escape
tab who the cube I've gooed you I don't
know what it does I'm not
reading I think it heals
me
uh no-oo
ball I'm goo ball oh my gosh look at you
you're
amazing thank you is Right looking at
something else there we go I going to
move over so I'm not blocking stuff one
second throwing
goo
okay oh and did you guys see the zip
line
above yeah yeah so this is every lane
has a zip line and there's a speed boost
that the cool down on it is really long
oh
so use this to get back to where you are
faster like after you die or if you need
to go back and defend the
base press space up here I'm smoking
everyone get it get in the Smoke where's
the smoke I think it only applies to
me oh that's a big
ass just like Legend So one thing is too
is if we cuz we're going to do a match
against real people at some point uh
they might take the character that
you're playing now cuz you can only have
one in yeah per game so it's good to
have like two or three you know
characters that you kind of know how to
play I think there's a way to change
characters now if you want to try a
different one oh yeah it says in
tab
tab who's this guy Mirage I didn't I've
never seen this
guy and did they add somebody else to
the game
okay now this
is this is the the robot you know oh the
robot if you know what I mean that guy's
nasty he has a hook and you can pull
from people from really far away you
could kind of go
fishing how do you change characters
again oh if you press Tab and then you
hover over where it says uh like the
person you're playing I
think I yeah it says Change Hero on the
top right is oh okay oh I see it yeah
guess that
works oh GG probably I feel like you'd
also be a good Seven Player he has like
a really big uh alt radius oh he's fun
too let's
go there there are some support
characters I mean a lot of characters do
a little of
healing uh or self healing but there's
ones that kind of specialize in it a bit
more like there's Calvin he does ice
stuff U and he has like a big b it's
like a snow globe and it it can do
healing in
there and Ivy she's a goblin like a
what's it called those Stone guys I
forgot the
name Golem gargoyle gar
yeah so if you guys are ready you want
to do um match against
bots here okay we'll do sandx with C too
yay sorry I I am having asthma issues
but I'm here to be a silent Menace today
no problem let's go I like these kind of
games so let's run it let me see if I
can invite you I think we might have to
go back to a Lobby okay
okay oh I I exited the game by accident
one second
oops just clicked on it all right let me
check something while I'm doing
this is this a br is this brand new this
game yeah just it's an alpha still
I noticed that yeah we had to do we
leave the S
invited uh uh I think so yeah I think
you might still get my
invite we got it
okay oh maybe I'll leave this party and
then we can invite oh I'm not sure leave
a
party oh there you go you joined
could I get a oh I found it just
kidding nice okay I think we could just
go straight into a bot match I bet cie
well yeah yeah okay oh wait I think you
have to leave the party okay invite me
please yeah yeah
okay aha I got it there's so is this a
game where we like
split um in like a MOA mhm with like
lanes and stuff like that yeah yeah
there's Lanes there's four lanes okay so
here is what I'm talking about like say
it says if the white one is your backup
character then yellow is your second
preferred and purple is your most
preferred for an ATT with the right
person and this will be over in no
[Music]
time selected is the one you want to
play uh purple yeah I think have to like
double click it to get uh different
colors where's Callie Callie's in the
party yeah she's I think she's going to
be a little quiet though oh you mean on
the screen okay hold
on I'll add
her one second let me get the F
[Music]
thingy I tried to play as the cute
ghosty girl cuz she's cute but I
she was I didn't know how to play as
her she is cute the sniper oh yeah she
is yeah she's cute yeah I feel like she
doesn't really do that much in fights
though it's kind of difficult to well
with her yeah she's like from really far
away really far away she could shoot
characters are actually really
cool yeah these are just also I'm pretty
sure they the designs aren't set
completely yet they're still working on
it yeah I like the guy with the long
head oh yeah yato
yeah I like look like of course
people oh yeah it's got a katana and it
name is
yam all right we just got to select your
thingies so but you know take your time
read through the abilities and stuff
[Music]
now when you're ready just press the
continue whatever
[Music]
button GG I'm picking this
one never mind I'll just do this
okay good luck it's I think it's just
yeah bots on the enemy team so be good
nice what is this hey I'm
jungler is there a
jungle there's no jungle all right we
have to be super aggressive you can
jungle in this sure there's one is I
think jungling is more so you just go
onto like buildings and you break boxes
and you get upgrades and you also I'm
going places I guess it's just
automatically chooses yeah yeah
automatically chooses yeah and there's
also little camps you can fight like
these little uh dudes with one eyeballs
who's with me
I'm by
myself oh nice
shot yeah usually in this part of the
game uh I'm like balancing between not
letting the guys push too far cuz you
have to defend your little Tower guy
right your guardian and then yeah it
hurts get get as many Souls as you can
cuz souls are
everything how do I see my health oh
it's the one next to me yeah yeah it's a
right next to me
yeah and then you you have to unlock one
ability I'm glad I'm not streaming my
perspective cuz I'm doing so
bad yeah I'm feeding pretty hard right
now it's really hard I think it's it's a
difficult game to play right away it's
fun though yeah I feel like getting
really into it me
too I'm done
are we going in are we going
in yeah oh no she left never mind oh she
left kill the turet chat do you guys
know if anybody else is streaming their
perspective is it just me in a lane by
myself so feel bad if you
guys okay thank you I'm trying to learn
what my abilties
this a I
remember well when I get my all I can go
fly and check on people the
Healer can you buy when you're at spawn
no so if you go back to kind uh where
your guardian is uh you'll see like a
little area you can buy but once your
guardian gets
down uh your the shop will disappear
it'll close but there's also a shop in
the middle of the map but it's like
underneath the city it's in the sewers
kind
of Myers
I want to see everybody else is doing
too ni
yay oh
no make a great thing we're doing so
good in our lane nice yeah I think with
the bot match it said we have to be
super aggressive otherwise the Bots will
just kind of like not do anything
oh really yeah
yeah uhoh I'm going to killed by their
turret my bad it's okay we got we
got yeah makes
[Music]
sense tutorial mode Bots pretty
much no I mean I don't think anyone
played this I think play
tutorial what are she doing kill her
kill her clown get out of
here I'm going to die to the bot no no
no he's trying to melee me I got away I
got away my heal's back in
seven are you good yeah I'm good I'm
good I got the healing the bot won't
kill me right thank you oh [\h__\h] you're
leaving cuz you're
afraid ah it's fine I'm fine wait when
did I use my zipline boost what the heck
oh she's low she's low I wish I could
kill her so
bad oh and then if you guys see that
little potion bottle that's underneath
the health bar uh I think that's until
your next upgrade like for your
abilities oh mm
oh a good way to heal
yourself uh I think if you a lot of
people will get life steal for their uh
kit so when you go to the shop yeah
there's like some life steal stuff you
can
get walk back walk back where's the shop
near find in our lane it's right next to
your guardian oh I see it over here Ena
we can shop oh there's also a creep that
has he has like a little flag and he
does some healing if you stand next to
him where are you g um do you see my
tower turn around right here oh no I'm
okay and then the Shop's right
here all
right so I'm going to going to purchase
these real quick
okay
[Music]
away
ow going in ow no I'm getting rid of
their creeps it's okay we have our Tower
so they push they're going to
die let's push the wave up to oh no
they're at our Tower oh oh but it's okay
the ground
pound yeah will we play a real match I
think
yeah realized what it actually does get
him get
him you got him we got him we killed him
you can push okay okay I got my El yeah
so our lane dead so yeah right now in
early game we're just going to stay in
our lanes but there are times where we
need to get together and push together
especially towards the end cuz yeah it's
how long do games last uh I've been in a
game that lasted for like 56 minutes was
the
long the DOTA experience just
like the the fastest game I've been in
was I think the 15 minutes so it can be
kind of short
yeah nice done
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I'm harassing
I'm harassing she's backing up
coward get the
turret oh are there bot difficulties in
this game or there just one difficulty
I'm not sure actually let me ask chat oh
no I'm being LIF I'm backing up I'm
backing up I'm backing up I'm backing up
I'm backing up okay okay okay thank you
thank you thank you I'm here I di oh
what happened
[Music]
oh okay okay
I'll hold I'll hold turet okay I'll get
the I'll get the upgrade while I'm
here just got to push I wonder how long
this this game will take this Bot game
as long as we're doing damage right I
got to I mean I haven't really bought
stuff so I don't
know how do I take that I'll do my well
I guess I'm
walking hey I'm walking here 1 hour no
I'm walking here won't take that long
don't say that yeah if you see little
gold statues they're like the really
round looking ones or the crates you can
break them and you get Buffs and stuff
there small
amounts oh I see come back if you need
anything else look's ready for a 2 A.M
Metro I know I just buy random items I'm
really bad about
it I got the on this
side
nice
well M left is also down the tower their
Tower I think we're winning against
these Bots
yeah that's good sign good
sign we just have to remember for when
the next match we're going to go against
people right so
it's kind of hard but we have to be like
a little aggressive you know make sure
we're doing damage I Ed right from their
though me and fauna have like a little
fire and ice thing going yeah we do oh
my god oh that's a big one that's a big
boy Callie's playing Calvin f is playing
INF ferace Ena on Dynamo Gigi on seven
bio on
yamuto okay solid team right there okay
I'm running
back where's it going oh
stupid supposed to take what push
[Music]
up what I'm being lifted oh no stop
it your presence ready for
aide I don't need to use
this I made a mo all right after I kill
this little guy here we got we got to
start we want to go check on what
everybody else is doing yeah yeah
yeah back off
buddies oh he's going into the subway
system nice nice nice nice
nice me one shot sh okay got him got him
got him got him be jungling maybe all
let's go check on
everybody
Relentless all right I got the tower
group up with you guys okay I got the
healing for you thank you thank you than
you okay so if you guys look at the map
you see that little blue
jar blue jar yeah yeah we got them both
you're supposed to pick that up and
deliver it across the map into it's like
a little delivery Z we got to push we
got to push and you get you get more
souls and stuff from that it's
good uh I wonder if anybody okay okay
okay I'm shooting it I'm shooting it
this guy not take it
right to it's almost down it's almost
down ow okay sour God
nice we can get him though he's half
Health they're so focused I know it's
good it's good it's good I just wanted
to fly somebody with the N but I'll wait
oh shoot my lights are flickering or
something light bulb that is true the
very large one
yeah oh [\h__\h] boy
oh very scary
looking does this very very I'm beinged
I'm fine I'm fine
heal ooh backing
up here somebody come over here to where
I am guys
push if you guys come over here I can
deliver the N with you
are you in a lane I'm
yellow
[Music]
y oh wait they took the
ear all right never
mind let's go
me the N has been dropped oh too far n
earn
like Drop It that hurts it's like the
walk we need our
creeps okay we'll push the wave so the
our creeps can push the thing I've
actually
never I'll try ow what the heck I'm
hello I got
stuck I'm delivering to earn yay this is
practice oh God what is he doing what is
that I think it's someone's all I've
only ever flown people to the
ear Ah that's it you just stand
here all right let me see what everybody
else is up to his eyes his eyes yeah oh
[\h__\h] does this game have I think we got
what
is uh it's got souls in
it I mean it gives us all everyone
like I why is my lagging thank you maybe
that uh come on video thing wasn't lying
about my graphics driver being out of
date people kill oh I got to kill sorry
nice thank you oh that's good thank
you ow it can throw little balls at us
uh let me see here you these boxes you
can break yeah yeah oh and then if you
come over here look at these guys this
is like the little jungle this is how a
jungler I guess would just go around and
kill these guys you can find them
everywhere see yeah and then you get
stuff for a
bit Yeah there's also uh I don't know I
don't know if it's over here but there's
like a little slot machine thingy where
if you just hit it a ton you also get
souls from that
gotcha I'm muted what do you mean I
muted not muted so many
turrets our yellow no
has destroyed triangle on the
map
really what's a
triangle ah she's so low these guys
[Music]
ah no sorry I'm just getting distracted
turret I know the
turret you need help no the turret is
just so strong and
powerful the walk
yeah you got to wait for the minions
minions come
back we're in this together
oh I want to fly G but yeah oh yeah g
with that character with that Al if you
ult then I can uh carry you around with
my
ult that's evil yeah yeah I think it
does less damage though
maybe you guys know if they updated it
didn't
they yeah this one's called The Walker
this big
guy it's like a oh he's almost down that
inhibits huh is it kind of like the
thing that inhibits we got wait we're
getting him we're getting we're getting
him inhibits a no I'm being lifted I'm
getting greedy speak
code I'm sorry I'm
thank you you saved my life you
literally saved my life
heing I thought I could get the Walker
there yeah you got to be closer there
he's dead he's
[Music]
dead go get
him nice
nice all right so these guys you you
don't really get anything for killing
them except uh it will make it faster
when you travel on the zip line above
these two Guardians yeah so you don't
have to kill them but it's good
too pretty sure right chat I don't know
if I'm giving you the right
information nice all right so it's a
little complicated we're getting to
towards the inside of their
base um there's these uh shrines that we
have to kill first and then we can
attack this dude in the middle so it's
this thing
here where I am
there's like this generator thing you
got to
kill I'm chilling
ouch my teammates are going to go in
with
me oh big dome yeah I really like the
Dome yeah I like his ice walk ability
it's cool yeah I've barely bought
anything I remember if you guys die to
buy cuz I always forget to buy by oh so
first we have to attack this thing down
here I think right oh
God or do we attack this guy first he
Shield right there's okay okay okay I'm
fine I'm fine what's this mid
boss mid boss oh yeah there is a mid
boss yeah it's like it's like most bobas
you know when the other team dies if
you're able to kill them then you can
get the mid boss type of
thing get his ass
nice I'm what is oh there's a lot of
turrets yeah they have the turret lady
on their
side level up oh
yeah uh true
[Music]
true I should have got my healing up all
the way but it's fine usually in a real
game oh yeah so there's this little
generator have to shoot first before you
can attack this big guy that's has a big
beam
excent uh Shrine on side yeah the little
generator sh it's called The Shrine and
it's shielding him so if you can't
attack that big guy is pretty much like
the end uh Power type of thing like a
crystal I guess I'm getting the
shrine I'm with you oh so the big guy is
there
Nexus ancient
exactly exactly but you can't hit him
yeah until you yeah he's shielded right
now with the generator thingy I'm
hitting the Barrack
[Music]
everyone
ow are they on the other side I'm doing
it right I'm doing it right guys right
I'm not giving the wrong information I'm
supposed to shoot this thingy
right I just I don't have any items so
I'm not doing good job
feels like it's taking so long it's just
me maybe they were on the other side hi
oh I'm going to
die
uh oh so many
else nice yeah I'm getting picked up oh
God I'm lagging I'm Ed
everyone it's so silly yeah it is
ah it's crunchy why am I lagging so much
I don't have two games open do
I never lagged so much in deadlock
before even when I was streaming it last
time it wasn't this bad ow Reinhardt ult
which one oh Reinhardt charge oh charge
guy yeah
Early Access kicking in yeah I think I'm
going to have to take a look at my
settings maybe my frames are too high
maybe yeah level oh yeah oh
my all right so now uh we have to attack
you see him uh that yeah we have to
attack him and then he'll transform and
then we can we can win once after he
transforms yeah wa he transforms he's
transforming now
yeah he transforms into a little ball on
the ground and we have to attack him
so
cug all right so now he's a little ball
over here in the pit yeah oh I like his
not in the pit
yeah and pretty much we just shoot him
until he
dies oh I'm going to die it hurts the
pit hurts yeah the pit I think they're
doing a lot of damage in there the pit
doesn't usually hurt by itself but all
right let me take a look at my settings
really quick
[Music]
you are in
my he's
[Music]
healing I hopefully that helps
oh you got
this uh I don't know what build I have
but it doesn't really matter I just buy
whatever
ow you guys are where the tow on the
right you forget I for they're
there it's cuz we pushed in oh
God I don't want to die help in this
[Music]
I'll save you cie wait
sa I was going to fly out but uh I
haven't played deadlock in a while so my
brain is kind
of yeah playing against SP is like not
as fun but you know it's good practice
good practice what
oh I'm going into the pit man freak
this respawn go crazy where's
VB trying to
Reinhard I'm on my
way what is everybody doing we got to
get into the pit we got to get into the
pit finish this fight in the pit fight
in the pit
pit in the
pit I'm going to die in the
pit oh the pit really hurts it does hurt
the P I guess all the Bots are just
really focused in
here okay we'll have to wait to do the
pit one's down one's
down I just feel like it you know their
bods we could get into the pit attack
the thingy and then play real
game two BS
down it's two when you guys get back
then we can go into the pit cuz we're
we're cleaning
up one shot let's go let's go
pit pit pit time
here all right
heals but yeah if you get the mid boss
you get the rejuvenator which means that
you spawn pretty quickly which is really
good for pushing yeah cuz then if you
just push and die and fail then you know
you just spawn pretty fast hit hit hit F
half F half all right good
time ow
Reinhardt yeah get him okay last guy's
in the pit
hard got it I'm good
he's still alive he's still alive he's
almost dead so much going on he's dead
now we got it we attack the orb attack
the or get him get him get the pit the
pit that's good warm up right yeah warm
up the match against real people will be
just like just as easy hard it's going
to turn out just as well
it'll be fine oh so we have to update
the game there's always updates that are
happening so just close it update super
quick okay see
okay so you guys like the characters you
played yeah yeah that was fun it was
cool I kind of want to try someone else
so just for fun oh okay oh I wonder what
what what do you usually like to play in
games like tanky
or jump into type of style probably
tanky tanky jungler oh Jung let's see if
chat recommends anybody let's see chat
what do you guys think what should cie
play uh
Abrams isn't Abrams like super melee if
you like Melee there's Abrams he's that
blue guy he's a
detective detec oh he's Reinhardt yeah
so he does that he does the shoulder
smash so you like charge at someone and
smash yeah he's really close to strange
and then um chat is saying Moen Krill
which is like that little pig looking
guy in the oh they're cute yeah he's
he's got some AOE stuff I'm pretty sure
Hees he has this really cool spin move
oo love
AOE let's see what else Warden oh
there's Warden who's kind of like a a
cop type of guy he's all right he has
some interesting abilities I don't I
didn't think he was that fun to play but
maybe maybe you like
it oh bop bop is uh I want to try out
everybody all these characters are
really
cool yeah their their designs
are yeah
Sheriff hold on I love me a sheriff all
right I'm inviting you guys back
okay who's missing they're going to
match us against people against our
actual skill
yeah yeah yeah it'll be people there be
lots of new players
right already grinded this right there
is matchmaking so don't worry don't
worry okay are people smurfing on
deadlock
already I hope not they might be though
it's
possible CH you better not be new
accounts to Smurf us okay we're new
we're new we're new no player
please okay I'm joining the game okay
yeah update's usually just really small
I don't even know what they do I'm not
sure little tiny little
tiny fixes
maybe if you change your mind you know
where to find me all
right m
okay I'm going to get water really quick
but don't worry um you know keep doing
your thing it'll it'll go on its own so
okay I'll be right back
[Music]
cat do you think the devs are watching
right now and they were like oh no a bug
we better patch that ping they saw
something on our screen like oh no
that's not supposed to happen
maybe it's gabin himself yeah g is
that do you know he has a submarine a
submersible he does what do he do with
it he he bought the company that
operates the dsv limiting factor which
is the you know the good submersible
that's actually rated to go down all the
way to the Marana Trench
[Music]
cool I think he just has an interest in
like deep sea exploration so he's just
like I'm going to buy a
submarine was it they found that that
subm merble that was like lost or
something found it and I I saw it I was
like oh that's terrifying it is
terrifying yeah there's no reason to go
down there there's just no
reason nope ear is nice I like air
personally air is
breathing breathing is great sometimes
you know land really good
too only some I'm alone here
no who am I with I'm back I'm scared
yeah I'm with you me me we're
together oh I'm I think I'm with bi boo
oh you're with me okay let's go slow
them down I'm trying a new Champion hope
it goes well I got chicken nuggets a new
what a champion oh new hero
champ um agent I don't know what game
we're playing I don't know what they're
called people I forgot yes people of
Legend the real people are
scary okay they're scared of you too
they're scared of you too they don't
look scared of me they're shooting me
they're shooting
me yeah if you need to back up you know
go back to base and heal you could buy
item
maybe yeah I'm not muted right decid to
come back quick oh maybe they are scared
of us scar they think we're much better
than we are as is with all competive
must the last
round they're shaking in their
boots you're not careful I'm going to
deny their CS
[Music]
them stop shooting at me every time you
say CS I think of cash get on maple
story everyone maple story I remember
map story oh I'm feeding I'm
feeding no I believe in you they have
great evasive techniques this is
definitely yeah the Bots would just
stand there and kind of take the shots
but not anymore these guys try to hide
oh they're
shooting
I li I'm
back I'm living they're shooting
me don't let them shoot you's quiet I
think she's just speaking quietly but I
can turn her
up I think she's a little sick right
now oh
[\h__\h] sorry I got stuck on something got
stuck on something on the map
what i is somebody goo oh yeah they do
have a goo guy we should kill them okay
jump on him where are they where are
they I can switch over get on get on now
get him get him get him get him get him
get himp I'm backing up I'm backing off
they're R oh they backed up okay but
that's good we pushed them out of we
push them yeah yeah we pushed them I'm
not going to push too far you should
heal okay I'm healing they're going in
on me I'm running no
I'm coming I'm
coming
where oh
no I should probably go and buy items I
know for it he's going to die punish him
he has one guy with the guy with low HP
back oh she
died I killed him I killed him oh he's
almost low he's very low okay okay the
other person is very low second can C
see
them oh Lord made a
mistake that the other guy with L his
back okay I might try to kill him I'm
eating CH nuggets okay okay we're
pushing up so we can hit this thing hit
the thing I'm hitting their turret I'm
hitting their turret me too good to
anyone the little guy ran away oh no
he's there I'm going to try to kill him
okay okay I can probably
die get no they were like two contenders
but like I'm running I'm running back up
back up back up back up back up back up
okay their partner's not here yet we can
keep pushing yeah yeah yeah keep hting
the
alone oh yeah yeah I can come after we
get this one yeah oh okay we have to
keep pushing coming ganking I'll come
and gank yeah we'll gank after we kill
this pull the line back towards yeah
it's good to back up once you get like
their Tower or something or you make
sure yeah yours is defended somehow o oh
it's almost dead it's almost dead almost
dead almost two on your lane
cie yeah one more hit one anybody else
on your lane okay we did it want no it's
okay I'm scared they might have switched
Lanes so that so that one of their Lanes
is supposed to have two that went to a
different one or something what Lane are
you in Ena uhoh I'm on the yellow
one I'm sorry
perspective won let them we won't let
them I Won't Let You de I'm not as tanky
as I'd like to be yeah you have to make
sure you buy items cuz that will help a
lot too okay if you oh I didn't I don't
know if I told you but you can browse
builds so when you go to the shop uh if
you click browse builds in the top right
and then you click public you can see
what other people are uh they have like
build guides I guess okay and then if
you select that it'll show the things
that you should be buying for that build
for your character H they're both
they're both sorry I forgot to explain
that to you try
protect the bio I believe in you they're
both here I believe in you use the power
of the turret help but also I'm doing
pretty good at pushing my Lane I don't
want to give it up they're up
above sorry you guys can't see what
they're doing scared of me yeah yeah you
have the turret with you you'll be
you'll be safe
forever they're fighting our
Tower I'm going to try pushing
forward okay do it do it here okay I
will I will hold them back for now yeah
I'm hitting their turret out
of speed zipline boost I slept him I
slept him I did not sleep him okay okay
he's low he's low he's low he's low he's
backing up he backed up he backed
up are we back yet they're really
pushing
me okay we're getting this tour and I'll
come back I'm almost dead no oh no I
want to go help you guys but I'm doing
I'm pushing my Lane up so I can't
beating so
hard maybe it's fine if I leave come
back our Guardians we lost we lost okay
we're we're even now even yeah it's okay
we traded our Tower so it's fine our
Tower is almost we almost have this
[Music]
one
oh sometimes it helps if I restart
stream that might help this is a really
[Music]
long green Tower is going to die I
think oh don't you run away oh you're
running away because your health is
low I'm
coming oh he ran to his Tower oh I hate
you I got to go by I should check out
the store they're pushing green Tower
really hard I might need assistance okay
let me
try well when you find the chance D I
don't want them to have my leg get this
Tower I need to restart
the hold on when I get a second I'm
going to restart it I SLE him I slle him
I SLE him if you want to hit him if you
have a skill you want to on him yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah oh did he ult he Ed
Ed okay okay we're alive we're alive
they have back up they back up now I'm
going I'm going to die oh I'm dead oh I
have to go back I'll be
backing no no no I'm out of stamina push
it's okay it's okay I got to help them
but I don't want to give up my Lane what
do you guys think I should do should I
go help I'm going to go help you
guys I'm going to go help defend blue
back to
okay I'm going to go help the B blue
okay push over there I will stay yellow
because there's now two B this is not
what I wished
for I'm here I'm here I'm here I'm going
to I'm going to gank yellow I'm coming
they back to Blue they're really pushing
green or yellow rather okay I'm coming
I'm here I'm
here I'm going to go back to purple
right
now oh green down
that's help nice get him get him need to
find a way to stop War oh they really
strong damage oh
ouch no one spped I spped
one
our a purple one is defeated oh no yeah
I had to step back from my Lane it's
okay I could come try to help you guys
maybe we if we're here we could push
blue the blue he's on the blue Guardian
so or blue Walker so I'm going to go
Blue okay I'll also run towards gu is
definitely special as a special guy
our then I no yellow yellow
no you can still come back from this no
problem no problem but we have to get
more souls we got to get more minions
cuz look at their souls up top yeah they
have 49 they have
20K no I think it's
fine all right let's we can we can
probably push blue here I think unless
they all push us okay let's try to get
this sh in our inner we have a shop in
inner uh there's one underneath the map
somewhere I'm not sure this guy's here
on the left
side I see him yeah I see
him my way all right we can kill this
someone's here
it's it's viscus viscus that's a goo guy
back up back up back up back up back up
he's
gooey all right back up back up back up
F but back up at the same
time nice nice oh whenever I use the the
burrowing move behind us the ground yeah
I'll have a shield behind us oh oh I see
them
[Music]
I'm taking us out of
here oh
God oh my
God 100% stream sniping right now all
all of them
are all right we're catching up on Souls
a little bit a little bit yeah yeah
we're getting shut down
[Music]
loer we need somebody to uh oh
man out of the ground like that I have
no
defense I'm on my way there might be
some items that would help with that
like I don't know what the build is for
that guy but maybe life steal type of
thing he's sleeping oh God I'm
leaving oh ow they're so powerful yeah
they're doing a lot of damage let's
together nice
nice I got he that was [\h__\h]
it was you had a lot of people in there
but we just needed to yeah I should have
said
something that's so much damage go guys
out of here I slle no he's rolling still
he's just rolling around rolling
[Music]
around got to follow go
rainbow I'm lagging so bad rainbow our
stronghold
wow oh nice we got to kill one nice
[\h__\h] I aim
ah
no I'm trapped I got
trapped I think I ran out of
stamina get get him
[Applause]
nice try nice try no oh you
out close to me close to me thank you I
don't really have a lot of items so I'm
not really doing that watch
that by left to
right maybe I should be jungling
more getting more souls spirit is
waiting to be claimed
uh-oh I'm under attack
eny [\h__\h] oh not the tur
again our has deated o sign what is
this noo it's okay it's okay we still
have fa have fath we have
[Music]
believe kill this guy kill this guy ice
guy ice guy
low okay here uh get this
lady Focus the orb Focus the ball I'm
I'm focused on the ball right now cuz
he's going
around damn this a
ball guy he's going he's
uhoh I'm leaving now
[Music]
uhoh all
right oh thank
you oh big heels thank
you oh no okay they're going to go to
our other Shrine now on the other side
to the other I'm molting I'm Ming on top
of them wasted my old
no we got one nice
ni oh ow don't get hit by that
exped oh the damage yeah she does a lot
of spirit
damage yeah so there's bullet damage and
spirit damage and that one is the blue
stuff Spirit
yeah and we're defending for now but uh
I wonder if somebody can try to backline
kind of
maybe call you could try doing that try
back lining see if you could do some
damage to there back door yeah yeah hit
their back door I'm on my way like go
around them yeah yeah like go behind and
kill some of their towers and
stuff maybe they won't notice I don't
know if they do just run and come back
it's
fine uh I don't know what to buy I'm
really bad at reading all this stuff
whatever I just buy whatever Panic bye
panic
this guy's low over here on the right
side uh ice guy ice guy he's getting out
he's going towards the left okay I'm
behind I'm behind he's coming in one
low oh nice nice got
him
enemies
ouches am I is a stream live sorry not
you guys I meant to do that in chat uh
my stream is lagging this person this
person is I'm
leaving oh this person's low where where
where I think there's ping middle Mouse
button oh I'm being lifted I can't
P oh this mob mob lady mob lady mob lady
she's low she got her got nice nice
there's this other guy Warden on the on
the right side right side right
side isn't over he's he's stn he's
stn behind it behind behind us there's a
guy coming he's in his bubble he's in
his
bubble I'm in the bubble too oh dear
uhoh where are you guys oh
dear they do so much damage yeah I'm
backing up for now I got to
heal roll out I should have died there I
think all right let's see intensify
magazine instead of poose I'm up in 25 a
lot of
souls no they came from behind me no I'm
back oh they're at the B ah I
died okay we're back I'm not lagging
anymore get out of our pit out of our
pit
that pit is ours our
[Music]
pit it's so chaotic right there's so
much stuff
going death comes for you like's much
better now good
sorry OWI oh it hurt it
hurt I messed up I kept trying to press
R to all it do it Le a l of
chin
oh nice try yeah it's okay at least
pretty
fun
yeah it's a tough game to get like a
hang up I think yeah it was fun
still
fun oh well if you guys uh if you guys
are feel satisfied with that we could do
that or we could do another one what do
you guys
think do you have time too yeah
I probably should go to the next game
May I mean we can yeah yeah yeah yeah
was saying one more I don't know you
think we'll do better if we go
again it could go better I think the
game is a little long if you don't want
to have yeah next guess that's true
that's true like a 30 minute game yeah
true all right well thank you guys for
playing I'm sorry so
chaotic ni try fun thank you thank you
it was a good time mhm all right have
fun see you see you soon yeah have fun
the
next
me enjoy enjoy portal and G than thank
you okay see you
[Music]
soon
byebye that was good kind of
I mean yeah it's hard for the first
game having so many new people at the
game
right all
right fun experience the vo has stopped
oh
no now it's big brain time
yeah I'm pretty sure I I have
played uh Portal 2 Co-op
before uh but it was such a long time
ago that I don't remember did I ever
stream it trying to remember I feel like
I
did that's okay it's more about spending
time together we're going to be playing
with
narissa I don't remember what time I oh
yeah I think we have 20 minutes to
do I don't know what should we do for 20
minutes let me see where she's at
oh she's
here right let me launch the game really
quick let me get
ready right let me make sure everybody
[Music]
has uh one
ah the steam sound so nostalgic right
valve sound I
mean all right I'm just snacking for now
but I'm trying to help see if anybody
has some issues for joining Gary's mod
[Music]
yeah before the stream I was like
rushing to test all of the servers and
stuff and write up little guides I
recorded little videos on how to join
TF2 and Gary's
Mod to help people who don't know who
have never played
before
yeah have you guys been having fun so
far we got to play a bunch of different
games you got to watch a bunch of
different
games I mean there were some frames
dropping yeah I'm glad
H good good
good all right I'll probably take a
quick break just for my
brain and I'll tell Nur see uh can we
start at this time
it should fine no it's not over yet
we're going to play portal um we're
going to play portal for like an hour or
so then we're going to go into Jerry uh
Jerry's mod Gary's
Mod uh let me just double check some
stuff
[Music]
Jerry's mod not Jerry's
mod excuse me excuse
[Music]
me one second checking
checking uh let me see
GG's
mod all right let me check something
really quick sorry hold on hold
on uh here
[Music]
oh s
right I see I see I see I see I see I
see hello yeah do you guys have any
questions for me while we wait while I'm
checking some
stuff who's joining Gary's Mod uh
there's a lot of people joining I think
there's like 18 people
playing but I'm not going to say who cuz
I don't know you know stuff might come
up people might get busy and then I
don't want you guys to be like
but you
said you said this person would join but
my o she's not here what the heck okay
just in
case uh one
moment okay
[Music]
yeah am I joining AR's mod yeah of
course I am I'm the admin
how can I not join Gary's one all right
hold on though I'll be right
back just give me a minute let's put
some text on the screen not food break
uh brain
[Music]
break please wait
Hello I'm and
bye hello how are you
today
[Music]
nope okay hello
hello are you excited to play portal I
am me too I really love portal like for
the first Portal game I uh even learned
how to speedrun it a bit so is one of my
favorite games oh wow well I'm not very
good at portal so please take care of me
no problem no problem well well we're
going to put our brains together yeah we
put our brains together and then we will
become even smarter yeah you'll be like
um you know detective and her trusty
Crow yeah
exactly turned up your volume level
thank you of course I don't I totally
forgot how to join Co-op so uh I sent
you an invite so you might be able to
check your messages and mayh you have
one
[Applause]
yeah
uh there it goes y
[Music]
okay let's do our best our two brain
cells put together yeah literally
that's that's
me I wonder if I should get your face on
the screen somewhere or your Discord
face hold
on I have I have a
solution do what you must thank you you
will be a cute
sock cute sock cut
scene we're getting built
are you a robot I think we're both
[Music]
robots oh my so loud I know
wa which one do you think I am and which
one do you think you are I I hope that
I'm the blue one and you're the yellow
one because it would work perfectly that
would be perfect also I can hear you in
game can you hear me in game I can too
oh I wonder if we can turn that off oh
yay it worked out
yay all right let me see today you will
be testing with a partner please wave to
your partner
hi oh hold on I'm looking at the
options
q
w hello
yeah I need to mute myself too for your
side it's okay I disabled voice chat
both you with
AOL please use your ping tool to select
your favorite animal oh favorite
favorite chicken
right I actually really like
wolves partner's favorite animal
good please use your ping tool to select
your favorite element from the periodic
table favorite element oh
wow uh they don't have the one that I
want shoot oh well that's that sucks
yeah I guess I'll go with what is this
gold yippe can I do it oh no I pressed
the wrong
thing
really okay blue please yeah ause gold
right I have no
idea but glattus is judging you yeah it
doesn't matter anything I picked she
would have judged me can also be used
rude your where you would like them to
place their portal hi oh we're so close
but so far I know separated by a wall
using your pain tool please indicate
where you would like me to place your
two portals ping each
location oh oh what is the Ping tool am
I crazy f f blue I can only place a
portal on portable surface oh yeah yeah
you can only place the portal on the
White surface yeah no I I clicked wrong
a now she's dragging
me are you doing it yeah I placed mine
he I placed mine too do I have to play
another
one
ah got to put
two oh oh I see I figured wait did you
figure it out
yeah two me too me
too orange is first to acquire a Portal
Device blue now device I understand
finally damn she's not going easy on us
two selfcontained portals please test
your device by portaling to that
ledge yeah I'll race
you easy
game wait where are you oh hi
calibrating Blue's weight calibrating my
weight you already know calibrating
oranges weight no variances detected oh
we're both the same it's okay oh really
we look so different though uh I guess
you're more like round and dense and I'm
like long and dense that makes sense
your ping tool is invaluable for
communicating specific locations to your
partner
oh there you go
oh
nice when will we be able to be
together soon I hope
okay ah it's all on me this time okay CU
cated wait I feel like I've been doing
all the work we're doing the work
together
variances if you want to upet a human
just say their almost killed me me yeah
don't press away don't press anything
okay
ah wait here you go oh thank you you
you're
welcome all
right yeah nice we did it we're speeding
through this yeah for real we're just
too
fast right now what
um hm good
question um Buton oh portal
what does the button
do
uh it's probably because you need to get
a cube and bring it through here I
guess
ah shoot your
[Music]
thing where
else there's nowhere I can go through
here what I see you I you put something
over there oh maybe I yeah wait what can
uh here can you walk through there the
portal disappears but I got it yeah
finally oh I had almost given up hope ah
we can touch each other the first
finally do we get more emotes
oh yeah high five reason to behave like
that now let's continue testing all
right come on a wave no ni yeah okay
onward ah so tutorial huh yeah I
guess I don't mind a little bit of a
tutorial As a treat it's a good
refresher sorry I mean a chicken nugget
oh no by all means I would I would eat
chicken nuggets if I had
them have you ever had um Snickers salad
please explain to me what that is I
thought I thought you would know it's
like a something that's like you know
Middle America type of thing uh we we
don't have anything called Snicker salad
per but I do am quite aware of
something called ambrosia salad what's
that you don't want to know if you don't
know wait
what I don't even know what ambro is is
that like alcohol no it's like a it's
not fruit but it's like
marshmallows uh P sometimes there's like
kind of like pudding stuff in it and
does sound bad yeah and then canned
fruit and like sometimes there's like
pistachio it's good I like it but um
some people think it's it's curse wait
so why why is what makes it salad was
originally created for I don't know EMP
team unlike us just because they want it
to be H okay I see how this
works
oh oh cuz it's got fruit in it yeah
fruit salad okay come through
maybe thank
you uh okay wait
there Hold
Steady okay go through the
door
oh okay by science
collaboration I'm just
kidding wait go go into there yeah oh
nice yeah we're
together that was really easy well I
guess it's just the first level yeah or
maybe we're just
Geniuses do you like puzzle games I do
like puzzle games I'm not very good at
them but I like
them I bet you're better than you think
you
are I was pretty good at poppy playtime
oh yeah you know some human Sports the
winner is the one who scores the fewest
possible points I just thought you might
find that
interesting be quiet
bles
collabor what hey oh one sec wait oh
okay let me hit the button thank you
okay be ready get on through yeah I can
put a portal for you here okay after you
cross over
okay
nice oh here can't we emo
here
yes stop it did you know we originally
used these cameras to capture moments of
int pain and Agony in test subjects oh
this
way the test what is GLaDOS going on
about she hates us it's AAR we gave the
photo to their next of K free of charge
I do really like the lore though where
she wants to test with humans but she
doesn't have any humans anymore so she
made us and she's like a darn I guess I
got a test with these robots I made yeah
oh ready at the same time okay 3 one
go wait what are we
doing there's two down here maybe we
should try these ones first uh wait let
me put a thingy for you yeah
uh all right wait why
oh okay ready yeah where' you want to
go
oh did something happen yes there's a
ball very good you really come together
te thanks to the one of you who appears
to be doing all of the the work
oh wait apparently I don't
know did you beat Portal 2 like the
storybook I did
ah I my favorite thing is everyone's
favorite the lemon speech ah yeah yeah
yeah
classic classic K Johnson I like glus as
a
potato me too I wish I was a potato
noted at all time day naturally maybe an
interesting challenge for one of you
given the other's performance so far o
smart
yes woo okay what I mean wa this is easy
this is baby stuff yeah they need to
give us the hard stuff
like
unbelievable oh
Cube wait what did I hurt you no they
hurt me you can never hurt me oh sorry
I'm kidding destroying them is part of
the test they are no more important you
than you are okay very nice and
then wa it goes through the glass
doesn't it yeah
okay ah then
oh
okay nice I just learned how to jump
you you only just learned how to jump
well I mean why it's only just telling
us the instructions on how to jump at
least one is doing very very well can
you stop being me test
never that's her job it's what she does
best she's such a good singer though for
a programmed lady ah that has that's
probably one of my favorite Parts too of
Portal 2 yeah the music I wonder because
we have Portal 2 per
right maybe we
have two song
permission I don't know what you think
you are doing but I don't like it let's
go new
gesture a gesture where I lose excellent
partnership with one of you handling the
cereal
CH I've seen
this right I'll go in you're not going
to squish me
right
ah I'll try I am trusting you with my
life
okay
um okay maybe go go back to where you
were this seems good or should I go down
wait am I going to get squished yeah go
maybe go down go down maybe stand here
yeah maybe not maybe that was
incorrect uh okay
okay I'm trapped oh
wait
[Music]
um uh H you can see the maze right you
got like a top view kind of yeah yeah
yeah there's Master view below you
there's uh maybe go go on to the
platform next to you this one yeah over
one
more one more down there yeah yeah okay
do you see on the floor
[Music]
yeah you killed me I'm sorry I didn't
mean
to we were getting somewhere though uh
yeah I guess so okay yeah yeah yeah yeah
try again oh so yeah the goal is the
cube yeah yeah yeah I know I think I
think I know how to get to it okay
so get back to where we were before
should be easy
okay uh should I stay
here
yes okay go
across
uhuh now get
on okay grab the cube Oh
yay okay uh wait I think I can exit hold
on
perfect ah thank you thank you yeah I
got you covered and now reflect a
cube may appear that I attacking your
accomplishments using science
collaboration I wonder what the world
record is I mean we're probably pry CL I
think we're the fastest ever
[Music]
seen like a portal speedrun no they
glitch into the wall and
stuff well what about honest speedruns
where you're not taking advantage of
glitches ah then we're the fastest we'd
probably be pretty close yeah I'm sure
somebody in chat
check is there a RuneScape
speedrun I don't know if that's
possible what do you mean speed has be
possible for like any game right it's
not RuneScape is a very interesting
conundrum defit ends yeah the work
really never ends in runes game
a
ever ever
ever like it's just impossible or is
really
difficult uh it's not that it's
difficult but there's just so much
grinding okay
okay I generally see oh what's going on
H
sorry okay now what you got to get
across um portal portal on the wall
portal on the wall and then yeah yeah
yeah uh here here here here here here
don't worry okay wait wait wait wait
wait I won't I won't let you die uh
um okay
nice maybe if I do this just in
case okay this looks
safe okay can you go yeah
okay all right bye
[Laughter]
bye oh wait now you also have to get
over here yes so wait uh you still have
a yeah
so give me
One MH
mhm oh someone in chat says the
RuneScape world record is 14 years and 5
months yeah that sounds about
right is that just getting everything to
level 99
probably some people they really uh it's
it's a grind though it's really not
something you can do fast it's kind of
crazy oh kiding they said they were
kidding they're just making [\h__\h] up
unbelievable
man guys don't lie to us we want the
truth sometimes testing has yeah but I
don't think I don't think anybody can
speedrun it like you said test is so I
can't I mean won't even tell you what
you were looking for you will know it
when you find it
oh she won't tell us what we're looking
for but we'll know it when we find it
maybe it's like something abstract like
love
or you know got a good
point I can't jump down
neither oh
wait oh kind of see like a little area
over here but I don't think I can shoot
portals yeah right I see it oh oh
sorry I don't know why I shot one
bye now you have to find
it no
problem oh we got to we got to do
together ready 3 2 1 go wait wait wait
wait 3 2 1
go 3 2 1
go nice oh
Portal 3 one
go 3 one
go bro it hates us 3 two 1
go
ah oh here you can take the dis oh it's
your color dis M disc selection are we
supposed to go back out I think I think
you might be right you were smart to
make portals yeah you know what it's all
about oh here we go
congratulations you managed to complete
this absolutely meaningless test
meaningless oh I almost forgot when you
go outside the testing courses the only
way I can retrieve you is to violently
disassemble you then carefully
reassemble you that's not very nice but
she does it carefully I mean she cares
about us at any only when she puts us
back together feel
pain failing by the way
it's fine I like getting blown up
sometimes
yeah I can I can you know she's
carefully putting us back together right
now I can feel
yeah very carefully oh hey we're back
stop it what if you froze like that
there must be something wrong with the
reassembly did you ever hear that as a
kid like if you make a funny face if you
get hit in the back of the head yeah
it'll it'll freeze like that right
that's true right chat can you guys
verify that's like something actually
happens
right I don't think so there's no way
what parents just say that so you don't
make any funny faces
[Laughter]
yeah they just don't want you to look
funny well so many people in chat said
yeah it happened to me they're lying I
don't believe them what would you still
have it today or does it go away after a
while I wonder
yeah it's got It's got to go
away or else there be a lot of really
funny looking people they said their
face is still funny looking
so was originally designed to build
confidence in humans to do that the test
okay somebody said it's not really I
think might actually be made up Follow
by meing for
another on how well they walked since
you are thankfully not hum I have
changed the test to make them far more
challenging and far less pointlessly
spawning thank you wait wait there we
[Laughter]
go how many how many levels are there we
might we're kind of speeding through
this we might uh no I don't think
there's that many but I don't I don't
remember yeah chat you got any answers
for us our timing is pretty good right
there's not 100 Levels okay yeah there's
no way
um
hm
oh
jump
okay ah do you have to stay up there
or oh yeah I don't
know you
do uh um
yeah look at you
go uh where's oh there it is almost
landed yeah I know it almost just did
all the work for us placing the Ed
safety cube in the receptacle you should
be that was a circle that's right you're
not humans I can drop the fake PR she's
broken you have no idea how tiring it is
to praise someone for placing an
edgeless safety Cube into a receptacle
I'm going to get you on me
a
stop I can see your
pelvis yeah I can see your egg shaped
body um so little eggy you're egg shaped
too snake eggs are round really I'm
pretty
sure chat can you verify this go oh
sorry I was just please confirm hum can
die in any of those
ways I'll switch it actually I think it
should be your portals then and no
consequences yeah and then I'll switch
it oh I guess it has to be my portals
I'll switch
it good luck
woo
wo okay I think you need more momentum
was that necessary yeah
hm okay all right sorry we'll try time
you just have to let me fall for a long
time it looks like you're building up
speed right
yeah sorry I forgot there I have to
press a button it's okay s right sorry
okay one more time you're you're too
good though yeah kind of get a you know
puzzle brain yeah puzzle brain for
real woo okay
uh for
me
yippe um I did a
flip oh I missed it there's a practice
run okay no worse I had two practice
runs
so my flip
I'm at this I'm
sorry bro how did you how did you get
you got to do the top one oh I got to do
the top
one yay nice work there we
go every time you was the secret way
things used to be but then there you are
again like nothing
happened I can't tell if she's happy
about that or sad oh we're her only
company so yeah she be happy she should
like it she she's so worried about being
lonely you know after she realized what
she did about herself confid is but also
I think she doesn't really care about us
that much cuz we're not she can't kill
us really just kind
of on second thought we don't have the
time just how much better you are Than
Blue
BL you are very good at I'm not sure
what bro why is she talking [\h__\h] about
me okay
button
[Music]
oh can you catch it I don't know can you
come there there's a button down here
can you hop down
here
ah okay but we can't take it through the
the blue thing can we not no
it'll you're
[Music]
right oh but I can go through the blue
thing okay yeah
so sorry we probably need to go all the
way back it's my fault oh that's
okay
[Music]
say go again you're so fast all right
I'm going through it wait but what do we
do after we get the ball oh I guess I'll
stay some oh I'll go back around and
I'll you'll give me the ball yeah
okay here give me now you go and I I'll
pass it
over okay we got
it it okay nice
where are we even bringing the ball
though yeah good
question up
here oh yeah oh you're so smart there we
go beautiful and smart I thought youd be
faster at this that I can appreciate
you're doing good too you're yeah we're
both T
side of disappointment in you
[Music]
remember you have such a big brain it's
like flowing out of your
skull well that's not a compliment no
like your brain waves your brain
waves told you that you were the only
subjects to so big
brain trying to remember oh yeah the
last time we saw each other in
Japan we we ate together right oh yeah
we went to like uh it wasn't super fancy
but it was like one of those those gr
places yeah yakin Nika ah yeah yeah yeah
yeah I love Yakiniku and you were you
were the chef weren't you I I was I do
always like to be the one to
cook
oh it was tasty thank you I'm glad I'm
glad I could cook for
you where he you
go nice wa
okay okay again again sorry I missed
it Go in yeah
okay okay okay
momentum nice wait bro it hates
me okay one more sorry one more time but
I have to be fast too yeah yeah yeah oh
uh and fall again yeah oh did I hit it
yeah you got it but I'm I'm going to
send you to the other side and then
you're going to get the other button
okay okay you can do it okay
oh got to build that speed yeah build up
the
speed nice okay
hit that's okay okay wait oh I see
what's happening yeah two buttons okay
two buttons you are so big brain ah okay
momentum
got okay I hit
it nice hit it woo okay uh ball oh ball
oh many balls one wait what I'm not sure
what she's doing she said we had to
juggle juggle wean our drops are kind of
like being clowns right literally we're
just like her little her little dollies
she sends us around and makes us solve
little puzzle she set up and she's like
what fun you little b-shaped things did
you ever have to learn how to juggle as
like part of PE class no did you
yeah maybe that's not common are you
good at it no no we just learned with
like scarves like these little tiny
square scarves so it was kind of like a
watching some dear a group activity in
even care about the outside do you H
yeah oh
wait wait for
me
Woo you're so fast you beat me
though I figured it out too
quickly I was I was caught in my
childhood
memory oh okay we have to work together
I
think okay
wait but hold on
uh ah I need to come over there right no
no no no yeah yeah just do what you were
doing
before
yeah
okay ni does you
live
barely all right my turn okay I guess
you can maybe go back through and then I
will launch you from
here you're not going to me die
right you you replaced my
thing
oh wait stay
there okay I see I see okay
so okay perfect okay
now um uh-huh uh wait how is this going
to work okay wait okay go
yeah woo wait but can you get up
here ah smart smart same way big brain
moment
ow wait so you're you're officially part
of like Hol toy or no uh no what you're
not a bird I I'm a bird I'm a part of
hotori in the sense that I'm a bird but
a part of the idol group no
ah yeah so you are a bird or you have a
bird I am a bird I am a raven actually
half Raven half demon my mom was a bird
you know oh like a scaly type of thing
no no no she was just like a raven but
my dad liked her so he turned her into
like a a demon you
know yeah okay okay I know what a
weirdo that's
cool you must launch
yourself somehow
okay I'm not sure how wait launch myself
where okay through the wall
probably
[Music]
no how did we get
here yeah that's right okay just hold
on woo okay now goodbye
now that's a good question oh wait I
think I have a good vantage point from
here to shoot
[Music]
no it let me
out
okay uh okay so we're trying to get that
Cube so we need yeah ah wait can we just
get it if you do that and then go go
back over there
if I do what uh get the
cube okay
wait yeah so were you born from an
egg uh Yes
actually cool okay I got the
cube uh now what let be out I can't one
sec I I'll free you in just a moment
what about you were you born from an egg
I guess technically all humans are born
from eggs
way yeah that's true technically
speaking yeah I'll give you this do you
need this I don't I don't think so are
you sure yeah there's nothing up here
unless do we place it on the
button oh here bring it back mayhaps you
were on into
something our little Companion Cube yeah
cuz the exit is
there yeah but then
uh okay then I'll fly through
it h put your Port your portals are
down
yeah aha
okay how do I get there
now uh maybe if you stand on the cube
you go grab the cube and stand on
it oh wait stand come down here come
down
here there we go woo yipp let's go you
know Dances around like an incile when
they accomplish the tiniest little thing
hum I knew it that's what you look like
right now you're better than that we're
better than that
you have a little antenna do I have
one I I don't know let let me get a
better look at
you yeah you do have a little antenna ah
yeah yeah yeah yours is longer than mine
I'm sorry it's cuz I'm rounder you're
taller than me so not high
enough your is way bigger even I was
created I was given too much empathy
with human suffering but I overcame my
handicap that's a
Cube Cube Where Art
Thou I guess the cube will come from
here is there no jumpy thingy oh there
is ah okay go again
okay wait but then you're going to okay
you can't die over there so that's good
that's
fine I okay now go through this portal
[Music]
uh go through it okay now what I don't
know wait no this is not
right let me
see um um um we fly through that one no
oh yeah so then set your blue Port set
your Blue Portal there oh the light blue
one and then you'll fly through it again
no
uh I need to get through here
then there you go
okay and then and then set your light
blue one
there and then I just got to keep
replacing it
mayhaps I know I didn't make it I don't
either I'm stuck oh wait I can go
through
here oh I see
can you you can go through on your own
and then I have a a portal over here on
this one I think he just got to be
fast um
hm oh I think while you're flying you
got to shoot yeah oh close close okay
wait okay okay I'm think I'm sorry I got
to I got to work it out in my brain
apparently
okay okay
what am I doing wrong with my life oh
you got to shoot that
thingy yeah you're right I'm just being
silly at this no you can do
it okay one and two one
perfect oh
nice oh I I figure it out eventually at
some
point
nice okay Cube I think the cube fell oh
yeah it did oh going through wait this
is
fine yeah we just catch
it okay it's down there thank
you all
right now
um now do you have to go back and I
replace your portals and then you
yeah okay it is
ready all right
oh
wo we made it we made it I feel like
this game could make some people motion
sick probably I don't get motion
sickness luckily do you yeah no no no me
neither I would suck for playing
games uh oh there's another excellent
work
maybe I can catch it good
job you are doing
wonderfully
uh oh oh I almost got it
excellent one
more I got it yeah wait what do I do
with this oh back the other
way one again no
problem nice work congratulations on
compl was wait that one was too easy the
other one felt more difficult I know
right I was like struggling consequence
of death is this even
science
science watching your friend get torn
apart and put back together again and
again and again we just get close poster
every time mhm wait are you
streaming yes okay good cuz my stream is
messed up right now no problem no
problem I I'll be there
soon try
again wait how you're I
see
uh might want to you can okay run run a
someone has to hold
it ah
[Music]
H all right stream's fixed now
Yahoo oh oh okay wait wait wait wait I'm
not on I'm not on the elevator sorry
okay get on okay I'm going to die go
fast I don't know what I'm supposed to
do
here something here let's switch Cas you
wondering you do not need to to this
test all right you go in the
elevator
okay oh
portal shoot wait one more
time oh
down what wait let me look let me look
around before we do anything drastic STI
so up
oh wait I'm not on it there's nothing up
there yeah why is why do we need to get
up here oh maybe we jump from up top and
then ah but then well what I'm wondering
is where where are we trying to jump to
there's a button all the way back there
maybe we have to hit it are you on go go
go uh yes
oh no I don't know what I'm doing jump
jump okay got it what'd you
get I think it turned off the things oh
okay
nice
yeah I'm going to bring the cube just in
case we need it yes do we sounds like uh
who who knows but it didn't tell us to
get rid of it so maybe we can yeah
launch the cube
hey you're so
smart I can't decide which is my
favorite okay press for crushing you
come back and you wait near the
door and then I will launch the cube to
open
it
okay maybe there's a portal we can do
make it
faster I I I thought of one kind
of okay are you ready
yeah it didn't work wait let me try one
more
time
ah okay wait use my
portal yeah I just got to walk through
it right
yeah okay just
mine is appar my my my plan is
apparently too too big
brain he go go yeah yeah
yeah ni I think after display we should
take a break from the official testing
courses take a break we're going to The
Unofficial testing courses
now
unofficial not approv stuff I love like
Secrets me
too
Boton oh yeah my partner in science my
steam name does actually fit with this
one pretty well it
does to anyone totally boring and
useless this is just a thought
experiment just to see how much time
you'll waste think about these worthless
documents the correct time is z seconds
uh oh there's Cube uh delivery system oh
nice
somewhere where does this
go uh found something we can jump off
of
okay and then it'll send me flying
to uh oh I guess I'll take number one
portal
H
H what did I
do ah there's our Cube it went up ah
okay I'll go
again does it does like a door open or
something
yeah um oh
wa wait maybe you have to go the same
time can you put a portal side by side
yeah and I'll go I'll press the button
and you catch the the thingy right I
think so
okay a oh so close I missed it I'm so
sorry did you go too
late uh yeah I think so okay ready Let's
uh yes
should we go at the same time oh wait
now go yeah oh okay and now I went too
early so close yeah just wait a little
bit okay you go
first okay I still went too early you
want to
swap
sure I just want to try cuz I want to go
I want to fly as far as you're going
yeah yeah yeah okay okay
um
okay I'm
going I didn't see it you have to wait
till you hear the hear the D do
do I see yeah confusing I was also
confused
okay okay I'm going okay
okay wait for the count wait I didn't
wait I didn't wait I didn't wait ah I
was so close I know
right wow
okay
ah woo you're so big brain well I mean
you're the one who figured it out right
wa we figured it out together
teamwork Teamwork Makes the Dream
workor what's
this I guess got hold it does it stop
the fan no it
oh ah turned on a red
light now what do we
[Music]
do well let me see cuz there's also this
ah there's a place we can send it
uh is there a way to get over
there there's got to be oh this is a
dead
end
H oh maybe we
fly you might okay I'll stop thing oh
sorry no problem
does that mean I'm going to if I if I
drop the cube you'll
die probably okay I definitely won't do
that ah okay I'm in
nice okay there's nowhere for me to
shoot over here I have to go into a
white
room
okay um oh I can see what you're doing
yeah okay oh I see the
thingy okay okay okay
no what'd you
do I don't know did something happen
yeah it's the fan stop or is the fan
permanent the laser yeah yeah okay then
you just need to get over here I guess
the exit I think so H okay
okay there's a door hello oh hello
ready yeah 3 2 1
go got it wait you blocked me I thought
I was going to
die no but it stays open the door stays
open thank
goodness yeah so close okay oh disc wait
does that mean we're going to explode
again no probably not you should be fine
right okay maybe we get to watch some
cool L movie you found those BLS I need
you to be in the room so I can see them
I want to be clear there's no reason
whatsoever for you to look at them oh
done I suppose she I feel like she's
making us do things for
her like why what are we helping her do
I don't know why doesn't she just put
herself into a body a robot body and do
it herself she was a potato once
maybe oh you know what maybe
sheine I don't know what you think you
are doing but I don't like it I want you
to St maybe her brain is too big and she
can't be in like a smaller vessel can I
steal
youa no no no you can't can't humans
only have one oh you beat
me okay wait
what why am I laughing she told a really
funny joke okay a yeah
egg head egg head shut
[Laughter]
up waa you beat me up
bro all right we have time to do a few
more before we it's time for Gary's Mod
should we do that one whatever that is
oh we can do anything ah wait where'd
you send
me the three hard light
stages let's go let's go Mario
I'm Luigi well I guess technically
you're Mario and I'm Luigi yeah cuz
you're the you're the cute tall lanky
one and I'm the chubby round one blue
Mario Mia
Mia wait aren't you actually taller than
me though this course was created and
then abandoned by humans not accurate
tend to do that yeah but our colors are
accurate so it's fine oh I'm lagging
aband it do you know why they abandon
this course Bridge Too
deadly too
deadly and then this one go you're too
smart I think it's like you know the
answer no I don't I don't it's just you
know makes sense
yeah
okay
yay my too
no all right this one I'm going to let
you solve it okay H let me look around
for a little bit okay so there's a thing
here there's stuff up
here uh
H um
uhh oh Bridge oh
oh oh okay
ah BR what okay you need to place the
bridge and then I have to jump okay I
think I caught you okay thank
you it's weird it's strange um okay how
can
I we need to move the bridge over to the
white on the
wall uh uh what move over okay you still
stand on the edge yeah yeah yeah the
other Edge oh wait this way yeah
yeah ah it's
okay okay all right go I I'll catch you
again okay your portal is going to
disappear though that's fine that's
okay
uh
uh there we go
just had to think about it for a
second okay I hit a
button now there
is a ball a
ball oops you go so now uh I got to
go can you move that up
further all right like consider
further
yeah never mind uh move it up further
and then catch me as I fall after I hit
it oh you you're so
smart
nice okay have you worked out the one
tra humans have yet let me give you a
clue it's the one thing you can't
do thank you yeah let's go nice work
nice nice
nice we're just too fast yeah yeah cuz
what is how many how many is the co-op I
think it's just four levels quote
unquote ah yeah uh four or five I don't
know we're on three already I think I
don't know chat do you guys know how
many levels there are kind of like the
level areas in terms of
like there six apparently six chapters
eight levels each still be satisfied
excuse me wait
uh put your portal down somewhere maybe
like
there wait wait wait wait no no we can
replace yeah replace mine and then put
your light blue in there
I guess
wait I'm really good at this game can
you tell all right go again go
again
okay Place light
blue don't press anything after you okay
I
won't okay
oh are we going that way I think so or
is it this
way I don't know all right cuz we came
from over there
yeah oh I
see yeah nice
wow it's really dilapidated in here yeah
I wonder how old cuz it doesn't really
say ortal like a year how far in the
future it is yeah well I mean shell was
here right so it can't be that old but I
mean you don't they don't really say it
could have been like hundreds of years
since the last human that's true I
really love the end for portal to it's
so
good yeah it's so such a good game oh
you know the turret
you know the
song
Yes
[Music]
like can you believe this you can't test
we tried they just sit there never
showing pain nor fear that is in
science
oh
smart really look like he could fall
right
now I know
I'm
scared okay but yeah we W have a lot of
time this will have to be the last one
we got to out
okay okay okay do this
wait uh okay Cube oh button oh there's a
button right there did we press that
button no I'll go press it though
okay let me go get it oh somebody in
chat says World 2 takes place 50,000
years after half lifee 2 okay be on the
bridge and get ready to catch it okay
okay how many years after half lifee
2 oh oh No Just yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah okay 50,000 wait they said that's
not true never mind th yeah I think
they're just making things up why would
you guys do that yeah why would you lie
to
us we are but humble
streamers we just want the truth we just
want fact yeah we want the
fact
sorry oh uh
uh
where
huh can I go over there I don't
know what's
happening uh maybe you oh I see okay
I'll stop you you put your Bridge
instead of mine and then I'll stop you
with the
Bridge wait no uh yeah we got to put one
there uh yeah
okay did you I think you hit the edge of
it
right brings back such wonderful
memories' don't
H
Dy all right just do I need to move it
over a little bit no ah okay and then
wait
wait there you
go I see it it's
perfect oh all right goodbye wait wait
wait
wait uh
uh now we just need to reverse it right
catch
me oh
wait how do I do that okay it'll be mine
and then like this and then you put
yours oh you can't I guess you can't
okay then it'll be your
portal don't worry about it
yeah
okay oh
wait what oh wait what I don't know I
don't
[Laughter]
know
y okay
yay yay we did it we we did the portal
oh W if you were human you would want to
we'll have to stop here that's fine
thank you so much for taking the time to
do a collaboration with me sen of course
it's really fun H yeah oh F oh we're
we're too good how about a little bit of
this a little bit of that oh yeah yeah
yeah oh oh are you doing the robot H I
think so you weren't doing
it no yeah a there we go yeah look at
us all right you're going to play right
no I'm not playing it I'm scared of
Gary's Mod that's understandable I'm
looking forward to watching it though
okay thank you I love you AM stand by
thank you for the fun memories of course
bye okay bye byebye Amy okay thank you
for playing yeah thank
you there she
goes H let me wave goodbye one more time
[Music]
byebye see
y I can't exit all right I got to set up
a portal too that was fun all right I
got some messages here let me
check all right I got to answer some
messages and set up so if you guys could
please wait thank
you all right one second
[Music]
uh
ah okay I just remembered a small little
thing for the Garry's Mod thingy one
second
all right let's put on some music while
we wait if you guys don't mind got to
figure out something
[Music]
for
in
[Music]
hello oh raid oh
redirect hello
[Music]
in
hello okay I think I pretty much sorted
everything out
[Music]
okay hopefully that works let me make
sure everybody's
[Music]
all
right see
[Music]
almost ready almost ready almost
ready oh some people are already in game
nice nice
[Music]
ah a little bit delayed start for Gary's
Mod that's okay I uh there were a few
steps I forgot
for Garry's Mod I totally forgot you
have to have Counter Strike Source
installed I think some people already
had it installed cuz they played Garry's
Mod last time we
played but some people are on new PCS or
they didn't have it installed so I was
like wait a second I have had it
installed for a long time
so yeah yeah it uses the same source
files
[Music]
uh classic valve yeah
let me check server really
quick yeah my keyboard
ASMR all right let me take a picture of
something
[Music]
uh one second
all right I found something that seems
useful one second
[Music]
ah this is strange I was able to connect
just fine earlier but I wonder if maybe
a lot of people are connecting right now
and it's having an issue with it I'm
going to do
[Music]
restart yeah Gary's mon service can be a
little strange
[Music]
okay yeah we're stuck at a
authenticating with steam loading screen
but I connected earlier and it
worked I didn't have any issues
connecting but at the
moment let me do a server
restart sometimes it just works maybe
it's a steam issue yeah maybe thank you
for the
gifts all
right seems like it's back up let me try
again
[Music]
all right now it's
loading let me see let me make sure I'm
loading in in
okay I think it's
fixed there we go there we go it's going
it's
going yep
[Music]
okay
nice all right I'm
in yes everybody's joining cool okay um
the plan is to use the in-game voice
chat so hopefully it's working let me do
some testing I got I'm going to show you
guys the screen in a moment after I fix
all this
stuff just wait just
wait uh let me check my
options uh uh-huh uh-huh test test test
test test test yep
working okay
yeah looks
good okay now to find what key I have
for voice chat I don't remember voice
chat
ahuh test test test test test
test wonder if there's a way to restart
the round I don't know what the command
is I'm in game but I'm in game by myself
hold on I think there's a button to
change
teams not sure you hear the steps
yeah
uh I remember what the button is to
change teams not M right that was
TF2 right let me check make sure it's
working for everybody
maybe there's like a white list I wonder
if there's a server white list from
before I don't
remember uh let me look at the server
files I'm able to join because maybe
because I'm admin sorry guys I had it
figured out I was able to join earlier
so I was like oh it's
working
okay it's just me setting it up so it
takes takes a while yeah it says people
are joining
but okay there should be something here
that has to do with white
[Music]
listing I think there was a file that I
added in the server files with like a
white list for something
let me
[Music]
see
uhuh that's working
[Music]
okay one
second uh
[Music]
ah aha wait this might be it
shoot I feel bad like I'm letting you
guys
down
[Music]
ah h
yeah it worked last time and I'm using
the same server setup and everything but
I guess this time it's not working
[Music]
properly one moment s
checked every
single
uh hello sorry still trying to fix
[Music]
okay it should be like right here in
the
settings I don't see
that I don't know hold on I'll be right
back
[Music]
for
hey is everything good
Oh I thought it was mut never mind okay
[Music]
everything is fixed guys I I'm going to
Quick idem eating but everything is
fixed so uh as soon as I get back we're
going to
play we did it yay
[Music]
for
hello hi I'm
back all right I'm in game I'm just
uh trying to remember how to change
teams yeah okay it's
F2 okay
test test hello is anybody else
dead
okay all right we're in uh I'm I'm not
in voice chat I think some people are in
Discord but I thought we could just use
in-game voice chat but I don't know if
maybe we should use Discord
instead I feel like it might be a little
bit simpler to use ingame Bo chat cuz
you know proximity chat and stuff
actually I don't know if there's
proximity
chat yeah they're
playing all right let me check just to
make sure
[Music]
tacos Bales joined props yeah on the
next round so there's only 13 seconds
left we can actually talk and
stuff check check mic check mic check
mic
check I think I'm only in one team so
whoever's on my team would be able to
hear
me yeah there's one in Spectators one in
Hunters
okay oh
shoot now maybe we should go voice chat
I don't know if I have mine enabled
guys hello can you hear me all right let
me check my settings really quick
sorry
uh Voice receive voice
enable yeah should be able to hear
it okay if not we'll just join
Discord say test test test
[Music]
test hello can you hear me hello oh yeah
I can hear you can you hear me oh yay I
can hear you yeah okay so if you press E
I don't know if you guys already know
press e on a prop and you'll turn into
that
prop I think I died trying to fix my
thing oh it
happens why is everyone just this bald
man that's scary
mod himself why does he just teleport
around yeah he just slides
around
beautiful wait I think you're still
alive if
you're if I can talk to
you
really I don't know if dead people can
talk in this game mode I'm not sure
te oh everybody learned the key at the
same time he hi hello oh sorry I had to
Old
tab hold the button yeah you got to hold
it can you guys hear me yeah we can hear
you I'll
go I'll go try helping the others in
invoice ah thank thank you oh so so it's
like a press button microphone yeah
press X
Y yeah okay unless you changed your key
some people might have used X to be
their player model select so if you did
you just have to go into settings yeah
hi I I tried to select the character but
it won't change I I just keep te posing
this smell teing yeah well you can't you
can't change this character anyways in
Prop Hunt I think unless you're no oh
yeah here MAA press e on this chair over
there I'm right next to you
hi yeah there this chair press e on
it what wait what's the key to hold
on
ah wait how can you move you got you you
got to use the W what do you mean what
do you
mean I maybe how can you move press R
maybe you're
locked what
uh Ollie how can you
move what did you do maybe you got
stuck oh really did you die
dang did you
die I don't know just tell suicide
killed oh don't mind that I don't know
why that's I don't know it's up there oh
you're not dead yet you can press e on
objects you're moving I see you moving
there you
go yeah you can become wait I'm an
object yeah yeah so this game mode
you're supposed to hide I I thought I
was in I was the
hunter oh okay but
luck this isn't suspicious at all to be
a microwave yeah there's a lock key
button but do you guys remember what the
lock is it's not e not R wait how to
press again oh F uh press
what to change the object Oh
e all right we could start for real
hello okay we're alive thank you
guys is the screen supposed to be black
right now happening where where're okay
so we're playing C help and maybe we
should play Murder first okay but we're
playing Prop Hunt and we're going to
hunt for the props that are hiding in
the
map okay yeah and it's like hide and
seek uh all
ew freaking Baby W
Smurf
cute is everybody else's voice shot
working let's see we have who are you
baby that's GG oh she's a penguin
now oh um I don't know the sound of a
penguin um is not supposed to have guns
why do you have a gun with me hold I'm
going to check make
sure all right just making sure uh there
we go
Stu correctly set up
voice oops there there is a tutorial how
to buy change the a to the o yeah can
you hear me oh I didn't look at any
tutorial CU I had a meeting before the
stream ah yeah I just barely made it to
I just barely made it probably it has
been been bind yet that's why yeah oh
okay then yeah it's okay I'll just be an
old
man okay I can I can show I'll I'll I'll
link you in Discord Discord just in case
okay if you're dead or something then
you can do it really quick it's super
fast
all right one
[Music]
second yeah I put a little bit video
tutorial to show how to change
characters here it is
all right little props where are
you who else is playing Ana I'm hovering
over something it says fauna but I shoot
it and it it doesn't do you see this oh
yeah it says FAA for some reason maybe
she's really small hello hi
how do I SP her oh right click on you
have different weapons if you pull out
your SMG
oh someone's dead is this B wait where
are you guys shooting
no oh that's was that MAA what the I got
her her her I guess she just had a lot
of HP so was she was sitting
there I I cannot see her wait why I only
saw her name and that's it oh if you
shoot
suddenly die you can die if you shoot
too many items it's like it lowers your
health
oh blue cat down blue cat
down
[Music]
oh I don't know why it says suicide
killed up at the time I think it's some
type of bug no
there got to be people
left uh hi I hear you I hear
you hear me yeah I can hear you oh you
can hear you now yay
hi hi I'm glad it works I think there's
like a feedback there's like a feedback
from my boys I don't know where it comes
from I'm going to TW with it a little
bit I don't hear anything in here yeah
hey guys there's so many dead
people bab's on the Run she's running
she's going to I only see my teammates
B's she's in the office I see her I see
her get her get her I'm running oh
no right are we uh I thought I would
switch sides but I guess we
swap maybe after a few
rounds the camera will show your name if
looked at ah yeah I don't know what the
lock screen right now for everyone right
I can hear you yeah yeah yeah hi Ms I'm
having some problems here what's the
problem I see it it looks really good it
does it I like it why why what problem
why
a lot of
Errors big scary letters did you do the
workshop
thingy yeah uh did I do it wrong did you
subscribe to
all hold on I'll be back okay I'm
clipping through the world help help
help I'm clipping I'm
clipping I think we'll we'll probably
switch game modes uh just so we have one
where we can make sure everybody's in
the same area and kind of test things
out one
second right so you can't just blast
anything yeah yeah you you'll lose HP if
you just kill if you just shoot at any
object you have to be sure it's them
let's
see oh and props can I don't know if we
can oh wait I see you why you shouldn't
have moved
bio uh biu on the Run she's in the Pro
she's in the projector room why we kill
Kyla oh where go what the hell she
disappeared and she's hiding here
somewhere hell hello should
Anil I killed her
I see someone moving I can't really tell
what they are though I saw a name over
here oh little crony oh little
box hi where's everyone hiding I have a
gun with your name on
it is is all chat not on I wonder guess
all's not on little baby all right one
second all right I'm going to I'm going
to switch maps that way we can talk to
everyone and make sure see if anybody
else is having any issues one second
okay can you guys all test hi I can hear
you now it should be like oh we hear
you test test is just having hi yes yes
yes
youing holding no I'm I'm helping for uh
sorry sorry I was talking to them sorry
hey can you guys type uh exclamation
point RTV in the chat
not you guys chat RTV
RTV thank you thank you
[Music]
we just want to kill you we don't have
enough RTV
people weird sound wasse oh I can hear
you hi no sorry Moa
it's working all okay sound good yeah
yeah it sounds good yeah yeah yeah yeah
awesome thank you thank you we should
have tested this before the stream sorry
hey look it work did it okay so what
what are we doing we're killing objects
kill yeah they're not objects they're
people they're people okay they're Souls
debatable yeah oh no oh we have to free
them from the
object oh they're trapped hey look turn
around and look at look over
here look do you see
it right here right here there a
penguin That's me yeah that's Chi shoot
shoot ma shoot this
box wait they won shoot we didn't find
them all all right hold on
what I wonder if it'll switch side oh
here it goes
all right nice try nice
try ah we can switch game game next do
you guys see anything there
what completely game mode next no it's
empty it just says which game next with
nothing okay it only says which game
mode next okay but it is asking us yeah
so thought that counts
right so nice of them yeah the illusion
of choice okay
H okay now now that we're have full team
we'll we'll beat them up they're going
down yeah
yes uh any second now any second now
something happening in your screen
everyone just says which game mode next
holding aage yeah all right hold on let
me check something
nominate a
map yep can hear you we can still hear
you okay no worries I think the stream
is
dying oh dead
oroni can you guys I'll type RTV since
you're all here exclamation point
RTV you can type in chat with Y open
chat
why can I spam it
myself it
works wait I cannot
type wait how to type uh y uh press y
press y
why oh no we need you
so
scuffed sorry guys hey we're going to
get there we're getting
there
ah no registered votes three map votes
left hello we can part of the
entertainment hi
ah oh shoot okay forget the RTV thing
what the
hell I see
so it does show up RTV shows up
happening hold
on okay oh yeah we're just waiting
I love Gary's Mod I it's the install I
think of
the yeah I think I could have changed
the
map six out of nine
but I I can't even see the uh server
thing do you guys know the co command to
change the freaking
map wait it says nominate your favorite
map okay okay okay it's nominate
clue I know I have clue
installed I think clue is probably the
best map for wait
hide or unhide the map voting HUD RTV to
start the vote for next
map change
level
clue change
level clue
a in the console I'm the admin don't
worry I think it
worked hold on it's loading
[Music]
okay this is good
hi oh
scary let me change the game settings
really
quick hello test test
hi
[Music]
hello Al's trapped in this room let's
see if she can figure out how to
escape does she know that there's a
secret door
it's like an escape room except there's
only one button you need to press
oh they're all RTV
too what team am I on on the on the on
the other on am stream you're blue like
you're like ah oh you're a blue cat oh
okay you're like but like on for me
you're just like giant arrow
[Music]
you did not
download I did I don't know why it's not
working you subscribe to
all I'm subscribed to all did you do it
in the steam
launcher uh no I did it in the game
ah see if you can get it in like your
steam browser launcher if you go if you
use that same link and then subscribe
all there and you probably have to
restart the
game okay okay I'll try going out and in
again oh Kelly there's a secret wall
somewhere you can
escape oh don't tell me that oh no are
you are you lying to me Watson
no really yeah how do I find the wall if
you knew where it was why wouldn't you
tell me where it is Watson cuz I want
you to figure it out it's an escape room
oh oh I don't know I don't I don't know
how much of this I believe
you got to press a
button oh my
God yeah I guess we can't hear everybody
uh let me check
something one second checking
something yeah I think there's a way to
have it on Discord uh sorry in all chat
button in front of a door it looks like
a bookshelf
oh I guess we should you I don't know
should we
uh I like the in-game voice chat I think
it's nice but maybe we should use
[Music]
Discord hold on still checking
okay all right I found the uh command
for it one
second um
armor uh yeah
wait where did they say that
oh do you guys know how to turn into a
prop uh
PR press e right you have to go up press
so like you have to like go up to a
chair and then press
e
okay oh you did it okay nice okay thanks
you did nice nice nice you have one
person
HP we are all this this old man now
hold on I can fix the old Chat
thing is the
vo I'm pressing you
have yeah you have to find a prop first
baby
down I can't become the
prop s your audio is scen for you guys I
was trying to figure out
what yeah oh I'm back y oh no oh okay
all chat is on now we can all hear each
other no matter what team you're on
right
yay
okay wait let me exit out of something
yeah okay just double
checking I could kill you if I wanted to
no don't
wait I'm pressing e but it won't it it
has to be like a specific okay look
just kill only some
props turn
off it's so scary you oh I feel bad you
didn't have you have like no opportunity
oh I feel I feel so
bad what you guys can press e on the box
I'm scared guys
it's a little bug hold on sorry
I tried a bunch of chairs and boxes and
a a baby toy and it didn't work oh uh it
might be something in your settings if
you check like no baby's
allowed I check I check the use items is
set to eat
[Music]
so did you make sure that the cursor was
like on the GL dot was on the item
there's like a little
crossair
stop all right I'll tab me again
I think I see you come sorry hold
on who killed the
monkey come into this what don't kill
the Mony there's a dead monkey I don't
see him who killed the monkey see if I
go into this I can't go into this room
I'm I'm hopeful you can find something
something to turn
into oh here no wait uh not that chair
supposed to be a try a smaller oh this
lamp try the
lamp yeah try the green lamp try the
chair that's on the
bed no nothing will
change how about oh how about the
suitcase wait oh see it worked it work
you did you
did it's nice nice nice just really
limited shooting nice that was CR you
guys all right hold on I'm checking
something no I'm sorry my instincts just
took over me it's okay so
scary oh
cie there's a fall damage in this game
yes you'll never find
really yes yeah I fell fell and that
baby wait what is
there where's my voice doubling oh I
don't hear it are we stuck here
I guys have 10 seconds 10
seconds oh no pick up pick up pick up oh
no let's
go no it's really hard to win as like a
hunter yeah it's super super difficult
to was I a prop last round I don't
remember was I yeah no did it switch
rounds like were we prop last oh yeah
teams have swapped okay can you um
switch again after you switched into one
thing I think so yeah F2 I think it will
wait until the next round
though wait to switch uh I think she
means a means a prop yeah you can switch
again afterwards
yeah and apparently you can right click
and you'll lock in as a
prop how do we leave the room
as oh we got to press e on the
door did I have I freed
you e I'm just like really
like a cute I see I see something
running up the stairs who is that oh T
where is
everyone I saw a baby I saw a baby where
it where why can't I turn into object
swe uh yeah me too Acky you're holding a
baby close to it you press e again you
have to like I see something upstairs
guys it's a
[Music]
lamb guys you see that you see that
baby where I'm
is that baby just always there run run
I'll protect you I'll protect you no did
I get it it
[Music]
fell
[Applause]
M all right who's next Who's the monkey
I think there's like some secret secret
passage ways we got to check
do I take fall damage found a good place
you this is crazy yeah
damage wait how do you switch to a
different
prop oh my goodness you have to go up to
some I suddenly
suddenly I'm pretty sure there's a
break I'll let you get away this
time have a flashlight you press
flashlight turn the flash on oh my God a
flashlight
how turn the
flash F oh okay okay okay I turn it back
on thank you if you don't want to die
show yourself I found you should it be
the opposite I will kill you to show
yourselves did I get it no Vengeance for
what you've
done H wait wait this place is confusing
I'm lost
I chasing something and now I can't find
it who are you guys shooting at I want
in someone was here where are
they get the babies out how could
you you are so brave that a good HP and
a dream I didn't know they will be there
cilia
please scared me I thought it was like a
phone thing I wasn't sure if you were
real were trying to kill
me my bad my bad oh good you look
beautiful it's a beautiful I just wanted
to like jump on you but for some reason
it was impossible I watch
baby got oh where are you one HP and a
dream
no gr damn rest in pepperoni
doing wait so who who's left are there a
lot of people left is in a good place
you got one she must be close
to if you guys go to the SMG and you
right click you get like a bomb it's
like a
grenade can you guys hear
me I can hear you ollie I hear you I
hear you
[Music]
she's trying to escape she's
going I'm sorry I got I lost clipped
into the wall little baby
girl we
won oh god oh GG nice GG's we switch
teams too messed up GG
okay I know where I want to go I know
where I want to go wait how do we get
please make it easy for us no
maybe wait how to change
again e
e i I cannot change you have to go up to
an object
back yeah and you got to you got to
point your Crosshair at it how do you
hold your SP
oh right click right click fellow baby
baby they come from the same womb maybe
right click isn't working for um it
looks like
it there's no baby here A bunch
[Music]
of e chat is saying e is saying
E I don't think that's it I think that's
canot
change it's not R I said change please
oh my left
click how do you get out of the house
out of the room as a hunter is there a
friendly fire in this game Oh e is to
open
doors oh thank you oh no
friendly
no C thank you C you doing oh you just
man you make sure that your little
Crosshair is pointed on something and PR
in this there's Friendly Fire you shot
me f f
Flashlight hold right click
it'sing it'sing it has to be like a
specific item like a smaller one like a
prop or chair or something
small how do we get out from here help
open the door e if I if I move around in
the game it moves my P right isn't
working with the
doors yeah I can't open the door I it
depends on the door
for for a second close the
G oh I think you have to stand back a
bit we just need to
click I
see get
it why you shooting that yeah a lot of
people haven't played Gary's before hard
to find any props yeah mine not working
I tried any items it's not
working uh are you a hunter or wait you
have to be a c oh you are props hey
hello oh
my yes we can hear you MAA check your Ed
key can you hear me yeah I can hear you
cop this one oh my I don't even know
what I did but I guess I got it to work
yeah oh yay nope it's not Chang yeah
murder might be better uh I got to check
something
one second I got to check something are
other people streaming I hope it's not
just my perspective cuz uh I keep
tabbing out to check stuff yeah there's
TTT but I feel like people will just
immediately start shooting each other
TTT but yeah we can do TTT oh after
after this round do you guys want to try
you want to try
TT it's a different game
mode don't know what that is but sounds
fun yeah it's a new game mode a new game
mode
okay
yeah wait wait what's that baby who's
that
baby the B baby there's a lot of
[Music]
babies take this
B I did so well just saying yeah shoot
me you
guys yeah yeah we're on push sorry mhm
uh yeah I'm on push
sorry that I'm
doubling you didn't double just now I
wonder if we have what TT Maps we have
um I got to
check one second
oh death run
can you guys press oh can you guys do
RTV again I just want to
check RTV RTV oh God we're stuck in this
one again RTV what there's there's
commands there but I can't see
them there's it's showing up but shoot
it's like all
blurry did I just press one which game
mode next that's the angel
question oh maybe we can vote my chat
doesn't send how do
vot
uh oh we're doing TTT now okay it's
working all right game mode change let's
go so maybe TT is a good one to
learn hi we're back what is this hi oh
yeah
TT what what do you do in TT so there's
one detective and there's like two or
three terrorists who are we don't know
it's kind of like Among Us right they're
like
Impostors and if you're a te you got to
try and kill everybody else without
getting killed
yourself oh this is among us before
among us became a
thing how do you know if
you uh right now it's preparing so we'll
see
afterwards okay okay okay yeah there
little
countown what's that no brother
no there's weapons weapons on the map
yeah and if you scroll and click then
you can select your
weapon they're nodding at each other
I killed
someone does this work oh my goodness
sorry naughty baby na baby sry naughty
baby uh yeah there is an echo somebody
has one I'm a detective hey I'm a
detective are you
killer who shooting this where's the
detective let's protect the detective
where are you wait what kind of deame is
this is different from before it's like
Among
Us oh RDM RDM I I thought we were still
preparing we know who is who is the bad
guy oh so you can test dead bodies as a
detective what is this making
me we have to kill them first uh
somebody has to die get away from me get
away from me who wants to sacrifice
their life in the name of oh there's a
dead body over here here
someone shoting me detective detective
someone shooting me detective I'm going
to shot
detective
what
C check her body check her body
P oh wait who's who's
shooting why is everyone killing each
other have weapons or not you if you
scroll and click you'll have
one did you check check her
body okay I check the body you you
scroll down and then you have on the
right side it says one two three and
three is shotgun she was innocent I
don't have I don't have say I'm a
traitor it's missing three two and three
was
you hey you have a rifle don't you kill
on site
Flo hey
each why are you killing
me I didn't know I was a train
sorry where are they where are they oh
Ma's trying to hurt me for no reason I
haven't done anything wrong why am I
Traer we have to lure them out there's
so many dead bodies fresh donuts I kill
any of those
donuts the detective
thought was
Gigi uh I think we're dead she hear me I
think we're dead I don't think they can
hear
us like Among Us
yeah how do you just like Among Us on
the heads oh no the babies are dead I'm
good at this babies I believe in you we
got this who killed the babies I mean oh
who could it be we we what that's
French we
wee
we we
we we we on the ground how do I how do I
put up the gun on the ground there's
like two death I can't pick up the gun
on the ground
either I I'm trying to shoot but I can't
I guess I can't do that I need to tell
them to scroll you have have you
reloaded have you tried pressing r
I pressed R nothing happens oh my God I
died deserved literally
deserved welcome to the dead just like a
Among Us oh it's over for the yellow
people welcome to the yellow
Squad yellow Squad let's
go
crazy oh tra won I didn't do anything
I the of the
round I died right after the start of
the round okay I thought there were two
traitor I'm going to tell you guys how
to play okay all right so if
you oh
wait why is she I thought
to all right so to pick up a weapon I
think you just have to walk over it or
press press e and then scroll and click
if you scroll you should see a little
menu and then you click on that what
your weapon is and then you can attack
with mouse one so left
click thank you yeah the weon selection
which one is the Crowbar sorry can you
can you repeat it oh yeah just scroll
like on your mouse and then click and
it'll bring out your
weapon
oh always three
Traders how do I equip it how
do scroll and then click to it so scroll
to it and then
click no it's a
compliment all right if you say
so anyway it says I'm innocent how do we
for myself I I was a traitor now I
innocent I see the bar innocent there's
a dead body here innoc
really kitty cat I don't want you to be
evil how how do we get the ammo how do
we get evil either I think we have to
someone a baby just threw a baby just
threw a grenade a smoke grenade at the
group of
people
itous wait I'm a baby wait am I a
Baby K you're you're the baby you're the
baby B I was a baby guys someone's
dead yeah someone
just my God I got I got something
good killed baby killed a
baby who Nana M was a traitor how do I
search m was a
tra yeah that's why I killed her but
then I got
killed as soon as I see somebody f off
their gun at someone I'm aiming for them
I'm how do you select the weapon again I
forgot you see it on the bottom right
and then you click on it oh click on it
again together yeah you just you scroll
and then are you nice are you an okay
person what who did that Ollie who who
did that was it Ollie are you one of the
bad guys wait what no she so I shot her
wait what happened
GG where are you it says innocent you
killed me last time you should
[Applause]
piss Che the
body who is it but that was the fakest
who this so I don't who killed you shot
oh I'm sure but it was a baby stop stop
stop stop oh that's a
massacre oh my God they don't
know
what I don't think you can check who
killed you ollie you've been shooting a
lot of people I was set up by another
baby can you promise not doore me but
I'm innocent I I promise I'm not going
to Sho you I'm just saying can you
promise not to do it
anymore insane
you I think
me what what did I say Allie killed me I
didn't shoot before I shot the glass
oh my God she's just massacring people
which one of them do you think is the
actual one time left and that means the
Traer is still here I know which one it
is wait so the only left like one person
which one I'm not sure I think there's
more but they're just not here they
can't hear me right I
think five people are still
alive which is Kyla olly Callie me and
Zeta
that's everybody here right are you a
traitor
yes are you tra are you a traitor
no are you I don't
think the only one I'm sure of is kylo
because when you go when you scroll over
her it says
detective me
up okay no I'm just kidding you
did baby I know they went to the wrong
baby I forgot I was
baby that killed me why tra
awesome because it's fun and I want to
win how about we shoot each
other what do it mean win what a thing
to say when you're not the traiter
though Kyla has made her choice I want
to win that's why I want to get rid of
as
possible what happen if they kill
everyone except k at least no she's the
detective she's the only one 100% not
not can't do that innocent I haven't
killed
anyone call can vouch for
me
yeah me I guess yeah
right says reputable and you're wounded
it's between Z and ol
killing is that a
GU that was
tragic I love being a big
rat so I want to come back inside
though oh GG
nice job that was
hilarious all these Violet terrifying or
are you calling for GG
GG's
both's one of them
GG come here
my we're just preparing again right yeah
yeah I believe
so it says innocent on mine guys it says
innocent on
mine innoc on
mine it's also says throw a
grenade you can throw a grenade how
great so we're all wow how do you throw
a
grenade looking at me kind of weird how
how can we get a weapon again oh hi Gigi
you have to walk over it hi why is
everyone your jacket just walk over it
and then scroll and click thank you
thank you how do you feel about my I
want a gun too why can't I get a gun
kind of threatening H why is everybody
wearing Green Jackets I see it's okay
it's nothing scary defaulting SC any I'm
just a bird it's K everyone with the
green why do everybody have a gun
scary kill everyone with the Green
Jacket
gotta get me no it's okay that was just
a little poke in the shoulder at me wait
why does MAA say she's a crude oh yeah
like if you hover over her it's she's a
crew Peng the
penguin penguin we going for the
[Music]
penguin
TR killed the penguin we were
awward I'm a detective too it was you
wait what what do we do you have to test
the
bodies random shooting us come check the
bod shoot the
P watch out leave me alone
stop why did you shoot me y who killed
her she's innocent Z was
was a tra
too where to go Meo nice
job I have my crowbar and me I don't
have guns like you guys fire my crowbar
death you got to walk over
fire what stop attacking
me you're SAU I'm inoc
please dud
anything I clicked by accident Kyla did
you start did you set a fire where are
you running Kyla start a fire today Ana
what did you do to our
inmates no I was just trying to poke her
on the shoulder you're being weird
you're being with a gun no help she's
trying to kill me I'll avenge you what's
going on here I know she's the traitor
please please I'm innocent Ollie ol hold
on a second you killed Gren what you do
you killed was a smoke grenade every
suspicious to
me you show that to me I did it
R what what' you do are you a good
person crony are you
good tra can you test me or could you
have done that cuz you wanted all the
glory there's a big rat over there see
all congregating in the hallway I am
innocent I'm now going to approach
I'm I'm innocent though I'm innocent I'm
innocent but why did you shoot us
earlier then if you're inocent that's
what an innocent person would say
because you shot at me confused no I
never shot you you shot me out of
nowhere I was just standing around
that's not true you fired your gun at me
and it was very frightening please I
innocent not true but there's only one G
right have blasted you all from around
the corner and I told you I chose to
tell you I was here CH I chose to alert
you to my presence and you just one a
killer would
do one tiny I don't know if I buy this
Kell it's a little big I feel
like silent you're definitely a traitor
aren't you I'm
not well
she test her test her oh she wasn't this
see why would you guys kill
her I
what is too I can't I'm not even that
close to
it I think the chicken I don't know who
the chicken is but they keep throwing
grenades I know but she told me she was
a detective I am a detective please
don't shoot me I have 4
hpec die but she said she was a
detective I'm I'm
innocent would you
like is the detective test me no
yeah she was innocent oh no she was
innocent oh no an inned being why why
this is where your lies will get
you there's only one I swear to God yeah
detective I thought were she said she
was
one oh my
gosh I love who who did that who did
that
that hurt
no no see
I Sil you
all silence is so suspicious to me I
can't get past it I just think it's her
every
time so evil
sorry messed
up let me check something
oh that's very dangerous I I
know please believe me when I say I'm
innocent from here on out we have we
have someone we absolutely trust is
there a way to test as a detective you
guys know chat here cuz usually like in
TT Maps
something some one person to trust I'm a
detective oh do detective who's
shooting what are you somebody's already
Traer shooting CC Trader CC
traitor
okay he's worked out for the rat with a
Glock that would be me I killed her I
killed cilia I would I see are you cool
just the map tra
hey tra good
[Music]
job no if I was trying to kill
you
what start with a at
the over her body I am I am concerned yo
K's a I saw KY it couldn't be that she
was inspecting the body she had a
crowbar out and she's completely silent
oh
no what should we kill her oh full m
keep an eye the detective is
dead oh no
stop I need a
gun one second
people let me check yes because they
fired at me first who wait who a likely
story Callie are you guys really going
to do
innocent you killed two people though
yes they fired at
me think me no one approach me why can't
if we approach you you're going to kill
us cuz you're a traitor no no not
because I'm a traitor because you're
going to try and kill me I I promise I
promise kill kill Cy stop wait who's
saying kill who's saying kill to defend
myself I just killed CR I just
killed okay check Cron's body check
Cron's
body where's crony's body I'll check it
I'll check it
where is she this is terrifying are you
following me people's following
me I'll protect you by I was the one who
killed CeCe oh okay yes she was a
traitor where's Callie did she die for
the of theame Callie where are you if
you find me you're going to kill me
no I'm lost everybody spread out okay
wait why does gigi want to kill Callie
so bad movie Stu is it cuz gig's a
terrorist if I was a traitor doesn't
whatever kill all of
you help me
uhhuh
[Music]
kill
way way yeah that's something a killer
would say killer making up excuses to go
after me you're the one who killed
multiple people already yes when they
shot at me
[Music]
is freaking me
out this is terrifying that scares you
her silence is so
[Laughter]
loud all right Callie tell me where you
are and I'll holster my gun she came
right I promise we can believe you I've
holstered my gun I'm here to make
amends going to kill me if you find
which one are you g no no look we can
talk I'm the penguin I think there's a
lot of corpses underground guys like a
lot of them underground underground
where in the garage there's an
unidentified old man let's see oh
wow there are wait did you kill these
people oh that's that's unfortunate
they've been
dead since only Di I don't I'm gonna say
I don't it's been three minutes that
killed
her they died three minutes
ago the crony was down there oh but wait
no cron was didn't you see was so good
at hiding died one minute ago I found
her before she's in this
building but now she's gone we were all
together except for
anymore she's she's not even defending
herself
I'm kind of scared of Ky a little bit
I'm scared of Kyla as well should you
take her out should we take her out
what's overtime why do you want to kill
people so bad
huh who's that who's shooting who's
shooting I don't know I think Kylie
died said shead where is she oh she was
a traitor didn't mean anything to you oh
wait oh she is so there's only one more
Among Us yeah yeah she is a traitor oh
the who's the first
traitor was CE I don't know if but I
killed her you killed her she was King
me she right where are where are you
now uh where's KY there oh Kyla's dead I
killed her killed her what oh oh should
we check her body to make sure she's not
the terrorist uh does anybody have
detective uh I think anybody can check
the
body okay hold
on here wait where
is is Alie alive hold on she's dead I
think oh okay cuz I notice that when
olie's the traitor she goes awfully
silent like KY you guys RTV I want to
see something
sorry Kyle was innocent
sorry one more RTV y oh murder okay let
me try to vote for one who threw that
who threw that I threw that why did you
thw that how do I vote how do I vote
don't you like how dusty it is now
that's no that's bad for my lungs why
should we vote for
one I don't know if it's oh yeah yeah
you can vote H I don't know if it's
working you want me to do that too oh X
it's exclamation point1 Oh it changes
right
away I want to I wanted to see if it
works but I didn't know it would happen
right
away I will'll never know who the trader
was
hello Who was the last tra who was it
wait so who is the last traitor
Sor was who M oh it's
m okay so this game is just like the
last
game yeah I have different names can you
hear me I don't like the we can hear you
we can oh juli
[Music]
Romeo this is just like the last game
mode but it's
murder what one person has a gun and one
person has a knife and I I just took
something oh if you get enough Clues you
can get a a gun and then you can protect
us I have a gun yeah they glow green oh
you can protect us from the
murderer wait the the murderer has a gun
or murderer has a knife oh my goodness
you have a gun I got CL as well how do
you know what you have what a glue uh it
should tell you on the bottom if you're
a bystander or
murderer oh so I so we need to find I
have nothing my we need to search for
guns Clues yeah they'll glow green and
then if you get enough make that sound
and you get a gun two Clues I have two I
want to find a clue I have lot of Clues
can somebody stay still for a can't
move oh you want to kill someone with
your knife is that why you want them to
stand still here Stay Stay somebody stay
still
please oh you can become oh you want to
stab someone with your knife no I want
to throw a beer bottle at
them why throw it at me
me it's a big map none of you are
staying still very
foll nobody will ever find me not
finding a single clue I'm
not get clues or like operate stuff hey
guys did you see what the other Maps
were uh did you guys in the chat was
there a death run I I didn't check what
sound is that that's the clue
sound you just lock a penguin inside
oh yeah wait I have some instructions
for the murderer if you have a knife you
can also throw it with right click but
you need to charge up the throw we got
to hold right click just letting you
know okay Hey Juliet who are you Juliet
Zulu I'm going to I'm going to come and
save you me you'll save me why are you
X-ray I'm save you wait come on come on
come on come on see the
little is there only one or is there
more than one
I think there
might one one get a gun as well oh my
goodness hi Romeo oh Juliet you're Romeo
right yeah
jul we should stay together wait why is
there there's a lot of Juliet what has a
KNE the penguin has a
knife KN pin has a knife is there only
one penguin
who are you who's the other You Killed
[Applause]
Someone
turn I have a gun I can
kill people What do you have to say for
your defense while the murderer can't
pick up a gun I thought that the wing
was the knife the other xray you make me
shoot an innocent penguin for that I I
am
penguin to oh no not the penguin please
hi
hi I think the is purple purple purple
there's somebody dead are you a are you
a clue oh no she's dead no no the person
in purple that's chasing me there's M we
need a gun who has a gun not me not me
I need a gun I need a I'm going to stay
by I'm going to stay by Calli cuz she'll
protect
us
penguin just tell me you to kill and
I'll kill him I can't move I'm
trapped the purple people all the purple
people what I didn't do anything ky's
been awfully silent Purple People purple
always peopley
to purple one maybe if we're all purple
she's not even using voice chat if
you're purple line up line up text
chat oh wait she's using it now is that
her are you Charlie Charlie oh Charlie
is me and I have a gun and I have a gun
murderer can't hold a gun all which
purple was it how do you get how do I
have oh clue oh clue I have Clues how I
I'm uh I'm white Charlie
[Music]
how get my gun oh you have to get like
five Clues she's good she's
good I got I got a clue how do I use my
gun but what if B lied on purpose about
the penguin no I'm sorry about the
penguin okay that was my bad I have a
gun why would you think the penguin was
holding a knife the penguin wasn't
holding a knife the penguin was stuck
earlier look at the penguin Wing the
penguin Wing looks like oh no the
penguin is dead
kuoko come in and
murder you guys killed an innocent
person no I think
they it's time
for is it you
guys hello wait can the
murderer oh the murderer can't pick up
again can't pick up a gun okay so it
can't
be it can't be either a gun cuz I have a
gun I see okay I had a gun too and I
lost it so can't be me but what if
they're
cheating yes that seems
reasonable yeah I mean what else do we
have oh dear I turn my
goodness one close wait who's Julia who
are you
KY jul J there's dead people oh my God
shoot her Juliet was here
too Ollie say something do I shoot KY
where's everyone there's another
Juliet oh this Juliet's
dead no this Juliet the living one this
one J's your defense me me I'm
Juliet what's your defense what's your
defense my defense I was here yes you
where where the murder
happened you were here too you picked up
the knife didn't I have a gun which
means I'm
innocent knife can you drop the gun
let's see if maybe she could pick it up
oh what was that oh she what she has a
knife she has a knife kill her kill her
what says I don't have
aapon can I not those
F what oh no it's Juliet it's green
Juliet it's green Juliet green Juliet's
the Killer
I knew it oh no where is she where'd she
go I got a
lamp I can't see she's
upstairs
Delta oh wait
what the
stairs dead nice
niceo wait
so wait chat sorry I asked before but
was there a death run
map jul jul it's you I'll this probably
be the last
round no no
okay
hi
hello hello if you're an innocent
bystander how do you get the thingy
please don't I cornered you now I can
finally pull out my
no please I kill
you please no ah you're not in order to
get a gun you need to
find I don't have a knife I lied
sorry press anything with the with the
green items or you just walk on it oh
press e on it I pressed e where do you
find a clue God damn they're just in
rooms
randomly they bit hard to find early on
oh crony here follow me I'll show you
through the carefully look this way this
way oh my goodness you want a
baby oh no there's a green so that's how
it looks yeah
yeah wait go golf with a with a why
didn't you pick up that up that clue I
don't know oh cuz she was
helping
seen no I think I'm talking about
someone else you see my floating why you
have a baby with
you for
you you want it why do you have a baby
with you thank you how do you pick it up
how do you even pick it
up oh scary scary
um whis
thank you
what whiskey is back hey
golf
whiskey
what whiskey what say you in your
defense uh I've been
vibing what's your alibi what were you
up here
pretty I was Ving with a bunch of people
happen ah wait what
nov um
what wait who was
it it was MAA it was was but I think she
disconnected she disconnected maybe
she's having problems
[Music]
problem I want
I want to be a
murderer
in I want to be a
murderer don't tell me if you find the
murderer I'll kill
him who's
golf oh
helloo
un you're the orange golf oh oh yes I am
the orange golf what's up why is it
doubling you stole my
clue I was just faster you need to be
faster okay oh murderers can pick up clu
pick up
CL what happens if they pick upth than
uh it just takes it away from other
people so they can't get a gun wa wa
wait I just saw the murderer I I saw
them they went in under the tunnel they
turned off the lights uh they were
wearing a like a guy it wasn't an animal
it was a guy just a
guyy just some guy okay it was not a
baby it was a man no cat it was just a
dude what color what color they to be
using baby I don't know it was dark
because they just activated the light
switch right so to do
that yeah I think oh they they just did
it again they just did it again it's a a
guy in a suit not the old man the one
with a small head it's a chicken it's a
chicken the chicken is that that M it's
the chicken it's not the chicken kill
the chicken why they using the tunnel
CH so what happens when you
ga oh this guy this
guy you're You're a murderer you're just
saying that blue or whiskey yellow
you're just saying that so you can kill
me
why are you taking that baby I don't
even know who you are but whiskey was
collecting Clues so that he can protect
the baby
down put the baby down it's one of the
guys with a
[Music]
suit I was doing
that murder shot kill
Meck then try killing me you can't hit
me you can't hit me you can't hit
me so I can get this
baby oh my gosh there's two zus get out
we're having a meeting they hiding
they're going to baby we're having a
meeting go
away it's my
baby
this going
that is that m not fair not fair was m n
she saw
you Mur that was me turning off the
light turned the light why would up I
don't know oh cuz for chaos I get it
yeah
I have a gun that wasck that you had the
same skiny ala hey ala
stupid don't do
that I was in the other room trying to
figure out how
you hold on
Alpha oh yeah Alpha come here come here
oh [\h__\h] it's not proximity
huh yeah it's
Sierra what the heck is that you look
absolutely absurd in a good way like
absurdly beautiful oh Gorge what
happened somebody died yeah
like
look you
someone sorry they the sewers I thought
they were
[Music]
s punishment where's your gun that she
should be punished for killing an
innocent for simply existing in the
punishment punishment so what happens
when you get a clue oh you have to
gather I think five and then you get aun
murder we offer up Olie as a sacrifice
ah well no but I have a gun we're going
to turn off the lights and keep her in
the main lobby and you can have
her if
she get the
gun messed up look I have a gun I have a
gun I swear so I'm not the murderer I
know but you didn't but that's not the
point the point is you guys how to use
clue again wink wink I'll press e wait
what what was that somebody just dropped
something from
overhead wait what oh that was me maybe
I was just holding a
suitcase trying to kill someone dropped
the suitcase oxop was dead in the
sewers that's who Ollie
killed that would all make
sense sorry she killed it's okay oh my
good you killed
poo bring Fox drop back to life what I'm
not
huh what we Al yeah wasn't it m oh oh
you guys I kill movement yeah no oh I
was the one saying that we should be
punished wait who
died this is why does it change our
names this is confusing yeah it's part
of it changes I think
a baby just turned up the
lights kill the baby I don't think I
don't think the
lights I think people just
just I'm trying to do
stuff I don't me baby hurry who's a
penguin can I be with you okay I guess
can I can I be in here too my
goodness going to kill me it's only for
one person sorry thank you you can stay
scare somebody kind of su what why are
you hiding here what what's so sus about
it November November I wanted to
surprise somebody but you guys are
ruining the surprise November bad
nov
may you good baby or an evil baby
there's no room I'm a good can I kill
you to make sure no please do not kill
the baby that is I just started living
my life just started I'm a baby kill
defe us her reason is she isn't the I
think she's the
traitor why I didn't do anything you
didn't say you weren't the traitor now
you're just I'm TR I don't have a weapon
she's she's only mentioning it now she's
just a
baby evil
baby how many clothes do you need for a
gun oh my God
damn it come over here come over here I
dare you turn on the light I dare
you I can't you're too big get out of
the way no oh my gosh oh that's so
ominous hey don't fetch it scary just
just too big this is my life he I said
no F shaming around here I can't move
I'm stuck yeah true she too you guys are
blocking
me she's too B your
shoulders may I kill you oh there we
go I can't find any clues around this
damn house me neither feel every time it
does like ding is when a clue spawns
easier to find the
CL murder no who someone stabbed me why
I think it was Victor oh no that sucks
Victor's right there Victor's right off
I could be the traitor hi Victor Victor
kill Victor kill Victor I turned them on
I'm a Victor Victor Victor is at the
lights Victor expl
Victor kill Victor oh you
killed you me to kill Victor who gave
this person a gun messed up I don't know
the game who said to kill Victor key I
can't believe you you kill an innocent
person
yes well someone did stab me in the
kitchen hold on no you guys are just gas
what's happening where's a
gun notic she
do I was just about to accuse you that
was very good
timing why would you do that to me cuz
you were you were so quiet everyone
being quiet is
suspicious you're also short L off again
but I have a gun a short gun yeah no
that's good we like for a fact know that
the murderer can't pick up a gun is it
do we no
no uh I'm pretty sure they can't oh you
really you really want it to be Gigi
yeah you hate me so
bad look there's clues in here you can
get a gun to I found a clue I don't have
to use it g
y yipp uh someone just di no oh sorry
okay no Just sh that exited oh my God
the penguin got a gun to there's another
clue over here someone get the clue you
can have a gun why don't you pick it up
why don't you Pi a gun already I think
who's the green person who's who's kilo
not me I don't know I'm whiskey yeah
it's me I'm kill why didn't you pick up
the
clue I couldn't pick up the clue cuz I
got
stuck okay
I I speak from firstand experience Anya
is really good at lying and getting out
of
things let me just compliment she
insanely good at lying and getting out
of things
I get stuck in games a lot I get stuck
in games a lot okay it just happens it's
like my secondary skill in life trust me
is
[Music]
lying well who did
that you guys are just killing each
other the murderer doesn't even to do
[Music]
anything can I kill how these things
go I can kill it was misunder
understanding huge
misunderstanding Echo kill on
site there's so many Clues which one is
CeCe Echo she's by the lights she's by
the lights Echo she turned off the
lights I'm follow her
right guys it's not focus
on oh free gun a free
gun I got a I got a
gun no whiskey
up
[Music]
no do you have a gun on me why is my
screen gun see wait can you not see I
see it armit and November don't have
guns and
I I have two GRE yeah what can I kill
November there's a here or this
penguin's blocking me hey there's a clue
here wait where can I have it I think
it's a baby I haven't seen the baby have
a gun where is it I I want the babies it
says it on my screen too two
what can I kill one of the babies if you
show me where a clue is I will pick it
up in front of you murderers can pick up
Clues I'm pretty
sure yeah they can
ollie yay gun take away her gun I want a
gun too no I can't pick it up press e
[Applause]
on I like killing people too much I got
it look at is the only one who doesn't
have a
gun okay let's kill Amy wait but I'm
innocent but you don't have a gun I have
I have one right
here
oh we keep I couldn't pick it up oh my
goodness that was tragic maybe I should
have given her more time
are we okay CCE might have been on to
something are we
sure we sure that traiter doesn't have a
gun can the trader hold a
gun I'm going to kill
whiskey
but oh my God no I I don't know G might
be
bad who's left okay should we rush and R
left who hold on screen is dark how many
of are left I think it's just us Street
unless someone's not talking how many
Clues do you need how many cluthes do
you need to find a gun well I just
picked I picked up somebody else's but I
could I don't how do you know how many
you
need uh five we need five oh we need
three
more
oh is it just us are we sure we three
left I don't think we are I'm not
convinced you know who's been awfully
silent who who's been awfully silent
k I don't know if she's in the game is
she is she in the I thought she like
disconnected I MAA got
disconnected oh is not here oh never
mind bro the game you're blaming her no
she's just been Qui are we we cannot be
the last thing is someone stuck us may
crony bro I haven't killed anyone except
you you've been killing everyone all I
know is that in the bottom right corner
it says by wait the live people can't
hear us right it says by yeah if they're
alive they can't hear us I found they
were there
go all right GG's
GG's okay I'm going to see if there's
another game mode otherwise I don't know
old wait
what what they
were Landing in the in the v I did oh my
God took a long time to and they were
just standing there for no reason so I
don't know help
yeah that was because I had an idle
meeting I was so ready for us to like
kill each other I killed
you yeah you killed me when I was AFK
congratulations thank you
congratulations us fight each other in
other in I got I got to go goodbye
everyone thank you for
[Music]
playing I want to V for
I have a gun and I can
kill sorry I'm checking
something I got like one clue and a
dream all right uh we're going to do one
I can never find any
clues yeah they're
SC slurping up all the clues hi the
murder taking all the clues I got fast
that'd be
smart n hi
you want me to kill
anyone what are you mo why why didn't
you take the clue kill me kill me kill
me kill me kill me kill me kill me kill
me kill
me Bes us it was
literally stop trying to
kill so what was it I don't want to
shoot you I took it all right what was
it it was you're definitely not the
killer it was a cash register oh my God
I
don't I think you're just reming
g
[Music]
off the light so uh how can I turn on
how could I do that if I'm over here
watch this down the stairs that's how
you did it you're fast are you watching
watch watch no I'm not watching what are
you stop it's scary in the dark I see
you I'm watching you I touched it I'm
spying you with my little eyes give me
that man I can't find anything around
here oh okay never mind the big rat took
it I'm slurping up the clues cuz I want
to prove my innocence can I stay beside
you because I feel safe here with with
you sure no we can stand the corner
together
yes what I me
like like people
each other hello are you the
murderer I'm not what kind
of
some that
K I will I want to be the
murderer all right let
Works who's killo it was it was the one
that was smoking yeah it
was her but I
love I'm changing game modes murderer go
wild go ham hold on we're about to
change y okay
of course you scared
here I
wonder okay this will be the last one
and then I'm pretty sleepy
so we're not lagging anymore right
hopefully this works I don't know if it
needs to be console or a specific type
of game mode but
let's see let's
see okay hold on let me fix
something oh sh
death run
yeah I don't think I'm supposed to be in
sandbox
mode it can't be sandbox
I stole start local server wait
really I think I might have done the
same thing for the wrong thing hold
on oops
here we
go all right it's working let me just
exit out of
something I was the murderer but I I
wasn't
[Music]
weird wait
what
what the murderer on the other side of
the wall yeah the motor is supposed to
be on the other side of the wall
pressing levers to activate of the for
they are not on the other side of the
wall there's nobody on the other side oh
they can't hear me no
what is this maybe like a safe Zone
let's keep
going maybe let's keep going then maybe
it's not the right game mode hold up
hold up I'm very confused yeah we're in
Murder mode I'm the murderer and I'm not
on the other side so can we restart yeah
that's how I was last time too I came in
late and I don't know what's
happening well do you guys know what the
game Mode's supposed to be it's just
supposed to be death run or sandbox
okay well the
r okay I don't think I have
it try to RTV okay hey can we
RTV RTV RTV
please okay thank you okay uh uh oh okay
I see I know why but my chat is not
sending ah it's okay it's
okay I don't think I have I don't think
I have it I don't think I have death run
installed I'm pretty sure I installed it
in the server
but I don't see it as a option to set
it
sandbox oh wait
I think I found
something oh it's switching
back yeah all right sorry what are we
doing uh I tried to put it on a
different game mode but I guess it's not
working right now so I know we could one
more round of this and then yeah
okay what did you guys like this one or
TT better Romeo where's my jeul I like
TT better okay let let's do that for the
last one then it'll be really quick one
second sorry thank you
okay what's a good TTT map what do you
guys think in the
chat d
maybe
yo there's no anybody want to pick me up
can we RTV one more time sorry are you
good okay thank you Okie doie we don't
have Minecraft city we can't do that
sorry I'll get you out of that
bathroom four right please save me wait
yeah body blocked
that penguin is so damn fast look at me
WD why is it going
one your zoom in is there a water they
call me
zooom zooo
lemon press for Ah that's
okay I guess office is fine
I had to press for I kept typing it
in
okay we're back here again you're the
best I
[Applause]
love what the
hell Xbox a demon that one
that
hi hey yo Gamers what's up
hello hello Mory kopy hello Hello's mic
sounds so
HD it's a lot more quieter now yeah I
think cuz you know it's late some people
are going to bed haven't seen anybody
yet yeah I want a gun SLE I want a gun I
want a
gunun sh my gun is shiny I can't throw
anything yet come up stop it oh no
no well we're just preparing the baby is
detective which
baby the chicken is innocent the chicken
is in B boo with a detective baby
detective is beo baby how how do you use
bab
stuff I think it's just a roll so now we
know how to trust you you know we can
trust you now that you're a detective
yeah
yeah oh now we're out here can we
kill can I can I do it here oh she AFK
no like her character but she's she left
she left she left
goodbye okay I wanted to do it oh wow I
can't believe you would shoot her just
like that she was unarmed you said she
was she left yo look at me with my yeah
yeah she was she was she she did leave
but that's awfully
it's very rude still get off my bedar
kill people with
it yes can I I'm going to protect the B
please oh okay you're going to prot with
the baby the baby is detective okay
anyone but the baby I'll just give
everyone a little
p
me it's a chicken it's a chicken craw I
was just
trying my craw bar I see you're trying
to help you're trying to help my bad I
was trying to you're cool like that I am
very cool like
that that is exactly how cool I am
you're so cool for not killing me right
there how I am not kill wait who shot
who's shooting you're innocent I know
you're
innoc I'm hiding here who's
killing is hiding that might mean it's
them
they hiding what no where are they my
God I can't see where are you guys their
strategy is hiding and they're hiding
who this ammo they're hiding again oh
why are you guys
hiding does that mean
everyone are you the trer seeing there
be
careful tra that I would want to run
around and kill everyone happing over
here
oh my
God somebody died
died she died 38 seconds ago
wow I saw somebody attacking her like M
I think it was
M oh okay I think either am is messing
with us or she is the person do not kill
M so why is
detective you're the chicken head
there's no way
who's shooting leave the chicken alone
alone wait check her are the detective
oh she was I can't believe you would
kill her oh no she was would you kill an
innocent Byer she was
[Applause]
cool wow bi boo wow I I think it's
probably GG really no why would you
blame me the penguin the penguin don't
do it you're Lu your H box is small if
you kill me I'm I'm
taking wait was she innocent
oh
hey she was innocent oh that's nice
okay I'm a killing I'm a killing no it's
not me I'm defending myself it's oh my
God it's
anyna no yes is
killing I'm
innocent there's no way you're you're
the
traitor I'm me come out come out
wherever you
are I knew it you know I love you
Senpai where are you you know I love
you wa your reason charge rifle went
viral I want to see
you I won't hurt you I'll just shoot you
in the head you're lying to me
be a quick death it won't hurt I don't
want the traitors to
win why not I'm still alive oh okay well
watch out for Olie she's wearing a white
coat okay got it damn just have your gun
out it's out and ready to go
oh there
go I told you that this strategy is good
yeah nice were you guys hiding then why
did you shoot me yeah
we I saw you you're going shoot me yeah
now we know your hiding
spot you look like you're going
you I felt threatened I did too
all right this will be the last round I
think so good luck to the
traitors okay
okay good luck good
luck
cute I'm a
penguin nice that's nice now we know
that's nice
way to flex on us who are I'm a
detective
oh
kill I'm a
Traer oh
no oh no I'm a Traer you're a Traer I'm
a Trader
too wa we can only
tra I kill Mor again okay I'm just I'm
just so you guys know I'm not
okay why would you do that you really
like killing what are you doing no I it
wasn't me last time it was last time
disgusting inhuman person oh I got a gun
don't talk to me you penguin I
say let not be like that away from me
why are you following me why are you
following
me I'm why because we're traitors
together was that you crony no I just
saw
who's shooting through the why would you
do that it's always
Ollie how does
Ollie CU I want to try using
it that was sketchy who the traitor
because she said she was a
traitor who did
that oh no what's happening why you
doing that Cory that is very
suspicious I just want to see what
legary grenade what you trying to
oh know if it was a smoke grenade or
something sounds like something a killer
would do but doesn't in kill her do that
when nobody's
around unlikely
story why AR you saying anything are you
the miror get out of here no is she I'm
not hey waa don't hit me hasn't said
anything in a
hot why are you trying to kill me no cuz
she's so SS she killed Callie are you
the murderer I didn't kill Callie I
didn't kill anyone in this game
man man I'm sorry there's too many
voices trust you why thank you where is
everyone I'm scared by
it's the
inary shooting me she's the Traer she's
the Traer get her
[Music]
get I killed her she was shooting at
me um I accidentally killed
one you accidentally killed people was
the traitor I killed her but but um I
killed more than one person um because
because yeah was sorry sorry
sorry you accidentally killed a
person I accidentally killed be well no
on purpose Ked but she was the traitor
it has to be G feel like Cecilia sounds
very very suspicious yeah no it's just
because I was panicking she someone that
would kill no come come to the body
she's right here no I don't know where
you are I'm literally with people's dead
body I'm trying to break I'm trying to
break out this window but I
can't I'm sorry I'm sorry are you really
sorry sorry I killed you no nothing wait
wait wait who who is it actually like
ggot her I think I think it's
g in theice you know the smiley is no
wait cron why are you dead I can't help
you w four kill but they a detective GG
versus
CCE
everyone wait wait talking
about why is no one else saying anything
where is everyone oh my
God it's Justice versus Justice where
are you where where where's everyone
else wait who killed you oh my god there
a lot of
dead oh oh oh yeah okay okay wait
wait like is there like a hit boox
difference if you're a penguin I think
so I think
[Music]
so think it actually EVS the hit box I
think it does also my P's
terrible yeah GG's for real G
[Music]
thank you guys for playing if I was a
murderer I would have been good oh thank
you for inviting yeah sorry it was so
[Music]
SCU thank you guys for putting up with
so much for setting it up you
know no it fine you for setting it up no
it's fine it's fine it's fine it's I
hope you guys had fun lot of fun it was
worth it thank
you I had a lot
of happy birthday oh happy birthday wait
what oh thank
you oh I finally am the detective okay
bye bye everyone byebye thank you for
playing thank you so much you guys thank
you everyone bye have a nice night good
night bye bye
all
right time to rest I have oh shoot I
have stuff to work on today all right
thank you for streaming yeah thank you
guys for
watching uh sorry for the scuff we got
to figure it out though eventually I do
wish we could have play death run that
would have been fun but I can't remember
the death run
thingy uh
command I hope you guys had fun watching
and yeah thank you I will see you guys
tomorrow what are we doing tomorrow uh
let me double
check hold on loading
loading okay uh my calendar is not
loading but I think tomorrow is the
charity stream I'm pretty
sure got to make sure everything is set
up for that that
so yeah perfect timing all right thank
you guys for watching I will see you
tomorrow okay thank you thank you oh
finally I get to be the Traer I haven't
been the trader all game or the murderer
I wanted to
try yes I'll be doing a charity stream
tomorrow I uh was originally going to do
it for a coral charity stream but I
don't think they ever got back to me
about setting that up but we're still
going to do something ocean themed and
then I have a really cool surprise for
you guys and and there's also two
collabs
tomorrow so yeah I'll see you guys then
okay thank you for watching and good
night good night good night good night
good
[Music]
night instrumental arbre
parade my internet's so slow right now
and my bgm is not loading oh here it
goes
[Music]
pap
Pap Pap
[Music]
p
fire Bye by bye-bye