[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
this is
you said that so quietly
I I I become really a hazakashi saying
stuff like that on other people's
channels oh I
on other people's channels I I hold back
a little bit too yeah yeah
[Music]
okay
Iris Would you like to introduce
yourselves to the people on my channel
um hiris it's Iris I'm sorry I can't
yeah
I'm Hollow live English project hope I
was the movie singer slash YouTuber
skfp I will be eating chicken tonight
yeah
this is a place where you get fried
chicken right yes I guess we can give
you one free order today only yay yes
it's done free yeah I'm sure we have
some Volunteers in the chat they look
shocked now but in reality they don't
mind and comply as always yeah I'm sure
they don't mind right yes yes yes yes oh
my God we are doing a German collab and
you may wonder why if you've been living
under a rock the past weeks months me
and Iris are being uh are performing and
being a guest at documents
[Music]
you don't know what nothing pretty soon
it's a big convention in Germany an
anime convention and it happens every
year last year I was a guest alone this
year iris is kind of joining me but
we're on separate days so we're not
really yeah
yes are you excited
yes the first convention experience
right yeah I'm pretty nervous but I'm
really excited yeah especially for like
the meet and greets and stuff yes yeah I
love the meet and greet part and I I
really really really enjoyed it last
year so I think you'll have a good time
meeting some fans friends so please
enjoy Germany uh virtually
virtual Germany yes I will enjoy it yeah
I can't wait to see like everyone's
outfits and compliment them that's what
I'm thinking yeah I didn't have I think
I only had like one cosplayer or so last
year and then even great like the
cosplayers haven't really come to the
meet and greet mostly but oh really you
would think that they would yeah yeah
it's just you know the fans usually
there's not many costumed people among
them they should be mom but maybe it is
yeah who knows if we're lucky we got an
iris cosplay
yeah I'd love to see that oh very
intricate costumes um I know yep
everything about the yeah that costume
is definitely musically but when I want
to make it you're gonna look gorgeous
guys yes
you're gonna look like me
like me yeah all right I wouldn't want
to look like Iris
yeah they're designed so much like the
first time I saw it I was like holy [\h__\h]
she's saying I love the design so much
red juice is good yes red juice is good
so I will be eating Iris some German we
only have an hour because I am under
time pressure sorry guys so this will be
a crash course
[Music]
teach me everything everything there
needs to be known yeah I will try to
focus on things that will actually be
useful partially words that you could
say during your performance maybe or
during the meet and greet and yeah so
let's start right off with greetings you
may have heard some of them before
um I think yeah hello you can either say
the well-known guten tag but there's
actually a way more simple way it's just
hello hello hello hello hello hello
it sounds like English yeah that one is
really similar so I think it's the
easiest way to say it
um guten tag sounds like very formal in
my opinion and just too long and it's
more cash you just say hello yeah hello
everyone hello that's cute yeah good to
tag is like evening right guten tag is
good morning a good happened is good
evening oh Advent is not okay okay I
make
yeah right now I guess over there it's
getting abundant uh here it's guten tag
or guten mug and yeah Morgan Morgan
Morgan yeah but that's like the only
German that I remember yeah we don't
need that because we don't We're not
gonna be there in the morning
unnecessary words okay
we have uh oh my name is now people like
to translate that in a very formal and
katakoto it feels to me like katakoto
because it's like not so natural
sounding they like to translate it into
my name is the one in the brackets
which also sounds similar to the English
one but I just don't think it sounds it
sounds very natural so I want you to say
the first one
it's the letter that looks like a b it's
a double s basically it's a special
letter that we have but you just
pronounce it like a sharp s
so it's like ish Heise like kind of like
that like it is yeah
okay I think that is way better than the
my name is
you can say that too maybe it's easier
to think of when you're like nervous
because it sounds like the English one
yeah but I think all right it's better
but be careful when you say that because
already some people have pointed out in
the chat uh if you pronounce it wrong it
can be like uh I
[\h__\h]
that's wait wait wait how does it
transition into that if you like words
it is really I should I [\h__\h] yeah if you
add like a [\h__\h] in between then it will
turn into that
oh so it's like like when you say ish
like ish just don't don't pronounce it
sounds like I I pooped
I poop okay so I don't want to introduce
myself as a as someone that poops in her
pants no um it's like it's like it so
it's you're supposed to pronounce it
like just kind of like the CH is kind of
Silent like no it's not silent but it's
like
not so much like if you want to be um if
you want to go to Switzerland then you
could uh really exaggerate it to look
but uh yeah generally the CH is like a
gentle
like a when when when when the radio is
not working
static okay static walking talking Noise
by the way whenever you don't have a
German keyboard and you can't type some
letters that are in the German alphabet
then you can uh the double that that b
you can double s as double s yet yes
that's what I'm doing right now okay
her name is Iris we know that now what's
next
[Music]
we don't use it like like for example
Americans do like in English language
you say like Hi how are you and then you
ignore the the other person ignores the
question and just says like hi back to
you right hi yeah a lot of times you're
like why did I ask but in in Germany we
would like you to answer as well so
we'll get to that later but uh you
pronounce this as we get S Dia V oh so
it's like not we it's it's V okay you
can imagine the French we I guess we
get S DIA
we we get SD sounds so cute when you say
that
I'm trying my best to sound like like
like the original like the original
that's why yeah okay it sounds pretty
good we get SD now if you talk fast uh
then you can like kind of
abbreviate it and say Vegan yes yeah
so uh it basically directly translated
means how going
it's you
how going at you
how going at you how's it going please
translate basically right yes yes yes
how's it going exactly
um okay that makes sense we want to
answer that right because we're not rude
people yeah we don't just say hi no we
actually answered yeah we won the
conversation so let's start the
conversation by saying I am fine we are
always fine right we're always fine yeah
we yeah even when we're not fine we just
try to yeah that's the only option
now here we have some repeat our words
from the previous phrase git s right you
see that in the middle yes so I noticed
it Mia is me I me Mia Mia s good you can
guess it means good
yes good good and tag good yeah okay now
that's right so yeah I asked you we get
as Dia and you say
Mia get as good
whoa amazing amazing and then you ask me
uh we vegan as dear so French
will never fellow word that you don't
really need to use but it sounds more
natural if you if you re
um if somebody asks you the question
back and you answer back Al means to
two oh okay okay so like I'm good too
sort of thing yeah but yeah it's
unnecessary it's too much information we
we're doing a crash course we don't need
us enough information
so make it is good and next we have
nice to meet you this one is a bit long
oh yes
with the dots on the o yeah you if you
can't write that you can even just write
an o or more correctly it is o e
o e
um yeah yeah
um when we don't have that keyboard uh
we write it like for example also the a
with the two dots we write a a e and the
U the two dots we write U E and O oh so
it's always an e yeah because it's kind
of I guess they imagine it to be kind of
a mix of OE or a e and so on
so you pronounce this as oh no oh
[Music]
what's an English word that uses that
sound
there really aren't many is it like is
there like an R sort of thing like er
no
when you do the uh your tongue is like
looks like a u on the butt it's like on
the bottom of your mouth not up or
anything but it's like a u-shape and
then the rest of your mouth is like a
really narrow oh
oh oh oh
oh
turn ah turn in an English accent that's
right turn
[Laughter]
similar so it's like
that was good okay okay gotcha okay okay
so okay we finally got that done that
that sound is really difficult for like
most people who don't know the German
language yes so it's understandable
yeah just like how Japanese people have
a hard time saying what words that have
an r in it yeah ah yes yes for example
yeah yeah if you're not used to making
this shape with your mouth it's actually
surprisingly difficult
um
[Music]
are often kind of like Blends in with
the rest of the word and turns more into
an a like when I say it really clearly I
say Le arnen but usually when I talk
yeah we don't say it that clearly so you
more blend into a leannen okay
my God
[Music]
I Am A Plus student yeah the
pronunciation you're doing pretty well
so far must say that should be a little
similar in Japanese pronunciation that's
why
oh yeah a little bit I think I agree
with that let me try to sip my tea and
you can repeat from the top please
okay
um
oh from the very top like hello or like
okay ha okay hello is hello hello hello
good and tag gluten tag everyone yes
um
[Music]
Iris
we get SDA
Mia get as good
wow you get as good
and
um
you're like blowing on your teeth like
your life depends on it it's so hot it's
so hot
and the last one and then um this [\h__\h]
should learn
wow nailed it there's one more dough
goodbye
bye yes one of these phrases I always
say at the end of my stream it's the
longer one
alpha Zen and in German we sing
thanks for watching
is more formal and it means see you
again while just doesn't necessarily
imply seeing somebody again and it's
just shorter
um
yeah I think just wouldn't Fury be
easier to remember but it has the ooh
sound which is not like uh but it's like
okay you can make that one that works
all right so it's like yeah
at the end okay
now in this case it has a double s but
you don't usually ride it with the sharp
ass don't ask me why it's just the way
it is
um interesting yeah it would be too
complicated to get into them
yeah uh choose and also
just as cute it's like a chew yeah with
an s
and I am Edison
which one you like more
I liked choose but I've finished it it
seems like it has a more positive
message since it also means you know see
you again yeah yeah and it might be a
bit more impressive because it's longer
so wait how do you pronounce again um of
Alf
it's like more like a z okay okay
maybe the Discord making sound weird we
we like again like a wee wee wee from
wee wee buggy
um
yeah maybe like I guess maybe a tiny bit
of like um like a like an F sound is
somewhere in there but not really
um
depends on how sharply you say it I
guess leave this in
um yeah
yes if you and once again we have this
thing where something Blends in and you
say it differently like I I will say it
like shorter if you say it very clearly
it's Vida C hen but you can just say
vitazine beta Zen okay yeah the H
Blends in and gets kind of silent so
don't worry too much about it just say
avidazine
yeah it's a little too early to say that
but I'll be the same
a chat so that's a good explanation I
guess the W in German is similar to uh
V the V letter
okay okay okay double sorry with the
Double U oh ww okay okay so it's not we
it's not we okay it's like a V okay
that's why we get s d is also V right
okay
foreign
[Music]
okay I say come at me I say hello Iris
hello Kiara oh hello hi sir uh
you don't know what that means but you
can guess is that is that like you I'm
guessing um
[Music]
foreign foreign
you can repeat that
[\h__\h] I was thinking for a second
okay cheers
it came so fast I was like huh okay
bye-bye
oh you deserve that one good
pronunciation
thank you now I'll teach you some quick
filler words
I love that chicken next to the kids the
mascot makes it so cute my secretary uh
his name is um uh Fabian oh he has a
name Fabia
it's a dude okay yeah yeah it's a German
name by the way Fabian oh I didn't know
it was a German name
write this [\h__\h] down uh filler words
that you might hear and that might help
you as well really easy ones uh for
example yes yeah
yeah yeah don't pronounce it like
English J but more like a y yeah why
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah and then you
can say no nine nine nine nine nine nine
nine nine like the number nine
no no no
no I even have that as a memory mode
for summer it's cute oh yeah you do yeah
I don't know why we don't use it that
often
time to get rid of it no oh and then
we're speeding for this because I'm I'm
looking at the time and I see we've been
uh taking too much time so here's Maybe
maybe how would you pronounce this
um when it's a w you say it's V but I'm
assuming maybe it's the opposite what
it's a v so it would be oh no
f f oh okay so it's finished
okay so the this if you see here in this
word we have an ie and an e i
if it's an ie that's what we call in
German we call it uh an a long eye so
it's like an eye that's a little bit
longer kimoti but not not really you
don't have to pay much attention to it
so you pronounce that one correctly but
when it's like an e i you pronounce it
as I
okay
[Music]
so it's going to be a little more like a
free life yeah
yeah he likes
oh my God
so imagine instead of the E just imagine
an a letter there yeah I'm literally
typing it like that yeah
pronunciation to remember
yes we liked oh
and
thanks is I've said it many times dank
it or okay
yeah I hear donkey soon yes it's not
shun right it's like sure yeah sure for
my super chats and sometimes people come
in and they're like what the [\h__\h] are
you saying what does that mean but yeah
it's thank you very much while danke is
more like only thanks
okay okay so Danke Schoen is just more
you pronounce it a little bit English
still it's not okay
oh it's not dank it's more like that
okay donk okay
donkey donk dunk okay
okay
amazing hey
I used to sometimes um say instead of
dancing and I used to sometimes say in
the super chats feeling dank which is
another version of it
um which is much bangs but people were
saying it sounds like feeling dank in
English
I'm feeling dank today what does dank
even mean like I hear this word on the
internet but design is it like feeling
good
what does dang mean guys
thank me good question indeed I don't
know what it means in English
dang dank it's feeling moist moist
really dang is moist
what happens
it means like directly translated
explanation okay but nobody uses it like
that anymore I think yeah nobody no no
no okay oh well I thought dank just
meant very cool yeah like what some
people are saying yeah I think that's ah
no we have one more filler word it's uh
please or welcome in in German we use
the same word so you can say give me
this please or you can say you're
welcome it's the same word oh it's the
same word interesting
you can also again just like the danke
you can add the Shoon britishun to make
it more polite sure
like very thank you very much it's like
the much right thank you very much
petition is very much okay okay yeah
um please very much yeah you can say
water please is Vasa beta or you can say
uh thank you for asking and you say
you're welcome
um yeah you can say it differently too
of course but it's I think easier to
remember because this word works both
ways yeah
by the way on its own means pretty so
it's like to describe yourself
ah I see you I was like oh why is there
only the shirt it has the emote okay ah
yeah that's interesting
honestly we don't use it like that in my
chats they probably didn't even know uh
now they always ride like Danke Schoen
in the chat when I read my super chats
yeah yeah yeah yeah so that's the field
word now we don't have time to be here
too long next one is small talk that you
can use either on the stage or on the in
the meet and greet yeah yeah so this
will be some phrases
Maybe choto muzukasi
oh you will have to read those down yeah
thank you for coming either at the
concert or uh at the meet and greet you
can say
first Common
[Music]
and first is four but you see I added
like a little thingy at the top and then
an S that's just me trying to make it
shorter for you this is totally legit
you can write it like this
kind of like yours in English
[Music]
uh thank you first comment thank you
donkey first Common thank you who's
coming okay
thank you for coming once again I think
sounds a little bit a little bit similar
to English with some words so thank you
for coming true I didn't notice that
until now yeah yes yes yes
wonderful and then we say thank you for
your support
a little bit similar but if you need
some some fillers in in the meet and
greet if if there's like a German person
coming in who doesn't speak English so
it doesn't speak English yeah I mean I
think if they come to your meet and
greet honestly I think they are able to
speak a certain amount of English and
generally in Germany also in my country
in Austria we have pretty good education
so the English skills of the Germans are
generally
decent if not perfect but some of them
have a weird pronunciation some of them
so thank you for your support is danke
again we start like that
and now we have a difficult word
which directly means under
support yeah like supporting someone
like holding someone up for example
holding someone up yeah
[Music]
um
doctor for dying
oh by the way I'm writing this in uh
in informal
the informal is an unpolite one right
yeah yeah informally
it's a mix like we're talking politely
but I'm addressing you casually so Dinah
is a casual way of addressing you but we
don't have time to go through all of
that so just you just so you know Dinah
is casual if you would say it more
formally you would say thank you foreign
maybe you can have a part two next year
if you come to Google me again and we'll
try to deepen the knowledge yes yes
can you you think you can say it
um don't give her dinner
yes so here we have again at the diner
we have it again with the e i when e i
is next to each other basically I
next we have maybe if there's a cosplay
you can say I like your costume so you
can say costume
honestly it's easier because it's an
English word but we want to be very
correct it's ich Mark dine costume
[Music]
it's the St turns into a [\h__\h] but
sometimes it's also just
it depends it's Case by case so
um I think you said more like costume
but it's more like costume costume
okay that's true um
when you say it it still sounds a little
bit like an ooh maybe you try to imagine
that you're going higher
higher I don't know instead of costume
you say costume
yeah it's okay though everybody gets it
okay
no need to learn too much about it but
yeah the costume normally costume but
costume costume costume costume costume
costume costume cute
is there a similar English word I wonder
tomb uh no no no not like two no no I
mean like the the u sound just the u
sound vacuum no perfume
no
no no no
nothing I see some naughty words no
um
[Music]
Edition
if it's a shirt and you've been like
Mary Sharon Sharon sure sure
yes and then we have
if you run out of toppings yeah I was
gonna ask that if you weren't gonna
bring it up I was gonna ask her how do
you say this but what is nice today and
I wonder if it will be nice on document
um the weather report has been looking
sus but oh really
sure
EU turns into like an oi
foreign
oh no Discord
amazing wow marvelous amazing yes
the weather is nice today yes very
simple
um now and then what if like what if you
want to say like how's the weather today
like how do you ask V is
[Music]
like w-i-e
uh-huh East IST
uh that's d-a-s
w-e-t-t-e-r Visa letter h e uh
um
necessarily I think it kind of is
self-explan explanation
I see it because it's just how how's the
weather so I think this is
foreign
[Music]
so uh the last one honestly I think is
the only
um phrase you will need during your meet
and greets or during your concert this
is very important
I like big butts and I cannot lie
oh yeah that's very important I think it
will be very useful
yeah
I never thought that I would need this
but yeah this this seems really
something necessary in a daily
conversation you maybe think like in
your culture they don't
[Music]
and we just cannot lie we're very direct
people in German and austrians generally
Europeans maybe but especially the
german-speaking culture we are very
direct people so we cannot lie so we say
it like this is
it sounds so cool in German
can you repeat that can you repeat that
yeah um but by the way I'm using a cute
word for it so don't worry about saying
it it's not like ass or so
um
I like Mug
is it
grossing okay
close the purpose
here again we have the EU turning into
an oi
okay um
how about how do you say um so wait if
this is for big buds what about boobs
I can write it down wait
first
I'll write it down it would be oopsie uh
oh yeah I changed my keyboard to
Japanese keyboard wait uh here
foreign
[Music]
but maybe this one is the most say-so
one okay the most
it's more of um like a medical term I
guess you you could say it's like breast
basically breast is blistered ah okay
okay okay
so that means um that means
is big yes
foreign
somebody wants to know I guess because
you also say it often I write this at
the very top uh
well I don't know if you'll be saying
this during the during the concert
because at that point hopefully your
volume is fine but how the volume is yes
[Music]
the is the
loud status or
yeah I think that's fine this is the
large Decker V is the
loud that's volume
[Music]
it's yeah literally
um if you translate it literally it's
loud strength
uh or sound strength
um we maybe I think this is a thing
people say about German and it might be
true our words are like really simple
combinations of words and and I had to
say like I've heard people say this
before about German language yeah we
just shove words together like for
example
was supporting underneath basically
um while I don't know yeah it's in
theory it's easy if you know like single
words you can like see a connection
there eventually I think
we is the
ouch yeah
yeah
okay okay
okay
perfect I don't know if you'll be using
that during the concert though but yeah
just in case maybe and let me change
that back to butts to propose because
otherwise it's an incorrect purpose
yes exactly
okay
we are going oh
that is um I really typed this perfectly
that is all the language but we have
some I I preferred some prepared some
facts flexible facts Lexing Flex on me
please yes I thought maybe
um because you're not actually going to
Germany for this event so I thought
maybe you would like to have some facts
uh as if you're going there uh I don't
really have many don't be too uh please
don't expect too much but here's some
facts uh Dusseldorf oh what the [\h__\h] did
I write this love has the most amount of
Japanese people living in one city in
all of Europe oh
yeah I guess I would assume that there's
not that many Japanese people in Europe
in general it's like right yes but for
some reason uh there's some history
behind that but uh in the city
Dusseldorf where dokumi is happening uh
there's the most amount of Japanese
people living in one city in all of
Europe and actually I think worldwide a
second most because I think Sao Paulo
has the most I think from what I've
heard or it has changed maybe
um yeah I think Brazil just generally
has a lot of Japanese people outside of
Japan uh but yeah drizzled up is that
definitely at least number two worldwide
I think as far as I know I remember I
remember you guys were talking about
this during the dokomi stream the twitch
stream yeah yeah yeah where it's like it
has like a Japanese Japan town or
something with like a lot of Japanese
restaurants and stuff yeah yeah yeah
yeah that's also why I like going there
so much because people
um after going to the event they all
have like dinner in the restaurant in
the Japanese restaurants in the Japanese
street because they're really really
authentic because a lot of Japanese
people work there they even like they
have families they raise their children
in just little doctors I think there
might not even be like a Japanese school
I don't know but definitely
Internationals
there's Japanese bakeries even yeah oh
hey Chris oh yeah Japan bird is good
there's even a Japanese hotel in that
famous Japanese street it's called the
the nickel hotel which also exists in
Japan
so that's why it's the perfect spot for
a production for me because all the all
the anime fans
um the thing is like we have Japanese
restaurants all over Europe but usually
most of them are not so authentic I
think it's getting better actually also
in Austria yeah over the past two years
three years
[Music]
yeah more and more authentic ones have
been showing up so uh that's good but
generally you know if you want really
really authentic food you go to
Dusseldorf um
I'm assuming getting authentic Japanese
and Japanese food in Europe is kind of
expensive though yeah yes it is
expensive it also is expensive even in
there's still a lot of relatively like
for example a robin like not the cup
Ramen but a proper Ramen in Japan in
Japan called sweat like
it's usually like around like I would
say like 700 800 Yen some of the pricer
ones you're laughing very cheap I think
in Europe you often go up to ten dollars
eleven or twelve dollars
yeah yeah yeah a little bit on the
pricier side it is but the ramen is
still like one of the cheaper things
maybe like for example unagidon I know
it's already expensive in Japan but it's
even more expensive in in Europe trying
to get unangi done and Sushi as well and
uh uh oh yeah yucky nickel uh last year
I went to a food trip to Dusseldorf and
had Yakiniku and obviously because
Yakiniku Japanese yakiniko is really
rare in Europe like literally like
Japanese meat yeah like the way they
prepare it on and all that like there's
other like Korean barbecue and all that
that's more more common but yeah the
Japanese one is really rare so they
charge a lot it's like a really special
special thing here
yeah by the way like you know in in like
um in Germany or like in in Europe is
there like a tipping culture oh yeah
you don't have to tip as much as in
America
um because like I guess in America The
Waitresses don't make much money and
they assume right that they get tips
right
um uh in in Germany Austria and so on
it's like first of all it depends on
where you're going like also I don't
know maybe maybe in America this would
be the same but like in a fast food
restaurant you don't tip
uh in a supermarket you can maybe round
it out by a few cents if you wanna but
it's also not very common to tip and in
restaurants if it's a fancy restaurant
definitely tip
um but yeah in a normal restaurant I'm
not you don't have to yeah it's it's
acceptable people won't be really mad at
you
um but yeah tip is always nice also like
for example for delivery
like ubereats for example stuff like
that there is a tipping option but you
don't have to again it's not so oh you
don't have to um
[Music]
yeah yeah and they have a better salary
so
it's okay they're always happy though if
you tip like even if it's just a small
amount yeah
I see I see it yeah like I don't like it
in in the US and stuff like that like
the The Tipping has been it's been
inflating I think it used to be like I
think it used to be like 15 used to be
enough before but now like if it's 15
it's actually kind of a little on the
stingier side now it's more like yeah
usually it'd be like around 20 yeah
pretty big yeah I don't know I didn't
know really the exact amount but some
people in the chat have been saying like
10 is nice in you know Germany Austria
um but ah
sometimes sometimes we even also I think
at fancy places go up to 20 I'm not sure
though
yeah anyway that's yeah there's a lot
many many Japanese people living and
they have this one streets where they're
the most Japanese restaurants are lined
up like in one street it's really really
cool after the convention you'll see all
of them gathering in that street and
there's insane
it's in front of every Japanese
restaurant and then like sometimes in
between the Japanese restaurants there's
like a burger restaurant or so and that
has no line and the other restaurants
never but only the Japanese restaurants
you have to like stand in line for hours
I swear it's crazy and food is good yeah
yes I mean the people
the people have this opportunity to eat
really good Japanese food
um outside of uh Dusseldorf so yeah
that's why they of course
no I don't have much time let's go next
pack it's the seventh biggest city in
Germany just so you know oh it was
pretty big seven E7 I think Germany has
a lot of big cities like for example in
Austria we really don't besides the
capital
there's really not that many like really
big cities uh so when I go to Germany I
feel like they have so many huge cities
like cologne Berlin uh uh um I've never
heard of cologne cologne sounds like
like the
um perfume cologne yeah it's uh the
German name is Karen but I think the
English name is cologne yeah yeah
Frankfurt is a famous huge city with a
the biggest uh airport in Germany I
think and yeah uh
handbook yes big big screen
yes
yes there's a city called Hamburg like
the hamburger yeah yeah yeah yeah
and when when there's a person uh from
Hamburg you you call them a hamburger
you call them a hamburger that's cute
yeah
all right next fact a famous attraction
is the media Harbor with a modern
architecture yeah they're
um
yeah
medial Harbor oh there's like a like a
harbor uh on a like a river with lots of
like impressive buildings modern
architecture looking very interesting
yeah okay okay it's kind of like a
little futuristic sort of yeah yes
exactly
[Music]
exists since 2009 it started in a school
yeah no they started like a really small
like happened it was happening in the
school
um as the venue and now it is the
biggest anime convention in Germany
they kept on growing and growing and now
they're the biggest isn't that a amazing
success story yes amazing success it's
2009 it's very only over 10 years yeah
13 years yeah
long long long time it's it really has
made a name for itself uh because it's
so good yeah the only thing that I think
they should change is they always have
been only two days we want the
conventions to be longer most
conventions in Germany and Austria are
three days
could easily afford uh having it three
days because more people would come they
would all love to come
[Music]
maybe at some point one day they don't
have it maybe maybe an exclusivity right
and then it might have some more
professional reasons behind the scenes
but yeah that's that
yeah maybe yeah so that's the facts and
that's all the German that I prepared
it's perfect let's go yes good perfect
timing time management it's not my first
time I have a feeling for how long uh
how much German I need to teach to get
to an hour
yeah I could I'm trilingual now guys wow
do you remember and something
specifically
um
since it's almost time to go choose yeah
Cheers Cheers
was there anything I didn't teach you
that you felt like you needed to know
oh
yeah more apples I can fit more on my
head yeah
um well oh how do you say apple in
Germany
also similar yeah
yes I got four apples apple strudel is
actually a German word you say Apple
Store
German
[Applause]
I would love to continue teaching you
German uh but I really had the time
pressure I need to pass it immediately
let's just go let's let's go
I would like to say I'll see you in
Germany but you'll be there virtually I
hope you enjoy it yokumi is great
um I think one thing I want to tell you
is a German audience might be kind of
shy and not know how to Vibe with like
Japanese songs and so on partially
they're a little bit shy like they don't
really have this otaku culture that goes
like oh yeah
so it first of all don't feel
um insecure about it if they're silent
you have to really motivate them to be
like
okay okay
gotcha I'll do my best okay okay I'm
sure they'll enjoy your concert yeah
thank you they'll enjoy all of our
customers
make sure to watch our concerts and you
wonder how the [\h__\h] am I supposed to
want to concert I'm not going to Germany
for this but no our concerts are being
streamed on Twitch on tweet throughout
the weekends
yes they have a a twitch Channel just
like last year the whole stage
performances all of them throughout the
day will be streamed uh both of our
performances are at the same time on
different days
11 A.M local time which is
um jsg 6 pm
around 6 PM yeah I think yeah I don't
know what that is in EST it's really
early in EST I'll probably put up a like
a stream reservation like a waiting room
with the link uh um at the top and all
that uh otherwise you can also check our
twitters will be probably putting up the
links there too and and you can also
follow the dogumi Twitter or already
follow the dookomi twitch Channel then
you surely will not miss out on it okie
dokie
uh coming weekend yes yes don't miss it
this weekend 5 p.m
no I don't think so it's more like is it
5 a.m later yeah yeah because it's going
back anyway uh thank you for watching
everybody
thank you for teaching me and in German
we stay
[Music]
thank you
thank you good luck
ILY is that how you oh really look it's
good luck yeah
look thank you
[Music]
alrighty we should have probably wrap
this up for your flight yes yes okay
bye thank you bye I'm about
I mean
[Music]
thank you