a
[Music]
la
a
[Music]
la
n
[Music]
la
la e
[Music]
k
k hello
everybody
K I just had a donut or two Donuts
actually for
breakfast they came
so late
so it was really giddy giddy s me my
sand I order like an hour ago I
[Laughter]
think could have ordered from something
closer but I was suddenly feeling
Donuts that's not breakfast food what
it's like
bread it's basic it's it is B basically
it is bread
is it not
bread and bread is a legitimate
breakfast
food yeah yeah yeah
yeah if they're not breakfast food then
what are
they let me drink some
water they are oh what you guys say it's
considered to be more of a bref in
America I mean I normally don't choose
to eat donuts for breakfast either but I
mean bread
generally sure surely is a
thing yeah dessert I mean
honestly no I wouldn't consider them
dessert more like a sweet snack because
dessert implies that I would eat it
after a different
food I wouldn't Donuts
no that's like eating a
cuaso
after a a
dinner that's
weird that's like eating a quo or a
French n French Toast French toast can
be kind of deserty if it's like a
smaller version of it maybe
[Music]
yeah and then Donuts are supposed to be
eating in cars while drinking
coffee and making the car go we w we w
we right the chat uh is looking funny
today but I I think I made the best out
of it apparently YouTube chat kind of
broke um the CSS
overall doesn't work anymore
um so I'm window capturing the chat but
I uh chroma key the background
so uh I think it looks good cuz now it
even has like kind of an outline makes
it relatively easy to look at I
think yeah I think it's fine looks
better than keeping the background I
think
YouTube YouTube
there is 1,44 yep uh 2K baby although
YouTube keeps on telling me that I need
to change the resolution because 2K
doesn't work but I think it it's working
I
think cuz you can choose it can't
you can't
Brave we got the AI summary what wait
maybe I got it too and I just can't see
it because of hyper chat oh I wonder
I got to check that next time I don't
have hyperr on I'm not going to change
it
now it was talking about
Donuts very
[Music]
accurate
hello viewers are discussing whether
donuts can be considered a dessert or
breakfast food and debate about the
nutritional value of donuts no we were I
wasn't talking about the nutritional
value but okay Donuts are popular and
are often seen as a weekend treat
weekend n every day every day is
fine H
yeah sorry I have been sleeping kind of
badly like the first few
days of me being in Japan I was sleeping
fine and
sleeping through relatively for
tonight but recently like yesterday and
today was both filled with nightmares
and um
also me just waking up what felt like
every 20 30 minutes okay maybe not that
bad maybe every
hour uh because I can't feel comfortable
in the bed somehow I feel like I need
maybe a fluffy pillow I brought my own
pillow but that one's really small um
and helps to an extent but the pillow
that comes with the place is like really
flat and yeah not much of a
pillow I'm just like not feeling
comfortable didn't that happen last year
too yeah but then I was like yeah yeah
just like everything was too hard like
the bed was too hard and I think the
pillow was too hard too yeah yeah
yeah now I don't know I I don't think
it's too hard but it's just
uncomfortable I feel
like I I can't seem to feel comfortable
in any
position and then I got so many
nightmares man
br br I'm at
[Music]
night
oh so my back hurts so much even though
I got a massage a few days ago and it
immediately hurts
again it hurts it
hurts ah [\h__\h] I've been stretching I've
been stretching but it doesn't help
man oh
oh man I don't know man I don't know I'm
still staying here for a while it's
rough
but uh at least at least in these coming
weeks in between I'll I'll get a little
little break from this bed and sleep in
another bed
but that's not
necessarily
good cuz I'll have to go on a playe for
many hours and that's going to hurt my
back
too H yeah might it might not be an
upgrade yeah we'll see we'll see just
the the fact that I have to travel for
to get to the bed might not be good for
my
back um how long do you stretch well
like for my for the back paint I've been
stretching like you know in between like
several times throughout the day like
smaller stretches
and then for dancing I'm doing like of
course more longer proper stretches
before
dancing another trip um New
[Laughter]
York New
York I'm not going I'm not I mean yeah
maybe I'm going with other members yeah
maybe I'm not going anywhere else
nothing nothing on anoun
anounced Big Apple Big Apple a big apple
a day keeps the doctor away for maybe a
whole year who
knows my
condolences you really like New York I
don't know never been there we'll find
out you can finally have a real
breakfast when you go to NYC a a a NE
and cheese a bacon ah a bacon egg of ju
a bacon n juice a bacon ju that how they
say
that New York is kind of
stinky oh no
stinky e it's kind of gross what the
city or the bacon neg and cheese
nah I don't think it'll be that bad and
I'm sure fan I find a lot of good food
I'm so excited for food food food food
food
so it's so weird like why are these
windows breaking
who
okay okay move this here we're going to
today finish this game which I'm kind of
sad about because I really really like
it and I'm missing out on the the cute
outfit that they um give as a console
version outfit
exclusive I'm so
mad because I really like that one and
I'm I'm a fashionista and I need all of
the pie Berry outfits
man yeah we're finishing it
today no matter what happens I'm going
to finish it even if I don't get the
outfit I don't care I don't care I I do
care I do
care yeah I thought maybe there could be
a miracle where because they saw they
saw my reply like who how do I get this
outfit and they know that I'm finishing
it so soon and and they could have maybe
made a miracle happen and somehow give
me the but I guess it's just n i I guess
that's more difficult probably than I
think probably like it's like bounds to
the console version like if they wanted
it to be in the steam version they have
to code it into it
m who knows if that's that easy probably
not that easy m
man I want it doll it looks so
nice damn it Dam it damn it
anyway nonetheless we're going to finish
um which spring R today which is one of
my favorite games of this year did I say
that already I said it I think in the
Tweet
but yeah it became actually surprisingly
you
know one of my favorite games this year
I think top
three top three actually like I I don't
know like it's it's really a really
really pleasant
surprise it's very W Coria it's what I
like in
games so it has exceeded my expectations
it's so cute and it's like I don't know
you should not underestimate this kind
of
game I don't know like it's it's really
really good and they put a lot of effort
into it I can tell
so um helis in New York
what that really ening game yeah I plan
to buy when it goes on sale you mean for
console or for Steam
if you do console then have fun with the
outfit that I'm not
getting yeah the story is nice the music
is nice the graphics are nice the
characters are cute so I love it um
we're going to finish see we're getting
ready for war we're like
so the only thing I'm so curious about
is look at our our four like special
accessory slots how come we're at the
end of the game and we still have two
left over look we played 31 on hours
what's the what's the
actual
uh like
um play time that they put like on
Google when you ask how long is this
game maybe NG plus oh maybe could
be rookie numbers for J PG yeah but like
still I didn't think it would be that
long that's that's really I really
didn't think it would be that long but
I'm happy with it
[Music]
you finished it in 20 hours well you
rashed through it 20 hours says
Google is that what it says 20 32 24 25
to 30 is average oh okay so I'm above
aage yeah I'm above
average mm do I have uh oops see do I
have training points yeah yeah I
do um what would I want to train what
what was I lacking was I lacking
anything I'm I'm not lacking anything
obviously cuz I'm above average
[Music]
but have you got all secret weapon and
summon I don't
know probably not
all we can have one more extra equipment
by I by talking about oh really one of
those special ones
okay
humility what cuz I'm saying that I'm
above
average
what 20 hours of gameplay 11 hours of
wild T I don't know have I really been
tanging that much to extend the game
play I don't I feel like a t a lot like
while fighting and all that no I don't
know ah I don't know I don't know I
don't know what do we want I I I I I
maybe I'll keep the points for uh after
a few fights when I realize what I
need I don't know right now
[Music]
um yeah let's just get this
stuff cuz I came into this game with not
full HP MP
huh but now we have recovered and we
shall what's what are we doing go to the
death squad lay okay but then let's
first go to Bal where is
Bal you do pause in between dark okay
but not that much
[Laughter]
right now well it's fine anyway illusion
plane
really um
um
[Music]
here maybe here B what Bal
was wasn't
that wasn't that the the big guy that
was protecting our place in the
beginning or was it this
Dragon what why am I not sure about this
right now what's your name
he doesn't even tell me his name
anymore your B is a Golem right damn he
wants to fight me again should we I
guess I can't get out of this now uh
yeah he's back up 90 90,000 wait is this
was
that was that manageable for me I don't
remember you can refight him infinitely
oh so we have done it was it the same
amount of Health
still I smacked him
easy
okay all
right
pets uh um um um oh my Dragons Dragon
de let's get this
[Music]
one how much was that cost I know I can
I don't have to look at the cost but
this one's so cheap even even though
it's so strong holy
[Music]
[\h__\h] what's this guy's element I don't
know but whatever oh wait I'm get I'm I
have fire and ice out they're going to
find ice death and life now they're
going to cancel each other
out sorry
bro ice ice bye-bye
I don't know I mean explosive shouldn't
be canceling out right let's let's go
with this
one fire I st Al now hi pressure never
look
down what does that mean what do the
lyrics mean I I honestly don't really
understand the lyrics much of that
song um they are a mystery to me what
are we going to do what are we going to
do I don't know
um oh we have ice circle now I forgot
what that looks like what is what is
that again oh go go that works good on
big enemies huh although 6,000 is not
much is it
[Music]
though
yeah I mean it's not it's I don't know
it was 6,400 or so that's not so
good n wait what am I doing I don't I I
I forgot how to
play I should probably put on the
defense would be
helpful I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I think
I'm sleepy my mind is still sleepy very
sleepy it'll come back to
me don't eat
me dragon versus dragon
should we just I don't know oh God I
can't think what's wrong with
me ah okay I have to wait yeah yeah yeah
I can't think I can't think I can't
think
uh probably we're
fine I still have full HP
how come I still have full HP ah because
of the
defense answering my own questions at
least oh he missed oh he
missed and didn't hurt me at all oh God
I obliterated this guy holy [\h__\h] look at
his HP and he didn't hit me a single
time
yet A's defense is too strong too op oh
my God oh my God 2
I'm taking him
down
what oh
wow damn nrow flash thank you that looks
yummy looks like like shark
meat respawning narrow I feel bad for
him he just he
just he's like is like a punching bag
for us now okay where is
belt do you guys know where exactly belt
is um I would like to
know maybe down
here south somewhere does this Lead
South at
all
without fighting is wait oh there is a
South path all
right keep going right I'm not South
[Music]
here go right
okay oh well a few rhinal horns won't
hurt have I ever been down here what is
this white rhino
[Music]
shelter oh I think I've never been
here H have
I I haven't fought any of these rhinos
before but I may have just generally
ignored the
[Music]
Rhinos wait I just I just want to see if
there's anything besides enemies
[Music]
here I have but it says a group of
enemies you have never fought
before see says at the bottom a group of
enemies you've never fought
before let me fight
[Music]
these I'm late but I'm here hello
thany welcome to the
[Music]
stream uh I wasn't sure about what time
to stream in today but I hope this is
okay guys as I said I should probably
take advantage of being able to stream
at an time Prim Time but depending on
how long this will go obviously it will
go over time
I'm just going
to take all of these down for
fun you appreciate it good as you should
I know an has several time zones yeah
yeah yeah but I I I I know and that
makes it difficult
too that makes it difficult too but I
try to
um like see what time is
good for both pstd and EST and
everything in between is
automatically resolved
then well EST will start suffering
earlier than P
today it is what it
[Music]
is for me for me the time is
fine
I uh have to
record my new song after this cuz I've
been saying that I'll be recording it
the past few days and yesterday I was
too tired the day before that I was too
tired but today is the
day today's the day I'm going to record
[Music]
it it's I would
say quite different from Kimera
um but still K-pop style
[Music]
H I think like if you look at all the
K-pop Style songs I've done so
far the one that it would be most
similar to is maybe do you but I think
it's still like different if if you
don't know if you don't like listen to a
[\h__\h] of K-pop like me then it might all
sound the same to you
but um it's not
okay B are you here or on the other
path okay maybe the other PA oh wait
there's there's an exclamation mark
though
what what
[Music]
the Yeah Kima being hard to follow up on
that's for sure a concern I had oh
[Music]
hello that is definitely something I was
like like ah what do I do about this how
do I how do I top Chima I don't know if
I can top it I think because it will
sound a little bit like a different
style of K-pop M it really just depends
on your tastes you might like it more
you might not like it
more or you like or you will like it
about the same
[Music]
H but yeah I want to try like all kinds
of different Vibes
so yeah there's there's
one um K-pop artist that I really really
love and I love her Vibes in her music
and so I've been trying to go for that
for this song so you will you will see
once you once you hear
it yeah what kup groups I'm listening to
these days well I would say new jeans
mostly um
and in
between
sometimes twice and
[Music]
um I don't
know uh mostly those two at the moment
H
twice
yeah that's right I have my mom's magic
now are you talking to B oh well not
really I can sense his mind M it must be
the effect of illusion's magic Kiss of
Life uh I have fun like seeing their
stuff and like uh videos of them dancing
and
stuff and I do like
[Music]
the yeah I know that
what um they have a funny twerking Coro
day like really like intense intense
attempts of twerking are being made
there they're all amazing dancers but
[Music]
um I don't know when there's twerking in
K-pop uh it it tends
to look a little funny
sometimes uh like holy [\h__\h] in that Coro
that the way they try to TW Twerk it I
am it makes me feel worried about like
their backs and like oh my
God
waa
[Music]
[Laughter]
uh but besides that I think uh they have
fun coros and and and nice dances nice
uh songs and I like I like how
they have more of a mature Vibe and
um they seem really titty I've seen like
some cute
interactive uh Coral from them where
they like kind of
M what's the
word I don't know they just like they
it's a four people group and they like
sometimes you know they pair up and then
they dance with each other with each
other and I like those kind of
interactive
dances oh yeah Le Sim uh I listen to
them
too but maybe not as much as new jeans I
don't
[Music]
know oh it must be the effect of
illusion's Magic ah that could be it Bal
I heard you were actually protecting me
all this time for my mom thank you when
you turned up in laak Village I thought
you were there to get revenge on me
call aha so you were trying to protect
me from the warrior I'm so sorry for the
misunderstanding so you were keeping
watch on me even in laak
Village
cool thanks for the membership
welcome I'm so Ted you're really
considerate wow but how did you get to
lak village with such a big
body but that question to me sounds like
a question that you would
ask
um uh a
wolf who is dressed up as a
grandma I don't know the way it's
phrased sounds like that to
me b b can observe and move between any
Forest on this continent he is one with
nature wow Bal is a much more impressive
Spirit than I thought B is one of the
three great spirits of Familia
that's it just a little bit of talking I
thought we would maybe I don't know
fight him just for fun a gift from B
increases recovery ability of tools or
skills when equipped nice oh are you
giving this to me a life Stone using
this will help you regain Health you're
such a good
Bo I'm so sorry for always causing you
so much trouble trying to leave the
forest you did go a little far
yeah I know B I'll do whatever I can to
bring my mom back to
Al
okay I too have an urge to punch my own
friends in the face
sometimes I mean that's not that's not
what I
mean that's not what I mean so does it
go here oh it does nice
recovers HP upon hit 1% that's not much
but okay recovers HP upon kill 10% oh so
if I kill like smaller mobs in a big
fight that could be pretty nice but the
yellow text doesn't say anything about
the increases recovery ability like how
many how much
percent but I guess we shall trust it
and believe it nice nice thank you for
letting me know about this
Pas m is there anything secret
[Music]
here one thing I'll say they could have
hidden more like secret treasures or so
in like hidden Corners like
this oh this thing plaque
bro I I mean I saw this but I didn't
think you could take it a branch that
fell from the white tree and grew on its
own without
roots White
staff is it good I currently have an
evolved flame staff like it's probably
not better but oh wow I can you upgrade
it though would it be worth to upgrade
it oh increase magic 60% plus 180
increase strength
120 that's one of the possible morphing
staffs what does that
mean recovers HP upon hit the kill white
trees blessing
H if if I upgrade it would it be better
than my current one I
[Music]
wonder you could have got this earli if
you fed the stuff you had
[Music]
differently you mean this was one of the
things it could have evolved into
what since you have lightning blade
after quest you can evolve that one into
sta uh
okay
[Music]
okay what you guys say to me sounds like
riddles but
okay I don't know where I'm going I
guess I can teleport now and go to the
lair let's continue the story
Picola
story not Picola
story W Berry and Pie Berry story The
Sword you have can turn to best of
what I have this sword
already cuz it sounded like I'm getting
it after this
Quest hey yo waa look at those
robots whoo whoo look look at him
sheesh wait has bunny
ears looks like something pickled I
would
build
Dam where am I where am I going Who Am
I who I need to talk to probably in the
probably the big
guy
scoozie Wawa coming through
hello p told ver everything that had
happened uh share please I don't
remember what
[Laughter]
happened hey
Rea hey
[Music]
no
recap M SL has been given to veran
current Sal of the palace giant Golem
maximizes the performances performance
of a Golem by injecting magic into its
power source Beyond its limits this
gives the Golem's magic Cannon an
extremely powerful blast range and power
great weapon
weakness they're wasting so much paper
using a new page each time each time
going oh my God the power source
produces extreme heat due to excessive
performance modifications as a result
the power source is exposed on the
outside of the
body the time it takes to condense
energy before firing is proportional to
the power of the magic Cannon enemy
responds however the pope is aware of
this
uhhuh expect a great weapon to fire
short burst of explosive power before
destroying the exposed power source
uh-huh okay
[Music]
cute she's so cute
mhm she studied the documents Matt
handed over
game is quiet
trying to remember who Ichigo was yeah
Ichigo was number one but also
strawberry
and number one as in
like number
one like of a product or so
[Music]
beautiful yeah my bird
wives are in this
game is he dying
he's shivering that's a sign of dying
isn't it black Joe are you
[Music]
good pize me
MIM isn't that where dead people
[Music]
are oh
he wants to go to his father's grave
wait
wait wa come to the conclusion that his
father is alive oh well maybe that's
when he will realize okay uh sure
Heroes Haven wait where is that where do
I go I assume that but he doesn't he's
playing
dumb
[Music]
Heroes where where where where
where I mean it's probably not in my map
yet right but close to
where behind Church yeah I thought they
said something about R Village
so do we go through
here but I have to like probably go from
either here or
here yay okay let's go speaking of waya
you know me and waya went to have
dinner and you know how I was asking
denma
to like get us a restaurant with a prate
room cuz in Japan restaurants so many of
them offer like really tiny private
rooms and when when I say private room
it's like
often not
really uh like a proper room it's just
like walled off a little bit or so with
really thin
walls wait which way do I go yeah it's
more like a boo thing but it really
helps to like have a more
intimate time or feel more like private
and
protected uh makes you feel like you can
talk about more stuff so generally uh we
get those kind of
rooms uh when we meet up with other Hol
members and so and there's really a lot
of them like so many restaurants
especially isaka isaka basically is on
the other hand rare to not have a
private room called
kosu um we go through here right
yeah and so I asked I asked GMA to find
me restaurants that we could go to that
have oh k a private room and you know
she sent me a few right and I I chose
one and she reserved it and then we went
there and the funny thing
was um it it was way more or no so
beforehand uh Jemma told me that there's
like a base fee per person per hour for
this place 5,000 yen which is like maybe
40 bucks okay maybe 35 depending on how
well the yen is doing in the moment or
how badly and I thought oh that's fine
because I didn't know yet at that point
that it's per hour also I just thought
it was per person and then we can be
like for 2 hours or so but because the
food look uh still pretty cheap the food
looks cheap so like why not right
whatever I really want to eat this stuff
that they have on the menu it caught my
ey so
whatever um but like when I arrived they
told us it's per hour per person so we
have to pay 80 bucks for the first hour
together and then if we stayed another
then it's
uh do you do the math 100 60 bucks I
guess roughly okay uh plus the food and
drinks but I didn't think it was
necessary to stay longer anyway because
when we arrived and we were led to the
private room they had exactly one
private
room and it's not really one of those
typical private rooms it was a party
room that's why there's a big extra
cost because it's a huge party room that
seats like maybe 30
people and there's like sofas and all
the tables they're like low sofa tables
so we ended up sitting on the
floor to eat our food um and there's a
big like screen and the K Machine and
like some kind of like I don't know slot
machine or some some gaming
stuff it was a huge party room and it
was just a tool and we were kind of like
yeah confused like oh this is okay no
but I mely understood the situation okay
so like it says it's a private room on
like the online booking
service and I guess that's a
misunderstanding it's a private room
yeah but it's also a party room that's
not really what normally you I would be
looking for just a small like tiny
partitioned room yeah so we had this
whole room and like we already entered
so I felt like at that point like okay
it would be almost embarrassing if we
back out now if we say uh sorry like Mis
understanding I mean I knew it was going
to cost you know a little bit but when
she said like it would cost per hour to
that's when I was like
H wait what do you think about just
staying in this room for an hour and
then we go out of the room and continue
on one of the normal tables because
honestly they didn't they had like a lot
of space and it didn't look like it
would be such an issue to just sit on
one of the normal tables you know or sit
on the chairs like ideally we would sit
on the chairs not on the
table Yeah so we stayed in there we ate
like our main course in there sitting on
the floor of this big ass party
room and then after the hour tick tick
tick tick over uh I I like left the room
and with rain and I I told the waiter
like hello sorry um can we continue our
stay here but exit the party room don't
extend our our fee for it let's just uh
can we just sit here on a normal table
and have our dessert there yeah I think
they were a little bit like disappointed
but you got to understand there is a
misunderstanding I thought this was a
normal private room but it was a whole
party
room uh so yeah the food was cheap but
overall the whole party room thing made
things
expensive there has been a misunder
understanding yeah of course they
allowed it and then oh my God the the
main course was already really yum like
it does it didn't seem like you know
expensive ass fancy food but still the
flavor was really good and and then the
dessert broke my brain I need to I need
to go back there the dessert was so good
oh my
God the dessert was what got me to
choose it in the first place I need to
go there again so good and I really
honestly like I L the atmosphere of the
place there was like it was like really
dark and kind of romantic and a million
millions of flowers everywhere and you
could literally you could literally buy
flower
bouquet in the restaurant there was like
this whole
section of flower bouquets besides the
flowers that were decorated everywhere
you could just buy the bouquet there
which is cute if
you not cute I think it's uh um what's
the word uh uh [\h__\h] it's on my
tongue convenient it's convenient but at
the same time if you want a date there
the date will see it when you walk in
that there's flowers you can buy there
so
I don't know like imagine your
date going over to buy the flower
bouquet right where you can see it and
then give it to you that that just kind
of destroys the
magic but you could maybe get inspired
if you go there with honestly it seemed
like a place that a lot of girls go to
not really men but if two let's say two
if two male friends went there and they
see the flowers and they're like oh I
have a girlfriend at home I'm going to
bring her the flowers home you see that
could Inspire them to get the flower
bouquet and bring it home
but if you're already on a date there I
feel it's like awkward to buy it right
there I don't
know weird but funny and nice place I
want to go again anyway why is this
Dragon Lady
here Ohio mus off do we know which a she
doesn't recognize
me oh uh kind
of well I'll I pretend I didn't see
anything I have I have no interest in
causing a f okay so she gets it maybe
she would remember my bird right even if
I'm dressed up like you know I obviously
still look similar right and there's
this fat bird flying next to me that you
should
remember man a broke
a maybe when the girl goes to the
bathroom you grab them but still like
you would L see where it came from and
that just kind of breaks the magic I
think he's not fat he's friend shaped
yes
true
true yeah the bird is not being changed
at
all I just noticed his butt like tail
shaking while he's flying I think that's
really
cute you notice oh wow you have a good
eye observing prin is my job I'm sure
you can see that uh yeah then please
continue to play ignorant wow wait
that's funny thing to say but I know
what you mean h why why are you sniffing
me you smell disgusting no I smell you
smell like you have a Tonia a dragon egg
how did
you I I I I can I can smell your Ovation
of the egg what no can't be it's not
it's no makes no sense what I've been
investigating that cia's dragon's
habitat I think the smell from The Nest
may have gotten stuck to you
pberry oh I see maybe this will
help
what
ooh cute it looks like an owl dragon
what the [\h__\h]
doesn't that face like is that on
purpose it looks like an owl the head
looks like an
owl looks like an owl the nose has this
thing this coloring that makes it look
like it's a
beak the the coloring around the eyes is
like very
owly and the the the the the scales on
top of its nose look like you know owe
feathers and the overall coloring of the
the dragon also is very owly I would
say that's
funny so we can if we use our spell book
we can make this we can hatch the egg
basically and make it into a pet of our
it's a method of incubating dragon eggs
taken from the nest I've been working on
it for a while while I was playing pal
World ah okay I see that's what you
learned dead okay
thanks wait what's of all these people
who want to talk to
me Justice is a traitor wasn't he
supposed to be the next Supreme Warrior
why would such a promising boy I heard
he was possessed by a witch no way
perhaps he had too much contact with the
witches and eventually lost his mind
such a try his father was a hero of the
spring War I they're all gossiping about
Justice okay I don't care about your
shitty
gossip by the way I finally saw the
trailer for the new Zelda game because
finally I almost gave up on the hopes
that he would do it he was really
late uh a few hours ago finally dendo
did his um
reaction of the trailer he just didn't
do it until now cuz he was on vacation
makes sense now I watched it
is this the right
way I wanted to react with you well I
told you I was going to like wait for
D yeah yeah he really likes it thanks
for
asking he really likes it he was hyping
it up he was saying oh this this like
this this hand grabby thing where you
can move objects is better than in Tok
even I don't know why but I I like it
and yeah I don't know it's really cool
but I was like curious about there being
a a wanted
poster for Zelda on the wall oh
interesting and and that makes sense
with her wearing a hood the whole
time like for some reason she's yeah
probably on the
run and she has to disguise herself but
she's still helping people who probably
if they knew who they were dealing with
would try to arrest her or
something now you can watch a trailer
with my she watching but you know I I I
I I I I thought you know I I mean I do
watch other trailers without myoshi
watching it because myoshi just won't
watch them but the stuff that she does
watch why not watch it when he's
watching
it disguise but not as Chic
right you admit that he's your oi well I
mean you could put it that way I guess
but
like I guess but he's just a YouTuber
that I
watch when I guess you could put it that
way cuz you guys have been putting it
that way so I'm just like repeating what
you're
saying well don't buy any merch
though didn't buy any merch of him ever
I just um okay I've been to one fan
meeting and that's it realized there's
only kids
[Music]
there kiala is just a YouTuber I watch
well yeah I mean
hey hey shut up what why are you saying
that I'm not even bothered by it I'm not
even bothered by it and also you're
lying I'm more than that to you let's be
real we're very parasocial in here and
you you I'm more than
that I am that but in addition to that I
am more than that I am above
[Laughter]
average anyway let's avoid the
conversation after all the Pop's Castle
just around the corner wait so it's not
here that tells me it's not here okay
there was another path that
looked like might be it where am I going
from the wrong side I don't know but I'm
thinking over
[Music]
there yeah yeah there's a there's a path
there and it's said behind the castle so
it makes sense sorry brain is weak and
slow why is no secret here
why so yeah was a good trailer looks
really good can't believe it's coming
out so soon too I'm really excited that
we can play it soon and it will be out
at a time where I'm finally not busy
anymore so I think cuz end of September
so all of October we'll be playing the
new to game well it probably won't be
all of October I don't think it's that
long
probably who knows I mean it's certainly
not going to be as long as like a Tok
playthrough I know there's one big grave
but let me look at the other stuff first
first this I do something here
no
okay yeah I'm thinking probably similar
to Link's Awakening or maybe a little
bit
longer that's excited and we played
Zelda can you believe it
[Applause]
[Music]
it's a good time to be playing Zelda
games my back hurts [\h__\h] me my neck and
my shoulders I need a massage
again but I ran out of money cuz I I I
spent all my money on clothes I needed
new clothes I needed new summer clothes
but I bought a lot of cute clothes now I
need to take out some money from the ATM
but I'm worried like what's this like do
I get much less money
[Music]
now do I get much less money now because
of the Yen being
weird or has it already like become uh a
bit more like before again cuz
like Yen tank oh is it oh oh oh he still
very good exchange rate
okay we will never financially recover
from this it's a strong again yeah so
I'm not getting as much as I got when I
exchanged
money like for example 2 weeks
ago
but thank you
L you get more hey I get more Yen
H it works that way
it works that
way even
[Music]
more even
more
bro if the yen is stronger it buys more
Euro but wouldn't I get less then I
don't
know if you're exchanging yes but if
you're withdrawing from a no it's not a
Japanese account I'm just using Japanese
ATM but withdraw from uh like my
Austrian
account 1 to
161 okay so I don't have to at least
it's not like a big negative change
[Music]
okay if you're trying to convert euro to
Y you get that's what I was saying yeah
that's what what I was thinking less
than compared to two weeks ago or so
this week's gone up a little
now up up up okay upes upes for the Yen
up yeah it's probably yeah not crazy
difference right in in any
case not that much less okay
up
aies yay the yen is getting
aies oh hey
jce oh I summoned
him
nice is he going to like show up from
the back or so after a
while
for Fore
[Music]
trying to massage my back but it's like
hard to reach
[Music]
what did we know his
name like I heard for the same first
time
[Music]
we are in the graveyard
oh Justice
[Music]
well that's me right just say it clearly
it's pretty obvious what who you
mean
[Music]
for Fore
spee
foree fore
[Music]
that's
it as if she was saying
yes okay well that seems like a little
bit tempting because she probably
doesn't want other witches to be hunted
[Music]
anymore but still that's the crazy
imagine the
new
yeah she wouldn't have tried to take him
down if he didn't start the Witch Hunt
but he started the Witch Hunt because
he's afraid yeah yeah yeah I I am not
taking in what you saying right now but
I think I know what you mean and I've
also been thinking of that uh while he
was saying that like is it is isn't that
um like what's the word
self-fulfilling prophecy yeah I agree
but I don't understand he
literally no uh I think I understand
yeah the circle of
life a self-fulfilling prophecy but wait
explain that to me again then explain to
me so she what
what he made the verific he predicted
come true
[Music]
for um explain um is it like chicken or
egg yeah I guess yeah Paradox a self no
no you don't have to put explain the
that to me like how how is this a
self-fulfilling prophecy I mean I know I
think I know but can we put it into
words uh no let me read that again the
kind of
thing she wouldn't have tried to take
him down if he didn't start the Witch
Hunt but he start the Witch Hunt because
he's afraid of her taking yeah because
the the arut arut he said she will take
them down and that's why he is trying to
take her
down but she's only she only has that in
her mind to like taking him down because
he's doing nothing so if he wouldn't try
to take her down just because I M said
she's going to take you guys down then
she wouldn't be taking him down because
he wouldn't be taking trying to take her
down but the simple fact that anamu said
like anamu is a troublemaker a trouble
starter a fire starter a little
[\h__\h] cuz he sees the future but if he
would just not have said anything if
Anam wouldn't have said
anything then the pop wouldn't know that
pberry would have that goal then he
wouldn't be mad he wouldn't think about
starting a Witch Hunt and then wouldn't
that solve all problems if adamu would
have just shut the [\h__\h]
up he could have just said
nothing that's so but then that's that
feels
like that feels like then he was just
like literally just gossiping adamu
basically just gossiping some [\h__\h] to
create the trouble that wouldn't have
been there if he wouldn't have said
anything
[Music]
this is what we call a
prophecy would still have been stealing
magic though wouldn't he would he I
don't know there there must be more to
it because otherwise this would make
little
sense because if Adam would can see a
future or so like and can make this
prophecy wouldn't he also think of the
logic behind it
like if it just wouldn't say anything
then this wouldn't happen I don't
know he's the bad one that's that God
thing I'm out of that's he's the bad
one all right
[Music]
okay and I want to know um he he says
I'm aware he's more powerful at the Adam
spring specifically
but then why he has a he has anam's
blessing too or what why is heer there
can we like repeat the the facts for
that
one why is he stronger in that spring I
thought only I'm getting the
blessings why is he why is he stronger
there it's a spring he controls he gets
power from it why how does he control it
he stole it
[Music]
ah he stole it and that's why Adam M was
probably like
bro I have someone who will take you
down and she will avenge me for you
stealing my power I guess okay let me
get potato
chips potato chips because this story is
so exciting we're getting to the the
high points you need popcorn or potato
chips
poat I want to just snack just want to
snack I want something salty right now
[Music]
it's like it's convenience store size
it's a little bit smaller than like the
big bags it's just 80
g no no
usui USU sh is the flavor um lightly
salted
that's not a big
[Music]
bag
yum once the war begins there will be no
time for maintenance so I must be
completely prepared I will have to tell
version when I'm ready oh
okay they're hinting to me that I
should get ready
[Music]
M
well yeah let's make the L
dragon and you guys are saying about
morphing my sword into a
staff how not here right
which
[Music]
one wait I
guess sword you take to the andle
H need to talk to Raina first for side
quest oh
[Music]
really I'm missing something those balls
can I make them out of smaller balls
thingies for sure right come
on no damn it
this also needs those balls where are
those
again oh wait uh those
balls clear droplet bag
do
see probably somewhere early you can buy
balls in un luck
really do I really need that lightning
sword
and stab they really need that probably
not right but why
[Music]
not I can find them in the Lion's
plane yeah but if I can buy them I have
so much
money why not buy them
flexing my
[Music]
money was it here I haven't really
shopped here
oh
nice I have so much
money let's buy a few of
[Music]
these I have so much m on it oh my
God got to invest is there anything else
I can buy
here no you probably don't sell anything
oh what is the item up
there
a okay
should avoid telling using teleportation
in the village yeah
yeah
[Music]
possibly I guess that dropped to uh
before I'm I'm heart Temple yeah it's
okay no need I bue I need to help the
economy we live in an
[Music]
economy what they
doing um let's make this Dragon oh it
needs the meat from the big guy which I
only have one of what did I use the
other one for when I fought him
before good that I fought him today
already
new pet it's got to be strong baby
dragon hatch from Tonia dragon egg yippe
tiny tough Tyrant don't let my size fool
you I got an
[Music]
achievement it gives you 100 per
wait holy [\h__\h] that's op because you can
kill him as much as you
want you can eat that a million times
and make yourself so buff
oh my God that's
[Music]
crazy eat it this Dragon I would have
eaten it when it was an
egg I wonder what dragon eggs tastes
like now it's too late to find out
[Music]
I wonder what the dragon eats
though
Ram base attack 3,400 that's
[Music]
good pretty cheap MP summon cost and
summon cost in general okay I want to
eat don't tell me you eat that big uh
shark meat
cuz following mother mimics tail strike
of a mother Tonia
[Music]
Dragon this is
um a surprise the ugly bird ah yeah
didn't all Dragon so far eat the ugly
bird meat anyway
[Music]
yeah black Joe
Meat I think I need to go to I don't
[Music]
meum gu I'll
go okay can I eat potato chips while I
go just
[Music]
myself
B it's okay I'm not I'm not I'm
[Music]
not e
ah yippe
[Music]
don't you dare comment on the length of
a lady's Idol
meeting you are not a
gentleman hul on usual room three
months three months I should give you
more I would like to give you more I'll
give you free mons though because I have
[Music]
mercy I do actually have to autograph a
lot of stuff yeah JMA gave me the the
birthday merchandise so was what is it
is it a Polaroid again I think it might
be a Polaroid I
[Music]
forgot yeah eh any reaction
no anything to your defense
[Music]
no okay what was I
doing yeah the hook hook Papa po yeah I
have to sign them I have them here I
guess I'll sign them while I'm in
Japan okay what was I doing
uh what what was I doing
we can go get the the quest the side
quest now ah cuz I hatched the pet and I
gave it uh full love I didn't fully feed
it oh
okay
thanks I was wondering while I was in
the idle meeting what skill element does
the dragon have none wait no
ground well the skill element is none
but generally it's ground okay
not
interesting Yum Yum Yum another one oh
it needs
free sironia J will have increased skill
power in battle
yippe anyone else oh you need you need
to okay nice anyone else you guys
nah oh and never Dragon who needs more
meat okay and this
one does the base attack go up 1 1,
15003 does it go up let's
[Music]
see
oh spewing flame of the flame T becomes
increasingly enraged and unleashes a
huge flame
cool okay ah it just it it it didn't go
up it went up by 300 sh R by
Shi
hello I don't see it in hyper chat but I
guess it started like around somewhere
oh w wow thank
you can't even find where it began now
that didn't take me 5 minutes I was
feeding my
dragons they were hungry
okay hello welcome thank you shi for the
wi yippee
welcome we're playing a super cute game
it might be the finale but I think you
guys can still stay and watch if you
want to because it's really cute and we
have cute cute girls cute
characters and um cute pets and cute
birds and it's fun it's
[Music]
cute and we'll do a side quest now
anyway so you guys said I have to talk
to
um our narissa guys do you want to see
narissa in this
game the novits do you want to see
narissa trust me yes you want to see
narissa she's in this
[Music]
game
mhm let me show
you she's
hot yeah cuz freeding the is tomorrow
right oh my God this is this is me
leaking her
fre is she up
here oh where is
she is she not where she usually is
[Music]
now not
here H Pastor she's next to the Golems
oh ah
[Music]
ah wait look at her picture look
black
hair blue highlights in the back overall
white black blue outfit with like a
white blouse and and the
arms yeah this is literally her like if
she was more of a fighter kind of uh
character
right that is so
her yeah
yeah Isa kinder a tall standing proud
she's so cool or I mean even if it's not
Nissa it could be like anyone from her
family any one of her sisters or
so it it could be like one of those
sister designs of her which looks
similar but not the same un horned yeah
no horns she lost all her horns now
she's just a she lost her magic with her
horns and now she fights with a
sword makes sense
and she will give us a side quest
apparently I see the connection of what
we're going to
[Music]
do why she pissed
off yeah never start talking about just
yeah there's Justice and I've been
playing this game since before Justice
came out so I've been
like I I I had justice in my head so
much every time the name Justice came up
in this game I was thinking of Justice
our new generation
maybe I manifested
[Music]
jti Nissa wants you to know she's
different from
[Music]
Justice we believe you Nisha we believe
you
no narissa has been for some
[\h__\h] the pulp is evil in this game
surprise
damn that's so
heavy of
course her Stinger is not working the
same as usual
oh
[Music]
no I feel like I have
that maybe no needs to look for it
okay maybe I don't have
it
no maybe I already used it for
crafting
[Music]
yeah I guess so light light no us where
was that again we fought it
before let's go home once get out of
here
yeah there Isa desires horns that's
funny what a
coincidence allusion planes okay yeah
the game is on Steam but it's coming out
on Console too soon and the console
comes with an outfit that I will never
have an outfit for pberry the character
that I will never
have so painful
we could fight him again soon
possibly okay who am I looking for the
light ah the light no service okay well
let me go get on a
[Music]
pet where did we find the light noer by
the way this is Justice uh this this is
Justice the guy is justice
he's our Crush he was our enemy first
now he's our
friend and we are deeply in love with
him and now we can summon him whenever
we want perfect perfect boyfriend
[Music]
material yeah we can't get piggybacked
by him
unfortunately wait
so guys where was where was the lurus is
it behind this guy up there or
[Music]
oh
okay okay okay the Golem the giant okay
let's take him down ah I don't want the
dragon out here but
okay yeah dragon
lion oh but hey they're weak so no
problem for us yippe
[Music]
35 months of membership you know soon
we'll be at four years and I'm I'm
looking forward to doing the only chat
uh only people who have been subscribed
for four years can chat that kind of
thing I want to do it
again I want to see you
guys what's the word shrivel and numbers
[Music]
one after another I want to see you go
and
disappear in thin
air and we'll see we'll see who's
left I will test
you wait how long is the respawn time
bro
I let's see how fast does it go up when
I'm standing here
oh
God it's not going up shitty download
speed the shittiest download speed when
when did we take it down when did we
kill
[Music]
him I am not in this game mm-
what do I do does it I wonder if it
considers me going to sleep in the
game or if it is just time of me running
around do you guys
know I need to fight to pass the time ah
okay
okay let's get
some m
[Music]
where where would be
good
snowfield I don't think the enemies
there are that weak I think we need some
you know good
enemies m
[Music]
what I don't know if you're serious but
of course I wasn't serious either you
know I wasn't comfortable using my real
name in February of doing trip I tried
to convert to a brand account but it
didn't
work what I don't understand why did you
try to convert to a brand account
though can't you just if you don't want
to use your real name can't you just
change your YouTube
name but don't worry it's just the dark
it's just funny to see the chat suddenly
go quieter and
quieter it was before it was allowed
okay well don't worry about
it I know that there's of course also
even if you are subscribed since day one
there's circumstances where you may have
unsubscribed once by accident or where
maybe you were playing games with me
when I was like doing um you know a
marathon to get get to a certain number
and then you unsubscribe just to see the
counter go
down or YouTube subscribed you without
your permission because YouTube
sometimes does funny tricks on you
doesn't
[Music]
it ah oh unsubbing and resubbing to try
to fix a YouTube issue
huh yeah so I know I'm not like uh
assuming
that you know I I know that some of you
guys may be subscribe since day one or
so even if it doesn't say
so don't worry about
it turn bonus let's go does this hit
both
no okay we have to f a few mobs to make
the
spawn uh
oh the spawn of the light noceros come
back to us hopefully that will be over
all worth it with a much more improved
staff that we get out of it hopefully
hopefully
hopefully doesa have any quests we can
check but she wasn't this way she was on
the other side I
think ah
Luna I miss her let's go see her I think
she was down here and then up
there right oh no oh she's up there
H I only discovered you like two what
really but I mean after four years those
two or three months they they're like
nothing don't worry but I'm surprised I
thought you were there since the
beginning YouTube turned my account into
a brand account a long time ago and I
was but why why does it just do
that n
[Music]
we don't even get to
ENT
oh oh
really I guess this could be sh
Senai could be sh Senai in her magical
girl
outfit I mean a little bit you know tun
and those the the shape of those eyes
you know the the tun
eyes the smug
[Music]
eyes and the the color fee kind of
fits
[Music]
yeah catching up it's so cute
she's the MC ofing too
what how did I not no
this
what so for spring players she's a
returning character
which spring to is L POV of the same
events
what
what how do I learn of this
now oh my God mind
blown but this is a remake of the first
game so pberry was the first MC
Aha and I guess Luna was already in the
non- Remake version of this and then
they the second game they made was this
this her story was basically like
a spin-off more or less well not really
but Side Story different POV
story
interesting oh yeah which spring 2 is
not on Steam right so I'm waiting for it
I'm waiting for it bring it to me
is it free on the phone maybe I don't
usually play phone games but maybe I'll
maybe I'll get
it maybe I'll get R Spring to to play on
my phone like on my free time I always
have my phone with me
so okay it's not free but is it even in
my Google Store in my Play
Store let me
[Music]
see which
spring
[Music]
to oh oh it's really cheap too yeah I
have all the all the witch spring games
here witch spring too get with play
pass play
pass what do what's play
pass why can I not just buy
normally so like a Game Pass don't get
Google Play pass I don't want to doesn't
show
wait I don't know I'll look at it
another
[Music]
time oh
do I love
free which spring free it's also on
Steam uhhuh f on Steam uh-huh but is
Luna in that one maybe
not by the
[Music]
way
is is this this person uh this one this
one or is
it yeah is this
person
Kim you
John
uh you guys see it
yeah one is this person the
death cuz I've been seeing them always
in the witch spring R streams
and they're Korean so what makes sense
are you are you
de
de cuz they they talk like it's because
of your favorite game ah just a big
witch spring R fan okay which spring
fan okay
[Music]
okay I don't have to get Google PS
really okay I'm look more into
[Music]
it is she giving me the last little oh
no
it's she gives me an ice magic
step but I probably won't use it because
I guess the other stuff I'm making is
going to be better
[Music]
they give me too many choices
of my stuff is good but can't be
upgraded nice to have
[Music]
she
said
D she kind of gives
me Vibes and P Vibes and like all of
them
[Music]
together aush love
child yeah there's not many of you guys
left you got to be friendly
[Music]
let me look at the
staff okay considering how upgraded our
staff is and evolved it's not bad but
yeah this would be maybe a criticism
from from me that there's so many nice
weapons that I want to use but you can
have a really overpowered or stronger
one like before you get all of the
others and then there's no point in
using them even though they look so
pretty
[Music]
ah first Wich spring streamer yeah I
think in in the whole life I'm
definitely the only
[Music]
one would be nice to have them as skins
really yeah for
example the strongest one is lightning
stuff okay we're working on that
one now let's fight another group of
enemies I guess I wonder if the
conversation just now also adds to the
timer
I would hope
so wait I want my fire
dragon and even though it's a short
fight let me bring out this Dragon too
oh he's he's not flying he just stands
on the
ground
a I want see them
attack he's shaped very differently from
the others but I guess he's a special
one he's a special little
boy 1,900 damage mhm okay and
you he Rams him 4,100 damage Ram not bad
such a simple tackle attack and he's so
[Music]
good h
5,555 nice
[Music]
number oh now you're doing more okay
nice good Dragon who a good Dragon who a
good Dragon you you have invited a
counter attack my friend this will be
the end of you a ram let's go 4,000 cute
our ow dragon is really cute and
strong he's a baby
fire dragon felt like the weakest of the
four yeah it doesn't it doesn't seem
super strong
[Music]
sadly that's also maybe it would be nice
if the pets were able to level like the
more you use them so that like one of
the earlier ones if you really liked
having them around and if you liked
their skills you could continue using
them that would be nice if they would
like level a little bit with you just
like depending on how much you use
them but it's fine it's fine the system
is fine
too I generally like using the new ones
anyway but some of them are like the
dragons like I feel like some of them
should be
stronger ideally
we go in
here they do scale in my stats really oh
there's nothing here that's where we got
one of the Dragons right or the cats the
the the ice cat or whatever that was one
of them
confusing bu the 120k armor oh I can buy
some fancy nice armor I have money I
could do it if it's better than my
current
one where where are the
enemies
hello okay pH
some mrail in the capital okay
perhaps perhaps we shall do that
[Music]
yeah I'm waiting respawn I have no MP
no ah
damn even with crle hit oh
no I should have broughten more pets
from the beginning oh
[Music]
well I'm not going to use MP item now
I'm not going to do
it whoa
nice this one's so strong like his
charged attack is really
good good
stuff okay let's fight this one and then
we will be checking back I wonder oh
wait I can I can check the respawns in
the menu can I not I think I I can I
remember very
convenient that you can do
that okay I'll
check
[Music]
I again don't have
uh MP but it's okay I get turn
[Music]
bonus you know the other day I randomly
really randomly ran into do not
Senpai
[Music]
oh I was I was uh I was at a uh at a
dance
studio
and yeah I'm I'm sure and then
R I was like standing outside already um
about to leave and then I see I see Rie
coming out
also and I I like I don't notice
immediately because I'm like focused on
conversation with my assistant manager
and then I realized though but at that
point she already turned her back on me
and is walking away but I'm like whoa
whoa whoa whoa whoa and I can't like
scream out her name
like I can't like say it out loud so
that she will turn around so I'm like
kind of like just saying loudly hoping
to get her
attention but she didn't notice so I ran
after her I I I tapped her on her back
and then she turned around and she was
like oh and I'm like
Yay hi what are you doing
here really
random what I doing where do you see
the
here no
uh ah 89%
89% okay is there a recharge sometime
[Music]
somewhere
man
carrots okay let's fight 89% how much
does it go up with one of these
fights that's a magic of being Japan for
real I mean it I guess it wasn't
completely random like randomly in the
streets meeting another Holo member by a
studio I guess is more likely than
meeting them anywhere completely
[Music]
randomly you keep using defense to regen
MP and HP a I guess I could
not
Alana today's my birthday so thanks for
streaming oh umbrella cedy season 4 came
out today W it's cool I can watch
[Music]
that oh yeah I was thinking about world
championship yeah but there's several
games like T rock also I could play t
Rock to complete that
challenge but I've been looking at my
schedule yesterday I'm trying to plan
things this is so [\h__\h]
full you ah I don't know I really don't
know how much I can do actually of the
bingo
I I have so much to do I try to do some
things but I don't want to stress myself
about it especially since the reward
doesn't seem to live up to what we could
uh have gotten last
year yeah it's fine okay how much did it
go
up 2% up it went 2%
up let's go somewhere
else
maybe where could we
[Music]
go this is where the dragons are
right yeah I don't think you can get the
the million
price which was the number one price and
the best price to get cuz you can use it
so freely if you can't get that
[Music]
then wait does it go up even with cheap
enemies why can I not fight them
automatically they're weak
does this also go up
2%
hopefully I went up more than 2% didn't
it weird okay then I'll just do a few of
these small
ones uh or this big one too
po 40,000 did we wait ah ah didn't see
it I want ah I wanted to see it did we
fight this one before it doesn't I don't
feel like we
[Music]
did I clicked it away
no my magic stat is not higher than
their
health
[Music]
um summoning you and you and you and how
about you that's four
right oh yeah when I kill these small
mobs I should be getting 10% HP back
let's see if this happens I want to see
we have 99 oh yeah we do it's healing my
HP
yippee
nice I
[Music]
absolute defense
ice horn smash should we kill the small
one I don't know I want the damage on
the big
[Music]
one 3,500 would be a waste
otherwise ah he almost died from the
backlash almost though wait I can H the
ol is attacking okay when when is my
turn again and the dude is still alive I
can just um do the the double double
attack
[Music]
thing he's not an issue to me
now okay
um swing oh wait he's gone ah
no she automatically attacks when
there's only one enemy on the field I
was just going to look for the small one
but the small one was already
gone that stupid move it's hard to see
because like we're so crowded there and
where the small enemy would have been
we've been covering him so I wasn't sure
where he was I wanted to
see oh well no
problem
okay right it's basically back one more
fight and we can
go who do we fight
yeah they're lasting me for a while I
know Dragon
[Music]
de
chips do you want to fight do you want
to
fight let's fight
[Music]
if they're lightning and this one's
ground by Pokemon rules that should work
pretty well but fighting lightning with
lightning is not a good
idea okay I guess I'll just go with
fire oh it hit everybody H I didn't
expect it hitting everybody I guess it's
the the explosion on
impact
nice yeah let's
go and RAM
[Music]
okay let's go to where was it
again uh was it the Elian ples
again who are we looking for the Reno
the Reno
right we've been waiting for
this
heal uh
hope I'm taking the right
[Music]
way yeah it's past
here hello I've been waiting for you for
so
long but let
me change the pets that I have outside
um ah actually no the first one that
should be in the beginning of the battle
should be
[Music]
you and let's spawn some
others does
ground does he give them some kind of
like status I wonder cuz it would
probably cancel out the fire too if it
was something ground related but for now
I'm going to bring out whatever I
[Music]
want okay
ah you know the strongest ones they
cancel each other out the ice and the
fire oh
well should be fun
[Music]
regardless I don't know why I just use
the lightning attack because I like how
it hits every body I
guess
whoa one hit
[Music]
wonder you know
yesterday it has come to light that I am
a
baby why you ask
yesterday we had
bantos in the
studio and it was Curry and they had
like so many choices of
curry in terms of spice and also what
ingredients and they told me in English
that
there's the like sweet amaguchi Curry
but there's also the super sweet one and
I kind of got curious about it
I'm a GUI the sweet basic one is already
sweet enough for me like not it's not
sweet but it's just not spicy but I was
curious about the super sweet one so I
tried it uh and and then when I when I
got it on top of it there was a sticker
that said okama Ami it said for
children like spice level for children
basically I'm
baby that kind of made me feel
embarrassed I chose OK spice
level
and jenma looked at
me she I feel like she was looking down
on
me and she she got the maximum spice
level that they had available and she
still brought out her special spices she
brings her special spices
everywhere has like some Indonesian
spices she brings it everywhere to spice
up her food it's never spicy enough for
her as she just has it in her
bag okay we have the horn I know where
to go I know where to
[Music]
go
yes yeah it was Japanese Curry but uh
she has Indonesian spices with
her because I guess that's where the
best
spices or like spice um spices to go are
[Music]
accessible ah let me pass through okay I
got your thing was quite a bother to
get hope you're
happy are you
happy I did this for you
[Music]
Nissa su su sorry succession
ceremony fore
[Music]
okay I was going to say just make her
into a pet this is basically
that okay we're not dressing her up oh
man' missed opportunity
[Music]
okay wait so um at
the at behind the castle they said but
um I didn't see a waterfall where we
went last
time Redbeard layers are
closest
okay if you say
so you can buy the armor while you're in
the
capital so
this I'll try to find
it wait is it really the closest this
already seems like annoying to get out
of
uh it's
round did I
go the wrong way
[Music]
what
ah I don't [\h__\h]
care I'll just go from
here once
I no I'm not playing for OBS what do you
mean
I'm just going to go this
way whatever works for
me this works for
[Music]
me and we've changed go go go go go
go let's go to the capital and buy the
armor
[Music]
I want to bring out my vacuum and suck
these
trees I'm sure there's gold bars in
there or a ghost
[Music]
something okay me it
SAS is this the one this looks like the
one
ah Advanced M AR o ah
[Music]
yeah I think I said before oh let's buy
this another
time this isn't even better than my
Tonio armor what the [\h__\h] why' you make
me buy
this what
a Senai of yours has been doing that for
years
who 25 speed yeah but minus two other
things so
[Music]
I'm a few of them yeah I can
imagine
what oh oh the gamer the gameer plays
for OBS and you guys always like [\h__\h] on
me
[Music]
like oh how the tables
turn I mean I don't even do it that
often I did it like my like three times
or so in my whole whole life in my whole
[Music]
life the person stand resistance is
better speed is just eating St
booster uh so I should not wear it right
I don't think so
either she's not known for being good at
games she's known for banging her head
against games for 121
[Music]
St is that something she found out about
recently
oh like that she talked out about
recently no I don't think you can
upgrade the
armor or can
[Music]
you she's been playing with a handicap
all the time I think I do remember when
I off collab with
her I think we did play through
OBS
but to me at the time I think it seemed
like it made sense because
maybe lack of space on the screen maybe
I don't
know I didn't assume that she was
playing everything for
[Music]
OBS told her when day were practicing
for if she was using a pass
through I can upgrade my but have never
bothered upgrading it
[Music]
uhhuh I wasted my
money
damn okay where's this Rocky stuff she's
at behind but it's not where the graves
are right is it over here on the right
side
[Music]
okay there's not that much
latency have you guys tried playing for
OBS like you don't stream most of you
guys so why we wouldn't even have a
reason to test it
out ah I need my water pad huh
is it here behind the waterfall let's
get my water
pad I tried it's not good it's no it's
like I don't see a difference I really
don't see a
difference can I dismiss him from him
here
no there's no difference
damn she's
okay Raven game maybe
[Music]
but I think you would get used to it
like you would adjust to
[Music]
it automatically
and she's going to get me that sword or
what thank you
ancestors let's go she's back to normal
so when she dies
oh I awakened my own sword
[Music]
here and I have it already right
you are welcome but I feel like if I can
dress up to get through the capital you
could have done that too and you could
have gone here alone
no h
wait is this the last
slot is this what I need to fill up my
last
slot yeah then there would be no pberry
involved that would be sad
and then I wouldn't even know about this
whole thing okay let's see is it here no
it's not is it for here oh what does it
do speed
up increase agility by 10% plus 30
Cool Fire magic
circles magic resistance
8% agility 5% plus 7 oh we could replace
this and have a better agility thing or
ah wait right now we have the
purification necklace I don't think we
need that on
there
[Music]
speed y yipp okay so
wait yes let's put our own sword in
there let's steal their powers for
ourselves what do I I guess I have to
put on the sword
this one ah the f
[Music]
ah the one isn't that the one we found
at the dragon's
place in two weeks you get to see me on
stage
yipp exciting let's go
there we
[Music]
go but AR like abusing her family's
power wait isn't this
unethical excaliber
M charging our
sword like a freaking power
[Music]
bank wow it looks
cool when was this girl
ethical not of her not part of her top
five worst crimes
damn Pineberry look at your reputation
here she has a really bad reputation in
the chat damn one of the fre great
swords of ailan Legend it can summon an
ancient
lightning I can increasing the power of
lightning I can summon the dragon
[Music]
that's
crazy imagine if the Dragon Lady knew
this can we tell
her that I can summon the big ass
ancient
dragon can we tell her are we going to
tell her
whoa what the
[\h__\h]
damn I
mean if if such a small indie game
series which spring R is able to summon
this
Dragon this sick ass Dragon at their
will then I I can honestly not find any
way to excuse HBO anymore with like
slacking on Dragon
animation HBO you got no
excuses you got no excuses
anymore look at this
boy you could have this no but their
dragons look great and um there have
been a lot of dragons obviously but
there could be even more
even more Dragon
action the sword's magic spreads in the
sky and summons an ancient Lightning
Dragon to summoned ancient lightning
dragons creates lightning bolts at a
random Point around a specified location
damn
CH I am concerned um is it wait is it in
here then no no it couldn't be yeah I
get it I get it h okay we did the side
quest let's go back to the main quest
the main quest tells me to find veran
location hand death squ L okay but I go
home first uh use my training
points so what should I be using this
the sword now rather than the St wait no
you guys said I can turn the sort into a
staff
right oh yeah oh yeah is it do I have
the
recipe where would it be
[Music]
wait how do I do on a a weapon up
okay I okay I have it oh evolve
no
ah so I nourish it I guess
[Music]
okay I need to nourish it then okay
sorry I haven't done this in a while
[Music]
um sure let's just use all of
them damn I don't even have that many
materials
anymore haven't been grinding so much I
guess can I use one of these big
ones I don't know if they're that
useful the frozen heart this one's big I
don't know is that really precious
should I keep
it anent should we just throw in no I
need it to evolve
it lava eye brings a good amount
[Music]
M I don't have that much
stuff I'll just use up all this oh
that's good I can get those I can get
those I can Farm
them yeah that's
fine the glittering eyes easy
okay evolving time I even know the sword
looks so cool we'll make it into a
staff ooh it better be much stronger or
else the sword magic sword it still says
sword even though it's a staff
now cool cool cool cool
cool wait we
can you can turn it back into a sword if
you do the whole thing
again like it switches back and
[Music]
forth okay seems like
it
[Music]
ah I'll look at the stats in a
moment want to
[Music]
train this
one and this
one and
[Music]
maybe why not this one oh wait we can do
we can do five wow we have full oh oh
damn uh we did a lot huh I didn't do it
in the
[Music]
beginning let's just do another one of
these then chances of getting that one
will be very high and then we get like
the the level three training
possibly yeah
yeah you will get more stats from the
bonus if I do it one by one what oh
well it's
okay oh
[Music]
okay
hi twil twirl twirl swirl swirl
swirl swirl
[Music]
clockwise
nice I am making something cool and one
more I'm a witch I am the perfect witch
yippee
dle
dle he
he
amazing o we're like on the same
level
okay and um yeah I want to look at staff
so we had this one before I want to see
like oh no we had this one before see
the difference plus
431 a little bit like strength that's
fine but also agility plus 100 oh that
that's very
good plus
441 that is
[Music]
incredible
nice should we change outfit one more
[Music]
time yeah I've been
wearing that one let's where this
one cute adult version of the black
outfit
okay do I need to craft anything else
yeah we we're probably
[Music]
fine I think it was said to go to the
Des Squad
layer was worth robbing a family
Monument yeah
of
course never doubt
pberry I could have slept
though to fill up my
mp oh
well uh wait
so is he somewhere in
[Music]
here this it says
hint here
[Music]
where where where would he
be
oh why do we need to find him when he's
right there I didn't expect him to be
there oh is this uh no return point you
cannot Jo journey to other regions while
infiltrating Pop's Castle but you may
give up at any time and return to home
after giving up if you wish to Contin
continue infiltrating the system from
the same point you may do so by talking
to verion oh okay I think we're strong
enough healing items maybe we're not
like super stocked but we're going to be
fine right let's go to war would you
would you like to go to war hell
yeah of course
glory to
wberry attack KY going to war once again
ah it's almost nostalgic isn't it us
together oh
man my jaw is really locked
[Music]
or bir Squad I would like to rename the
death squad
please rebirth Squad
VI death squad actually is weird Long
Live should be rebirth
[Music]
Squad okay I only have Crums left and I
love CR potato chip CRS
hello Justice
[Music]
nor potato chips which is probably good
that that's over sorry for the snacking
potato chips are the end of
me but a wellfed Wawa who has also gone
to an idol meeting will last longer
yeah I can't find a war on an empty
stomach right
[Music]
yeah I'll be first anyway
guys
[Music]
everybody
war with the w
Justice will be
served this is like Game of Thrones the
night the night of all
nights winter is
coming it's just going to be super
underwhelming but we see more than game
of FRS
again HBO what are you
doing nice
Golem
oh they have some big ass Golems too
don't worry
[Music]
they don't look that weak to
me
enemies but we're
stronger k
[Music]
k great weapon
she's so small in the big golem
oh she's like in the
robot it is very exposed
they should have put oh wait it's not
exposed
bamboozle she has aim Hearts
defense I was going to roast them on the
exposed cockpit
too but
they they thought about
it good night thanks for watching
oh
what
what wait she's sitting the same way she
sits on the house she's just
chilling flip flopping her
legs cute
[Music]
this is
silly
Justice wait the bird
he's doing all the
work you only knew
no no you're the you're the girlfriend
not the friend
we're slowly revealing it this is a slow
reveal
huh I am your father Justice sh he's
still
not
Cliffhanger still not going to say it
but we got so close to
it let me fill my water cup
okay let's go guys let's go let's
[\h__\h] go let's [\h__\h] go
oh what an
entrance oh Ice Ice Baby
[Music]
Luna
Lun no what
happened a friend
[Music]
to Rob
foree fore
forch
[Music]
for she sounds like Aqua when she
speaks and
seriously
[Music]
nowhere
for that sounds like
[Music]
her you saw him
blink
[Music]
for oh
no let's find the p a luno
no she sounds so
sad this girl to like I I wonder maybe
in
the maybe in the spin-off the Runa
spin-off maybe you get to see more of
her I wonder and which spring too
we got this to find something in the
cells maybe
not
no yeah cuz I'm curious about her I want
to see more of
her Po's Castle Lobby the floor is on
the wall
why you know what I
mean ceiling
carpet where else would you put a floor
floor on the wall why
ceiling FL on the
ceiling
why hey what's up guys let me bring out
a
pet what he's a
pet I have to summon him in the
fight I can't summon the pets now
they're not even taking up all the spots
it's just two of them oh
well wa I just want to look around sorry
oh I'm low on on P oh is that
why oh I am yeah really
low ah but they're weak no
problem
who nice one hit
kill um give me MP please how much
warar Golem
Essence how many can we get all of them
what a
deal e my new power that I stole from
the grave of one of my best friends from
her
family the power that I'm not supposed
to inherit but I don't give a [\h__\h] it's
mine
now I'm a
grave uh what what do we call it like we
talked about this just yesterday or so
not yesterday didn't stream yesterday
but you know what I mean a grave robber
yeah I'm a grave robber
yippe but I think I realized well I
didn't realize on that day when we
talked about it cuz I I think I was more
like imagining that grave Robert are
looking for Treasures or so that people
put in there with their beloved ones
like gold necklaces or whatever but I
was thinking like that's not really that
doesn't seem like a very lucrative
business but I realized are they looking
for
um like are they looking to open organs
or to get or but wouldn't the organs be
dead wait maybe that's not it maybe
that's not it or wait can you is it
still does it still make sense to
harvest organs from someone who's been
dead for a
while you got to do it early
huh no okay but if you do I don't know
it it's usually not that early okay okay
I thought that was maybe one reason why
they might do it but yeah now that I was
like saying it out loud it made no sense
to me either
H so is it really just for
Treasures like golden necklaces and [\h__\h]
I don't know doesn't seem very
lucrative people used to be bird of Val
yeah I guess in the past it was more
more stuff in
there anyway
[Music]
Isa oh God don't you think she'll like
look at our staff and be
like what's this lightning power you
have on your staff my friend
quick hide hide your staff
Byberry we're not fighting for victory
here we're fighting for
justice wait she says that but wasn't
that a side quest she is this a a voice
line that she normally wouldn't have if
you don't do the side
quest
maybe yeah that would be
nice wow
oh I can see under the stairs it's
great haven't tried not doing her side
quest yeah so you don't know
huh both players you played it twice oh
a lot of you guys played the game
already is that exe oh they they are
very familiar looking executors
ah let's go
boys
Alfredo what are you doing
here who the [\h__\h] is he that little
spaghetti
man I'm worried about him
it's dangerous to go alone here take
this big pie oh my God thank you
actually but his mom it looks really
good and I do need healing items I
think you don't want to be a war anymore
what you want to be a pie maker
ah wow he loves me I'm like his
God
yippee can I summon a pet
now no it wasn't even the MP was just
that I have these two guys out
there the two girls Olia and whatever
the name of the other one was
I'm sure we were can we I'm sure we can
return her to her normal state right oh
and Kate Olia and Kate not
Ollie although I don't want to return I
want to see Kate die she's not really
nice she's never been nice
[Music]
also I don't think Kate really needs
saing she still very much uh knows what
she's doing and who she is and all that
while Livia is
lost
sadly okay wait even the even the side
mobs are relatively
strong what a nice surprise
[Music]
oh it doesn't count the guys right
now I thought it would because they are
in the pet menu what the
hell
[Music]
okay oh look at my
Army hey let's
go six p that's
baby oh I have been cursed you've been
cursed you thinker
all ouchy
ouchy okay one down how about this one
another one
down let's use aim heart's
[Music]
defense um take some MP back just a
little bit is
[Music]
fine yeah let's do some
fire fire fire light of Fire
another one fights the dust Warlords
blade how much damage does that
do 2,600 n a little bit disappointing
but our dragon can finish
him 2,800 our little dragon slam does
More Than This Knight's big ass sword
should be
embarrassed even your son does more
damage
nice oh yeah Kate's already down
wow I can't do Arrow right
okay keep on Switching Fire and
Ice okay nice warm up
nice warm
up you don't want to give her credit but
she died after
you in this fight
okay Chio
Chan
n she's
revolting is that the
word over rebelling I guess oh the music
wait this soundtrack remix is different
first I like
it you
all she had to do was take off her
blindfold oh it slowed
down sounds good
[Music]
is she nice to us
too no you look
[Music]
sick I likeing
was
[Music]
she and Dad you did
okay she stands so elegantly she can't
be feeling too bad can
[Music]
she look at my cat in the bag a
watching so many cat videos on Instagram
and stuff man
[Music]
car what cat did you m
type
car I love cars
[Music]
the track is really nice
but it it Loops barely
your lord and savior lightning M Queen I
thought your lord and savior was
[Music]
yeah yeah stop your loveby Dy F
stop I ha
flashing get a
room get a
room yeah he he wants he doesn't want to
see this l
[Music]
yes we
will okay don't die on us liia
[Music]
n okay what what is he saying what is
this the dog C was holding fell to the
ground can I not pick it
up we should pick it
up
[Music]
h ah it's that cute oh wait it's it's
my
okay uh let's heal
uh makes me nervous go back you can
reenter the room for a cut scene wait
why did I not what go back
Ah that's you know what's going to
happen so you're telling me go
[Music]
back
foree spee fore
for being a doll is the only way you get
acknowledgement I don't know about
that so sick you're so dope you're
amazing but you just you're just really
rude can you just be nicer
rude girl this is your
problem
[Music]
damn
wow this is her father right damn She's
So
Mean Poor Dad
[Music]
what they're just
friends
what not that old he loves old to
me
friends
okay whoa I like this like weird wo like
we're going we're walking up a
mountain optical
[Music]
illusion what did I eat let's eat
these okay that's
fine let's
go it's the nose I know the no has
nothing to do with age but it's the nose
and the facial
hair she's so cute
[Music]
foreign
spee
fore yeah
[Music]
okay yeah
yeah
fore no
only 44,000 oh she has no chance she
stands no
chance by Barry with her basic voice
land say she always
says I'm going to learn some new magic
Yi cute okay this is enough this is
enough we don't want to Overkill her a
poor girl
don't fight with your sister adopted
sister
yeah I don't want to hurt her
[Music]
either don't worry just a few punches
and she'll
regain some brain regain brain
yes should be easy she's almost dead
yeah no
problem
attack yeah easy easy easy easy slap
some sense into
her her attacks are really
cool the scy scy
attacks
nice and probably last deck
a
almost damn
it okay my pet will do the thing that I
couldn't
do there's a whole life sum of voice
pack is that the one you tried really
hard in
um is it just announced but not
downloadable yet I don't know if it was
the one it might have
been there's just so many right now
oh is it dropping in a few hours okay
please get it I think at least I didn't
do badly in
[Music]
it
oh Mommy not Mommy
actually adopted Mommy
that will bring her
back she's so deep in it but that will
bring her
[Music]
back come on mle do it look at
her look at your mommy
your name literally in Japanese means
look look
[Music]
stop stop letting them abuse you come
back to us
[Music]
she learned her first
word literally cuz she doesn't say
anything
[Music]
else oh no oh this is
no
[Music]
for
Fore annae
really I feel like she's going to snap
back any moment and try to kill us again
scared don't get too
close
really I don't trust her I don't
believe but what if she still will
attack us and that will give us the big
[Music]
shock nah it's probably
fine took them long
enough will M take care of them actually
might be immediate Redemption Arc
[Music]
okay but then I lose my
pet L is
back Luna she's so cool I love
her wow easy
RPG
party you need to go back to normal so
you can be like super cute witches
together with Luna and
pberry and the other two small ones that
I forgot the name of
[Music]
ir and and what's the the the smallest
one wow you remember that
[Music]
thanks I hope she
doesn't
become get the taste for executing
people
again really oh my
God she's mentally a Babu yeah do their
mental thing not does it not does it not
grow when they're in that
state maybe we should use her as a test
subject for science to test that out oh
no am I the Banny are we the bannies
[Music]
thanks
girl oh a friend who triumphed over
grief it's you and me now oh I got a
steam
achievement
[Music]
yay does this game have a post game I
would think maybe a little bit he's
right there guys he's all alone
me and my RPG party look at him wow
cute let's go I what the [\h__\h] there's no
healing points
anywhere which is fine but like weird
normally RPG games have healing spots
before the boss so you're doing
something wrong
okay let's go wait is this really the
last like
fight I could uh use these
things now that we're at the end of the
game oh I with stood a small amount of
dark
magic what does it do to me
increase Max HP yeah let's do
this strength agility
sure save it for second
game don't say that as if it's a thing
that I can actually
do wamp Leaf sure wamp
WP special increase all right Max MP
sure
strength don't think we need it but
sure okay save it for Luna what what
wait you guys make me really
doubt don't say that it sounds like I
really should but I should it's okay is
there okay let's
go
epic yeah
I feel like there's there's going to be
something else right like a second boss
fight I don't know should
be can't be that
[Music]
simple dad reveal
Justice
dump let's go
what why are you trying to stop him from
saying that
bro maybe because he wants to reveal it
himself guess we'll talk about it
afterwards
oh oh he's going to say it while he's
being attacked and then they're going to
be like whoa and break the barrier on
their
own n yeah see he's like shocked what
what what do you
mean no well I mean you can't expect him
to focus after such a reveal should have
told him earlier when you were on the
the train tracks
sh I am your father
Justice you surprised
[Music]
is BL here he died if anything he died
as here
[Music]
here yeah he's like on the side he's
complimenting his beautiful blonde hair
oh nice of him I like the
positivity yeah bleaching it more would
have turned it white exactly
they don't get
[Music]
it hug hug it out
maybe
fore
why
Justice why
really
why I'm missing
something Y in front of the boss yeah he
could attack us right now isn't that why
he was revealing it like to interrupt
this like barrier now he's not making
use
[Music]
oh well
thanks are you with us
Justice
oh what a service
[Music]
let's
go no the real main protagonist and the
real
danger
Jo he needs to kill black Joe he just he
just doesn't want to say it because then
he could just fly away he he's he's
pretending it's all about pie Berry but
in reality it's about black
Joe oh nice
trick ah
cool they look like they're from World
of
Warcraft ah should I have put on my dark
magic thingy on my accessories
[Music]
explain yourself
then tell me
then battle
formation oh they all have question mark
question mark but it shouldn't be too
much all right let's let's use a shield
Stone why
not so you telling me I can still bring
four pets in oh
yippe that is
big tell me if I should like be
summoning something else if something's
better than the ones that I keep on
always
summoning I'll bring the mask though
should be good
good let's go
attack the death is near of the pop Pope
will die Pope Must
Die
go it 1,600 Luna
really I guess she's got to she's got to
still be weak because in the which
spring R 2 game you know obviously if
she's overpowered makes no sense she
needs to start at a lower level so she's
got to be lower level now you know what
I mean cuz it continues with her and
then although that's not a continuation
though wait it makes no sense it's it
starts it starts from the beginning of
this game
probably yeah she seems so op like when
she takes care of all the Warriors out
there with her eyes cuz she wasn't that
op after
all gotta go byebye thanks for
coming it's okay guys as when I get my
aim hard defense there we
go everything will be
D and my pets are going to come up with
stronger attacks soon as
[Music]
well oh it's Pope time it's pop time
oh no he has the same
[\h__\h] ah okay then let's attack the the
side
mobs so what I was doing
anyway
okay I'm guessing it's like the same
thing that if we attack him we
get damage back so I'll be
[Music]
careful all right one down one minion is
down
nice also
actually all the
pets they don't have HP so you don't
even have to be care careful of like uh
getting hit back if you attack with the
pets right H but that doesn't make sense
anyway if he doesn't get any damage from
it so
[Music]
true though yeah very true oh what is
that what the [\h__\h] you're going to drop
that on us now
or
uh-oh oh Luna's doing something cool oh
she ah he did get some uh
damage okay okay but I think it's it's
not too much though should be
more ah damn it this would all be
stronger if you didn't have the AIM
heart defense
on oh
well okay my AMR defense is back but I'm
kind of scared of that
[\h__\h] what's this do again uh this is
this is going to happen anyway right
so we do get the crit
now which is
nice let's do it a r
Arrow critical what only oh yeah cuz he
still has he still has a
barrier oh well nothing that can be
done how hard is it going to
it wait that's not the that's not the
thing
unless what is
that can we use the big dragon oh yeah I
want to how how how though wait I need
to look into that oh wait I need to
move does this hit
you yes yes
yes he's dead
anyway let's go Justice got the last hit
I said I was going to be the
one
no okay stage
two phase
[Music]
two too easy give me
more Sal
[Music]
oh he calls him
father
jce don't tell me you're like brothers
or something like that nah [\h__\h] you
is's dangling that in front of us to
keep his dad
[Music]
alive he did find out the way because I
mean
Kate I guess like it worked on her kind
of I don't know
he's definitely been testing actively
his test subjects he he's been
actively learning a lot from it he's
been doing
science he's
cooking it's not just like blindly
crowno right I know it's not just
blindly
like transforming people and not doing
anything with the knowledge
would you guys look at Luna's face over
there why is she so delighted
[Music]
see p is
more like feeling the atmosphere reading
the air
[Music]
but she still
laughing no
Luna cut the camera angle
[Music]
foree
for oh no
[Music]
a crown I don't know just throwing
something out there black Jo is it black
Jo is it black
[Music]
Jo must be black Joe because he's black
unlike the other
birds no no way though no way right
so n no it's not BL that's ridiculous we
already saw his real form
too n that's [\h__\h] poy
jum what a weird
logic oh it's
Crown he silences the pope before he can
tell us it's crown
[Music]
oh
no so the
crown k
as always there's
problems just like in the Medieval ages
between the crown and the
pop they hate each other
spee
[Music]
speee fore
okay
H oh fighting scene oh let's
go ah dodge dodge dodge dodge oh nice
Luna oh oh he's using his like Darkness
oh
[\h__\h] oh my dragon wait a second
[Music]
what that
Dragon was that main story to get that
Dragon wait which dragon is
that D
oh killed witches let's go
justice
justice nice narration byber
do it do
[Applause]
it just do
it foolish humans and
witches Jude all these real name
reveals for
[Music]
so what pop is helping us right now what
the
[\h__\h]
oh right in the
pelvis we're not quite more into the
abdomen close enough
yapping was a strat oh he became the
Dark
Knight oh really wait
really what I wanted another fight St a
real
one
fore
foree
for
[Music]
justice no I just thought this line was
funny do you know how long I cover up to
of the loss of my father with r like I
don't know somehow it's funny to
[Music]
me does he have a different name too
Justice
spee
fore
foree
[Music]
fore foree
noed
no no you can't give him more warmth if
you if you you become a couple not best
friends
forever Justice
[Music]
foree
sweet nice let's go W let's go let's go
the final Dragon it look so sick let's
go final fight
y y oh it looks
nice Lau
Dragon I shall name it Lapu
Dragon
what that's J but I thought it was crown
[Music]
what the garden animal I thought the the
garden animals were all nice so is there
like evil
[Music]
ones wait let me spray out
flum random flum moment
the the atmosphere of the final battle
and I'm like oh wait let me spin up some
FL more water too spit at him you think
my flum can damage him maybe he'll get
some
debuff
fore
foree fore spee
[Music]
what completely vanag after the spring
War he's been hiding his magic with
golden armor all this time to trick the
spring hold armor I mean
Crown Crown's armor So within that
that's why they called him J it's the
same thing right crowd is Crown is um
like just like a compact version of this
Dragon was destroyed by me mortal in a
tiny D I need to that shell to continue
deceiving the spring
[Music]
ah the spring as
in a
mood to accomplish that what was
possible for your kind to save the world
from dark magic save that makes no sense
to me save the world from dark magic
when
you're yeah that M Spring right so adamu
doesn't know that his
Guardian animal is going crazy and
wreaking
havoc does he
[Music]
know okay but that sounds like a good
goal right so
far wait I mean I mean makes sense
though like if you were to for the cause
for for for the sake of the whole world
if you want to rid it of dark magic and
your sacrifice ing yourself your own
body and suck it all up then of course
you're going to turn into something evil
looking with all the dark magic in your
body so I mean I could believe
that trust me
bro I I I might believe him
I like his attempt of gaslighting us
then mhm is that what laas darkness is
doing is she gas sliding
us isn't her goal world
domination and she says she loves Earth
but
like she's stocking up all the dark
magic from the world look she's purple
just like this
guy and maybe she's also just
gaslighting us that she's sucking up the
dark magic and then yeah she's just
trying to help us but I mean look at her
she has horns just like her just like
this [\h__\h]
Dragon fake ass
horns and you know you know how how how
Crown's armor like was like keeping this
all together maybe her her horns the
thick horns they're about to explode and
and those those long sleeves all of that
is just it's just trying to
hide it's just trying to hide and
contain all that power to continue
deceiving
us I might be cooking with this
one same thing Jud and darkness less
Darkness same
thing you guys just wait there's going
to be a big reveal about L this Darkness
one
day and I I I will be the one saying I
Told You So I've tried to warn the world
but everybody just believed her when she
said she loves Earth ass everybody
everybody believed
her and just went with it I tried to
warn
you the prophecy
[Music]
I like his
tats look at his
arms nice
TS looks
cool yeah
[Music]
lention will start with
left n you're not twisting this to say
nah stop you're not twisting this to say
that Pope was
good nah he I guess he was just he had
his own evil intentions but in order to
be the number one evil guy he had to get
rid of the Dragon so the executors were
in a way for the Witch Hunt but also
more than that for now to also get rid
of the Dragon guy right if if the pope
was good him I feel like that would have
like he would have said different things
when we just met him like why would he
go against us because he would only go
against us if his end goal was to be the
number one top evil guy but first he has
to you know kill his boss
so he's not good yeah definitely not
he wanted to use her to to kill
him mm
[Music]
I like this I like this plot twist
because I feel like it's more common to
have an evil guy turn out to be a good
guy or Obviously good guys turning out
to be evil guys but I don't think I have
played many games or any games where
the evil
one is just he's definitely evil but
he's just doing evil things to in the
end kill the real evil like they're
working against each other
actually I feel like normally the evil
ones work together but these
ones they're like trying to overthrow
each
other that's interesting
they've got their own
problems
[Music]
yeah last fight okay let me get agility
this seems to be really the last fight
but maybe maybe maybe another form of
him but at least it's The Last Enemy I
think all right bring out the boys we
don't have the dad anymore oh
no bring out the Dragons Dragon de
dragon and my cat which the whole time I
think this is also a
dragon keep on thinking it's a dragon
all right uh
yeah it's dark magic right I can use
whatever but let's start with
this uh four three three
four 40
40,000 no 48,000 per minion wo
let's
go not
bad yeah he's
strong let's go boosting ice damage yeah
the good good cat good
cat the minions are not weak they're not
weak at all
it's
okay I have my defense and my pets have
no
HP we're good but I'll
heal I'll
heal now we can use up all my healing
items and not feel bad about it
sure you
sure ice horn
smash nice maybe I should focus on
[Music]
one
ram dark oh yeah Alter Ego it says Alter
Ego they look like Crown don't
they oh yeah but it is ground I forgot I
forgot I God it was Crown like this
whole thing is Crown everything's Crown
I'm
Crown I had the big dragon
attack yeah uh let me check how to
activate that when it's my
turn is it in the magic
slabs it's not tar right
what's ah wait it's the ancient
Lightning Dragon ah it's grayed out so I
didn't see it uhuh Tamar was pretty weak
if I remember correctly so I'm not going
to use him um four turns after combat
starts
okay maybe I wonder if you can use it in
combination after using aru's arrow and
then going for the ancient Lightning
Dragon should work work
right okay some minions will be down
soon counter baby
nice tomaro's AOE doesn't he I don't
remember so well how good it was I just
don't think it was very
good nice one is down I hope he doesn't
re uh recast his minions so don't think
we've had that before in a battle
so I hope he doesn't learn and realize
that he should be doing that for sure he
can I feel like he's capable of doing
it strategic crit
H well first of
all ah I guess this is the third
turn so we don't have ancient Lightning
Dragon yet I can't combine it okay no
problem no
problem wonder if I should be scared
right now
should I be scared cuz now I don't have
my defense
anymore but can't be
helped okay another Minion
[Music]
down actually I could have ah maybe no I
don't think my physical attack would
have been strong enough wait ah
ah okay I killed I killed the minion and
did some damage on the dragon too
Blue Moon once in a blue moon Luna
decides to hopefully do some good damage
let's see oh I that's several ones let's
go how much
oh oh it hit the other one too I think
that was like 4,000 time three right oh
my
God
[Music]
okay that hit
nothing what the hell cat I'm
disappointed in you
uh
okay only the big dragon left I hope he
doesn't spawn more
[Music]
Minions that barely hit us because we're
all too small your aim was too high my
friend way too
high okay
what's this again only ah that
drastically decreases the enem is
able agility for the
enemy I want to use this too should
I does this take up a
turn it doesn't
[Music]
let's go how much damage does this
do
28,000 but damn how much [\h__\h] HP does
he have we did 28,000 damage and his HP
is still so high
wow okay everybody's going for the same
now because we only have one
enemy 10,000 not bad bro not bad
okay I'll uh he's currently
Frozen I guess I could hit him with the
six pillar ice Circle cuz um the AOE
field will hit only the dragon be
[Music]
good oh yeah 11,000 is fine and I don't
get rid of the The Ice debuff that he
already has
good keep him keep him on ice keep him
fresh
yeah yeah yeah oh let's go let's go
let's
go how much was that in total no idea
why he's past
[Music]
50% oh nice wa look at him go my owl
dragon a bro he's never getting a
turn he's never getting a turn he's so
[\h__\h] he's on ice and he has the the
Duro field man oh and we got the
lightning bolt now should I keep it for
next turn cuz next turn I have
crit maybe I'll keep
it I'll keep it and I'll I'll heal a
little bit in case he wakes up
[Music]
soon
mhm another
11k that's 18K wow
[Music]
ow yeah he's definitely going down with
my with my crit Arrow I
think oh
yeah oh I got my bell armor H good
morning what are you going to
do ah easy no
problem okay okay
okay oh I get so many turns bro also cuz
my party is just so big it's four pets
and two like
friends damn okay I wonder if this is it
I wonder if not then my pets are going
to probably end
them 20K it wasn't it but
wow
nice he doesn't get a turn for a while
oh he's almost de he's almost dead he's
almost
dead oh the protagonist of the next game
kills the the boss of the first
game how
poetic how beautifully poetic oh wait
that sounds like it's not
over oh it doesn't sound like it's
over okay
okay the music also doesn't
sound like it's
over why you just saw he's saying he's
respawning and I can fight him
[Music]
again okay yeah we got to go to the
spring
yeah hey are you going to leave me
behind oh is a spring coming to me oh
what's happening
um oh oh oh that was fast what the [\h__\h]
we're going to leave Justice behind
aren't we or Justice and Luna
together so that I can go to the
[Music]
spring and maybe the others are also
coming back to
help
no he revived so fast
uh he's going to he's going to he's
going to do it black Joe right no shut
up BL how about you transform for
once he's like oh guess I'll
die he literally said guess I'll
die he tried oh
while
oh the adults is there adults in this
room besides
me oh nice
so
oh cuz he needs the spring to be intact
for his power now he moves away so we go
we go go go
for unless
[Music]
spee
foree
fore it's below
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah open up
FBI yeah there we
[Music]
go I'm losing another
companion did she say that
twice she said that
Japanese
damn
ah I'm I think I'm glad it's that wasn't
the end the end because
um while the fight was pretty good uh it
needs a bit more oomph this is giving us
the
oomph apocalypse
[Music]
baby
[Laughter]
[Music]
for good morning hello welcome to the
Stream
P more died cuz Wawa wanted to see the
action
yeah very
possible he still didn't learn about his
aim wow
[Music]
what okay let's go good thing you bought
the
armor what
run run run run run run oh no oh
no
what that's so Random I
mean they're doing the RPG thing with
all my friends coming to help me one
after another and then leaving me one
after
[Music]
another okay stop talking do it do it do
it I need to skip the dialogue so that
they do it
faster otherwise they'll die
[Music]
okay okay just do it do it do it do it
you'll die
otherwise he skip dialog to save
them okay this one's not
skippable don't say things like that
kind of raising a flag of
death shut up
okay let's
go skip skip to the end we finally
reached the final spring are you sure
time to gather the last blessing and
revive the temple
Lords the temple Lords not the river
Lords let's
go be careful of the stones falling
please do I need healing I I didn't
check
I'm not going to fight him right I'm
going to get his power and then fight
the dragon again or
[Music]
so possibly well that was easy
thanks that really was
easy oh
[Music]
no see now I'm alone I saw this
coming
oh oh romantic
ah let Joe carry us out of
here
left bro
no we're kicking him
out yeah I need to get to this alone now
you know how every every one of the
companions left us first your dad then
Luna now it's got to be you
oh
romantic okay wow wow what a man
he wants to break the friend zone he
wants to break the friend
zone wow
This is
Love are they goingon to are they going
to
kiss kiss kiss kiss
no you can
join you can join
Joey yeah okay oh my God don't talk here
do you see what just dropped above your
heads
bro have some sense of
urgency Mama Mia
ah we will one way or
[Music]
another mother has been
ditched for a [\h__\h] bird and for my
future husband I
guess
oh sorry Mom I wasn't going to ditch you
of course
[Laughter]
not
[Music]
mommy Lucio it does sound a bit like
Lucio doesn't it what the [\h__\h] I just
realize that
no you finally with your corrupted
ruthless unethical heart you finally did
it and made someone fall in love with
you I never thought this would happen
because you are just like insane little
girl oh that's not what she meant
[Music]
I thought you were a lost
cause
Lucia I thought you would never continue
our Legacy and give me a grandchild
[Music]
yeah the bloodline all
dragons
wow the dragon let's go
[Music]
watch out for vegar
he's like five times your size but
you're still not going to see him coming
for some
[Music]
reason nah Tamar is one of the good boys
W let's go
oh he Dragon tackled him oh oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] I like how he he's holding his head
down that's pretty cool Power stance
asserting
dominance don't ship the dragons no no I
only it for a moment don't
worry who
the wait is that my dad what
the looks like
me
H we never saw him before
[Music]
good night Tamar I say you got like put
back into a ball like Pokemon oh he also
looks like me
[Music]
but come on guys
that's not how I imagined aim heart to
look like and that's also not how I
imagined dur to look
like they were both supposed to like
amard was supposed to look like a
paladin D was supposed to look like a a
a super strong ass Palin dwarf
thanks for the membership
[Music]
nice it
worked I'm an adult hello pay
[Music]
attention I
grew oh
maybe this is more
oh have you noticed something there's
dragons there's white-haired
people who all look so similar you might
think they're related and they're the
powerful
ones don't they all look
related and they they have control over
dragons
h h
who which one of these is my
[Music]
daddy where's your
house oh we just destroyed
it have been our house
[Music]
yeah he seems to be totally overpowered
you were just a guardian animal they're
Gods bro
[Music]
oh Mommy let's
go yeah I like her voice
too
for maybe you were the test subject all
along no okay
you have a point
[Music]
dude
fore
[Music]
foree
spee
[Music]
fore fore
this is like an intervention
I can quit dark magic whenever I want
he said
it what he said
it oh my
God
[Music]
for he sounds like he's snoring
Byberry
[Music]
really
oh became strish huh
[Music]
aren't those examples that we
experienced the the dad
the power of family and friendship and
love is enough to purify everybody from
dark
[Music]
magic
for that's definitely that must have
been that that was the deaths
hinting that they love H
life that's just them putting a ref
reference to H in there right right
right reference to takik
Froman
[Music]
confirmed
for eating a milk away
[Music]
humans killed in the war were brought
back to life by my mother's Powers wow
wow humans began to make wishes to the
gities
again for real do they even learn a
lesson though if everything's back as
normal as if nothing
happened hm
yeah and what about the pope though you
didn't revive the pope
right did they revive the
[Music]
pope because if they
didn't then that's certainly not like it
was before there's a a role missing the
role of the
[Music]
Pope he died during the war
yeah pie of course we had
pie we had so much
[Music]
pie they could get a new pub or just no
pub at
all just got a
[Music]
king is more fun and interesting for the
plot
[Music]
fore
foree you were trying to drown us
he says it now like he was trying to
protect us but he was trying to drown
[Music]
us evil 8-year-old
child
[Music]
for shut up you didn't don't say it next
to the mother
is she
serious no you're beautiful you're
beautiful you're beautiful
Joe love
[Music]
yourself you can move around more if
you're
[Music]
smaller oh
no but she already kind of met him
[Music]
English and German
name
combin no
H
what this one in the
middle that's a new
[Music]
one that's a small version of the one
she was riding right
oh yeah oh yeah yeah yeah she's with her
daddy
now cute because he's free from the
prison isn't that
[Music]
sweet now they can work together on
these
things
[Music]
fore
for engineer
[Music]
fighting for
I haven't seen Ralph in a
while what was that
[Music]
again rebuilding mobilia
for well now they have a new
Mission like
[Music]
when you need demolition bombs when
we're rebuilding things I guess to clear
up
the like broken stuff
know yeah I guess so clear Rubble sure
sure only that that's all he will do
right nice they still have a purpose oh
look at them
oh that poor Pig oh my God he just cut
through its ass wait he's cutting for
the middle oh my god oh the poor p how
is he cutting for that like bone and
stuff oh my
God poor Pig
[Music]
is still in the in the
air oh oh oh oh ah she has BL hair again
but she kep the clo
good oh a
[Music]
wait who the [\h__\h] is that cutie
ptie what
[Music]
hello the princess
ofia we've never seen her before what
the [\h__\h]
oh did we maybe
once she looks so
cute he doesn't want to revive his daddy
[Music]
okay what cute good job
girl oh
a she's she's like red now instead of
light
[Music]
blue wait but also that pet is is
optional so would this cut scene be
or not existing at
all oh the Lightning Dragon
yet don't get eaten oh wait that's the
that's the ancient dragon is it it's not
the ancient
[Music]
one oh so she found the ancient dragon
let's go good for her
[Music]
the family honor that I
stole
[Music]
oh come
on come on look get him suffering
[Music]
the Arya
character does that mean I've got every
Quest yeah this is like showing you I
guess like some scenes that you normally
wouldn't see if you didn't do that stuff
look at that cute
[Music]
where her ears
though you didn't see them huh
[Music]
that's nice that you get rewarded for
doing that stuff by seeing those scenes
nice of
them yeah
cool I surely also missed something but
I got a
lot thought I
fore so
this foreshadowing for the next
game I missed one scene oh not
[Music]
bad
for how did I get up
here get down it's dangerous up
there are they about to bunge jump
[Music]
oh shut get the
v
[Music]
no shut up
please stop
stop get a party room yeah I don't know
man whatever whatever
[Music]
girl you were mean too
because you're hot
[Music]
misunder
understanding whoa
whoa who
what where the [\h__\h] is
that we did it we
did see it's all all the same person
let's
go there's two people two people so far
oh who w wao wo T back okay QA manager
what what does the QA manager do okay
here well obviously the illustrations
are by different people obviously but
the da
damn W animation suong Jong background
modeling suong Jong suong Jang is goat
look how
cute it's my ice
cat and those those dust things
cute
wow soong Jang kind of goated
man oh oh cute all these illustrations
so
cute wow special than takas did you see
it no I didn't say that
[Music]
oh
oh oh
[Music]
oh a so
pretty I was thinking of using a
different illustration for this final
part but I figured actually the the one
that I've been using makes it look
pretty clean and and at least you see
that it's a series thing easily didn't
want to confuse you guys with the last
thing but they have so many cute
illustrations wish spring a
[Music]
P's voice arst is Takahashi what the
[\h__\h] that's like basically my
name thank you for finishing no thank
you wow party party
[Music]
party the current ending data has been
saved New Beginning
cool we did it a look at the whole game
w
wow what all of the all of the D is that
all of them yeah that's all of them and
M is there now and W the the other cute
girls everybody's there Robin's there
everybody's there liia is back to
normal uh although was she even yeah
yeah she was a executor on this screen
before previously
okay we did it yay so it took me five
hours I did some tangent thing and I did
all the side things there that we didn't
need to
do they're holding hands no they're not
who's holding
hands who is gay no nobody's holding
hands
[Music]
yeah damn jce and they don't look like
they're handholding to me at all he's
holding his
sword yeah yeah he's holding his
sword thank you Richard I hope you guys
had fun with this series I know I know I
picked some games where you guys maybe
in the beginning are like he what is
this game I don't know this game but I
think like I personally really was
pleasantly surprised rised with how much
this game had to
offer it was it was such a wbore game in
the best way yeah it grew on me too way
more than I thought it's definitely one
of my favorite games this year and I'm
very interested in in the witch spring
game series as a whole now I'm glad that
I chose
it um you know giving some smaller games
a
chance I think always is good thing yeah
people people should give these smaller
games more chances you know and I'm glad
if I can spread the love for it a little
bit on my
channel I don't even think it looked
like a phone game
honestly it it may have its Beginnings
there but I think this remake if you
wouldn't have told me that a phone game
I would have never known so I don't
think so at
all they did a good job at remaking it
wonderful
job
yeah yeah yeah full feature RPG it was
amazing very
very very
intricate
beautiful beautiful game much content
big map too lots of different places to
go to lots of optional
things M cute outfits cute character
designs nice character like storyline
and
developments
yeah we didn't have that like fight that
I uh expected after the dragon rebirthed
itself I thought there was another fight
coming but that's fine like ending it
there uh having that the last fight
makes more sense but at least we still
got more you know story there and like
uh a clear up about the story uh and the
reasonings and everything makes sense
makes sense they just talked it out
yeah I mean it makes sense you know at
that
point yeah we got the we got the the DTs
to wake up and they did wake up and then
they restrained that stupid Rebel
Dragon
M yeah yeahum maybe you might want to
consider like uh if you play this game
to not do normal difficulty but uh like
a little bit more difficult art
difficulty might be still very
manageable thanks for playing thank you
too it was so much fun I'm going to miss
it it was definitely my my comfort game
for these past weeks something really
comfy to go back
to now I want to cry I don't have my
comfort game anymore the next weeks are
going to be so stressful it's okay it's
okay it's okay I'm just going to play
some small of games or not stream at all
and be in the comfort of my bed and and
cry
H thank you for giving us our RPG fix
same same same
yeah Fallout is not my comfort game not
at all makes me
anxious I feel like I don't know what to
do when I
suck but this game doesn't make me feel
like I suck you know and it's cute as
[\h__\h] so
[Music]
cute I'm glad it's your comfort game
no oh thanks guys thank you thank you
thank you I I hope the the deaths
enjoyed my playthrough too they seemed
to be like watching here and there
judging by what they wrote to me um in
DMS so I hope I hope I did their game
Justice I
try Justice I try my
best um to give it the love and the
screen time that it
[Music]
deserved wow wow
thank you too thank you for watching
good night thank you for staying up so
long you did superb thank
[Music]
you did you ask him directly about the
outfit no no not not at DMS no no
no you made me buy the game you did it
justice let's go y be enjoy your own
playthrough of
it so I'm guessing there's like an after
game stuff but uh for now we'll end it
here and I will move over is this
room how's
this
oh
uh okay well uh let me just pull up
something some
background um
something something something
something oh wait we have we have uh
summer new summer backgrounds shut where
did they where did they post
[Music]
um ah here found it
for you know for the summer they made
some stuff again like last year
[Music]
um o
nice how do I download
this H
afternoon where's the difference
4K and Full HD is full HD 2K
then
download oh and there's a
table wow what a beautiful
table okay
so
whoa Loop
nice who that sky is moving fast I can
actually slow it down with an OBS maybe
I'll do that because this this is
freaking me
out yeah now it's
slower
okay okay Waba
[Music]
Berry yeah maybe sometimes they move
that fast I feel like it's a bit too
much
here we
go
nice wow I'd love to sleep over in a
place like this but it looks very hot
like these kind of traditional Japanese
places houses this one this one looks
like it doesn't have an air
conditioner looks like it might be kind
of rough in
here I got some water
W delicious that's pretty
big yeah Ina
life old like there's like most Japanese
houses and apartments have uh air
conditioning but I guess on the on the
countryside the these big old houses
probably might not have
it okay
oh yeah I want to sleep on the floor on
the on the on the um what's the word
again I forgot I want to sleep on the
floor maybe it's more comfortable than
the bed I'm sleeping on at the moment
[Music]
um
sorry saw a message I needed to I felt
like I needed to
answer hey W melons o
o call call your census we're going to
read super chats but maybe we need a bgm
M hello do I have LC on here no I do I
do I
do
I do no no we I don't okay
well I have some
tracks or oh you know what let's go um
Holo
life um
sagm okay which
one uh bosan NOA and Jas miic
maybe yes
okay and
where where should we be reading the
super chats what
stream I would love to
have nobody said anything yet
[Music]
right birthday C with guests you didn't
finish
[Music]
m m
M you know uh GD sleeping really GD
sleeping let's maybe I can find it
birthday birthday K birthday K
really
bir for
real oh God do we have no idea where I
stopped
[Music]
yeah F I don't know maybe maybe for now
I just read the ones from today and
whatever I know that I didn't
read until we have GD again with the
over
viiew also Luigi's manchion from
yesterday and probably Treasure Mountain
too let's just yeah let's go
backwards Gall read um Lu's Mansion now
[Music]
bro if I do a super chat reading stream
next week I barely have days when I can
stream so that will take up like a whole
thing I'd rather do a gaming stream on
the few days where I can stream I
[Music]
think
okay you think I read
those I don't think so I don't think I
read super chats at all
on this
[Music]
stream you're saying I read
this what okay maybe I
[Music]
didn't okay yeah I just I just read the
spankenheimer super chat with the being
licked by in your face by your cats that
sounds familiar what about this one you
guys say I didn't read this one
[Music]
let's
see yeah I think I
didn't
okay D Jacob 47 D Trevor G D ala it's
time for my
ual reminder that today is
international awar
day uh I feel like you could have
squeezed owl into a r
too so here's an owl fact did you know
the Stan owl's Vivid orange yellow eyes
can appear bright red when illuminated
by light much like Mo's new eyes she got
red eyes I saw she got some new stuff
but I I didn't see the red eyes I think
what red
eyes
Che
fancy
H wait what isan owl the thing that she
was San
owl damn wait when I Google
that damn okay those red eyes are
[Music]
spooky I guess it's like the same kind
of
M circumstance as when Cat's Eyes
reflect or is it kind of different
she's a barn o right so it's different
but not a very
interesting owl awareness day I would
say it was today though cuz we saw the
owl
dragon owl I was very aware of the owl
today I did finish the Koka oh
okay okay I just poured way too much
water into my cup and it spilled
over oh well
[Music]
okay okay he finished him on last okay
okay that's good electric mango Channel
d Sean D thank
[Music]
you wait what's n
Metroid zero
[Music]
Mission I mean I don't know currently
I'm not considering it maybe someday in
the far future currently it's not one of
my candidates to play
it I
this wait it's your birthday on that day
I thought I saw someone in the chat with
wishing a happy birthday today in the
pre-chat or like right when we
started was it your birthday on this
day so your mission is fun and rro yeah
but I don't care I'm going to play
something else for the Retro
mission on the fourth oh well happy P
birthday
ah you shared with
M I think I remember seeing that though
yeah I just got confused cuz somebody
wished you a happy birthday
today
uhhuh happy
[Music]
birthday
congratulations another
birthday sorry I'm not going to gift you
me playing Metro Zer
Mission I can't give that to you I I'm
not like uh feeling it right now maybe
sometime in the far future cuz I do like
um like you know I do like
samas but for now it's not on the
horizon but we got lot of fun games on
the horizon always
always
yeah Prime 4 uh is that the like the
next
one I don't
know you still going to play The Witcher
I think so yeah I think at this point
I'll just wait for the new season to
come out then it's you know kind of like
relevant again although people will
probably hate the new season but you
should give it a
[Music]
chance yeah the trailer mhm the one that
they just announced yeah yeah so there's
definitely a higher chance of me playing
that first uh Alex the star child D
black Dan The Dun celester Dun
oh thank
you uh oh MEC chicken I eat that often
too yeah but I always add uh
Tomatoes guess you want to to
investigate row and the Bingo if you but
if you need ah you're suggesting Ghost
Trick um yeah I don't really think
that's what they meant with investig get
something or
so uh but it looks like a fun game I
just don't think I will would start it
now cuz I it's also it has to be
like you know I think these tasks have
to be done within the within the
month I'm not going to start that game
now so yeah I I generally I don't have
time to start any new game now at this
point on until I'm out of
here I know I know I've been already
told that I finished the K super chats
it's okay it's
okay Bru KY stamps J J Monkey D zip Dan
Kenny STS d and delar d and hu thank you
for the pinky
[Music]
game game
game g g
[Music]
n what what
Pap game
tacle yeah I it's supposed to be game
dle
[Music]
you you the
T why did you say that to me
okay I was maybe not so good in this
stream but
still thanks for the pink Super
Chat okay let's read
uh where's your
Mountain why not it's not
much let's do this
[Music]
ban thank you thank you oh welcome
welcome Sky d c n g y dun will dun arm
D and take Monkey
D that's
it that's it that's it and did I read to
dama for
example I'm guessing
not I think probably
not that's D hook come thanks for two
pinkies my birthday is on the second but
you working hard on that day I thought
I'll send a super chat now yeah this
seems new last year I was saying that
I'm getting old but now I think wait a
minute more than half of my life spend
ahead I'm So
Young H how do you know when you're
dying well how do you know cuz you could
like it I don't know how old you became
but that I don't know if you became like
30 you would say you would imply that
you're going to die with 60 but what if
you die with like 80 or
90 who knows who knows could live really
long knocking on the
wood your hard work inspired me to
revive my childhood dream of becoming a
race driver and maybe one day race with
wobble on my car but for that I need a
driving license ah ah well you were
already doing your Fury test though damn
how can you do it so fast and car and
racing license on Wawa liy Livery waa
liy can you stay in Hollow for 10 more
years you think it's going to take 10
more
years well you on your best way to get
the driving license that's already big
step to become a
racer
wow like if you don't do it as like you
know like like as professional as they
do it on TV
I guess is that just like a like do
people do that as a as a relatively
normal Hobby and just meet up on Race I
guess I do I just never really see it
it's like a pretty hidden
hobby I
[Music]
guess I guess they race in the streets
like in
GTA be careful careful not to Bonk into
anyone always be
careful well good luck with all of that
and happy Bela
birthday
congratulations you stay on the RAC
track yeah there's I guess there's RAC
tracks that you can use huh even when
they're not being used for like more
like big events
right vroom vom vro vom vom vom vom
hokan goes vom
vom don't we have we have a someone
who's a race car right a race car
specifically otherwise we could like
change your your job so to say
within within here yeah Harline is
Harline a car or just is just a car or a
race car
though hline is just a car
we have a race
car what's same is a racer is it is he a
race car though if it's free you can
have it if you want to change your
title Jacob 47 D oh hul on again
D
and you say pronounce it like it's STM
and are you sure about that because then
it would be koham with the c would
be I'm guessing it's actually
coam
right
eh is
this what really
koham Camas
K like
this
[Music]
was a
oh you're
[Music]
welcome Poland go po polish a little bit
of Polish polishing my
polish MJ
[Music]
D7 Kong Kong D gamer
d d Tracy d space waterful
d
to finish
[Music]
okay what next we can
do Earth
Defense or did I read last episodes
which which spring super
chats probably not
right oh I don't think
so don't think I
did what did I
[Music]
let's read that take
47 P SP wonderful than soon take monkey
thank Studio R thank you for the pinky
song request something anything by Tori
Amos you would do an awesome version I
Know It uh it would to be totally
covering T
to I don't know her and it's too late
now
sorry I don't know her songs
though is maybe there's a song that I
know and I don't know that I know it
[Music]
Cornflake
Girl I'll see if I can find any song
that even sounds familiar to me
afterwards but can't promise you and R
Dan Nath cotton f for the pinky ouren
only has one addiction streaming to us
kfp I don't know I wouldn't call it an
addiction but um I do often you know
feel like no I should stream you know
but I don't I don't think it's an
addiction I definitely still very much
appreciate the moments where I don't
have to
[Music]
stream I wouldn't call streaming the
addiction
maybe maybe
maybe
kiar
takanashi and kfp like the existence of
it is maybe an
[Music]
addiction like but I wouldn't call that
an addiction
[Music]
either Twitter is an
addiction and looking at your guys's um
replies is I guess an addiction I'm more
addicted towards that than to
streaming I'm too much on Twitter I
can't be saved I can't
be
yeah
help froo thanks for the red of chat I
didn't close myself at work in the
toilet to listen to W stream I'd never
do something like that I'm not sitting
here for like 10 minutes okay after go
go go love thank you a you were trying
to listen to some wa while you were at
work home oh yeah that was probably in
Europe that was a normal like working
time cuz I did it late
jst sorry it wasn't at a better time but
I'm doing a rebroadcast um sometime next
week uh I'm still figuring out the best
time to do it but it might be
Sunday um Sunday morning for me so
Saturday night for Europe and Saturday
evening
for uh
[Music]
Na might be kind of late already for
Europe but I mean it's a Saturday to
Sunday so maybe you can stay up a little
late if you want to see it again if you
miss the from the first time my
Europeans European
friends thank you froo for trying to be
there
anyway Mystic a py
h they do be popping up everywhere yeah
money money wrote
lyrics uh for nerissa some of her songs
in her
album which by the way the teaser of it
was very
nice yeah for
Shatter I didn't listen to all the songs
fully yet cuz I didn't have time for it
but some of the songs are giving me like
Loki K-pop Vibes
Loki
so I'm I'm interested to hear
more mhm
but not just
chatter not just
chatter low
[Music]
key yeah yeah yeah yeah they're using
her for for Hol Justice and Holo Advent
stuff too yeah my
girl Hol lifee staff they wouldn't even
know her if it wasn't for me do I get
like a discovery reward or something for
the discovering a treasure
hello
hello they would not know
her my
girl now they using her for
official like generation songs
man referral bonus exactly where's my
referral
bonus
H yeah yeah she's kind of like the go-to
person now for English
lyrics good for her go get that bag Moy
go get the
[Music]
bag the
gamer wer thank you for the red super
chat ah so my general will take away
from the songs in today's K is W's a man
she wants to make me her girl
and I'll have a great time if I ride W
skateboard deck well I'll try anything
once w w
w Wait what song gave you that take away
I guess several songs
but uh which I know I know there's
something there was certainly there was
certainly something like
that
uh ah the skater boy gave you the skater
deck yeah I mean that makes sense
no other
[Music]
implications
yeah thank you green
wielder
funny funny aren't you
[Music]
py thanks for the pinky today we hit
1.54 million Subs but you totally
deserve Millions more keeping on
fighting keep on fighting entertaining
singing and Shining as you always are
for congratulations for fostering a
fandom like no other I love kfp and I
love you my oi thank you thank you thank
you uh yeah I'm I'm really happy we
reached that we've had like good growth
the past like two or 3 months I think we
climbed from 1.52 to
1.54 uh in a definitely way shorter time
then it took me to get to like 1.5 one
and two so little bit of little bit of
speed there very nice very nice I think
it's slowing down currently it's too bad
we couldn't do like Olympics today
because
that might have helped a little bit but
it is what it is I'll try my best to
increase natural growth one way or
another thank you for the support guys
thank
you I feel like nothing would have
happened even though I hear you guys
confirmed that Olympics are really
strict and blah blah blah I feel like
nothing would have happened but they're
they want to be extra careful okay sure
it is what it
is but I've been seeing a lot of
Olympics stuff every day on uh on
Twitter it's been looking really
interesting I feel like a watch along
would have been fun
honestly oh well it's okay let's do our
best let's keep on spreading the Wawa
word thank you Psy for spreading it too
thank
you yeah of course I saw the pole vter I
mentioned it before but have you seen
the like speed sailor
still humping the
air
bro have you seen
[Music]
that yeah you didn't see that I'm more
up to date on all those Olympics memes
than you
[Music]
are why am I watching that because it's
just on my
timeline yeah they hang off the side of
the boat and then like
hump hump hump hump hump hump hump
hump they're like making the air
pregante get pregnant get pregnant get
pregnant is what they're saying to the
air
bro that is that how you sail is that
how you
sail they're drifting the bolts I guess
yeah it's like d dto bats dto it's
crazy it's crazy it's funny
though ah like you know within their
thing their sport that's normal right
but like can you imagine there's so many
so many people who have no idea how this
stuff works watching that are they
thinking about how what they're doing
looks to them of course it doesn't
matter you got to do what you got to do
but
like like all these normal people like
me looking at that and they're like damn
what are you doing do they feel like
embarrassed and shy I wonder no they're
so into it
probably they're so into
it shut up you were here all along
[Music]
I guess some people think it's like that
but they see it from the pro
perspective yeah I
guess yeah you got to discard your
embarrassment they're too locked
in
yeah air babies air babies let's go
congratulations sailors
[Music]
FAA ja7 hild theard dun py dun 7 dun
Alvaro dun flaming pants dun B ad dun
and Jim Tracy pinky congratulations on
hitting 1.54 million W absolutely
awesome Koka today great set list and
you sang them all so well we even got an
extended German section yeah Yi yeah a
little bit
but I'm sorry I'm sorry it went on too
long I almost want to cut it out of the
the K and then not have it be part of
the rebroadcast it's kind of cursed it's
kind of
cursed but thank you no not Snappy the
the but snappy as well though that was
unnecessary uh
yeah well thank you so much I'm I'm glad
I'm glad that I can see some growth on
my channel after it was like kind of
dead for a really long
time yeah nice you see kfp growing a
little bit thank you for supporting me
and continuing to support me
everybody making KF be
strong h
that was S no that was the C
okay
and let's do which spring R part six
which was the last
one this
one see we're catching up nicely on all
the smaller ones R than C spe than the
Sai the game lunch box D 47
d
h thanks for the Super Chat hi Danel is
this time of the year again where I'm
sending you a red super because I
miraculously survived another Year yay
I'm now officially closer to 30 than to
ooh oh so you turned 26 GL I feel old
but thankfully I can just want you to
distract me sincerely a loyal chicken
you feel
old you feel old with
bro bro
yeah you're so
young that's like like the time of your
life the time of my
life never felt this guys recently uh
what did I what did I sing ah ah my M
stream my M stream yo where I sang The
Bold
song it got even though I had no not the
same lyrics at all and I had um
I had no uh music
on it
got
flagged but where is
it where the [\h__\h] is it ah had to watch
[Music]
along it got well I mean it doesn't
doesn't get like copyright strike or so
but Viva laida got recognized and
content I did
Content ID
claim no no no it's not like you flagged
it it got automatically recognized
because I I basically I sang to the
melody but I didn't have bgm on and I
made my own
lyrics ah it was too close to the
original oh
no oh
no well well well thank you PA good
and happy birthday to you
congratulations but don't feel old you
really are
not 26 is like one of the best ages I
hear for most
people so enjoy enjoy it make the most
out of it enjoy every
[Music]
day Unown D Jacob 47 dun pikab dun we're
doing Moonlight thanks for the pinky
heading to bed right now but we'll leave
the stream open for some relaxing music
while I lay down ah hope you have a fun
time Kiwa and kfp catch you later thank
you for coming by hope you slept well
can't think of a name d Studio Rob
thanks for the pinky fat cat
setup
what what are you saying Studio Rob hm
H
H there was no fat Gat in the
Stream ah I was call Fat acid ah was
this my first stream after I arrived in
Japan I think it
was makes sense everything makes sense
now okay that makes a lot more sense
now J D Sky d you are D admin one the
FRS of the pinky hi Ki it's about to be
my friend's birthday soon and I wanted
to surprise him with some kind wishes
from you his name is Mikey he and I both
love your streams keep up the hard work
tento I feel like I reacted to this on
stream but uh again uh Happy Birthday
Mikey now it's definitely too late but
congratulations
Mikey please continue watching my
streams both of
you k okay
[Music]
golden oh glad you enjoyed it big
speed Jimmy Russ bus regulation director
niy Son Space wonderful
Dan D
[Music]
com oh yeah speaking of concert viewing
these Korean Bros are talking about the
live viewing but did you guys see how
fast I wonder how fast those extra
tickets were gone I was not looking at
Twitter at the
time but there was uh extra sales of
some extra tickets
right anybody who got one of
[Music]
those comes
on they we gone in like 2 minutes oh
well good I guess that's
good you want it really Honolulu
no no you mean eh you mean concert
viewing tickets right for you now I'm
talking about the IRL like uh at the
venue New York
tickets but also nice to have concert
viewing tickets in Korea that sounds
like fun too I got one you got one PLP
from the resale like not resale but like
the extra sales I don't know what it
was thank you good luck have
[Music]
fun nice Jim Tracy D take monkey Chris
gito thank
you
a oh my God I hope you feel better by
now I hope you feel hugged by fluffy
chickens and W
wa chocolate insomnic thanks for the
pinky you're the only streamer I'd stay
up for a while thank you for the long
stream thank
you you're the best thank soon for
ruining your sleep schedule for
me simply
D
okay that's that was
[Music]
that
okay I need to record my new song and
that's going to be a lot of vocals so I
might end it here
[Music]
so I can save my voice a bit more and
rest
it
yeah uh tomorrow is ID cup practice with
waya um she'll be
streaming I'm probably going to be
streaming too but not
100% necessary I don't know I don't know
for sure yet but in any case you'll see
me on Raina stream if I don't stream um
I don't know yet if I should I don't
know I'll see I'll see probably I will
maybe I won't who
knows yeah if I don't stream then I'll
be on way
stream uh and then there's the ID cup
the real one on Sunday so two days of
Minecraft this
weekend yeah
[Music]
okay I'm still busy though cuz after
those streams I I have some things to
do after the
streams so it's making me
anxious it's all voice chat so you can
take a break from streaming yeah I I
could but I don't know maybe I don't
know I'll think about it before I go to
[Music]
sleep I think tomorrow there will be um
me way and then I think S stand by E
standby
and what was the other pa ah Cobo and
Canada so three three more
pairs because they also couldn't
participate in the other
practice so we won't be alone in our
delayed practice cuz the first one was
yesterday and couple of pairs
participated there but the others
couldn't oh by the way I met soda
Senpai uh again and it's been a while
but we talked a little bit and she she
really wants to do like a collab with me
and we talked about it before when I met
her and then you know nothing happened
um so I think I have to like she really
wants to do it but then she doesn't she
doesn't like like like push me to do it
so I should probably be the one pushing
um but I don't know what to do like I
want to come up with something fun but
I'm I'm currently kind of out of
oneon-one collab ideas I can't think of
much good stuff at all like four people
or so easier a little bit
easier da da Senpai dce Senai you suck
with dce Senai
I know yeah I mentioned too like could
do a
k
but that's like that's what I did with s
it seems like such an
easy choice but I guess we could but I
don't know I'd prefer something else
maybe
[Music]
yeah like what gimmick
though talk about Japanese snacks Oh you
mean doing it making K but like adding
some gimmick to the
K would be great if you invited roban as
well well that's the thing I also met
roboco again and she was so
sweet she was really touchy and she's so
cute and we were just like showing each
other like cats like she gave me cat
updates her her kitten grew up so much
and it's so cute I I want to like go
over to her place again to get some cat
energy cuz her cats are so cute and not
ignoring me like the cats in the cat
cafes so I'm thinking of visiting her
and maybe combining it with a collab
again
too M but but the thing is I don't have
time for so many collabs so maybe maybe
it could even be an option to combine s
sampai off collab with the Senai off
collab if they want to and have a triple
or invite a fourth person and we all go
to Ru sire's place and I pet the cats
win win win win win win
win that's just so many wins
so if we're talking about four people
collabs was there another like game for
four people that I might want to do as
an off collab I don't remember if I had
another
one like any particular one do you guys
know go play Mario Party yeah or that
new uh is it out yet that new um
the Mario the Japanese Mario Party game
the Japanese Monopoly game what was it
100% origes well who who who what's that
again what's that
again 100% orange juice I remember you
guys mentioning that at that one I don't
know if we have perms did somebody play
this
before yeah
[Music]
M orange is better for online okay
yeah m is there's a new one coming out
but like when is it not out
yet honestly I personally wouldn't mind
playing Mario party again I haven't
played it in a while I'm I'm in the mood
for some Mario
Party off collab Mario Party could be a
little bit more intense than uh online
collab Mario party I think it would be
more
[Music]
intense it's definitely more
intense
H who would
I I think I know who I could invite as
the fourth
[Music]
person cuz it would be nice if the
fourth member was also
like a non-japanese
[Music]
member okay
yes okay so I'll be planning that but I
honestly don't know where to squeeze it
in it's like almost
impossible my schedule is
[Music]
insane I'm like so busy next week so I
think the next two weeks I might not
even put up a
schedule because the schedule might just
look very disappointing and I still want
to stay somewhat flexible in case I'm
too exhausted on one day where I thought
I could stream after dance lessons or
whatever and then turns out I'm I don't
want
to but yeah I I do hope to squeeze a
members stream in in next week either
continuing the watch along or doing just
something else
um yeah I have lots to
do recording lots of things learning
lots of
dances and I don't want to I don't want
to have a like breakdown so well I'm
going to take it step by step and no
[Music]
schedule I was considering taking a full
week off one of these weeks
M
but I maybe I don't think I'll go that
far but it might really be
scarse I don't think I'll go that far no
but it might be scars we'll see we'll
see thank you for offering me
that oh thank you I appreciate it guys I
appreciate
it I mean around the like concert thean
concert uh I do you think it will be
almost a full week of no
[Music]
streaming
yeah I won't be streaming uh but maybe
doing Twitter
Space Twitter space is very
possible I'm kind to get so much [\h__\h]
down let's
go take a week call thank you but it's
okay it's okay for now take it step by
step and see how it goes
I'll analyze the
[Music]
situation take the week up
no I don't
know we'll
see okay so I had a lot of fun finishing
which spring R today
Yi I'll miss it I'll give the 10 the the
game a 10 out of 10
yeah it's a 10 out of 10 For
Me Maybe that's too nice maybe it should
be n out of 10 but I have no complaints
especially like it's not it's it's a
freaking indie game made by two people
what the
hell what the
hell freaking 10 out of
10 pie out of
pie yes if if anybody asks me to recite
pie I will um open my archives for this
game all my stream
archives and I'll play The Archives have
them listen to it and I'll say I'm
residing Pie as I
[Music]
speak what what that's not what I'm
saying I'm not saying it's 3.14 out of
10 no
I'm saying the game is
pie you know
that g
[Music]
what see you in Minecraft
tomorrow cherish these normal streaming
days because next
week
y y
ah in German we say in I'm going to take
this cape and this hat off because it's
freaking hot here in the
summer isn't it hot hot hot hot hot hot
hot hot hot what
[Music]
a
bye-bye
bye-bye bye-bye
bye-bye bye-bye bye my merch bye my
merch Link in description merch merch I
forgot to put up that tweet with the
happy I completely forgot it
bye-bye remind me remind me after the
stream on Twitter remind
me
bye-bye there she goes no I haven't gone
yet
bye-bye Rubber
Chickens say
bye-bye the
smell
s w plastic let's go
[Music]
M
uh
[Music]
ah meow meow meow
meow meow
meow meow meow meow meow
meow meow meow meow
meow
[Music]
meow meow meow meow meow
it was streaming throughout my whole
stream
[Music]
it's like we were kind of breathing the
same air
through YouTube virtual the same virtual
air
[Music]
CU we're in the same virtual
space it is
true it is
true can I raate
meai no
no okay okay bye