[Music]
i'm tired of the
is
[Music]
baby
give me
[Music]
family
is
[Music]
[Applause]
something to keep
[Music]
two of me
my brain is so slow
what am i doing
[Music]
oh
mum
[Music]
oh honey
do you feel the music
come on
[Music]
me
oh
[Music]
because
brain's so slow
so maybe it's
suitable
hello everybody
yay
yay how's it going
i finally got the time to play
hollow cure
in the past couple
days weeks two weeks one week or so
uh so many of the whole men have been
playing this
but as you know i was here and there and
everywhere
okay i was in america
and therefore i didn't have the time so
far or the opportunity yeah but today's
the day
sorry water thing is really really heavy
we should okay i've got like two liters
of water
oh [\h__\h]
i'm watching your first time really
then i must be the only whole life
member you watch in general
if that is so then thank you
hey everybody
my mane is playing my main oh we don't
know about that yet um i've heard i'm
only good in the beginning
sad
so sad
i also like i got
um wait don't talk too much in the
beginning chihuahua
talk talk during the game just okay so i
originally looked for holocure on steam
but apparently it's not on steam and
then i realized okay it's like on some i
o thingy
okay
and it didn't even need to install
what
so
here we are
okay
let me show you
bum bum
[Music]
very much however one day an evil force
came in and took advantage of the fans
and their love
the evil force brainwashed the fence
isn't me turning them into mindless
minions blinded by their own love sounds
like me
with a beach bastion they had to help
their fans and come back to their senses
and thus began their quest to save the
fans
[Music]
cute
the music is already [\h__\h] banging
let's go
he got on the true final buzz it could
be
could be true can you change like this
is the second time i opened the game but
i never went
past beyond beyond the this screen
there
[Music]
hey thanks for the red super chat so
there's a shop there's a leaderboard
well i guess we just start to play
uh you can change the bindings to wasd
oh are they currently other
binded to something bound to something
bad by default let me check
i don't wanna
oh wait huh
ah
i see it's just the arrow keys sorry i
tried to click with my mouse
no mouse in this game or what
keybinds
ah
confusing very confusing
uh
app is w
down
is s okay
uh should i keep the cancel on the
special confirm and wait confirm is that
that's confusing because sometimes my
keyboard z and y are
um different
uh
what's a good key q
confirm strafe
strafe what does that mean i'll do q
and a cancel
i guess i'll just do the closest other
one e or j and k
is it bad if it's too close
i'll try with q and e
no
i have space and confirm oh that's good
too oh yeah okay how about how about
that uh
space will confirm
and cancel let's do x
i think that's good okay okay
uh
okay escape
escape
i wish i wish there was mouse
play [\h__\h]
okay ah
choose your idol oh you start with
hollow myth oh
okay so there's a a man with a pistol
shot
could have the trident frost
you know with the summoned tentacle
on the phoenix side short range slash in
front okay i am once again a friend
fighter which i in reality don't really
like
uh
kelly has with us through scythe of
course
um so i mean we'll obviously start with
me i've heard that i have a lot of hp
which seems to be true 75 65
70 wow i'm such a tank i would never
play a tank in like mmorpgs or anything
so
but
what can i do oh crit oh critical five
percent one percent five ten
ten oh
speed
i don't know like i i didn't play the
the game that this is supposedly based
off of a tank
a vampire survivors so i'm going in here
with absolutely no knowledge
[Music]
well well let's try stage mode endless
mode
defeat the last boss to complete it
should i start with stage mode i think
yes
oh okay
how do i fight oh it just fights
automatically right there's like a
certain rhythm
and
if i understand it correctly i collect
all these items and then i get stronger
because when i collect the items
i don't know i get like
some points or something
yeah these whole live logos
suspect is playing out [\h__\h] love
suspect oh there's so many coming come
at me
come at me oh it only does it in that
one direction okay well we gotta get
stronger skills oh there we go okay what
is this i've always seen this when other
people play it but i don't know what's
going on here so i can increase
my damage by twenty percent
that that's a lot
wow
moving gradually increase ah is dancer
skill not although gradually uh moving
range increases damage by two percent
you guys say free what you mean nurse's
horn or what
got the horn when the target is defeated
there's a 20 chance to heal
oh
it's okay
only 20 though
i'm not taking any damage for 10 seconds
or longer increase crit by 10
wow
wow the alcohol
okay horn is pretty great i agree to
free okay well i don't i i want to make
some decisions to myself but a lot of
you guys say free so it's rare
oh wait is this like random the choices
that i get here is this random
it's okay to backstage it's okay
it's random oh well then i gotta make
some smart decisions i don't wanna
regret anything okay so let's go up the
horn i guess
where's my hp
i'm confused where's my hp there's a i
can't look too much at
things when i'm trying to survive oh so
fast
okay i'm at 89.90 the green line the
green bar
what green bar
hold that to aim in the direction set
but for me it's not that anymore is it
above character okay okay wait so we
have phoenix start again glowstick oh
to nearby a target and then spins back
to player uh-huh oh it's a weapon these
are weapons these are items when a
target wait is if it's an item do i have
to activate it or
does it get activated
by
like automatically
it's passive aha okay okay
every 15 seconds this shield refreshes
interesting well i think we need to
upgrade our weapon
okay so where's this green bar i only
see t-shirts oh my god why is it lagging
oh now it's okay
i don't wanna be close convent
too close they're different
can't be
why are you not helping me or did they
help me they didn't help me right
oh my god i need to i need to collect
those things they're too close to me ho
ho ho
wait but it's not set for me is it
though
i changed it didn't i
what what's that for me
space
wait what
oh that's just a
it's just a menu
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
oh what is that what am i doing what am
i doing
what did i just do
okay
this is very stressful
it's very stressful
oh
i locked my aim
onto what this is too much for me
i thought this was easy
okay it's okay i have i have a lot of hp
i'm fine i'm fine i'm fine okay
so we have
asaku fire fire fast piercing tail
targeted at a random target increased
attack
area
oh
that's that's good when the target is
defeated there is a 20 chance oh we have
the horns again
the heel for 77.5
of max hp created an area of miasma
around dealing slow damage to enemies
inside uh-huh so we're between two and
four
uh how do you switch weapons though
like can i can't do two weapons at once
right
hold space to lock the way you attack
marked by the arrow ah
ah so even if i'm like running away in
one direction i can still like attack in
the other direction
oh
you can it's automatic everything is
passive all weapons are always active
what okay
all right so if i
huh
ah like this ah
oh my god
mommy okay so this circle now is this
miasma that i just got
okay okay okay okay oh wait maybe up
okay okay okay oh [\h__\h] it's big is that
a boss
level up level up level up oh lava
bucket elite
that's fun
uh drop lava on the ground burning
targets slowly but how often like all
the time
oh you want me to use that it's very
elite
if it's all the time then that's that's
that's amazing
[Music]
but everybody says one
miasma knocks enemies back at level
seven
your words mean nothing to me because i
don't understand
it's like every three seconds
oh
oh does it follow me where i drop it or
does it stay where it is where i dropped
it drops at random oh i'm guessing it
stays
crease area
ah this is cool
because it's random you don't know what
you get it's like a surprise
um present yeah surprise party
that's random okay pumping hit increase
crit by ten percent okay no
okay
oh
yeah
[\h__\h]
kill this [\h__\h]
looks like a big dragon ebby what is
that whose fandom is that supposed to be
because it looks like a mix of a shrimp
and a dragon sorry abby was shrimp
no no attack up
wait wait
it is a shrimp okay looks because the
head looks like a dragon
hmm
okay okay nurse's horn again
phoenix sword attack area mm-hmm
oh my shiv every 20 seconds foot will
drop close by
also increase food drop chance
of food from defeat return
increase level area by 20 percent
yeah okay now for now the lava is fine i
think
is this what is this
is this a character
[Laughter]
what is this spider cookie it's not a
character oh you can get like weapons
too huh
why would i drop it is there a maximum
of things i can carry
this is good though
yeah spider cooking free upgrade let's
go don't drop okay take it take
what is this
upgrade
oh
oh reduced time between attacks by 15
increases damage by 30
i would say the sword
okay
success rate hundred percent
that's funny that's like an
mmorpg when i try to upgrade [\h__\h] okay
uh
mommy mommy mommy mommy mommy mommy
mommy mommy
oh no
okay just now i'm doing it right now i'm
doing it right oh
they said so much
uh there's horde again dancing moving on
two percent every second up to forty
percent
that increases damage by two wow wow
that's actually pretty strong
okay
we want more skills more more oh there's
so much stuff here let's get that exp
oh my god i left so much stuff here
holy [\h__\h]
uh hold a bump a bomb that explodes
dealing damage to
all nearby targets damn
increase weapon attack speed
by five percent ooh any weapon this now
i have fast piercing tail turning
um
okay
chad feedback sitting strong and i'm
somehow relying on it i shouldn't i know
i shouldn't okay let's get back to the
masses
and ben no don't hurt me
think shield ah
but my name is kiwawa if canada has not
taken any damage for 10 seconds the next
two hits taken is half and stay but
staying available for 0.5 seconds that's
so short but [\h__\h]
it's not taking any damage attention
next two hits taking us half and stay in
uh-huh
traveling leave a burning fire
underneath kiara whenever she moves that
deals 30 damage per hit lasts 5 seconds
wow
strong boys
okay fire
what the [\h__\h] it's lagging
wait this is
what
why do they suddenly disappear are they
like time limited
are you ready
oh god oh god
and my pc is good
i don't know what turn up damage numbers
how do i get to the settings now my pc
is good
i might have to change settings though
yeah
oh
[Music]
everyone's pc likes to this game really
not only me
from escape okay okay ah
oh i'm gonna upgrade
fifty percent that's nice
yeah sure why not
uh escape
uh what's this
oh
[\h__\h] uh
no
the rest we can keep right
uh confirm
there we go okay
okay no need for damage numbers
[Music]
yeah my my screen uh the game screen is
really tiny i have it really really
really small and barely
it barely fills up the screen
oh my
[Applause]
sh
wow
spirals outward from the player
can hit twice per slash oh
that sounds good too let's max it
oh my god oh my god but can it says can
what do you mean can
so is there like food randomly on the
map besides you know that uber thing
that they talk about
wait the hearts the hearts are not for
me right
let's get this ah
yes
i have yet to see it is it pretty rare
it is rare
okay okay okay
increase damage by 20
increase movement speed by ten percent
okay
it's perfect for me
sword is engulfed in flames and can hit
many times
yeah
is that good because it feels good to me
it just feels like fate all right dick
that looks so strong
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh fried chicken
let's go
oh my gosh
holy [\h__\h] surprise it didn't kill me
they swamped me
damn
exciting
ah increase damage increase lava area
um
spins back to the player
i mean if it's
all doing it automatically then the more
weapons the mario right
oh [\h__\h] that was fast what the [\h__\h] how
could i get another level up
immediately
uh chris is damaged by 30 percent sorry
i need to read this stuff guys but the
other revolver members probably already
know everything i'm sorry i don't know
anything
um
might need more healing
looking at
how my hp was looking before more
i want to try hollow bomb oh there it
goes oh
burger
what the [\h__\h] can't be
i i i have or um pretty fast realized
the irony of this game
doesn't the logo say save the fans
but we're killing them
what does this mean
[Music]
opposite opposite uh psychological
influence what increased damage by 20
okay
i want to get out of here
give me that yummy yummy yummy exp
i'm saving them how am i saving them
[Laughter]
oh leave a burning fire underneath kiana
whenever she moves until 75
damage period last five seconds also
slows target for three seconds are there
level ups ever getting slower in this
game by the way cause i kinda kinda
wanna
talk a little bit
i don't know what to do
um
yes okay
the 20 percent chance to heal
[Music]
i don't know let's do this i don't want
to go too much by what the chat says oh
oh
i will not run from you anymore i stand
strong cause i'm a tank let's go
come come here come here if you if you
have the courage
try me
okay we have another phoenix shield
uh
uh-huh
okay new weapon
oh the lag
oh
it's understandable that's okay it's
okay
besides the lag everything's pretty good
in this game so far
yeah yeah drop those bums
bam bam
bam
face mask increases damage by 30 take 40
more damage
i don't like these kind of items that
like
hurt and help you
um
let's get some hp
oh
oh sure
i'm having still a little bit of trouble
getting used to how to you know um
uh lock in the direction but oh well
okay so we get an upgrade
uh
oh
maybe sword again
huh
price damage by 30 lava
two or three
no no
i say this one
big shrimp big shrimp
big i don't even like shrimps
i don't really like seafood much i know
it's very disappointing every time i say
that people are so shocked and
[Music]
increase explosion size by 15 percent
le gasp
onyo me too yata
gain a shield
yeah
since i'm a tank a better shield like
this
is now
a good idea i think
is this why is it why i said oh i was
just gonna ask like why is that one
blinking oh i guess it could collect
everything in the area noise
hp by 20.
always want more hp
four
[Music]
princess presents presents princesses
it's just like my members only stream
where i opened all the presents oh i see
at the top left now
the slots are filling up ah
so if i want any other weapon i have to
drop one of them myself
okay nice
explosion size by fifteen percent
bronzo
hamburger
consumable
so this one i'm i'm assuming is not
automatic
can't drop weapons oh okay
um
that's one-time use
i took the wrong one
oh wow
i'm so sorry bubba is so mad at me for
saying i don't like him in particular
i'm sorry
i'm sorry don't take it that way i i
feel like i don't like you i just i just
prefer cats you know
don't take it the wrong way
i'm sorry you're so kind of cute and
yeah
i mean
i wish you all the best and happiness
and oh what they're circling me
you need to break the wall
this is like at komike comic market when
a popular cosplayer is staying in the
middle have you guys seen these photos
before
when they have like a huge wall of
photographers around them
coming
[Laughter]
[Music]
for a few seconds or minutes and then
somebody goes like okay three
two
one scatter and they literally they all
they all listen to it and leave
so kaku
okay
been to comic con and tokyo game show
and all these kinds of japanese
uh events a lot of times so there they
go
oh
oh egg legs
[Music]
20 chance to heal for
10 percent
[Music]
throw two lava buckets oh
no why none
that's pro two lava buckets the mortar
merrier
oh
my god so much
uh so let's do healing
what level are we level 24
already
what
do you get like your hp healed when um
when you level up because i haven't
really paid attention to that oh there
we go oh my hp is healing up okay it's
looking better it's looking better it's
looking better
can't lose track of that holy [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] deadbeats lurking now no
not much lurking they're like pretty
obviously there holy [\h__\h]
with the bat are you for real
oh my god oh my god oh my god
[Music]
baseball bat
i've never played baseball before it's
not really a thing in
austria as it is in america for example
as much as it is in america
a punishment stick
it's not a stink anymore it's way past
the stick
oh headphones that's something new 15
chance to negate one hit and create a
shock wave that knocks back all enemies
shockwave knocks back hell yeah
okay knock back this bastard go golf do
it do it
what the [\h__\h] oh my god oh my god oh my
god oh my god
my right screen is looking good though
holy [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
this is gonna disappear after a while
right
holy [\h__\h] they're gone okay
headphones let's go don't even think go
how'd you survive that cause i'm a tank
tank
[Music]
okay
okay and here we have a upgrade
yeah
bigger area
oh my god
now my decisions are getting faster
because i care less
because i'm invincible no matter what
increase frequency
frequency
[Music]
damage by 30 percent increases an
increased duration of lava by one second
size of glow stick
big glow stick
have you guys all played the game
already oh my god
the chickens make the game leg
yo i gave them a knockback in the
absolutely perfect set kid oh
oh oh scatter scattered can't be
oh oh that is fun that's kind of fun
guess you all played it before
damn
what a big success but guys there's so
many more fan mail games you should
check them out
this one's pretty damn good though
and playing endless mode right now when
how do you stop
how would you stop
when do you know to stop oh look there's
a burger
even though i used to always eat like
chicken burgers like especially the
crispy chicken in burger king
i kind of um recently have been eating
a lot more beef burgers but my condition
is that it's not
like from the two big
the the two big double o wow
so cute so fluffy i want to adopt this
cute cattle
i love you so cute
so cute
[Music]
no
no why
i thought i was a tank
you have to decide from the beginning
where is the safe point
i called it a cat
no
it was so cute i wanted to hug it you
know i have a problem with fluffy things
that look like a cat
eh
oh no i do still love you chickens i do
credit card
finally i get a credit card
i've been really needing one cost of
enhancing is ridiculous
okay well i think
everybody
has to you know like do one try where
they first you know get kind of warmed
up and learn these things
yeah
can't help it
you need to survive 20 minutes
oh and then the stage is clear
oh i feel like i was kind of close to 20
minutes man
i can get upgrades it was a really good
first try
first it was good try really thank you
thank you
okay
pick up all the the the hp and nothing
is the experience points
i've never seen this one before
that feels rare
should i get this door oh
okay
oh no i love you guys said something
else but we need to you know experiment
so i was saying about the burgers
yeah i don't know for like the big big
big chains i kind of don't trust their
meat that much the beef so i've been
always going for chicken but recently
i've been eating more burgers from
non-big chains that i've been trying out
more like
yeah beef burgers with like cheese and
all that you know yeah more beef than
chicken these days i'm sorry chickens
i'm i'm trying to keep you alive you
know i want you guys to stay alive
yeah but i will always love my crispy
chicken from burger king that's the best
ever
okay
make phoenix sword stronger
thoughtful yes i know i'm very
considerate have you seen my playthrough
of uh cookie yummy
i think that
must have defeated all depths of me
being
an inconcer a considerate person oh
thank you
thank you very much i shall upgrade my
sword well ah chickens
i didn't get them at all
oh
fan meeting has failed
oh gotta try pop eyes oh never tried
that
is that a chain in america because i
didn't see it
i tried in and out though
it was very good
[Music]
and i don't know if you guys saw
did you guys see on like when i on
twitter when i asked for like
um
recommendations
when i asked for recommendations oh
hello hello let's try to kill one can i
can i even
[Music]
uh of what to eat while i'm in america
um a lot of you know you guys answered
but
it's not only you guys who answered some
fast food chains answered especially
after being mentioned from some fans but
there was this one uh fast food chain
wasn't what was it called again
reese's or jesus or
no no that was not it wait what was that
what's that you guys it's checkers yeah
check it rally rally checkers the one
that has like two names apparently
a full meal yummy yummy look at those
fries i love fries that's not a full
meal that's a drink and fries i mean i
love fries but
yeah
and they were like hey yo
uh
if you're
like uh if you want you hit us up and we
can provide you a free meal
and you know in general like i really
appreciate that and i would have loved
to get that free meal
uh
but
you know
it is
putting me kind of in a difficult
position i can't i can't really like be
like yeah yo hello here's the dm that
you've been waiting for i'll get i'm
kind of doxing myself to this company
first of all we would have to go for the
whole process you know doing an nda and
all that [\h__\h] and that's just
too much
too much too much
let's get this while we well we have the
option
oh my god
are you ready
oh there we go oh no what's happening
okay
now so
um if i had more time maybe i don't know
one more time to talk with them about it
but it was kind of like close to the end
of my travel so
um i would have liked to check it out
though check check checkers or rally out
because it seems like they're not too
bad from what i've heard
hmm
[Music]
ah
look at that
checkers is pretty good
really
and now i'm regretting not trying it but
i can't eat freaking maybe i could
i was gonna say going to america i can't
eat burgers every day twice a day but
maybe that's still the goal maybe that's
the
the real way of enjoying america
[Music]
unless i could
maybe i could maybe i should have but
it's not the last time that i
will have been in america
there will be more times
[Music]
that sounds like a lot
[Laughter]
what the [\h__\h] i don't understand those
armies
i'll get it
[Music]
i like their viking helmets cute
huh
no traps unless
do i have to kill all of them like how
would that be possible
if you land the killing blow
on only one though right i just have to
kill one or
all the dead
mamma mia
watch hp okay oh [\h__\h] yeah
oh nightly milk oh
milk increases attack range of area type
weapons by ten percent
oh also increases pickup radius by 30
okay you guys seem to like this one
probably for a reason a big taco daddy
all right all right all right
[Music]
no
no that didn't happen it didn't happen
it didn't happen didn't
hey happen kyla hello
i'm new to this okay this that was my
second playthrough
what's the main screen huh uh-huh
[Music]
quit
for
buy stuff
but then i restart from the beginning
again
upgrades wait
do i quit
oh [\h__\h]
shop
oh 643 coins so the coins don't get lost
buy upgrades
oh
crazy is all damage
you have no skills
increases movement speed by
special where's the special
[Music]
special
ah special attack
unlocks a special attack for all
characters whoa it's really expensive
okay
press the secondary button x to use
should i should i buy any more wait wait
the other ones are
oh they're all expensive
i can't even afford anything now anyway
ah except the hardcore challenge okay
oh my god
it's kind of cheap you earn two to three
k on the complete side ah okay
well then i want to do quiz again
okay wow as long as i can
but if i clear a stage
then i can what why is there leg now
if by clear stage i can
hopefully
change the character
without resetting everything or
is everything reset anyway when you
clear a stage
any programs open
not not nothing really
it's oh it always resets uh-huh
oh
does it get more difficult or is it just
always the same like difficulty
[Music]
i guess i could
okay
you get to be rich
nice
same difficulty different traps okay
cool
ah maybe i shouldn't have done the fire
oopsie oh well
fire kind of
not so necessary right now
oh well
[Music]
i want to talk a little bit about my
trip because i still have some more
things
not so much i talked about most of it if
you're curious and you didn't hear about
my trip to america i did a
stream when i came back
and
it was like a couple days ago so check
it out i told a lot about my trip yeah
but uh i heard that kelly mentioned it
so i wasn't sure if i could mention it
but now that she mentioned it
i guess i can mention it mention mention
mention mention mention in german means
uh humans by the way oh i have a skill
[\h__\h] cool
hey yo
phoenix power so cool
and it's a circular thing okay okay cool
leo cool yo ah what should i do
[Music]
high chickens and it leaves a fire here
too which is kind of like a wall to me
too
yeah oh nice
oh it loads up pretty fast too
okay
so
attack area increase size of x
[Music]
okay
literal firewall
yeah okay
okay upgrade sword
stuff i was saying uh kelly mentioned it
so now i think i can say it um we stayed
in like a place that had a pool
i was so excited about it
like lag lag like luck look like the
moment i arrived and i saw the pool i
immediately changed into my swimsuit
immediately
and then
i
quickly went into the pool
um
all healing is doubled wait all healing
is doubled
maybe no need for it
okay phoenix chill let's go
yeah the water was really really really
warm or like yeah no i wouldn't say the
water was hot but you know it was really
hot outside the sun was blasting
yeah yeah
i thought it would do more damage to
this big shrimp
oh let's drop some lava
oh yeah
i feel so good to do a big attack
yeah the water was really nice and i
started swimming around but
you know no one joined me
i was all alone in the pool
so
i was like hey yo callie join me in the
pool
kelly please and first she was like no
no i'm embarrassed
and then i was like can we know you have
nothing to be embarrassed about you got
that hot ass body come on in come on
don't be shy join me don't want to be
alone enjoy the water
so
yeah i
i motivated her to join me and then she
was like okay and then she seemed kind
of happy about you know making that
decision so she changed into
she changed into her
uh swimsuit and joined me as the only
other person in the pool yeah
but i think it was a good decision
and then throughout the whole stay
besides that one time that kelly joined
me i was i continued to be the only one
to make use of it
i i know um
good i had a swimsuit with her i don't
know why she didn't join
she should have joined you know the pool
was so nice so freaking nice yeah
i don't know man
i think
no floaties
maybe that was the reason i could have
taught her how to swim without floaties
i mean i'm not the best swimmer either
but i really enjoyed it man because it
gave the whole thing a little bit more
of a
vacation feeling oh my god
[Music]
no no no i want to go left oh yeah
i never feel this one correctly
ah [\h__\h] i forgot i could have maybe
activated this oh well
oh well well
uh
[Music]
sharky is shy i don't think so like i
saw her wearing her bikini top but she
never actually went into the water we
want to try the boys lava book okay got
the middle
oh
oh here they come again
[Music]
i swam a few laps and i was like
floating on my back
and then yeah i did a few times
i jumped from the side of the pool
into the pool i did some bombs
in german we like to call it ass bombs
ash bomb there
when you jump into the pool with your
butt first and make a big bra kaboom
oh yeah the girls told me it's
cannonball in english yeah yeah
i learned something new i feel like i
heard it before though
[Music]
right now
i tried to stay in the middle you know
because i was like oh it's going to be
available soon i need i need i need to
be in the middle for that oh [\h__\h]
that was really close i saw it i was
sweating
that was
very risky
[Laughter]
okay
healing doubled yeah we probably need
that right now yeah baby
okay there we go there we go we're back
in the game baby maybe or maybe not
give me healing i want to pick up that
box but
remember it's on the left side
i'm trying to i'm going to try to reach
it again oh
[\h__\h] chickens
i love you though i love you i love you
there's an arrow oh it tells me where
the where that is that the the important
thing to pick up okay
okay
uh increases damage by thirty percent
increase duration by one second
uh leave a burning fire underneath when
i want this to be level two now
they're all [\h__\h] there
oh my hp is okay now i'm okay i'm okay
ah lava bucket i need the lava bucket
now drop it right there
okay i'm okay i'm okay i'm okay
okay
[Music]
it's nice to see that like all of the
skills are kind of good like it seems
pretty balanced like everything
everything does a good job okay i need
healing
um oh there's a
burger my hp is really like oh
it keeps on going down and up and down
and up and down and up
[Music]
and forgot the special oh there it is ah
okay
i may have forgotten it yes
[Music]
level three
okay
okay okay
chill
chill chill chill chill
oh
okay so i was saying i was enjoying the
pool okay
i was
i think i entered the pool every day
while i was there which was not even
that long anyway i think it was what
three days
two nights three days
[Music]
are you ready
oh it was really nice it was kind of
like a vacation thankfully because after
that after the whole recording
um i actually
uh
let me tell you
um
i
after
doing the whole recording
i switched uh
accommodation to a hotel in downtown i
told you that already and that hotel
had a
pool but when i went to the pool it was
like so crowded that oh god there was no
seat available for me
on the pool side oh special oh okay
[Music]
yeah there was no seat available and the
pool was so busy too
[Music]
i don't
know said i immediately left like i made
one walk around the pool and i was like
okay i guess even though i specifically
chose this hotel because it had a pool
i guess i'm not getting to use it
huh
very sad about that
oh my god
oh hp back up
[Music]
welcome to comic market baby
oh let's take the
bomber glow stick um
last time we had both of them
oh oh you're telling me to not even go
for that
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
are you ready
is that is it always suspect playing
because so far i only heard suspect do
they
have any other remixes
nothing is against suspect the suspect
is really good
as always suspect
[Music]
so on the dlc there's a dlc
you're working on others i see okay
i'm looking forward to that wow wow wow
wow wow
[Music]
[Applause]
bang bang
i know i'm playing this game because i
don't like hurting my fans i feel sorry
for it
i don't want to hurt you
what is left baby don't hurt me
don't hurt me i'm sorry
i'm sorry
but they're hurting me too why are the
fans attacking me that's also the
question i'm just i in the end i am just
protecting myself i wouldn't be doing
this i wouldn't be hurting my fans if
they weren't hurting me i'm saving them
i'm curing you okay if you think so yeah
you are brainwashed i guess so
guess who brainwashed you in the first
place
oh he's gone
i'll finish you never free hmm
and now i'm thinking the food is
actually a good idea too
because i'm i'm on lower speed so often
i want to survive
oh there's food on the on the left side
oh well there we go now we'll get the
food for free basically
um holy [\h__\h] though
um
i'm out of here
[Music]
phoenix invincible
i shall survive no matter what
i must win this fight
yes i'm tankanashi kiara
hi jinkins
sheep delivery yeah the burger is saving
my butt
[Music]
so much
exp yummy hi cafe
wow
it's so cute
the chicken attacks are so cute
at this point i see
this
um
lag as kind of like a
take a moment to think about what you're
doing moment
like a
slo-mo attack
like a matrix style
it's it's on purpose
it's a feature
trying to
you know because everything is really
stressful here
they want you to
chill for a moment
that's a good thing it's a good thing
[Music]
lowering fps strats on purpose
on purpose stress
english local stress
i'm ready
what do i upgrade now that forbids eliza
can i have a kill for bazilla
time for revenge
oh god
okay i would like to
clear the stage this time
okay at least it seems to only shoot oh
god
uh
sideways
so i think we're fine and it's rocking
walking into my fire into my lava so
we're good but i wonder if that laser is
a one-hit kill
yeah i'm just gonna stay below or above
yeah mm-hmm
this is the way no taxi no taxi
okay i can do it
survive
i'm sorry for looking senpai i love you
and i respect you and you're the reason
i found out about whole life in the
first place
what's the reason you guys found out and
gotten no found let's say found out
because that can be oh i did it two
different people
like finding out and then getting into
something
what
thank you
look out kelly kelly's trash tasting w
yeah a while ago when i asked this
question there was also a lot of those
answers
[Music]
oh scatman i have a [\h__\h] scatman
yeah that's that's that's a cute one i
like that one too
okay
and for me it's actually
um
kind of like
fukuki's
artists uh drew characters for like a
character for a game oh new new enemies
a [\h__\h] rat infestation
is that a word is that correct
ah oh there
oh there
yeah yeah
yeah i i really liked uh that character
and i liked the game and um
it looked so similar to fubuki senpai
you know and and then
maybe we should use this
kill them burn the rats
i thought i got rid of casper
and uh and then i saw oh there's like
another character that he drew called
fukuki that's a victor wait what that
what
yeah
yeah i really really was a big fan of
kavakaze and then i saw fupaki and i was
like oh wow cute killed oh so like what
what is this and then i kind of looked
into it a little bit and then i got
really really strongly into
into pequoros and five wow the rats
oh god
kill them all kill them all kill them
all
okay i feel like i've reached a stage
where i'm invincible like nothing can
hurt me
hell yeah
i understand why people play this game
now i think
it is fun
like the whole spam of everything is fun
what
[Laughter]
yeah
okay i'll go for
the book
nice to see some more new ones so
council is uh
doing
some appearances now
let's just see that
nice
keep it give it give it give it
thank you
level max oh we could max out the book
or
oh okay okay wow seems like everyone
wants
that
i trust you guys for today
um okay
wait i thought it was max that can still
oh i can still go in even further with
it
collaptam what do you mean collab time
[Music]
what's collab time
i feel like i've heard about that
don't upgrade past max max ranks are
important
different opinions huh
wait that arrow that you guys talked
about where is that arrow i don't i only
see my my direction arrow
or is it not do i just not have it right
now
[Music]
that not because minutes
that felt like
so long
no on a clearest stage
no item on the screen so no ira okay
i did pay attention to my health
no
it was almost 13 what 20 minutes is so
long
am i
am i really bad at this i feel like i'm
not so bad at it
okay so we go to the main menu and we
would do something with this right
idle costume
cute
yeah
i'm doing fine okay thank god
i wasn't sure because i i thought
clearing stages was easy
uh i can't fool with philadelphia so
that's a big improvement
okay okay
fan beam oh should a powerful laser beam
from the microphone horizontal only
these are new items that i can get
randomly
i suppose okay we have uh almost a
thousand
wow
[Music]
great job for second try thank you
should we buy upgrades or i don't think
i can do that because i need a thousand
almost gotcha should i keep it
then let's keep it
50 more yeah
wait for gacha okay
[Music]
oh there's i guess there's so many then
ah so currently you can get mint council
and hope and then later they're adding
gamers and some generations okay okay
should i try calling she's easy
easy mode you say
i mean we could yeah we could try some i
want to try
you know
let's try whoa
tacticals
nice noise
i always wanted to
try out enos tentacles
they're so cool they're so fancy
they're like louis vuitton tentacles
can you blame me
like designer tentacles
louis vuitton or gucci collaboration
when
honestly for inna i feel like we could
make it work
wow okay so we have new things here oh
colt for every target within 150 pixel
increased attack by five percent up to
50 percent uh-huh
summon
ow every five seconds owl creates a zone
of uh 40 dress to convert targets to
harmless taco dodges
okay
whoa
hey
i want to see that happening
i want to see them being turned into
harmless taco duchies
oh look at that that's so cool
uh okay let's make the tentacles
stronger
oh the tentacle actually has quite the
reach off
wait so those tacos are those my friends
know but they're still following me why
are they see-through
why are they see-through
oh i don't think
[Music]
okay so that's in a special attack i see
i see i see
[Music]
okay okay okay
does only not have that because i didn't
see anything like that with kiwawa
the hill when leveled up oh okay okay
eh two
oh i guess you know because
ina for example is not a tank
we wanna be careful and focus a bit more
on healing
than with kiwawa who has a lot of hp
anyway
so it's not so much of a concern
if if that's the case then we should
increase our
i suppose she is a tank
you guys said i'm the tank
he knows the tankiest
huh
uh
what
oh thanks for the burger
oh
i was try killing them
just one time i want to kill them
give me the kill
are you ready
maybe i need to activate my special
attack when those are there so
so that's so that i get the kill
all right
all right oh so they don't heal me now
there's so many of them
[Music]
it's fun though i like this
i like this character too they're
probably a lot of fun
you're an offensive tank
and she's a defensive tank
the axe is back psycho x
yeah there it is
swoosh
so many ghosts
yeah i'm scared of girls
we should have told each other ghost
stories at the
real meet up with myth i mean i don't
really know any ghost stories but you
know good and so um they seem to know
some ghost stories
should have had a spooky ghost story
telling time
you know it's a bugged tank
iris is a healing tank you are a dps in
a defense tank oh
interesting
missed opportunity a little bit yeah
ah
this is the one that we got before
moves slower slower the void oh
slower
my hp is not looking so good though
take take
okay
what do we want to upgrade um the
tentacle or the cycle x
a tentacle
gotcha thanks
i need a i need a burger
i need wait i have this i forgot
oh critical hit chance um by four
percent or cycle x
it's just psychopaths whoa whoa whoa it
goes on pretty long
we got those coins we want the gacha
we're gonna be doing katja after this
ah we can have the miasma again
yeah why not why not i'll take it
big big boy big boy
shrimp
i'm sure inna would love to eat that oh
it's gone nicer
[Music]
ina is bad with crits
spider cooking is worth it on inna
no i see okay
now
[Music]
myth
and myth i guess i'm not the only one of
the cult inna has a cult too
[Music]
oh god oh god
and i'm sorry i killed you i needed to
get used to us it was [\h__\h] laggy and
totally blaming it on that
40 coins i i think that's not quite
enough
so close
let's try callie
i see the girl
yeah the scythe is so cool damn the rage
and it goes all around
wow
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah i think i've heard uh kelly is very
beginner friendly and strong
like not not beginner not even beginner
friendly but like even even later on
[\h__\h] op
she was buffed to pee levels yeah what
the [\h__\h]
what about me
what about my character she wasn't
before
i see
okay
workaholic interesting i like how
you know everything is
so accurately related
to
the memories
made by fans
poor fans
everything is about
whole life that's nice what is this
lagoon
maybe maybe they can do something some
kind of update
for the lag because i don't think it's
my pc i mean i played i played alden
ring on this pc okay
i sure
uh
i don't think a pixel game like this can
be more resource eating it's not your pc
okay okay okay
and then i already i closed chrome and i
closed on oh
i closed
steam everything
kind of number crunching
it is your pc
and the other said it's not my pc
all right ooh what's this death when
defeating a target with side swing or
death there's a 20 chance to create an
explosion for 60 damage and a five
percent chance to ko
i am gonna die though death is gonna die
if i get many more hits oh
oh it just it just sucked them in
i would like some hp please
otherwise i'm [\h__\h]
[Music]
so ah it's a dps buff ah
okay so it's not really like some big
big big attack it's more like a buff
okay
i
i'll i need i need to help
[Music]
no heal everybody
oh nice nice nice nice okay okay
maybe this
what do you mean you did download it
yes i downloaded what do you mean
there we go coins
[Music]
why seriously that's what i was thinking
too and i
double the zero heal is still zero
healing hmm
we'll get there i am i am on the grind
i'm so close to death
i am i am very close to them
all right what do we have
um
let's still increase so i can stay away
from these
dangerous dangerous death traps
[Applause]
okay
okay okay
um
increase increase that damage
leg
leg is good we like the leg
we need to kill the shrimp
i'm sorry i'm sorry gouda oh there we go
i wanna go there but oh there's a purple
one whoa
whoa whoa whoa
explosion for ninety percent damage and
eighty percent okay all
right where is
[Laughter]
[Music]
we got the automatic collection does
that only pick up everything that's like
in my current
view field of view or also
everything
that's out of the
field of view
the whole map okay nice
i was wondering about that targeting
honda pixel take 20 extra damage
go for that oh
interesting
it shows me where the 100 pixels are
i guess
oh
i see it
the ones that are affected once they
walk into the circle they get this
shield down thing
defense down what is this with my hp
though still i need [\h__\h] healing
okay get get away from here no no no no
no no no no okay thank god wait let's go
on
i've been on this low hp for the longest
amount of time now
i don't know how i'm doing this
you you must admit at this point i'm
really good at dodging everything
[Music]
i need some kind of skill that heals me
was it just kiwa that had so many of
those or what
oh hello big tacos
[Music]
the horns um that would be nice
okay
[Music]
i don't know i want to get those
xp there
can they walk oh they can just walk for
that fence like that what [\h__\h]
[Music]
i'm just constantly running away from
them
okay this is over soon it's over soon
i'm sorry callie
i'm sorry but
oh
[Music]
death itself will be literally
dead soon
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh why is it free
why am i getting free
whoa
thank you
lucky
oh baby you're triple
shoot the powerful laser beam from the
microphone
increase damage by 40 let's [\h__\h] go
i don't want to die
[Music]
[Applause]
poor it's been a dream
i want to shield the thing i don't know
the laser
death bike yeah look at them they're
gonna kill me
they're right there
i'm scared mommy
which direction do i go
[Music]
did i kill them or what just happened
and dodged them nicely
okay oh my god
[Music]
there's
take oh
but the question is are we gonna raise
the food in time
before i die
[Music]
i see it i see the food i see the food
is right next to me if i go to the right
side
okay
okay didn't somehow i survived this this
stride of death
oh my god
now i feel strong now i feel strong
but clutch holy [\h__\h] okay what are we
upgrading yeah thank god maybe the
pillow kind of saved me
okay
okay okay
um
the feeding attack of the side swing or
death there's a few percent chance to
create an explosion for 128 damage ooh
one ten percent kale
okay
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh the lagoon oh that
was that that stick thingy that only
shoots in one direction oh
nice
frankie over shape magic
oh there we go we have the idol costume
we do special cool down by twenty
percent
[Music]
okay i don't need it
don't need that
i wanted to talk also about um something
i completely forgot in my recap
uh we went to the arcade
really [\h__\h] late at night on one day
uh wait what did i go for
okay
uh
and i
have
i go really rarely like i haven't been
to an arcade
besides maybe in japan but even in japan
um it's usually like
um like only for purikura because if you
go to uh
a game center an arcade in japan
um then there they have purikura
somewhere in the back
[Music]
if you guys don't know what purikura is
then look up
[Music]
tangent p u r i k u r
you will thank me and never forget about
it ever again
but it's basically a japanese cute photo
booth that has a lot of cute effects and
uh yeah you can write a lot of
write a lot of things and put stickers
and all that it's really cute because it
makes you look cuter it makes your legs
longer and it makes your your face
smaller and your eyes bigger
um
yeah i i had a long long long tangent
about that a while ago
and people really enjoyed hearing about
it
i loved putikuran so much
yeah i even i even once did i i don't
know if i told you that but i worked in
a i worked for a particular company in
japan before part-time
did i ever mention that
i did mention it
maybe i did
[Music]
oh hello what the [\h__\h]
ah
[Music]
hey for once i'm actually killing these
walls of enemies
yeah
[Music]
shoot yeah oh this is really useful
right now and still i get nothing for
that
[\h__\h]
okay so that we can get a stat up
i don't know if that's use uh
worth it yeah oh we have milk too
increases attack range of area type
weapons by 10 also increases pickup rate
is by 30 yeah why not
we're doing it
holy [\h__\h] she's speed right now the
speed is really useful
wow so yeah we went to an arcade
and um
it was one of those
round one
arcades
they there did you know that round one
is originally from japan
hp
[Music]
okay and
now we can upgrade
[Laughter]
one to two
two three two two three
awakened
[Music]
okay this is a book
yeah so round one because it's like
originally from japan it has like so
many
cute machines that are like rhythm games
and so many cute crane machines that
have super cute
super cute
uh plushies from japan and all that
so
but it was actually my first time
entering a round one like
they have them a lot in japan too but
they also have a lot of different
uh
game centers arcades in in japan and i
always entered the different ones and
like the sega sega
oh yes they they uh had vodka two yeah
with whole life songs i didn't try out
that one though
[Music]
the x one thing i didn't really
like about the these arcades arcades in
general i guess is that theirs
but now we can gotcha
[Laughter]
okay killed by the deadbeats that's just
sad
uh i was gonna say it's so noisy
it's so freaking noisy
do you want to try and get council
members i also hope because
we already have the myth members why
would we do them ah because duplicates
make them stronger but let's do uh let's
do council
[Music]
i feel like she would be really strong i
feel like she should be really powerful
[Music]
i want to try
okay
that was
not that was
i feel like they should make the kata a
little bit more like
riveting exciting like
more they should make me
shake and shiver about what i'm going to
get
okay orbit
become big die with the kanji of dai big
sounds good let's go
whoa
oh is that what what
what the
planet is that
i don't want to say anything stupid
jupiter okay
good that i didn't say anything because
i was not thinking of jupiter
oh
fancy fancy
i don't know let's start with gravity um
every five seconds creates a
gravitational blast that deals 125
percent damage damage is also increased
by area increasing effects
oh
it makes them go away from me
okay that already seems pretty up here
let's go
go do it yeah
i want to see that when there's a lot of
enemies around me
sorry
oh i like the art for the
skills
okay orbit let's do orbit
what was i saying oh yeah arcade um
so the first thing like i first had to
you know figure out what the [\h__\h] is
going on when we went inside
but um basically me and ahmed
we
um were kind of
this seems like we were kind of the moms
in uh
this situation oh don't you
what should i do speaker of space really
good oh no we'll get it again we'll get
it again
i'll do a psycho x
um
because
we me and emma we bought those cards
like we bought two cards filled it up
with money and then we kept on giving it
to the kids
[Laughter]
and yeah switching around like oh you
need a car now you want to play this
game all right here you go here's the
card
yeah yeah yeah yeah
nurse oh yeah should i get nurse's horn
then
yeah okay
oh it the blast doesn't work on them
sad oh lag
a bit okay well then i guess not
oh big
oh i should have done that well when
they were getting closer to me
but if i'm so big
am i not also
a bigger target for attacks no wait it
seems like
since i only collected what's really
close to me
did i still have a small hitbox
you're
invincible while big oh
let's go
all right that sounds good
then i like being big
very much
so me and amy bought cards and we loaded
them up with uh with money
and then the first thing that it was
used for guna immediately tried the
ribbon game machines
and she was really good at it obviously
of course
like i said speak up space there we go
no surprise to no one's surprise
and then i was like i don't know i don't
know what to do i don't know any of
these games i don't know what's fun
what's what's what's a good one
um
and i think enough was also like pretty
quickly
off to the river machines
yeah
they both look good at that kind of
stuff
not me
[Music]
shall we get the bucket
no
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] my hp stay away
[Applause]
da
yeah and then the first game that i
tried because like i was kind of like
unsure oh
is ahmed ahmed showed me um this this
dancing ribbon game
told me to try out that one but it
didn't even have like any songs on that
are new except for like
one k-pop song the rest was just random
songs and i never knew no i don't think
it was ddr
i think it was a similar one where you
step on the ground yeah but
um
i don't think it was dtr i'm not sure
anymore there were several ones
pump it up
i'm not sure but the songs were kind of
weird
um but there was as i said one from
black pink
black pink in your
that one i did that one
korean usually means pump it up uh-huh
but they only had like two or so
it wasn't even that many korean songs
so i tried it but i was so [\h__\h] at it
i was so overwhelmed by it and ame was
watching me
and then while i was doing it uh i think
like
me also joined to watch because i guess
she was done with her game
and i was feeling
kind of embarrassed because i was so
[\h__\h] at it
i panicked and i just stomped the whole
time randomly didn't know what i was
doing
[Laughter]
you know i'm a good dancer but like
with choreographies that i know
but
this was just like i had no idea what i
was doing
you're the best at actual dancing maybe
okay i'll take that thank you
i would like to think so
but then
uh because we accidentally i think
accidentally we loaded up the that
machine with three tries not just one
so after i was done
amen was like hey good at you want to
try
so
good and amen
tried the machines
and they were both a million times
better than me but they both already
like tried this kind of game before
previously
it was my first time my first experience
i was really [\h__\h] at it oh my god oh my
god oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my
god i'm actually really grateful for the
slow motion right now
oh sure
get out of here move move get out of the
way
ah
thank god
let's do gravity level three
nice so good timing i was waiting for
that i was shaking
shivering shaking so anyway good it was
really good ammo was really good too
almost seemed like um she just played
that
often times before
like she had some experience with it and
gouda seemed like she may have played it
before but she's also just good at it
because in general
she is
just
good at any kind of rhythm game she
really has that that talent that skill
oh orbit awakened we speak of space free
ariana little attacks damage increased
by 40 percent
one okay
there's a burger on the right side i
should go there
cycle
did you guys see that i was so close to
a good night's sleep
ah the clutch
the clutch
are you ready
[Music]
we can do
reduce delay between attacks by twenty
percent
acres lava area
we will do lava for now because our lava
bucket is really
not quite elite yet there we go
oh my god
don't touch me
so and then after that first game that
dancing game
i kind of
like
felt more comfortable like first i was
like i don't know what to do but then
after aman suggested a game for me to
play i felt more confident and i looked
around and i was like i want to play my
account i want to play mommycon i want
to play marika because there was a there
was a mario kart plays with the with the
wheels and it had four seats i think so
i wanted to play with four but all the
ones that joined me was ame and ina
so ami na and me
we played
a mario kart against each other it was
really funny but it was very different
from the usual mario kart
and
in the first round
i think ina won and then ahmed uh
went off close by to play something else
very close by
yeah
but she was still kind of watching us
and it was just me against inna because
i really really really really really
wanted to play one more time it was so
much fun
[Music]
try me try me
and then in the second run i want
against enya i want wario cards
hell yeah baby
even though i had no idea what i was
doing we both didn't quite know what we
were doing
because it was really different like
i don't know
yeah i didn't even know how to
uh
wait what was that
there were certain things i just didn't
know how to do
but it was fun nonetheless
yeah and then uh
i think alma was like she tried playing
some kind of stacking game and then
and then
oh we started playing so many different
games i played a game that i missed
i'mma kept on suggesting playing like
certain games to me because i didn't
know i didn't know my way around
and so i tried for example some kind of
karate game
that has like i think three
on each side so total six but three
um like things that you have to hit on
next to you on your side
uh
it's getting getting stressful here
like a reflex game yeah it was really
fast
and at first i tried to you know
actually like look at it closely
and um
smash everything accord hit everything
accordingly but then soon i realized
the reaction of these
hitting thingies the targets
was really low even though i was hitting
it pretty pretty strongly and my hands
started hurting but it didn't work so
well so then eventually i just started
like
hitting everything really aggressively
randomly without really looking at the
screen
that much and that worked much better
and then we played um
air hockey because i kind of wanted to
play air hockey so i played against
amethyst and i was once again really
really bad at it but i had a lot of fun
anyway
and i was screaming a lot i'm
i'm kind of like it seems like when i
play these kind of games
um i panic a lot and then when i panic i
scream just like in my streams i
i turn into monkey mode
and no not really competitive but yeah i
get really excited and i jump around and
i scream and i'm like
[Laughter]
yeah
um
so
that was fun
i think
maybe the milk hmm
[Music]
yeah
emma was really good at air hockey
so i panicked
and then i lost
uh and then kelly was close by so then
she
played against amen air hockey and holy
[\h__\h] guys
you know i've met kelly many times
several times
and
in many situations you know
and i've never ever
seen
cali like this before
her face
when she was playing air hockey
was so intense and
oh my god i'm done
[Laughter]
[Music]
was your dad serious yes yes she had
this death stare
and she like while when i was playing
and especially i'm a tool with the air
hockey we would like move around a lot
you know but but kelly was like
she kind of like
um
bowed
down
uh
lowered her upper body really close to
the air hockey table and then her arms
were in a really fixed position she
would never move her body or her arms
and her face was so close to the table
yeah yeah she leaned in she bent over
she she was so in the zone she was so
serious her face it was like her
eyebrows they were like she was like
wait she was like she looked like this
the whole time even when everybody else
around was laughing
no one could make her laugh she was so
focused and
and she was so good
she won against that man
because her defense was absolutely
insane you could not get that air hockey
pin past her
that was insane i've never seen her like
this before i was kind of scared like is
this kelly
it was impressive funny really funny i
had a blast watching that i was so i was
so excited by saying that like holy [\h__\h]
i was never ever so immersed in
like watching someone else play
something like this before
it was so funny man how much how many
coins oh we almost got a thousand again
we got a lot of coins from that
i think i'm gonna keep them until i have
a thousand again
and she claims she's not good at games
maybe she's better at games like that
that you play in real life you know like
the air hockey
you painted a really clear picture
really
i was hoping so um
[Music]
summer was pretty fun
should we
uh play her a bit more someone else
you can spend them then refund them oh
it's okay i'm gonna save them for now
that's right okay
oh
my god
we need more weapons that's for sure
because this pew pew pew i am constantly
missing
i should have no no shoot upwards
[Music]
oh
there we go
okay
huh
i'm trying to huh
trying to shoot
towards them
does she always shoot cycling she does
oh i thought i was doing something wrong
companion let's go
oh that's so cute
wait that is so adorable
now i can actually imagine
ahmet
in the
in the like in other games like this
holy [\h__\h] hold peter pan
what
do i look like i have time to pet a dog
uh i might try though
uh shoot one edition okay
i'm pressing p
does he have to be close to me
oh my god
i killed one
oh special attack do i want to keep it
wait a second i'll wait until i have a
few more
mobs around me needs to be close come
here
i'm pushing it
how close i have to be
huh
i don't know
i kept on i i was on p the whole time
i'm holding it yeah
anyway
so
where was i oh yeah the air hockey holy
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] that was incredible
so
besides that oh my god we tried so many
games wow it's so cool
oh it makes them stop wow now get food
okay
and we've tried
yeah you got to press and hold
what i'm doing
i can't
whatever forget it
you know i'm a cat person
oh
[Music]
um
critical hit by 10
let's go
or
i think we'll go for that i have to
stand still i'm busy right now maybe if
i'm [\h__\h]
invincible then i have some time to do
that
okay okay okay and then one time uh
me and ahmed played um what's it called
uh it was some kind of rabbit shooting
game where you hold a gun
you hold a gun
like the fps monsters that we are
shoot that way yeah yeah yeah yeah
that's right that's right that's right
yeah okay
uh it was not mario rabbit something but
it was some kind of rabbit game yeah we
were sitting in front of the big screen
and then shooting the
infected zombie rabbits or something
like that
[Music]
yeah
that was
that was really easy though that game
was really easy and then we played um
all together at some point because at
least that one oh triple
baby
thank you
we played
and
okay let's add that to the slow motion
we play this i don't know what it's
called i'm gonna i'm gonna recommend it
because i think if i understood
correctly it was actually free
some kind of
uh ball shooting game where you shoot it
up towards
a lane and then it lands in some holes
ski-ball yeah that's what it was
ski ball skipper
i need a dad
urgently
ski ball
but i shot the balls
very aggressively in the first round i
was actually pretty good about it i had
uh
one or two
lucky hits
and
i'mma goes bro
yeah
i had a few lucky hits
where i got a lot of points but then
besides that i was mostly bad at it and
then in the second and the third round i
got more aggressive because i thought
maybe the key
is to
[Music]
throw the ball
as as aggressively as you can but then
oh that's not fair that's not fair
that's not fair
i can only shoot sideways and they're
coming from the tab at the bottom
ramen's tough
okay my pistol shot has awakened
uh
oh my god okay so yeah i was pretty bad
and then i shot it really hard
but it was fun at least that we could
play a game altogether uh yeah
what else did we play most of the time i
think most of the time gouda
and inna were playing the rhythm games
and oh god we played so many games
what did we play
holy [\h__\h]
basketball oh yeah callie was really
good i was just watching that kelly was
playing that with i think ina
i'm gonna die i'm so sorry i'm so sorry
amir uh
[Music]
yeah
i'm dead soon
they just want inna's back where they
won't get in here
this is not the place
oh god let me get out of here
okay okay okay
don't touch me don't touch me
[Music]
where's his horn
i understand now
i understand everything
i'm failing
yeah
i'm alive
i'm still alive and okay maybe not the
right time to use it i don't know
uh critical 20 [\h__\h] percent guys
man
wow
those crits
i'm not hitting anything though
oh
nice dodge
oh my god
okay i got the food
let's drop some buckets
nice nice nice guys
bubba is hitting yeah i think boba's the
only thing that's hitting anything at
all
[Music]
i should like when i shoot sideways i
feel like i should continuously go
upwards or downwards
not sideways
so that i can kind of get more range
here
bubba mbp bubble fast i don't even i
don't even see him i'm so occupied with
looking at amit
[Music]
oh it doesn't stop those
special ones that come in walls huh
weapons deal 25 percent increased lava
area by 20 decreased area by 25 percent
i'm trying to remember what else we
played oh at some point at the end
um
it was like me and ahmed together trying
to use up the last few points on
on our card because it wasn't really
enough points to use
it for some proper games but apparently
it was enough
to
play the crane games
oh yeah i was like in the dreaming jitsu
music video yeah
true
oh sorry i didn't choose the one that
you guys wanted
and
and ahmed i don't know i felt like she
didn't say it specifically but i felt
like she was trying to get something for
me
[Music]
okay yeah really tasty
really sweet because she tried so hard
like we would fail at one machine and
then she would quickly go to the next
one and was like what do you think about
this one what do you think about this
one you want you like this one
uh what do you think how should i
how should i get this one like i was
mostly watching her sometimes i would
try myself but most of the time uh
i uh almost doing the the hunting
what did you want plushies
yeah we were looking at some cute
plushies um
um we tried her best but in the end we
failed we didn't get anything
they were really hard to get did you
guys know that i know maybe it's a thing
in america too but my experience from
japanese
gaming uh
japanese arcades
is that the staff will help you you can
request um
them to help you
or
sometimes they even like help you
without
without you even asking them
yeah god's hand look kind of like that
but like it really happens a lot
in
the arcades in japan
and they put it into really easy to grab
positions for you
really really really freaking helpful
american our kids are more raped
they just reset in america
that's so sad i was i was wondering you
know when we were struggling with the
crane games
if we could maybe ask the staff close by
uh
if they can like help us out but
i'm glad i didn't ask because i guess
they don't really do that in america
they will sell you price prices if you
pay a ton
aha
yeah
i don't know well anyway i will go for
[Music]
i'll
go for this one
in round one they don't really
maybe i should have asked
[Music]
it's just a scam anyway the sad thing
was that
um
at the end
at the end uh
i'm trying not to die
i should use this
[Music]
yes yes so at the end we wanted to use
uh the points or tickets i guess that
we've accumulated on our cards
um to get some items but the item shop
was already
closed
so sad
i'll go for the body pillow now
i'm scared about dying i want that
shield
yeah but the ammo told me that the cards
can still be used like
and like on another day
but yeah so i hope ahmed will use the
cards to get something nice from it
uh
[Music]
oh wait i got this
okay okay okay okay okay okay
i went back in that direction because i
was feeling like there might be yeah on
the bottom there's something i need to
pick up
ah
spider clinging level max i never went
that far with that nice
i might get to 20 minutes swim on it
okay
elite lava bucket
okay i need some food
oh okay [\h__\h] off
sorry i love you guys
feel so bad
hurting you
oh i'm back to full hp let's go
[Music]
i'll keep the special skills a little
bit later
[Music]
focus on lava
oh okay okay okay
food i'll stay close to here because
right now i don't need the food
stay close by i'll remember this one
on the right top right
here lava there you go
a bright is
food top bread is food
i'm getting further and further away
from it now though
i guess i don't need it
i feel like with this
everything's so scattered oh was that
but i only shoot sideways
but this is
that's [\h__\h] up how do i hit it
i'm please
oh and she's not shooting anymore
oh god holy [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
yeah i just need to
make her walk over my
my lava i guess
that's very difficult she she don't
shoot
let's move straight left alright
good cat good cat
i did it i survived
even though i was barely able to do
damage like only the miasma like all the
extra things but i couldn't shoot her at
all
on my own
um
all right oh we have uber sheep
for the gold anvil
is it fall did you guys see it i didn't
see one
i wonder where it is
follow the arrow ah that one okay okay
i see it now
there's still so many weapons that we
didn't get yet
how about
see now this one also shoots sideways
but i already shoot sideways i want
something that goes more around me i
think
so i can cover my bases you know my
bases speaking of bay there it is
bales is everywhere cora
i mean cool
what does that mean
there's only two things like
sparkling
press that
are you sure
that doesn't work for me you mean space
right
[Music]
ah okay combine these two we have seven
items only aha
wow collaboration of elite level bucket
and spider cooking elite cooking may
have severe unknown side effects okay so
how does it look oh oh
now instead of the level
holy [\h__\h] i'm covering like everything
oh [\h__\h]
now the miasma is not around me but it
gets dropped like the lava bucket
that's crazy
that is crazy
oh yeah come at me wow
okay i'm doing it i'm finally doing it
the 20 minutes are finally mine
let's go
easy no two i'm too op now
that's really hot on my tamaya
something that she would be cooking
oh my god
so you'll see
collabs are game changer
interesting so at level seven you can do
these fancy collabs not a huddle i like
it
don't jinx it
and we'll be fine look at us
even though i was having troubles with
amith at first
now it's easy peasy
oh
okay don't forget to hydrate
[Music]
all the
up what's up we want to fight fight me
try me
weak as hell
defense so low
crony's defense so low i always knew it
i knew it from the times i collabed with
her
it was so obvious
what should we do
oh we can even more
uh make this even stronger
[Music]
i'm not even using my skill anymore
because i don't need it
i don't need my special skills
[Music]
oh wait what the [\h__\h] is going on
what's going on with these clocks
don't run away
don't you dare run away
it's crony time
it seems to oh
it's the
king clock
king club king kong king clock
has anyone ever noticed that see how
fast that one died oh my god
[Music]
okay
let me try to remember
for the arcade if there was anything
else and i remember though i forgot the
things ah there was one game i really
wanted to play but we couldn't
ah minecraft
that was a minecraft game
couldn't play that one though
i don't want to play that minecraft in
arcane
yeah minecraft dungeons or something
like that minecraft
i think it's not the same as minecraft
dungeons
but by the way i did want to play
minecraft dungeon sometime on my channel
i should
also also also speaking of games i want
to play because we talked about playing
catherine
i realized i actually i bought the game
for ps3
ages ago it's on my shelf actually now
i'm wondering if i play catherine should
i just use that version
what do you guys recommend a different
version
uh
if i wanna play casper in on stream
what do you think
oh by the original oh i'm not sure which
one it is
[Music]
oh my god
because i already have it so i might as
well use it right i never played it
though i just bought it because i was
thinking oh one day one day i will play
it
full body version
probably the original
ps3 would be original ah okay okay okay
yeah i'm i'm asking which which console
or so you think i should play it on not
which version
[Music]
we got headphones
wait oh yeah i have one more item slot
headphones
i think let's go headphones
every stream i need some headphones
[Music]
oh god oh god
oh my god oh my god wait i should have
just
oh my god oh look at that look at that
look at that
yo i was so close to that again
q what's q again
what did i put on q again didn't i
change
huh
[Music]
there we go that way
wow i'm number 40 i don't think i was
ever this high level before no no way
this is definitely the highest it was
oh you mean the song
okay
level five or increase the bomb or the
body pillow
[Music]
bye pillow
yakuza
shrimp
now i see the reference finally
okay
[Music]
that's a tough one
oh there's so many presents here
speaking of brandon's my birthday is
soon after this stream i'm gonna upload
the next countdown video
so
keep your eyes open for that turn on
your notifications to my channel
sounds like such a youtuber
i think i got used to sideways
shooting yeah
[Music]
they're always on thank you
yeah yeah yeah
how far am i for 20 minutes is anybody
counting
you any more owls cute more
i can do it i can do it i can do it i
can do it i can do it
[Music]
sideways sideways
there's a timer
where the top blue bar one wasn't that
my xp bar
okay
[Music]
oh sorry i didn't care much because it's
almost over anyway
saplings
saplings don't touch me
the owls can touch me now i like owls
i just want to fluff them
i want to catch an owl
into an alka play before but it's been
so long and i don't really like the
whole
um
the lack of space for them
[Music]
oh no oh i want a bird attack
that wasn't too bad
where's this timer that you guys
mentioned
[Laughter]
about to die
and because of that i kind of want to
use max hp up
the middle of the screen whatever i
can't look at that right now
blind show yeah yeah sure tell me
say whatever you want
i like that that is literally the only
food option you have in this game
very healthy as long as there's some
tomatoes and lettuce in there you know
some coins
that one looks really evil what happened
to you what did they do to you
who hurt you
they're done for
how long are four minutes what the [\h__\h]
it's the longest four minutes of my life
[Music]
and twirls and twirls oh whoa whoa those
look like
those
those saganas
they
remind me of what's that
oh japanese
that the one that comes out of the tv
the horror movie one
yeah am i the only one who thinks of
that because of the
i don't know it's kind of spooky
looks kind of spooky to me man
i shall let's max it out baby
ah and now i see the timer
and now i see it oh hamburger
um
holy [\h__\h] i don't even know what's going
on anymore
[Music]
close
the end is near
[Music]
it's so tinted that i'm clearing this
with ame
isn't it
well we must be making a lot of money
from this 1200
let's go
yeah come at me no matter how many
you're gonna send me i'm too too strong
too overpowered
try me
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] never mind never mind
what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] what the
actual [\h__\h]
what the actual [\h__\h] what's going on
what's going on what's going on
[Music]
uh
what the [\h__\h] is going on
[Music]
i'm doing good though
my hp is looking good
yeah my special okay no problem
oh my god 30 seconds
[Music]
let's go let's get out of this hell hole
mamma mia
bubba are you okay how is bubba
surviving this
oh my god
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
wait did i not clear it does it just
continue
run down now defeat small ammo i thought
it was just okay i guess there needs to
be a bus
um
oh my god
why you say run can i not kill her
it's it's funny how the last boss is
just ahmed herself amir versus ahmed
wait where did she go
oh there she is
[Music]
does it slow down on me too
oh look at that
oh yeah
what does this one look like oh
collaboration of bl booking psychology
and this boys love how
[Music]
she almost got me she almost got me she
almost got me
crazy that girl i'm telling you she's
crazy
[Music]
my first stage hi meow
my cats sound like
they're suffering
you okay
well
sometimes when i scream a lot they're
like
meow i think i need to check for a
second give me one second
are you guys okay
i think they're i think they're just
meowing at a fly
probably
yeah i think chonglis was meowing at the
fly that she couldn't reach because she
was on top of the kitchen god they're
looking looking up to the ceiling anyway
i'm so proud with level 50 free
score
365k
whole coins gained 1355 plus 830 free
48. yay oh study classes increases x
begin by 10
thank you guys that was so much fun
yeah
i want to play more though i think
still early
i want to clear one more stage
increases normal attack damage by 30
percent but lose 50 percent critical
chance gorillas paul that's like out of
a horror movie too no
injection type oh no i guess it's like a
reference to kanata
[Music]
you know what time it is
we got a new one
it's gotcha o'clock exactly bails
another new one no dupes here baby which
i just probably jinxed myself so let's
go third one
[Music]
ah okay now okay i i drink myself that's
okay
who's the strongest out of santa bales
and cronies
[Music]
tell me
because i want to play them
next sana
bay bay okay
it's been 16.
she looks like her speed yeah would be
very high
play nice for rather die the number on
the die determines the damage what
that's so random
wow that's fun
we already played sana so i guess yeah
let's go with them let's go with bayden
let's do another run
with bay
baby baby
[Music]
i'm doing um a snapbox review
if you saw my schedule um i'm doing an
australian stack of snack box review
with snacks that bales sent me
from australia it's a huge box holy [\h__\h]
i haven't opened it yet because i want
to open it on stream
but it's really big and um she said
she's gonna she's gonna try to call in i
think it's
uh
gonna
be a little bit of a difficult time for
her
because i think she's currently still in
america but she's gonna try
so
yeah it's like a low-key collab maybe
but i'm not gonna guarantee it i don't
wanna put any pressure on her because
in america it's gonna be like in the
middle of the night i chose a time that
would be good for like
australia because of my snack box
reviews
i wanted to be
[Music]
um
at a time that makes sense for the
people
from the country of where the snack
boxes from makes sense right makes sense
okay
uh
what do we go for
i think i want the spider cooking
makes sense yeah yeah yeah big brain
yeah then on that day we have two
streams as well
uh
one with elena i think was on that day
and then we have before that we have the
snapbox where it's really early so i'm
sorry you american viewers or canadian
viewers and so on you're probably going
to have a hard time watching it i'm
sorry
gum in the story
oh
lag play that dice
i'm hardly hitting them
and when did when a dice
stays
like stops moving
[Music]
i wonder how
if it goes through someone
ah that seems to do damage too
and then boom
if they walk into it after it stopped
i'm assuming
it does no more damage or does it
that's what archives are for yeah
vodka and euroscope two dice oh
now now we're talking
die still does damage if it's still ah
okay okay
okay
oh yeah i saw that now
oh wait my hp
but
well great i didn't know what was going
to happen crack the clip oh
critical hands will roll the same
percentage chance again to deal an
extended critical hit
dealing two times damage
make way for the red queen
because i need to go pick up some
burgers really quick
where are the burgers
[Music]
i'm going to die
i don't find a solution quickly please
give me food
where food
a big boy coming
actually i need to go to an idol meeting
but i'm too excited to go and now we're
in the middle of something if we die
then i guess i have time to go but now i
cannot possibly go
[Music]
are you ready
oh what's this down under
why that's like the dancer no
isn't that
i know i can pause but still i don't
wanna
should we go from down under you can
shoot up and down
oh wait that's interesting
[Music]
people say it's really good okay okay
i trust you
i mean we have to experiment we have to
try out these characters see what they
can do
pretty nice
i'm gonna die
[Music]
oh now it's shooting
huh
i can shoot in any direction okay that's
good thankfully
sorry i'm just going for
anything at this point i feel like i've
learned that i need to
focus on certain items and skills
sometimes
these wrapped ng reduce our attack
damage by 15 but increase crit chance by
30 percent
i love me some crits
wow those dyes are so powerful
oh we're getting already so close to
maxing out that weapon what the hell
[Music]
we'll try again in a second
brb
yeah
i'm back
oh
the screen that i'm coming back to
is very saddening
oh
what
why are there pickles what's going on
why why why why why
what's happening
welcome back thank you thank you
i want to
give bails another chance
i don't want to give up yet on her you
guys say she's strong i want to see that
in action
i mean the special attack already
already
makes me think she's very strong so
we'll see
[Music]
oh lag
there's nothing on the screen i don't
know why you're lagging
taco's fleeing the tacos didn't let what
happened
what happened while i was gone she's the
hardest to use
whales is the hardest to use but then
she makes up with it then i guess
because you guys said she's the
strongest
[Music]
tacos lost their mind after enos bring
i can see that her critical cuts are
insanely powerful
[Music]
yeah she seems to focus a lot on those
crits huh
they really made every character so so
different from one another
so much variety and like
fighting style
really amazing i wonder how long they
worked on it do you guys know did they
ever did they ever mention it
how long they worked on this game
[Music]
it's very well designed yeah
the art is cute too [\h__\h] sorry i walked
right into that
four to five months wow
wow that's really fast
impressive and now they're working on
more members i wonder if one day we'll
have all of them available
[Music]
that was fun
um but [\h__\h] is not looking good
uh lose no we don't lose hp
even holsters are getting at it wow
oh that's fun
yeah we need more weapons i need to
protect myself
stay away from me
you don't want to challenge a rat i've
tried it but they are invincible
i've tried it myself in real life i had
rats in my ceiling aka casper i i mean i
still don't know if it was rats or mice
but
i i'm gonna assume it was rats because
they were just so
[\h__\h] invincible
i couldn't do anything about them i got
professionals to help me
ordered by the owner of the of the house
and yet i was never able to get rid of
them never
most likely rats mice are pretty
tenacious really
[Music]
i was really like obnoxious at first
like ah it was
i don't i always like in my mind i made
like i laughed about you know
those
like in in
tv shows like
a comic what's the name for it again
comic tv shows i don't mean animes i
mean like uh
cartoons yeah thank you
in cartoons where like the ladies get on
the table and of the kitchen table when
rats are running around
but
then when it happened to me i was just
as freaked out about it even though i'm
thinking like why i mean
it's not
not such a big deal
it's just rats
oh we're gonna increase egg speaking but
ten percent that's quite a lot but i
don't know if we want that
tom and jerry yeah
just like in tom and jerry
it's probably more to shock if something
suddenly carries around yeah
and i i don't i just don't want it to
like get too close to me you know
she'll get the bucket
i think you want the bucket
oh my god so much xp finally
okay
yeah uh don't want it to like crawl up
my leg or something oh my god oh wait
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
there we go
all is good again
all the same
oh wait i should have used my skin
sometimes i forget about it the special
skill
[Music]
that's such a pretty effect yo
i didn't even hold on for that long it's
just it was just four minutes
okay i want to give cronini a chance
let's become a clock that was out of
nowhere
let's try this oh
oh
that's interesting wait
it's like a clock it moves like a clock
oh my god
but other directions like somehow random
like one will always go in that
direction that i'm looking at but the
other one
goes wherever the hell it was
interesting
small hand is random aha
well that's not bad
i like them they look really cool
tick tock
time is ticking
if you guys have some good advice
for how to fix the legs
let me know maybe i'll play it again and
i'll try my best to
fix it until then
[Music]
because
i don't know what it is i'm not running
anything on my pc right now
try glow stick okay next time i get it
offered to me maybe
time bubble every 10 seconds create a
small time bubble that freezes targets
in time preventing them from moving or
attacking
oh nice
oh there you go
it's all turned dark blue and they
stopped moving fancy
they must have had a lot of time a lot
of time i would just say a lot of fun
creating the game
also did you guys see like akua senpai
has like a or it already came out i'm
not sure
what
wow
a visual novel coming out
did you see that
what is this what is this what is this
wow
cool i don't know what's going on on the
screen right now
you saw it hey you didn't know
it looks really cute like she's the
she's the main character and if i
understand correctly there's no other
girls that you can try to romance she's
the only girl but it looks really really
pretty
i saw some
only in japanese language sadly
ah well then time to learn you know
language shouldn't be stopping you from
finding love
[Music]
i bet it'll get translated
i don't know about that
[Music]
ah wait i'm dying i looked at the chat
for too long
hey maybe i could play it and then
translate it to you guys
[Laughter]
wait can i check something really quick
ah [\h__\h]
i closed
the gun
i might die anyway i'm at five hp
[Music]
okay
[Laughter]
okay and what should i go for clock
hands or perfection while hp is full
increased attack speed pickup by 33
percent i also increase haste increase
and basically increase everything and
then chronic up the increased speed and
hits by temperature holding the grid
what even is haste
that's a scale at the very bottom but
i'm not sure what it does
get it i'm gonna die i'm gonna die
shingles
[Music]
i'm not sure if i like the clock hands
because
it feels like it's too random i don't
know where it will go
attack speed oh
i see
ah we'll try again though
i want to give up oh nice double kill i
want to give up to easily
[Applause]
nice
and it feels like the hitbox is so small
with the
these spiky
clock hands
[Music]
feels kind of difficult
and it gets larger by a lot oh that's
that's good i guess
[Music]
i'll try to make them as big as possible
then crony will have the biggest clock
heads
anybody has ever seen
okay now i've listened to the song first
for
three hours
now i'm sorry but suspect i'm getting a
little bit tired of you
um
somebody said glow stick before it's a
nearby target and then spins back to
player
why not
looks like a boomerang
it's literally a boomerang
[Music]
feeling alone
feeling of love feeling of love
oh
tell him the strangest part yes we need
a sparks remakes in here
i want to hear sparks in this in this
style in this remix style yeah
have you tried windows mode i am in
windowed mode
oh [\h__\h] maybe i should have chosen a
different weapon
[Music]
i need more weapons
like i'm putting these shrimps on a
skewer skewer
wasn't there an 8-bit box yeah i think
it exists i must have listened to it
before
now we have the time bubble back again
oh
still not quite sure what's happening
when i use this
oh okay okay okay
but it looks really powerful and strong
[Music]
you can turn off the music yeah yeah
yeah i saw they also like the creators
one of them they were like yeah feel
free to listen to something else
[Laughter]
i will upgrade the glow stick
sorry guys for the disappointment
oh perfection while
perfection aka
a synonym for crony
and i haven't talked to crony in a while
huh
i wonder if she'll call in tomorrow
tomorrow
i can't believe it's [\h__\h] time oh my
god tomorrow is the countdown stream to
my birthday
i
uh
it's not really a countdown in my time
zone it's a countdown in a japanese time
zone actually
um there's i already know yeah tomorrow
a lot of oh there we go a lot of the
japanese
members are calling in
yeah
i'm excited
of course english members will be
calling into indonesian members
everybody i've i've taken a lot of a big
time slot like a three hour time slot is
what i'm planning currently
so everybody has time lots of time to
talk to me and i'm thinking of doing
like uh some kind of wheel too like a
topic wheel for the shy people or so
topic or
or i don't know i'm not sure i didn't
make it yet
uh i might just
copy something similar to what fauna did
so what does it do
there we go nice soup
sounds like a good idea yes
yes
i think so too
should we level up time bubble or the
nurse's horn or should we add a new web
a new weapon
i think we'll add a new one
oh there we go now we got the clown cats
level four mm-hmm
[Music]
now
ah
so many choices
to
the fan beam
okay yeah we gotta make it stronger
strong
crony
i know you could do it
so what do you guys be watching my my
calling countdown frame tomorrow
it's such an exciting time the countdown
and then the following day we'll have
the big big birthday concert i'm so
excited
i'm so excited
what time is it
oh i don't know what what time zone
you are in but tomorrow the countdown
thing starts at uh 11 pm jst
i think it was something like 11 a.m est
or so
at 10 am 10 am is to 7 am yeah it's
really early for you guys i'm sorry but
it will go on for a while so
please say hi
i'll be at work but there's always a
vlog here
[Music]
now
i'll be tuning in for sure thank you
vote live
what time gmt uh gmt plus two i think
was 4 p.m
i think
oh i'm so fast
[Music]
actually when i think about cronie and
i've never met her before but when i
think about her i feel like she's
someone who moves
really slowly
who takes her time haha
when moving around
the world walking very slowly
taking everything
very slowly because she also kind of
talks slowly
gracefully perhaps i'll have to see if
she really walks gracefully one day i
have to go check that out
i guess we'll make the clock hands even
bigger oh sheesh
even bigger
[Laughter]
what time bubble croycopter
even bigger
oh my god
and now i think i kind of want some
healing though
it's getting dangerous
oh burger dough
didn't even need it at this point in
time but thanks thank you so i'll go for
the nurse's horn
just to
give me some security nets you know
oh god you're broken nice
oh my god i'm scared i'm scared
i won't die we're only five five and a
half minutes for you
does time pass really slowly in this
game or what
it must be rigged or something why am i
running away from them
attack attack
it does pause ah that's that's true i
guess yeah
that could be it clock hands away
decrease damage by 50 stone targets for
0.5 seconds
wow they are bigger
sorry i kind of ran out for all that um
i will survive though
i will
i do kind of want to see a combination
of the glow sticks and the fan beam
they they are both light blue so i feel
like they will fit
it's just
so satisfying
oh my god
everybody's so fast
[Music]
i'm just gonna run away from all that
it's too stressful
gotta take it easy
take it one at a time don't stress
yourself out guys
you feel like everything's just too much
oh then you could also activate your
super special skill
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
so creepy they're so creepy
those those them
bubbas look like they would walk into
the store
and steal something or there they would
stare at you
in the subway
and you wouldn't know why but they just
they just stare at you forever
give you the death stare oh my god i'm
dying
the bubbles killed me
[Music]
crony
it's so tough man
wow how many coins 606
don't you
i do want one more run
yeah we should try to win with kiwawa
i want to clear the stage once with
kiwawa
i need upgrades
okay
what do we get for kiwawa
ah good attila didn't try gonna hmm
[Music]
but i want to win once with kiwama let's
let's try that and then we can try out
good uh
damage
attack up
it's 300
i can't buy that much i can buy one more
[Music]
attack spin coin
for future ah now i don't have enough
for that
twitch
crit or speed
speed is
kind of cheap wow
movement speed by six percent per level
movement speed i feel like was really
helpful once i was faster with certain
characters
i feel like it helped me a lot
okay
let's do that for now
and we'll see how far we get
kilometers me again
hey how you doing sorry i tried out some
other characters but
you're awesome now i have so much
experience
that i feel like
we can do this
you and me together kiwawa
the dream team
kiana plus kiwawa
stronger than ever before
next gen
strength
overpowering all right we're at least
already kind of noticeable so
i shall go
for the phoenix shield first
[Music]
and then i want the fire behind me i
feel like it's a little bit too early
for the fire
there's barely any any enemies here
anyway
phoenix sword
[Music]
easy easy easy i feel like i'm already
better at this than the first couple
tries with kiwawa
however
my thumb that's on my spacebar the whole
time
is starting to hurt
[Music]
let's add a cycle x so we have some more
weapons
don't stop moving oh yeah don't stop
don't stop just going your own way
i'm excited to show you guys the sparx
choreo
it's really cool
it's really fun
it's really really active
[Music]
we need to make a petition to buff
kiwawa is it like what we saw dokomi was
the same choreographer
but definitely went for a different
style like for heart challenger i wanted
a really energetic
idol like cute korean um but for sparks
it was more like less [\h__\h] dance a
little bit feminine
and
um yeah the focus is just on dancing and
a lot of energy too um
but definitely different style and dance
moves while heart challenger was so i
don't like spark system like maybe a bit
towards k-pop a little bit
not quite it's more like
there's definitely a lot of normal
normal dance while we're talking about
dancer here comes the dancing skill
yeah
[Music]
should we um a book
um
yes
oh and hello
um
sword upgrade
oh they're coming
oh oh wait i need to go back there
wait wait wait wait
wait i'm i'm i'm i'm all my way i'm on
my way
but there's so many of these mobs
[Music]
cause she finished my work i have with
amit with alma i did
it was
pretty cool
[Music]
a lot of fun the ending was really
dramatic
there we go psycho x thank you
thank you thank you
[Music]
yeah i did too when i was playing with
almond got a lot of collabos
two two actually i think was it two
i think it was two
oh i cleared everything so nicely
i'm good at cleaning in this game unlike
in real life but
i did some cleaning before the stream
and now i'm gonna do some more when the
stream is over because my my sleep
schedule got really [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
although i do need to wake up a little
bit tomorrow i have something to do
before
uh the stream i think
[Music]
you guys still am into max of sword all
right all right all right all right i'll
listen to you
all righty sleep no i'm getting enough
sleep it's just uh
it has my sleep schedule has been like
pretty decent for a while
and then now i really messed it up like
when i was in america i was basically
forced to wake up early anyway because
there was so much to do
didn't get much sleep in general while i
was in america just so busy you know
before that too i feel like my sleep
schedule was pretty decent for a while
unexpectedly unexpectedly no it's not
the jet lag it's just that one night
where i woke up in the middle of the
night and then
even though i fell asleep so early and
but then you know sometimes
sometimes i wake up and then
my brain decides i don't want to sleep
anymore and that messed it up because
then
i'm
i went back to sleep at like 7 00 am
yeah
so today as well i woke up at like
3 p.m
or half past 3 p.m
but oh well
i still
got some things done anyway
surprisingly i went to the store
and
i should use that
yeah
i went to the store and then i bought
some things that i needed
and it was like
they were like like i saw two different
cases
of two like relatively young looking
boys like okay maybe not boys teenagers
like they were like maybe 17 18
20 maximum
uh who were like trying to steal stuff
from the store like i was you know just
walking
um
walking down the stairs
minding my own business and suddenly
like
two
strong looking men ran past me and i'm
like what the [\h__\h] is up was what's the
problem with you
cutting off my
um the path in front of me and then i
noticed i was watching them and they ran
after those two
young
teenagers
uh
and stopped them and they pulled out
their badge and they're like
you stole something didn't you suddenly
done
check your pockets show me what you got
in your pockets and everything
oh scary
no it wasn't in america no no no no no
i'm talking about today
i it's not something i see all the time
though in austria
[Music]
huh
but i saw that twice today in that one
store
in the same store
like while i was walking out of the
store i saw police officers
uh standing three police officers
standing next to two guys sitting on the
on some
chairs because they got caught for
stealing something
what you doing man what you doing
seems like that store has good security
then though
cause they're busting everybody
finally
fire fire fire fire
[Music]
upgrading the axe oh god i need to be
careful about my hp right now
ah
oh wait i have my skill ready i'll
activate that
[Music]
i need to find food
um
maybe i should activate uber sheep level
two
now stuffy glasses
one headphones okay
all right i trust you guys
i trust you
don't betray my trust
[Music]
i think i want the body pillow
where the [\h__\h] is the food
[Music]
i'm literally the [\h__\h] potential of
kfp why am i having troubles getting
food
i should be surrounded by
the food at all times
oh sometimes a little prayer can help
huh
guys you know
you know when i swoop i saw something
really funny today
um
apparently
uh in in texas
on the coast wait texas has a coast
i didn't realize
um
there's
there's really creepy [\h__\h] dolls
being washed up to the coastline did you
guys see that
it's like those those baby dolls
so
creepy they have like barnacles and [\h__\h]
in their eyes it's really [\h__\h] creepy
yeah apparently they have there have
been found like 40
in recent times
ford isn't that weird like what
i was thinking maybe
maybe
maybe there was like some delivery of
dolls that kind of like
like got like the ship fell apart
but then they're different though
they're not all the same dolls
so
why
if it was all the same dolls you would
think it was some kind of shipment right
but it was like all kinds of different
ones and even one doll with
its mouth very wide open so that is
confusing
uh
but
what the [\h__\h]
is so creepy
you looked it up
i don't know what the hell is going on
there
don't throw that kind of [\h__\h] into the
ocean
[Music]
what are you throwing into the ocean man
stop polluting the ocean with that [\h__\h]
the creepy ass [\h__\h]
i mean i'm not the type of person who
like feels really creeped out by dolls
in general like
i i don't care about them that much
um but seeing them like so [\h__\h] up
from
from the ocean that's that's creepy
that's creepy indeed
i'm really scared of those
i don't think you need to be scared of
dolls they're just dolls
like it from a container ship that lost
a crate
yeah that's what i thought too but then
wouldn't they all look the same
like that's the only solution to me that
makes sense
chucky i never watched that i think i
know it's about this chucky murder doll
or whatever though yeah
i wanna combine the books with the axe
if possible
please
corrupt soon
[Music]
oh
i'm being surrounded i know
[Music]
i'm good i'm good i'm okay
i'm okay
i'm fine
[Music]
pick a direction run yeah that's what
i'm about to do oh my god
um
ah here psychoaction yes
oh god they're still
coming
they're still coming go away go away go
away
they're about to teleport their butts
away i think
oh no we cleared that up pretty nicely
yeah
worth it not running away look at my hp
i'm doing fine
okay
[Music]
i'm sorry
sorry i hurt you i love you you know
that
you're so cute you guys are so cute
oh so cute
but you won't get past tension no no no
you're not gonna leave your shift yet
your shift is not over
do we want the shield yeah
[Music]
there's so much exp holy [\h__\h] and we're
at 10 minutes
we're 10 minutes halfway through
where's the halftime show
[Music]
almost almost there
why don't you hurt us more what if you
love us why don't you hurt us more what
you're asking me to hurt you more
muscle hystic little [\h__\h]
[Music]
so much food oh my god it's all the
cadavers
of my chickens
[Music]
oh mom
okay okay okay okay okay okay i got it i
got it i'm fine i'm fine just stay away
i'm not gonna be killed by fogo key
again
it's so fluffy though look at that
fluffy tail
stay below stay below
stay still stay below oh
[Applause]
oh
last time we um combined the book with
something else right or was it the same
was it the same
oh
my god
it was the same okay okay okay
so now
we could add um
we could do spider cooking with lava
pocket again
again
[Music]
it's a very strong choice
holy [\h__\h] is that gonna be turning like
this forever
[Music]
it's the phoenix fire
oh wait this monday
is ax over
was it friday saturday it's four days
right is it friday saturday sunday
monday is it still going on today
today's the last day who's there is
anyone there right now
i'm still watching the stream i feel
like you you shouldn't be watching
there's better things to do at ax right
even though it's a holiday
oh wait yeah it's the fourth
before right the fourth is that special
day in america
whoa
giant jackal
no i didn't see it
[Music]
yes
was there or is there
i hope he's enjoying his time uh
oh my god
hope he's having a good time
and ax
is
so will there be lots of fireworks today
over there
you guys do it like
is there a certain time you guys do that
because like for for new year's you do
it for midnight
a ton
night time
well how long does it go on do you even
get to sleep must be so noisy
poor babies and pets oh the poor pets
must be so scared
do it all night well
maybe i will add the asaku or the
movement spin could be fun
pick a branch
now go for a new weapon
the more the merrier
oh my god
i didn't get them i didn't get them ah
the clocks are going crazy but i'm like
uh twelve and a half minutes yeah my dog
is always scared
oh wait now i'm thinking of almonds
cat
uh
i always forget the name
hendrickson no
what was his name
[Music]
wellington yeah
i combined henry and wellington to
hendrickson
oh but wellington must be so scared of
the
fireworks oh no
oh no poor baby because he's always so
scared of everything
no
i want to protect him
[Music]
people should make earbuds for cats
so they could give even less shits about
everything around them than they already
do
[Music]
ah
you're back nice to meet you again
that that clock reminds me of alice
[Music]
um
didn't have that one yet okay that's my
last weapon i guess
obliterated
there's special coats for dogs what
i'm i did have like a
a weight and
weight weight and heavy blanket
i didn't try it out but like ina for
example tried it out was laying under it
and said it was really incredibly heavy
good i tried it out too i think
basically everybody accept me
yeah
i think it makes you sleep better
but it's also really crazily
surprisingly heavy
really hard to get up
when you're under that oh but ami told
me that bubba
likes to be under that blanket with a
miss but if it's already heavy for human
i wonder if for a pet
such a small dog must be
really really really really freaking
crazy heavy
how
i guess he just lacks the feeling of
being held
tightly
very good i had it oh i mean it probably
makes you feel like you're being hugged
or something
[Music]
which i can imagine would be really nice
okay it's going pretty damn good so far
it's getting really busy
but we're doing really well
i'm gonna pick up some exp
oh my god
laggy ah
[Music]
tankanashi kiwawa staying true to her
name
[Music]
i'm gonna clear this game there's five
minutes left i'm gonna prove everybody
wrong
[Music]
but i still want to
buff i still want the puff that i
deserve
but this as you see even even with you
know not being the strongest even with
you know how things are takadashikiana
just always
fights through no matter what is what is
being thrown at her
ah
so realistic maybe that's why they made
me weaker than the others
maybe that's why
kill them
kill them all
i need some
food ah there it is
that didn't help much
ah
[Music]
there you go
gonna
[Music]
makes your tummy feel happy and filled
with love
[Music]
is that a word
i feel like i've seen it but i don't
know how to pronounce that one
oh dear oh the clocks
oh they're clocking in for work i see a
csc
almost ready for the ulti
[Music]
i love my ulti i mean we must admit that
my ulti is one of the coolest ones in
the game right
i ready
[Music]
is cool too because it keeps on twirling
and twirling yeah
it's pretty decent excuse me a little
[\h__\h]
it's pretty amazing
oh my god
[Music]
is it workable of course it's trackable
ah sana's ulti is cool too yeah
it's decent just doesn't sound good
enough
anyway
shouldn't there be a golden anvil
somewhere now so that i can upgrade my
collaboration my my maxed out ones
or did i understand something wrong
[Music]
i can take a bit oh okay
[\h__\h] i need food i need food
ah i kind of urgently need some food
[Music]
i don't see any food
i just see angry saplings and owls
am i missing something
[Music]
i feel like i'm stalling i want to fight
but i also need food
ah there
oh another one oh it's a trail
they're luring me in carefree's luring
me and i told the santa monsters
i should probably leave this space
yeah yeah yeah
where food is there lies danger
okay okay it's about time for my scale
now
okay that was dangerous that was really
dangerous
that was
danger ninja
okay dangerous very dangerous
i need to go to the left i need to go to
the left
to the left to the left
[Applause]
get away from me
[Music]
okay
golden anvil taking a while why why is
it a random time
seafood
where i don't see it i don't see
anything right now
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] i don't i really don't
see [\h__\h]
to the right
okay
i tried to go there but we've reached
the time it's one minute left where
moving
is difficult
um
[Music]
i'm not gonna survive this
no
[Music]
[\h__\h] yeah didn't have the horns wait we
still had so many slots left
[Music]
i will not give up no
wait we buy some stuff
we become stronger we become stronger
yes
[Music]
maybe one more
okay now i can't afford
no [\h__\h] gotcha
[\h__\h] godzilla
gives you nothing
nothing but
losing money
it only takes
no maple leaf don't say it like that you
you sound like
i've given up but i haven't given up
kiwa never gives up
[Music]
maybe maybe haste
or more
experience
i can't can't
can't find
i guess haste is fine
you really want the coins huh okay
okay
one more time
one
i'm more close i was so close guys
i'm so close
[Applause]
i can do it i can do it i can win
i need a win
[Music]
[Laughter]
fry a cleaning duty all right how about
you clean my my home instead i really
need some cleaning put on a cute apron
and come with those fluffy feather
things oh yeah you can make it out of
your own feathers
the dusters
i kinda want the dancer too
i'll show you i'll show you what i can
do
i was so cool it was rigged it was
something happened
was rigged
and i was supposed to
win that playthrough
it just all happened too fast
i was i was lured in by the golden anvil
that i didn't even need at this point it
was
meaningless
abby avr your little [\h__\h] don't run
direct into enemies well i was
surrounded by about
2 000 of them
not like i had much of a choice
they were everywhere
i hate that kind of argument
but i'll be more careful around the end
next time
i want that axe with the book again
that's like insane
[Music]
sword
and now i'm not relying on the chat all
the time anymore
[Music]
independent woman
let me prove let me through
[Music]
accent lava
wait
axe is a reference to who
[Music]
ah
i kind of feel like in the end game
the full meal will be really open
yeah okay
glad you guys are green
[Music]
because i was picking up all these
tiniest burgers and i was like this [\h__\h]
barely heals me
so
this time
i'll get a actual full meal yo
after a hard working day of dancing so
much as an idol does
you need a proper full meal
here we go
yummy
[Music]
trapped you ha ha
oh baby a triple and we got the horns
and the bucket and yo
thank you that's exactly what i needed
exactly what i wanted
you read my mind
thanks game
i guess now the developer is watching
and helping me just kidding they can't
do that
just kidding
now we got the nurse's horn too okay
it's looking pretty op so far
no no one around really but
like playing with the muslin game and
make everything burn yeah
i feel you
especially in combination with the lava
like everybody can use the lava but it
just feels so right when
you're playing chihuahua
doesn't it
just feels so right
[Music]
yeah the taco dachi vikings
have you guys watched the show the
vikings before
i watched it uh during my time
when i was in japan before holo like the
the first half of my one year in japan
where i was like
basically doing nothing all day
and the vikings and i really enjoyed it
i was binge watching through it but i
felt like until
around the end when the suns got like
older
it got really
bad in my opinion what do you think
the first few seasons were good and then
when the when the suns get older
and certain things happen
it's it's
kind of cringy
and that character the the son that uh
what was it i think he can't uh he was
like on a wheelchair
i hated his personality so much like i
understand you know shows need some
some
evil characters or whatever but he was
just so unlikable
yeah yeah
[\h__\h] hated him
such a
creepy
idiot
yeah hey to that guy thank you
you're supposed to hate him
i get that but there's like a way to
make
characters like
feel like
i don't know
make them
evil
but still kind of
likeable or relatable or i don't know
he was just a freak
it was cringe and hateful yeah
it means he's a good actor oh yeah i
think i read that here
this is the thing with actors who played
their evil roles so well that they get
[\h__\h] for it in real life
which is
sad and must be actually pretty
bothersome
oh man but i'm not hating on the actor
i'm hating on the character okay
i wouldn't hate on the only after
i'm sure that in real life he's a decent
person
yeah when you're too believable oh yeah
with game of thrones yeah yeah yeah uh
what was this yeah what's his name
joffrey yeah oh yeah the two biggest
most haters actors are the actors from
jeffrey and from harry potter malfoy i
guess
maybe especially because the biggest
fan base or the biggest viewers of of
harry potter back in the day was
children when it first came out
and i guess they just didn't really
didn't really like
separate the two things
maybe
that one is the actor and one is the
one is the character
gotta remind yourself that it's not
not the same thing
we're already maxing out the cyclops i
feel like we're speedrunning it right
now
i'm not thinking much about
what to choose
there's not many consequences either
that's nice
i wonder if they upgrade like the
not upgrade but if they if they
bring in more characters to play
i wonder if they think about like making
new maps too
or if there are already new maps and i'm
just not seeing them
no i don't need rum
would be nice to see some different
areas yeah
like a desert area or a stone-ish area
x-bucket
yeah i don't know what i'm going for
right now uh i'm definitely maxing axe
right now
and then besides that i'm not sure uh i
guess [\h__\h] it yeah i guess we're going
for bucket
oh [\h__\h] i didn't see what we got
sorry
uh there we go
bucket max
[Music]
oh they're both maxed now
we're just gonna find a golden anvil
that's fast
when are you going to brazil again is
what i read
i'll know when no no plans right now for
this year
[Music]
milk
not much of a milk drinker i got
sacrificed oh there we go
if i just drink milk alone i don't like
it makes me feel ill
but if i combine it with cereal or
whatever oh
cool
collaboration of elite lava and
psychology real business partners me
comment
cool
wait is there like a combination of like
a takamori weapon for example
if this exists then
can you combine some
not yet ah i guess ah because like the
weapons
extra weapons are mostly
uh the japanese members but the
characters so far
the en members
imagine like a scythe
that's
twirling around
covered in fire and
it's not just twirling around everywhere
fast and crazily but it leaves a fire
trail as well
oh
oh wow wow wow wow
sounds really strong holy what
holy [\h__\h]
whoa these maxed collab weapons are
really [\h__\h] insane
obliterating everything
[Music]
i missed some at the top
i'm gonna go get them are you still
there are they gone
holy [\h__\h]
including the frame rate
oh my god i want to see all the
collaborations this is really cool
uh let's get the nurse's horn
it's like a apocalypse holy [\h__\h] i'm
ending the world of this i'm not just
ending the fans
i feel like this will have really bad
after effects that um the humanity will
blame me for after
but you gotta do what you gotta do
to save the world we barely have any
weapons we need more weapons should we
go for asakoko or never tried ah this is
an item though
increase normal attack damage by 30
balloons no
no
okay
holy [\h__\h]
what do we want to combine the asaku
with
oh there you are hey time to burn those
bones down
who wants roasted bones for dinner
i know there's not much to eat with that
but it will give me calcium
fan beam uh-huh
let's see if we get that though
okay
that helps us
okay we'll take that okay we'll take
another one
triple upgrade thank you soon
[Music]
who said bomb
rose and bones make great stuff ah soup
stuff
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
just get straight out of there just get
straight out of there no [\h__\h] around
i was scared really scared for a moment
oh
[Music]
boy the boy's love book combined with
asaku to me seems like a very erotic
choice
um but yeah let's go for headphones
[Music]
surprise jim king
kfb when
chihuahua
opens the pre-chat
to a new stream
wait closex no you want to you want the
one let's for now i guess and uh upgrade
until we find the one
unless we don't find it
i need to get the rights to the chicken
attack song
and then officially cover it
but i'm not sure that's like basically
just a joke song is it really worth
worth getting the
the rights to a song because i think
that costs a lot of money
it would be so funny though
now
uh
you need to learn how to you know who
says i don't know how to yell yet i'm
austrian
i have a probably a hidden skill for it
i didn't know i stepped on that thing
that collects everything
we're not getting the thing that i want
guys i'm sorry i guess i'll go for
a bump
[Music]
holy [\h__\h] as if the mekomets
were not enough already
now we're adding bumps to it
oh dear
i'd like my life to be a bit more
peaceful than this to be honest
[Laughter]
oh [\h__\h] is it time oh yeah it's ten
minutes that's what's gonna only show up
in ten minutes huh
i'm not even
i think
[Music]
okay okay it's no problem easy peasy
easy
oh
you're going down
you're going down lookie i'm sorry
i'm grilling you once again and little
candles there hmm don't let's go
straight up after this
yeah
i think that was my fastest football
kill so far which means i'm really crazy
powerful now but now the second half
stop top starts
and you know what that means things
aren't gonna get stressful ah here's the
fan beam
[Music]
i don't know if we want to invest in yes
okay
okay i need to go back up
but there was an animal there
and now
we shall upgrade
the fan beam like this oh increase the
size so i guess they're gonna be really
[\h__\h] fat after a while covering
almost the whole screen
hopefully okay maybe that's hoping for
too much
[Music]
as fast as possible okay i'll try
because yeah we're 11 minutes
we're gonna do it this time
no matter [\h__\h] what
[Music]
get something new or upgrade the first
one
three okay
that will be good
more body pillow
four
[Music]
ten percent exp increase
too strong i'm too strong somebody needs
to stop me
[Music]
ah
that's what we're looking for
oh rats army
how can i obliterate them
i don't need it
[Music]
looking freaking good right
now catch all the [\h__\h] out of these
enemies yeah
[Music]
imagine when you do a ketchup this is
the fan beam that will come out of the
of the ketchup
it's not it's not getting that big
i want it to be wider
hoping for it to be more wider
i'm scared i'm scared i'm scared
minutes 30
hiwa enters
maximum focus mode
clock invasion
okay
xp
i need to max out my fan beam soon
because the golden animal is probably
going to take his stamp sweet tom again
until it shows up until the very last
freaking moment
oh
oh oh oh okay
careful careful careful kappa
okay
got the distance
i got the hp
oh
laggy really
yeah
nice shockwave she got going there
i'm just waiting for the golden anvil oh
it shoots in both directions oh there it
is
so fast i guess i got a speed delivery
now
hell yeah
now this one i haven't seen yet that's
well that one is new to me let's see
plug type asakula fan beam turns into
dragon fire
oh
accurate build yeah it's all fire thank
you guys i see now why you wanted me to
go for this one it all makes sense now
let me drink some water
before we enter the last sport
it's a boss breaker
[Music]
wait a second
i will play hino toy
i will
i will play all kinds of hinotoyi
now turn off the music in a second
here we go
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
wow
i will live to keep on fighting
[Music]
is
[Applause]
[Music]
is
huh
ah
it's nice about music
look at those chickens running into
their death
isn't it beautiful
it's so peaceful
i like silence
because then you can
focus on the important things
in life
which is nothing
because nothing makes sense
nothing's worth it
sad twerking is the only thing i can do
but i can't stop
just can't stop
i can't [\h__\h] stop
i'm cursed
i could kill them all
gotta burn them until there's no single
one of them left
calling me a psycho
this game's calling me a psycho
making a fool of me
i won't rest
i want rest
i won't put my foolish ambitions to rest
because they're not foolish
they're not foolish
what was
that i don't know
it's okay it doesn't matter nothing
matters
i want that fire back
i wanna see the flames
and i want the flames to be reflected
in my enemies eyes
when they die
and they look
into the flames
and all they see
is death
and then they'll wonder
was it really worth it
was all of that was any of that
ever worth it
nothing's worth it
nothing
unless you watch hololive
watch hololive subscribe to your whole
life
subscribe to takanashikiyana
subscribe subscribe subscribe
leave a comment leave a like
subscribe
subscribe subscribe
bell
everything must be activated
your life will be consumed by me and
youtube
it's mine
it's mine your life is mine
dance
i
wanna dance with somebody
i wanna feel the heat
somebody
i want to dance with somebody
somebody who loves me
i can die
go away [\h__\h] taco duchies
[\h__\h] clingy as
hell ah
priorities
that's good that's very good
take it take it
i need to feel the power
awaken
the
phoenix and me
get out of the way
[Applause]
hmm
there's no need to worry about me i'm
fine
i'm fine
i'm fine i'm perfectly fine
everything's fine
i'm fine
i'm okay
i'm gonna hug my yonko body pillow
cry myself to sleep
but i'm fine
don't question my life choices chet
crying about it
that looked even better
when it was lagging
because you can see
them suffering in pain slowly and dying
slowly
the heart
losing its speed
slowly
i don't need another one of those body
pillows
cringe
cringe who wants a juggle body pillow
that's beneath me
okay maybe you guys do one and maybe
maybe they should sell dead
[Music]
i want
i
want i
want the same weapons back
[Music]
[Laughter]
feels good
dance
give same weapons or as i actually
forgot what did i have before
i need i'm missing the asaku right
[Music]
get away from me
hmm
that's what i was missing
dodge dodge
dodge dodge dodge
[Applause]
phoenix
here we go let's go let's go
you need to max them
knock them out
i don't feel the pain that they deserve
need to end the fans
it was only a lie
so it was all i there was no saving to
do
justice
needs to be served
something good
or i won't recycle you
shitty books
that's perfect that's perfect
gotta wait this time
almost 10 minutes [\h__\h] and i don't have
life my comment
yet
hurts
[\h__\h] i'm not strong enough i'm not
strong enough
why can't we be friends huh
why can't we be friends
it's okay easy
and nothing against the phoenix
strong
is it
when life gives you lemons
poison them
poison
but okay
don't worry guys
when this ends
then we're all free
all free
we'll all be free
by the injustice of this world
end of this stream
chad you can
once only tell me what to do
once
okay
you know what happens if that was a bad
choice
you know what will happen with you
that's correct
usual room
tell me
it's important
we cannot lose another time
it's all different numbers
go for two because i need to
collab soon
and i need a collaboration
i need the collaboration
um
[Music]
hmm
captioning
yes
peacock
died
wait so we need to combine
fan beam with masako
and lava bucket with
axe
wait was that what we did
have a bucket with x
yes
oh
no
i think i
i focused i didn't i didn't folk i
focused but i didn't focus on certain
attacks i need to collapse earlier while
i spread it out too much
so i didn't get the
epic
attacks
early enough
we could fix it we can fix it
we can fix it
i can fix it
i shall give you the music back
[Music]
it's different music
i'll give you back the music let's go
we'll do it this time
i know it's
five times before
we'll do it this time
[Music]
horn
not quite sadly restored but
i know you guys are gonna worry about me
if i
don't turn back into normal kiwawa
sooner
than later
[Music]
there's also cocoa right there
should we get it already
okay
now we already have weapons now nice
oh yeah
oh yeah slice them up
slice them up take them down
put them in a sandwich
yummy yummy crunchy sandwich
and now we have to upgrade the sword
we're not gonna do anything stupid this
time
gonna be smart
burger
i'm looking forward to dinner
get that
level three sword
no it won't be an eight hour stream
doesn't even feel that long four and a
half hours it feels like i've been
playing for
free
it's like
the time really goes by so slow with
this game
[Music]
when it's almost midnight
i kind of wanted to upload the
content video before midnight
oh well
sacrifices have to be made
uh we combined asa koko with
[Music]
i forgot
are we getting the poison book
are we getting the voice on the book
we need it
with the fan beam oh yeah and then the
uh
axe with the
rocket okay so we don't really need the
[Music]
now i want as many weapons as possible
we also got to focus on the
double
ideally
we got like a triple
triple present thingy
[Music]
now go for the lasso coco first
now some of you guys say do the weapon
first and then some of you guys say
do the choreographers so
it's really
different opinions there
can't please everybody
okay that's good
i appreciate that
swoosh
ah the glasses oh yeah if i see the
glasses i'll try to get them
axe
right
just move away from those stop following
me no no no
upgrade
um
now i don't know
[Music]
sorry guys
i'm kind of
changing my priorities here i don't know
if it's good or bad
[Music]
you know what this word reminds me of
now diablo
[Laughter]
diablo 2
with the way things are scattered
and the point of view
and these these these these things for
example
i don't know kind of reminds me of the
able to
oh okay
ah got some new choices um
we still didn't get trailblazer
we need trailblazer
nice sick burn baby
[Music]
nice
yeah yeah yeah follow me follow me
follow me
[Music]
we're at
almost five minutes
i thought that was that uh okay ah all
healing done oh nice okay
[Music]
should we get some sheep food polita
no
book
we don't need the book
not now
okay
so many good choices
[Music]
okay
get good gamers
[Music]
almost finally that's a different
combination
chickens trying to distract me or what
wait i want all the eggs speed
[Music]
oh
fun [\h__\h]
wait that's what i wanted
uh
huh
lima we need to get it up fast
ah
[Music]
right yeah we need to get it up fast as
i just said
as i just said
are you ready
i need the bucket too
but
i think i need the glasses they could be
very helpful
don't worry don't worry don't worry
don't worry we will figure it out
i could have
could have done it last time but i made
a small small mistake
oh there you go
wait uh axe with
axe with bucket right
okay
excellent bucket
let's get a bucket
keep on forgetting
the combinations
i need to awaken my sword to now though
awakening
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
okay we're almost there we're almost no
no not axes
actually no axe
[\h__\h] up [\h__\h] up [\h__\h] up
[Music]
food
but i'm running away from them
okay i'm good i have full hp no need to
be scared
[Music]
but no need to be cocky either
okay okay okay i have arrived
i've arrived
ah
[Music]
what do we got what we got we have
five
free
uh i saw coco
with the beam
and axe of the bucket
dragon fire i'm coming
i'm coming
[Music]
okay
sword on the nurse's horn
yeah we gotta get done with the sword
so the green ones bring more ying speed
on the blue ones i assume
oh my god
okay
[Music]
no
stop
[Music]
i tried you saw me trying to escape
right
you saw it right
i tried
there were so many what the [\h__\h] it was
so so early in the game it was 8 45.
um sad pickle
sand pickle
but we cleared the game once with ahmed
and people say
people say kawawa
is you know kind of
not not the strongest one so
sad pickle no sack pickle
[Music]
oh fans keep on hurting me man
they keep on hurting me
ah
[Music]
okay
i think we need to learn when to stop
because
i think
that's my favorite character that's why
thank you
i'm glad you made you were probably able
to clear the stage already
with kiwawa
um
all right i will
i will read super chats
uh yeah i need a break i think
it'll break
but
but it was still a lot of fun
i had a lot of fun i'm glad i chose to
play this game yeah you know quinoa
usually stays away from like
all these games that everybody plays at
the same time because i feel like oh
everybody's playing it why do i
need to play it people probably don't
need to see another stream with the same
game
and
yeah so usually i stay away away from it
but i want to take a look at this
because it's like a fan made game that
looks really good with lots of like you
know whole life things in it so yeah i
want to check it out it's really good
yeah i will play it again next week then
because like this week i already have a
full schedule yeah
i'll play it again because i need to
clear it with guava
i need to
clear it otherwise i'm not satisfied not
happy
yeah
thanks for helping me out teaching me
how the game works and all that
now we move to my office come with me
move move
follow me follow me
oh dear
i'm so big again
y'all are welcome to stay we have fun
when we read super chats
yeah yeah we have a lot of fun
and tangent very much
i am the queen of tangents as they stay
yeah older lady
i'm a lady now
don't forget smile oh you're right i
have a small office of good
well then we shall go here
ah now i'm so small
wait
yo
if i fit size it
yes i i left the chat somewhere
wait
i left the chat uh where are you here
you are
and there we go
yeah hey what's up chad you're small too
you're very small and i'm like you
i'll make you fit
[Music]
uh-huh
and
uh
i go
i'm not
quite maybe like
this
you guys are so small
i can barely see you i need to buy a
magnifying glass for you guys
okay
but it gets cut off though
i didn't cut it off it's too small now
[Music]
nani
then
we make
uh
we add
200 there we go
and then
of course no one can radio if you like
this
i'll put you i'll put you here
okay
well i wanted to play all these pinot
hairy mixes and then i died and then i
couldn't play them all so let's listen
to them now
well listen to this one
the lone alpha one i feel like it's good
for like
at the end of the stream or so
uh if you haven't seen i shall show you
uh sorry members i didn't i didn't
upload the
image yet for the members but but but i
shall do it afterwards if i don't forget
i was awake really long yesterday doing
some work
but see schedule for this week looking
exciting because tomorrow's birthday
college yay
and then we have the free daily birthday
concert the day after
and a preemptive super chat reading and
minecraft unveils aussie snack books
review and untitled ghouls game with
reina now the snack box review is not
necessarily a collab so to keep that in
mind but the one with lena will be it
might even be on her channel so keep an
eye out for that
and close your nose schedule this next
schedule for amps no it's pretty big
what the hell there you go made it
bigger for you
you need glasses you need glasses mate
okay
now let me read super chats because
i want to be sure that i'm not falling
behind too much and i i caught up
yesterday but it's still not enough
i need to make sure i'm always
always caught up oh sh
oh sh
you know what effect you have on us why
did you write that like that
so
edgy hope you have a great birthday
thank you
and birthday week
so exciting
oh my god i can't believe it's been a
year since the last one
birthday is gonna be yeah big wave hmm
i'm scared i'm scared
okay i'm scrolling by the way
i missed it did you win and i only only
cleared the stage once when i played oh
man
but
it's okay i'll i'll try again i'll try
again i won't give up
yeah
yes okay i reached the beginning
of the end
birthday's always a year pass bad but it
feels
like you know crazy that
time passes by so fast and it's already
my second birthday
hmm
seen some streams right i didn't clear
at all really
what
then
then i shall be a little bit proud of
myself
yeah
okay so first up we have doug hood thank
you for the rainbow
whoa
right in the beginning you squeezed in
the rainbow nicely
it's finally birthday week i sat down
and thought to myself what do i love
about kiara and here's what i came up
with
kiana's cute
the best cat mom mm-hmm can i respond to
fans i do
canada is a great senpai
i don't think so too i agree with that
okay i love jrpgs yeah that makes
delicious looking meals
chiara is great at voice acting kiana is
hilarious
kiara playfully flirts with thirsty
chimpkins
nah
wouldn't do such a thing kiana m2
cannot sings beautifully there's one
thing where the for the
grammar is kind of love sounding kiana
m2 but i forgive
kiana's dance moves are stunning keanu
gives us fun content went away uh-huh i
try wasn't there uh wasn't able to
prepare too much for the
america week though kiana promotes the
underdog believes in us kayla wants the
best for us canada never wants to lose
us you know canada wants to know us
scared takes care of her health even
when it's hard and motivates us to do
the same
yes
you guys must be healthy so you can live
as long as possible
you gotta keep up with the phoenix
straight edge phoenix
kind of surprises us sincere kiana helps
bad chimpkins be better employees for
the usual rule
kiana reminds us that we can't have
everything but we should work hard for
creativity
wait this goes oh it's a double rainbow
oh my god can i just skip the chiana
canada says spoil her
she spoils us stays with us in the outro
because she knows we already missed her
korean creates the best content even if
it's exhausting or near impossible
it gives us long streams has fun
collaboration streams
kiara appreciates a good night's sleep
oh hell yeah i love sleeping kyla shares
your favorite shows and music with us
because you must watch it too piano
tensions frequently in cute ways
cara is a great tales ambassador kiara
loves good chocolate mmm carlo gets
nervous meeting other whole talents yeah
even though everyone thinks she's
fabulous oh it's an amazing talk show
host comes up with new ideas is in
control brought together an amazing
community
voice
voice is divine and her cute love melts
my heart kiana likes pictures of me
taking my papa out for stuff
gotta help me and lots of chickens for
hard times thanks for being you boss you
deserve
it's another rainbow are you kidding me
you deserve wait where was i
yeah
you deserve a billion fans and i know
you'll get them because you're amazing
keep climbing higher and higher to reach
your dreams we'll keep stacking chickens
on top of each other and boost you up
until you reach the stars
so cute glory to kfp please forgive me
for not sending just a red super chat
with a happy birthday i considered it to
save you some reading but i also wanted
you to know how much you appreciate it
i'll send a short message for your two
year anniversary i promise
it's okay i like your message
ah so much praising it's like homonobi
for me
praise kiwawa love chihuahua
thank you
i like homemade we should be doing that
in kfb um
you remem remember when noedo told us
about it
in holotalk that they have this one day
where
uh
her fans they praised her a lot on on
twitter i would assume
um
komenobi it means uh when you get better
through being praised
yeah ever since i heard about that i was
thinking we should start doing that
[Music]
but you oh yeah you do you do praise me
every day but you also tease me
a lot
and i i feel like it's a it's maybe
if i if i do such a thing it would be um
how to say
maybe we shouldn't be doing it um but um
sounds like a
good thing
teasing is
fun too i understand but praising is
nicer you guys feel free to praise me
whenever it makes me very happy don't
need a whole day for it but
but just scatter it out and i will be
happy that's good i also i'm trying to
open
oh
whoopsie i'm trying to open some
the another snack that uh oh that's very
bacony
oh wow
oh
it's like
croutons
that are salty and have a strong bacon
taste
whoa
let's see it's the one that said
um
on the package that beer goes down
really fast with it
but
dummy did it
wow
that's so crunchy
[Music]
um
it's pretty good
what
too bad i don't have beer i guess
okay
i'm not done
okay that click continues can i dedicate
your kids to blue for finding those
whole cute pngs for the thumbnail in
fact lots of champions tried to fight
yeah i saw thank you guys for helping i
googled and i tried you know was my
usual trick
by setting the color to transparent in
in google images
yeah
but i couldn't find too much
you can have root beer i'm sorry i
really don't like root beer i tried it
once and i'm like what the hell is this
sorry
i really don't like it
anyway thank you blue and everybody who
tried helping me last night when i was
making
the thumbnail really late at night thank
you mwah and doc hood thank you for the
huge rainbow of the sweet words you such
as sweet sweet sweet chicken oh my god
mwah
thank you so much
that's that's a great way to start off
the super chat rating
of such a
praising full of praises
beautiful rainbow i appreciate it thank
you so much thank you i'm guessing this
is
a preemptive happy birthday super chat i
think
thank you so much take it monkey duncan
thai team thank you for the pinky and
the red super chat
thank you what it just says test and
test
what why would you test over red and the
pinky
ah
you should have just tested with a blue
or whatever but i guess tai chi doesn't
doesn't go blue no no no no
tai chi the only color
tai chi knows is red usually even the
pink one is unusual thank you very much
tess was a success i guess yeah
thank you
pepsi thank
[Music]
hi back to you thank you for watching
and enjoying the stream today and thanks
for the support
[Music]
oh my god it's almost midnight
i've been seeing a lot of news recently
about flags being cancelled and delayed
and so much [\h__\h]
no they're not scheduled i wanted to
upload them after i'm done i didn't
think i would be streaming until
midnight
goddammit
it got me hooked the game hooked me
i love smokey and i'm more than normal
kiara what
i think it's nice to look at um every
now and then but imagine i was like this
all the time
then you would be thinking the opposite
way
probably
and call it like a fish
nice change of pace right i think so too
erasmus
garden park dan kishin and she says the
contradiction
for not getting pets thank you soon
sorry jungkook
that name looks new to me come sanita
for the pinky
king it is my first time to watch tantra
stream all in life and also my first
time sending super chat to someone ah
see i knew you were a first timer i'm
always watching in an archive and
cheering for you you are my number one
aussie it's a little bit fast but i hope
you have a happy birthday
[Music]
thank you for making it to the stream
live even though this one must have also
been at a yeah awkward stupid time for
you but thank you i appreciate you
making the time during your busy day to
watch me
thank you
and i hope you can watch the concert
yeah
maybe live too that would be the best
but if not make sure to watch the vlog
okay
thank you so much
lost traveler six four nine three down
question
elsie lapin
oh
oh the whole life meetup at anime expo
photos should be online soon if you'd
like to see oh i would love to see them
i did see like like uh individual ones
here and there scattered throughout
but i didn't
see them together have you watched the
concert oh it's not done yet i've seen
like
snippets
getting close to
the end though i hope it makes it in
time
and what you have seen i've seen a
little
[Music]
oh wait now i understand serious dragon
wrote full meal equals enemy drops
burger plus fries and drink oh yeah
that's why
that's why the the full meal icon is
just fries in a drink because you
already pick up the burger ah
now that makes sense now
what's on having a cat as a pet
are you aware that i do have cans as a
pet are you asking like how it is
i i love that i mean i've been used to
it because i've i've had cats as my pets
as my uh throughout my whole life
i'm gonna stack on some pokey
yeah
when you have cats
no i love them so much i feel like
they're also much less work than a dog
so if you don't have too much time
yeah and if you also
um
okay um
they don't
they don't need too much attention but
the more attention you give them the
happier you will be
but if you think about getting a cat
consider getting two at once
so that they can entertain each other
also or hang out when you're busy
you ever raise a munchkin cat no
i know i think they're really cute and
all that but i
i guess i would feel kind of bad i
talked about this with ame when i showed
her some cute videos of of munchkin cats
um
that we talked about you know they have
some they have health problems
and
yeah
because they're like
breeded to have
short legs they're like it's like
supported day
what's the word
not supported
they
forgot the word i'm thinking of
forgot
but yeah you know what i mean uh they
look really cute and
but then again you know the the problem
is and this is the
the
circle of hell
you don't want to
support that but then again if you see
them like in a shelter or whatever
or
yeah even in a pet shop
if you're i mean i guess somebody's
gonna get them
if you don't get them i guess
but sometimes i mean munchkins i guess
are popular enough that they don't have
to worry about
not being adopted
i guess
yeah but it is a cycle like
you don't want them to not be adopted
either
because
you know what happens to them and yeah i
know like buying from a breeder just
supports them to breed more but i feel
like breeders are even
depending on the country maybe too but
they're even even more likely to like
just throw them away
without mercy
if they
are not being bought adopted
like
i feel like shelters are more ethically
morally correct in choosing what to do
although they take them down too yeah
but they take them
ah
it's just so sad i want to save every
cat in the world but
you see i've heard bad stories about
breeders what they do with the
the pets that are not being adopted
so
you kind of want to save them right
ah it's such a
such a
heart
territory
tearing apart my heart topic
yeah i want to save every cat
yeah
[Music]
got my kitty from michelle the poofing
was abandoned that's sweet of you
[Music]
world is a harsh place yeah it's a
business yeah
i wish i could help them too
go get a cat or a doggo or any any pet
that needs help
yeah
let's go get some pets
like even if you don't have a big enough
apartment you know
there's some pets out there that are
small
really small
like you know um mice
or hamsters
and you can keep them in them in the
cage that's not so big doesn't take too
much space
hmm
still waiting on the charity stream
yeah that's like
i feel like i need to remind them
because like when last time i said i
want to do a charity stream i was told
like oh yeah we are like kind of like
planning something so i guess we can add
that to that
but that was ages ago i feel like
their priorities shifted i need to
check that out
[Music]
gosh there we go before i forget it i
did it
yeah it would be nice
it would be really nice
and when was i uh here crow avant-garde
thank you for the super chat thank you
excessive boots thank you so much
again thank you very
asaku and much stick makes best collab
weapon
but we did uh asakuku and um
the the the beam thingy right
i wonder what the glow stick makes it
look like then
thank you oh you tried to help so much
thank you
crow evangelically
[Music]
you can't combine them
i didn't they meant to beam then
probably ah okay okay okay okay
oh some things don't combine i thought
everything was possible
interesting okay okay so there are some
combinations that don't work good to
know
brandon
[Music]
membership card sticker from last year
birthday merch on the round one card
nice
yeah nice one that's a good place to put
it on squiggly mustache thanks for pinky
forgive me fire with chicken must i
sabotage caffeine friars
and i kidnapped your chickens i do what
i must for bunks from mama ina tentacle
needs bunks
oh is this one
is this
was this while i was on the idol meeting
is this why you guys were like oh takoda
takodachi's
excuse me you did what exactly
[Laughter]
is be wilding what the [\h__\h]
burn him
i won't forgive you the [\h__\h]
but they want they want the bunks
i'll leave it up to you guys have fun
with him
by leaving it up to you guys it will
probably be more more painful more
torture than if i do it myself
so have fun
use them as a punching bag
or whatever the hell you want to do
eat them
poke him to death with your beaks
i think that is like
about the same
pain as stoning someone
let's go
[\h__\h]
you're no extenual
thank you for the pinky
pick pick pick pick we take our pink
glasses off
well do you even need them when it's not
a chicken that you're dealing with it's
a taco that's you afterwards the glasses
are just so you don't attack each other
right
imagine next year birthday emerge
pink sunglasses
too deep the meaning is too deep
yeah
perfect merch
uh dolphin cruiser dan oh and others
flush jets those look like flush jets
[Music]
in german they wrote that there's a
beach
where there's garfield phones stranded
what
when we were talking about the dolls
what the [\h__\h]
i never heard about that what
garfield oh some people know
it's a thing
i need to look it up now
garfield phones beach oh my god in
france
oh wait i might have seen
eh
now they said i feel like i might have
seen a picture of that before
oh
garfield phone's beach mystery finally
solved after 35 years
a french coastal community has finally
cracked the mystery behind the garfield
telephones that have plagued its
picturesque beaches for decades
since the 1980s the irois coast in
brittany has received a supply of bright
orange landline novelty phones shaped
like the famous cartoon cat anti-litter
campaigners have been collecting
fragments of the feline for years since
they cleaned the features
can you not talk about it as if it's a
real cat
but now the source of the problem has
been found a lost shipping container
yeah that just makes sense
uh huh
the garfields have been lost on yo
ono
[Music]
wow
wow yeah these things happen but the
guard feels at least like kind of
makes sense because they look alike they
they seem to be the same type and they
match each other
so it makes sense that they're like from
the same
container
but the dolls are all different
anyway so maybelline thank you thank you
soon
maybelline with the double red super
chat and i'm
i'm so sorry
i'm like really disappointed in myself
that i couldn't clear it also for you
she may not have hit 20 minutes but at
least she's forever in kfp's hearts good
show tensho kiera takanashi ultimate
strongest part time warrior and then i
made you
admit
that i i can still do it
you sent another one
apologies i'll take a prior cleaning
duty as repentance
and i did i didn't
now
now i feel like i have to take up fire
cleaning duty
i'm so disappointed in myself
no man
next time there's always the next time
i hit 20 with vomit yeah you know
having you in our hearts is all worth it
so romantic and
thank you
thank you so much so sweet thank you all
for believing in me
such a loyal sweet chicken
donkey shoe
abby or thank you for the pinky you can
do it but maybe don't
a little [\h__\h]
that little [\h__\h] i already got angry at
you
have you reflected
on your words heavier
i hope you did
that one triggers me hard
it's like in an alden ring where people
told me to stop rolling
except for this time the running into
enemies was kind of inevitable sometimes
okay
no nvh
[Music]
burn it all down
yes it felt good to burn everything to
the ground
really cool skills yeah
i enjoy those
i want more of it
makes you feel so powerful i want more
i'm a chin
bad timing when i was
silent
dan dan osidan
murph laser thank you thank you
and purple dragon duncan
mr kazakhstan and
oh maple leaf again thank you for the
red super chat wow
all those canadian dollars
she's the wildfire that is approaching
provoking flames of motivation reclaimer
of her name born in flames she has been
blessed her family crest is a phoenix of
death beautiful graceful kawaii
phoenix's ash in dark divine descending
hope idol destiny realized
is that a reference yeah i'm wondering
is it is it oh it is a i was thinking
that must be even though i didn't play
it that must be a devil may cry
reverence
for a while i was motivated again but i
still couldn't do it maybe it was too
much for the day
thanks for believing in me
putting your faith in me
i won't disappoint next time
spiritual steam okay
i had a feeling yeah
emergency down cause you know what
wicked night l elbow duncan
a new visual novel called amen
really
at 40
420 trash phoenix no [\h__\h] way
wait is that something i saw
huh
it exists
what
what the trash bins
i need to look into this
interesting i like the the main image
it's just me in a trash can
i like it
it's a murder mystery based on my death
why haven't i revived oh have i revived
and they tried to investigate the
previous death ah i died in rebecca okay
that only makes sense
i'm curious now
oh
the game is really really mean to me
it's a bad game for you don't play
me
as in
like as if someone who hates me made it
yeah why would they
kind of degrading
more like you were unlucky
well that's weird
[Music]
some people like it apparently
poking fun
oh well uh spaghetti and blankets thank
you thank you thank you
and demi li
really happy birthday attention thank
you very much
hope you can watch my concert i'm done
now i will go immediately before you
guys send any more super chats so that i
can upload the countdown video and go
cook some food so thank you guys for
watching today and then jeremy say i'll
read this in and see you tomorrow oh now
i'm getting nervous oh [\h__\h]
uh but collins coins are fine cones are
gonna be fun fun fun fun gonna be
announcing birthday merchandise tomorrow
as well so
yeah you should come
thank you for having fun with me tonight
[Music]
thank you guys thank you
bye bye
bye
yay i'm waving i'm waving
[Music]
do
you