[Music] My
bones are wet as I wish, and I close my jumps
on the ground.
Someday, my
voice will turn into a soft one, and I won't
be able to
hear it anymore.
[Music]
This place is the
closest to the sky.  I just got up
[Music]
So
[Music] I
'm here, I'm
passing by, I'm
fine.
But Kara-chan's voice
De-chan
De-noisy
Mai Mai Gully Lee Lee
Lee
Lee I'm going back now
yo
Big Senkyu Big Voice Senkyu Big
Voice Thank you for saying yes
and the white group has gathered together
Wow White Team White White
[Music]
Chi is telling me  That guy
is amazing. He's really telling me. It's fun, oh, it's so fun. It's okay. [Music] It's too loud, isn't it? Ee-chan [Laughs] Width, handsomeness, good.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, that's it.
So, I'm a little late, but ok, this time, oh,
oh, oh, I'm here. Okay, then, uhm. I
missed the team division, so I
thought I'd make a little announcement about that.  I
'm thinking right away, but are you okay? Please,
don't fight with me. Stop fighting for me. Are you really angry? Stop and win.  Don't
get in the middle. Show your reward. Sorry. Go. I'm
fine. I'm a junior. I'm fine. When juniors are energetic, they seem to be very
energetic.  I
would like to announce each of the competitions.
First of all, let's talk about the follow-up. It's a
competition where you climb higher and higher.
Yes, it's a game where points are determined by how far you can go within the time limit.
Oofuro-up Gae Roboco-senpai and
Kia I'm here today Kia Good luck Kia I'm a bird so I
can afford to go I can go I'm sure I can go to the top in one blow
How about one blow?  The
game is a
game where a knight protects the princess,
and the princess has a lot to do,
so it's quite a difficult game, but Azuki-
chan will do her best.
Wow, it's me,
and the next one is Iroha-
chan, and the fourth one is Mumemu. It's
good. I'll ask Himekoshiyama to play with these four. Yes, it's nice. Yes, I'll do my best. But Dice.
When I heard Iroha-chan's English, it was me.  I
thought I didn't have to support them.It was good, wasn't it?English was
good.Special EnglishGeniusThere are
times when English is more lively than Japanese.That's
certainly not the case.  It's not
like that, it's not like that.As
expected, it's not like that.It's the next obstacle.Rele,
hey,
yes.  E Shirokane Noel Leader
Marumaru Leader Maru Ho Nobi Nobi Taro Taro and
[Music]
[Applause]  There are
three other members of Muajahimehime team besides me,
but then Kaela
[Applause]
[Music]
Kaka, then finally
Neri, Saonee, and the last Holomen
Hunter Hahomehahunting, the first person is
Noel Shirokane Leader Holomen Hunter  Taro
Taro Jiro Taro Taro Jiro Saro Ah Onee-chan, No,
and the second one is Chiara,
Kia
Pi, and then Aa-chan, Ame-chan, Onee-
chan,
Onee-chan,
and the next one is Kaela.
[Music]
Kaela, then Neri-san, Neri-san Saneri-
san, and the last one is Raden. It's
been adjusted so that it will appear once or
twice.  It seems
like there are some people who have never done it before,
so yeah, let's go around the venue and try out the competition,
please.I want to do it.  Are you
going to use up all your calories here?
Just tell yourself, ``It's fun, it's fun, it's
fun, it's fun, it's a scary, scary spell.'' Okay, I'm
happy
now let's go, come here, let's go, let's start with the first floor-up,
okay?  I'm going to go from here. It's a little dark.
Is it difficult
? It looks difficult. It's quite high. It seems like it goes all the way to the top. I'm going to climb the stairs
to the roof. It's
scary. Is it okay to follow the Fire Service Act?
Fire Service Act Think about that and make Minecraft
Hey, I'm not sure if I'll get caught.
[Applause]
Takeko
will be participating in the event, but
I've never done that Only Up. I
guess it's rare, because everyone else is doing it.
Well, everyone was doing it, right,
right, right.
Please Ratclick
Kuku Then Ero Noe Trident will appear. Yeah,
weak and strong will come out. Yeah, weak and
strong will be true. Left is right.
Strong or left is light strong. Yeah, it's
weak. Yeah,
look at it.  It's climbing, it's flying, it's
flying, right, right click where you want to go, and you can fly. Click
right, right, hold and release, or press and hold right. Yeah,
let go, it's going to jump.
Jump.
Hmm, there are strong jumps and
weak jumps, right?
Well, when should I use the weak jumps when the backboard is weak? I
guess when the distance is short. Okay, let's
go! Clio, nice, nice, ah. Oh, okay. With this, we'll move higher and higher.  Aiming for the top Aiming for the top
Yes, it's difficult, it's difficult, it's
difficult
Asu Asta
[Applause]
Oh, I
got it right when I got home.
Relily I'm going to die, I'm going to die This game I'm going to die
Death senpai Sorry Accident Accident
Super Accident Berry Accident Kill Berry
Accident Pre-play Berry Accident Pre-No Accident
No Life
Reno Accident I'm going to eat Can you
erase the real cloud?  I do
n't think there are any real clouds right now. I can see them.
It's also in the book, but it's not from me.
Why?  No, I
wonder if the cloud is interfering with it. I want a clear sky. Is this a setting? It's a setting that says whether there are clouds or not. I'm
sure it's there somewhere. Well,
it's in the video settings.  Hey, Deo
Seona, this is this, this is
it, it's gone, it's
gone, it's gone, it's
gone
If you fall, you
might die, you'll die, so you'll
go back to the checkpoint.Go back
to the checkpoint.There's a
bed in the middle where
there's dirt, so click on the bed.Click on it and you'll be taken
from there.
Respon I see
[Music] It's
difficult I need a lot of practice for this, right? It
feels like that. I'll practice. Nice
One Piece
. So let's go watch the next competition.
NEXT I
think I'll die.
Right-click on the left side
of the debug item Right-click on the debug item
Yes, no, I wonder if I won't die, right now.
Keep up the good work,
Kia,
everyone, let's
go home from here.
Rakocchia Okay, next is the obstacle race. Yes, yes, it's this way. It's this way. It's this way
. It's this way. I think it's here. It's the start.
What's going on here? On
the day of the event.  Well, here's where we
start. Yes, Adema starts from here, but
instead of one lap per person, it's half a lap per person.
Oh, I see.
So you can run from here, and there
's a line over there on the other side,
but the people who run all the way up here
have to say goodbye, right? So, from here,
run halfway and go to the other side.  How many laps are there that it feels like the people coming back are
divided into two teams, or rather, two?
Well, that's about 8 people
running. 4th
week people
May
[Music]
Oooh.  Okay, let's
try running all of them for now.  It's
the same with everyone. Run around and find your weak points. No, I
think this is the way I like it. I wish we
could talk about it. It
's pretty rough. If you touch it, it's a monster.
These hurdles are too bad. If you touch it, it's a monster. Oh, it's
true. There's something wrong with it.
Maybe it's slow, but I'll try running for a bit. Or maybe I'll try running a little bit.
Oh, pants are pants, pants are pants
Ah, right -click right -click
Right
-click Wait for a right -clicked right -click Wait, Easy Easy Ah,
this is just a powder snow, so you
can't get it.
Good, good,
good
[Music]
No, it's better to go from the top.
No, I can't take the bread. I can't take the bread.
Click, click,
click.  It's
left, right, left, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right.  I
want to pass here. I want to pass here. I'm doing something. It hurts, it hurts, it hurts,
it hurts, it hurts,
it hurts. Something's happening. What's wrong? It
hurts. Is it Kai? Is it Kai? Are you okay?
I'm going to the insurance room, Kazu-senpai.  A-senpai, a-senpai  I
didn't know that she was the one who hit her junior.I didn't know that she was the one who hit her junior.I see, I guess that's why I
hit her.I'm
sorry.  Let's go all over here
Let's go Oowanwanaaa Oran Aras can't get it off
Okay, this is difficult here.
It's okay to move forward in the water, my way, yay, yay, yay.  I
won't give it to you, Raden-chan, turn around and see where you are, Genius.  I'm
coming soon. What do you do? I ca
n't climb Jump Jump I can't climb I can't
climb Runjun, I'm going to keep pushing a good space.
Lily Lily Lily
I can't get along well
Horo Live This is a
terrible Rai This is a Folo Live
or this  It's a live performance.
Yes, I'm going to swim through the pool and swim out.
Nice, nice,
nice, nice
,
Nolan.
Ah, Nice Genius.The bread place is
no good unless I get the bread.The bread
place seems to be set so that when I get to the bread place, I'm really
hungry.  It
looks like it's going up. It's not right or left. It's left or right. I feel like I got it with a normal click. It's not a light. I don't understand it anymore. I have to eat this. I see.  It's
like eating while running, right? If you
don't eat while you're running, the
next stage will be tough.
If that's the case, it's
better to eat before you go. The
snow is deep.  You can run fast where there is nothing, you
can run, it's getting harder and harder, you're flying and it's like it's not powder snow,
so that's what it is.And it's powder
snow ahead of here, so run as fast as you can and
jump.This is where you jump.
If you hit it repeatedly, you can run faster. That's the ice.
By the way, jump, jump, render. It's
true. Jump render. The last jump. I
see.
[Music]
Oh, I
see. It's a perfect timing. This
is the
snow part.
[Music]  It's
okay to step on it.
[Music] I
see. Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's what it looked like.
Obstacles. Thank you for your reply. Thank you.
Next time, I'd like to go to the princess escort race.  I'm
going to escort you. Is there a princess today
? I'm far from being the princess or the number one princess.
But what about that team? I'm me, I'm me, I'm a
fraud. No fraud, no no, no, no I'm not a fraud.
No, no,
no. Which is difficult?  I'm having a hard time.
Princess Gade isn't there. No, no, no,
no. I don't think that princess doesn't smoke.
But it smells like cigarettes. No, it's gymnastics. Her
clothes stink. No, no, no, no.  I'm
not smoking today. I have
n't smoked today. I haven't smoked yet. I haven't smoked yet. I have
n't smoked yet. That's right.
Princess Hayaka, who smells like cigarettes. Well,
this is a team of four people.  But
first, I decided on a princess,
then there would be three knights, huh, huh,
yeah, Kaela, I thought Kaela was missing, and I
thought Kaera was missing.  Let's
get the seniors home, let's go home, find the princess, find the princess
[Music]
Oh, oh, then there's exactly four of us, so let's all
four of us try a little experience.  I'm
sure there's a lot of people here, right? Let's try it out
with the actual team and members who aren't the actual team.
Let's try it out.
[Music]
Or
Aki Agozaru White Princess Team The team is here.
Which one is more difficult for me as a knight
? Well, it might be more difficult for a princess.
Well, that's right. As a princess, I have
to tell the other members about various things,
but I'll try.  I
think you understand, so I'll explain a little while I'm doing it
. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Then, the
princess might be
Iroha, Iroha-chan. I can speak English and Japanese, so I'm sure it's Koi Roha. I've done it, I've done it, I've done it, I've
done it.  I'm a
samurai, but no, I'll protect you here, princess. You're a princess, right? Do your
best here, princess. Thank you. Do it.
Other than please, I'm a samurai, and I'm the lightest of the Ents.
Please right-click on this.
[Music]
Oh, you're beautiful,
princess, nice. You're so
cool. [Music] Let
's try it in the middle of this side [Music]
Chiara, who should I call Princess Princess here? Kia,
yes, yes, yes, yes,
Princess
Ops Mapse
[Music]
Punpun Magical Princess is here.
Gozaru Magical Puri order.
Well then, let's start.
Haehiri, let's start the game.
I'm going to protect the princess. Where do I enter from here? It's
here. The gate is open. I'll do my best. Let's get open. Let's go.
Please go ahead, I want you to get used to this first,
so yeah yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes nice nice nice
where are you right now I'm
on this turn it's going to be a bad mix so it's
a bit too bad
But where are you Opika now?  I'm going to ride for my senpai now.
That's what I'm saying.
Nice, nice, nice. Now I'm going to ride for my senpai.
Yeah
, oh, maybe it's the next button button.  Come
down, press the button,
button.
Do this for now. Are you here now? Climb again at the end.
Please move, Kado-senpai. Kado-senpai, Kado-senpai.
Move, yes, stop. Yes, come. Move, yes, yes. Yes, yes,
move. Okay, I won't do it.
Lista, ok, top ok.  Nice,
nice, okay, oh yeah, that's right,
get on here again and step on the stop, Akichi
Stop
Now, my senior's senior, move on, nice, nice,
nice.
Nice, it might be easier to tell where you are right now. I know where Chiara is right now.
Rio please step on me, uh, who is this?
Step on me,
please. I'm on top of the senior stop.
Stop stop, everyone stop stop. Ooh,
nice, nice, naooo.  Nysla
So, answer what you're making.
Restart. Restart Architecture. Architecture. Architecture. How do you
do it? Architecture. When you press the E button to
open the inventory, you'll see all sorts of things
in your creative mode-like hands.  I'm going to
go into it, so let's make
it here. We can see the theme that will make us.
Everyone is the same.
[Music]
Oh, this is it.
Eh, I'm going to make it.  I
already know what to make, so
yes, yes, I
have a book, so I have a list of things to choose from, so I
have a list, so there are options, right?
Yay, yea,
yea, one more, one more, one more
[Music]
Oh,
no, wait, I'll do my best.
Hey, this is it.
Nice, nice, my princess.
Tell me what you want to eat right now. Steak and
Ellie.  At
alwaysR, the steak
is made by combining raw beef with a knife. Hey, I wonder if
this one piece of beef is enough. I'll
buy the beef, this, and the panma, too. Elite.
Elite Pan Elite Pancake Elite
What is pancake? How do you make pancakes?
I see! Wheat, eggs, sweet, we
need berries, barley, eggs, barley, eggs, where are the eggs?
Is there one egg here? Eggs, eggs, eggs, eggs.  Cut the
wheat and sweet berries on a chopping board with 5 eggs.  There's a place
where you press a mark that looks like an axe, and
there's a mark on the left that looks
like an axe.  I've
made flour. It's really
chaotic. I don't know. I don't
know. Is it better to separate it? I don't know. Don't you know? Tepa.
Wheat and eggs are cooked together on an iron plate.
Now, let's add some flour.
Oh, I understand, I understand. I could
n't hear it at all. I couldn't hear it at all. No one was coming, but ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, they came. Okay, I'm sorry, I can't hear anything. That's right.
Wait,
I'm hungry. I'm so hungry.
Three potatoes.
Okay, thank you. Thank you.
Yes, I'm cutting wheat on a cutting board.
Ah, wheat and sweet berries, sweet berries, sweet berries, sweet
berries, sweet berries, sweet berries, sweet berries, sweet berries, sweet berries, sweet berries, sweet berries, sweet berries, sweet berries, sweet berries, sweet berries.
Cut it,
cut it,
yeah,
put the light berries in it, oh wow wow wow wow
wow I'm sure it's sweet I
can do it wow wow
now I can fry comunico and eggs on the next iron plate,
but it's a griddle.
I wonder if I should say, ``Holehopple, grill, grill, grill, wheat, flower, egg, egg, etc.'' I feel like there's a place where it's getting stronger.Maybe there's something like that on the iron plate.  Oh, it's made of flour, I'm opening it with this
Mmemme-chan
egg Uh, put the E-egg in here, uhm-
senpai, pooz-pushie
AIS I
have where, uhm, priz hot play
pleas click hot play hare
Okay, put it in there, put it
in and it disappeared, it disappeared, it
disappeared, the egg disappeared, oh, there it was, I threw it
right now, throw it my egg, throw it, nice, nice, nice, nice, pitcher, nice
egg, pitcher, wow, wow, wow,
wow, click light.  Click
Prison Oh yeah yeah now egg
yeah here oh nice nice nice nice
nice nice That's it, we've
got a zinnia, we've done that, we've done it.  It
's just a pancake, it's just a
pancake, it's a pancake, it's a
pancake, don't serve it, um, this is the serving table.
Beet pancake Oh, how about this? I
can see it, oh, it's
made. It's so nice. It looks delicious. It looks delicious. It's so cute. So cute
. Please give me that. I'll give it to you. I'll give it to you.
Nice nice too Steak Steak
Steak I'll buy Ste Ste Me
Buy Wait
oh oh
Nice ah Nice Nice Nice
Pa I need coal too Yeah yeah yeah yeah I
need coal when that happens I need coal
Yeah I'm going to grill it and grill it and grill it and I'm
just going to buy it  Noise, steak, okay, hot,
hot, hot, okay, okay, nice, nice, okay, okay, okay, let's go.
And then I get blown away, so I'm like, okay, there's
only one spot where I can guess the spot, and that's
probably the one that you can see in this colored box right in front of you.  That's
right, yes, it's four, four, four,
four colors,
four blocks, uh, out of the blocks, right now,
Iroha-chan is looking at it and looking for what's missing.
Right, just do it  Let's
try it like that. It's
difficult to explain, but the left arm is in Japanese.
First, the left arm is the upper left is orange. The upper right
is red. The lower left is red.
This is here. That means this, this, and that.  The upper left is here
Orange orange
Range light upper light light up Yeah
red light down that resoli
left left down yeah red red red yeah
right right bottom right so this this.
Apply the numbers to the four blocks you don't know, and then you're right. One two, four is okay. Well, I guess we'll have to
do that a little later as a strategy.
Otherwise, I might not be able to tell Mu-chan,
so I'm sure that's it.
I'm a smart and unusual genius, and I'm a genius,
and I'm a senior, and I just found
this, and now I know what colors are.
Hmm, what color is that? Well, what color is the answer
? The top left is orange. The top right is red. The bottom left is
red. The bottom right is red. I don't know the bottom right, but if I can figure out the color, then
I'm going to find that pink, pink, okay, nice, nice, nice.
Noneso Chews De Kochi Cheesy I'll
explain it a little later Ahsoo
Thank you Genioke Geniuso
Thank you Amo I'll defeat the monster I
'll defeat the monster Yes but from now on  All you
have to do is defeat the cicadas and those things.
Well, I heard that they won't attack your allies.
Even if this and that thing that doesn't attack your allies hits, it's PPVP, right? PVP, yes.
PvP. I
can hear the sounds of daddy and stuff.  Yes,
yes, I was here. I
'll go again. Yes, that's
right. So, should I go to the back?
Yes, that's right, it's better to protect the princess one by one.
Okay, yeah,
yeah, okay, I see, oh
, that's right, the bow is here, okay, okay, okay,
fight Aoi Lemonster, peace, do your best and protect it, oh,
nice,
Nasuo, next level 2, ah, then this too, there's
one person to protect the princess, and she's strong.  Ah, chichi, chichi,
then I'll protect the princess.A
bow might be strong.A bow is better.What is this?What is this?It's
dangerous.It's dangerous.
Who are you? Hey, please run
away! Please run away. Nice, nice, nice! Oh, I'm the old man who last trusts. I can't force him. This guy is strong. If he falls down, call me and I'll come to your rescue. Oh, it's okay, I'm dead.
Thank you, ok, ok, where's the rest
? There's someone else upstairs too.
There's a magic person upstairs. A magical guy. Wow,
where, where, where, where is that?
Maybe it's better, yeah, but it's not
strong at all Nice nice nice nice Nana yeah yeah yeah
yeah Nice oh wow
nice nice Nice nice nice nice nice nice nice Let's go back Shall we go back? Thank you for your hard work, thank you for your hard work.  I'm back, I'm back, I
'm back here, I'm back here, I'm back here, I'm back here, I'm
back, I'm back, we're we, we've been about 5
weeks, 5 weeks, 5 weeks are over.  It's
a lie, it's a lie, it's a lie, it's
true, it's true, it's true, it's
hard to explain, yeah, yeah, it seems
difficult, right click, right click,
please, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, it's hard to explain.
Oo start ah
Nonono suru
Wacha entry
entry Re entry list
Rio eh How should I press it? It's okay, it's
okay already oh
oh oh chaa and I'm so sorry
However, I was displaying everyone's icons on the stream for the number 4 person earlier,
so
could you please go back? Sorry. Sorry, sorry
.
Thank you. Thank you. I
wonder if I'm getting through to you. I'll let you know. Sorry, Sorry.
Thank you,
Hey.  I needed a little strategy, I
needed some practice, didn't I need to practice?
Maybe it's okay if I
play the game while explaining it to you. Maybe if you
understand the rules, you'll be fine.
Well, maybe I'll have the Japanese do it for me,
and I'll try my best to speak in English.
Well, I guess I'll look up the necessary English, and it looks like I
can do it, so I'll try to do it with some ingenuity.
Maybe Iha is the
type who would be better off fighting hard, because he's
good at dealing with enemies,
Minecraft Minecraft is scary, because he has a good sense of humanity.
Maybe I'll try doing all the princesses
again, maybe next time, yeah,
yeah, Otis,
I'd like to go to the Gozarujiga line.  I'm
still adjusting it,
but it seems like yes, yes, I get it, yes,
but Holo member hunting
doesn't require much practice.I don't need practice.It's
clear, yes, yes, yes, Hololive.
How well do you know the members?
I guess everyone knows me,
even if I'm a newcomer. I heard that even a newcomer won't
lose. What do you know about me?
Sorry, I'm sorry.  It's
okay to apologize, I lost, so I apologized right away. Well, the battle against Kiba is a game where two people fight, so by the day of the game, we have to decide on a pair of people. Ah, I
see, I see.  I
don't think the trauma of the two of them will come back to life, but that
two-person group with the even number is not Touma at all.So, the
one with the even number is the trauma.Yes,
the two of them become a pair.
I guess it's okay if I get it. I'm not
going to participate, so I'll leave it to everyone. Well, everyone's going to participate. I guess everyone should participate.
Everyone should participate. Everyone should participate.
[Laughs]
Well, we're going to be participating too. That's
right. Well, today is
today.
Now, for now, we
need someone who has to press that button.
For example, what will it look like?
If you want to try it, then yes, I'll ask you to do it with Azu-san and
Iroha. Well
then, Az-san, try
right-clicking on the white Kiba line and
pick it up, then yes.
I got the one that rides on my hand, so I asked the person who rides it to take a look at it, and here
it is.Wow,
how strong is this?  It
's like you're
running around and
Zuzu-chan attacks, yes, it's an attack. I see.OPERSON
Yes,
Allhor
[Laughs]
Hor
also punches each other, punches each other, and competes for the number of kills.
Oh, even if you hit the number of kills, you wo
n't die just by getting hit, but I'm pretty sure there are only 3 hearts
attached. 3
haha, that's what happens when you start the game.
Maybe so, but there's only one set.  I don't have one,
so I probably can't do it, but yeah, yeah, I'll
try one more group, then Yellow,
and then one more group, oh yeah, yeah, that's
right, senpai, please use me as a horse.I ca
n't help it, then.Okay, let's go and ride.  Ta
Hey, where did you go? I
can't lose to that Lereret. Light click. Now let's get that
Kaela on the orchestra. Hey,
Kiara, I'm sorry, but
please wait for a while.
Oh,
this, Kaera.  It's
a little weird.
When I right-
click on a book that doesn't exist, I see a block that looks like it's going to turn into an elephant. I
click on the block.
What should I press when I open the book? What should I press when I open the book?
[Music]
Oh, that's nice, even if White isn't there right now, you
should open this. Open, uh,
right-click while holding the book.  So
click on the block in the middle of white Oh,
nice Taa-chan
Alright, let's start, let's go, let's go,
let's go When we're fighting, there's something
dangerous coming from here and here. It's
dangerous, it's dangerous.  I
did
it, it's amazing, I did it, go go, go go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!  Alright, alright, alright, alright, alright, alright,
alright, alright, alright, alright, alright,
yayashi
[music]
te
kekekekekekeke yay
yay yay yay yay
yay
We
're strong, we're strong, we're strong, right?
This is what we call a game. It's a bond. We're all
born. We're all white. We're all doing it. We're
all doing it. We're all
fighting on the same field.
[Music]
At the same time.  At the same time, wow, will
beall
TE, so 21 teams, 21
teams, 21 teams Yes, that's true, but the more you
swing your sword around, the more you can kill.It
feels like the strategy is good.I see, it's
kind of surprising.  If you
defeat the general, you'll get a good score.I
see, so
maybe the general will become the leader of each group, Mio, Miko, Subaru, etc.  It would be really
nice if you could take it with you
. When one of them is fighting with the other,
White is already beaten up and both of them.  It's like
going fishing, fishing, fishing,
etc. It seems like a bit of a strategy,
right? Let's focus on that, and let's
all go and
punch an octopus.
Moreover, I think we need to decide on a pair of people before the actual performance. I
see, it's okay to have fun. It's okay.
There's a gorilla here. It's okay. Oh yeah, it's a gorilla.  I'm not going to get
lost, so it's okay, gorilla. I'm going to be a gorilla. I'm going to be a gorilla. I
'm not going to leave. I'm going to get there. I
say yes. Well, I guess I'll
go to Hunting just in case. I
feel like I can't go yet.  Well, I guess I can't do it yet,
okay? Well, I'll just mark the place somehow,
and then I
'll go.
Yes, all I need is knowledge. This is where we need to get along and
get along.
Friendly, this is
me.Hanta.Those nipples are sticking out, but
on YouTube, is it okay?Is it true that you say the neck?
Is it strong?I think it was bad after all.Gozaru Yomi-
senpai.Also, it's pink,
but it's okay.It's pink, so I guess it's
safe.  By the way, in English,
those nipples are Nepos, Neponels are round,
Nils Nils are round, and Bars Nils
is a figure because there are two.  I
wonder if that's what it's going to be like? No, it's not, it's not, it's not. When the actual Susu stage is here, how will it be, who will stand where, and what will it look like? Good evening.
Well, for example, the red team.
Three representatives from the catcher side and the hunter side
come out, but
when the hunter comes out, the red team is all
off, and the white team and yellow team are all off.
Participation Uh, there will only be one
grouper. There will be 3 hunters. There will be 3 people in each team. There
will be 6 people per red team,
but I will divide it into 2 times. It will be 33.
Ah, off HPERTeambok.  So,
when the red team and the hunter come out,
the yellow team and the white team are the ones who run away.
So, the three red and red members, uh, and all the other white and yellow members. Yeah, yeah,
TE explanation, thank you.
Ah, there's a question.For example, there are
people who catch animal poop like ``Eroa'' and ``Aaaaaaaaaa''.
Okay, for example, if it
's ``Ajakanatan,'' then it's uh, right.  I guess you can use it by clicking. An
item will appear. Yes, I see. I see.
What is that? The rope thing. It's
not Kula, it's the lead that catches it.
Lead, yeah, lead.
Right-click on the lead.  yes
It's got a leash attached to it, and it's being taken away, and it's being taken
away, and I can't run away anymore. I
can't run away, right-click on this hunting, and I'm going to
decide whether or not this cage is, uh, an animal.  I
'll do it for you No no no animal
[Music]
Oh
Come on, let's go inside, let's go inside If it's a hit, it'll be in. If it's
a miss, it
won't come in. If you catch it, it's heaven. Is this okay?  The
hits and misses were decent.  The
experts are doing it for you,
so don't get into it. It's okay because it's an animal. That's
probably okay
. Who are you? It's not an animal,
so remember that. Angel Angel, my
angel, no object, no animal,
no
animal.  Yes, there are 3,
so it's a game where the hunter has to catch a random question, and it's really
interesting.Oh,
sorry, I just have one more question.  Do
people who aren't you run or
do things like that?Ah, run, oh, so run away,
oh, oh,
run away.There
are all kinds of things like this, so use them to your full advantage, like
climbing buildings and things like that.  It's
like running away, running away
,
oh, I
see, come on, ooh, it's amazing, yea, yea, you can easily right-click to lead the lead, get kicked, oh, oh, it's interesting, it's
fun, it looks like it's fun, I want to do it quickly
Instigator
[Music]
[Laughs] I'm
really looking forward to it. I'm looking forward to it.
So that's it for the explanation of the competition and the competition.
Thank you,
thank you. Thank you. I
really respect your
seniors. You sound like a good person who worked hard.
Thank you.  Looks like it's
okay, I don't have any questions Kuen Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa-aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
please you good
sleep enough to me, senpai, you're busy, but please sleep properly.  Let's go to
sleep, no, sleep, sleep, sleep, it's okay, okay,
okay, thank you, thank you,
yes, please go to sleep, sleep a lot, please.  I'm going to
practice here for now.Then I
heard that the broadcast will be disbanded here.If
you continue, you
can continue or leave it.You can continue.Okay, okay, you can continue.
Yes, I practiced and practiced.
Oh,
practice, practice you
PRBEAMIwantpractice
alittle
bGoBack
sleepOK,
okay, then I'll just stream it here.Thank
you for your hard work.Thank you for your hard work, everyone.Keep up the good work.Unext.Again
Hey, aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa right now it's like these people can't hear it right now everyone can
only hear it to the listeners.
Thank you very much for speaking in a place where I can't hear you.It was
really fun.I
was able to participate in the Namine Sports Day and seeu Gorillade.
So, I've been able to connect with a newcomer, so I'm
looking forward to seeing you at the highest rank.Well, I'll double
check this one more time,
and this is what A-chan made for me.For
now, I think it's confirmed.  Well, the
competition is structured like this. I don't
think there will be any changes, but I
'm sure there were entries, so if something were to happen, it would probably be on the day. It's
like everyone has changed, right? This is Home Hunter, I'm interested.  I
wonder if they'll take me away? She's a cute, beautiful girl, so there's a slight chance that Katas will be taken away. That's okay, but on the day of the call, it looks like they'll be splitting the call group into two, so I'm still not sure if I'll get a spot.  I
don't know who will take it, but I don't know who will
take it.It's still a bit of a mystery whether I'll take it or not.Also, I'm going to
do some cute things on the other side.He's
cute.He's cute.I can't help but think he's so cute.  I want to
eat it, I want to eat it, right?
So Jata-san,
let's stop here for now. Thank you everyone for streaming.
If Katas takes the frame, I
'll do my best to use everyone's camera, but I
couldn't include that one.  What's that about Opti
? That zooming thing. The
athletic venue version of this cat hasn't come out yet
. Hey, there's no zoom this time. Why
do you get as close as you can without a MOD?
This is how Kia is going to do its best this time, and if an
updated version of the MOD comes out by that time or that day, it
will be a bit of a sudden download,
but it might become a little transparent.
Anyway, I'm going to try to think of ways to communicate
as much as possible with all the people overseas, so
this Saturday is tomorrow, and the
day after tomorrow, everyone.  please  I'm looking
forward to it. I hope everyone is looking forward to it. I think I'll practice behind the scenes,
but all I can do is Sane Kaneda's voice,
so I wish I'd put out a follow-up. I do
n't want to. I was really good at it. I'm talented.  I
felt it, but I thought it was a follow-up one-chan hot pot.
Yes, I want to agree with the princess.
So, how cute is she? It's
cute. She's so cute when she's next to her.  So, see you soon. I'll
play the ending. Thank you for today,
everyone. Bye bye, let's take a look.
Bye bye bye
[Music]
Bye, here we
come.
[Music]
Thank you everyone, bye bye Hanakaze. There's
still a little bit of splash left,
but it's much better now, so please everyone. The
recording was also completed successfully.  I've
been posting a little less often, but thanks to that, I'm
getting better, so don't worry. I
don't have a fever. Thank you everyone. Take a good rest. Good night.
[Music]
Bye.