K I say that quietly because we are in
Shinjuku in Tokyo in Japan in the world
to record um a very special
video well what might it be there's some
kind of reward I have heard at the end
of this that if we fulfill all of the
missions we will be rewarded I'm excited
so first and foremost I cannot tell you
the missions yet because I don't know
are randomized missions I think there is
eight of
them so hopefully we can complete all of
them here in shuku I think so I think I
chose a good place so let me pick the
first
[Music]
one find weird English oh that's easy in
Japan then there is many many shirts or
other objects where you might find weird
English on it all right then it is a
mission mission
start okay we have infiltrated a store
that has many stores we will now go
through it and find some weird English
let's go is that is that weird English
no that's pretty good
English that's also pretty good English
I think the store has two good English
we need to go to a clothing store
but like a cheap one don't mind about
talking by the way we can just cut it
out when you're
[Music]
talking oh okay
okay yeah don't worry we can always like
put some music over it or so cute
clothes I want to
shop we English there is that we English
I mean it's not I'm looking for
incorrect rice cake every once in a
while you find someone who's irent
is that
weird wait there's a lot of English
there SP sparkly English you're too good
to take my eyes
off you'd be lying what you would be
lying H heave in what where do you where
do I read this you're just too good to
be
true can't take my eyes off you you'd be
ly you'd be ly what you'd be ly heave is
this so English to touch I want to I
want to hold you so
much at long last love has arrived and I
thank God I'm I'm
allive I'm alive you're okay maybe it's
correct it's some song lyrics or
[Music]
there I can not see okay
judge not good not
weird that is
weird mission
complete all right this was a great
success we have found uh weird English
now next challenge let me randomly pull
it from my hat which is here
here I go I'm going
[Music]
in win something from a crane game I'm
really bad at crane games but I will do
my
best ooh I smell I sense kuko it's
close my favorite place oh there's one
here one please hold while I'm trying to
find something that is not strongly
copyrighted
okay I think I found something I
genuinely want this colorful
bear um I guess we should probably aim
for the
closest oh I can move it as much as I
want with in the time here we go try
number
one it's grabed
[Music]
okay hold it no
come on you have the power yo yo is that
good okay this is good maybe I get
both oh oh that's
bad only was here oh that point
closer oh o that's not good because
[Music]
my yay it's not my favorite color but
it's cute mission
[Music]
complete all right guys this is now our
mascot to talk for me uh we're going to
pull the next challenge are you guys
ready okay this bear is going to go pull
it
[Music]
oh it is get find a weird vending
machine oh that's interesting because I
think I saw one already uh around here
so that should be easy I think it's
pretty weird like Japan has the typical
vending machines which are great already
but we're looking for one of the weird
ones there's like I've seen like dashy
soup stock ones before and I've seen um
some that sell clothing as well all
kinds of things but this one is kind of
perfect for me let's
go oh my
God so
cute okay got a little bit distracted by
some cute ass
kittens and some people even got to
carry them on their lap not
us why
not 100% fresh orange juice feed me
orange indeed feed me Orange
please let's get
it uh what down oh the cup is in oh it's
producing already show show show show
show he's
producing where's
draw wait what use the knob to open the
lid tap the inside PL on tap inside
[Music]
PL orange juice it has like a plastic
lid so I'm going to like poke it with
the straw once I get
it tap it I like
this it's it's there but I it's not
coming up come on come on come on oh I
reached it okay that's kind of difficult
it's was stuck I think yeah now it's now
it's there okay here we go
mission
complete the bear is going to take a
sippy instead of
me it's so fresh fresh orange juice all
right I'm going to pull the next message
here we
go find a gacha machine and pull
something out of it let's go the capsule
machines easy I think I know where the
one is like over there on one of these
floors there's a whole floor with gacha
machine H gacha capsule machines I'm
pretty sure let's go so I'm pretty sure
that because of the construction here
they had a floor oh yeah right here with
a million uh capsule
machines yippe let's find a good
one 500
yen what a
deal I hope the company is paying me
back for
this will again place your bets
now more
who is it e e let's go let's free her
from this somewhere where it's more
quiet let's free her y
EA y wow so
lucky she's so cute okay can you tell us
what our next challenge is yes of
course find Japan limited ice cream in
Baskin
Robins I got you fam I'm on it I love
Baskin Robins how did you know thank you
for this challenge back into the ball
with you no that goes out don't
[Music]
know what that's
scary it's talking to us like like it's
an alien all right I know Shinjuku so
well by now sadly that I know
somewhere
within sub there's a Baskin
Robins found
it all right let's find out what
Japanese only or Japan only flavor Basin
Robins currently
has they currently have a
gooda collaboration going on but also
because it just became o wait is it
October no what am I saying it's
September but they're already showing
the October flavor September
right so September flavors are Mango
Tango Tea oay cotton candy lemon sherbet
that doesn't sound very Japan only but
I'm sure the good dive of Baskin Robins
Club this probably Japan only so I'll
get one of these and of course my
favorite that they have here throughout
the whole year lot potion
31 my favorite
manager John which one do you
want Oh Mango Tango all right I'll get
it for you ta I got a pretty fancy good
diva cup and of course it has the new
flavor and my favorite flavor and for
manager Chan we have the which also a
new flavor the Mango Tango is this like
chocolate gooda chocolate and hazel nuts
apparently here we go
H I'm barely getting the hazelnut
wait it's too much too much chocolate
and not mixing my love potion oh well
it's tasty it's really like rich
chocolate flavor that's for
sure and there's little pieces of
something crunchy I think this just
chocolate chips or something like
that yeah this really
good all right we'll finish this up and
then we'll go to the next mission but
for now this is a mission
[Music]
complete okay that was really good now
let's pull the next
[Music]
[Applause]
challenge okay it is H find exit8
interesting that's quite um convenient
because we are kind of more or less
close to
station and there is Exit 4 there all
right I'll try to find exit 8 let's go
sped up version of me finding Exit 8
speed it up cow
[Music]
carrot wait
there there's so fast okay so to the
left through what through the toilet no
I guess through this exit
[Music]
right oh that
one okay
mission complete shall we walk through
at
least that was really faster than
expected here proof exit eight we're
outside this is surprising I swear I got
lost in Shinjuku station so many times
does this look like the game guys
stairs stairs
yippe
okay I made it we're
in
kabuk which means mission complete you
be okay let me pick another challenge
then here I go by the way oh my God is
that my love it new jeans I think so
here you go new jeans give us a
challenge oh find a trash can in Tokyo H
and the condition is for it to not be a
pet bottle trash can which those you can
find quite a few of but a normal trash
can that will accept any kind of trash
is more difficult I have this feeling
that maybe if we go to like a public
toilet it will have a trash can I'm
going to try to go back into the station
I have more trust in finding one there
ironically and it's not as hot and humid
down there
PMA I have de signed her name she is
slowly coming down the stairs there is a
public toilet which is uh like outside
of the station but inside of the station
if you know what I mean so let's try to
get in there am I solving these too fast
and too easily I'm just too too good at
[Music]
this yeah you can do anything in
Shinjuku going through the Shinjuku
underground maze once again speed it up
cow carrot
[Music]
I don't know about men's bathrooms but
there's always tiny trash cans for
women's products and ladies bathrooms so
that's what I have just found while I
felt really weird and creepy about it
that's why I'm quickly made a run for it
so mission complete I say
yippe all right this nice little corner
will reveal to me the new mission
find something time limited Kang in a
Japanese convenience store okay that's
easy just need to find a convenience
store but generally that should be
simple let's go it's Japan so we'll
surely come
across a convenience store randomly but
maybe let's take an exit but not Exit 8
cuz that scares
me this is our Target
it a stream of people let's go let's go
let's
go let's go
what's there's usually always like time
limited uh lipin
drinks no wait that's something else
they usually always have a Time limited
flavor well for once it is not according
to my plans this looks
K but it doesn't say so but it
definitely is
but that won't count no usually has like
some kind of like seal like this it says
Kong
G oh censor that but that is that is
gante 100% a certain green Nintendo man
okay I think this counts it says
seasonal limit key set G I think that
counts mission complete
okay everybody that's it we have
successfully completed all eight
missions I didn't even realize but that
was a last mission I'm back where we
started now it's night time and yeah you
want to know what the reward is well
let's find
out all right show me what is the
[Music]
surprise oh my God what finally oh it is
my 2.0 life today
reveal oh my God didn't I say that I
wouldn't reveal it before well it seems
I have changed my mind because it is now
actually quite interesting quite
something you want to see so make sure
you guys will be there on this date to
check out my new self it'll be exciting
it will be Dem year it will be
magnificent so thank you so much for
watching this thank thank you for
cheering me on during my missions it was
totally not
rigged and thank you for H celebrating
my fourth year
anniversary yay and in German we say Al
Vin bye-bye