[music]
ya
oh
[music]
[music] mio [music]
ya
[music] oh [music] oh [music]
miomi
[music]
oh
mi
[music]
oh
Oh
[Music]
Miya
Oh
[Music]
[Music] Miya [Music] Ojio [Music] Ji [Music] Oh [Music] Miya [Music] Ya [
Music] Oh
[Music]
Oh
[Music]  ]
Miomi
[Music]
O
Miji
[Music]
Oya
[Music] O [
Music] O [Music] Mio [Music] Miomi [Music
]
Oya
[Music]
Oyao
Mi
Ato
Okay,
Okay, Okay,
Okay, hello
everyone Hello, I
didn't open it. I
was surprised. Oh no, that's wrong. When I start, I
always start after I go to that loading screen.
Yeah, yeah, the loading screen
started streaming as soon as I got it. I
see. It was pitch black. It was pitch black. It's
okay
, it's okay, it's okay. It's okay. Are you all set? Umi is all set. Are you all set? Nami is
all set. Yes, today is that squirrel.  Tori will
explain the rules and guide us, so
today the three teams practicing are Ifi
, Rane, Chiara, Lele,
Taunra, and Pabu.
Oh, actually, wait a minute, I'm going crazy.  I
can't move. I can't move. Yeah, it's true. It's really a
bug. I'm
going to restart it one more time. Oh, it's Japanese. It's
set to Japanese. Yeah, it's not. If it's set to Japanese,
then wait.  Adjusting everyone's volume Here and
there, yeah, that's right, that setting. If you press that escape button,
something will come out. It's just me. Yeah, I
set the voice level to 300%.
Why is it so messed up? It's quite loud, I
thought, but only one person added 300.  I do
n't know why, but I
always thought it was a demon's job.It's
scary how loud it is.That
voice chat was 300.It's the same voice
chat that I used in the previous Holodoro series.
Maybe, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, at that time, I'll
make it plus 300. Yeah, yeah,
I don't participate in Hodo, so I do
n't know. No, yeah, maybe I did that at that time. Yeah, yeah,
yeah, I'm going to sleep, maybe I'm going to sleep. Probably,
maybe sound 2.  Maybe I don't like it, but it's
perfect for my frame.It's the chat side
2.I don't have a bed, I don't have a log, it
's okay.
So
[Music]
Now we're in the middle of the day.
Thank you very much. Thank you.
[Music]
[Music] I
made it all myself.
Sorry, I put it in again.
Nice.
And then,
Dada
Kura
[Music]
Doul, where should I start explaining?
Where,
here, here, I'm going.
Okay, yes, yes
[Music] I'll just
leave it here for now. Well, let's
do it one more time.
[Music] There
are 5 games,
but I'm
going to explain the rules to you, erm, I haven't finished the pre-games yet, but I'm going to explain the rules to you.
Raids collect and exchange it for the final game's must-
haves. The event includes
challenging gimmicks,
platforms,
brain-damaging stuff, and tasks that require teamwork.
Need to search for Chisto for now
There are various places such as inside blocks, so all I have to do is
search for it. It looks like it's a
treasure, but I want the location to be a surprise right now, so I
guess I'll just explain the rules.  I want you to want to be
sorry
if you are regrettable, I will explain the next game
[Music]
Yes
Lida
Over there, that
Maze thing, oh Maze, that's
how it works, but I don't know it either, but Nuna was
doing it. Yeah,
Redstone, I don't understand it, so
[laughter]
[Music] It's
safe and secure.
[Music] That's what it's
for.
Introduction
[Music]
Simplybe
say Mu's platform is here,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, it's just, um, Saimsez,
everybody's doing a lot, but um, I'm going to explain a little bit
beexplalittle
B, uh, each Hua is going to stand on stage,
uh, give directions to Kinkai.
Yes,
India is doing well, Ido is doing well, and I think he's
still a little better at time, as the show will be held on the Indonesian train, so all talents should learn some simple Indonesian words beforehand.  Hmm, I
still don't remember either. No, it's okay, it's okay, it's
okay.
Teams earn emeralds based on how much they want to give to C.
Oh yeah
[Music]
Everyone remember this,
I'll teach you the words Kiri Kiri Kiri Kiri
left and yeah Kanan
Kanaka
right
Majima
Yeah behind you yeah
[Music]
from door
Gataa 12345 That's right
Tiga
empa
Emma
Marima and
ter
Somehow Kokoro  You can do it somehow with your mind.Is
this a
clan?  Can you
go to the left? Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
, if you say Hap, it's almost like you can go to the right.
Once you remember it, it's easy to win.
Ajiko squats, Jinko squats. What else is there? How do you
do a jinji-un throw?
You don't have to worry about that, you don't have to worry about that. You
can do anything with that throw.
No, it's a
real game. I'll
give it up. It's the one with the button to throw.
From here to here, it's from here.
[Music]
Oh, I'm sorry. It's okay. I heard there's going to be a wall later here. The
wall.  I can't do it, yeah, yeah, yeah, I can't do it, left Kari
is Times, that's right,
Ka is something like once
or twice, or if it's a door red, it's like two times.
Mera is
probably that
Shimera is this for the time being. Red, good,
Rima. I want to do it while watching this. If someone
says Rima, it's 5 times. If someone says Rima, it's 5
times. That's right. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well then, I think it's easier to remember that way.
Well,
now you understand, right? Well, I guess I'll
just go out anyway. Well, I'll be here, then I'll
be here, then I
'll be here, and it'll stink.
It's the opposite.  I see.
[Music] That's it. I
don't know who I'm talking about here. I'm going
to give you some instructions. Finally, I'm
going to make sure that I can stand in the impression spot.
This is oh yeah.  Yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, they're both going to the left or right
. What
is this? Yeah, I get it. I mean, we're in two pairs of each other.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, I get it. It's
okay, in my heart.  Are you ready
? Yes, let's start. Let's
go with Oris. OKexample
willwillhave
Will There are
three stages.
When the countdown is over, I guess we'll move on.
[Music]
Where should I turn?
Hey, look at the squirrel, look at the squirrel, look at the squirrel. I wonder if the squirrel is facing the squirrel. Yes, the
nerd is definitely
on the stage.  Hey
Waronpa hey
Ronpao is nice and nice I
see I see
If it's the same then it feels like Bell is there
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Ueronpamajimaji Saka
Ria Et Haru Ue
Same Same Same
Same Same
[Music] I
did it, I did it, so next time I
want to see Rene and Chiara, so let's go over here
Oh, yes, go Rene
[Music]
Kio is okay, it's so-and-
so time  That's why you don't have to worry about it
[Music]
Time oh
I see, it's red, it's red
[Music]
SL
slok
slok stay 1
Hanan 3
[Music]
2TRUSTTRUST
uporafter
BACK
BACK I see
2 Wow
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] I
want to go like this
for the time being [Music] [Music] There are about 10 stages, right? There are about 10 stages.The first one was the
Stan stage, and the other one
was the Stan stage, but there are about 10 more stages.
It ’s just a jumping jumping jumping jumping jumping Jump Running Running Running Running Running Left Left Like Left.
There are about 10 stages, so
please do your best.If you do your best, you'll
be able to do it if you hit at least half of the stages.Let's
move on to the next mini-game.Hmm
, next time,
Rango.My poor memory will come out.  It's
okay if you don't remember it, it's okay, it's okay, just have fun, right?
That's
right, that's right.  The
team
is made up of the seller and the form.The
body is made of colorful wool, and the Ur side cuts off the wool from the top in the lunar realm.The
team that sells cuts off the upper part of the wool, and
Formen is the star team.
By destroying the upper floor, you
can also drop the opponent's foreman to the lower world.If the
foreman stays on top, the opponent's foreman
of the color of the chimu
will win.  Let's go
Wool
[Music]
Hey, there's one person at the bottom,
and there's probably a bottom here as well.
This is the top and the bottom is here. It's better
to memorize it while you're doing it. Yeah, yeah,
one more thing.  There's a lot of floor space
at the bottom, take the bottom, and it's divided. There's a person on the bottom
and a person on the top. The
person on the top can get the wool.
Cut the wool and
take it out from under the wool.It's
fine if you can get it off.For
example, I cut it, and my sister is on top.She
gives birth to the wool of her team's color.  Yeah, I'm going to paint it and give birth to it later.When it's
empty and my sister changes her team's
color, the team with as many colors as that will
win.I guess there's wool in that color
somewhere, too.  Somewhere
later, it's
handed to me. Oh yeah, that's the other team. For example,
Chiara is on top of me, and my sister
hears that Chiara is on the left over there. I cut it, and
then that Chiara drops it.
Yeah, I guess it's a win if Chiara drops it.
I see. I see. Yeah, I see. Yeah, I see. [Music] [Music] Let me take it away. Let's
take a look. From here. From above. From above. It's okay from above.
If you look at it from above, it will look like Ukaru, so the squirrel will look like Hum.Oh
yeah,
yeah, that's right, you cut it from the bottom, but the one on the top
will be the squirrel.Oh hey, simple,
simple, simple,
simple.  That
's it, that's right.
For example, I see.
[Music]
That's right. I see. That's right. That's right. That's right. That's right. That's right. That's right. That's right. I'm going to make a
cut. It feels like I can open it quickly. If I
press green, the game is over.  I guess it's like,
yeah yeah,
yeah yeah, the more of that power
there is, the more that guy wins,
so oh yeah, let's do our best anyway, sister,
which is better, upper or lower? It's the bottom, so cut off the top and
put it in.  That's right, you
can do that cutting on the top,
but what I'm saying is, I
can break the white wool myself, but I can't break the opponent's color,
but the team below can, uh, break down.
Yes, the members can also destroy other team's colors.
Ah, I see. If I were on top, I would have
no choice but to include them.
Oh yeah,
that's right, I can destroy the white wool,
but I guess it also destroys the other team's wool.  It's
easier to understand from above, so I'm
not going to do it below. I
want to do it.
Oh, I'm going to
take the wool under the wool. Is
that a cutter?
Well, what
should I do? What should I do?
That wool is
that jadiITU
CjadiCaku
Ah, only those below
can break it, but they
can break it with that,
yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, okay, wait, I understand
[Music] I
know that's my specialty.  My
senpai is at the top. It
seemed difficult, so I put it at the top.
Oh,
yeah, I guess it's fine either way.
But yeah, you
can do it without thinking about it. If you're at the top, that's right. I'm
at the bottom.
[Music]
[Laughs]
harusfirstperson
person
Fmenuilang
[  Music]
BL
[Music]
Kiara is an orange here.
If you have one stack or a stack of oranges, I
think 1 um, 2 stacks will be enough.
2 stacks of
stacks. Is that okay? I've
fallen quite a bit from the game. Wait a minute.
It's not okay, you're so
cute
A
[Music]
ADIASAMASkiriuoh
Ijangandiah
Bbisa
AMAtidakADADI
okekiriKIKANkalau
salahjatsalahikiri
kirikiriKANKAN
[Music]
Kana people
[Music] Are
cute people too cute? Cute people are seriously too cute. They're cute, really
.  The above thread is too cute, is
n't it? [Music] Kanao, is it too cute?
[Music]
Loet
Thank you very much, thank you very much.
B
[Music]
Meg
ITU
F
FPleasePRfok
[Music]
Position  But I can't do it right now, where are you?
[Music] Why
can't I do it on the left? I'm here. I
don't know. I don't know now. Look at me. I see.
Where, where, where? It's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's
dangerous.  Danger, danger, danger, danger Danger, danger,
danger, being dropped, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous.
I see.
[Music] I see.
If there were three teams, it would be even more powerful. I see. I see.
Senpai: When you made a mistake and placed it this way, it's
okay if you don't follow it.
[Music]
So,
would you like to switch?
Let's try a little.  Let's do that, let's do that. That kill and the
jump. I feel like it's okay if we don't have to jump. We
did that earlier, so let's go. Let's go down. The person under there, uh,
press F1.  I can't remember my partner's
name, so I
have to press F1,
so I'm sorry I didn't know where your sister was just now.
Yeah,
yeah, if I do that first, something might happen.
Yeah, if you
give me that color, I might be able to find the place. Yeah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
I get it, I get it, I get it, that's
what you say, that kind of thing,
uh, please. Yes, it feels like this,
oh, um, ta.
Let's hit [Music] I'm
ready [Music] [Music] I'm ready
[Music]
Desu 4
3 Where's Daa
BL
Danger, danger,
danger I wonder if it's here. It feels
good, it feels good, it feels
good, it feels good  It feels good, it
feels good, it feels good, it feels good, it feels good
[Applause]
[Music] I was
left
[Music]
have I
got it, oh, there's more
left over, white, so-so
[Music]
[ __ ]
4 Huh?  What do you think? Do you want to do it again? It's
okay,
sister, are you going to be on the top or bottom?
The difference is that it's difficult. It's difficult. I'll go to the bottom.
Thank you. There will be 4 teams later, so we'll be having a lot of fun. Is that so?
4 teams at once? Yeah, it's
not 22 at once.  There's 44 people out there,
so it's a lot of trouble. That
's right. It's not bad. If you open up a lot, you
can hit the other people so that they fall. You can hit the ones on the top. You
can hit the ones on the top.  It's okay to fall, it's okay to
fall, it's okay to fall, it's
okay to fall, it's going to be a battle, it's going to be a battle, it's going to be a
fight.  It's
going to be 3 people 3 people
or 3 people at the same time or 3 people at the same time So that Yu will win that later That
final land will be there ah 3
Team 3 teams will do 33 and final final Yeah yeah
tournament yeah yeah
yeah 6  I thought it would be 6, but that's
too bad. [Laughs] That's pretty bad
. It's going to turn out to be a mess.
Oh my.
[Music]
[Music] There were
people. In the end, it was
the 3rd round, not the final, but that 3rd
round. All 6 people.  Ah, okay, okay, okay 3 We're
playing a game, right? Soo game. That
's right. It's so
bad. It's so bad.
Everyone's going to fall at once. I'm sure they'll be panicking later.
If I can get to that green color, my mom
is here.  That's okay, okay, okay,
okay, I'll do my best. If that's the case, then there's the
white team, even if it's not the white oil, there's another
team of other colors, too. I guess I'll destroy them.
Well, my sister doesn't have an opponent yet,
huh?
Don't just leave me alone, just punch me. That's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's
right.  The more I look at it, the more
I think it's a win. I thought so too.
But no, the one who remained at the top won.
screens
or I see.
Yeah, yeah, no.
Senior, I heard that six teams would be participating at the same time.
Why don't we try one more round and do it with everyone? I want to
see that chaos. I
want to see it. I want to experience it.
6 Yeah up and down
6 Yeah
BL
[Music]
makes
HORN
[Music]
I can hear the sound
again
[Music] Let's do it
[Music]
[Music] There's something
wrong with that,
but that's how it
begins
[Applause]
Yone
[Music] It's
so bad, it's so bad, it's so bad, it's so bad, it's
so bad
[applause] It's so bad, it's so bad, it's so
bad, it's so bad, it's so
bad.
Okay, I see, I see. I own a house.
I should just come in here normally.  [
Music]
[Music]
That
's right. I heard it's a smartphone. It's vibrating.
[Music]
That's it.
[Laughs]
Mao, are you ready?
[Music]
[Music] I'm sorry.
Okay, okay.  You can hit it, you
can hit it 35 seconds 30 seconds, it's okay OK
OK OK
Onju Oung Range Don't forgive or orange
orange Green Green Green Green Green Green Green Green Green Green Green Green Green Green Green Green
Greenery Wear  Stop Stop
Stop Stop It's overlapping, it's overlapping, it's
overlapping
[Music] I see, everyone's still alive, so I'm going to do it. I see, I'm counting. [Music] I made a
mistake when I stroked it, but Nene-san immediately
fell asleep.  Give it to me
[Music]
It's delicious,
it's delicious, it's delicious. It's not a good idea to keep hitting me. You can stay. Yes, that's right, that's it. It's delicious. I've
tried both, but it's pretty good. The one with
more people fills up.  Maybe I'll fill it right away, so there
might not be a hole to
fill.Yeah, yeah.That's right, so I'll give priority to filling that hole.Well,
that might be better, if you put in the number of people.I'll fill it
right away, so there might be people who are hard to fill, so yeah, yeah,
yeah.  Okay, ok, ok, yeah,
then I'll hit you hard. Oh, I got it. I got it. It's the first treasure, treasure. The sky makes the same movement as before, this, and two more. [Music] It's okay to do that.  Eh, where are the predictions? It's
this, this, this, this, the next. Let's
play a game.
[Music] Well, we
don't have much time, so let's play the last game.
[Applause] I'll
put them all in.  I wonder if it's teku, rice. Well,
rice is okay. I feel like I need food other than rice.
What kind of rice do you have,
senpai? It's chicken, okay
?
Let's have the same rice for now. No, senpai, please use this.
Potatoes.  Potatoes,
potatoes, okay,
okay, potatoes, potatoes, potatoes.  willbeUStheVCAfter this, we
'll be using the VC group, so we'll
just have to practice in a group
group.Do we need a group voice chat?I don't need that group voice chat.For
now, let's practice the settings.Let's
go to the settings chat.
Even if it's a group chat, it
's a group, uh, yeah, it's a group, right? It
's a create group. I see, who makes it? I'll
make it, then I'll make it. I'll wait and let you know when it's done. I'll probably make it tomorrow.  It's not coming
in, so
what's going on?
[Laughs] Yeah, it's coming in.
[Laughs] It says, "Hey, I'm here. I do
n't know what it is. I don't know. I don't know. It's
about 1111. Yeah, it's about 11. I think it's about 11.  I
think I'll change the password later, but I'll go with 1 for now.Yeah,
right now, that voice is that chat, so I
can't hear the voices of other teams.That's right, that's
right, that's right, that's why we can talk in chat.
Naoishooooooooooooooooo,
lady, I suddenly came out and said, ``What's the password?'' But I thought, ``
Maybe you can't hear me.'' Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I
ca
n't hear you, so let's leave the normal group chat.  I wonder if the
user of Kamiteru
[Music] is
back.
Hey, Ern is already here. Hey, I'd like to explain the next game. Yes, this is the last game,
but, uh, Maze Fight.
That's right, the
team consists of a fighter and a navigator.I
see.The navigator
guides the fighters through a maze that transforms into one body.Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, the navigator's mission is for
the fighter to defeat the other fighter.  The
goal is to help the team,
and the team with Fighter
advances to the final round.In
that
case, you see, I was the one who made the move.Then, it's okay for the older sister to be the one who moves.I don't know what to do, but one of us should
move properly.  I
thought it would be better, so I
thought, Okay, I'm probably going to die, so I'm going to die. Well, I did that a while ago.
Well then,
here we are
[Music]
Mel
It's the best game to enter, so I'm going to turn
that emera that I've been able to get really well into into that weapon,
oh yeah, so there's a lot of it. I guess it's like if you
win the game, you can get a good weapon.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, the
weapon changes depending on the number of emeralds, yeah,
yeah, yeah, if you don't wait, you'll have to go bare.So, if you're
bare, you'll be a fighter.You
can do it with your spirit, somehow, somehow,
somehow.  You can do it, right here, right
here, over here, over here, over here, right here, go above here.
Hey, there's no weapon, there's no weapon here. Yes, we're all using the same weapon for the time being. Yes, this is practice, so the weapon is over there.  This is
not a weapon, sorry.
Yellow one.
Yellow one.  Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhededrus
Yuh, is it okay to hit the fighter or another navigator.
Here, there, that
bed is gone
[Music]
emeral
PIN
uuu My
sister navigates with WEAPON, and then
that Kira is there, that's right,
if Demaki has another team, my sister
can also do that.  Um,
[Music] I
guess I'm on the wrong side.For now, what I can see now is yes.So
, um, Yuffie will try to stay out of this purple as much as possible.So, um, um, um, um, um, um,
don't ride this.
Maybe it's a recipe. Hey,
I can do it. So far, I'm going to
climb on top of this and look at it from here. I'm going to look at it that way. I'm going to look at it that way.
In the group chat, Yoff is currently in a slightly umm,
pink mode.  It
felt like someone was there, so she ignored it and said, ``
There's an enemy over there,'' or that there's another team.I guess
Nee-san can hit that and that, so Fi should try to play the
purple and pink here as much as possible.  Are you in this range with the golden one? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, I did my best. There's a device over there, but yeah, if I'm standing here, I'm going to be targeted. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right, from above, so please. That's
right, so please,
ooh.  No Neko PERSON
When I drop it, it comes back because there's a staircase here. I'm going to
go into the group chat.
In the group, I
change the lair password to 5555, okay, 555.
[Laughs]
Oh,
you've changed Oh, you've changed Oh, you've changed What's that? That's it,
you've made a gogo. It's
about to start. I'm going down there.
I'm in a
good position. You
can see it well, too.  Kotooh
Yay, I
can see your name, so you can see it.Oh,
okay, okay, okay, I wonder if it's a
start.I
wonder if it's a countdown.Litwa okay.So, I
don't know
if it's Rene or Chiara.So I can see someone, I can see someone.I
can't see anyone right now.  No, I'm
going to go to where Yuppi is a little pink, then I'm going to go to the place where Yuppi is a little pink, so I'm
not going to be in pink or not.  I do
n't have Reine, oh yeah, I can
see pretty well so far I can see the name, I can see the name, I can see it, I can see it, I can see it, it's in the back, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, I can see the name, I can see it, I can see the name, I can see it, I can see it, I can see it, it's in the back.
Oh no, I'm getting hit a lot. Well, I
'm in a bit of a purple state right now. Try
not to get too close to the bass. I can
hear it a lot. Pa is getting hit a lot.
Go over there. Oh no, no, no, I'm going to get shot too.  Wow,
when I was there, I
heard someone say, ``Hey, I'm downstairs.'' Wait a
minute, right now, Pink is going to shoot me with my power.  I
can't go, I can't go, I
can't go anywhere. It's
back to the purple color that's in my bag. Maybe
it's better. Maybe the pink side will
jump. What is this? What is this? Oh, I'm really aiming for it. What is this, where is
this, yellow?  In the yellow and purple place,
Nene is behind me, behind me, behind me, behind me, chasing me from behind. There's
no path.
But I'm shooting, I'm shooting
Rene Now I'm
shooting, I'm
shooting, I'm shooting, I'm shooting, ok, ok, ok,
oh, I think I forgot to eat.If I
don't eat regularly, I'll get killed, right?I
forgot to eat, ok, ok, ok.  Congratulations,
Congratulations! The
road is often blocked, isn't it? That's
right, that's amazing. I was being chased from behind, and I was being chased
around. Yes, I was being chased around, and I wasn't
able to get to the other side.  It's like that, isn't it
? So, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so,
so, such
group chat, oh, all, it seems that there is a
group chat, all open, um, all,
tatata,\ha, all, I'm going to go to all.  That's
right, I'm going to
go all out. I see. Okay, but the punch hurt. It was a sword. It was a sword. I'm sorry, Mavro. I'm sorry, Senpai. I can't see where you were at all.
Seriously, where and where did it come from?
Tepu's red cousin.  Yeah, the more I blushed, the more I
thought that was the case,
but I
couldn't see it, so I thought, ``I
can't see it.'' It's
quite small, right? To be honest,
Iofie and Unu were fighting.  Sometimes they both
had white hair and were so far away
from me that I couldn't tell which one was Iofie or which one was Una, so
I didn't know at all.It's
true, but my name is
Rinji.The name is so small that I ca
n't read it, so it's in color.  I could only make a decision.
Yes, yes, yes, and you
play, but do you want to switch it up like this? Do you
want to do it again? Yes, I understand. Is it okay? I
understand.  Yes, okay, rules, okay, rules, okay,
do you want to switch?
Yes, my question, ah, ah, by the way, down there, ah,
people, ah, people down there. Do I
have to press that F1? No, no
. Thank you,
Chiara.  I haven't been shot at, so I do
n't know, but if I get shot at,
will I die someday?
DIHknow, ah, navigator, yeah, I'll
die
, I'll die,
so I'm going to die, so I need Bed and the others.
Is that senior dead? It's barely okay.
But it was terrible, that was the last moment, that's it, that's it,
that's it, I feel like if I get shot, I'm going to die. There
's no second time. There's no second time. If the navigator comes back to life, I
can be the navigator again. That's fine. Not
at all, but uh, time.  That's all
resp
figh,
if the gator dies, it's
okay to live again, but
if the fighter dies, then that's all
there is to it.Then the navigator will come back to life.That's
right, the navigator
is the phoenix.  It feels like Phoenix
Yeah, yeah, yeah
way
isthatalsolikewhere
ATeamwouldbe
orthat
knowOL
Sorrycommunicating
with theSTwhatwasthe
likeWhereIstandIfI
LooktomyrightThere
islikeBIGHOUSElike
mergingwithAnother
EnemyAREAbutlikeis
thatwhere
HowthereTOWERSeach
Side
Going3
think6, thinkhave  It wasn't there, it wasn't, it wasn't, it wasn't, it wasn't, it wasn't, it wasn't, it wasn't there, it wasn't there, it wasn't there, it wasn't there, it wasn't there, it wasn't there, it wasn't there, it wasn't there, it wasn't there, it wasn't there, it wasn't there, it wasn't there, it wasn't there, it wasn't there, it wasn't there.
]
Smile
, gogogo
Okay, okay, we're not Chiara,
so let's do our best not to get angry. Let's do our best. If we get yelled at, we'll have to
eat bread or potatoes right away. It'll be
dangerous.  That's right, I can't hold the potato anymore. No, I
left it somewhere. So I left it there. I did
n't know what to do and it
disappeared. Well, I'm just practicing with the potato. So, it's practice,
so it's okay. It's practice, so it's
okay.  Yao, that
's fine. I don't know
where everyone is. I can't see this. I can't go back. It's not gone.
Yeah, even if I jump, there's no one. If there's no one, then I
can't see anything.
Yeah, this is me.  You can't go
here. You're going to be targeted. You
were targeted just
now. Okay, where are you now? Pipi isn't in Pink.
Pink Pink. That's right. Pink. Well then,
uh, I
can see you right now. It's a
sight to see, Chiara.  I can't see it at all. It's
moving so tiny. It's so tiny. It's
moving so tiny. I ca
n't reach it. I can't reach
it. I want a telescope. I want a
telescope. Can't I use a telescope?  While I'm at it, I'm
sure I can't do that, but I can't hit that. It looks like I won't be able to do that.
The chair is a red one. It's okay. Oh, for the time
being, I'll try not to stray too far from the base.
[Music]
For now, I'll see
where I'm going. I'm
shooting, Wow, I hope I hit it.
For now, I'm still on the purple side.
Oh yeah, that's Yufu. There's
someone there. There's someone on the pink side,
so I'll invite you to the purple side. There
's also a yellow one. There's also a yellow one.
Oh, I'm going to invite you to this purple one for now. My
sister is hitting the person underneath there.
Thank you, thank you, yellow.
There's a squirrel on the side, but the
road was blocked for a while.
Eh?  Well, everyone is in yellow.If
everyone is in yellow, will I go to yellow too?Or
where?I heard there's a squirrel on the left right now, right
?Everyone is there.Maybe there is.But I do
n't know.I don't know.  I
don't know the way to go. Where should I go? I'm here. I'm here. I
'm here. I'm in the middle. Is Rene currently in the purple? It's over.
Okay, okay.
Which one are you? Souris is right next to me. It's scary. I know, I
know.  It's so scary,
it's so scary, it's so funny, it's so
funny, the squirrel is laughing so much, it's so scary, come on, come on, it's so funny, it's scary, I ca
n't get it right,
there's that lol, it's
scary, the endermen haven't found anyone, I
don't know.  I don't know if it's me or not,
but the squirrel is
trying so hard, it's so bad, it's so bad, it's so
bad, but it's gone up, up,
up, but what should I do?  Ah, I went to purple, I
went to purple. Ah, I wonder if it's
true. In the middle, there are hot potatoes. But wait, please eat and eat. But right now, Ken is going to break easily, so what
should I do about
this?  Oh, purple
is here, oh, let's move on a little bit. Purple, purple, purple, purple, purple.  I
see,
I see, I don't want to do this, but yeah, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, this just
happened, the sword will break quite a lot.
No, I think I'll change it as much as I have emeralds,
so for example, do I want to
have one strong sword or multiple weak swords? Yes, yes,
yes, yes, I'll ask you later.
Well, it's because it's so worn out that you can get that item from the person you just defeated.
Where's everyone? I wonder if everyone's voice is still
in Gluoru. I guess it's a group.
Well, that's it. I'm
going to go to Oruuuuuuuuuuuu. I think I'm missing
Guru. I
just heard Peko. I want to hear it. Hey, Peko. Senpai is
here.  Is that what it is or what it is or what it is or what it is or what it is or what it is or
what it is
or what kind of sword you can buy as many swords as you want.  I
feel like
that sword just fell apart during the battle, and I
can't use it anymore.I feel like
if I had a lot of money, I could buy many, many swords.Or
maybe just one.  That's right
[Laughs]
DYiber
[Music]
duanybertikitabeliA
SWORDrusak
lagi
mennyaini
APABIMnantiKANini
emeral
akanemalakanDIPUN
jadinantidiis
ajaI have to pay already.
Well, the rules have changed again.
Well, if the navigator dies, he
'll come back to life, but he won't be able to navigate anymore.
But the game won't end. Ah, the
navigation will become negative. I'll just watch it.  I'm
just looking at you, so don't
use that too. Don't use it. Take it with you.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Is your time okay? It's okay.
My time isn't okay.
Yes, I see. Nesoka. Well, it's
okay.  But it's okay, Naru
[Music] You're
chasing me like crazy, but
who's the enderman
?
[Music]
This is where I'm going.  Is it better to stay? I
pick it up. I can't carry anything. Now
[Music]
is
[Music] [
Music]
How can I do it?  Yes yes so they
set that stage within a part of Momo 1 where the
players try to guess what it is and the
pair have to answer and then the emerald is
demanded
Yes that's okay
Oh
what color
too
Okay, then I'm going to
make the yellow one. And who's going to make the building? Which one should
we start with? Okay, I'm going to
make a little bit. Let's build the building.  I'll
do my best
[Music]
21 Hmm, I
feel like it was like this, hmmm, seriously, hmmm, wait,
wait, seriously, this is so hard,
okay
, uh, hey, uh, that's it, uh, that's
it.  What
's this? This is it. This is
it.
No question mark.
[Music]
Hey,
oh, it's not grape. No. No, uh, that's
it. The color doesn't matter.
The color doesn't matter. It doesn't matter. No, it
's different.
So, this,
this, this, this, this, this, this, the color is related, the color is related,
the color is
related, it's
not like a snake, it's pondering, this is here, this is
pondering, I like this, I
like that third one, it's Moon, yeah,
that's right.
Oh, I shouldn't read the chat during the actual performance.It's
probably something like this.If it was the moon, I would
n't be able to tell
because it was just a round shape.So, yeah, I imagined all kinds of things when it was round.I
like balls and
things like that.  Hey, oh
Senpai and Chiara-senpai, let's try
it [Music] Let's do
it, oh Okay then, then
[Music]
What the
hell is this? It's good and difficult. I like it. I
think it's difficult, but it's difficult. Yes, I'm ready.
[Music]
Yes, yes.
321  What is it, what is it, what is it?
But I
guessed it right now Who said "no tree"? I got it right, I got it right, it was a hit, it was a hit, it was a hit, it was a
big hit, somehow I knew it.  It's a
genius, thinking that it's expensive, so
it's a tree that looks like a genius.  It's
always this or that change
[Music]
SIKmanglebih
baiksemuaKATAdilar
aja
[Music]
Maybe Bener is talking to the management.
Yeah, I don't know about this. I don't know
how many rounds I should change that.
What is it? I wonder which one it is. Well, I
just heard that the squirrels are
talking to the management and they say they
won't do it even if they say how many times they'll do it.
If it's 3 or 4 times, we
'll be replaced.  That's what it is,
right? It seems more fun to take turns. Yes, it's more fun. But if we take turns, it's 2 rounds or 4 rounds. Yeah, yeah, it's okay. One of us
writes twice, the other writes twice.  It's not a problem at all even if I can answer.Okay, you
guessed it right away.Somehow,
somehow, you came and told me to say it.And even if it was just
one surisa, it
turned out to be a pop, so I said yes.
So I went down once, and I was
like, ``I'm going to make it all fluffy and round.'' Well, I see.
Then, before that, please answer me.
[Laughs] It's
good, it's good, it's
good, it's
good.  I'm
feeling healed.What happened
earlier was that
bond in the sky, telepathy,
telepathy.I wonder if someday we'll
climb a tree together.I'll climb it.Will I climb it?Will I climb it?I'll
climb the tree.At
that time, I'll go and help.  Yes, it
will fly to me. Yes, it will pick me up. I
can climb up the tree, but I wo
n't get down. I can't get down, so I can't get down. Probably yes. That's why I
'm going to help you. I
'll burn that tree. Don't burn it, I'll burn it. Hey.
We're being burnt, right? No, we're not going to
burn, so let's burn. We're going to
use the stairs and stuff like that. Stairs Stairs are
a little difficult to use to summon Faa Fighters.
Fufui
Faifai I see. Don't you think? Don't you? Don't let it burn you. Don't let it burn you.
What is telepathy? Is telepathy
telepathy? Telepathy?
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
No matter how you look at it, it's Anya.
[Music] She's
been wearing her same face since two months ago.
Somehow, there's Anya who has been wearing Rene's voice for a long time.  I
thought,
[Music]
Hey, it's similar.
Dee
Mao
Pa Yeah, I'll talk about whether or not I'll change the details later
and how many rounds there will be.
Yeah, yeah, I do
n't know yet, so I think I'll probably get a notification today or tomorrow
saying that I'll be at that disco.
[Music]
But if you still want to
practice, um, let me know.  I do
n't need it, I'll try it one more
time I'll try it one more time So who's going to make a bill? I guess I got it right in the first shot,
so I guess I'll try it again. It's too much. Let me ask you the question.
Think
haveang
think.
Oh, it's over.
[Music] Are you
making Tae too? I
had a question. Is it okay if I build a building on top of it or use flooring?
Either is fine. Either way, it's okay to use the
floor. The floor is
easier.  Yeah, when I'm on the floor, I'm looking at it from above too, and I'm
thinking, ``Okay, this is it.'' I think it's probably
easier to do it horizontally than vertically, so horizontally is better.Okay, let's
look at it from above here.For now,
okay, okay.  Are you ready?
Yes, yes
[Music]
Well, let's go.
Yes, it
's 321. What is it?
[Music] I'm
Ida Hana Ahana. The
bond is so strong. It
looks too strong. No, no, no, no, this is this. This is
this.  I was thinking about making this shape, but it looks like a
plus, so I wanted to make it, and I
wanted to make it. Wow,
I'm so bad at it,
so I guess I'll start from here. I
thought maybe it would be better to separate it into different places. I'm
starting to bump into places.  Well,
if you want to do it on the floor, that's fine, but the
location is a little
bit.It's a squirrel.I see.I'll
leave it to Una, so I'll probably do it on the floor.I
won't make it, but I'll do it one more time.Okay, let's do it
one more time.  Please, please,
let me know.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Yes, it's a nose, it's a nose Hey,
yes, I'm sorry, I'm
ready.
Kakokochi Color doesn't matter, but it
does. It doesn't matter. It doesn't matter. It doesn't matter. It doesn't matter. It's
a start.  3 Ai hei hei 21 What is
it? I'm so bad. I'm so
bad. I'm not good at it.
[Music]
Time here.
Erm, I'm looking forward to it. I can't
sleep. It's
only 30 seconds.
Fireworks.
Ah, nice, I don't think it's bad, but it
's not bad.
[Music]
No, no, no, no, I'm
not getting angry. Hey, it's
easy to understand if you look at this. No matter
where you look, where you look from,
jump, fly.
[Music]
Okay, Okay,
Okay, what a banana seems to be so
good I understand this is a banana. This is
so good.  I
thought it was the favorite mark. That's the
Mark Mamark. Well,
this time, the older sister
guessed it. Let's try and see if it's a hit. Then,
oh, then I'll go ahead and do it. [Music] What should I do?
[Music]
Have you? [Music] [Music]  [
Music]
Oh, I heard it said in Indonesian. I
don't understand. I don't think there's any need to turn it off. It's
like that. There
's a building next to it. It's better to look at it from that floor.
Oh, ladies. Yes, ladies.  Desu Radio
[Music]
321 Um, tree, no, no, no, no, no, no, ah,
spoon, what should I do?
Spoon, oh, spoon, ah, tennis, I
thought it was a tennis racket or a spoon,
oh, oh, are you doing it diagonally?  When I
saw both of them, I thought, ``Oh, I
see.'' I thought, ``I'm sorry,
sorry.
Ah,
even in Pima, we have good chemistry with each other, so it seems like we're no longer in the game.
Heh
[Music]
Yeah, yeah, I guess I played all the games. I wonder if it's nice.
than
Yeah, for now it's a group
[Music] I think we should
go out at least once.
Da outside outside E outside
Apa Piand ah good ah good
then let's take a picture of outside outside
[Music] I
think Muneo oh oh good I think that's good
E where is that
from loli
here
here I'm sorry, someone, the show
is tomorrow.  Oh, it's true, it's tomorrow.
So I thought I'd use today's practice session spectacle for tomorrow's thumbnail. Ah,
I'll use it, okay? Let's climb here.
[Music]
Oh, how do we climb?  No, this,
this, this, this, this, this, this, my sister,
where are you going to climb up here?
[Music]
Oh, it's still night, there are zombies
Where do I want to take a photo?
Wow, this is the entrance, isn't it? It's the entrance, so I think it's okay here. Is it okay to stay here? Where, senpai? Oh, it looks like a nice place. This is the top, so I wonder if this is the right place. This is the top. The chair is good. Okay. Okay. Wow.
Unrita, I want you to send me a photo Oh yeah, do
all the seniors want to take it? Or so. I'm
fit, but I want to take it too. Really okay,
cheese cheese,
can we get closer? Chika and Usu aren't together. We're also practicing Kamenkan. Group
6 people.  You can use the thumbnails of the 6 people. Let's take a screenshot of the 6 people. Is
that okay? I can't get too close to them. If you get close, they'll all get huge. Let's take them. Let's take them.
Thank you for being so nice.  Send it to me, cue,
yadade desu
[Music]
Nanwa,
taja Akira Oi,
do your best from here,
everyone, too.
] Waniwa Waniwa Wani Wani Wani Wani Ni Ni [Music] Wani Ni Wani Wa [Music] he fuwa [Music] Wawa Wawai