child
[applause]
[music]
Private Aqua Occupation Super Ultra Anything
The perfect maid today is also my husband's
I will do my best for
It's Labora Love Love Mido.
Well done
Taco Maid won't come, there's no Med.
Ojihose
is
If the rice is burnt
It's scary
Please forgive me, master.
[music]
I'm angry because I only play games
Cheating with a cat face
Nyafusu
Well then, the chin is the master, the chin is the master.
No no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no.
She's a lazy girl, but she's the main character.
Can you make it your way? Let's be friends forever.
wrinkles in the future
It will remind you
This win
Asan's
[music]
As expected
Hello to all my husbands
Aqua Minato Aqua
today
haha me
[music]
trial of
Thank you for visiting
Everyone, you were so energetic until yesterday.
However, many people thought so
I hope you have a look here
please
[music]
The sky was building the TT Tower during the day
This is a trap tower.I hope it helps everyone.
When I sit down and think about yesterday's sins with Nuru-chan,
As we work together on the game, I made a DT data.
I was in the middle of working on that game.
[music]
Today I slipped and died.
The trial will take place
I thought it was time to introduce you.
I would like to introduce today's
It's a mission
I went to the Nether to get a soul and got tangled up with it.
Going to collect frog eggs with a stranger
Please go and defeat one Ghast.
create a potion
Sanano
I was supposed to sit with everyone at
There is also money in
Masu here
Distorted mushroom to get glowstone
What twisted mushrooms do you get?
What is Tekochan distorted mushroom?
Yeah, wait a minute
A distorted mushroom
What, wait a minute?
oh nether boat
Kotoa Nether Boat
[music]
It's a different nether boat.
It's not nether wart, it's blue.
Mushroom, Peko-chan, Peko-chan, a little bit
Wait, the information I got from Peko-chan and Peko
The information that Chan gave on his stream today was different.
I wonder if they changed it midway through.
3 Mayoisho skeletons
The first discoverer of the Nether fortress to defeat.
Did you change things a bit along the way?
Momechan, these are the ones
Is it a little good and today's
Event starts from today: Sky Trap
The tower
Completed villager attack station completed
God's punishment for Hosa
[music]
I want to do it too
Okay, but if I keep doing this, I'll die.
It's a problem, so I can't help it.
So let's go get fed today.
I thought
I'm thinking of going to Bare today.
Thank you in advance. Yes, it's just carelessness.
I fell and died
I messed up. I seriously asked if I should go home with the BGM.
That being said, I'm going to do it.
I wonder if everyone is there. There are so many.
There are so many
Hey, wait a minute, there's one thing I want to confirm.
Good job
I'm actually that dead.
But that's it.
I'm dying so I guess
There's not much I can do.
Chocho
The trial has already begun
Really
The first Lyrica-chan trial is about to begin.
It's starting
That's what I'm doing.Wait a minute.
Let me just check it out
Maybe Peko-chan here in Netherwut?
Something like mine
Well, the information says Nether Wart.
But wait, is this a distorted mushroom?
Hey, just a little bit on the way, Pico-chan.
Help me
Distorted
is
Mushrooms?
Well, the first thing I got was
According to some information, it was Nether Wart.
But I did it with a slightly distorted mushroom distribution.
I think that's probably the correct answer.
I guess I'll go see the trial too.
In court
I'm a little late, but I'll go see it.
Wait a minute
Is there a fence?
The fence is crispy
I'm going to take a look.
Kadoko
Dakocchi was there!
Let's go take a look at the beast.
Let's wait for next time too.
These guys, these guys!
I felt like I was okay
Oh, I'm on trial. I'll have endless meals.
making
I wonder if I made a mistake. I made a mistake.
No ne
People who have died twice have brains.
I want you to give me something. This is Manjou 1.
I'm glad Lyrica-chan is back.
So, Lyrica-chan, what about you?
Congratulations on your recovery from today
thank you
Don't work too hard, don't cause an accident, don't let it happen again.
Please be careful and use it as a shield.
I'll give the diamond blocks to Pecola later.
Please stay at the house where Neme started.
I'll leave it for testing, so please take care of it.
I wish yes thank you thank you
There is
Thank you very much for your help, welcome back
Welcome home, good luck, Senpai.
Yes, yes, please do your best.
Yo gym clothes, someone who can defend Ami and A.
Are you here? Are you here?
You lose
I don't know what happened.
I don't know
Well, these people witnessed it, so they witnessed it.
I am a witness, not a defense attorney.
As a witness, I would like to ask you a few questions.
I think it's a bit of a nuisance after all.
There are some people who have experienced various things such as
I can't stand this life I've been living in this situation.
It's true that my wife was pushed down.
The book that came together with everyone is fun, it's fun
I'm a senior, I'm a senior, I'm the most senior among them.
I'm sorry, but it seems bad, but it's not good
I would like to confirm the circumstances under which he died.
Can I ask you to tell me what happened?
Yes that uhm
Yeah, while I was working on that case.
I fell off the TT Tower and slipped.
I fell down and died. Yes, that's right.
In fact, it's like a shipping accident.
Do you feel that way?Yes, I lost my leg due to a bad accident.
I slipped
Witnesses, is that true?
Actually, it seems like we weren't witnesses.
When you say what to eat or what to eat,
It's true that I worked in prison.
Yes, the three of us were having lunch today.
It is true that he worked in prison at high places.
But then I realized that Aqua
My voice suddenly stopped and I was in the middle of telling a fake story.
When it disappeared, I checked the log and Aqua was there.
I fell from a high place and looked down.
I'm dying to see Aqua's items scattered around.
That's why we, like Aqua, did it too.
I don't see that moment, I see.
I have something I would like to ask you.
But it was just a slip and fall accident. He's an old man.
If you know what a carpet is, it's behind that.
I didn't watch it and that's a shame.
Yes, yes, all you have to do is do that lift.
That's right, you're the enemy.
Thank you so much, thank you Achan
Thank you, I'm sorry. I'm sorry for putting that away.
But it's true that Aa-san was a bit like yesterday.
Pecola says that the new boss is a little bad.
It is also because he was accused of a crime.
The fact that he also died in an accident
It's a bit sad though
I kinda hope you're doing something wrong, but 1
How much is a little bad towards the Kaicho guard seat?
There's a bit of a problem with the senior.
Is it okay to count? It's bad for the actor.
There are people who have been
Very surprising
Good luck! What did each person do?
Just to confirm, what happened to Kazu-chan?
Takahi is a little annoying
Let's get a little closer
I want to talk to you when I feel like it.
Just when I thought that, magma was poured on me.
Tayaba
I can't use this, it's burnt, there's nothing to say
Oh, I burned it. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, but it's not me.
My wife's family
Lami-tan is in that foot house.
From behind in a very deep hole
He was crying and said he had been pushed away and dropped.
Get rid of it
I've been pushed down too.
I was pushed down too, and this was the first thing I did.
Who are you? Who are you?
I see, you're a little different.
I'm committing a lot of sins, isn't this true?
That's right, that's right, that's right, that's right
I'm waiting for you to say that.
Please, can I wait for a while?
Please, let me just say one thing.
It's not just a term for itadama.
But that's the TT Tower.
It really wouldn't be complete without the power of Aqua.
I see, so that's all there is to it.
I hope you keep that in mind.
I think so, thank you, you worked hard
So, is there any stone left in the rock?
It's okay, I'm sorry, just a word from the leader.
I want to say it, you know, after all, ah Noe
Atty, I would like to say a few words as Nene's bond.
I want to, but yes, there are bonds behind me.
On the first day, I gave Dan-chan a diamond.
2 I was deceived.At that time, the leader
If you say you were scammed, I won't say anything.
Without hesitation, is that something flint?
I started burning chan.
My heart is so hot
It's a bit noisy, but in the midst of that, friendship
I'm a shy kid, so it's a bit like that.
Please give me a chance.
Oh yeah, the way to do it is a bit difficult.
But that's right, there is humanity.
Kiddy candy that makes you think of candy and whip
After listening to what has been said so far, even if the inflatable seats are revived.
If you think it's okay, please refuse.
Please, please, please, really
Please, please, please
If I'm going to Endra, I want Ata Vanguard.
That's right, I want the front. If you're greedy, you're
You don't have the right to vote, Subaru.
Since I'm at the bottom, you gave me this memory tag.
What's the point? This is amazing
This is a very important item.
While saying that, he gave me a ta.
I see that you have a kind side as well.
That's right, that's right. I'll be cursed if I don't give it to you.
It is also said that
I don't have any memories, Miritairi.
I've been gone for more than half a year. Wait, who is who?
is not doing it 12345 who who who who who who who
You're not even raising your hand. It's a joke.
I don't know
There is a possibility that the nage guy will break down because of this.
In Niaya, more than half of the collections were eaten.
So this time I will call it a revival, but I will go.
However, she was different from Ririka-chan.
A little bit of a bummer
I think I'd like to give you something new.
Next
I am not innocent. Yesterday,
Is this a problem?I also had the problem yesterday.
I feel a little guilty for you
I want it to hang properly.
Well, you've become my dream forever.
Become a little servant to me in that management.
I'm begging you for help too
He also participated in the hell project organized by Pecola.
I'll take it, so please take care of it.
And so that I can turn on the people around me as well.
Please live your daily life by doing well.
Be grateful. There is nothing you can do today.
Hey, it's already dangerous, isn't that guy?
Thank you very much. It's really a goodbye.
It's flat to say
Thank you very much for your hard work. Thank you.
Thank you
Thank you. If you do that,
Well, Nether, I have a press conference starting today.
People who want to go to the nether, go to that nether, that gate.
Let's make it hahaha
Thank you for your hard work in making it. Resurrection Resurrection Someone's
I almost took the temperature. Honestly, I'm glad.
Ati that can take the temperature of the Nether, everyone.
Licca-chan growls more than I want her to make it
Nice to meet you
Okay, where should I make it? It's the Nether.
I know how to get there, I know, I know
But Peka-chan won't make a gate first.
Peko-chan is here, what's this?
It seems like you're busy, so I'll leave that place up to you.
Anything is fine as long as it's close to that place.
I'll tell everyone today that God will punish me.
I have it, so I'll do my best with all my equipment.
Etenpa
God's punishment, go somewhere
Well, I became that servant.
So I'm also concerned about Peko-chan's throat.
Tsutsuema, let's all do it together.
Let's go to sleep. You went, right? Awesome.
Wow, you're talking really fast. What are you saying?
I didn't know. It's true that divine punishment is too scary now.
I wonder at what timing?
Okay then.
I'm going to be crushed, my arms and legs are torn apart.
What do you think? I heard something good about this court.
That doesn't mean I won't use it here at the gate in the future.
Let's do it!
Well, let's make a nether gate.
Are you there?
Um, water
And obsidian, isn't water enough for magma?
I'll drink water with my mom.
It was in a dead place, but it was a diamond.
You can go with an ice ax, but it's a no-brainer.
I have an ice ax, everyone has one, Diamond.
I have an ice ax. What can I bring?
That's 99 pieces, 2349, right?9 That's it.
Can I go with 9 Okay Yes 249?
1010 or 10
But there's something underneath the foundation.
About 15 years old, I want to do the whole thing.
That's right, we are equipped with Ririka-chan.
We can't do that.
Is it like diamond equipment?
Oh yeah, let's go back one step at a time.
I'll be back again, I'll be equipped again.
Masu
123456789 Eh 10 At least 10.
If I were to do this, I'd need about 14.
Okay, then I'll get about 15.15
It's better to keep a little more than that.
Nenechi might be good, about 15 diamonds
20 I made a base out of glass and magma
It's impossible to pour it in with water.
stone 20
I don't think I can do it if it's below me, but still
It's totally fine, it's just water, it's totally fine water
I have a bucket, but I have a good firestone in the dirt.
If I don't have it, I'll bring it.
Then bring it
I thought it was Aqua Subaru
Tandabutsu Saun Aqua's Sako's revival Kinsada
Have you become angry?
What is this?
What happened that I forgot what happened earlier?
It's nothing, it's Button-chan.
Okay, scary.
Pico
[music]
You forgot to take the money, huh?
I forgot to take the diamond diamond though.
It's already closed
Nabakacho, wait, I'll be your servant.
That's right, we have to do this here.
There isn't, so it looks like this, but it's already been replaced.
I stood on the management side, on the management side.
I was left in charge of standing up.
I understand that you are useless.
I get it, it'll be okay, calm down, calm down
Calm down, Aku, you're seriously going to die one more time.
What will happen to me, servant zero?
I guess that's because it can't be revived.
Although I was revived for a while,
A little Peko-chan Peko-chan
It's a bit difficult
I see.
A little ah I died separately
But if I'm Peko-chan's servant, I can do it.
Well, that's what Peko-chan is all about.
Why would I be in trouble if I disappeared?
Thank you very much
Yes, thank you very much, you have changed.
Do you want to go get even a small stone?
If we surround it with the soil here and there and let the magma flow
It's okay to ride
Put the money you don't have in the chest in the house of beginnings.
Please take that seriously.
Bae-chan I'm watching that broadcast I'm watching this
That's wrong, Peko-chan.
There are quite a few people like that.
Oh no, it's not that. It's not that.
Aim, what do you think, what do you think?
Hey, I wonder
By the way, for Aqua today
It's a lie because I dug diamonds
Yes, that's right, after that, yes, this too, really
If you don't want to die in that nether, yeah.
Maybe it would be better to put on that flame stance or something.
Yes, I did enchant it.
Maybe it would be better to enchant it. Then, the gate
I'll make it, save some time, and go as a group.
It doesn't matter if I write it or I'll look at it already.
Well, if I really, really, absolutely,
Maybe some people feel like they're about to die.
That might be better, that's for sure
Well, for now, let's just drain the magma here.
The obsidian on the base under that water jar is
I'll probably be able to go, but by the way, it's so cool.
I really know where obsidian is.
I took it from there and everyone came.
Okay, but everyone is here. I wonder if they brought it.
I brought it, thank you for coming.
It's 4 stones, so there's a bit more frame.
Alice Kako today Subaru super diamond
I found some super obsidian while digging.
You can cover it with a square inside here.
Yeah, that's right, it's 123 tall, isn't it? 12
123 This one below is probably somewhere outside here.
Is it no good?
This is 14, so it seems like it's enough.
I need flint, right? I'll bring you some flint.
There's more to it than this.
Senkyu, this is good too, please break it down.
a
Okay, hey, hey, hey
oh
Hey
You can go, I'll just sit on the water table.
What is this?
[music]
The person who went there is already going to the first Ako-chan.
Let's do it from here
These are people who can't even post a log.
Hold on a second, just in case
It's a waste to make this
There are a lot of cobblestones that you should take from there.
It seems like it might be better to make one.
I think it would be better if you did that.
Be careful not to put it on the bed.
By the way, I'm leaving the bed.
There's a cliff-like thing on the left, but it's not an enemy.
Hmmmm
First, the gate is surrounded by a fence.
Please make sure to do it first so it doesn't get damaged.
I guess I should go, okay? Is this okay?
What time is Sui-chan and Aki-chan able to gate?
Are you coming here?
I should have made a certain head. That looks good.
It's totally fine. It's safe. It's kind of safe.
A loud voice sounds good, right? The place is surrounded.
let's let's
Make a little hole
Wow Gusto screams, yabei Gusto
Anyway, I don't have enough stones.
Come
Wow
I surrounded it with stones and it's already destroyed.
I hope it doesn't happen
scary place
Be careful when working
Feet that don't look like yo
Like a senior who doesn't exist
Well, everyone, like that sister.
If that person really dies, there will be no next one.
I congratulate you on that enchantment.
I'm enchanting that fall system
I'm wearing that flame system rather than the falling system.
Maybe it's good, certainly both.
Yes, it might be better to add both.
Please wear it if you are in danger.
Please enchant it before you go.
I have a PT, so please help me with the workbench.
Let me tell you something
Before going to Nether Nether
[music]
If you are worried about going
Yeah
I recommend it after enchanting.
court entrance
but
This is the entrance to the Nether.
Leave it to me, Okepeko-san, Meko-san.
Take care, be careful, be careful
Everyone, everyone, be careful, everyone, be careful.
Please go ahead and wear it.
Okay, Peko-san, Beko-san.
Is there anything I can help you with?
I was a little satisfied with Nabiki Tekko-san.
Or once
I want to listen
I wonder where Nako is? Looks like she's here.
What?
mosquito
Upeko's
I sleep soundly
Maybe, maybe, I'll help you right now.
I don't have any, so I like you, oh, I understand, I understand.
I understand, you're looking at me, I understand, I understand.
is
Yeah
yes yes
My Peco
[music]
Yes, my peko, then I also have Subaru.
It looks like they dug up diamonds so I'm using diamond equipment.
Then I'll go to the Nether with everyone.
It's a big deal
[music]
Hey Subaru, give me the opened Subaru diamond
too
That's good, that's good.
I thought I should wear armor and that kind of thing happened.
Hey, wait a minute
That's okay
I'm coming this way. I'm coming. I'm coming.
Look at the soul diamond
Please, are you okay? You're really, really okay, aren't you?
Seriously, we've built a house so we can live together.
I have a house, I have a house, but I'm not in that house anymore.
I might not be able to change it, so I died so I used it.
By the way, I almost see it as a mistake.
You can use this from today. That's a lie.
I want to go further
I'm so rich that I have to build a house
Okay, don't say this, it's home.
If it was, this wouldn't be a point anymore.
No, no, no, no, no, the one who will be played again is Ana-chan
Wait, it's diamond, it's diamond, it's diamond
Here's a diamond, here's a diamond, here's another one
There's a little bit of that there.
I think there is a possibility of it being stolen. Hello.
Hello, how are you, how are you, children?
How, how, how, how is it?
Hello child, child, today is also delicious.
Thank you very much. Things have changed.
Eat that, wait, then eat that, that's rude.
Please let me
Let's go, you haven't eaten yet.
I'm not hungry sorry
You've changed, Minato. You're not like that.
Where did Tikiri go?
Thank you for your help back then.
Please again today
Why are you doing that so quickly?
Wait a minute, Subaru too.
I'll be around for a while, so I'll just say 14 or something.
Okay, okay
Yes, thank you, yes, thank you. You can sit down.
Wait a minute, this is A.
How much debt is left?
teeth
Wasn't it 1633 or something like that?
Looks like I can give it back
I'm lying because I have 14 on hand.
This isn't the chest plate, it's just the armor.
Even if I enchant it, I might die.
Don't you die? If you fall, you'll die.
I don't know what to do with that potion.
Maybe I should make a flame potion.
If you drink the flame potion, you won't die.
I see, it's a bit like a flame potion.
I understand that the level is high, I got 35, so I only have 21 left to go.
Apparently, it's not enough at all.
[applause]
I'm happy for you, it's not enough, I understand.
Hey, are you going to the Nether today?
Should I go to Hama Nether? Peko-chan's work
unless there is
Oh, well, I'll just do whatever I want.
You can increase your experience points and attack.
Let's take a look at the attack, I don't know where it is.
Well, that's me too, but I won't do it.
Hey
Maybe this is it, everyone?
Diamond Ataha Ungami
mosquito
Yeah, what are you, you still haven't figured it out?
Work
[music]
If you have emeralds, you can exchange them for iron.
Chan explains that it's good iron, that's not it.
[music]
Everyone is like that, but it's still a little iron.
I wonder if you'll cover me with diamonds
Tee aaab
Chaabu
Everyone took it
I don't have that iron trap, but iron
I'm sorry, everyone is taking irons and I don't have iron.
However
Let's not
It's easy though.
yes
Wow, I'm a little confused.
Is there anyone who has diamonds?
Wait, you can exchange something other than iron.
Nothing
I wonder if it's so funny
I'm studying Minecraft Nyatemikore
A diamond with a heart on it
It's true, it's falling, it's falling
falling luck
Pikki please do it one more time
No way
I guess it's better to just go and stand up, Daimon.
falling body
Damage reduction is really good.
Wait a minute, this is really good
Peco-chan, Pecola-san is gone.
Just a little Peko-san
Wouldn't it be better if everyone disappeared?
I have a mission where I have to look after everyone.
From Gadomo Adomo
I'm going to live my life as that Pekoro.
This is Mr.'s dog.
Thank you in advance.Is there any problem?
Please let me know if you have any Yes
Thank you for your help. Where can I get gold equipment?
Can I enter?
I'll give you some equipment, please give it to me.
I feel like I've changed my mind so please go ahead.
Moshishita's house
I had heard the information, but there was something else.
I was wondering if there was a way to get it.
Please come to my booth.
Please accept thank you
Thank you very much
Warm
Oh, I have a sister, as expected.
is
As expected of Chotakata, thank you very much.
Thank you, please use it
It's like my first time seeing Aqua-senpai as a tea garden.
Hajime-chan is also in a tea garden.
Please beg me for what you want, senpai.
Yes, my senpai, yes, yes, that iron.
I want a lot of them, but I just don't have that outfit.
Isn't this iron?
It doesn't work, but I took that one earlier.
If you're here, I'm sorry, just four things tomorrow.
Only four push-ups, but just a little
No, I'll make some. There's only 4 of them.
I'll copy it from somewhere.
Hey, senior, what's going on? Come on over.
Please, please take it
Oh wait, I ran out of iron.
What should I do? I've been kept alive.
But management is so difficult.
It's a lie, Peko-chan said, eating Mac.
Wait, what are you doing, Suichan?
Tesui-chan that
No, the voice is not connected.
Hey, do you want to go without a voice or a chair?
I wanted to do it
I'm going without Kazunashi. Aki-chan's explanation today.
I think I can explain it.
I'll do my best, thank you very much
Add Masu Asomo
Let's install the Tai Noa MOD.
That's right
Etse-san, do you have some time?
Would you prefer a phone call?
This hurts, Tsui-chan.
Sei-chan, who doesn't have a MOD, has a MOD.
No, I'm going without Sei-chan's MOD now.
Probably Nerui Rui
Can you explain it to me?
Is it okay too?
I'm going to go 6 times as much as 6 times.
It's probably difficult if you don't put it in.
Masu
mosquito
Well, of course it's difficult.
It has to be, probably this voice.
I can't hear you, I can't hear you
If you don't add more, you probably won't be able to hear it.
Haven't you heard this much?
Um, is this it? Um, Mr. Mizuo is Mr. Mizuo.
where
It's night, it's night
is
[music]
Maybe Lulu will do her best and then explain.
I wonder if that's true? I looked at it 6x and there it was, Lulu.
Wow true
It's okay, I think it's okay. It's my job.
It's gone again
Well, I don't have a job.
I'm a woman who remembers her well.
cormorant
I hope you're okay. I'm going to get some sleep.
Changa
Achan-chan, its okay, Im not here.
It's not okay, it's not okay.
Distribution has begun Distribution has begun
Hey, um, first let me explain.
I wonder if it's Kuren?
What to install if you do that
Yes, this is
Installer
Yeah
I was able to download it and am currently looking at the steps.
Oh, okay, you can watch the steps.
Well, I downloaded this and double-clicked it.
Click to open the installation screen
Yes, did you open the installation screen?
This is serious, this is serious, this is serious
It's bad, but it doesn't include "maybe"
Is it okay?
In that case, you have to put in jaab.
If not, download this
Please
Mom, is this it?
Do this and install JAV first.
Yes, please download JAV
That's why I'm that little guy's dog today.
Thank you in advance.Comments only
I just became your dog's dog.
For some reason, I became Peko-san's servant.
Please, double click on this
I'll open it.I wonder if I'll open it with my hand.I'll open it.
What happened next?
status
Yeah until I get the okay soon
[music]
Ah, you can close that one.
It's okay if it's installed first
Yes now what can I download now
I was able to go to 4G with the installer.
home
I can go to Posi
Taie
Ie-chan, you can share it. Share your screen.
Please share your screen, I'll show you everything already
From everything, yes, everything, everything, everything, everything.
It's nice to hear the sounds of Sui-chan
Yes, yes, yes, that's the pose.
Open the one that says
Yes
Deetta voice chat Fuji 1.20
I said, "Open it." No, let me open it.
I'll take it. I'm sorry if this happens.
no adobPhotoshop opens
I'm sorry, I opened the AD.Open the AD.
Right now, I cut it with task manager.
More amazing!
Esui-chan's BGM is amazing
It feels a little naughty.
Why is it not naughty?
I don't know why but it's cute
This sho that looks like this shomono.
I said it's amazing how it feels.
I guess it would be nice to have a bath. This can't be helped.
It looks like Java can't be installed.
That's it, that's it, double click this
Do you want to insert JAV?
I installed it now.
Then install Java from here.
You can start
Yes, it's already installed.
Yeah yeah yeah
That's why I can't assign it.
The one that opens with Java is also modded before.
Sometimes I gave up, but yeah...
death
Tara
[music]
Well, I guess this was done.
Um, is this it?
If anyone in the comments knows, please tell me.
Let's do this
Thank you, I don't like this.
Please download it
Even though I have JAV installed
The installation begins. This is JAV.
I installed it
There are people with irritating words.
Let's erase it
Do it
Hey, let's install this.
Try installing this and open it with
Youn
Hmm
I guess this is okay.
So what?
No, it's out, it's out, it's okay, yeah, it's okay
Something is hardened
If it's okay, then open it.
I wonder if there is?
Oh, it's here
No, the hammer no longer responds to anything.
It's not coming out, it's not coming out, I can see it now
I can see it now and I put it in at the very end.
That thing about him never comes up.
This doesn't come out at all
Nokono O is spinning around right now and that Ok is me
I can't see it, I can see it, I can see it.
Tetaraeo
Yes, it's okay if you can do that.
Um, yeah, open it.
Isn't that the one next to it?
That's the installer
open it
Ah, come, come, come, come, come, come, say okay.
Okay, wait until you say ok, wait until it comes out.
Please wait for it
Masusei-chan is going to the net today for the first time today.
That's right, I can only participate today.
So you're going to die, you know?
I don't care if I die, I'll say goodbye today
You can come back to life once without any penalties.
I heard it seems like it's true
Well, I do need those Dragon Balls anyway.
Ah, it's necessary. It's necessary. Ah, it's necessary.
What's up, maybe it's necessary
Ooh, what did I just see?
I stand up to Ai-chan who erased that someone.
It will be erased. Be careful, I'm not careful.
Even the members can easily turn it off.
I've got a boil, so please press OK.
Well, I'd like you to open Minecraft.
Or should I just open Minecraft?
Yes, please open Minecraft. Minecraft.
Open Minecraft Yeah Open Minecraft
Itadaki
of
Features of Hoiet Minecraft
There's something about the composition, oh yeah, that's right.
Yes, please open the function configuration. Yes, dynamic configuration
Yes, please check the file at Fuji's place.
Please open the place, there it is.
Files called new MODs
Please make a MODs.
I need to create a file.
[music]
M: Yes, open this, yeah, open it, um, there
It looks like that guy who just did it 4
uh it it it it it put this this.
This is it, yes, yes, yes, put it in.
Yes, that's okay. It's true.
Open it in that state.Yes, then clean it.
Let's play, okay, let's play
I wonder if you came here. It's like a hammer.
It's the first time I've ever felt like this.
I just opened it, it's so nice
Wow on the desktop
Scary, wait a minute, just Aku-chan Saz
You can change it, ok, go ahead and change it.
Something is appearing on the screen.
No screen appears
Are you okay? Are you okay? Are you okay?
wildly
Ta
Yoihoo! For a second, that Minecraft thing was on screen.
Okay, okay, uh, this is okay.
yes this
1280's 720 That's what you do.
Well, Fubu-chan taught me this.
As expected of Ohbuki-san, Fu-san is also amazing.
It's huge when it's full screen, but when it's in window mode
As expected from 1280 because it is small
Wait a minute, then take a screen break
There's still more. There's still more to talk about.
I'm so sorry, Dad.I'm so sorry.
No, but I understand that MOD.
That's right, press MODS.
I received it and set it to Minecraft.
Yeah, the left one
Eh, sample voice chart, I'll show it.
Yes, that's right. Sample Yes, that's right. Middle.
The settings are in the
hey
Can be set
Oh oh oh
Skip this is Iknowwhatdo
I can't read that English
Yeah setup simple voice
chat this setup guide
helpyouto
I don't need conf. Anything is fine.
Good next ad, set it there.
I got it and it seems that way.
Please tell me what you want to hear about this
Voice activation push
It's not talk, right? Eko
Let's stop the noise. What's the point?
Uh, noise uh
Once
Well, for now, that change is fine.
I know because I can do it.
Just because of those MODs.
Um, open the MODs and get a simple voice.
If you do so in the chat settings, you will be able to appear.
This is what I'm trying to say.
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah uh uh uh
Are you okay? Please wait a moment.
Hey, I'll check it out.Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, it seems okay, so uh...
I have been to the world once.
Enter, enter, and press the V button.
please say this actor's voice
I can hear you, so just a moment,
I'm going to talk to you in Kura.
Ah, I can hear it. I'm glad I can hear it.
I asked someone to open the V button, and something happened with VV.
I was able to enter the settings using V, which was used to enter settings.
I'm sorry
There's something called that audio adjustment.
So you can adjust your own audio.
Wait a minute, this will be reflected in everyone's eyes.
Thank you for adjusting the volume.
I'm glad I was able to go.
This is a world where everyone has a voice. This is a world where everyone has a voice.
There's a little bit
Usaoo that was good thank you very much
As a thank you, I'll give it to you.
It's okay, it's okay, please do your best
I'm going to die, I'm going to die, okay?
Nene dies
I'll die because I'm fully equipped, so that's fine.
S
Hey, just this for Sui-chan.
I'll give it to you. Thank you. I'm dead.
A message from everyone who did it
Wait a minute, it's too late, everyone.
How is the volume balance?
Shall I raise my voice, my little voice?
Tsu-chan's voice sounds small
It seems to be okay with the settings here.
I'm glad everyone was able to give it to me around here.
Make it small and check the condition of the Nether.
Let's go. The Nether is looking good.
Tasui
Chanato is probably that.
Na Potan-chan
Gatsui-chan is kind of the same as me.
It's like I'm going to conquer it because it's like
I'll start setting up some equipment.
It's looking beautiful
What is this?
What the heck is this hole over there?
Hey, Ade is already digging something.
Nothing yet
I wonder if it hasn't been done this much. It's still underground.
The person digging
Are you already digging this?
Yeah, but I'm heading over here, wait a minute.
That's right, I'm a little gold-equipped Azuki-chan.
I gave it to you
go back once
I got more gold equipment.
Ji looked like Arinos
hey
Okay, I guess the equipment is a bit bad.
A little bit of that Polka-chan thing
Should I go to Karaida?
Polka-chan has arranged quite a lifeline.
It seems like he's taking care of me, so that's how it is.
Oh, how, how, how, how, how, how
Please take care of me, bring something scary.
Are you saying this? Is it for potion?
Are you going to eat this and that?
Is it okay? I like such high-class ingredients.
Please try it, it's delicious and it's poisonous.
Yes, it's far away
It's okay, I'm that Peko-chan's dog.
No, it's okay, is it true? I understand.
Well, I'm hungry, so let's eat.
Thank you in advance
It all died
Wait a minute, change your keyboard regularly.
I end up switching to Japanese mode on a regular basis.
But mix it up at the end of that one.
Looks like everything is scattered
It's warm here, Polka-chan's place
to
How much money do you have?
is
I have this, so let's have a little fun.
kana
Oh, will you make a diamond?
What should I do with my equipment?
And there are 10 pieces left, right? 4 pieces.
body
but
123456789 fuselage 9
or the rest
2Do you want pants?
[music]
Wow, this is annoying
hey
Is it good to add it with pants?
[music]
hey
1234567a7
pants and legs
What should I do with
After all, it's dangerous in the Nether.
I wonder if I should make a Tedema sword or something, then someone?
Hello, I'm here.
Oh my god, it's a souvenir.
A-san's hole was loose when I let her use it.
Looks like he was giving a gift to Ni-chan.
I'll take a look at it. I haven't seen it yet.
No, it was dead, but I think I've seen it already.
I received a lot of information, so that's it.
This is for you, Kito.
I thought it would be a good fit and gave it to you.
Thank you, I'll take a look
Please take a look when you feel like it, thank you
Thank you very much
Bring some meat too.
Sorry to bother you
[music]
I'm going to make my own equipment.
Dako
I want a room too.
of
flying sauna
W.C.
Eh, idols don't have that kind of thing.
What are you doing?
I'm just doing that, so I'm sorry for bothering you.
I said, but I couldn't hear it.
What are you doing?
Please don't trespass.
Oh wow wow wow wow wow
I'm catching a lot of fish. I'm catching a lot of fish. It's so close.
Close, close, close, oh, it's broken.
I'm sorry, what's broken?
My fishing rod broke
hair
Akagasankaga
When I was fishing Sanatan, my fishing rod broke.
What's wrong with you? I'm sick of it.
I was thinking of breaking Kirusa
I have too much, I have so much
Well, this is the last one.
Eras 1 is so wonderful when I grill it.
We are also working on this together with Mao below.
That's amazing
It's a wonderful beautiful house
Yes, I tried to squeeze my lips a little.
I went to see Polka-chan's Saare.
Wait a minute, I'll bring the horse. I'm tired of moving the horse.
yeah
So I guess I need a horse.
and
Subaru also lived with A-tan.
Don't call that a home
That's a hole, no matter how you look at it, it's a house
Hey
Peko-chan's house is also Peko.
chan wanted to live in this house too.
I'm a bit rebellious so I'd like to make one for you
By the way, where is this my horse?
Where is my horse?
Tokoma
Is that the best?
Is everyone going to the Nether?
Nayoshi let's go Akutan
I wonder if all the Black Widows are going to the Nether?
I'm a little worried though.
Okay, let's take a look at Polka-chan's
Go see
I hope everyone uses it TT
tower
Experience points
to
Okay, I guess I'll sleep a little longer then go to bed.
everyone
[music]
Baby is sleeping tonight. I'm going to spend the night.
I'm thankful that I can do it today, Dad too.
It looks like he might come, oh hello
Are you writing this?
I'm pooping
Apparently everyone hasn't been there yet.
That nether that I haven't been to, the nether
I guess I'll go to the Nether and do something like that.
But at TTT, yes, yes, until now.
I said I wanted to do a little pulling.
So the obsidian is lying in the sky, so the obsidian is
I'm about to give it to you right now.
It feels like obsidian now, oh the nether, right from inside.
I'm going to connect something like that or something.
I see, I see.
Hey, I already have all the obsidian, so I'll leave it for now.
I'm just giving it to you, but I can't help but feel like sleeping next to you.
Shall I go with you?
I want to go with you
I also want to go to TT.
Teyoshi
What's next? I want to get it.
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it
I hope you received it properly.
I should have thought of throwing it. Hey, he's talking.
I don't think Yone-chan and Nene-chi are here yet.
I was surprised that he was talking alone.
It's sad that I'm all alone. I was talking all by myself.
What are you doing as a broadcaster?
It's normal for broadcasters to talk alone.
It's terrible because it makes me feel sick and tired when I watch it.
My family asks me why I'm talking.
Na
That's right, it's fate.
I'm missing one item and I have the key.
I went back and bought it.
That's right, that's where you're going.
Oh yeah, let's connect it over there.
Nosa, I want to go, so let's go, ah, let's go.
Let's go. There's only a little bit. There's only 22.
Thank you for just one thing
Thank you so much, let's all go together.
everyone
Let's go
Let's go, okay, it's almost time to leave.
There wasn't
What is the knowledge of
I have a stomach ache.I have a stomach ache, but I can't get it out.
That's painful, that's because my stomach is tingling
Ganene-chan that's what Akutan is
I don't poop like that because I'm an idol.
I don't know what you're confused about.
Look, it's not there.
You're the best
It's coming out.
Don't ride, don't ride, go to Adameka
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's ride
A horse that can go without moving
There's a boat. There's a boat.
Then change your horse, then follow me.
Please, yes, we need a boat, two people.
It's okay because I can ride it.
It's okay to have something like this.
Let's come here, please.
Yes, please come forward. Yes, please.
Thank you very much for your help, jump!
Please dash first.
I dashed
It's getting late, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Please don't fall from a high place
Please don't fall. It's scary. Which one is it?
perhaps
This way, maybe this way
This is it, Atan Black Fall
Where am I black here?
Can you go straight? Yes.
It was connected before the Nether, really.
Are you okay
What is it?
drop
horse mahoki
Leave it in front of me
It's this way, so go straight and on the left.
image
That's good, isn't it?
Yoooooooooooooooooooooooo, diamond equipment is really nice.
It's necessary to go without taking damage.
It's necessary, isn't it? Is it necessary? When will there be a leader?
Full body equipped with diamonds
Please log in a little early.
I borrowed that Kazama-chan's Sayattetsu.
That's right, that's what I did.
It started in 45 minutes.
After 45 minutes, it was probably Azuki.
The leader will be there at 5:00 p.m.
It seems like they have been replaced.
I was watching the news
That's right, I saw it on the news.
No, I didn't mean to appear in the photo.
He's the one on the news
I wonder if it's Takochi or not, it's still half way
That's about it. Is this still completely correct?
I think this fits
By the way, I've been following along without understanding anything.
But what kind of excursion is this?
I'm heading to the trap tower now and I'm already there.
1 piece gate
What is a rap tower?
It's far away
It's in Saa's first response.
I wonder what's wrong with that low transparent part
I thought so
I wonder what that is, maybe a potion?
It's a transparent part that I haven't used yet.
Transparent, or rather, everyone's voices are cut off.
Is that rude? Are you being rude? It's kind of transparent.
I mean, there's a building.
I wonder if it's like that.
It's like I didn't understand it, it's like the sky is the sky
It's red, it's big, it's good.
I could see the cherry blossoms
Yes, Oji-san, it's not the time for breeding, Oji-san
I don't want to say that.
Sanoshi breeding
Doroeooo
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm coming. Do you want to go slowly? It's okay.
Is the length okay?
Be careful, there are some holes, so be careful.
Please put it on. I understand.
It's a tough road
Is this correct? Wait and comment
I have equipment that is stopped.
Length comment
So wait a moment, what's the comment?
I was logged out.Wait a minute.
There are a lot of comments, and there are a lot of them sometimes.
It's common and seems to be happening recently.
There seems to be a disconnection during the broadcast so please log in.
It's like, "Please, please." It's so bad.
Sorry for not being easy
I can see it, I can see it, this is it
This way
I can see it, I can already see it
It's still a long way off
[music]
I think it will take a while
Yes, but I've already gone straight to the end of the sea
It feels like it's quite far to walk, yes.
I guess they're going to build one on the beach or something?
It's like a sky trap, yeah, yeah, yeah, the sea
It seems like it would be more efficient to make it
I see, I wonder why.
It's surprisingly far away
And it was this far away?
[music]
It became
Po, I wonder if this matches the scenery around here.
I want a map that doesn't exist
[music]
How many minuses are there?
1600 Ah, I can see the jungle
jungle yes
[music]
I'm here.
I'm getting closer, yes, I'm getting closer.
Everyone's voices are cut off
It's a great effort
I will act as a guide for everyone moving forward.
oh
Beyond that jungle
I hope it will be easier if you connect the missing nether.
[music]
Hey, it's a bit far to travel now.
Well, it wasn't my car, it was a horse ride, but it looks like a car.
Don't die.
Do you sleep once?
Yes, will everyone sleep?
I'm sleeping in a place like this
Kanesu
Thank you for watching.
Oh, I'll come anyway. Oh, I'm so glad. I'm so glad.
Nice, that's good, yes.
Let's go to the orchestra
Yes, this is it.
Thank you, this way, this way. Yes.
It's okay, you'll see it soon
Yes, I want to defeat the skeletons more than the next time, so tonight.
I don't have to sleep
mosquito
Oh it's here
It was a bit scary, but
Use this
[music]
That's right. Just leave it as is.
Yeah, that's right.
Wow, let's fill in some of the holes here.
I wonder if it's okay
Is it okay to have just a TV?
Take the colorful one in the middle.
I don't have any diamonds, but I do have them.
people are
Leave it to me
I wonder who's cutting the onions to save the day.
Nachakanaaraarakill
It's fine here, what's going on here?
It's a trout, well, if it's over 3 meters high.
I'm sure it wasn't okay.
It's more than that, so just connect it to the one above.
It's probably okay
That's nice
Thank you very much for your help.
Okay, please open this one too.
Please let me know the length
Oh, let's go in.
Well, I guess it's okay.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Yes, coordinates, coordinates, coordinates, here, coordinates.
It is 20774
Hey Chinami
Did you see this side of the mackerel? It's okay.
It seems okay. By the way, the other one
Appearance
and 13 of 70
2 also 13 yeah 72 270 27070
2 70 and
22 and one more frog 204 of 204
of 45
Ihohon
Height is also important. But height is also important.
It won't change like that
Hey, okay, let's go in. The two of us.
Peace of mind, it's dangerous, it's dangerous
It's dangerous
As soon as I entered the room, I gusted.
Well then, with that gust
Let's have a home run derby
Can you do it? I was really shot suddenly.
But I'm sleepy
Where was the pork pig just now?
Be the leader wherever there is Kegagas.
There's no such thing as a bow or something that bounces back.
If you bounce back
[music]
That's what I mean
Ouch
Ta
[music]
Come, come!
Which way should I go?
[music]
Don't come here
It's okay
Or is it okay or is it the limit?
Installation
Wow nice nice
[music]
Don't worry, let's make this place. Nice, nice.
nice
Hey
Nice, the gate didn't break, nice one
It broke, but by the way, it was nice to fix it.
As expected of you
Okay, okay, there's also Susto.
Leverage
nether
Woot, I can't use this.
I feel like there was something like Kakoru as well.
Karayoshiyoshiyoshi
I also made the roof
Let's go!
Everyone, don't put that bed there.
Yes, that's the bed. It's scary. It's higher.
Don't do it, it's expensive
I just need to change this.
It's a bit like a designer's apartment.
It's like that
Irregular shape
Stylish, stylish, stylish
Are you okay?
What kind of magma?
Just a little bit on this side.
It's okay, it's okay
Yokoko's magma is a little scary, scary.
Be careful
[music]
It's easy if you don't
But build a wall
Toko Wall
Maria wall aqua little work
It's dangerous outside
So I've already converted.
[music]
Hey, it's just as you were born.
Where are you?
This way
Did you return it?
[music]
Wow, where did this go?
It would be better if two people did this.Two people.
I think there is a quest for two people, so two people
Please do it
Oh my god, if you press that pin with your sword, it will bounce back.
Click left to go.
Quest Quest Ora
Oh, don't go, leave, leave
Oh
Good luck, but I missed out on the Dan.
a little bit
I guess something happened when I defeated this guy, right?
I'm pretty sure I should have gotten diamonds.
I guess I was able to escape.
Looks like I'll get 10 Kawawa.
Doubles
I want to be like that doubles battle
It's gone
Around here
Well then, shall I go? I may have made a mistake, but I'll go.
Wait, whose body is this?
Um, minus, uh, we have to move on to plus.
There isn't
plus
[music]
Reverse direction
Plus, wait, wait, maybe this way?
This side this way
There are a lot of torches because it's around Nemakoko area.
You can shake it, right? 4045
This way?
Naoi, I wish I could go in this direction.
Maybe
I can go around the house
I'm sure
I'm lost here. Oh yeah, I'm going to surround this place.
Let's go
Once in a while
[music]
Shall I dig here?
I'm being teased by all the dangerous people
Maybe you should be a little careful
Magma might come. What is TT?
Um 77
Kakeho-chan is here, isnt it true?
everyone
[music]
Titi has a lot of money Padre I want money
Maybe
Hey, yeah, yeah, I got some money.
Awesome
Hey
Well, not at all yet.
is
4080 a little more
I can't hear that voice
People
Some kind of attack is coming
Rutte Raid Raid event occurs after 9:00 p.m.
Yes yes yes yes yes
Yes, if you go, that's it.Maybe not.
Well then, should I go back? Is it still okay?
Are you okay
Attack or attack is bad
Wow
Frame impact
That sweet potato
Attack, Commander, I've attacked you before.
I wonder what the hell is going on with people?
It's like if you knock your body down and then defeat it.
Hey, have you ever seen a new enemy?
But that must be dangerous, it's strong.
Some people have bows and some don't.
I'm playing around with a lot of things.
I think I might need a bow.
hey
Oh, but there's a skeleton portal
It wasn't
It's called something like Kenenechina.
Let's go together for a moment.
I'll put it in the men's and women's pine trees, thank you.
Zasu azasu
Yes, the diamond speed is amazing.
I can hear the voice of Gust. Walls and walls are a must.
[music]
instructor
Thank you very much
Sensei nice nice nice Subaru
get lost
Subaru is lost, where is he?
is
Even if it was Subae, I would have gotten lost.
I wonder if you're in trouble. Shall I go and pick you up?
This is also true
There's a lot of Maruishimarua, something like this.
I'll give it to you anyway, Captain, give it a try and experience the thrill
It looks like it's going to be exciting, so you should squat down.
It's a thrill, a thrill
I'll do my best to improve my skills.
It's not here.
I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'm squatting now, Captain.
It's okay if you squat down.
Please make it really okay
Yes, but my predecessors cut it for me, so I'm saved.
wall wall
Hey ah
[music]
I'm so nervous, it's scary
Scary
Too much screaming
But nice, nice, do your best, I'm sorry.
After all, I was able to accumulate my experience.
First, let's dig.
Let's have lunch
Yes, let's do a little maintenance here, ah, magma mama bear.
ah
If it's dangerous magma, can we avoid it?
Yeah, which one do you prefer?
Nako magma came out, what should I do?
Yeah
It's like this coming
I don't mind filling in the teacher's name, but I feel like I can fill it in somehow.
I feel like
But it looks like one block
Fill in here
Well, it seems to be okay. Yes, I'm a bit worried.
Maybe it will come if you put on
do not have
Looks like it's not even Hoia, nice
Nice, ok, ok, ok, take care when you go.
I'm going now. Be careful.
It's a hole
Hole, it's true, confirmed, no enemies, no enemies, no enemies, proceed
It's moving forward, wait cobblestone
Nana Muscle
Muscle too
do
Yes nice
nice to do
Good, maybe soon
Well, it's a waste, just wait a moment.
Please make ice ax
Then from that side to the top
I can hear some voices, please be careful
Maybe a little earlier
I've been going up the stairs for a while now.
[music]
Kae 13
Hey, I lied, I'm down, I'm down, I'm down.
This is below 80 or something, even below it's hollow.
Maybe
Konoto
Hey, it's under the gun.
I'll go down below.
but
Is this okay? I can hear it screaming.
But is it dangerous?
Once here or next to this
[music]
mosquito
I wonder if it's a lie
[music]
or
4445 I think I can probably go if I dig here already.
but
Yes, it's true 2.
[music]
Yes, stay here
I feel so nervous
My heart is pounding, it's a little over here. Yes, that way.
Is it possible if I dig that?
Yes, what a crisis!
So, 1 device per fire is 1 fire.
is
I guess it's better to be on the same page, just in case
scary okay
Emishite
What's that? That's amazing. Maybe it's lightning right now.
Oh, that's it, right?
I'll give you some muscle and I'll do it.
No, it's not.
I want to make a mistake, I'm scared
Good luck, it's scary
Is it okay if this is straight? Is it okay if it is straight?
That's right
Yes it's fine
Yes it's hot
I tried digging there, and I dug it.
Do you want to
Well, just in case
There's a sound on the wall
It's scary
Okay, I'll wait a little while.
[music]
Kayoshi, come wait.
Here I come, yay, this guy was so fast!
I was able to do it before the attack, and I passed it through.
Tao is being maintained
Nice, it's here, it's here
Thank you, it's dangerous up there too.
this
in
[music]
Nice ceiling. Maybe I should increase it by 1.
That's right, because you can't jump.
If it's going down like this, what's going on down here?
If you don't have it, it will crash. It's a bug.
Maybe you should try it once. There are no stairs.
Sorry, it's not 3 at all, I'd rather go with 3.
mosquito
I've done it before, so I'm fine.
Okay, Moe here, I'm going to pull a tiger, right? I'm planning to pull one.
I wonder what it's like, it's better to pull Ne-chan.
It's convenient, nee-san, where are you planning to pick it up?
If you didn't plan to draw a draw, then 2 squares.
Is that okay?
That's what 2 squares means, 3 squares horizontally.
thing
The shield is
Right now
I don't have enough trains to go to.
Maybe the stones aren't like this, so oh
Okay, there are still stones, then.
Then I'm pulling
Just fill in this space.
Yeah
Good, good, good.
Okay
Nice came out
Oh nice, now it's open.
What should I do about the ceiling?
This is it.
ka nice nice nice
Arrival Yay yay, are you going home?
Better
[music]
oh
Oh, I want a signboard.
[music]
The signboard is about to be attacked on Iron Planet.
Isn't it?
TTTThis is hard to understand
Here it is, on the contrary, it's too simple.
Too simple
hand
Hey, okay, there's still time until the raid.
It's coming. Wow, I want a diamond.
a bow
I want a diamond sword
[music]
Hey, let's be a little bit edgy.
I'm going to TT.
Welcome to this
[music]
Hey, please do the raid.
Maybe it would be better to enchant it?
Maybe
No
Raid Since the raid event starts from 9pm, armor is required.
etc.
Align well
hand
Align and align
I recommend that
[music]
LEGO-chan is a fun raid event.
Is this okay? Everyone dies.
I wonder if we can go if we all do it together.
I'm a little worried
But I'm just enchanting you
Maybe everyone is already doing enchantment?
Kana armor, don't worry about me
[music]
I wonder if it's okay
I'm going to TT
It's about 9pm with only 10 minutes left.
It's my body. I'll make it in 10 minutes.
I wonder if it's dangerous, it's dangerous, I'll die once more
I'm jatting
So this life that Peko-chan bought me won't die.
subordinates
No one is preparing.
village
Collapse is a lie. Maybe the village will collapse.
[music]
Everyone, seriously, don't let the village collapse.
Yo
Countermeasures group
I'm sure it's there
Chives and Kai
tub
No no no
No, no, no
shellfish
No, I'm taking precautions, so I guess it's okay.
Full of dreams
I have a lot of dreams
Not quite at all
I'll wait so
[music]
I don't mind
I'll make some for everyone too.
There are a lot of them
Do you want to distribute it?
Not at all
Nayato 10
[music]
A little enchantment that might not fit the minutes
go to table
aside
I wonder if that's it
It's a bit time consuming
There are more people in that holosaba.
Probably because the map has expanded since that afternoon.
It's also hard to come out.
is 21:00
It's probably just like that and it's already a countermeasure
There is someone who will do it for you
Then somehow it will work out
[music]
It'll work out somehow
I want you to help me with the 21:00 attack.
Masuto
[music]
picture
Everyone should wait for the T-bow.
Well, bring it.
[music]
Well, there aren't that many, but I'll go.
Or not at all
Do you want to sleep once?
[music]
3 bows are missing
Difficulty Hardcore Max Uub 7 times
Masu
E-yui-gae
Probably an attack
It's dangerous everyone
E SOS
Probably
It's terrible, it's terrible, it's outrageous
It seems dangerous
Oh, you translated it for me. Let's go to sleep once more.
Wow, someone is going to die, I'm so hard
I remember dying even if it wasn't the core.
To be honest
I don't have much time.
[music]
After this, then
Let's go now
It's a bit impossible for me to reach level 30.
Enchant from level 20
I guess I'll peel it off later and apply it again.
is at level 2
I think I should enchant this.
I don't have much time
[music]
So I probably left out the enchantment, even if it was simple.
direction
But cows are dangerous.
[music]
Hey, I don't have enough arrows.
Yes, there is an infinite bow. Yes, there is an infinite bow.
Well then
It's okay, it's okay
[music]
Neki
Masuunto
I want to put this one on the opposite side of the door.
this
fix it later
Let's do it
or
More than enough
I wish there was a teru arrow
Toyabaika
Nayabata
Oh no!
sea bream
Peko-chan near Kaet Peka-chan
It's near Holo House, right?
Good job!
It's time Hey time
Hey, I don't have time
Wasn't it around here?
facility
It's this way. It's this way.
Nayabato 4
[music]
It's awkward
Wasn't it around the cat?
[music]
That
mosquito
Um, damage reduction 3 Wow, I want this, wait.
Lapis lazuli
Not good
The damage is light, the flames are impossible.
Posture Endurance
power flame
Subtle and subtle
[music]
Too subtle
Damage reduction 2
Put it on once
It's a bad flame position.
1 bug
Tokoira
Hey
Are you strong?
[music]
Namada
Is it no longer possible to go?
I can go
falling position
Sanke and Keke toke and for a while
O
[music]
Erm
Okay, shall I go?
I brought some lapis lazuli
I'll wait and see if I can make it in time, but I'll return it later.
There must be a lot of lapis lazuli.
Let me answer that for a moment.
[music]
Will I make it in time?
Hey
Everyone wants it. Let's fight. Yes, let's go.
go
Yo
Oh wow, my legs are so placed
Feeling protected
do not have
Wow, what kind of battle is going on here?
It's a very strong enemy
This is coming. I wonder how it will come.
I don't understand, even we can understand it.
Or do you fight? If you just climb, you'll be fine.
I'm thinking this is going to be burned.
Are you running away here? It's definitely a stone.
Well, if you die, it's over, so run away.
It should be fine, right? It's fine, right?
A sexual mentality where only you can survive by using it as a shield
Wouldn't it be nice to have it?
Give me a different boat, I'm sure it's a boat
I want this block. Show me your cousin.
I'm in trouble, I'm in trouble, oh yes, here.
[music]
Let's go, what kind of divine punishment is this?
Besides, it's probably 9pm at the door.
I'll put it away
The final one will come
Kape-chan's uniqueness, how can she get over it?
I climbed on this block on my own.
Raise yourself up, do your best, understand your strength, be on your own
Well, I don't have a bow.If you have a bow.
I guess it's better to just leave it to the bow body.
Please let me climb it, I'll make it special.
Hello, please let me come in, Senpai Tokkou Chiru
Kaaa Bancho Naka
Does your wife have a bow and arrows?
Thank you very much, thank you, Aoza
My senior looks like a cross, and I also have a bow and arrow.
Why are you so cute?
Well then, there are 57 books.
Aruyami, that's where I just picked it up.
by chance
If you have any leftovers left over, put them back.
Please, I have it for myself.
The leader has arrived.
Leader falls
Certainly
It's okay to try something different, A-chan.
Sorry, I don't think I'll use it.
Someone please, can you do this?
I can't do other things, but can I do this?
Moshimo-chan is amazing, Ade
They're doing it over there, they're doing it too.
Make it but wait
Wait, wait, I'm making a golem
golem iron iron
Pumpkin pumpkin on top with bu
A golem riding a pumpkin
Where, where, where does it start?
Where are the people attacking?
I wonder if this came from this.
I can hear a buzzing sound coming from the side where I dropped it.
Oh, it's a pillager
Pillager Pillager shoots me
I'll use remote control over there too.
Do I have to have a bow?
Nice, strict, or almost friendly, and strict.
Wait, wait, wait, there's no golem golem.
Is this Uub 1?
The new one is coming. Where did the new one come from?
Because cows are cows, cows are bad, so they look like cows.
Yes, yes, something is coming, cow.
Someone like that will come. He's dangerous.
I wonder if anyone will come after the bow is gone.
Where do I get off? Where do I get off? Change the BGM
I wonder if I'll try this?
This is a fun BGM. What happened to me?
I'm coming from I don't know what's next I wonder if it's coming
where
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared
I'm so scared that I'm so worried.
I wonder if it's over already
Takaa, everyone is too strong, just take a look
Come back!
[music]
Teru
Oh my god
[music]
stomach
I don't really come
There's a book in the back
I'm looking forward to it
This way, this way
I guess I can't climb up here.
[music]
What is it?
[applause]
You're nice, nice, nice, you're classy
Okay, I'm going to sleep
I want to give it to someone who will use it at night.
[music]
I'm trying my best. I want some stairs. That's in the ocean.
guess
Tee
It's so bad
It seems like they're doing some scary stuff too.
No, the golem is doing it, it's amazing
A group of golems are doing this, right?
It's burning! It's burning!
Teru
Nice, nice, it was on fire, it was on fire
Something like that
It's a really hot bow and arrow, and it's really strong.
Hey, I feel like I can win with just Golem 3.
Golem strong
It's too messy, I'm coming
Teruene, but I have a desire for tactical goods.
Very strong
All I can do is
Hey, are you crazy?
[music]
[applause]
Let's divide this up into chunks later.
Let's all sort the items together.
is nice nice
I'm riding something like the milk in the back is cured.
It's scary, it's scary, it's scary, it's scary, it's real!
what
What, what, what, nice nice nice
That's nice
There's something dangerous, hurry up!
There is one
That's scary. What's wrong with that guy? He's so nice.
[music]
lucky lucky
[applause]
Epolka
Polka is Pol-chan, so Pol-chan's Kusu
I've been murdered by someone and I'm holding my hand open.
It's not close, it's not open.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Okay, there's an item that looks a little important somewhere.
Thank you very much for being here
Thank you, Ru, please help me survive this.
Who is going to make this?
There's no such thing as a Polpolu product, but it's a milk bucket.
It might be the one Polka was drinking.
that
Oh well, I'll make a grave for you.
A little bit around here of me
Chan died around here.
I'm used to going to Matsu
There is also one signboard
Let's have a farewell party together
have a farewell party
Everyone was writing in their diary.
Let's go to sleep, let's go to sleep.
Good morning 21:07
Apparently he died very early, at 9:07 p.m.
Thank you ok
Yeah, I still see it as a ghost.
Now, I'm holding Pol-chan's grave.
Let's make a big grave here
This is where I died.
I died here, I've already made it
It's a little bit longer here.
Better
Good limbs are faster if they are long.
It's like a plus alpha element, flowers.
Aohana's hands are really long.
It's true, hand-throwing at 9pm.
Touch the length of the hand
There may be some
Don't be shy
I'm starting to feel like I'm starting to feel weird.
It's amazing if you don't
Something amazing happened to everyone.
Ruttei
Well, it was a farm house, so the face
I want it, but there's no trial, so it won't come back.
1 time
I loved this, you could go as far as you wanted.
Hey, you like this. You liked this.
It's a great opportunity for everyone to take a photo.
Please take a photo from
Let's take a photo, let's beep beep beep
Yes, thank you. I'm not lonely.
Because I'm at Yomio Yoichi
shellfish
This is me too
It's unscrupulous to say something like this. It's unscrupulous. It's unscrupulous.
Too cautious
Hey, thank you for your hard work. Thank you. It was good.
Thank you everyone for your help
Thank you very much for your help.
Thank you very much.
It's sad, sad, sad, Pol, Pol.
I have some leftover arrows, so I'm going to use them up.
There is absolutely no problem. There is absolutely no problem.
I would appreciate it if you could give it to me, thank you
Thank you, Aki-chan.
Now I have a bowgun!
Shall I go get that back?
If I don't go back for a while, someone will be there.
It's all over now, Polka is dead. Polka
died. Hello, there are so many people here.
There was an attack event right there.
That's right, Miko was in danger.
Miko is seriously naked, but that's really bad.
Emiko is seriously going to die if she's too equipped.
It's dangerous, it's better to be equipped, seriously.
I suddenly feel like coming here again.
Apparently it looks like that so be careful
Kanakaku
What should I do? A little attack
Miko wants to put the items somewhere.
What locker is Miko?
Is the locker Aramiko's?
No locker, no locker yet
Well, I thought I should make it here.
I wonder if there is such a thing as a diary? Yes, I should make one.
Kuren's rocker Emiko-chan's picture
This is the locker, this is the locker.
Yes, it's true
I've always had the Ukasa Swaru called Sarae.
I tried this once once.
It's a big space, so my luggage is packed here.
Anywhere is good here. Anywhere?
Okay, let's do it here.
Anyway, why are you talking like that?
Yo here here Shibuja here here etc.
Okay, that's terrible.
Here it is, here it is, here it is, here it is.
It's Mi-chan's locker, so I'll stay here.
etc. is given, so there is no need for days etc.
Please tell me a little bit
I don't really understand, but I see.
Well, what are we doing today?
What are we all going to do today?
We all call it the Nether.
But I guess I should go to the Nether or something, it's opened.
Apparently, someone is 120 kanamamazu?
It's okay with me
I think what I did
There was a time when I was 200 years old.
I was talking to
Yo what what what what
Mikoshi and equipment
Moe
Miko-senpai looks like she's in a messy system
Everybody, please
Please, senpai
Eh, I already hit you, so you don't have to give it to me.
I'm sorry, it's so big, it's so good
I'll give it to you yes
Well, it's an iron sword, right?
Can I give it to you? I guess I can't because I came late.
There's nothing. It's okay. I'm at fault.
I ended up returning it and getting this in blue.
Yes, I'll give you this, look at the red poppy miko-chan.
It suits you.
If that's not the case, I'll show you where the iron is.
The place of iron waiting for this rule book
First, let's look at the rulebook that taught us
It's a rule book that you can read.
I want Kaan, it's a lie, read the rulebook
That's a lie, the rule book is that Peko.
This is something that I was taught by Chan.
Thank you for the rulebook.The rules are
There are some changes, but please read here.
There's nothing like the end and this place.
I see. If you read this, you'll be fine.
That's right. That's right. My voice is small.
That's right, Senpai, what's my voice like?
What is this signboard in Teagen? What is this signboard posted?
What is going on here or here?
About 10 to raise
[music]
It's not just me who's small on the side, it's everyone's voice
but
I borrow it
The voice of the wiring is coming from
ah
Ah, just get it this close.
Or this is fine
Is this okay? Everyone please wait a little longer.
Just lower everyone's voice
Can you all lower your voice just a little bit?
well
Everyone's voices are broken
That's right.
I'll leave it at that and hear everyone's voices.
huge
Too bad
I'm just doing it somehow
A little bit of parse is suitable, but what would be better if it arrives?
Kotoan
Dasononi
Macra
[music]
It's not worth it
Haso's cross will come down and I can do it.
It's huge to be able to do so much
Distorted mushrooms, etc.
You are free to make your own home
Let's go and get this.
Let's go, this is the action stone in hand
I'm a beginner in Minecraft and don't know how to do it.
Frog eggs with someone I've never met before
I took Ron to that hut while he was going to get the eggs.
It's in the diary storage area inside, so at the end, yes.
Write your diary and upload it here and submit it here.
It's true that I received it.
Thank you in advance.Thank you in advance.
Hand holding hot mushrooms
Is it okay to collect Akuta frog eggs?
let's go
It's coming. Shall I go get it?
Are you going on a mission? Yes.
I ended up becoming a management dog on a mission.
Let's go. This is a frog's egg day.
It's 10 but seriously
Please, please?
So that's what frog eggs are like.
How and where is this frog?
Eggs are minecraft's English.
I wonder where the egg is, I can't see it.
Wait a minute on this
Silk touch with the body of the body diamond
It seems like there is
I don't have it, I've been doing it since the first day.
Didn't I die?
I've become the management dog.
Yes, yes, that person is employed.
in
Maybe I can just make some equipment for now.
Wait, wait, wait, right away
Alka-chan, I'll explain it to you here.
Please come here once you know where you are going.
yes
Yes, Polka-chan has that basic life.
All the lines are in order, so I'm dying.
But Popo-an made a little comeback.
Get it
It seems like there will be a revival or a revival.
It is up to God that he will be resurrected.
What is that?
Ah, hello, hello, hello, hello
Hello
Hello, Kusaku, Kusaku, Kusaaku
Hey, did you just hit me when you wanted meat? No.
Miko's now capon and hardcore
Capon is really dangerous, I can't help it.
Well, it's a place where fish flourish.
Osoda Senkyu Senkyu Yes, the fish are kind
This is the fish I caught.Good boy, good boy, do your best.
Please don't forget this.Forget this.
Maybe not, I'll load it with food first.
Nokai
Even after that, everyone is still confused.
If you don't get hit, get hit, get bored, get bored
It's raining
Thank you everyone for making sure things got worse.
do your best
Thank you bye
I don't know who is saying what bye
No, what do you mean it's bad baby?
There are a lot of babies here, hey.
Miko-chan is seriously that one-chan
I'm afraid I'll die if I don't have this equipment, so I'm here.
I have a free one, so please take a look.
Thank you so much Pomatsu too
Pol-chan, there's some meat too.
Can Pol-chan be revived?
It's okay if it's just something, even if it's just something
That's amazing!
These are the gold boots that don't come with it.
Let's have some
Yes, I can carry a bow. Yes, I want to give you a bow.
I can't hear your voice so I'll pass it over here.
I see, thank you, I'll give you a little peach.
Itadakimasu Tokunea Yamosenkyu
How did you get hired?
Thank you for turning into a dog and becoming a dog.
Please, please provide the equipment.
I would like to introduce only Nemiko-chane.
Thank you so kind
There is a trap, so Miko-chan is a bit
It would be really bad if he died, yeah.
Let's just get the iron equipment ready.
Hey, here it is. Iron is iron. That's what it is.
There's that Taa Tetsu, Unsuma-chan.
Hey, today at noon, that's all I heard, okay?
After getting the iron equipment done, I feel good.
If there's anything you don't understand, just ask.
Please, if I die, it's over, okay, okay.
Okay, okay, if I die
Does it look okay?
I'm a little worried.
But there's something I'm equipped with.
There are so many of these
is dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous.
It's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous
So please drop your feet and go.
Are you going to Acta? I'll take a look too.
I thought I'd go to see it.
Let's talk about everyone in 100 people
I already found this fortress.
I feel like I don't know anything yet
Let's go, bububububububububu
Big Bububu was kicked out, Bububu Uikochi
Ting ting ting here
Wow, it's a nether laser.
This is also this
But I brought a bow and a bed with something suspicious.
It would have been bad if I had brought a bed.
Well, the bed is going to explode, so it's okay.
If it wasn't there, I wouldn't put it there.
Should I keep it in my inventory?
too
Let's go and see TTT
Or explore, explore, explore
If it was a bow like Kauncha, it would be possible.
Thank you Ademoni I need that or a bow.
Hey, what's the military here?
I don't know
Wow, what kind of military weapon is this?
It's so weird that I don't know what the military weapon is.
Hey.
I can't help it, maybe the moment I threw it away
broke in
Ah, no, I can't pick it up now
There's no diamond, there's no diamond, it's an attack
of
[music]
It is a product
to
Please take a look at everyone.
go to
What should I do? Should I go?
Yeah, I'm going to go check on you all to see if you're okay.
Let's go, let's go, let's confirm that.
place to keep it
Oh TT, go take a look.
Surprise
Starting Minato
Ah, I don't know if it's a good idea to get this.
Nyanone
Acha is iruka
Please don't burn me down, next time.
It's okay because it's a dog, so it's Inumeko-senpai's dog.
It's okay, it's okay
[music]
Where is this place?
It's scary here, yes, here, here, get out of here.
Ba
I understand that if you enter here, you will be connected to TT.
A little bit
Is it hard to understand?
The person who saved Nako
It might be good to do it easily
The road may be a little difficult to understand
Well, it's a little simple.
Let's just say it, it's enough
Hey
That
fault
Yeah
What are you doing? What are you doing?
Oh wait, what's that? There's smoke coming out.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa hot
Ah, the two of you are like that.
Maybe there's a difference between the two of us doing something together
That's not true.
What are you being touched by?
I was doing something
Kaaae
Yeah, yeah, that's amazing, it's swimming on the ground
It's amazing how easy it is to swim!
Peace Peace, that ship
It's for two people, so there's a difference.
Echo wait ah seriously Aku-tan is
What on earth was Rami doing in the first place?
I was there, so when I came to see it, I was told that it was nice.
Ah yes, the leader for now.
I thought I had to do something, so I went to TT Tower.
I thought I should go, but I found two people.
I'm going to go do something like that.
I'm going to go tomorrow.
Let's do it
I'm finally here
This guy this guy
hit
Hit it and it will bounce
Sorry sorry sorry sorry sister um
I wanted to get some glowstone.
Yes, yes, yes, today's challenge.
Yes, there is a glowstone.
It happened, everyone took it, they didn't take it.
No, that's not good at all.
No, shall I go?
By the way, Glowstone Lamicha
Did you find it? I haven't given it to you yet.
terrible
[music]
Oh no, I defeated this one, so it's Rami's too.
There are two people who defeated it. Two people defeated it.
Without it
I think all of them are going to die.
It's okay to think and lie, it's okay to be an enemy
I'm heading towards someone big and bulky like Kirito.
I'll give it to you, let's go look for some food.
Let's go look, let's go, let's go gross.
Let's go, let's go, let's go, hello, next time
If so, please defeat one of us. I understand, please help me.
Please help me, oh please help me, help me, help me
There's a glass here.
There's also one here too, it's serious.
That's amazing, there are so many crossstones
Yes, there are these. How many of them are there?
Kuro
Wouldn't it be better to say something like "Ston-e"?
Hey, the number wasn't decided yet, was it?
It's already fallen, what should I do?
Either take it for now or get the flow stone.
It's okay to put in one piece at a time, because just one piece is enough.
Sounds good, I guess I'll go.
I have no choice but to ask someone to load it for me.
Matoa everyone, there's a stone here.
Let me load it up a little. I'm getting burnt out listening to it.
Hey, men and women are idiots.
Pile up stones
I'm going to get more and more, I think I'll just wait.
I didn't have Silk Touch. This is Silk.
It's no good unless you touch it Glowstone
So yeah
Eh, even if it's Silk Silk Tachi, that's it.
Without an enchanted bong
Yeah, no one
I don't have Mia's Shirukotachi.
I don't have Silco Touch. No, I don't have it.
Holding a bow like Gogomi
Garbage that doesn't have a bow, like Naia-san garbage.
With a jaw like a bow and a discussion
Are you okay
There are bows like that, that's that.
Thank you very much nice
It's here, it's here, now I can go long distance
I see. A Klausto who does crafts.
If you collect them, you can make them with crafts Neneyou's place
I found this and wrote it in the comments.
Well then, shall we collect some? Ah, let's collect some.
But, but, I'm a little bit
They said they'd break up as soon as they found friends.
Because there was no silk touch, silk
There was no touch
Let's go together, let's go together
Everyone, everyone, let's ride and ride
Ride, yes, ride, here, here, here, ride
Yes, yes, yes, no, who's loading it?
Kuren's this is yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes to Kuren
a
Survivable but dangerous
I'm in tune with you
It's okay if you're a genius
Glow Stone Dust 4 pieces in 1 piece
It seems you can do it, so mark 4 here.
Thank you for this.
Thank you very much, this is also here
It's true that you made it
I've got this and I've got it.
Hey, I have it, I have it, I have it.
Oh, it was perfect
It's perfect, this is so good, then you're tired
Desuokasa But there was something else as well.
Aasusuke defeats Easan
Mr. Susan is here, Mr. Airune SK.
I defeated you, I defeated you, I defeated you.
He's the founder of Kurenai Enata Tara.
Thank you thank you thank you thank you
Thank you very much
Why is everyone like this?
dakomo too
Why is it normal that everyone does this?
It's here, it's Te.
I think there were only two beds.
I have a bed. I have a bed.
Oh, why don't you have it for practice? Why do you have it?
I'm sorry for the sticky stuff, but it's winter.
So I decided to come.
I'm not ready, it's okay, it's dangerous, it's dangerous
Sorry for being a little nervous
I'm sleeping, I'm sleeping, I'm sleeping there, I'm sleeping
Go to sleep, sleep on top
Go to bed, good night, let's have a little time together.
A little girls talk to deepen the experience
Or girls talk, uh, something like that.
ah
Okay, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.
Go, go, go, why is this?
The moment when we suddenly became three people
More and more
What's wrong with this? Someone needs to take care of this.
There's something strange about this
I can see something
Hey, it's up there.
[music]
I can't see it, I don't care.
There's something like this
A deck that looks like it might have some kind of deck.
It's necessary.
Today is good too
The weather was nice
say
[music]
Please wait for me, La-chan
There's something different about yesterday. Yesterday.
Yesterday was the only day
I'll give you a head, Ramy's head.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
this
I wonder why it's like that?
What's that, Haramiku-san?
Okay, so let's remove the skin.
I'll try to remove it, but don't open the settings.
And hat off yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah oh yeah
Yeah, yeah, that's right, here and there, that's gold.
It looks like it happened yesterday when I took off my helmet.
Yes, that's amazing, Gerardon.
This is not Gerrard
Gerardon-san for sure everyone Gerardon-san
It has become
I received it
That's amazing. What's this? I didn't know this.
It's a bug and it's called a bug
Hey, look at this, you can do this.
Don't explode, it's okay, it's okay
[music]
There's someone here who can still fix it even if it's broken.
It's amazing because I'm sleeping here
picture
skeleton
I may or may not have defeated Esuke-san.
It's here, it's here, it's coming from above.
I've come, I've come, I've come, I'll defeat the three of them.
Kill one of them, and there's only one left.
What should I do? There's still one more body left.
Nari 3
Sisters, that's right.
Hey, it came, it came, it came, I defeated it
[music]
The guy who beat Mr. Nice or the guy who beat him
I took the opportunity to defeat them.I defeated them.I defeated them.
That's right, I've already defeated you. Are you already gone?
There aren't any special items or anything.
There is no bow or arrow.
Because I got it
Let's go, shall we go?
I can go from here.
Wow, this is completely spreading.
You can fix it, I'll just go with it.
I really cared, I really cared, the bonds
Dayono
a
Nososu
[music]
Cliff's
Kirito
I can't hold it, it's okay
Should I stop? Should I put it back? I can't hold it.
[music]
Okay
Yo
debt
Oh, are you going home? Are you going home? Oh, I'm going home.
Let's go home Let's go home
Well, well, well, well, it has changed a lot.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, that's it
I never expected it to be that way.
That's right
Hey, he's the best of all the recent actors.
It seems difficult to do, but it's okay
Yeah, I guess I've gotten used to it as well.
That's what I thought, but it wasn't there yet.
It's been a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time.
Yeah, I guess so
Yeah, yeah, I guess that's what happened earlier.
If it was just the two of us, we would talk normally.
But I guess it's strange when this rabbi comes in.
It doesn't seem like a good idea. Look, the combination is new.
That's what it feels like, yeah, yeah, yeah, I guess 3
I was so excited when I became a human being.
Or rather, that's what it is, even if it's normal.
It's the same with humans, you can do it with just two people.
But there are three people like that here.
Let's go
Yeah, it's so refreshing, everyone, good job.
Thank you for your hard work, I hope you don't have to worry about it again.
Thank you very much. Don't forget to check your head.
Yes yes yes yes thank you
Thank you and yes
Yes, it was kind of awkward
It was kind of awkward. Why was it like this?
Was it awkward? Was it awkward?
Hey, is there anyone? Let's go.
If you don't die, you're an experienced person.Ah, an experienced person.
You're leaning on me
Hey, what did you do to get all fired up?
Maybe
I think I'll try to wrap my head around it.
Come on, you're such a dangerous dog.
It's so tough right now.
Since it's Pecola's dog, I asked her if she was being strict or rolled her up.
Did I say this? It's okay, roll it up into a ball.
I was told to join the baseball club here.
That's just how I play baseball.
Looks like it's rounded.
No matter what, I thought it was someone else. It's okay to be evil.
Wait
I don't want to worry about it, I think it's impossible.
But no, he's not a monk, he's a horn, so no.
Minna Rinan
It's fine
I'm your sister, so I guess you got rejected.
stain
Do you like your face?
[music]
To remove the skin of the hat,
It's getting better, it's from a different setting.
Maybe Minecraft's water supply was rolled up.
Ran-chan's name isn't round, it's round.
Everyone is rounding things up. Maybe this is also true.
Just a little bit
[applause]
How did you make it yellow? How did you do it?
What did you do? What did you do?
Somehow that setting, that setting money
from
This is in the back
Nada-chan's black hair is really
Be like Gerardon
Teru
Some people are going
And I'm the only one in the front
Arukopopopsi looks like a baby
Well, I'm the only one who's already getting tired.
It's terrible though
Come out
[applause]
From Yomi-chan-chan's settings too.
[music]
Amazing chaa-chan da-chan
It's so expensive
Mechami group photo Toro group photo This photo
This is the last one because there is a possibility that it was filmed.
There is a possibility that it will be a group photo of only me.
I don't like having hair in my bangs.
Well then, it's a cute and lovely Roga.
Wait, wait, wait, we'll get together
[music]
Look, definitely look, it might be the last time, wait?
This might be the last one, wait, Subaru's Subaru's
It's like he's looking at Kill for some reason.
The Subaru name is in my line of sight.
It became, it became
It's too funny. Let's all go.
Hey, let's do our best. Let's all go to my summer.
What's going on?
[music]
Oh, wait, Anji-san is coming.
Wasn't it? Oh yeah, it's coming.
I'm coming, I-chan is coming too.
Are you going, Lee-senpai too?
to
Get it, what are we going to do now?
Now I'm going to go to the Nether and explore.
I've been looking for it, but I haven't found it yet.
If we all join together, we'll all be the first.
I think it's possible. There's one person here.
It doesn't say that it's just you, so it's good to see it.
Don't say anything to the dog, come here.
I don't mind if I interrupt you for a little while at work.
It's Kamochi, it's a bit of a pain.
Everyone's four are here, everyone.
Dayadaya, there are two more strike plates.
You can get it, but there is definitely something.
Then it's not me
I'm aiming for it, but I haven't gotten any chats yet.
Not
a
wait
[music]
the bed is gone
I'll use it
I wonder if that's the case
I have 6 diamonds now and 1 more to go.
You can get one cod chisto plate.
There's only one left, so here it is.
Thank you very much.
That one day is 10 times better, thank you in one day.
Thank you 10 times
Sleepy
Ta
forget hello
Hello, thank you very much.
Please, let's all go together.
Noeare boyame
You're going to the neta now, aren't you?
It's dangerous
If you feel like that, you'll die.
large
Is this all impossible?
Tayoshi yoshi yoshi profile Ado senpai hello
Hello, thank you very much.
I hope you will be kind enough to help me.
Thank you Anya Japanese
It's fluent, isn't it?
It's the first time he's not Japanese.
I don't know, yeah
ENG Japanese ooooooooooo Aina-chan too
I guess I'll wait a little while and try to figure it out.
Oh yeah, I did it already.
Yes, I want to be
Hey Ramirami, someone bring me a lot of food.
I only have 10 pieces of meat 23
I'm a little old man who wants to eat the food he has.
The one who died is said to have it too.
Isn't that the case? Is there someone to eat for Ramy?
Looks like Teti made by Super Akutan
Hey, but it's in the Nether, so let's go.
Thank you for allowing me to go from the Nether.
I've got some food. It's a mistake.
I got 3030 pieces of miso food, seriously yeah
That's right. Is 10 pieces of rice and meat enough?
Is there not much in the Nether?
I'm going to kick you a bit. Wait a bit.
Is it better to bring it?I did the fortress road.
I wonder if my breasts are okay? There are no more cobblestones
I brought it, man.
hey
How about I give you some cool black stones?
Ah, thank you, just thank you, that's half of it.
About
Let's get this done, Noruha
I'm going to go there soon
There might be something
It looks like it's going to be a long time coming
I don't have it either.
It's okay to work
There's a wall, there's a wall, there's a wall, there's a wall, there's a wall
Dangerous distance
The cherry tree we meet is probably the former shrine maiden.
It changed from something that looked like a pumpkin to a blue pumpkin.
No, someone is planting this.
This blue pumpkin is not yet
I don't mind if I meet his eyes when I wear it.
What are you looking at? I'm sure you can't watch it.
If you look at Ani-san, you'll see that. That's right, this is me.
I'm wearing a pumpkin right now, so why is everyone on the ground?
facing
Let's go, it's dangerous
Let's go let's go let's go!
[music]
I'm scared of going to bed, so I'll leave it there.
Nayoshi, someone with something like that could use it.
Let's just leave it alone
I'll put it on top
Toko
Good job
Let's go!
do not have
Go go, there are too many people, let's go
I can't do it, let's go, let's go, it's too much.
Yes, in order, in order, let's go, please
Yes let's go
Let's go
Rua wait
Yaba
Block is dangerous, I have a junior close to this.
There was a portal, right?
Naimi has prepared it for me.
Arii
[music]
Thank you very much for your help
Is this the place to be?
Thank you can go from here
I see
So which way should I go? I'm still exploring.
I'm sure it's good that it's not too crowded.
scared
Now
There is
That's scary
Even if this is scary, I'm sure he'll have to kill me all at once.
kill the gust
Gust's becomes diamond diamond.
Very loud voice
But somehow
It's quite inside
So I'll also be loading everything, senpai.
Do your best, do your best
Do your best, it will help
I'm going home
It's not dangerous
It's scary
[music]
What kind of way is that? That's not true.
It's either there or not, it's on the top.
This is different, this is different, this is different.
It's like Rega. It's like Rega.
I understand, that's what it is.
I understand, I understand, this is a normal road.
Hey TTT Kayabaibe
That's dangerous
let's go let's go
What should I do? I have to do something.
I'll dance, I'll save you, I'll save you this time, this time, this time.
Oooooo I don't know what's going on
What's wrong? Yes, pink pick pick.
dejapic dejapic dejapic
Danger
Kuja Danger
[music]
Danger, are you okay?
Let's go
[laughter]
go go go go
If you don't press shift shift, you can press waiting money equipment.
If you don't have gold equipment, you'll be fine with gold equipment.
Goal equipmentGoal equipment
Go Go Lets Go Lets
Go, it's dangerous, I'm riding a horse that's out!
[music]
There was something like this
Hey, what's wrong with that one tomorrow?
Wait a minute, that's crazy.
But that's all I can do, but I'll do my best.
What is that? It's over there. What is that?
Which one is it? The one in front of me is Pipic.
Pickni's Fortress Pickni's Fortress
The fortress is here, let's go.
I'll get this fortress. Can I get points?
I saw the point and said, ``This is dangerous.''
Get dressed here
Awesome, I think I'll get points for bringing this.
Isn't this nice?
If you take a photo, you'll definitely see everyone in screenshots.
We all watched it together. Everyone watched it.
So everyone is an adult
[music]
Go, it's a bit big
This might be a good idea later on, I'll save money
Kya
Yes, there are some good ones too.
I wonder if I can go?
Looks like it's a little higher up.
But I feel like it's a little dangerous.
I'm sure you can go
Yo, you were Pecola's dog just now.
Even if I go there now, I'm sure it's fine.
Okay, I understand that you can go and try it.
It makes me sleepy
What is this?
Something dangerous is coming from here.
Not often
It's 30 per person who will find it.
I'm sure there's only one person, 30 per person, I want to go.
I'm going to go ahead and kill you.
I want to but I'm really scared
It's nice to go somewhere raw.
Maybe the left one is the left one.
It's close, I went left. Let's get it.
You can get Glostone Diamonds, so Glow.
How many stones were there?
There's a hole here so be careful everyone.
Yes, no, Stone and Senpai are stubborn.
It's too bad just to put it in.
Falling Senkyu is nice this way.
I just want to check on my way home.
[music]
You can go there if you take this road.
O
gogo lie
Right?
scary nice nice
Eggplant This is IQ 50 million points IQ
50 million yeah nice IQ 100 distorted
Even mushrooms have an IQ of about 5000
It's dangerous, isn't it?
That's right, the red mushroom is distorted slightly above me.
Is it a mushroom? It's not a distorted mushroom.
That twisted mushroom is suddenly worthless.
Don't tell me you're ignoring me
You're ignoring me, you're ignoring me, so go punch me!
Why is it okay to hit my senior once? It's blue.
You can afford to call me out and get excited.
I'll just double check
[music]
What's going on here?
It's also a red forest
everyone comes
To Kashira Red Forest
Going to the Red Forest
Chau Amikogasa collect the glowstone
Maybe you're giving it to me
look
How can I do this?
Teru Ako's 4 glowstones become one
Masu
Don't take it and die, thank you very much
Even more amazing
Glowstone from a high place
Thank you very much
With four
Block, that wasn't Silk Touch.
What?
Can I get the blowstone?
It only says that, so make it that way.
I think it's okay, but I see, I'll bring it in powder form.
If you come back and make a blog with it
It's okay, I have it on hand, maybe I can make it now.
Ao's
The rain in Glouston
Maybe I'll go for a bit.
[music]
Oh, you're done, I'm going to give you a great hold.
Please make it. I'll go get it.
Is that what you mean? Let's go get Sana Mito.
So that's it, up to the top, no, with that hand
I can make 4
It's like picking up something that's falling.
I mean, I brought this. I have this.
Yokoko
Akita deki
Taki
People who don't have taro
I made an Irodoroki
[music]
Yes yes
Yes, there is.Oh yes, there is a certain blog.
It's a waste, everyone is fine with this.
Looks like it's okay, everyone get it, everyone get it
Ah, you also need sole sand, easy.
Speaking of soles
Is the sandwich okay?
[applause]
Alive, Alive, Alive, Alive
I forgot where it fell and it was hidden there.
hand
I'm glad I'm glad I'm alive
If it wasn't for Dai, Yomiko would have died.
It's better to have this and this that you collected.
So Miko-chan has it.
Okay, if it's that bad, please drink it.
Bruise
I'm going to watch it, so let's move on. Yes, I can't stop shaking.
Maybe it would be better if the ship sailed through the red forest.
I don't think so. I think it's better to go from the forest.
I don't think so, even if I say I'm going to cut it,
It's bugma, it's dangerous, this side is fine, the right side is fine
It's safe, right, it's safe.
yes right side
Is this true?
[music]
is
That guy on the right, what did you see and say it was true?
What is true?
It's okay
Red, red, let's go, let's go.
It's impossible, red means I'm definitely going to die.
I might sleep
You can't defeat a wild boar.You can't defeat a wild boar.
I think you can beat it while watching, but together
Something you have no choice but to do
Wait a minute, what are you fighting against?
It's a mushroom in the sink, so fight it differently.
The distorted mushroom is over there in the green.
Is it true that you can get off for a while? Oh, it's true.
Where are you from?
I'm sure that will make you some money
Let's go, the throw that stretched me out
It might be a good idea to take the stairs here.
Stairs Should I make these stairs here?
It's possible to pass by Mowachako though.
Oh, that's how it goes.
Probably because pigs are really strong.
It's true that I should make some pork here too.
There's a real boar here, it's scary
It might be better to go from there.
I'm sure Dad will come soon.
strong pig
I have a bow, so I'll wait for the battle too.
I'm sorry, God, is cleaning so much right now.
Eaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Fall
Ta
Who was it? Maybe when I threw it
rug on
I'm sorry for the inconvenience.
Maru rag rag rag rag this rag rug is alive
I'm alive, this is laggy, it's stuck in my butt
Teru
Rugguggugu
I did.
[music]
I need stairs
nice
good
Solly Rug Solly Rug is Rug Solly
It didn't hurt at all. It's okay, gentle.
Let's go on Go Go Press Yes
I'm going
or
Let's get down from here, where we can win.
Reaching Nanaoo
Oooh, what should we do now? Go away!
There's a green mushroom over there.
Where is that?
There's one behind the magma over there.
I have to collect enough for everyone.
Can we go from here because of this tree?
I can go from here as you stretch out.
Where is everyone waiting? Are you going to play Gasurko?
Kill Gust, Gust's voice is so bad
Is it enough to kill it or kill one with all the ghasts?
What's wrong? It doesn't say how many people there are.
It seems like it's hard to do one thing at a time
I'm sure it's okay if we all defeat one.
mosquito
Just take it one by one, everyone
That's good, that's good, senpai, so everyone should have one.
I'm going thank you for this Ako
Senpai, I don't have a block anymore either.
I'm sure it'll come, I'm begging you.
Yes this is gone
Please block me please
tenkyu scary
Scary okay
It's like Kahishi Yabahisi, wait for me, I'll go back to blue.
comes
It's okay, it's okay
the best
I don't like it
I don't know how to hit it straight.
It's red in the red forest, and it's always above the mushrooms.
I have no choice but to go slowly as I go along.
There was one more. Another one stopped.
Don't jump this guy
Go
Stop it, this guy lives in the Nether.
I don't know, but I'll give it to you. You're doing your best.
Everyone, this is it
Give it to me and wait a bit. I'll give it to you.
I'll give it to Miko-senpai, thank you.
I'm a little scared so I'll drop it somewhere safe
Yes, that's right. If I drop it, I'll try again.
I had to pick it up, so I was a little scared.
I have another one to connect to the side.
It's okay, it's a little magma around here.
I want a little more depth.I'm still 55.
It's better not to have this thing here.
Yes, it's better not to do 5.
There was one over there too, so I grabbed some.
Masuonan looks like he's running an errand.
I'm going to go get it. You can go like that.
It's not here.
That's fine, there's still a long way to go
It's far away, but it might still be a forest.
Sounds in the forest are scary
But
Right, okay, blue. Right, okay, okay, A-kun.
I fell in the blue, I want to fall in the blue, right there
I'm back
I have 2 more to go.
Yes, there is at least one pig, so it's a pig.
Let's beat it
It's better to cut it because it's not dangerous.
I don't think so at all
I'm going straight one more time.
It would be better to cross over
No, straight ahead
I feel good
[music]
It's almost time to block
I heard a voice once, I'm saved, I'm saved.
There's a wall over there. Cross it! The wall is here, it's almost here
Are you okay reading?
It's coming!
depending on the
No more blocks
This is definitely what they did on the first day.
do not have
What to do on the first day of
No, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's soul sandwich
Yes, there is Sol Sand. There is Soul Sand.
I'm not saying it was subject to recall, but it's quite
That TT Tower is everywhere.
Water stream that could be used for elevators etc.
It's an elevator, yes, it's true.
Are you okay everyone?
It's okay, it's okay, I'm grateful to everyone
There's enough distance to make blocks
Can you sleep?
Is there anyone who was looking at it? It's okay, but I'm sorry.
You can't say that
I was called, so I'm going.
Please come and give me your dog. I'll do my best in the fortress.
Please look for it.
Please, I'll go back in a bit.
Please, do your best, do your best
I got a big mushroom. It's okay, mushroom-san.
It's okay. Is it okay?
Then please excuse me
Eh wait
It's okay.
[music]
But there is something.
But it's a little scary. It's okay. I'll get back.
won't die
I wonder if it's okay
It's a little scary. I'm glad I have a dream.
Octopus Chika
Here, here, leave this landmark behind.
good
If there's no landmark, everyone can go home.
I wonder if everyone will come back this far.
I wonder if it's okay, I'll leave it to everyone.
Let's go
Masu
Heading now
[music]
Are you okay? It looks like I won't be coming home.
But I'm a little worried
I guess it's a bit impossible if it's just Subaru.
I'm sure Momo will manage somehow, Mamiko.
Shimiko-chan who is there is also a bit pop.
There are some, but Miko has been in Minecraft for a long time.
I'm sure you'll be fine, just leave it to me.
Let's say I'm Hato-chan
What is this as a dog?
[music]
Come from here
Tanana
What is this? It's more like a road than a computer.
Aka-senpai, what on earth is this?
Koyori Road On Koyori Road Searching for that fortress
I've been digging, but haven't found anything.
I see it's a road, so where is that?
Well, after everyone digs this.
Lost child this is digging
Ta
I'm going to have a good time going there.
Even earlier
There was a road even earlier than Kotoe.
[music]
Thank you for not being here or here.
Thank you
It's starting to get complicated
Is everyone okay?
I can get this
It's so cool
mosquito
Now, which one is Towa-chan?
Nitowa is
Mamekotawa-chan
Oh, I was waiting, I was really lonely
Did you read the chanok rule book?
Were you able to call me what I read outside?
So somehow you understand the rules.
I wish you could love me and survive.
That's right, let's love it and survive.
That simple thing can be regulated by someone else.
I think that method is the quickest way.
If it's 3 races in the middle, oh yes, that's possible.Who is regulating it now?
I think anyone can do it, as long as there are regulations now.
But I mostly go to the Nether.
There are no people here, but I'll die alone.
But it doesn't seem like it's okay.
Mikoto Suba was in the Nether with me until just now.
So, Sui-chan and the others are probably in the Nether as well.
Where do we go to the Nether?
Shall I show you around the Nether? There's nothing here.
You can just go. It's not so good.
Well, first of all, let's prepare the equipment.
Well, I guess it's okay, isn't it?
Please click here
I guess there's something
its easy
that
[music]
Just in case, that Polka-chan is already dead.
I'm sorry, but yes, Polka-chan is here.
someone
I'm here
Commander Kitsu is the leader of the group, let's make him the leader.
Please let me control
Please, what's up?
I started it right now. Is there something wrong?
What is there?
Napoi
Well,
Well, I thought I'd give you some bread like this.
Even food is food and food.
Understood, I'm going to show you around now.
Are you doing that? Eat that too, Captain, on the way.
I have something to do on the way, so I'm going.
Let's go, let's introduce that iron first.
It's a good place to take a train.
iron with iron
There's a place where that machine is located, Nori-san.
Let me introduce that first.
It's bad, it's already bad, it's been a day or two
If you don't, you're not Urashima Taro.
Actually, it's Taro Urashima. He did it on the first day and is already a big brother.
If I hadn't done that, it would have been really bad.
Run with that crazy jump
Even in Masua, there is a phase where I walk slowly.
I thought so, but now I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Sorry about that, I had to go for a walk tomorrow.
Sorry, excuse me, below here.
Nidekee sound
Wow, that's amazing. I got that iron and made that equipment for myself.
please make it okay okay
Well, first of all, let's open up the workbench here.
Comfortable pants and shoes
All you have to do is do this
Well, first of all, what's going on here?
I'll use a pickaxe and an axe.
Seriously, this guy is crazy. He's so energetic.
Half the year is just Jia
How many screws
No way
I'm ready. Let's do it in a month.
But it's good news here.
But yeah, you can become the strongest in no time
I have a trick, do you want to hear it?
I want to hear about this iron that loves shortcuts.
Oh, I'm going to steal everything. Yes, I'm going to steal everything.
I'm going to copy all of this iron, it's a shortcut!
I'm going up there
Yes, yes, I'm here
I've added some poppies.
Oh poppy
[music]
This is amazing. Yes, you are truly darkness.
You can use the falling route.
Because I'm still a devil
Is it already taking something?
It seems like it's been that way up until now.
It was
Yes, I can see it over there.
I'm not dying.
Eh, I fell into the falling magma.
This is wow
Lalala sometimes things like that happen in the dark
While we were talking, Magma Tanane was a little bit...
It's a bit ominous, so I think it's a bit bad.
teeth
It's okay already
Well, Kaekoyori-chan is crying and crying.
Wait a minute, Koyori-chan is dead.
What should I do?
Send a message to Kasako-chan
Let's go ahead and let it go.
When I walk for a while, I get hungry more and more.
I feel more hungry when I walk, so I run.
If you try it, it will decrease in jump.
It decreases when you jump and run, so it's true now.
It's no good if you're not a calm child.
Please eat as much as you can.
I think so.That's right.That's true.That's true.
I'm going to eat this bread that I received.
become
I'm going to replace this iron here.
That's right, diamond equipment etc.
It's not dangerous. I'll do this. It's dangerous.
This is short cuts, Iroha-chan?
Apparently, they made one for me, and there was one more in the back.
There's also that attack field created by Kara-chan.
picture
Amazing development
Do I have to make it an emerald?
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
It's getting so expensive
I'm tired of being eaten
Wow, this is what it is.
This guy is a nuisance
Spring is hard to move
I wonder how cheaply I can replace it.
That's right, that's right, this guy is a cat.
So I came here with a cheap one, but there was a cheap one.
There's already one
What should I replace this with?
Is it okay?
Even if I don't have a sword, I'll go to the Nether after all.
You'll take a lot of damage, so equip it.
I guess at first I had equipment, but it was equipment after all.
Yes, okay.
It's a bit iffy, the shin equipment is 30 ah the equipment is expensive
It's expensive, I don't have any good equipment.
Even if it's not there, you can get diamonds at any corner.
So it's quite cheap.
Yes, that's true. Daya will be included.
Wow, this is a really tall body.
Gaeshi
This and that are the first ones.
I'm waiting for 7 of them.
7 pieces
Hey, this guy is suddenly selling something.
He started it.
[ __ ]
Then 19
Now, the body and pants-wearing body are slightly lacking.
and pants body and pants body
Pants
[music]
I'll go get another iron in a bit.
I think it's piling up
Yo
lever
Amere
Are you okay? I'll leave for a moment.
Yes, please go.
I'll be back again, I understand.
Just do your own thing
Maybe I should give back my lapis lazuli.
I have to, so maybe everyone
People you want to enchant
Maybe there'll be some lapis lazuli fishing
Let's just take it from my house and take the horse too.
kana
I think I'm a little grateful to the leader.
The leader is watching
This is so helpful Peko-chan
It's dangerous to do it alone
Seriously
Sopol-chan's present is also Pol-pol's.
present
Thank you very much, Peko-chan
What do you think of the resurrection type for me?
can also be done
Zupeko-chan
Thank you, it's hard
[music]
The truth
niyolopeko
[music]
is
Okay, there's a lot of lapis lazuli
Okay, should I donate this?
Is Nami there too?
leave a little bit
Maybe I'll leave about half of it and ride it.
good
Yo my delicious
Bean koyabee
Seriously, where did you go?
I wasn't in court.
[music]
Hey, my horse is gone
Where was the last time I saw you?
No way
Kasan Black was good at escaping.
Na
Aita Tatata
Taa, Actor Black was nearby.
[music]
Thank you
Thank you, I'm doing it now in the place where it started.
Na
Go to the camp for a bit.
Let's see
There is a way to come back to life now.
It really suits you, red party, thank you, thank you, it's back
I'm not allowed to do it
I wonder how that Peko-chan will recover?
I'm doing a resurrection ritual now. I'm doing a ritual.
I wonder if I was born here. I wonder if I was born here.
I'll wait a little longer here, Peko, just do your best right now.
I have to give it to you, I have to give it to you.
What's the punishment? What's the punishment? What's the punishment?
Batowa
I'm at a loss. I'm at a loss.
It's Gebo-kun, so let's start from 1 with Sosa.
Peko who collects 7 diamonds is a total failure.
This is so bad for Nana, then I'll revive her.
Let's use Pekososa to get big mackerel from 1.
Quite a bit
fine
If I can get about 2 pieces, I can go.
After finishing, add about 3 chunks.
from
Where am I?
Create a world with
That's a terrible mistake from now on.
Does this mean everyone is going to be like this?
Pera-san
That's right, everyone who died from now on will be like that.
There are 7 diamonds in Naruko mackerel.
It's fine.
Is Yoeji Paw Paw the same as Paw Paw?
I've always wondered what happened to the potty
Are you working behind the scenes behind the scenes?
Diamond block heavy
Too mega hard
Please wait for the core diamonds.
7 such diamonds
I gave up on this because I thought the paper perspective was better.
Apparently so. Is it okay to be a god?
Hardco is fine for now.
Well, what happened today? I'm going to come back to life.
I'm sorry, please come to my house.
It's okay to receive it. Let's do our best together. Let's do our best.
Thank you bye bye again
Do you know this cat? What should I do?
or 7 accuracy is
Teko-chan, can you hear me?
Naoba-chan
Dada-chan, are you okay? Leave it to the leader.
I'm here, so let's go for a bit.
I might be doing something at that time.
Possibility of mood Moa-chan
Yes, yes, yes, what is it?
[music]
or more than 30 minutes
Pol-chan is gone too.
Ta
Uota-chan and the others are still doing it?
I'll go and check on the girls for a bit.
Peko-chan, I wonder if you can hear this?
Maybe you can't hear me?
[music]
Leave it to Haigo-chan
I wonder if she's there already?
Thank you for your hard work, Senpai, Hajime-chan.
I haven't seen it, but I haven't seen it.
It's good to see you come back to life
Thank you very much
Masu
Well, maybe I'm going to fight.
If you like that armor, I'll exchange it.
I'm going to do that work here today, so it's probably going to be a battle.
You're going to the Nether now.
It's always about Peko Peko's dog in my private messages.
Yeah, but if I die again
I'm in trouble, can you please come? Yes, it's okay.
If you don't mind, I'd like you to exchange this.
Thank you very much, okay?
When should I start this?
It's the same one I got from my uncle.
Thank you very much, I will give it to you as is
I heard that there is a serious iron shortage right now.
Well, I'm currently not available for streaming, but I'll try posting soon.
I'll make another trap
Yes, I'm so excited, everyone.
I'll make sure to equip you with the equipment.
Please tell me to wait a moment
If there was
Okay, I'm sorry, but with the equipment I just had.
However, the Nether is a bit tough.
I'm sorry, but I think so.
Thank you. I'm an angel with visible wings.
I'll go find you, angel.
An angel descended in front of me
Where is Nichan living?
leader's
What an angel
What can I say?
Oh my god that was a baby
Onya meow onya meow
Cheers
Nayar
Na-chan, don't do it
Na-chan is funny
Can you make it from a block by grilling it?
mosquito
It's good to build up my body now.
What are you going to do when you get home? Make a golden body.
That's what I want, because that's where the money is.
Yeah that's nice
Thank you wonderful Naina
Nice, now I can go to the Nether.
Well, let's go!
I just added some emeralds.
Thank you, thank you, that's helpful
Thank you
Masu
Is this okay?
Now, I also have a sword or something.
I can do it. I'll dig the easiest thing.
What's going on in the Nether? It's called Nether Note.
That's right, that's right, that's what's shining
That glowstone, that glowstone
Ah, this is a mission.
I'll give you a bow, thank you, Gust.
If you make it, it will be okay if you use this.
I wonder if I'll divide it into 10. It's quite a bit.
Areal-chan from Tokanaka-dancho Ichichu Yumiya
Apparently there are some souvenirs left behind.
I wonder where that souvenir is?
It seems like something is going on in this house.
Wow, this is different
What kind of toa is it to give birth to?
This is what you found for me
Oh, please use it comfortably, I'm a little oh
What makes it so strong is its diversity, so it's amazing.
This is a legendary sword, a legend.
A legendary sword handed down from generation to generation in SAO
That's amazing, it's Pachimon
That's Iwasaku or Elisidata's Pachimon.
Polka's Polka
I was watching Ruka in the sky, and I also said that I won.
That's fine, just be quiet and use this sword to rule the world.
I'll take it, thanks Polka. I'm a dog too.
But don't do anything. Are you looking at me? Are you looking at me?
I'm sorry, but I'm saying something.
It looks like it needs to be quiet. There needs to be people.
That's what I thought, right?
Let's read this. Are you going to the Nether? Let's go.
Okay, then everyone goes to the neta.
Yeah yeah let's go
Let's go, we'll meet a lot of people.
I think I'll be able to meet you all.
I'm here, so don't get excited, let's go.
Let's
yes i have
I'm not the only one who doesn't like it.
No, no, no, we're walking over there.
I just have to follow you. Is it hot?
I don't understand, I'm going at double speed.
deer
Well then, just that little bit
I don't want to go, Nanka-chan
Chan-chan
Chanchanchanchanchan
Chanchanchanchan
That's not true
If Momma-sama goes ahead, we'll be there.
It's getting dangerous so please go now.
Yes, protect me.
I wonder where it is.
Before that first sponsorship
Connect this and that
Where did that go?
It's like this.
Right?
Yes, I'm going to court, everyone.
This or the court
[music]
Tokoro, wait a minute, Captain.
is
What are you doing there? Why are you looking up at the sky?
Oh sorry, the leader enchanted me.
I said I was going and came home in a flash, so I was out in the open.
If you look up at the sky, it's like that.
That
the court where the court was tried
That thing has become so beautiful.
That's right, that's a trial.
It was solved by Pecola's dog.
That's why I solved it.
Pecola's dog woof woof woof woof woof woof
Don't say it looks good on you, it looks good on you.
Does it look good on you?
It's a little early.
Enchantment Enchantment has exploded
Zehehehe nice nice
Nice, okay, let's go.
[music]
Let's connect first.
Nayoshi
Oh, I'm taking a detour.
I really want to meet you
Even though he was riding a horse, he had a safe look on his face.
Wrong, wrong, stop the horse.
I wanted to meet you first, I see.
It's a waste of time, so let's be efficient.
Let's go, let's go, this is the bed
If I put a nice bed in the tub, it would be right here.
Even if you leave it behind, you'll die.
If you die, it's over, Let's Go Let's
Maybe I'll lose weight on the first day
There is a possibility that it may happen. It's scary.
That's a bit serious, I have to be careful.
Okay, you better bring lots of torches.
mosquito
Well, it's good if you do a lot.
I'll help you, okay, okay, please mark me.
So where are you going? What do you want to do?
It's not a mission, but it's a mission.
What is that shining?
I'm gonna get that one, too, Block.
There was
I can't dig here, so let's dig here.
Oh wait, the floor could fall down
That's right, yes, what should I do with this?
dig straight
Fuori
It's not bad, next door next door
Next to me, wait a minute.Wait a minute.
video settings
Let's focus on the visuals instead of the operation settings.
As expected, Yoshiuyaba
Wait a minute, I'm squatting down
It's totally fine, right? I fell when I squatted down.
No, it's okay. I'm in danger too.
This is so scary!
Oh no, oh no, oh no, it's so dark
Hey, just don't press it anymore, don't press it anymore.
Yeah, it's definitely dark
I stopped playing because the difficulty level goes up. I'm still at 1.
Even though no time has passed, I'm trying to kill you by building a store.
There is a road below
I wonder if that's the way to go to that TT.
I wonder if that's wrong, that stone isn't there.
Oh, I don't have any stones or anything, so please wait a moment.
wait a minute
That's the leader who doesn't seem to be having fun.
If you dig raw, it's around here
That's right, but
For now, I'll do just one step.
Oh thank you thank you
Thank you, it's a JIT coaster
Yay
It's nice and dignified.
Leader Leader
That's how I did the side mission.
I guess it went through like that.
To-chan, what are you doing here? Oh, here, here, here.
Please dig it, it looks like it's right in front of Chanako.
Well, I'll come as well, so it's okay.
This is dangerous
Because there is a hit
I'll die as soon as my fathers get in trouble.
It's okay to play together when playing, it's dangerous.
Seriously, that's bad.
And this is terrible, this is this again
Create a path with a fluttering one and a messy one
Do your best on the road.
Let's make it OK go
Let's go, what should I say?
As long as you squat down, you'll be fine from now on.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay
Yeah squatting squatting
Looks like Deruya pinky is fishing
A little side-by-side, side-to-side seriously, ai-ai-yoshi
Okay, okay
Okay, okay, okay
child
and
And oh nice
Nice Gichi
Scary tight
It's so scary, it's seriously scary.
this
I think it's glow stone, glow stone.
I have to get it
Hey, what's that sound?
This is a pig too big, it's not dangerous.
This is so bad, he's not coming.
This guy is coming, he's dangerous.
I'm here a little bit
This is really dangerous.
Let's have a look at that dangerous boar.
Ah, the nails are going to glowstone somewhere.
do not have
That's a glow stone on top of that.
There's nothing on the top
[music]
Na
Yeah, I have no choice but to move on.
It's okay to play a pig that's not dangerous.
The courage to play a pig pig There is a glow stone in Ako
Hey, it's really in a position where it looks like it's easy to get to.
It's right above me, it's so slippery! Wait, it's on the side.
It's true, it's better not to go inside too much.
That's not true, it will fall.
Don't push yourself too hard over there.
everyone
picture
Where is the pig? Where is the pig? Where is it right below?
You can do it directly below or with a bow.
[music]
Okay
Ah, something's on fire, man.
Enchantment with a frame
strong
Do your best, you did it, you fell down, you fell down.
If you just go to the side
Seriously, wait for the book.
I'm trembling, I'm going!
Yes, but it's a red forest from here, so it's a bit
Be careful that Ino
What is the red forest? Red is like that Ino.
There are a lot of them, so he's really strong.
Honestly okay seriously
mosquito
Yeah, there's something in the bottom left.
Hmm, bottom left
Is there something?
There was something walking around.
I wonder what it is?
[music]
You can even get this
fault
Why was I-chan taken away?
Pretty much everyone goes there.
Well, I guess the majors are in a bad place right now.
Is this okay to dig with iron?
It's okay because it's going to rock
You don't have to dig, just dig.
That's what I did when I took it.
[music]
No no no no
Did you say that?
4 of them make 1 piece
I think it's okay because
It's really some kind of craft powder.
It's like, ``I'm done tomorrow, I'm done tomorrow.''
Okay mission complete
What should Senkyuo do when he gets back?
You can search for it, but the fortress has not been found yet.
Okay, let's attack. Okay, look at me for a second.
Let's go look for ghosts, I'm already a senior.
I will
not found
I hope I can find it by now.
I'm doing some stuff
Hey, I want his bow. It's a crossbow.
But I found a fortress somewhere else.
That's right, it's the Piglin Fortress.
No, it's not a nether fortress.
I'm sure it's probably heh
I don't know what it is, but it doesn't matter at all
I guess it's the August 8th group, so I'm here now.
Oh, it's so true!
I did it by chance, it's amazing
Is there such a thing?
What happened to this little happiness and big Emi?
Stop doing that, my mom was so happy.
Let's turn this feeling into a saying.
The eye on the right is okay, it's really good, it's nice
I like this, I guess I'll live based on this.
Digging in two rows on that side
Digging. It's dangerous to do this alone.
Hey, it's dangerous, so I can't help it anymore.
Everyone
Thank you for your hard work Aao
Thank you for your hard work.
Wow book
Sorry for the inconvenience
Louis, Louis
Hey, I had fun
If it weren't for you, who would be the one to attack?
I'll do it, leave the proof that you're alive here.
It's not super cheap because the main character is super cheap.
I have no choice but to pass it on.
hey
I decided to do my best.
Alright, here it is, that's it, that's it, oh, yes.
Pico-chan, please come.
Yeah, don't push it, don't push it, don't push it
Okay, let's go, let's go
The iron tsuruha of Mashou seems to be suffocating.
I endured it too, I endured it when I said that.
It's time to leave it to you for a while
Too bad
I'll dig it up. I'll take it. Be careful.
Yes, wait a minute, what should we do?
That's right, that's correct, that's fine, I want to give you this.
Thank you, I'll give it to you, thank you
Is this dangerous?
What do you think of this?
Let's move on a bit
Kayabee reacted so fast that Uko is laughing.
The judgement is quick, and the scales are smiling too.
Good, I can go, nice.
Nice one
Go, I was just drinking water, okay now.
I'm just happy, I don't have anything to use, so thank you
Hey, close up the Nether.
[music]
It's still okay
Yes, yes, the leader is also broken, but I can hold on.
It's okay, it's okay.
The truth is, there is a difference between the good and the bad.
First thing today because I was digging for diamonds.
I have it there
Then I'll help you downstairs too.I'll help you downstairs.
Let's have a chat
That's helpful, this and that.
Hey, I'm lucky
Noa, this, what is that, the one who dug it
Sorry, that's a normal diamond.
It's just a normal piglin fortress, Pig.
Pig?
It's going to bend. It's really strong now.
Just take a look
Please don't miss it even though I just started today.
amazing
It's okay if it bends.Can it bend?
Maybe it's bent quite a bit
Probably go this way
Let's
Is it better to have one row or two rows?
That's right. Even one row is fine.
There are 2 rows so everyone can get in easily, but now there is 1.
There are three of them even if it's only 1.
It's a bit small, but I'll probably dig in there.
Seriously, be careful on this right
It's so bad that I was alone when something like Majiba happened.
I'm stuck behind me and can't pull back.
Oh, it's dangerous, there's a possibility that you'll be killed by your allies.
Mr. Monokini and Shirata seem to be fighting.
That's why I say it
Why are you saying this while laughing a little?
Don't say goodbye, don't be happy, one day's life cicada
The cicada had a short life like the cicada.
I did
I want to go more I want to go more now than Robin
I want to go more than Robin.
The Robin I want more than the Robin I want you to stop licking
I really want to go there.
I really want to go, I really want to go
Taiyoshi
It's scary, the roads are connected
It's messed up
That's true
It's going to turn from here.
[music]
Yes, I'll go this way.
What kind of pig is that?
war what pig war
I'm so impressed by what you're doing.
You know, it's not a line that a child would say on their first day.
This is a tingling cat
It looks like it's going to be fun, maybe for the first time
Today is also the first time for Kadadaha-chan.
I feel like this is the first time I've been on the list
I don't know what to do
If there is
[music]
Please go home
I guess it's okay because Mi-chan is here. It's okay.
well
No Peko-chan Peko-chan
If someone asks me to work, I'll probably get mad again.
Noyade Maamaaatan
showed us that we are only full
It means taking it no matter what.
I'm the on-site supervisor, so yeah, that's a lie.
It's still there. It's gone.
Oh yes, I'm senkyu.
Dayoshi
Okay, time to give it to you.
That would be a great help
It's okay
But when I look at it, I think, "That's right."
I think it's fresh. It's the first day after all.
Karasakou is full of hope
I don't think I'll do much more, it's just normal
It's been so long since I played Minecraft that I don't remember the controls.
It was so normal that I was just an aunt, but I logged in.
When I did that, I became an old woman. How would I do it?
That's the trick
I feel like I've regained my senses.
I'm glad I got it back.
I'm starting to have the same body shape as Minecraft.
It's okay to have an egg body.
Good job, I don't need money.
Is money okay? It's dangerous here.
Not at all.
cut down
cut it down
[music]
It looks like it's fun. It's important to say it this way.
This word when you're on it
direction
cormorant
Hua
It's helpful, it's good, it's good, it's good cooperation play is good
Hey, I'm cutting onions, everyone.
Teru
Everyone was cutting onions in Yonanka chat.
Okay, it's true. What is this?
I'm already registering the emoticons
I've registered so it'll come out soon.
Are you registered? It appears in the emoticon house.
I'll do whatever it takes to make the quickest face.
It's magma, but I can dig one more.
Can you stop it? Can you stop the magma?
No, Suba-chan, Subaru is dead.
subaru
Why did Tsuba-chan come back to life?
It seems like there isn't, right? Probably.
This is sad
Yeah, I can't stop magma, I don't know how.
No more, just make a road like this
It's over, yeah
The voice is scary
[music]
Let's go
Okay mom, go straight ahead
Thank you for coming here and for your hard work.
favorite quote
Nice try!
I haven't received my money back.
I have nothing to say to Subaru, the dangerous leader.
Are you okay
Certainly one word Unba-chan and Suba-chan
let's play
It's sad that I can't play until the last day.
This is also Subaru's Minecraft
I worked hard to make a schedule.
I can't help it, I'm pretty busy.
That's right, so thank you for your hard work.
It's really dignified, it's too scary.
I wish I could tell you this
Be careful, magma is dangerous!
Oh no, this is on the right, what should I do?
I guess it's okay, wait a minute.
I'm going to do a really amazing move.
a
That and that
between us
Ta
Ah, it's a little different, okay, okay.
That's amazing
It's a little different here. It's a little different here.
It's really hard to move forward here.
Give me this for a moment
I'll leave it to my seniors.
Wow, seriously, please stop meeting me.
If you rush into commenting, you'll die, so don't do it.
hand
It's scary
circle
Yes, I was told to bend.
It's okay to turn, this is already the road
It's impossible to be nice
mosquito
No, that's it
Yes, yes
Hey, maybe I can get off here.
book
I'm digging here
leverage
scary
It sounded like a child's laughter.
It's Gust. I might want you to build that wall.
It's probably dangerous, but just one line is fine.
What should I do?
I'll leave it with that feeling, sorry.
So if that white object comes near you,
If that were the case, Toa-san could also ask Matsu.
Okay, I understand.
and
Whatever, whatever, whatever kind of person
kana
No, just one more time
[music]
It's already the phase of listening to what you have to say
Naiyako nervous
If you have a strategy or a strategy that you don't have, then...
What if I eat it?
If I get shot, if I get shot
It seems like the bow will hit back and hit back twice as much.
There are only 6 of them, but they seem fine, I'll die after one.
He's like that. He'll die with just one shot.
That's right
Actually, there are various things that seem to be going away.
[music]
Uncle is back to life
I'm under the roof
Hey, it's true, I can do it, I can do it, I can do it.
It's sunny, nice
[music]
Nice morning, I'm here. I'll go next time.
Maybe I should try using a bow for the leader too.
It's included in the game, isn't it?
Lots of missions to get stuck in between
It's complete. It's complete.
I've cleared it, thank you very much
That's fine for now.
Hey, I heard that polka is making a comeback too.
Looks like both Terue are back, great.
Good
[music]
Ta
Beep beep, the oxygen is getting thinner 1
Should I open it? Open it, open it.
Ah, the air
Nagochan
Thank you, there are no Gusts on the left and right.
I can hear a voice.
Well, Aqua is already a dog, so that's it.
There's no point in doing it or doing the mission.
Well, it's still possible to strengthen yourself.
I'm so excited about this cat
I don't know if I'll get the diamond tomorrow.
Until I look at it, it might be that radio.
There is absolutely no possibility of it happening.
That's scary
[music]
It's scary, how far should I connect this place?
is
It's scorching hot all over
Hell is here
If you hear a little voice, I'll ask you, okay, yes, men and women.
Let's do it
I can hear it from the left, so it's probably to the left.
Yes, it may be above, so be careful.
that
If this or that
Oh, if it explodes, it'll blow you away and you'll die.
That's why I added two layers just in case.
I recommend it
Ah, 2 tiers. If it's 2 tiers, it doesn't fit.
It's okay, why did we make eye contact or even get looked at?
If not, it's okay
Yes, I thought it would be 2 steps.
There is a blue forest
What is the blue forest? The blue forest is better than the red one from earlier.
I guess today's quest is mushrooms.
Write down how you can get distorted mushrooms.
It was written there, Yukino.
There's a hot water pot, and it's amazing.
It's like rice porridge or rice porridge.
What does it mean?
thing
Kerona
Wow, let's go, leader, let's do a little bit.
This block has many blocks.
Yes, thank you. Sorry for the wait.
I only gave you one. Where did this go?
This is probably in front
I said it like a Pokemon.
Na
I came from the front, so I'm probably in the front.
There's a possibility that this is right in front of me.
Is there a chance that you are in front of
I don't know where it's coming from.
To be honest, I couldn't see either and got shot.
I feel like I ran away
I'll cancel it.
Kakoho
Then, if you hear that voice, please run away.
Yes behind
My hands are slippery due to sweat
Yes, my hands are sweaty and slippery, like rations.
Let's go
I'm so nervous
[music]
Let's cut it, it looks like it'll be fun
As expected
It's like this, first time is necessary, so Cho is too.
I really need it, I appreciate it, it helps a lot
Even if I'm too serious, I get choked up
It doesn't matter, right?
No, that's right. I want to get off.
[music]
Hey
I'll probably be able to get off though.
What should I do?
Are you serious about getting off? How do you get off?
of
Well, it was like seaweed yakiniku.
But no, it sounds like yakiniku, so it's okay, I can't go.
of
You're using it so much. I heard your voice. It's okay.
Get off for a while
Wow, that's serious. Wait a minute.
[music]
My hands are so sweaty!
Thank you, I came, I came, I really came
Come on, I need a landmark. I set up a tie.
There is a date near Kaneko
fortress in
Sorry, I'm sorry, but I'm already
There is something like a castle
There is a thing with big ears that is dangerous.
Surely not
[music]
That's not true, I'm against it.
Wait a minute, once
Settings are fine
mosquito
There you are, what's that?
Yeah, it's nothing like that.
anything
I wonder if there isn't one.
Is it Stone? I don't care.
If only there was a soul sandwich
There's one nearby that I want to take.
It's okay if you don't have to
Let's run away and be careful
Look, leader!
Nice nice commander, you defeated him, nice feeling
There is a hole so it's a little brighter.
I'm not going here, so I'm going.
Let's just leave it alone, sure.
I'll go if I get lost.
Is that okay?
[music]
If I do that, I won't get lost.
Finished
[music]
Leader Ade M is too shitty
Moko
Kaatan is amazing, it's okay, Kaatanchaa return
Teta-chan, where did you go? Are you going here?
There was a time when I was there.
It's somehow too deep.
[music]
Yes, it's a really dangerous road.
If you really find that fortress
It's probably the sea under those feet, but the sea
It's probably better to cross, it's pretty low.
I definitely can't stand saying that.
What can I say? There is definitely a lower limit.
There's no top, but there is a bottom, so it's easy to find.
If you ask me, the one below is probably better.
The lower eye
But it's a bit dangerous and there aren't enough blocks.
There's no
Yes, it's true that there is a block right now.
There are only about 70
There are only about 2 stacks of Nato.
Maybe that's true. I came back after preparing my equipment once.
I don't know if it's better or not, but it's quite an adventure.
I want to know
Nenanasa
Yeah, be careful there, there's a hole there.
Yes there is
Or will I go home for a bit? Or will I go home for a while?
Well then, the excursion is until we return home.
Okay, be careful
The person who said it would be safe in the end dies.
It is not safe at all from
A game where the flag jumps and the flag stands
Amogron closed down in an instant when it disappeared.
I got the stone, I got it, I got it, oh
O
Yeah, it's really reliable, I see.
Haha, I'll follow you.
Good job, good job!
Is that okay? Please, please, thank you.
There's a nice explosion of flames.
Let's put it on and go next time.
Because it's safe
No, I didn't even close the knot.No, no.
That's right
red
The manufacturing flag that was completely destroyed is gone.
Chimau
It'll be a big place, not a small place.
Sorry, sorry, I was surprised.
There's something so surprising about it.
There's no way I was born like this.
I have never been surprised.
Lol
Tachanwaro
It's been a long time since I've been in a while
This is because Wadama-san fell down.
It started with a fall, but now there are three of them.
Warotawaro
It's funny, it's funny, it's funny, seriously
Don't fight, then say something to the leader.
Please, please, it's another matter, but it's been a long time since I've been LOL
Wow, an image comes to mind right now
Yes, there is.
Toa was the wrong person to consult with, and that leader is Toa.
I'm sorry, but it's natural, isn't it?
I'm sorry I won't get into it, I'm sorry
The butterflies in Saisoda also seem to be a little long.
I'm sorry for being a blur, please.
I'm going to have a little trouble or a big traffic jam.
That too
Please come over here, Grin.
It's a fortress.
Hey, you survived.
Chanma sense
Good sense
Are you asleep?
Let's kill the octopus, go ahead!
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
It's okay, it's okay
mosquito
[music]
Nice, it's quite painful, but the sense is like that now
Yes, it's a sense
Is it okay?
Oh
Captain Yoisho Nice Nice also wanted to go.
Nice nice coming
That's good
[music]
Fall, fall, fall, the way I came
I'm falling, I'm falling, I'm not falling, I'm going home
Yes, it's falling
[music]
[applause]
O-baku
It feels like coming home
I'm going to sleep
People sleep, everyone who sleeps is alive
Excuse me for a moment
Okay, excuse me, leader. Flowers in both hands. Flowers in both hands, left and right.
I just said it, it's so embarrassing
It's like ASM, I'm sure.
Stop it, stop it!
Wait, I walked up to the microphone, and it was broken.
But Mike, are you okay? Destroy it!
everyone is back
Lulu is in danger, she's dead.
Tasui-chan was definitely the main character.
I believed it, Tsui-chan, Tsui-chan.
It's already 23:00 time limit.
It is so true that the bones were buried locally.
It's amazing to bury the bones in
What do you mean by leaving only the soul behind?
I put it into it
Tajamata again
It's too dangerous and I'm trapped in a piglin fortress.
That guy is in trouble, he can't come back.
Did you conquer the Agri Fairy? Then there are 4 of you.
But somehow the losers seem lame.
So there are only two left in the chest.
It wasn't there, so I just raised the chest by 2.
I'm back, I see, I see, I worked hard
You worked really hard, that was really nice.
I wrote down the coordinates, so if you want to go, go.
Please cover me
But there's no fortress, just a normal nether fortress.
That's right, I didn't use a nether fortress.
Yes, it was a long way, but it wasn't there at all.
I was able to come back so long that I was dying
I'm glad I'm back after 20 years of sleep.
Because now
I don't look like a grandma, but a grandpa.
I'm becoming a grandpa.
It's amazing how you drew such a grim face.
Or like Golgo, like Golgo
It's becoming
That's a deep face. That's a deep face.
hand
No matter how you think about it, it will be written as Yabapa.
Yes, I lost my life right in front of my eyes.
I've experienced it and it seems like it's strong.
Rui Rui was killed right in front of me
What will happen to VG when Kara dies?
No, VG, that's it, it's heading for that soul.
It's going to break, it's going to break, it's going to break
That's why it becomes that God's gaze camera.
That's how you become a ghost, right?
That's true, that's true, that's true.
Peko-chan from If You Want to Come Back
[music]
That's my judgment too.Do you want to survive?
Yes, yes, yes, I will do it.
I guess it's true, but it's almost time.
What if it was in the second half instead of that?
I wonder if I won't be able to recover on the 7th day.
It seems impossible. Yes, on the last day, I'll go to Haruka.
It seems like you can only revive once. One time per person.
It seems like yes yes yes
Yes, no, I'm irritated, but I'm irritated.
The best part is when I'm building a bridge.
At first I was attacked by Gust and thought I was going to die.
I thought it was over already.
Yes, sorry, I said I was dead.
As I said, I'm dead, so I'm fully prepared.
Something came from behind too.
I just finished it
Thank you for your hard work. Did anyone show up too?
I went back and forth
Tatekimasashi
[music]
It's already the second time my friend has died.
No more
So, what did you go out to do?
It's better to come back and do a mission you won't forget.
I wonder if it's not for that purpose yet?
There was though
I came here and made it.
Tasa
Thank you very much.
What happened to the guy who defeated Gust?
It's my first time, and it's an item mission.
I have to take a picture of that one.
There is a commemorative photo spot
Please, please sleep in your bed.Yes, that's it.
I won't die, of course I don't know.
Good, good, let's go, let's go
Let's go, thank you
Mishi's Mission Mission That
I wonder if I can draw it too
Oh god hello hello hello hello oh god
Kaela God, that's God
God, God, God, oh God, go home!
Minecraft God
You don't have to sound like a god, huh?
Dorin Dorinkoli What Goli Drink Goli
Drink a
Medicine medicine drink medicine drink medicine drink yeah
Those who return home are the best at Japanese, aren't they?
That's right, nice nice Igo
This is a lie, it's like I'm going to take medicine, I'm going to take medicine
I have to take medicine for other games.
I feel like I had something to say.
I see. So I'll try my best to remember that.
That's what you gave me. Oh, that's wonderful.
After all, we are connected with Toa through medicine drinks.
I don't know anything about medicine like medicine drinks.
It seems to have a different meaning, but...
It's scary, isn't it? Wow, both of us are like that.
That's how it feels
I didn't think so, but that's what we both think.
Haha, I usually say yes, first of all this is this.
Whoa whoa whoa mission is this?
That's not a nether fortress, that's a piglin.
It's a fortress, so I guess it's written here.
So how do you cook with oil?
I don't know how to write, so please tell me how to write.
Hello Kochi
Thank you, Howaku
Is there a problem? It's okay.
I don't know if I've ever seen it or not, I have to take this once.
No, I want it, right?
I'll take this book
The virtue of
I need to get a book.
It was
But I'm going to write a little bit and go to my diary.
If I didn't, I would have gone somewhere with the money from the first one.
Listen, who took the book now?
I'm looking at this, so who's going to do it?
Then da
I heard the report earlier, so I understand who has it now.
Please leave it to me. I'm very well.
Hey, May, I see, I see, who is this?
What is this? I don't understand this.
It's too much to leave it at that.
How do you feel? No, this is the one who will be given wings.
Those who have been blessed with no platinum
Only the sound of the white rice is delicious.
Hey, what did you do?
Well, on the growth desk that will be clearly revealed
Narrow
Chau Glowstone Unku was good
Write
Now I can talk about things like
Mr. has grown up
Oh yeah, there's also an enchantment.
enchantment
If I try hard too, things like this will happen.
nice
3 Yoshisu-san
It's a little sad
I wonder if it's enchanted
Enchantment written in Enchantment 1
Kappari
It must be nice, the three of us together.
Because I just came here and I was enchanted.
Sasamori kake
This is the first time I've heard if it looks good.
Karane, yes, that seems like it, right?
As I wrote, both of us are doing that.
I'm flirting with you though.
I'm not flirting with you.
It's a little hard to work even if you do this.
It's true
What kind of skeleton is Umasuke?
Skeleton, that bow guy, the one throwing it, Toa
It's glowstone and ghast subjugation, isn't it?
Thank you and the attacker's Zencha Miakore
If it's 5 diamonds, go for Loluta.
Please write down the theory mission once per person.
I feel lonely because I was getting along well with everyone.
Chanchim's place suddenly had some amazing interpretations.
It's out, it's scary, it's scary
Scary, I wonder if it's okay to display it like this. Oh, if I put it back,
It's okay, I'm sorry, I borrowed a book.
Please be nice, I'm fine today.
It's just the right time, the leader is about to do it.
Let's do it. It's starting at 5 o'clock, right?
Yes, thank you, thank you for your hard work, thank you for your hard work.
tired
I'm surprised at how tired you are from seeing you again.
That's cool, thank you
Good night, thank you for your hard work.
Baba
Baba Kagari was quite shocking or surprising.
It just felt weird. I thought it was a bug.
It's simple and gives me a headache.
[music]
Taare deke
What a cool craftsman
Noisyajaki-chan yes this mission
What should I do with all the stuff I packed?
It's not a good name, just put it here.
Is that okay? I don't know, but I know more about it every day.
Kara-chan's locker is here
Well, there's something like a diamond here.
Once you clear the mission, the diamonds are here.
It's going to be placed here.
There's no West where I have it outside, no West where I don't have it.
I'll do it once here
The water is amazing. There's too much traffic.
The traffic jams are amazing! The force is like a typhoon.
It was so unbelievable. Now, who is it?
It's like we're sleeping together
This is the bed, this is the bed, let's all sleep together.
happy
[music]
Hey, people think we're good friends.
Wait, it's too bad
I wonder if it's okay. It's raining so I'll go to bed.
There's a sleeping pad over there on the bed.
I played around with the sound, but it's wrong. It's about the distribution.
I feel like I'm somewhere west.
Suko
Small, yes, yes, here.
It's okay to lower the price.
If I'm going to do something next, I'll probably use a stone or something.
It's necessary, oh, you need a stone with a hand, right?
stone
If you need a book, please get some.
That cobblestone that I got my hands on.
There is a manufacturing machine, but it looks a little ugly.
Excuse me, but I don't need it.
Ah, here it is, even here.
It's a little boring to dig for diamonds.
It's a bit like that in terms of the picture, isn't it?
Masu
Let's do something, okay? That's right.
do what you do do what you do
If there's nothing to do, it's over
No, let's have some Edra.
I'm going to the TT Tower. I'm going to the TT.
Let's go on a mission!
I've done it the times I haven't done it there.
Let's do a mission. That good frog can do it.
Even if you don't have any equipment, let's survive.
What I stopped doing
Don't try to cheat, don't try to cheat
Right, Solsan
Grown Kitetawa that
[music]
Run
Does anyone have a lot of rune stones?
If you ask someone what it is, they will tell you there are a lot of stones.
It's not a possibility, just ask
Is it okay to ask? I'm heading to TT.
Let's go, it's late, it's late, it's late.
I don't know where to go quickly, where is the TT Tower?
Niankakocchi
Why is that? No, that's not it.
It's a little off here.
I don't think there's anyone who's a sub now.
I can talk because I do things like that, but normally.
I'm a little nervous about going there.
Well, your belly is sticking out so much.
It's not a lip, it's the sky, it's here, bye
Bye bye, it's too easy.
The people who died in the Nether I want are smiling.
Masu
I'm going through that Nether.
Yeah, that's amazing. I'm here. Go to the bathroom.
Can I come now? Is it here now?
I'll have to wait a little longer until TT.
Hmm, ok, oh, oh, here and now, just a little bit.
It's dangerous so let's go to TT right here.
Don't do it, don't do it, don't go, stop it
I'll do it
That's what I'm doing with Tokoyami.
Idol
Well, she's an idol, but Toa...
A different type of idol than Aqua
Nen Attack Type Idol Attack Type That Ticket
Idols and sleeper-type idols
Ticket idols are like that these days.
I know it's quite a trend.
What do idols do?
Like how he uses manga material.
Yeah, I'll do it. I'll say what I think too.
That's what I say
That's a little talented, Chi no Chi's talent.
There's a certain number of people here.
Here, here, there's a stone.
There's a lot to talk about here.
It's so beautiful, it's a panda
Oh, there's a panda, nice Aeto-chan
catch a panda
I can't catch the panda.
Maybe Mikochi is playing the role of a teacher.
Good evening
This is cute today as well.
Hey, what's that?
My colleague
Senpai and Sui-chan are a little silly.
I wonder if Su-chan is cute today.
Today's show is so boring.
It's Chansu-chan. Can you count anything?
It seems unlikely
Now, I don't think I can do it because I don't know.
Chan
fake fake
Dada
Bye bye bye bye go to babakara's house
Come on, bye bye bye bye bye ka's house
Goku-chan and proper got it.
I want the infinite darkness, I want it a little
No, let's go, let's go, we
Please take a look at his masterpiece!
Subaru, Nene-chan, and I made it.
It looks like it's going to be hard. It's dead, so I made it.
Look, the sea is a bit different.
But here it is
Dadan
Wow amazing
Kukokukoyapasato is a little different.
Karasa's reaction is
Yes, you're already used to it, right?
The reaction was really good earlier.
I got a reaction.
You know, I don't like people who kind of agree with me in the Nether.
Nayone
After all, this character is cute
When I was told that
Wow that's amazing
Talk to a girl about not being able to do things like that.
So cute in winter
Nene-chan doesn't like that cute way.
That's why Sui-chan's somehow Sui
There's something like that, right? It's incredibly cold.
I'm cold so I need a response.
Tetowacha says something is fine.
I've pretty much ignored that. It's gone cold.
I'm sleepy
I'm here. My stomach isn't dead. I'm here.
I died making this. Yes, I died here.
I died. I think it was a courageous death.
I went to the toilet. You can come here.
I'll definitely go now for a bit.
I need to mute the VC first.
Hey, it's dangerous, so I'll ride it.
It's fun to ride, so give it a try
I want it
A little bit
Wait a minute
What should I do?
There's a lot of netherrack here.
I received
I'll go with this
What should we do?
What shall we do with you?
Listeners
Teru Mi
Thank you very much, I saw it.
Hello Tachan Tachan is in the toilet
I'm on my way.
Well,
Good things about Etta-chan
Ha, what's going on? I'm To-chan's.
When I go home, do you want tea or water?
He said, uh, my glass of water.
When it runs out, red tea is fine. Red water is fine.
That's where I always put that other person in.
Thank you very much
Masue isn't home yet, it's a bit late.
It's not too late, isn't it?
I don't have that much time, but...
Umm, something
Etota
Chanta-chan
of
The best part is
picture
Well,
Erm, erm
Well, you always talk about me in the studio.
When I see it, I can't help but grin.
I can't do that. Come early.
Something
I didn't mean anything bad at all.
The good thing about Shieto-chan who doesn't appear is from Kara.
It's true that you're so crooked.
I don't have time to think anymore, just like that
Teto-chan, are you grinning right now?
She's grinning. She's got a serious face. She's grinning.
Girugii
from
Grinning Dad
Chando-chan's face is grinning.
Are you in Yotosa?
Yes, it's an iron sword
this
Yeah, listen, what should I do?
This will explain that if you defeat this
It seems like you get experience points.
You will be able to enchant.
Is that so? Yes, that's right.
I have introduced this, so if you go below
That unfinished, unfinished thing of mine, just in case.
There are some cobblestone tools, it's amazing.
When can I go to pick up the cobblestones?
Well, I'll do it. I also have a cobblestone.
Okay, this and this are not cobblestones.
This, this, this, this, I can have this.
Oh wait, I have a big club.
Mission after defeating the mother skeleton
But Celtic this is it. If you defeat it now
It's the first one
It's tough, it's probably 3, so I'll defeat 3 of them.
It's good because I can go with
Please use this too, Na-chan.
Hey, are you being targeted? I wonder if you've lost your body?
It's over now. I'm going to sleep. What's going on?
Thank you now
He did a really good job until now.
I did a really good job today.
It was fun to sleep here
Can you sleep now?
I want to catch some zombies
I want to catch zombies
There's Loki
Oh, what's that flying thing called Loki?
It's Phantom. Phantom doesn't appear here.
Right?
The code will be fine next night.
[music]
I don't think it will come out.
Because I just slept in bed
No sleep
If only we were asleep
It's okay, come back, come back, come back.
I went to sleep, so I'm going to sleep.
It's so detailed because it appears in the places of people who don't have it.
This is dangerous, I'll go from here.
Oh, I'm surprised, Jato-chan
[music]
Wow, it was a bit lil, yeah, it was cool again.
I did it!
Where are you all? Here
Good chan
I'm trapped in a Piglin Fortress.
I didn't say I was locked up.
Tat
He said he slept with Guriyo.
I feel like I'm going to sleep with Nesakki Guriyo at 11pm
I don't want to talk to you, so let's go to Fortress Pikrin.
Hello everyone, I'm sorry
copper
Hello too
What are you doing right now while taking a walk and eating soul sand while taking a walk?
Is it from the Netherland to get it?
That's right, right? What's going on?
It's solidified, it's not solidified, what?
If something suddenly happens without a word
Please say yes thank you
What is this thing? This is the TT Tower.
Well, it's the TT Tower Trap Tower.
Please feel free to use it. You can go check it out.
Well, I really want you to go see it.
My grave is also there, so please take care of it.
I'm dying, I'm going to the grave
Well then, go away, are you going to come back now?
Yes, I'm going back tomorrow, I see.
I see, thank you for your hard work.
I feel so distant, it's okay
Yes, it's a honorific language, so it's better to use sahacha as a honorific language.
Kanato
There's a switch on, so it's like that.
Kototose's switch is on.
Thank you very much. I see.
Hey, that's how it went, okay.
Okay, bye bye, good luck
Are you trying hard? Yes, I understand.
Do you want to go to the Nether? Can you please let me go? Maru 1
teeth
oh there is also netherrack
There are a lot of them.
Tsuruha is not that, Tsuruha is also
I can make it, but there's still a lot left.
It's okay, let's go or go.
Are you going?
Where would you like to go next?
that
Well, what if this is Su-chan?
Yes, Sui-chan might be in the Nether.
There may be
Na
Let's listen to this one
Maybe it's okay
Zu-chan is joining us
I won't buy either Tamasui-chan or Zu-chan.
It's true, my friend, Azusa-chan, Ta-chans
Chanzu-chan came Azu-chan
now nether netza noe
The base is deep down.
[music]
What should I do about the pain?
I wonder how long it takes to write
Once
Ah, let's go back to that base for now.
Okay, let's do this.
Let's poop
There were a lot of Oguri fortresses.
I don't know which Piglin fortress this is.
do not have
Takashi
What is it?
Or what?
mosquito
What is it?
No, what is it?
Do you want to say nothing?
What is it?
mosquito
Or something.
We are together
Kanansukananka
Are you laughing all the time? It's the same if you don't talk
All I can say is, why and where are we going?
Let's go
I'm in a hurry, I'm in a hurry, I'm in a hurry, no, no, no.
No, no, no, I'm pissed off
A woman without a husband
Where are you going?
Where do you want to meet me?
No, no, no, no, no, no, I saw it.
I just saw it, so I can't stop it.
No FC or 832 FC right now.
883 It's quite deep, yeah, it's a little different.
I wonder how it got there
This way?
I don't know where to start.
Takahawa, this place is not dangerous, this place is dangerous, right?
After someone dug it, we thought we dug it.
Akocchi or door Sui-chan is here
Yeah, uhm
They're sending me the coordinates.
But there was a door around here, where was the entrance?
I wonder if there was a door, but I'll go back once.
Where did you come from? Wait a minute.
Come here
If you are not at the TTT gate, go here.
Not
[music]
Did you go all the way to poop? Come back.
That's the sweet thing I said before that I'd pick you up.
How was it?
590 Probably from this cat
It kind of looks like this.
I guess I don't remember it because it was a long road.
this this
The road is quite far, it's quite far
It said No Maina 832.
Minus 800 is quite far away.
Not Nakochi, I wonder if Waaki-chan is there too.
Aki-chan
If you can all go together, go.
I want to go and pick you up.
I don't know if it's not the cat, but it's here.
If you see a familiar road, this is it
Hey, it's Kanapo here, isn't it? It's almost time to go home.
Remember only the path of
Let's go here, let's go!
Please check
No, both of you, Achan and Tachan,
It's not over here. It's not over there.
Not over there, not over here
We're not going to TTT.
come back
So let's go from the non-TTT person.
Huh?
The signboard for Tama TT
Where was the trap tower I was going to pass?
The trap tower is this way.
It's here, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's here.
There's nothing here. There's nothing here.
Cat? I figured it out. I got it figured out.
Thanks for understanding
Thank you, I remembered this.
Thank you, thank you, Nether.
chan is lost
That's late, sorry Dash.
dash dash jump dash
I'm sorry for jumping, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It's this guy who's closing the door right now.
Is this guy really here?
I don't think so.
I'm hungry, but the negatives are fine.
Teru
Na
Minus Akocchi doesn't look like Kocchi
I think you can go if you go straight
But if I go to this door and go straight ahead,
It's not straight, it's straight
If you go, you'll probably be able to go to the coordinates.
That's right, this Roso is the basic one.
If you follow it, we will help you
Did the cat go upstairs?
I'm long
terrible
Oyayya
Hmm, I'll do the work here.
[music]
I'm coming around here too
Where is this place? We also come here and there.
It wasn't there
There's something that's been coming or not
A landmark
They've built quite a few big bridges, so it seems likely.
yes
Oh yeah
[music]
There is no line and it is a straight road.
picture
almost to death
yes
Are you here?
Oh road
But something happened
Yes, that's true.
[music]
There's no one left
Tae
Yeah, I'll open tomorrow, sorry.
I was surprised by the sudden acceleration.
It's just funny
that
There may be wild boar poop, so be careful.
Please understand
It's a pig, it's not a pig, it's a slime
It's not a pig, it's a pig
It's hot, it's hot, it's hot
I'm glad you came back.
It's Gagast, it's Gagast, please run away.
Where where
I can't see where
I'm looking for posepo
What are you going to do now?
I guess so
I wanted to find you, so go home!
I'm glad you're back, Sui-chan, you're back.
It's good, it's good, it's good, it's good
I thought I was going to die because it was cheap, but let's make a road.
I'm glad I did. It was really good. Honestly.
Good, it's a pretty beautiful road.
You can take as many magma cubes as you like around here.
It's an area where slime is springing up.
Oh, what happened to get to this point?
Yeah, it's like Stranger Things
Hey, Stranger Things
I don't know what else to say, it's so funny
I haven't watched the drama Seriously Stranger Thing
Su
What a really interesting foreign drama.
That walking that I've only seen before
Dead, yeah, walking dead
Wasn't it a very long series?
Oh yeah, just watch season 1
It was so hard that I quit.
In what sense is that person already
I'm going to die soon, so my spirit is gone.
Ah, thank you, thank you Baba-chan
Noarabye
Bye, he didn't say anything even once.
I walk away without looking back even once
big back
Where did it come from?
I was looking for something, but I just discovered a nice forest.
Oh, what is that distorted mushroom?
That's okay because there was a mission like that.
I didn't put it anywhere near my bed.
There was a red forest. Oh, there was a red forest.
Where did you go from that big place?
I don't remember, I'm against it, I'll go back to this once.
I have to, I can't go back.
It's different in the first place, maybe even if I go this way.
It's a shame there's no fortress.
It's probably not really close.
Ae-chan is alive
Teru
[music]
I thought he was definitely dead, but I thought he was dead too.
I'm not even alive as I thought, so what's going on?
Collision here and there
What are you doing in front of me? It's so close.
That's because I was wearing shoes in a falling position.
Rinse it, it's great
Tayame
hand
I was really surprised, it's really interesting.
That's good
I thought it was going to end here, but I'm done with it.
We just happened to meet each other
It would be a miracle if we just met
I laughed about the miracle, but even if I died,
It would be dangerous if it happened, right? You'd laugh out loud.
Even though I got lost when I went to pick you up, I came to pick you up.
It's so sad that we finally met each other but died outside the stream.
It's true that all three of us are there.
Let's do it
Hido-chan and Luna-chan
Hello Terun
I'll look for it
There aren't any
Hey, that's the voice
nice nice nice
There is
ray
I can't pick up Nice Gust's tears, I have to understand.
You can't do it.
It wasn't on this side, but it could have been that.
I'm drowning
Isn't it Kokocchi?
That wasn't it
I'm too scared here and there, don't worry, I'll go home
I'm going back to Popo, where is Popo? Thank you for your hard work.
If so, thank you for your hard work.This is the book.This is the book.
What's this? Dad just came over here.
This is it, this is it, this is the wrong dog.
There's no rap, I wonder which one is it?
1 time
Sakocchi's Sae is here.
It's this way, it's this way, it's this way
Books
That's it
Oh no
Ndoko
I guess I'll go look for it.
But that's not it, if TT came.
I tried looking for the opposite one, and it certainly worked.
I don't think it was the TT one.
It seems like Toa and the others were digging that place.
oh yeah
Yeah, I'll give you a little bit.
Everyone, it's a little big at first.
I feel small, so if there's a small person,
please tell me
[music]
Ekocchi?
No, it's not this one, it's not, which one is it?
I think it was like this and that.
But not this one
Where did that go?
Here, there, it's open, it's here, it's not here
Ah, it's here. Is it here?
Here it is here
Oh, it's full of holes
It's true, this is the street I passed by.
It's seriously small, it's seriously small
Because I'm making myself go
Seriously, seriously, seriously, seriously, seriously, seriously
Seriously
Chii me remix remix
Version Seriously Seriously Seriously Seriously
Chii Maji Majima
[music]
What happened to Chiato-chan?
Listen to the seriously cautionary remix, don't listen to it.
Maybe it's too far away to hear
No, no, this is a waste, I want to hear it
I'm doing it because I'm streaming it.
If you don't pick up her voice, please stream it.
Seriously, there isn't.
Oh, be careful, artist!
It's a remix
Awesome, this is the next Balikaa Magma Cube
Yeah, let's kill him, kill him, whatever, whatever
I'll make a potion of "I'd rather kill you"
It's probably going to be a saka potion.
Let's go to the potion!
Doing this and that is good for division, but the number of divisions has increased.
The division is too creepy, the magma has increased and died.
I can order cream or not.
I guess it's no good if I try.
I guess it was a mistake, so I can't bring anything.
Is this the one you got?
Yeah, let's go or something.
Can I have this for you?
I need a block, so thank you.
Right, I'm not a bastard, that's why
I'm grateful for that
Probably not.
Oh, don't be too careful. It's scary now.
You'll look like Sui-chan, so be careful.
There's a hole around here
Hole okay
It's okay, it's okay
From behind after Toa stepped on it earlier.
Sei-chan had a blast, so wow
The moment A caught his attention, his eyes flashed.
I was worried about this before.
There's a pine tree that's not cheap.
That's it
There's really no door in here, Matsu.
I just put it there, not this one.
I feel like Taeko is back here.He's back.
This goes down and goes up
is
Yeah, I feel like I'm back. Why?
what
So it's nothing
Oh, but let's move on.
do not have
If I go this way to the left, something will happen.
Let's go left Let's go left
Okay, let's mark it.
Be careful, it's like falling into a hole.
Kiijiri
Boi
Ah, I'll connect here.
or connect
I'm going to see
Or this or that?
Thank you for your support
Let's buy this and that with the ice axe
I can get it
The lie I just went over here
Liar, lie
I don't really understand what you're saying though.
This is how I'll do it for now
You're wrong, just say it if you think I'm stupid.
hand
That's wrong
I wanted to tell you that it's a lie because it's a joke.
Yo, don't keep your distance, don't keep your distance
Well, I just installed it right now, so it's quick.
The feeling is short, the feeling is so bad, I'm sorry.
Sorry nee-chan
I haven't heard it, I haven't heard it, I'm interested.
There isn't.
It's okay if it's one more road or not.
It's going to be pretty, it's going to be pretty
The main road is even safer.
Yeah okay
Thank you for placing Yoshimatsu.
Someone wants to dig
There's no way I'm here. I'm not here.
And then I arrived at the Red Forest.
Red Monja