[Music]
do
so
[Music]
do
hello
oh
the discord isn't even picking up like
noises i swear immediately i swear
i remembered
hello
next to you mermaid
[Music]
we don't talk
yeah that guy
that guy yeah
i mean i'm sure there's a lot of
movement among the human a lot of women
oh
men um
honey oh i see i see what you're saying
there's moo men among the who men
i don't i don't know what you think i'm
saying but
perhaps some women but most but they're
who yeah
ah i think i see what you're saying
maybe
i think
possibly
yes sorry guys that were late um
everything
was uh a little bit of pain in the butt
literally every application we are using
right now caused some type of issue
yes but now it seems to be working and
actually one one problem was caused by
this game where we were in the if you
would think it's there right in the
online the online
thingy and then we go into a room and
then it's like okay but what now and
then you realize about a million years
later
you don't continue there you go out of
that screen
and then probably
we gotta go to play yeah we haven't
actually tested it yet we are assuming
we press play now
and that will start the game that is the
assumption yes that is oh i hope so
i think so
i checked and told senpai's stream so
yeah it's been a while moment since we
played something together like
one-on-one the last one was minecraft i
know how long ago was that
that was your first collab meme
oh my that would have been done like six
months ago right yeah
it feels even longer than that i feel
like um time zones make it dumb
and and the the thing that we built the
shrine it was so popular in may it was
yes
it was everybody went there everybody
got their fortune wasn't that one
yes it was super cute
thank you very much
the most used attraction in that whole
square it's probably the one of the most
interactive
yeah yeah
so we built something great yes top top
visitations
on the halloween server yes
because of you i can say i contributed
and helped build something because
that's all i said yes yes yes
oh my gosh
minecraft today actually this game right
now i remember remember this game uh
maybe you remember two mommy i wanted us
to play this as our actual first collab
yes
but
couldn't back then
because we couldn't and now suddenly we
can so finally we're playing kiwis
i remember oh my gosh you're right you
did ask for this one first
in the beginning i was like look
roommate this game is coming out or it
just came out or yeah i think it was
about to come out yeah yeah i was like
my mum
oh i hope i hope this is all we have to
do we're ready to play oh look at us
yes i forgot who's who but
oh you know what you decided or do i i
think i i just pressed start
an introduction to the telegraph
basics
here on the telegraph let me make sure i
might screw this over a little bit
actually because i keep on looking over
yeah it's a bit a little scuffed right
now we're also covering this green
so
so already i'm going to ask that you all
look away for a second
look away guys look away do not perceive
um
couldn't make us when roommate tells you
to look away you better look away she's
a scary girl i'm fixing us yes
yes you better pick me up you better
don't don't
let my mod my mod
uh
persona kick in okay
you were there for that
you were so freaking me out moment
i really wanted to um
um backseat you so bad
actually i think i needed some back
seating because i kept leaving her on
red and she kept leaving me it was
so frustrating
very painful memories thanks for the
memories even though they weren't so
great
she tastes like you only sweeter yes
you sounds like an edgy enough song for
you to sing and karaoke thanks
thanks for the memories thank you
memories
oh loud boy let's go fall out boy
almost fixed us i'm so close is it
taking so long because you're right now
in the chat deleting all those messages
because i see a lot of message delays
that's um
don't worry don't don't focus on the
stream okay don't focus on the chat stop
deleting messages stop it could you do
me a favor sorry i'm not trying to mod
you right now could you look to your
could you look to the left a bit
okay i think
i think we are set
almost oh my god we're covering the
screen
oh my gosh
nummy is trying her best the pros and
the cons of overlays am i right all
right i think i fixed us
i love your overlay though it's so nice
i love it too i just i'm bad at managing
it i wish we could stack
all right but hi
hi
i'm just looking at the youtube screen
right now but
just because he looks gets in the way we
will you have to press start movement
you're right
wait but i did
[Music]
i would like to play this please
nope i also press start why is it so
weird an introduction to take up desk
space get ready to use your butts i'm
ready to use my butt
this says waiting for a response on the
bottom right and for you it says i want
to start a shift right
no
wait oh wait yes it says
what oh my okay i see i see you okay
oh let's go
okay
there we go we're figuring out this game
in real time no problem yeah all right
so an introduction to telegraph desk
basics are we going through the tutorial
together
yeah i'm ready to use my butt are you
i'm gonna die okay okay when i read this
read it oh
um let's start you off with what kind of
person i won't worry about right now
let's start you off with sending some
messages on the telegraph machine we
call her juliet be gentle with her she
said she's a genuine telepost antique
oh very gentle
well you are gonna roast like what kind
of person uses a telegrapher weren't you
[Laughter]
[Music]
have to activate and and and okay
everything oh is that it apparently
oh you might impress anything
he was done talking to us in all right
we do oh we need to type need is that it
shift
is coming one word at a time better type
oh we have to type that
i'm trying
excuse me am i not pressing
n are you pressing out
no you shouldn't be pressing again you
should be pressing down i think or
you're not ending but
maybe i'm a little confused
what what letter are you on
oh wait you just need to activate that
thingy oh okay
and then that thingy press shift on it
oh my gosh
oh okay okay oh it's capitalized now
it's
you capitalized the end now please i'm
pressing n
or do i have to
press it yet
dammit that's wrong
we're failing on the kind of
time no don't jump don't just jump dude
press the down button on the arrow
button down
there we go
all right and now we need where the e's
oh the e's are up here
[Music]
more i see it i see more
more and then over here
is the all right
go mumma get the o yeah
parkour it's like popcorn there's like
parkour where's r there's r where's the
r where's the r maybe actually oh i see
it's over here this way oh can i do it i
can do it don't worry
i got it more and okay i'll get this one
can we fall down oh yes oh dear oh
that's so cute
thank you
oh my gosh we're adorable
we have no arms
i need more bangles is what they're
trying to say oh wait yeah we have no
arms
dude i don't know much about kiwis do
kiwis get bigger than this
i don't believe they do
we have the g
i don't think they get bigger they're
pretty small
lily moment you're you're supposed to be
knowledgeable but i don't know if i
trust your knowledge here oh no oh chad
says nope okay well then i should have
trusted you quite small don't they
burrow where should they burrow where's
the s oh got it what's
burling like
i pressed it
it's the same time oh one three two one
nice yeah oh my gosh our beaks are so
they're so pointy
ready for watch wait i love those long
pointy ones incoming message shift
bonnets okay so shift yeah
i have obama
yeah yeah there's more stuff in your
territory right now yeah and then
oh wait it was capitalized it doesn't
matter
they have large eggs well we lose points
oh no
oh they're backspace
they're backside
this backspace
oh i am
so cute
this is actually so cute
and i was wondering why they're not
using their beaks there we go
okay bonnet
you
[Applause]
[Music]
okay i got the b
back back back
i think i believe it's back in style
yeah
it was a difficult beginning but yes now
it's so simple
yes it's so cool i hope there won't be
oh wait there is a there is a timer on
the top right but i guess it's oh it's
not counting on yet
it looks stuck yeah oh at the same time
okay three two one
they're very forgivable i forget they're
for you the thing maybe
swallowed
oh okay
that's also a bird can i come over oh
[\h__\h] that didn't work i can come to your
side i just realized
yeah but oh that didn't work i had to
capitalize it yeah
yeah i i capital please
nice
okay
um
and an a
double l please
double
o
oh
w i has and i has cheeseburger and i has
an e and i have this one
nice
nice nice next one please hey
hey ah oh next one please
above
you
what kind of bread
g
d g okay oh together that's the message
that's all okay
gg
nice oh my goodness
a lot of messages
okay who are we even sending these to i
don't know did they tell us and we just
we're paying attention
are we sending it to juliet
actually it was the name
i thought that was the name of this
machine
where is the oh i know we're looking for
the d okay okay there we go
avoid the
uh
[Music]
yeah
we're so fast
speed speed yes um actually i'm
eh yellow i got you i gotcha i i used to
run marathons you know did you
not really although when i was younger i
did enjoy it
but you forgot to eat
yes yes and now now you can go
government marathons when you were
younger
i mean maybe
i joined one but i as a child
but but yeah i did enjoy running but
preference you you do have a preference
i do have a preference
do you have a
anti-preference hmm
let me think about that
i don't think these are good wait where
are we
so good
what what berries are yellow i can't
actually think of any right now
oh [\h__\h] indeed indeed there's only one
yellow berry that i can think of that is
edible
which one but i forgot the name it's the
one the one with the two leaves
sticking out of it that people that
restaurants like to use as a as a
decoration i think you know you're
talking about oops yeah
oh is that one called oh it's
but we're talking about not not we're
talking about culinary berries or
someone is a gooseberry is that
is that the english name for gooseberry
i honestly don't know i know
gooseberries are a thing i don't know oh
yes yes that's the one i meant
yeah
i guess yeah it does come up it does
show me on youtube the right one oh we
were
fine we were so slow were we
you know what we'll just get faster
because we took a lot to learn
oh
well we got some stamps
okay that was the tutorial well we can
be faster we were chatting on the side
exactly chitchat learning the basics
all right how do we
wait okay oh
you want to play a shift i want to play
let's do it the transcription room oh my
goodness
here we transcribe customers recorded
messages onto paper for them then we
send them out for a speedy delivery by a
member of the cassowary career team
don't let them hassle yeah they're all
talk
a hack
the big burps the blue ones
they were
what
do you still want to do the tutorial
um we should probably should no it
probably should
they look like dinosaurs
they look so happy
they creep me out i really like them are
they our enemies
i think they might disturb us they're
friends
pop that bad boy into the stereo okay
music no message real
there we go
oh we gotta get back up i'll go get it
i'll go get it
happy
now create the message if you forget it
you guys
play hit again
okay so okay oh that's cute okay
what is it like that you stick to my
butt
oh my gosh you're there with your blood
do i press it try to find
a py
wait i'm trying to there's the py it's
down there oh but we place it here i see
so it's on there
oh it's on our butt
it is so cute
happy birthday mom or what was it
birthday yeah happy birthday mom where's
the bird there's the birth
you see the birth all right i'll look
for the day
okay hey
there's the day
you got it oh i died no i didn't die i'm
okay what no
mommy no you're not a phoenix be careful
i'm just i'm a simple i'm a humble kiwi
really mom oh yeah mommy's here mommy
mommy
kiwi mommy
why do we fly so high
uh
okay discord ping don't do us dirty
three two one
i did it a little early
nice hot mail ready for delivery pick it
up
oh my gosh end up disturbing us at all
oh but what's that there's fairies
we have to jump up here what what do i
do we can ride them
that's cute but what
oh we have to put treats in the bowl
oh
look at that berries
oh man oh one found me maybe one person
does this
is that it a lot of melon there oh there
oh
really
one and was there a time limit would
kind of be faster
maybe one of us get berries
why is it taking me so long to pick it
up
it almost took me with them i saw that
that's how it's done are you ready for
the actual round oh gosh
okay give me i got the thingy
go get the message we have a job to do
all right what's the message gotta
deliver those messages
uh oh yeah play it play
pizza
for rent okay i have a duh
uh maybe you can try the pizza
pee pee pee pee pee they're up here up
here oh there it is i see it pizza and i
saw the oven too
pizza
[Music]
wait does it need to be capital no okay
ah i have to just because i have it's
because i have the it has to be an order
pizza and an oven and rent
i got four
yeah
eating pizza out of like a proper pizza
oven i don't think
you were so forgiving before three two
one
i'll do it when you say two
okay three two
one nine
i'll take this here
oh okay i'll go get him you wanna do the
berries this time
yes yes yes all right
let me tell you my my uh one of my
friends
got themselves a pizza oven
and
when you put the pizza in it's done in
like 30 seconds for real
yeah whoa because it's so hot it's done
immediately but it's also so perfect
kazoo recital tonight okay i didn't know
i thought because i didn't know it was
that fast
i thought i found the wreck
recital oh this idol is up here
get it
tonight
there's an eight i see
a ton right there to your right
here oh to the right my right ah oh i
didn't see it
okay
did it all right nice count down
wait because it is is is uh wait who was
playing the kazoo in the whole life
someone was playing with a kazoo before
i remember that like multiple people
played because this
yeah callie kelly yeah i think i'm
thinking i'm calling oh she's having her
is that a recital tonight
yo
oh
let's all go oh my gosh actually though
i'd love for kelly just have a straight
up recital kazoo recital of it awesome
look at the time oh no three two one
oh gosh you don't work outside three
two one
i mean i'll jump at one you jump at two
yes i'll do two three two
one
oh so silly
oh okay okay yeah we gotta do another
one i'll get the berries again all right
look at the berries
berries because if you do it then you're
gonna eat them right it's very tempting
i hesitate too much
all right
message
i'll push this button looking forward
partner
oh that's sorry that was my message
sorry
are you
yeah sorry that was my message oh
uh in
four i see the four and the part
four
oh yeah
oh my god i have to do it like
right after you say two
that
you do the seems
buckle buckle them seat belts i buckle
yeah safety first
bye bye
goodbye
oh no welcome back
man just trying to get a break oh this
is strawberry it's so cute
look we took less time to do this one
we are yeah we are excelling
think nice
we still only got five though we're
still bad but okay
okay don't worry about it this is fun i
like this game it's cute
super cute
number three let's go
i think at this pace we might be able to
do the whole game today oh
is it only this these three weeks i
think i think i think so there isn't dlc
though i saw it on steam
for a sequel
chad you girls are fun too
you girls are cute too your chat is so
nice mommy yeah yeah chat you girls are
cute too
cute oh yeah i'm sorry i was supposed to
play press few okay don't worry
lay
so cute yeah
okay so adorable
oh you want to read this one shipping
floor uh he's going to repeat it anyway
oh i did not see it i pressed enter too
fast maybe
okay down here on the shipping plate we
process packages and parcels if it's
bigger than an envelope you can bet
it'll pass through here
oh okay okay
all right incoming package
yes
oh there wait oh is that bowling
wait dog hefty babies brought me looking
dude okay it's just a message we don't
care i'm just kidding uh the customer
notes will tell you where it's headed
look for the keyword to help you choose
the right packing sticker
this is important you gotta worry this
painted cliffs
oh
check the map for the postal code and
use the typewriter to type it out you
can run up to the item if you need to
reread the note no no no no this is a
hefty baby bro
a location painted cliffs okay and then
what do we do
and then they're here on the map it says
six six two four free so we gotta type
six two
four
oh you three pick it up put it on the
bowling ball i think yeah oh the crate
on the crate
oh gosh oh gosh stick there pick up the
knife i pick up the stickers slap it on
the lid i'm trying to pick it up there
we go oh down i see
of course i see ice
on the lid i got it
who's this for
jump on the crane
what oh gosh pick up
huh oh
use the crane to pick up the little okay
i'm gonna pick up this this thing wait
how do you move it
i would say
we both have to use it at the same time
oh is that it
right
are you
um
oh
pick up blizz what huh i have picked up
but i'm trying to move it it says up
the up button huh oh
what oh
that's weird yeah it looks like yours
would be yours yours is up down mine is
right left yeah
it's weird
oh we have to put the lid on it how
about how do you do that i thought you
were supposed is this what you used to
put the lid on it
yeah
i mean
i think
huh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
i can enter the crane but like
it huh
burp brains let's go brains where brains
unite work together
huh
help us
do what happens if you press up mama
this happens
yeah
do we have to eat it
if i press up i can only press it down
but left the right does oh wait oh it's
swift w a is steve
is it
oh
let's go we're gonna press s right now i
press
you should have told
okay and now
we pick it up and we go
oh
uh i think a little bit more down a
little bit when did i die what
oh you walked down the table oh oopsie
yeah
what
attach let's do we both have to push it
do we
oh oh wait what do we did we go too low
can you go up a little bit
every time i try it makes me leave
oh that's so weird
all right there we go we figured it out
finally switch the conveyor track to
send that crate to the north or south
the pole check the map if you're not
sure which oh no
so you know your maps this is south
right
yes
hit that send button hold that track
lever in what a track lover track lover
a track lover track lover the travel
lover
track lover
the track all right now the game is only
showing us the send button hmm
is there a lover
ah one of us has to hold down the cell
phone ah because it goes back out okay
i'll go get it
oh now you can place it
okay that took us a while i thought it
was like a dial phone where it just
comes back
okay
[Music]
real deal now what's the first thing we
do
we're gonna pack uh
yeah
all right and then i
get it excuse me there we go all right
yeah we need some bubble bubble wrap too
though for that one it will break
otherwise
yo put it on oh there we go
i ran a bit extra now
all right and we have to use the
wait oh my gosh what now oh my god
hello heavy heavy heavy it's heavy we
just had to go is it riddling it's here
i grabbed that it's nothing
oh wait is it heavy oh it might not have
been
oh oh there's also parachutes right
there's a perishable oh no
i think it might be fragile to be honest
can i not check again
i can't check it is
handle with care handle it yeah okay so
fragile i don't think that means red
jelly okay i got the fragile though that
goes on the on the lid here
okay okay
i also used to be very fragile as a
teenager you know oh
yes life life was really tough man oh
i thought you meant yet
you had frail bones
no no just saying edgy i was edgy edgy i
was pretty edgy too i was an edgy
teenager
uh wait what else oh i think you do the
cream i'll move it okay okay okay
oh it has a little our feet signs on
there to step on there i didn't know
this
that's cute okay all right
we can do this uh
so i go down
one noise
and then oh wait a little more to the
there you go yeah there we go
nice with me
oh you got this oh oh nice
all right
and it's supposed to go
to the tree
okay hold it hold it nice pulling and
holding it holding it to normal
bye-bye good one
new lid a new one new one a new one
let's see we found this in a storm drain
we thought you know what
lick lake busy two two four one all
right i'm on it okay did you see if it
was fragile oh
oh [\h__\h] no i didn't i'll check i'll
check i'll check don't worry
i'll check
you'll check
yeah
you're just getting it in the water
yeah back in the water
what even was it
what handle with carrot says
okay
um
oh is it
animal does that mean it's perishable if
it's a live animal
thanks no
i think so i think that makes sense wait
chad said urgent oh there's an urgent
one
oh there's an urgent one here we didn't
even see it oh okay
well then okay maybe that's the one i
mean a perishable would not be wrong so
hmm
all right i didn't say food i didn't
look what it actually it said live
animal
oh what really yeah
oh dear okay um
bit more higher like up up i see the
shadow there we go
let's go
[Music]
there it is
there we go all right one more one more
oh [\h__\h] uh where was it going
uh lake bessie so no one right all right
[Music]
i guess if it's just like small
animals like snakes maybe they get scent
like that i think yeah i think you can
sh there's some animals you can ship
this one is perishable here's a salty
flat it's perishable okay
oh
my god my pineapple on pizza yes or no i
will i will deal with it i don't mind it
but i won't ask for it how about you
yes definitely yes and also i will say
pineapple on burger also very much yes
oh that's interesting oh i like a shirt
uh what would you call like i think i
know how you mean to slice
it yeah like a slice yeah a slice yeah
on top of like i think it's usually it
should be beef um it's a it's a hawaii
burger it's really good oh that does
sound good actually
it is i like me i like um or i've had
uh chicken with pineapple pineapple
chicken and that's also good yes yes yes
actually at kfc we would have a
pineapple burger it's called the phoenix
burger oh
yummy yummy yeah
it's kind of like best and south wait no
oh
it's very refreshing
refreshing taste
well done
great job great job
oh my gosh
thank you thank you thank you ina
we did it
how long did this one take oh you know
what it was okay not too bad oh oh but i
just realized
now there's like silver and bronze and
gold on that timer thingy huh we were
not that far from silver and it's our
first time it's okay it's our first time
we were talking about pineapples yeah
important topics yeah i'll just try i
almost done with our first week mermaid
oh my goodness our first week does it
start to get harder is this how they
lure you in they make the first week
seems easy it might be more straight
yeah and then it gets harder and harder
and you're just stuck slowly that's zoey
zoey
zoey in the bathtub oh so zoey in the
bathtub
wow
oh my [\h__\h]
she's nice dropper depot we process all
the incoming and outcoming mail oh okay
you'll be working with zoe our head
administrator she's great at
multitasking i bet i am not
multitasking
hold on molly
send that letter up
pick up okay pick this up and do what
send that letter all right
and push the package into the correct
card be sure to check the labels
okay
oh what's up i guess
what
send that letter up the correct sorting
tube
ah
it should go through
yeah because it's blue okay
and push the package into the correct
card chirp we sure tripped over my head
and then push south
i pushed it oh you did push it i know
down there oh i pushed it up but i
shouldn't have pushed it up okay i'll go
again
you go there
you go there okay
looks like they're picking themselves up
too first let's get window one their
package window one uh-huh
pool oh
[Music]
why don't you hop on the rotoscope oh i
find the right one
oh my god how
galvez better pick up for hell that was
yeah yeah yeah yeah all right uh
oh i can i can read the small ones i
don't need the roloscope oh you don't i
see him yeah
this one yeah oh
pick it up i see that goes out
about
helping a customer we did it
cute
other folks might be more demanding so
stay on your toes i'll leave you on
zoey's eight what eight cap capable what
toes are you ready for the cares holy
moly no no no what do we do first
under the north north goes north maybe
no no no
but these two maybe
oh can you not move both
okay no too heavy oopsie i'll damn it
and north
come on
and then you got it
okay okay one job done all right uh move
this one that way
okay
go get the package
all right what about
what is this um
oh okay this is for belle b elbe
that's not that's not new zealand accent
don't mind me uh oh you have to chirp it
it makes you want you to like press
oops i died again
does that give us minus points i hope
not i hope not
now
early hugo
actually my very very very very very
first cat uh was called hugo oh really
that's a good name
i forgot about this thing
but it was a baby cat and um when we
adopted it it was already sick and then
it died like the in the first couple
weeks i think the first two weeks or so
and i was so sad i was a small little
child and i was so sad about them
a baby cat from a farm
[Music]
and i cried so much
oh
sometimes
thank you yeah baby kitties don't always
make it
you know especially because like when
you adopt them from a farm they often
have like uh like those
those cat um
um illnesses that you can't yeah
yeah yeah
oh we're working so hard
i'm getting a little distracted but yes
all right who wants to hire us chad do
you guys want to hire us
yeah we're pretty good wanna hire us oh
painted cliffs
gum tree bro okay
and popkins franklin
i got him oh my god
gosh these are great names
are those not realistic names
i think i mean
i've never read a popkins before
oh by the way i wanted to ask kiwizar
typical for new zealand right yeah i'm
pretty sure they're native to new
zealand
let's get those letters all right i keep
trying to jump the other way
let's see
yes yes
i only hire ostriches i've i've ridden
an ostrich before when i was small
really yeah have you ever been in an
ostrich i've never ridden an ostrich
before
what
it was during a vacation but that was
like a million years ago i think it's
it's like it's one of those touristy
things like like riding on a on a camel
or so but i don't know
like the worst thing is i think riding
in the elephant because they don't treat
the elephants right i've i've heard
about that
german for austria and it sounds like
austria
we can send so many letters is that
repaid and stamps
so we can send letters to our family
asking them to pick us up really um
maybe one day they're worth a lot of
those stumps
right
yeah if if only we keep them for 50 60
years then they might be worth something
right
we could retire maybe in 50 60 years
with our stamps
we're on week two
we're going to congratulations movement
oh my goodness
wonders so now so it looks like we got
all the basics now
yeah right so now we're doing the
lighter one again oh dear there's male
flies okay
what what are these male flies they love
the taste of the sweet gum glue we use
and they make their nuts out of paper
they must be from mischief they'll test
your concentration oh no
oh no
no
oh they look very annoying already no no
i saw someone in the chat said when i
said it was easy someone said it was
going to get much much more difficult so
oh gosh they're buzzing
they're buzzing from male flies to
scatter them okay
oh we run around a lot and surround you
okay
and wiggle to break free
okay wiggle how do we wiggle you wiggle
maybe you'll tell us like maybe we tap a
button okay
[Music]
this game found a pretty cool run i
found a pretty cool rocket pretty foul
you have the founder
where is that where's the o where's the
oh
[Music]
did they steal it i moved them always i
see cool i see the cool one you see
where am i where am i let me go let me
go
pretty where are you
where are you where are you hello oh
there you are there you are
oh thank you for pressing it bug we we
were hit
cool
don't steal it don't wait all right
let's go we gotta do the we gotta do the
latency okay three two oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
whatever that animal is nice yeah oh my
gosh there's so many
uh
some spray wait uh all right i got it
there must be another spray here come on
sprained my dang tails sprained
how did you sprang you sprained your
tail oh i see the spring
i see it
i got it sprained right
my dang tail where's the mine i have oh
mine is up there at the very top it's
red i'll get it i have to delete this
you protect the letters
my mine okay spring and then tail will
be right here
okay i'll go one thing about it
there you go all right
three two five oh no
i've been taken
based on you
three
two
one that's kiwi napping
you cannot allow that oh why you better
not
oh you better not smoke
air snake snakes
yes
there's more and more i swear they're
they're they're increasing
one more we can do it moment is there
one more all right we got this
what's the message this time the
important dimensions out here
gullible investors want to invest
[Music]
oh my gosh i cannot jump yeah
[Applause]
sorry i think i think mommy would be a
good gullible investor no mommy and
tutorial
okay all right no no no no don't you
think about it three two one
[Music]
eat it
we deserve silver for that we were so
close
we got brown
that's okay
really
okay look at how close we were moving
how close were we can you see how close
we are yeah yeah we were like one
millimeter away from it look at that
look at the arrow
[Music]
2.77 seconds apparently oh my god okay
two seconds that means we have to redo
it i'm just kidding
all right ready for this one
uh we're sending messages again oh
what's that what was that i don't even
the first one that we learned very first
one actually we're gonna type the
message um
oh right let me type it oh it felt so
recent not so long ago
are there no flies this time
is that oh type the decoded message
blanked out spaces will be one of those
letters now we have to guess
what oh we have to guess it's like that
game show i forgot about the game check
the swap list that e might really be an
o
what
oh that is confusing we have no enemies
but we have these
these
things messing with our brains oh gosh
uh all right
uh well
what first okay first thing let's do
shift and i see the p
oh yeah okay we gotta start with that
p
oh
we actually that was uh that was capital
as well or apparently it shouldn't have
been capitalized one yeah
okay
[Music]
okay that's my guess are we right
oh we might not be right
oh please more more more please more
maybe more move
ah
how would we know i don't think we can
now
where even is oh
oh we need the m first
okay i'm thinking too much
does it does it do something if it's
wrong
[Music]
let's see maybe we can test it so it
could it could also be meat it could be
meat
meat do you want to try it press the e
real quick
yeah i don't even see an oh am i blind
oh it does tell you if it's wrong
oh no
so it's meat okay that was a t he's up
here
ah oh okay didn't see it oh it tells us
me
here
uh nice night at night
um what you doing it's not nice not a
little bit too late to be out
past curfew at
what else
[Music]
all right
i forgot
break my mind mommy come on read my mind
i'm doing the opposite
i did it
new message
oh we have to switch them
so what does that mean
f and s and e are switched between b and
v so
oh yeah shift okay so i'll do l
so
y it's actually e
i think oh so should i type the e yeah
and then a
z
a
and s v so leave it's probably leave
leave
ah
um
[Music]
e
oh
[Music]
yeah you've been disconnected
my entire internet
woman
oh god hello woman can you hear me i
hear you can you hear me
yeah
my internet completely disconnected
everything
nice nice let me try to join i don't
think you have a room the the room open
you know what i mean though
okay i'm going to see if my am i back
are we back hello
yeah yeah it looks it looks like i'm
back hi my internet totally died one
second
no problem no problem all right i'm
gonna retrieve piana
oh oh gosh
oh my god
my mom is watching the stream
um and she just saved me
a picture of me as a child
on an ostrich oh my gosh
how the hell
did you get that picture that's she has
it on standby that's so cute apparently
i'm like i don't even know where all my
children's pictures are oh
and the ostrich i will send you the
picture later movie it was so cute
the oscar has this huge smile it's like
laughing into the camera like literally
i'm not looking into the camera but the
oscars the ostrich knows
that's so cute i want to see you please
hello
that is so cute you guys hello mommy
she watches my streams quite often hello
mama phoenix hello what about does your
family watch your streams
they don't know what i do
oh wait did you tell me that before i
don't think i've told you that
oh
i don't mention it they will be very
confused
and they don't know at all wow okay
i just say i say i'm a s
i'm a streamer you see
how can you hide it forever like
did i know you're a streamer and just
not what kind of streamer
they don't even really know what
streaming is i think honestly
wouldn't they be wondering like how the
hell their daughter is making money yes
but it's simply yes they do one day
that's i mean i didn't immediately tell
my family either but but
but
my impressed you kept it a secret by the
way the card for the room i i sent you
again yes please oh right yes
it's the same room though oh let me uh
okay let me hide the game first
sorry guys okay oh hi
so i'm a legitimate businesswoman i uh
mother owl has an idea but i've never
shown her
anything
is it that's how it is
all right online
i'm gonna join the room again
there you could you could say you are a
moderator for uh youtube chats
i can't say that i could say moderate
youtube chats do i not
you do a great job at it too thank you
okay i think you're back in the room i
think so
oh yes you want to play shift hell yeah
let's play a shift let's do this oh i
might have made us too big we were so
far with the message man
you're right we didn't finish it didn't
we
oh my gosh
is it the same words i wonder
that'd be nice
if it were if it is the same
we're gonna have record time all right
please
okay and remove shift
it was this one
yes it was this one s and then e
okay
[Music]
please yes me
and it was here okay i got um
me
[Music]
meet
uh i think it was me
me
i got the um
[Music]
exactly eight eight i have the e
e g h t g h
oh i messed up
okay got it and then we
okay
and we combined our powers
three two one
nice we're so fast
all right well is this again leave i
think
so
capital oh okay okay capital leave
this requires a lot of brain power
lean
okay
leave
them
[Music]
generally pressing more buttons than i
am but
but you're you're a younger kiwi and i
am so the younger kid
more eyebrow around more
yes agile kiwi
this is why they cut us off but we're so
fast now
wow
[Music]
i'll shift it and then w
i don't think so wait no that might no
that's probably not no no no no no no no
oh
no
l is an h so ch
chan
chan changed changed changed
[Music]
oh god that's true that really scares me
still have to half the time
oh my goodness
he
pop part
password password the password who
changed the password oh past piano big
brains
okay
change your password man i gotta change
it to the base dangerous
are you gonna give us silver for that
because we were so fast coming fast
no what
we were pretty fast man
okay that's fast enough
i want to see people speed run this i
thought we did pretty well
i bought some tools
cause it wasn't even our first time okay
whatever we're happy with bronze bronze
is fine
oh dear the next one is called postal
pest problems not again
previously piccolo's property
ppp
okay i'm sorry i forgot
did you hydrate make sure to hydrate
okay i have no water but i'm
i have nasal spray does that count
nasal spray
are you i can i swear in your channel
let's just say are you
kidding me
i have
it's water you need water you need water
to drink when you stream momentum i
usually have water but
i made coffee you need to go get water
okay right now
are you sure oh yes i have nasal spray
that's hydrating that is
you're such a weirdo movement
thank you
guess it's back oh no the flies are bad
oh we got to do the crates again okay
oh gosh oh this one oh gosh this is
going to suck with these bugs
no
they're going to play with the stickers
they're going to put wrong stickers on
our crane no
okay clear the swarms from incoming
items okay will we be able to handle it
um
let's try
tutorial or skip
oh
i'm waiting for you i'll skip there we
go oh god oh god oh it's the first thing
we do oh what's the first thing we do
let me check what oh my gosh look at all
them get off
they're perishable i'll get the code
it's five one one free five one one
three three one three oh god i got it uh
oh i'll check again what it was it's
probably perishable it looks very
perishable that's what i assumed
perishable uh-huh got it uh oh down i
see
here
get up here no stop that get off
heavy oh no
um all right there we go yay
and now
is it already time i think it's already
time
no don't play with the third they can
even play with the trent and with the
crane oh my gosh
oh a little bit back there girl
no no no no do not mess with it oh sorry
let's down
there we go nice okay all right
oh yeah wait it's not done uh north
north north okay
bye-bye
at least we got it back
don't worry i got this
wrong okay
don't worry i didn't even know where it
was going
numbers what the hell go away
again okay what are they what is it
salty flats but what is it
i'll check later it's pasta
it's so chaotic oh
[Music]
oh my god
is it perishable
okay okay pasta
okay uh wait what what was it
yes perishable yes perishable i need a
new one
okay okay
go away away from the crane let me do
this all right what why is it over there
oh because they played with it oh little
they still got a little they are they're
okay so guys
okay okay
i hope they didn't do anything
bad with it when we didn't notice hey
and where's it going uh now this one
stop stop stop stop stop
they put oh my god mommy look at the map
they put a fragile sticker where the
code is little
what is it
oh it came back though oh
did we took the wrong sticker
huh
oh i guess it's not ah because it's
pasta it's not actually perishable
because it's uh like raw pasta oh yeah
delicate fragile hold on yeah i'll grab
it okay with the cream again i gotta
just take that one
all right it's uncooked okay okay
[Music]
but what kind of medicine
selfie is against salty flats for
consumption buffalo consumption only oh
as soon as possible this one's urgent
okay
so buffalo makes the coffee stop using
my machine
one round three there
urgent you say is that urgent yes i'll
get the urgent sticker
get out of here on my butt my butt is
urgent
but why doesn't it why is it sometimes
the wrong way around out of there
all right
wow we can't even place it anyway yet
oh you're right we have to wait oh is
there another way to make it go faster
no
they can't keep up with us we were just
that fast we were that fast
all right all right it was a gal flat
[Music]
not so bad i must say
we always average the same time i know
so within like between 4 20 4 30.
nice
we're always so close to silver but i
feel like in our hearts we're actually
silver oh we're actually going we have
hearts of gold
[Music]
wow
a lot of plants grew here a kutsu
infestation oh no
this is why we close the windows at
night during summer help zoey out and
keep those vines away from the mail oh
no
okay
so this is where vines went
the most
vine
yes they were like there for six seconds
and then they came here now they're here
so that's what happened to the vines
[Music]
compilations just for the memories
oh we have to
we have to pack the flowers oh that's
cute they look nice though why don't we
don't want the flowers oh
no boxes away from greedy vines easier
with two kiwis okay
vines will hide envelopes around the
room
oh okay
you'll peck each other out from the trap
vines or you'll be hoisted into the
rafters oh
oh god this sounds dangerous
let's go
oh no um
oh my god where do we even start
okay oh wait we should probably first do
these ones here yeah let's move these
kind of two at a time oh you can't
i'm moving here and i'm moving this one
oh wait i messed up
these stupid vines you're keeping me
from moving this back up oh
[Music]
i get it ah you gotta pull from the
other side oh
oh
that's manageable alone i still can't
wait now there we go okay herself
here
all right
and then can you uh let's move the
number one all the way to the right and
the number two over here good okay no
not again oh gosh
okay can we work together
yeah but you gotta be on the same side
oh never mind it's okay
okay all right and then
i'm going south away
from wait i have to first uh
i see this one
can you bring number one here oh i moved
one already up here
that's good you can move it number one
has to come here sure oh you mean so
that south goes first okay yeah sure
here we go
oh no
we have the same idea with these vines
okay okay okay now one can go
all right all right
there we go kim limbo
okay i'll send a letter to pimple
where's pam here's what is that name
tim limbo is a
ham limbo are they related ah pamela and
pamela oh they tried to bamboozle us
oh they did they
where's pam
you died when you fall into the water
oh what it's just oh yeah
she probably
how would you swim
wait uh uh this leather
oh we have to uh
trip it trip it that's what i have to do
i have to go up here and trip it
okay
and we're done i think we're done with
that round yeah
oh gosh
[Music]
can you move the number two to the very
right please
maybe we should do north first
okay oh gosh i gotta get rid of those
vines anyway how do you how did you grab
it to move it
um uh first the up arrow and then to the
right
ah
the up area when it gives you the prompt
and then
uh you can let go up up but you gotta
push it to the right i have no problem
that's weird
oh i get it i get the up up one weird
but to the right with wasd
there we go here's the north
pole
oh wait uh move this one here
oh this oh oh oh oh sorry don't worry oh
[Music]
i know
i don't get the prompt i don't think do
you see the chat
i'm confused
i don't have the
oh gosh
wait we're gonna be a little bit i need
to do this because i can't
okay okay okay don't don't take her
don't take her
you go work on something else
yeah you're right i was just watching it
very intensely okay uh i'll set this one
free too
just work on the letters or something uh
oh can we do the letters all right we
can't do those already i didn't realize
we could already do those i don't know
how to do this
i'll do the buttons i'm stronger i'm
stronger
oh damn oh this is getting close all
right royce
okay okay where are we right now i'm
doing rice darling oh my gosh darling
here
all right oh we're good we're good
okay okay
oh my gosh we are not gonna have enough
time i was too distracted ah oh i was
just stressed i assigned the packages
you just do something else you do
packages okay
well i'll send the packages i didn't
realize i could do these like
while other people are doing them this
is not the right one
[Music]
a moment by the way
yes you you told your viewers right that
you're probably gonna visit me right
i hinted yes did you know that
i right now on my balcony i am growing
berries
no way what kind of berries
i'm growing a
red currant
and a [\h__\h] ton of raspberries
i'm not sure
if they're gonna be renting
by the time that you come but there's
like i have like two batches of
raspberries i wanna look at them one of
them will be uh
one bush will be edible in
um
in summertime and one will be edible in
in
uh autumn time apparently
yes
oh dear wait did we run out of time i
don't
know we are we
we're simply bronze that's all
we're still apprentice it doesn't even
make a difference at this point if we're
a good apprentice or a bad apprentice
they don't seem to differentiate that
getting the work done
wait when did you plant the berries
um a while ago
maybe like
at this point one or two months ago but
they grow really fast and my mom brought
me like like kind of like starters
um from her own garden oh cute
yeah yeah yeah she brought me like those
um they were not um sprouting yet
uh at the point where she brought them
to me but then we put them in
earth and soil yeah and then and then
i've been i've been pouring water over
them and then
recently they started sprouting with me
that's exciting oh i've been wanting the
garden too i just haven't started it
oh
how are you with with like green stuff
can you keep it alive
before i had some trouble but i think
that was cause i didn't have much
sunlight
in my
home
but now i have sunlight so i think i
could think i could keep plants alive i
do keep an animal alive so
it couldn't be too hard
interestingly enough i think keeping an
animal alive is actually more easy than
keeping a plant alive i think you might
be right because the animal will tell
you all the way around the animal
reminds you it needs to eat plants don't
remind you
yeah for most animals it's more obvious
what it needs and how to fix it than it
is for a plant yeah often for plants
like i have no idea what's going on what
it wants from me that's true too like
even with most animals you kind of know
how often but i guess you could google
how often you need a water plant but
will you remember
how do i water my dog and my cat yes
water
water dogs
water dogs yeah wait okay what is this
summer in bungalow basin maine sandstorm
sandstorms
does new zealand have sandstorms i know
that oh my god and we've got a real
nasty one blowing in anything that's not
bolted down it's liable to get blown
around including small flightless birds
no oh the big ones should be okay the
big boys but not the small birds oh no
we do not want to fly away
i got an incoming message i got it we
were really good at this one mommy so
we're good at it my beard blew up
my beard blew off i seen my beard i got
mine okay
i don't have a beard guys chad does your
beard blow up oh there's blue i see blue
and off here
okay
occasionally oh dear there's a sandstone
oh sorry i forgot
[Music]
but here i am here i am caught in it oh
my gosh
all right okay i'm feeding the big bird
oh it has nice glasses this is cute
fancy smells
all right easy peasy lemon squeezy they
have such an easy message
just handing me stuff
oh close your shutters yeah that would
probably be a good idea where's clothes
i got clothes yeah and yours
yeah i see you're i see you're just
gonna wait for it oh yeah i see turs
oh there's oh yeah you can cheers
[Music]
did you see that i don't think you saw
that
shutters
we got it
three two one yes
all right time to give it to the big
boob to the dinosaur bird dinosaur
[Music]
three
two
one
these birds are unbelievable holy moly
look around me
holy mackerel oh gosh
if there's no post office hiring us
after this and i don't know what their
problem is he must have gotten silver
oh my oh my god
oh my god
[Applause]
this is our specialty this one is our
specialty
gold come on one gold gold give us one
gold
there's more sand in the glass
sand a lot of sand isn't there oh my
sinking feeling
see oh go oh no
all right
we gotta
move fast because we're gonna sink in
the sand
oh you watch your step down here or you
might get in over your heads oh
oh my god um i feel like at this point
this should not be handled by two tiny
kiwi birds but some actual humans humans
could be way more efficient with this
yeah
yeah what the hell where is the vacuum
cleaner hello
uh keep your feet on solid ground
uh-huh
run over pieces to uncover them
okay
use whatever scattered lids and stickers
are available
wait
uh okay
oh no
you're good i think so
i'm a little sli oh no just the game
just i'm nervous okay like smells so
difficult but we can't do it
uh
oh gosh
oh bessie
and this is probably perishable just
don't let it spoil or things get weird
and like busy okay there's a parachute
or is that washable
oh
wait oh god
how do you clear stuff again
running over it i i'm stuck oh i'm dead
i i leave
i wish to leave you run over it oh
uh
wait it said lake messy though how do i
look at the lake bessie man uh
oh there it is beautiful found it i knew
it i remembered it was up there oh my
gosh
two
two two
four
one there it is up two
okay
oh gosh
all right i want the perishable sticker
give me the pair it won't give me the
finish of the sticker
is
where is the isn't it this one i got it
i got it i can't see it
uh wait where's the lid
is it ah it's that one
oh it's different
okay gotta put it on it on the right
side ah now it was on the right side oh
there it is okay okay oh and we gotta
move it ourselves okay
now i'm just gonna pick up the lid
already okay
oh sure i'm here i'm here mommy
what ah there we go
all right
you know i i do prefer this over the
bugs
yeah definitely yeah definitely
all right
what was next north north north
north we go
done all right next one
incoming package what is it
oh a conqueror
i'm sending it to the same place we
never had painted cliffs or a bell being
yourself oh which is it's still
aggressive
okay this one's heavy
lake bessie again right if i saw
correctly yes it's like best see where's
the lid oh the lid's up there right why
can't i have some
four
one can you clear this
i know that goes uh
oops
uh the lint the lid is now somewhere
else i think is it okay is it is it and
on this here down there sticker goes
there but i'm trying to find result
where's the lid
i think it's it's this one this one this
one this one this one
what the heck is one or this one one of
those
oh
where's the heavy sticker
heavy heavy i see fragile
oh god oh god oh god oh god oh no oh god
i'm sinking i'm sinking
moment this is like titanic just with
the water okay
okay
put that on one of those both seem to be
all right you're yes and uh i'm gonna
move this one
[Music]
there we go
oh refrigerate immediately so urgent no
oh sorry okay sorry why do i keep on
doing that i do it too um tree grove
i'll do them you'll do that all right
i'm gonna find the urgent sticker
what's that wait
i know there's
uh urgent
urgent
does that work
it's like a it's like a
searching game urgent like i spy
there's
perishable oh there no
no isn't it
perishable orange and i said to use it
immediately but maybe
okay
i don't see urgency i don't see it
either maybe it is supposed to be
perishable maybe but maybe it's a trick
maybe it's a trick
trick let's use let's use the perishable
yeah let's try it will tell us if it's
the wrong one anyway
okay
uh
uh okay ah i'll push the thing into
the box if it lets me oh right
milk milk milk
we got this
yeah it goes bad really quick i feel
like it could be both
um
oh sorry down down down right here
there we go
oh dear the time actually stopped i
noticed that i'm kind of concerned
are we not gonna get any it means we've
done extra bad today oh no we're working
hard okay we're trying our best this is
uh now no
apparently
not south not north it's now mouth
oh my gosh what
oh wait wait that's over
hey what is it about that it just
doesn't show the time
[Music]
we really have a talent for this have
you ever worked at the post office
never worked at the post office don't
lie to me i don't think professional
little kiwi
i don't think i'd ever want to oh my
goodness have you seen
have you have you been to the post
office and seen people
yeah many at times many times what is it
about post office that brings out that
side of people
i don't know which post office you go to
and the post office i go to they
all they don't they're not that crazy
really
you're fine the ones i go to have a
slime that's like tell people not to be
mean basically really yeah it's
apparently it's that common i've seen it
like twice when i've gone yeah i mean
okay that's so
uh that's understandable i heard that in
in north america you have a lot of
karens
yeah
yeah yeah
i mean we have parents too in europe
yeah but
yes we have karen's everywhere it's a
normal thing but i i've seen a sign like
that at the doctor's office before like
the secretary the ladies secretary desk
that's where i've seen like a sign that
if you're mean to them they will call
the police oh
man
yeah all right we have two more levels
we'll make oh my goodness it was done
apparently for summer that's really all
there is i think there's like more
seasons but maybe we'll just do
something
yeah yeah yeah i think it would be
good
to end it there but
uh what is this headquarters sentence a
shipment of newfangled postal equipment
they do this uh sometimes always cooking
up inventions to make the teleport
faster it's a noble goal all the same
i'd like you to test the stuff out
before we make any permanent changes
put these gadgets through their pieces
and report back with your findings is
this bouncy bouncy trampolines huh see
oh my god what is this what do we bounce
on
springboard oh boy color coded button
oh my goodness oh
doesn't even give me instructions like i
don't know what you're reading
hey did you not see the
instructions maybe i did and i just
wasn't paying attention i'm not sure
launch letters where they need to
go oh dear
letters from the in slot get launched at
the matching mail blimp what does that
mean should we do a tutorial
should we go for it
scroll to find your customer's name and
then launch at okay i think we have to
experiment a little bit with this
do you want a tutorial or do you want to
skip tutorials oh yes let's do a
tutorial okay
move packages using the color-coded
buttons okay
oh that's what i was just reading oh
really oh
all right i'm already done reading that
one i'm sorry i see it oh yeah we see
real quick so you launch it what
okay launching it right from the end
okay
all right
and then let's go
i'll figure this out oh this is the last
one all right
okay holy
i feel like i'm gonna have a hard time
with this
um there's no vines this time so i guess
we could oops we could try to figure out
the particles together i was looking at
yo kiwi
am i cute
we are
so probably
oh where does this go wait but do we
have to think about which one to do
first
[Music]
wait a minute where do i put this
uh that one um
the things are gone was i supposed to
launch it
okay i'm gonna try to figure out the
parcels the packages
um
oh i see shoot it mommy i see i see
oh
this one here
oh oh
oh i did one okay okay
north can i not do it
what
i press wrong button
don't break it oh
are you on are you fine are you
understanding it i understand i keep
pressing the wrong button and i'm like
why isn't it working
with me
it was your big brain i know
[Music]
my
what else is there to do of cycle names
ben
roma
mama
it took me so long to process this oh my
gosh
okay again you seem to have learned how
to do the other thing i have i
understand
all right horn cobb collins that's a oh
shoot oh no [\h__\h]
okay i can go backwards okay
look at me go
like a pro
i guess if i ever leave whole life i
know what my job will be done i'll join
you
oh where are you
so we're moving to new zealand but new
zealand sounds really cool it does sound
cool i actually would really love to
visit new zealand yes yes me too on one
of my one of my top places i want to
visit
like there's a lot of great movies that
were filmed there too such a beautiful
landscape remember how i told you i
haven't watched the lord of the rings i
still haven't watched the word of the
names
i'm totally up for that i miss i miss it
let's go let's watch it soon
we're the rings marathon i would be down
we could wait we could turn it off we
could watch it
yeah that's even cozier and it's even
better than we don't have to sync up
because we're in the same room when you
come here let's watch it oh my gosh
we should absolutely watch it please
that sounds fun
i'll finally be able to
tell people i've totally seen things
we're gonna watch the whole thing
all of it one sitting
my cats don't really join me anymore
when i stream because they they realized
oh she's busy oh really whenever she
talks um to the computer
oh that's when she's busy they they get
it oh
that's interesting yeah
what the hell my animal i think is
starting to get it
at first she did not get it
for a long time
oh it doesn't bother me while i see my
annoy you while you're screaming you'll
be incredibly annoying yeah
huh um that's love that's called love it
is love
all right i'm sorry for the weight don't
worry indeed
yours is harder than what i was doing
can we get silver come on come
it's okay that was fun though that was
fun that was fun i would say the post
office should adapt these new machines
yeah oh no it's more plans now
more plans i don't like those stupid
plans okay okay please i'll i'll do the
wait but this is the plants in a
different setting in the different oh it
is so which one is this oh my circular
one differently
okay
um let's watch the tutorial
yes
get rid of vines yes yes we had that
before reattach keys that pop off oh
big flowers are carnivorous no
oh gosh oh my gosh
really dangerous
are those phoenix kiwis the fact that
they can get back to life after that is
surprising to me you're right they just
respond and oh peck pots the free trap
okay
you have to save me if i am stuck
vice versa that's so cute they're so
cute
oh my god it is cute
all right all right where did we start
okay
[Music]
oh wait because of the
oh
there we go
don't eat me please smile big
oh big is being hot all right eyes up
here
oh please i have hey no i don't have to
why are you hiding it no no no no no no
no my god
oh
is this good not talking to us again
uh-oh do we have to wait to be digested
now i'm pushing buttons but nothing
excuse me please that is free
what are we gonna do ah i'm free it's
time limited
okay
[Music]
come out of there
we have something to do
i'm sorry big toe oh yeah
next one oh hurts
you
i got uh
oh
oh they steal buttons because uh so
are we looking for our
[Music]
oh there are the buns over there
we're already ready to activate it
we don't need those buttons
[Music]
did you ever break your toe before
because apparently that happens a lot
without you even noticing
i have not broken my tail have you
broken your toe thank you
i mean i don't know because apparently
you don't notice you don't notice when
you break your toe what apparently oh no
it didn't it didn't work i'll
okay
[Music]
i need to pay more attention to my bad i
keep looking it tastes so good i don't
want that oh it tastes like dirt and hey
it's not good
uh wait is hiding it again uh are you
not over there
kind of slow right now that's all right
oh gosh where's the eye
on the eye
but where does it go it goes over here
okay
i'm coming oh gosh
[Music]
oh my gosh it's annoying i swear i
pressed it
okay i got it
oh i i've been
i've been taken again i saw it
you take the i i hate the v
and the y
ah okay okay and then
three two one
oh gosh there's more last one plants
plants plants
[Applause]
no no no i brought you a flower boom
thank you thank you very much
where's the pee why don't i get him
better walk right and do it again
you just look too delicious you gotta
like dress up or something wait wait no
i want to save mommy i want to save
mommy okay
okay where's the pee
oh it's still there no mommy mommy i'm
here
i'm on the way
there you go
okay i'll i'll i'll press the shift
because it's gonna be uh shift it's
gotta be shifted wait one second not yet
not yet uh and now
hey finally
where oh
[Music]
oh
that makes me feel better about myself
thank goodness
okay okay okay okay
suck
wait okay
[Music]
there's a lot of meat on you apparently
so
no need to be hectic oh there you go
hello plants
this is just everyday life
daily life
live always
people want to eat us unbelievable talk
oh beautiful
that's one of the few buttons we have
left bye
[Music]
i don't see it oh it's up top it's up
here okay i'll get it
i got it oh it's here
oh there it is
[Music]
ready
uh
yes uh one second okay i'm here three
two one
[Applause]
extra tasty
oh beautiful so was that it was that the
game i think that was that all of it oh
it looks like summer i think next will
be fall
oh oh would you fall on that oh pretty
nice oh my gosh they're so cute
they're small they're like little brown
chickens they're like little brown
chicken chicks not chickens chicks
little brown chicken nuggets
wait is there more there's i think you
can do more spaces more
what are there four seasons chad does
someone know yeah actually four seasons
it looks like there's
four seasons but i think it's the same
games i think because it looks like it
when we complain again on my channel
sometimes
i would be down this was really fun
yes so cute
this is really really really adorable
[Music]
thank you mama for finally playing this
with me
yeah i had a lot of fun
oh that was really cute
it was so cute
actually maybe
maybe this game will inspire
um
the management in her life to put in a
kiwi burp into whole life oh a kiwi burp
yeah everybody would probably be really
a small person really small it would
actually be so cute a small kiwi a short
kiwi that had no arms that'd be adorable
no no
no arms me too but
interesting or maybe maybe they could
make it so like you don't know if they
have i have arms because they
wear like a like maybe a poncho
really a puppy poncho so you just can't
see it but maybe they have arms cute
that would be oh my gosh
that'd be adorable no arms meet you
that's that's gonna be an interesting 3d
w one day easier for papa's to
to uh bring to life
yeah
but that's less stuff to rig so yeah
yes
all right i'm gonna continue growing my
berries for you thank you i'm so excited
yeah maybe when you come you know what
we could do um um we could use my
berries and make i don't know uh muffins
or cake or something cheesecake or a
raspberry cheesecake or something i
would love to cook i'm not very good at
cooking but i would love to cook or bake
with you if you want to yes yes yes
berries cake i need you some pictures of
your food and i'm like oh that looks so
good
don't worry about it i actually don't um
know how to cook that much either just
just a few things the few things that
i've cooked on streams are basically the
other the only things i can cook please
don't judge me for how i chop garlic
oh don't worry i don't know how to like
chop garlic and onions properly even
like you you're supposed to hide your
your fingertips yeah yeah you're
supposed to like bring them in but i
never do that yeah it's like
it would you do that yeah i'm just extra
slow and careful yeah
oh and did you hide your your fingertips
no
okay i'm good no we both don't do it so
one day we will both be missing our
fingertips oh they look so cool we can
say like they got bitten off by a
predator or something no no we can say
that we were part of the yakuza and day
oh we took our fingertips because we did
something really bad because we're bad
girls like that oh
we're back
that's how they do it at the yakuza
we've been we've seen some [\h__\h] we've
been through some [\h__\h] movie do they let
us keep the fingers once they're cut off
because then we could like trade them
like have little keychains of each
other's fingers
very cute okay um i think maybe two
hours is maximum time i can spend with
you
just wait just wait until i visit you
hopefully help me
get me out of here
together
yeah yeah yes that was that was fun that
was
thank you so much mommy and my dear cole
hine
for
having fun with me and working with me
in this post office thank you for having
me
pleasure yeah lord of the rings run time
is way over two hours that might be a
problem yummy oh yeah
how long maybe like 10 hours
i don't know i'm gonna have to is there
something like maybe like a drink or
something that calms you down maybe i oh
not casually
i mean i think alcohol makes me a bit oh
okay here's the thing alcohol will make
me more chill but i will still say very
weird things
um but will i actually do them probably
not i'll be like yeah
it probably will make you weirder it
will make me a little bit that is okay
i'm just kidding you're perfect the way
you are with me
but but no trading of fingertips okay
okay okay and also not don't put them
into a
uh
what do you call it
a thingy to pickle them we're not gonna
make people king i was thinking oh they
don't want them to decompose so you have
to probably
furniture
no no no finger tips in a jar
yeah isn't it like a biscuit called
finger like lady fingers is that a thing
have you heard them
yes lady fingers lady yeah
lady finger biscuit oh don't say you
make tiramisu of those no oh do you
remember me
oh
i think is that what you used for
tiramisu i thought this like you spread
it you use that for tiramisu yes you do
yes you do
interesting that's the only reason why i
would ever eat those just inside of a
tiramisu although i don't like um
you know there's most tiramisus taste
like coffee and i don't really like
coffee and mommy so oh
you don't i like well you can make
tiramisu that's not coffee you can make
for example
a very tiramisu
i want to try i want to try
fancy food with kiara
yeah do you want to do a cooking stream
like i've been doing that a lot i would
love to i actually really want to know
how to set one up but i would love to do
one with you
i think uh if you would be there i might
be
even more nervous about [\h__\h] up but
but but it could also be good because
like then
um
one person can always
take care that uh nothing goes wrong
yeah just sometimes when there's both
four hands on the screen then then we
gotta be careful but i think i think
having some help could actually make it
easier i'll help you
yeah
let's make some stuff of berries we
should we totally should oh i'm so
excited oh you know what
what we could also make maybe
my mom said that i will really get a lot
of raspberries out of the bush i don't
really know how much it will really be
but but but we could also make raspberry
jam for you to take home
so cute
i would love raspberry jam yes please
yeah my favorite yeah raspberry
strawberry thing making jam is pretty
easy i think you just cook it with a lot
of sugar
and cook it and cook it and cook it and
then put it in a jar i think that's
basically basically it oh my gosh
i would love some i hope you have enough
ah
self-made raspberry jam
[Music]
it will be it will be delicious i'm so
excited
i'm really happy that you coming with me
actually recently
so
several several
girls have been telling me that they'll
come visit me not all at once but
some people may be overlapping
so
it might just it might not just be us
too might be a party if some other girls
could make it
it could be a little a a little itsy
bitsy party little party
a small party small party
what if it was like a
more than four hands in a cooking stream
oh my gosh imagine how chaotic that'd be
looks hands yeah we can do so many
things with six hats we can see so many
things oh my gosh
we could cater for like for a wedding or
something like that
how about a delivery or yeah open a
restaurant well yeah open i have a
restaurant what the
oh my god i need some more hands because
the friends of chickens they don't
really have proper hands right i have
proper hands
that's that's good to know i want my
hands
i'll keep them safe mommy until you come
to my place keep them safe i'll make
sure i don't lose any fingers
i also want to warn you i have um
i may have super cute cats but what
comes with that
because they're long long hair cats
is
like cat hair
is there's so much of that in my
apartment don't worry and i'm in front
of us clean but it's still going to be
everywhere
my animals my cats are crazy yeah animal
sheds a lot too when i when i saw the
other girls i tried to uh like lint roll
my clothing but animals still followed
she's
probably when i see you there will be my
animal hair like
i have so much
cat hair on my clothes that i really
stopped getting
every sh
yeah unless it's a black coat or
something then i try to
get rid of a little bit but you still i
can never get rid of all of them yeah
it's too much i've stopped i only cared
when i uh went to see them i wasn't sure
if anyone had allergies
but
yeah i i i get i've given up i have
given up i vacuum like every day but
i've given up on the clothing really
i've documented every day dust bust
every day i don't actually vac like
bring out the big boy vacuum every day
but i use a dust buster every day oh i
never dust
oh it's like a it's a it's like a bat
it's like a mini vacuum
it's a little vacuum maybe i should buy
a little one but the thing is
my one of my cats chunkers she's really
really scared of the vacuum cleaner even
though i've been using it for years now
and she's still so scared of it i don't
want to use it too much you know i
understand that animal really does not
like the big one but she's gotten used
to the smaller one really maybe mine
could get used to the small one too yeah
it's a it's a little it's quieter
i think you just gotta find the right
one
right the right actually yeah i think
she would i think she would be able to
handle it that's actually a good idea i
i wanted to buy one before but i i gave
up on it and i don't know maybe i should
get one very handy
i like it because i don't like bringing
out the big vacuum it's a pain it hurts
my back
use dyson so no noise oh guys
i want a dead i want a dyson so badly
but every time i look into it i get
overwhelmed sponsor please just kidding
there's just so many ways to get
overwhelmed oh my god we're suffering
from cat hairs and animal hairs please
help help help please help this is
like
being excited over vacuums and dyson is
how i know that i've become an adult
oh i'm excited about cleaning appliances
oh
dyson i've never i've never felt so
excited about the vacuum cleaner before
actually i've only felt excited about
the roomba before
oh i don't have one those look cool i
have one but
i am
i actually didn't set it up yet because
i i read the instructions to it and it
said that it's really annoying uh to
like set it up again once you move
like a piece of furniture or you have a
new piece of furniture whatever
something changes in your layout so and
my my
apartment is like there's still
furniture that i'm missing still stuff
that i want to buy and i'm not sure of
the whole layout so i was like
i'm gonna wait until everything is
complete right and then set it up but
it's been taking a lot of time i do the
same thing i have stuff like i want to
get a new desk and i want to upgrade my
get a new pc
but i'm like oh i should wait until i
get this before i do that oh i should
get this first but then i'm like which
what do you get for it yeah i understand
um
yeah i also want a new desk i want a
bigger desk man
i think i'm gonna get like a custom-made
one
big size
i don't want to look into custom ones
the ones i want there's there's one i
want but it's never in stock so i check
like every week but it's never in stock
but custom one
yeah i mean i'm not really custom one
but like self-made one just go into the
to the place where they sell big big
wood yeah that's actually what i want to
do and they don't have to give up that's
what i want to do but they don't they
don't have the top that i want
ah yeah
and that's sad yeah that's sad how many
monitors do you have i have two right
now i want new monitors because they
suck well they don't suck but they're
too big
uh cause i have free monitors and
even like when you buy a generally big
table once you have free monitors
even the ones that are supposed to be
big are too small and then i have like
the audio interface on it and the stupid
stream deck that i don't even use
all this kind of stuff is on this table
i just don't have space anymore i need a
bigger even bigger one
now one of my my cintiq is mounted on
the monitor arm which is pretty cool
that's nice
i can move it around pretty freely but
still still so i don't even have myself
even that label anymore it was
so big and i didn't use it enough also
it's kind of dying but
i think your mind is dying the cintiq my
cintiq is pretty old
oh
you have an old cintiq holder i didn't
take very good care of it because i
traveled with it a lot an old cintiq too
and it didn't work anymore either once i
joined whole life so i got a new cintiq
oh mine stopped working around the time
i joined what
nice or actually sad
still nice because we're matching
something yeah
it's really sad though because the
cintiq is uh quite the expensive product
pricey
it lasted like if i get it
it could be it could work again if i if
i get it fixed brian is so dusty now
it's so bad
oh i just dropped my ipad now
get that duster get that dyson get that
dice it on my cintiq
oh my gosh that that'll fix it
oh surely surely that will be it little
dyson will make do a miracle but anyway
uh sorry we started tangency
wait one more thing did you show your
viewers the logo i didn't show them but
i talked about it
you need to talk
are you scared
my brain kind of goes oh if kiara saw it
that means everybody saw it i kind of
forget like people don't like
i don't know so i'll show it though like
one person that means everyone's alive i
saw it that means everyone else saw it
funny
i'll show it let me show you all
i talked about how um you mentioned it
was related to arrested development and
i thought you were i thought your
reference was something else that was
far more you buy
i will tell you i'll tell you all stream
um so yeah why no no no no no no
well i don't know if you guys watched
arrested development but basically
uh there's like there's a time when one
of the characters tobias he wants a new
start so he gets his car he gets a
number a license plate and it says
it supposedly says and you start but a
new start wouldn't fit in there so it
says
and then i was here listening to mummy
saying
uh and you start and then i i i
suddenly out of nowhere i felt like she
was singing and start and then um
because because i've been commissioning
spirit snare who made that logo for your
song i've been commissioning him since
like
so
long ago so many times so i was like yo
yo yo yo can you can you make this into
anustart and he was like i'm on it
and there it is
congratulations on on what was it two
million views on anu's time oh yes thank
you yes anna start now has received two
million
views 82 million people watching anus
times million people watching and
listening to the anus tart yes
please oh that is beautiful everybody
loves anus tarts
oh my gosh
i also i really loved the like
i loved the inner start but then it also
was the nana then nana's moves is what
made me like actually laugh more i was
like but we both didn't really
understand what what that means it
sounds funny but i'm not does that have
any meaning
yeah didn't i say i was like isn't it
moon's
a word for like chest but it's not i
just told myself it was
is is that what that was supposed to be
bloomers maybe
is that
could that man has not as boobs
what am i thinking of memories no
no no no
no no
not
wait that just that just made me think
everybody calls you mummy but one of
your nicknames could also be nana from
nanashi
i've never been called by nanashi
you know when i first joined i thought i
would actually be called
nana
oh really i thought so i thought people
would start calling me nana
huh but you should have you should have
asserted dominance by yourself in that
case
please call me nana
and then people would have probably done
it but probably but when people say
i think it sounds so funny
that i'm what
i don't know mummy
what's funny about that
because they say
if you want i can try to start calling
you nana but now it's like out of
nowhere like do i even look like a nana
like a new person
yeah
no no no it's a cute name though on its
own no cute name
[Music]
moment
yeah no i don't think i can change that
anymore in my mind you're you're a mummy
you're too far into it seven yeah seven
months too late seven eight what the i
don't wanna think about it yeah i don't
wanna think about how many months it's
been waiting again sorry no new
nicknames that's okay i like moonlight
all right
my cutie pie it was
thank you oh yes my mom's thank you
thank you to your rooms too
and i'm i'm excited to maybe play this
again sometime maybe um you know in two
or three weeks or so sure i will be more
free then so yes please yes show our
skills again then
hopefully we don't forget how to work at
the post office until then
i hope we have a talent for it so yeah
we're naturally naturally gifted in the
post office yeah professional yes
okey-dokey
do we say goodbye oh i never say bye but
we can say goodbye goodbye chad that's
so rude
we don't even say goodbye say bye just
don't give them the chance to process it
is all wow okay
you see me now you don't bye
do you have any announcements kiara yeah
you have anything
no no don't worry about just the
announcement that dead
i
i like this bird next to me
i like the bird on your head and you
[Music]
get out of here bye-bye i want to leave
now i'm i'm sad
i angered i upset the bird
totally i'm so angry i'm gonna slap you
silly i hear it in your voice you're so
you're
i'm so angry angry
angry very very
angry okay well look forward to the slap
bye everybody bye bye bye bye
good night
[Music]
so
do
[Music]