[Music]
ah
help me help me once i started streaming
my mouse disappeared that's why i
couldn't find the mute button
at the unmute button help me why did my
mouse
disappear someone make my mouth come
back
[Music]
i can't do [\h__\h] without my mouse it was
it's ctrl
is it because like stream because i'm
like in some kind of streaming
alt f4
what is that supposed to do what is that
supposed to do ctrl
shift w are you sure about that are you
going to kill my pc or something
i seen in these in these situations i
don't know who who to trust
i'll tap really really
really what is alt tab
what does that do
oh what did that do i don't know what
that did do but it did not it did not
bring back my mouse
what does that do
[Music]
w really
oh no no no it's not unplugged it's not
such a thing when you unplug it it shut
up
it was literally there before i started
streaming
see they'll shift
help me ctrl r what does that do
i can't trust you guys but can we be for
real because like i need my mouse to
play this game
why is it because of is it because one
second oh god i don't see it almost
one second ah
welcome to the membership i tried to
drag click what
oh my god
use keyboard for you but i don't i need
my mouse for y'all
smash the pc
[Music]
but try to right click yeah okay
well but that doesn't bring my mouse
back either
at least i know where my mouse is when i
do where i click oh my god
oh this is horrible
by the way today i'm i'm doing uh you if
you can read then you can read that
sentence i suppose so read it
press f5 really really i trust you
oh no it didn't do the trick
and ctrl shift wouldn't be i don't i
don't trust
i don't know how to trust
mouse no
maybe
it came back after i opened the task
manager and i followed it by myself
i am smarter than you guys i am smarter
than you for y'all
i am smarter than you booyah
okay so everyone um we are today we are
playing
no sure okay i don't need so many videos
we are playing
uh dot io and this was originally not
planned
on my on my schedule i was supposed to
take the day off today
but some things have happened
what what i mean i messed up everything
here
some things have happened and uh
yesterday i had a collab with
inaudible and calling punyo and we
played the
puyo boyo tetris too you might have seen
that and uh
there i have uh i mean
for real though you know won 11 times
kiara me won two times cali won
one time
so if you see it like that i did not
lose
the bat but if you see it differently
which is how i see it to be honest
is that um i
lost first i i
i i i uh
uh fell out of the the how do you
explain
i we were playing against each other and
i always would lose first for you
uh almost always for y'all but i won
more than kelly doesn't make sense to
you guys for y'all
i don't need your solutions anymore i
already have found my own solution
[Music]
uh i came up during the stream with uh
batsu game which is like a punishment
game
uh saying that whoever loses
the most which is really what i think i
originally said so i think it's fair
that i'm doing it but some people like
to say that kelly has to do it but kelly
won't do it
so i'm doing it like volunteer i'm
volunteering volunteering for it so
i said that whoever loses the most at
the punishment game has to end their
sentences with puyo for their follow-up
stream which
whatever stream it is puyo and um
it's me and i didn't want to do a fire
emblem six hour
stream with puyo the whole time so i i i
have this
i have uh uh decided to do a guerrilla
stream today
for you and i love how you guys are also
using puyo constantly for your well guys
slipper
dot io is actually a game i had my eyes
on for a while but
uh never found a good uh good
opportunity to actually
play it on stream for y'all but
okay what kind of snake do i want to be
brian
um as you as you can see
in the thumbnail i made myself become a
snake boy
maybe we can find is that germ is that
germany
is there maybe a similar snack is that
australia puyol
is there a similar snack to mine for
y'all what is that
it has a ball like a oh who was that
what what what
that is creepy brill
very fancy snacks boy i must say
by the way guys you can play with me but
how please don't
please don't gang up against me
whoa what is that bruh what is that for
y'all
that's is that pewdiepie boy why does he
have it i also want my own snack for
y'all
why does pewdiepie have his own snack
for you i want my is it canada canada
where you at
uh switzerland oh god please please stop
it wait that's cute
that's cute i want that for y'all
[Music]
oh please don't gang up against me let's
go let's go
i'm a snack for you i'm a snack for you
i'm just a lovely little snack we are
let's see
let's save my if my lovely kfp employees
join me on my victory
journey
okay all good for y'all what
wait that's so that's a flag of a
country but i like the star
what
[Laughter]
no bgm oh [\h__\h] i don't have busy m
i need to turn it on uh is it is it a
problematic uh
is it problematic
i might change to a flat uh no flag
but i want to start how do i get out of
the game can someone eat me
eat me how was the chicken did it taste
good
well what are all these what if i'm
can i just be red or yellow
or orange
let's go for orange okay i'll look right
to i look way too normal but
let's go yeah smell for y'all
i'm orange for you but kind of like a am
i glowing i don't think that's normal
orange is it like a glowing orange
wheel oh [\h__\h] wait
wait wait wait wait don't eat people
wait wait wait i'm tapping out i'm
tapping out where's my we're here
here here here and there you go for
y'all
oh i'm still alive i'm still alive
wow i can eat myself for y'all does that
do anything probably not
[Laughter]
probably shouldn't eat myself
[Music]
of course i'm doing it seriously puyo
how about you do it to puyo it would be
really cute for y'all
i think i think it would be adorable for
y'all
by the way do you know this game for
hello orange party for y'all i want to
be friends oh my oh it's my oh my god
this is getting confusing is this is
this my kfb buddies for y'all
are you guys on purpose making yourself
orange for
oh there's a glowing y'all i ate it for
y'all it makes me much stronger for
y'all
hello orange friend for y'all
[Music]
stop faking me guys stop you fakers for
y'all
let's all just say puyo for the next
stream
let's do it together for y'all can i eat
you
can you nom nom
i feel like this dude actually like
wanted me to eat him
[Laughter]
i died for y'all i tried too hard i need
to
maybe i maybe i shouldn't go too much on
the aggressive side for y'all
maybe it's a big boy boy it's a big
snack for y'all
wow there's an even bigger snack for
y'all but the good thing is
the bigger you are the slower they move
so um in this situation i'm the winner
but i can't eat them oh my god oh my god
there's so many so many
no so many snacks
we need some distance for you from the
big boys until
until we go strong
[Music]
live
someone protect me kfb employees protect
me for y'all
yeah bye for y'all okay i think i'm
i'm calm again for you
to start crazy or someone protect me for
you
oh
[Applause]
the panic got me okay
calm down for y'all oh no
no no no don't eat me plyo you look so
fancy
way blue away
rest in peace please no he it's here
he's here again
to protect me will someone protect me
for you
no please save me well i'm just just
not for real though someone bit him
are there no nice stream snipers someone
someone nicer
[Laughter]
oh i need protection bro
help me there's nothing around here
where i'm live we are
yeah so
i'm gonna go away from all the all the
ganging up people i'm just gonna go on
the travel alone for y'all
this is my own adventure for you
that was definitely a stream sniper yeah
but can i have nice stream snipers
please
it's wait i'm sweating for you
oh who is that is that orange are you i
a friend of mine
will do you wanna protect me
you can embrace me how about you circle
around me so that i can
like be protected by you
please
oh this is uh this is nice let's get
that
yeah become
bigfoot so that you can protect me brian
please
thank you is that orange boy a friend of
mine
or a foe no no no no no no
let me eat your poop oh yeah no oh he
died did you do it on purpose
yay thank you thank you yum yum yum
yummy
oh so yummy oh no
he's so big let me eat you
can i eat you for you no oh no is he
protecting me now is he trying
okay bye-bye no that's that that's that
for y'all
i've i for a moment for a moment i was
thinking he might
he might be trying to protect me but he
was probably just trying to eat me again
it's hard to survive out here in the
wilderness isn't it for you
who's this big boy are you a friend let
me see your name
what's your name wait i can't go that
fast
i can't go that fast for you
no don't eat me for your hope
wow for y'all nice wife and welcome to
the membership pool
so here who is that started whoa
your friend don't eat me can you can i
get into your womb can you like can i
get into your
belly like not in that not in that lane
i'll give him another protection away
for y'all
you protect me from the from the scary
big man
from the gray one yay for you
we're on
are you trying to eat me oh no wait wait
wait this is like a snake that is like
how you call that anaconda or something
they're trying to
wait wait i need some more space for
y'all thought you were trying to protect
people y'all
i thought you were trying to protect me
brian
i don't trust anyone i cannot trust
anyone for you
trail i thought you were my mama boy
wait i can't cut that one
big one
don't eat my poop for y'all that's my
poo-poo i eat myself oil
betrayal food it hurts me
painful
careful
can i eat you oh you're still bigger
than me i don't think i can eat you
you're a little bit bigger let me eat
you good let me eat you please
okay that's also it works it works thank
you defender for you yay
yay who's that boy
no scared for you
[Music]
i'm getting longer and longer for you
thank you was that on purpose did you
try to eat me or did you try to
sacrifice yourself to me for you there's
so many people here
i want to go away oh
guys here's your chance to get eaten by
me
make your dream come true sacrifice
yourself to me i will
i will kill that fool dude what
what thank you oh wow
yummy this is what i like this this is
this is how it's supposed to be my
friends yeah
yummy thanks for the breakfast don't
chill
shallow will kill you i will find you
again i will kill you
oh no no no i need more sacrifices
please for you
i need to grow big again for you please
i don't know if that person did it on
purpose but i will uh that person will
eat my revenge
well for not so fast my friend
whoa
[Laughter]
[Music]
this is fun is that like different
servers or is it only one server i
wonder
because i can i can imagine many people
trying to join
i wonder like if it's easy for you guys
to play with me or if it's hard to
it's different servers
different service oh boy oh that must be
[Laughter]
oh are you not watching how to ah
how's my stream right now for y'all
don't eat me
rude this is so much fun
i'm a small snack i'm a small snack for
y'all
i'm a small snake
[Music]
and every time i i
die and rejoin i always end up in the
same server i suppose because i i do
keep on seeing the same
people i think
how does it decide decide who gets into
what server
how can i join a different server for
y'all
[Music]
you mean that these people are in japan
for you
location puyo i guess you can use a vpn
where am i where are my kfp buddies for
y'all
come back to me i felt
a tiny moment of reassurance for y'all
oh boy oh boy they ask how you are and
you just
i love that meme
do you want me to eat you
wanna you wanna wanna like bump into me
by a total ex
my sacrifice has been eaten by someone
else for y'all
where where is my defender right there's
someone in number nine called chicken
killer boy
are you trying to tell me something
brian
please do not kill the chickens for
y'all
that's just rude for y'all you're trying
to scare me or something brio
you look like a christmas sweater brio
oh my god what what what's going on for
y'all what's going on for you
let me out of here wait you look like uh
what's that
uh what's it called deadpool thank you
caleb thank you for letting me leave for
you
yeah yeah i'm gonna eat you
eat he's eating me instead okay
i have been eaten by yago puyo
let's see let's see we can do this for
you
no give it to me
kelly's psychic huh
what do you mean kelly said there's no
such a thing does not exist
hi hello hello
hello
i love you for you all you're delicious
we are
a boy
i'll help this is confusing me there's
too much orange here guys change your
color boy
there's too much orange for y'all
for your friend for y'all simply
i hope too many people too many people
for you all
please social distance for you please
panic we are
[Music]
oh
oh my god good job on making it into the
server dope y'all
yeah bye at least
who are you to eat my rainbow those are
my sacrifices for y'all
mine not yours who is this a listener
stupid snack for y'all stop eating my
stuff
let's go okay get kfp guys follow me
let's go somewhere else
[Music]
what's up guys this is like a fan
meeting in real life
and you just tried to show me who has
the longest snake
oh who has the longest neck show me show
me my my
dear oh god there's too many people now
help me and so many people
so many people i'm gonna roll myself
up okay
help me go away from me
where's my manager we gave her free
lemon for y'all
how did you make it in or is that a fake
oh my god
thank you for you wait why are you
eating my
mayo eating my stuff yeah my
carefree mafia oh god are you on my side
or
it's a hippie mafia on my side for you
go away everyone what is going on
big for y'all oh god
[Music]
oh no someone else is taking for you
road to the top phoenix worm hell yeah
only the top is good enough for me i
will become the biggest snick
hello cafe manager you want to be eaten
you can offer yourself to me
what up thank you
please clap you have asked for death kfb
it's your turn kill him
you have asked for death you will get it
for you
my my employees are very protective
they are very protective they feed their
mama and once someone ate their mama
they will kill whoever ate their mama
boy
[Music]
i love all these names for you you guys
are so creative for you this isn't the
cult
it's it's not a cold it's not cold it's
not a cult
i want to i want the shiny
[Music]
you're still so small become bigger and
then sacrifice yourself to me
thank you
[Music]
who are you who are you
are you trying to give me like a heart
attack or something oh my god for you
you'll buy blue ah i'm scared
oh
it's too many people again they're
ganging up on me again
or are they are they trying to to
protect me i don't know it's stressing
me out oh my god kfb america hey there
how's it going over there
how's it going
i lost that beat
okay
everyone's right everyone's sacrificing
themselves from meepo y'all
this might actually be a cold
[Music]
oh my god stupid
leo you're trying to help me but you
guys have to follow the social distance
rules for y'all
oh oh my god
stop zooming i'm a boomer i gotta go
slowly y'all
oh my god bottom left here what's up oh
wow thanks i love you
i love that
[Applause]
[Music]
who is that green puyo is that high
tension
potential is it you is it you is it you
oh my god you're really long
oh oh thank you i don't know if you
actually tried to do that
who are you what are you shining where
are where's your top
oh you're not hiding so okay whatever
one
hour one
sacrifice sacrifice
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
shark is a bit dangerous here please
please my distance i don't know where to
go
go away
oh
what are you guys not understanding brio
when i say
i need some distance for y'all why is
that so hard to understand for y'all
kiara's neighbors be like yeah probably
they must be very worried for you
but it's it's daytime right now so i
think
they're probably out working or in
school and stuff for y'all
hopefully they're not at home
you made it in too hey judas are you
going to
betray me or are you going to be on my
side with a snack
thanks for the snack you look like a
snack wheel
i ain't going away i'm still not big
enough
i need some more time to grow big for
you
how did you make it in what the hell
how are you guys making it in for
this is like a super chat reading i
should just read super chats in
in in sliver.io
that okay probably that doesn't make any
sense it doesn't work but um
silverwheel this is like a supercharging
hi they love 67 dancers
[Music]
you know who's at the top of the food
chain for y'all
it's me boya oh yeah bye boy
sacrifices pool
help we don't care for you no
for you this is getting dangerous i see
my death already
[Music]
oh help me some more i need more tips
for you this is too crowded
just be a circle be your circle be a
circle for you oh thank you for the
sacrifice for you
very much appreciated for you
oh my sacrifice wait i can't go there
because all the people are eating myself
okay that's what you guys that's what
i've come so far beyond what you guys
don't understand
you have to oh who is that that's a
weird looking boy boy
that's a long snack for y'all
damn y'all
i love you guys that's so cute
well just bring snacks together isn't
that wholesome for you another called
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh my god oh my god thank you for your
sacrifice but i can't take it it's too
dangerous here oh my god
why are they all here already oh thank
you
oh thank you thank you for you thank you
would you wanna do you wanna make me are
you a fan of mine would you like to
sacrifice yourself to the kfp
company not called thank you
thank you good choice good choice
good luck for your thank you
[Music]
it's getting crowded let's go oh no
no no no no
[Music]
no one uses that anymore for you oh
thank you for your sacrifice but i gotta
go
it's too busy here for y'all
[Music]
dude can someone like eat him
can someone eat him help me happy
employee of the month
oh someone sacrificed thank you oh
thank you hey why are you taking away my
food they're trying to feed their bird
mama okay
he's so cute i love you guys i love you
guys thank you for feeding me brian
this is very this is very symbolic i
have to say
[Laughter]
help me brian help me for y'all
help me out help me
help me getting so crowded again
laggy bodyguard you're supposed to be a
bodyguard and you kill the person you're
trying to protect
are you [\h__\h] kidding me
you
me
[Music]
[Laughter]
i have eaten you every single bite of
you puyo
[Music]
yummy almost killed myself for y'all
oh my god how's it going for y'all how's
it going what did you have for breakfast
i had um pancakes with strawberries and
bananas and a [\h__\h] ton of nutella
on top of it i ordered from uber eats
the guy the guy who delivered
it was like was actually speaking
english to me very surprising
[Music]
he probably fought like since i opened
at like
what time was it it was definitely far
after morning time and i just you know
in pajamas
i opened the door for y'all and i'm like
thank you for the pancakes for y'all
this is tough oh
my breakfast
what on earth we are where it's next
yeah
it's an ad it's an ad
you're an ad but this stream is not
sponsored wheel
i don't want ads in my stream wheel
yeah it's time for a concentration for
you
thank you amiibo kfp supports amoebas
[Music]
oh that those are those i accept this
thank you for your sacrifice for y'all
yeah the friend is back welcome back
we're strong and big you're smaller than
me right now so that's not gonna help me
very much
stop you guys are not supposed to take
my food away from me okay for y'all
yeah bye bye huh
hello
[Music]
thank you that's my boy i have to grow
bigger for you thank you thank you
oh yummy yummy yummy yummy yummy i got
love in my dump
here comes the sacrifice says you
yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum
there's a party going on oh my god for
you this is totally not the cults people
are not
sacrificing themselves for me no no no
please youtube don't ban me
please don't terminate me for you
hi denzel yay hi
guys how's it going puyo help
when you try your best but you don't
succeed for your
you get what you want but not what you
need
little people well
i was too greedy for you i like turtles
hello i'm back i'm back for y'all
i'm back to eat some people for y'all
where are the other snacks where are
they
where are you who are you are you a fan
for you why does it not show your name
boy or show me your name
[Music]
okay guys i wanna that number one shark
on the leaderboard must be a must be a
shrimp a chum bud i think we have to get
kiara the kfb leader to number one i
think we have to do that for y'all
[Music]
you got you i know you didn't do that on
purpose but thank you for your sacrifice
oh my god we all oh my god
i i i don't know if you guys are on my
side
or if you're not on my side for you but
you have to
make it clear to me puyo if you're on my
side
then stop [\h__\h] around
[Laughter]
where's this long boy
[Music]
who is this i don't see your name for
you mama
mama mama for you
okay you small one you sacrifice
yourself to mean do it now
do it just do it hi this is
this this is this person is projecting
me thank you yummy yummy
oh there's a there's a bunch of white
you open why did you open your circle
why did you this is a dangerous day
so you open up your mama circle and
see this is what happens this is what
happens when you open up your mama
circle
[Music]
will
oh yeah will i ever find my real mama
for you
where is my mama for y'all
i was i was hoping someone would protect
me for y'all
i like all these references for you
shiny thing shiny
[Music]
help
i'm so scared for y'all i'm so scared
[Music]
oh
i want to be number one for you
you guys need to i know you guys like me
and want an autograph for y'all but you
need to
have some distance for you
[Music]
on
do you want to sacrifice yourself please
oh that's mine that's mine that's mine
thank you thank you
his sacrifice wasn't for nothing because
you guys killed me
oh my god burger sacrifice was wasted
this is so depressing we all
carefully and believe we are would you
like to sacrifice yourself for y'all
wait it does it does really sound like a
cult
oh my god oh my god for you now for you
it's mine for you i asked him and he did
it
for y'all why would you do that for you
don't eat my my sacrifices pleo there's
a reason they sacrifice themselves
if you eat my sacrifices i will
sacrifice you you will pay
you will pay for y'all let me tell you
that
vote for kiana thank you
okay guys you know what this is
it's too dangerous
[Music]
which one are you using our vpns itself
are not illegal right are you trying to
like let me eat you
that's so cute we're making it
but whatever you use them for could be
an illegal action now
hello i i like this this is very um
judas you have eaten
judas you ate my sacrifice and then i
i was too too depressed to stay alive
for y'all
that's okay i'm a phoenix i'm a phoenix
[Music]
it's like everyone in here is from kfc i
love it
the names for young long chicken you're
not very long i'm longer than you
okay
[Music]
there's too many people for you i will
die for you
i'm too small for this for y'all
let me get out of here
oh go away for your stupid stalkers
[Music]
oh my god yeah that's a real gamer
that's right but yeah that's why i'm
playing
sliver io because i'm a real gamer
that's why i'm playing this game
[Music]
are we starting our best friendship for
you
[Music]
is close to 1 million views people
thanks for bringing it up for y'all
close to 1 million views please have
everyone please go to my channel and
watch hinotoni every day for you
and share it on twitter and share it on
thank you share it on
facebook and instagram and all those
fancy websites for y'all streaming
tonight
[Music]
this is how you how you do promotion for
your own what's that hino toni
thank you callie's ted for your ted
i knew he existed she tried to deny it
for you but i knew it had exists i knew
it
oh my god thank you for
go away that's my food i'm trying to eat
here
don't disturb my dinner booyah i mean i
literally just ate breakfast but that's
okay
oh my god oh my god you call yourself
food for you but you're not
quite there yet you're not quite there
yet you're you're actually scaring me
i think this dude wanted to kill me and
then died
but then i also died but it wasn't
obvious that he was trying to kill me
for y'all
right quit smiling
much
yes we are he just wanted a hug for you
he was saving he was getting raked
way too close to save me brian
i love you i love you everyone else ate
you as well
it's not nice for you i'm so very small
pool let me let me be
let me grow for y'all oh my god help
and there's like so much is this is this
is this is
yes yes yes yes yes
that's how it's supposed to be for you
help me oh my god help me
lord save me for y'all help me
go away for you now's the time now's
your time
be careful
go away please go away pianist i love
piano players but please go away
oh thank you that's my player
well you died as well so congratulations
chiara let me what
what did that say chiara did me what
what did that say help
i'm so scared i don't want to die again
for you please go away guys please i
guess i'm gonna care for you boys around
me
help me oh my god
yes just kill it kill each other eat
each other oh my god it's the pickle
pickle guy again
[\h__\h] up booyah
unless you're trying to um protect me
then that's okay
okay wait i think you might be trying to
not eat me
oh are you a good guy after all
i need to get out of here i need to get
out of here i need to get out of here
it's just no
no no no no no laggy vpn
[Music]
we guys are having quite the quite the
conversation here we all
i'm talking to you so much for um
no i'm just panicking sorry guys but
yeah there's not much of
a deep talk today for y'all
i just i just want to eat for you oh my
god we are you came there
way too close brian okay now you're
letting me eat you thank you
thank you i keep dying well me too
the world is tough out there for y'all
even for someone like me
a leader
am i i am quite big now bro
thank you can i eat that for y'all or is
everyone gonna steal that from me why
are you guys stealing my food again oh
mm-hmm that's the food chain that's what
i call a correct food angle like oh i go
like walk
away like why are you eating that
help me what is that who is that red one
who is the red one go away it's way too
long
i thought i could just eat them up from
behind
no wait it's already been an hour but i
want to play more for y'all
[Laughter]
i thought i could eat them up from
behind no
your sacrifice is much appreciated for
your very generous of you
that's basically a red supercharger
every guardian plea will you call
yourself a guardian puyo
[\h__\h] for y'all
thanks for the super chats even though
they weren't so great
we are right
thank you i'm getting used to that real
thing maybe i'll just do it forever for
y'all
cafe germany hello basketball
yes we are please don't forget
[Music]
guys help me help me help me help me
crazy fbi where's the fbi help
i have been killed out of panic my own
panic
from like being scared of about
oh my god oh my god what the [\h__\h] is
going on man
okay this is my last run
this is my last one so i want to get to
number one
oh my god i love this we might do this
more often for y'all this is fun for
y'all don't you guys agree for y'all
this is like so much fun for you
is this easier for you guys to get into
the game than mario kart puyo
i agree with y'all this is very friendly
okay how do i even have the time to look
at the chat for y'all
[Laughter]
last run for y'all yeah thank you thank
you
[Music]
thank you for supporting my last run
this is the last one guys if you want
the stream to go on longer you better
not kill me better not eat me oh my god
[Music]
oh my god we're getting too close here
we're getting too close my friend oh my
god
help me help me help me help
one more one more one more this is the
last one this is the last one
but how how come no one was protecting
me from that uh
kill kiara dude how how where are my
lawyers
where are the kfb lawyers what the hell
do we have lawyers in-house canada
helper oh my god thank you
even with the australian flag i like it
that's totally the australian flag no
complaints taken
oh my god thank you
um excuse me what the [\h__\h] for y'all one
more for y'all
one more that was not there was nothing
for y'all you can't count that kihala's
feeder
wait are you going to
ha what the [\h__\h] was that
what the [\h__\h] was that for y'all
you fed yourself my friend bruno
you fed yourself you're a hypocrite
[Laughter]
i love you dopio i love all of you for
you
can't be right for you worry me
i love these names for y'all this is the
most entertaining
like part of the stream for me are these
names for you
australia if we are australian
whatever you're kiara's wife y'all can't
have me burgerfield
was also ganging up for me again for
y'all
of course that'll make sense for you
oh my god i think casper is like getting
really excited right now
um maybe this is the last round
maybe i'll think about it
i'm just having too much fun thank you
for your
call sacrifice for you
[Laughter]
sacrifice yourself for your thank you
for you
i love you for your
this is how you get yourself remembered
without sending super jets if you if you
protect me
i might remember your name how about
that
for the people who wanted their name be
remembered how about getting it
remembered in a good way
you know come on
it's getting too crowded again
what's this
no cheating i'm not cheating oh
thank you so much
[Music]
thank you don't take away the food that
others paid for
y'all i mean i didn't pay for anything
oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god
oh
oh oh thank you so shiny i love shiny
things
well i'm a bird and birds like shiny
things you know
yummy
[Music]
retreat retreat retreat soon
i'm growing so big no saggy fake go pick
up
y'all oh my god help me help me there's
too many people oh my god oh my god
there's too many people
oh thank you wow that's very shiny thank
you
i feel like half of uh half of the
viewers right now
are in the game right now or are like in
a different server and trying to get
into the game
so people are too busy to write in the
chat are you guys here
oh god oh god i'm feeling itchy
are you guys here we are right there's
heights for y'all
help people
i won't even eat that for you i will eat
that for you
go away go away go away for you oh my
god
oh my okay don't be greedy
okay for real last game for real last
game for real mate
this is the last one for you
i love this for you oh i want to play
this with members maybe as well members
only
this is so much fun for you who's the
next talk show guest for y'all
[Music]
i will not reveal that yet we all
i was thinking about it for a second but
come on baby
wow kelly's my player definitely not for
y'all
definitely not for you help me
[Music]
wow wow wow
that was fun that was actually really so
much fun
that was so much fun that was so much
fun oh my god
how can a so simple game be so much fun
for you
guys
i want to do this more often for you
i couldn't find the server for y'all
let's try for y'all next time
[Music]
thank you all for participating that was
so much so much fun
so much more fun than i was expecting
right
man and like so many people can
participate for y'all
i mean i i don't know how to get how you
guys can get into that server
puya maybe there's some kind of like
way to trigger i don't know
uh but a lot of people seem to make
their way in real
good
how did you bleep your voice i have a i
have a go xlr
go xlr and uh there's a beep button
[Music]
i know
did you guys have to change your vpn to
japan to the ones who who actually made
it in for y'all did you have to change
it to japan for yeah
[Music]
yes yes yes oh really
oh there oh i see okay everyone who
wants to make it in next time you have
it here as a reference everyone's saying
yeah
what nobody anita what the hell we all
i don't know
no vp what i got i just got a hiccup
all right guys
oh some extensions you mean like browser
extensions
that lets you choose uh what oh what do
you mean extensions for
for sliver io
[Music]
see people you're a little bit sleepy
boy
i had a i had a weird dream that i was
uh like super late for this stream
y'all like 50 minutes late or something
for you
i don't know i don't remember the rest
for y'all chrome extensions
what okay guys for reference and for the
next time
i'm i'm sure we will do it again it's a
good game for like a gorilla stream i
guess we all
i feel like it's very fitting for that
okay guys let's do a quick a quick super
chat reading video
[Music]
i bet that the super chats will be
filled with pre-operation
[Music]
did you guys like my thumbnail for y'all
i thought it was cute for you
i i
quick yeah it's gonna be quick it's not
that much for you
but first um the first i'm reading
uh i'm reading the ones from the
good from nepo yo thank you it was a
cute thank you for you
first i'm reading the ones from the
puyol for your tattoo stream
which uh basically is the reason why
we all ended up using puyo puyo
[Music]
oh yeah by the way the puyo tetra stream
was sponsored thank you very much for
that that was actually
a lot of fun like like i i had so much
fun there
it was a really amazing amazingly fun
stream if you missed it
go watch it but i have i have another
uh sponsored stream coming up this week
two sponsor streams
so much going on i'm so happy to get so
many like
like how you say
partners um i guess so
okay the for your thumbnail is nice yeah
that one that one was that you know
i made it i was like really stressing
out yesterday and i had like no time to
make my own
and um so i messaged inna i was like do
you have a film already
already and she was like yeah should i
make one for you i didn't even ask her
and she just offered
to make one for me and i was like oh my
god thank you
so uncanny
was not sponsored but they still gave me
my code for a giveaway which is really
cool
i already checked the hashtag yesterday
i'll check it again today and then i
might be sending out the codes already
to everyone who
participated because 24 hours is over i
think
i think so is it probably um
thank you ina yeah she made such a cute
thumbnail
i love how she also like often just
draws her own thumbnails
like she makes like small chibis and
stuff looks very cute
oh yeah i'm forgetting puya oh my god
also my my friend kind of hurts for
y'all
let me drink something for boy
[Music]
how about instead of thanksgiving i just
said say puyo
is that okay oh my god you changed your
name
do you love you changed your name we
love 67.
crack
your
[Music]
device i can say your original song hits
1 million by friday really
i mean this friday i doubt it puyol well
how far is it right now
this friday seems a bit uh
it's too impossible for y'all
[Music]
let's see oh
940 cable yo
[Music]
let's do it together guys
one million let's go wrote that keynote
only wrote to 1 million
thank you guys for your support for you
all
[Music]
in btm yeah you are okay and
an airborne cat player for you
[Music]
if this is a game you enjoy i would love
to see some members only room play
if it allows it and would give me
another reason to buy a switch
oh you would buy a switch for that
well for blueprint touches it was
sponsored but i would play it again if
it was a collab
or possibly with members but would you
would my members
like buy the game in order to play it
with me for y'all
yeah for real for y'all
thank you puyol
okay we can think about that then bryo
all right if we all maybe i'll get
better at tetris then for you
and just like with with chess yeah i
made obvious
improvements in chess as well
[Music]
yeah amazing miracle brilliant video
game
[Music]
oopsie that's true that's wrong
people go on
cleansing
caitlyn embry open your
i'm so like in my mind i'm still playing
sliver dot
isle i had so much fun
i know
let's play more i want to play more but
actually i only wanted to play for one
hour because i
i actually need to do all this stuff and
i i i i got to do
i mean i'm probably going to end up
procrastinating anyway again but yeah
just got here booyah you're late for
y'all you missed so much fun for you all
you better watch your archive for you
[Music]
i found you and thought you were cool
and then
i saw the video when you were talking
german and i really loved it
[Music]
foreign
you
[Music]
online
[Laughter]
[Music]
feeling dank you heard that one didn't
you guys feel
[Music]
at least y'all my german viewers are
awake and partially watching me from
work and from school
[Music]
the people are placing their bets that
inna was gonna win and yeah they're
pretty right with that
professor jennifer kosovsky
[Music]
for you eric love for you
patrick chen for your the dumbness just
to embryo
thank you
f.e.t
[Music]
is
welcome to the membership for y'all
oh i can't read that one moment
[Music]
that's who i was talking about
yesterday uh who wants to put your boy a
tattoo stream
who watched it kia the fred wheel
[Laughter]
yep yep yep seems about right me me
oh my god so many booyah thank you guys
for you
so i mentioned a youtuber who
uh was like literally just staring at
the camera for every video
right not many people guessed it ryan
there were barely any
but i was talking about a youtuber
called magibon
who is not really around anymore but uh
she was she was very cute you guys
remember now
[Music]
well there's barely anyone remembering
very nostalgic yeah
[Music]
what
a guy who also did that what really
it's cute we are it's very um it's very
mysterious we are don't don't we all
like mysterious women for you
and she hasn't been around for a long
time for y'all
but back then for the people who don't
know she she got quite famous for doing
what she did for you
respect for y'all
thank you for the stream kiara you're
welcome thank you for coming
there was a dude who just stared at the
camera and smiled for hours but that's
for hours that's creepy for y'all
a few minutes okay but hours what the
hell we are
that's very why why
my god for your little calico cat for
your
dakuma cave gt right in for your
fight guys frozen for you wow
yeah i bet you'd win two games in a row
since you
did win two practice practice matches in
a row so that's a win
okay you're bending the rules but okay
bryo i'll allow it so if you can cheat
the puyo stream i can do right for you
i'm gonna follow the boss's example
i didn't cheat for you when did i cheat
we all
fight guys for y'all big poopy boy pee
pee pants going on the dominance just
sarah from faith for y'all
[Music]
i was very proud of myself there thank
you for the thinking
and the official black crewmates
jacob cord cordon arrow my family opens
christmas presents in the evening as
well on the 24th oh but you're from
america
it's interesting to see other cultures
do things differently as well
well interesting interesting that you do
that even though you're probably in
america
interesting puyo
[Music]
i posted a new used card for you today
hope you will get it
looking forward to it for y'all so few
tangents for your ass because you guys
don't give me tough stuff to go
unattentioned about
well yeah looking for that for young
the number nine large and number six of
extra div and number seven
to number forty fives the winner stays
in the large extra so
large soda soda
[Music]
we are
thank you that was very random haven't
had that one in a while
was it a large extra soda
[Music]
for y'all beyond it hasn't shut up in
the wobbly y'all yeah
we are
[Music]
if we are slime for you for your slime
for yourself
my habit of saying thank you soon
[Music]
well valiantly for you but was
ultimately defeated leo and now you're
cursed with saying for you until you
overcome this challenge for you good
luck for you i believe in you for you
thank you
[Music]
is the thing to say on a bright
australian christmas day that's the
outback reading that we sent to you from
the land where the ding goes straight
is that from like is that a quote for
you
thank you
[Music]
it's from a song i kind of recognize the
first line yeah
a little bit
rhyming is easy to stream for y'all no
need for much drinking or skin for you
i feel so inclined to add to each line
and ending puyo as a mean puyo
good job for you that sounds beautiful
for you
where is it for yours for your video
customization video for you
patrick's channel
is
one one zero five for y'all p p
v t p y one e four y'all need to give up
yeah what was the bet for y'all that i
would that i would uh no no if the bet
was whoever
loses the most it has to
um add puyo at the end of the sentences
after the that stream in the following
stream
for the whole stream and i did it for
you
if we
[Music]
german that nobody works from
westminster i want to play more for you
where are we like really hooked on
sliver.io
that's so addicting real it's so
addicting
i need more for you pull you out for
your video darren wait for your real
your bat was for winning for y'all
really we all agreed for you but you
love kelly too much for you yeah
i i don't i don't want to push it onto
herself but
i just i just genuinely enjoy doing it
for y'all
i just love doing it for you if kelly
chooses to do it then she can do it but
i don't think she's gonna do it for
y'all
big poopy boy pee pee pants
[Music]
i want to see how many times i can put
your boy in the sentence after this i
will pull your belly stop
that's a good one but that will never
apologize for y'all
hello i wonder how tired of saying this
you are going to get me off
[Music]
i'm not too not quite tired of it just
yet
maybe the super chat will help you a bit
for y'all to be honest i'd forget to say
it afterward
you know you can do this center for
y'all yeah we all we are i did
[Music]
you
they ask how you are and you just have
to say you're fine when you're not all
really fine
but you just can't get into it for you
yoshi
[Music]
become the best we all never give up for
you i hope you have fun for you
thank you dude that's for your nagi
[Music]
what is happening or some people don't
understand what's happening huh
well i lost the bat so i am adding puyo
at
every cent after every sentence that i'm
saying
james mcphee thank you for the red super
chat for you for your
love for your
[Music]
very deep what a deep thing to say of
you puyo
thank you for your thank you for your
support for you
did you try getting into the game with
me
hope you had fun watching the stream for
your video joking hazard
to have it to have it is coming out
tickets for you for your nova tiger free
of
your cyber feel for you will two nine
zero five
nine zero point beyond this secret free
up for y'all
i don't really want to read your name
for you
um but your text is saying i love you so
much
for you thank you for your
thank you puyo i i i just wonder if your
name is maybe not not so good to read
but
thank you anyone for your dude where's
the pizza
yo the pancake lover of ryobi or razzie
for yourself
it's hard to figure out where you are
and that accidentally died for you yeah
right for y'all
we should do it again sometime for you
my name is wayne with ya
this is not weird nothing worried about
that for you
how about how about how about putting it
in the front though
be available for your case before life
for your real spider brio for you
for your love for your boy trooper free
overall
thank you for the red super chat am i
imagining it over you also in the
in the game did you i feel like you made
it into the game as well we hope you all
thank you for the red super chat
thank you thank you for
enjoying the stream together with me if
we all
i'm just checking the chat if you're
answering but
you're not answering
[Music]
where are you in the game i feel like
you're wearing the game
[Music]
you killed me she
and true bravo
thank you for the red super chat for you
i'll be visiting you soon for you
if my friend called kelly over mauricio
it's over for your bill
[Music]
pack your suitcase for your wheel
what's the best time to postpone on
twitter i've made a decent amount at
this point but you've only ended up
seeing like half of them because i guess
i feel like i'm pretty much
liking everything just sometimes
like sometimes even though some people
add
the hashtag sometimes it still doesn't
show up in my search
but that only happens sometimes that one
thing
um there's no good time because i
usually i scroll down
until i get to the point which i already
saw
weird
but maybe you can try if you didn't do
it maybe try both hashtags both the
english and the japanese one
and there's maybe a higher chance we'll
[Music]
a weird way of finishing his sentence
and freaking out and having fun
what is not to love about this thank you
very much for the great girl gorilla
stream
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you it's a warm eat bird world out
here for you
jacob alvio judas beyond
thank you
creator 498 free for your real hope you
enjoyed the snack
where you were you the snack
were you the snack someone called
themselves kiara's snack or something
like that for y'all
thank you i want to play more
charity will you be on
i got diagnosed with depression things
are negative right now but watching your
streams gives me a lot of joy
it feels like i made a new friend thank
you for being so loving to us
oh um
well i hope you get the help that you
need for your
[Music]
thank you for watching my streams video
for you all
i hope you feel a virtual hug um
i'm hugging you virtually hugging you
real
eat some cake cake is very good the
chocolate and stuff
chocolates very good cheer out please
but y'all get some ice cream puyo
don't feel bad about it for you get all
that
all that healthy junk food into yourself
it's okay for you
i'll do i do the same for you glenn
michael priyanka yum
let me refresh one time because i'm
already at the end for you
how shocking for you
[Music]
where are we
that was very fun to definitely play it
again thank you
you forgot to say puyo in your last
superhero how dare you forget it real
sifx people real it's really quick
though you're making fun of me there but
that is actually quick
one of the quicker ones for you
kittens thanks for the stream for your
video these sort of streams are always
so relaxing for you that was relaxing
for you
looking forward to more atelier though
real you really seem to have
uh be having a great time which i always
love for you thank you
but tomorrow we play fire emblem
mb 737.00
a red super chat with no words what
puyo i guess i don't think that's the
first time you do this
wheel why why are you doing this again
and again boyle
when you send red super jets please add
something meaningful brio
i i don't know how to how to how to
react to this bill mb737 for y'all
let me interact with you properly puyol
please please i don't know what to say
for you
what do i do for you
[Music]
oh yeah i can't slap anymore it doesn't
work anymore
[Music]
next time write something please please
please please and thank you for your
support
for your
you get some i can give you some blows
wait that's [\h__\h] weird oh my god i
take it back
let me see us
[Music]
there's also agar.e.o and df.eo to play
as well
is it like the same kind of game df.eo
isle it also has different game modes
with teams and links to groups
what
for real should we use that next time
boyo
i wonder if we have permission because i
just know we have permission for
sliver.io i don't know if we have
permission for the other ones
probably we do but i'll check that out
for you
yeah so it's also a snack game
we will thanks thank you darren wait for
your bill the boss we preach at
we're making sure people watch required
employee training
that stream and company policy you know
the rules and so do i for you
thank you but yeah i noticed i noticed
you guys uh probably a lot of people
kept on asking
the wednesday we were saying puyo puyo
and then you guys help them out thank
you guys for young
thank you thank you dead for y'all
that finger fool you changed your name
quite your name quite a bit there
almost didn't recognize you a lot of
dedication for the poor punishment for
you of course brian
[Music]
i don't date these things slightly
i take these things very seriously it's
my it's my
obligation to take a punishment game
seriously
especially since i brought it upon
myself for you
it's i will protect my honor brielle
very that's very true
brielle
i just had so much fun for you
[Music]
is a yeah girl with good tasting games
but y'all also play stream art and
medical aren't
dude i don't have permission for y'all
too
people keep on people keep on telling me
about these games
thank you now oh i tried to get
permission for it
[Music]
thank you
i'll i'll check it out definitely even
if i can't stream it i want to
since you guys recommend it so much i
want to play play it privately for you
get permission for this i don't know how
to pronounce it this gear
we actually do have permission for that
i don't know for which one i think like
does this scare seven
for example
[Music]
this gaya okay okay
this guy here
we have permission for some of them not
only one
i've seen it in our list
i don't think we have seven yet oh oh
oh you guys seem very excited about that
i always i always liked the art style of
it and the character designs i've seen
uh quite a bit of it but i never played
it myself
just never pronounced it the same twice
in a row really of other people with it
this gia this gaya miz
[Music]
thanks dude
well yeah it's a it's a game that i have
been a little bit interested in for you
but uh the game play for y'all
from what i've seen for you is
not exactly my thing for y'all but i i
actually didn't see much of it for you
so i might be wrong for you
vengeance
i see what you did there donated 10 10
10 out of 10 and then rights
stream would put you again so 10 out of
10 stream would for you again thank you
reggie steele
[Music]
team these frank's wild ears
poo and i can't stress this enough yeah
thank you
[Music]
for your spring
sorry i'm getting quite tired goddammit
i'm getting so tired right now
thank you bronx thank you so much always
really like i don't know how to thank
you enough
all of you i don't know how to thank you
enough
you deserve so much more
you uh how do i
how do i thank you enough
i can't thank you enough for you
[Music]
how do i thank you
marry us well i offered that to you and
you said no
[Laughter]
no my quality is so much better
from last time i tuned in well you
haven't been in a kiana stream for a
while and huh
thanks for coming back
it's been good for quite a while like
the go xlr made it even better but even
before
since i got my shure sm7b it was
it was really good
so the shure sm7b i've had for over a
month
maybe one and a half months no actually
even even longer maybe two months
already i didn't wait
i've had the i've had the sure sm7b for
quite a while
and then eventually i ended up getting a
cloud lifter which improved it even more
cloud lifter i got maybe a month ago
yeah the sure sms 7b i feel like i have
for two months
the cloud lifter i feel like i have for
it one month
and then the golden salary i have for
like two
two weeks now i think
it's just improving and improving but we
have finally found the right
the right settings and the right
equipment i think
sexy low end what do you mean you're
that
[Music]
cloud lifter made you sound way better
yeah yeah because it just um it just
made me much louder it helped a lot
and the go explorer made it even better
yeah ever since we got the cloud lifter
people were like
wow but yeah
yes i am happy with how things are now
low end is the base i got bass in my
voice and my
instrument
um
did you guys recognize what i just sang
you all about that base about that face
and anyway bronx i don't know how to
thank you honestly
i'm i'm at a loss at this point i don't
know how to thank you guys probably
anymore i wish i could just give you a
hug
oh man it makes me sad
i can't thank you guys enough makes me
so sad
oh yeah i'm forgetting the boys for
y'all
oh yeah right but that's not enough
that's not enough it's not special
anymore
[Music]
it's not special anymore
you bronx thank you
i really really really appreciate it i
really do appeal
patrick jambo smooth operator for you
hi kiana can you say
[Music]
no i cannot
i cannot
[Music]
are full of good boys that fed and
protected you for you
i don't i don't know which stream we
were watching for y'all
but everyone was that getting so close
to me that i
died every goddamn time way too early
for y'all
i don't know which stream you were
watching i mean yeah there were a lot of
sacrifices but then people i
keep kept on eating my sacrifices
instead of giving it to me
and then running into me or so that i
would die what the
actual hell no
everyone was a snake very fitting yeah
for you you should have protected me for
y'all
yeah your name was easy easy to say ten
times sean
marshall's hand was tense you're killing
herself we all that's a lie but y'all
that's a lie for y'all
yes i was reborn yes just like a phoenix
i
rose i've risen from my ashes
majestically for you
rts man for your exactly your video
beyond because you add to okay if it
means to your bio
i think i ran out of space
[Music]
oh wait i have a bit of space let's see
if we can get it in there somehow
ew
that's going to be difficult kfp memes
okay but i have to damn it
uh
[Applause]
yeah but i can't explain what it is but
i guess i guess it explains itself
um what
that works okay it's in there now
i hope i mean for you guys it might
explain itself but but for the japanese
viewers it
probably doesn't explain itself
sorry i'm really tired i can barely talk
why am i so tired
my mouth is uh is not moving
[Music]
for you
i've been tripping off forever young k-8
one free
from you i went to christmas present
shopping and now i'm broke this is gonna
be my last super chat for a while
no value guys did you also start uh
buying
christmas presents for your pool
[Music]
i think i'm only gonna like
buy one for cali
maybe one for my manager
and a few people who i
might collaborate with christmas pool
i gotta start don't don't do it too late
it's gonna be gonna be hard if like
shops are closed and stuff
because of various reasons but you'll
what about your family well i'm not
with my family but i did buy my
my brother and my mama an early
christmas present a while ago
christmas present that's on four wheels
so that's basically taken care of
[Music]
but they're they're not here so
you're about to make matching bicycles
oh that would be cute that would be so
stupid
a vacuum hell yeah but i bought i bought
them a vacuum cleaner
for you i'll keep on forgetting puyo now
what the hell
[Music]
i it was that it wasn't it was a um a
second hand so
it wasn't like insanely expensive
and my my brother like um
i don't want to talk about this too much
because i feel like i'm like
it's kind of weird to talk about
like making big purchases but
my brother had a car and it kept
breaking down
and my mom kind of needed
him to have a working car for various
reasons
and so they both kind of needed a
working car and it kept breaking down
and they couldn't afford
to fix it blah blah blah so
yeah i i wanted to help them out
because uh why i mean like there is
i don't even i don't even know what to
buy for myself
i don't know i feel like i think um
probably when i get back to my country
i want to buy some eventually when i
move into
my own place eventually i'm going to
live for a while with my roommate again
i think
but eventually when i get uh when i move
out again which i will do probably next
year
i probably live a while with my roommate
and then maybe after half a year i'll
get my own place again
and then i'll i just want to you know
get my own furniture and stuff so
it's good if i save the money i think
i'll get a good apartment
for my for my kitties i wish i hope i
can get like a
apartment with a garden or with uh
um a balcony but i prefer garden because
balcony scare me
because um not me but it scares me
because of the cats
so and i'm too stupid to make it cat
safe so eventually i'll get
a garden hopefully and then i'll put a
jacuzzi there
just kidding
how much does a jacuzzi cost
oh yeah the garden has to be made safe
for cats as well so that they don't run
away yeah because my cats are
house cats they're not supposed to go
outside
[Music]
but i always wanted to give them the
opportunity to like
feel the ground on their parts like i
feel i feel sorry for
like keeping them in one house like in
in between walls for their whole life it
just seems sad i want to
show them more of the world you know so
i was thinking of putting them on a
leash and walking them because some
people do that with their cats which is
so weird for you
thank you for the red super chat for
y'all
it's so weird for y'all but i wanna i
wanna
i kinda wanna try that but the the area
where i
lived until now in australia until i
moved to japan
that area wasn't it was kind of a noisy
area
with like lots of cars driving so i
didn't want to do that
like i didn't want to stress out my cats
maybe i can get an apartment in a quiet
area with a guiding and then i can let
my cats out there
and they'll be like hey what the [\h__\h] is
this green stuff can i eat it oh no no
you disgusting
[Music]
buy a castle but i will
i will get more cats eventually i will
get more cats
probably if i move out from the place
where i live if i'm with my roommate i'm
probably gonna get
maybe two more kittens so that i have
four cats what do you guys think about
that puyo
get another cat call it for you that's
cute
that's a cute name for a cat that's cute
come here for you forget yeah i'm just
worried
how my current cats would receive the
new cats
but if they're baby cats i feel like
they would get along like if the
if the new ones are baby cats like
kittens
crazy cat lady kiana
yep that's me boya
they smack him no but my cats are
very nice so i feel like they would
probably be okay with me bringing in new
cats
you can never have enough cats exactly
for you
i want more cats for you
[Music]
getting cats used to each other is risky
you've done directly keep one
yeah yeah i've i've already watched a
lot of videos and stuff on how
people introduce new cats to their old
cats
by keeping them in one room for a while
and then let them first get used to each
other's smell through the door and stuff
and then eventually let them like like
a sound like let one into the other room
and the other one into the other room
without them like being in the same room
but just being in each other's rooms do
you know what i mean
so that they can like smell the room
and all that so yeah there's there's a
way to get it done
correctly and i will i will do my best
yes yes brio more cats for you
i will get so many cats for y'all that
during my during my streams in the
future you will hear
background noises the whole time you
will hear so much
now wow
wow you will hear that constantly
oh that will be nice nice background
music
oh
[Music]
i'll take a double triple phoenix elixir
on a raft four by four animal style
extra shingles with a shimmy and a
squeeze light axle grease make it cry
burn it and let it swim
what
[Music]
greetings from switzerland that's that's
cool hey there i was in switzerland once
in my life
do you know a swiss german word i
actually don't feel
well you're welcome to teach me for
y'all read
it for your videos
am i like to do priority this stream was
pretty awful
nonetheless and i can't wait to put your
next standard for you
thanks for your thank you for your
very dude
uh i don't really do shout outs um but
yeah thanks for watching the archive
jeremy
thank you patrick chamboise
the person who has the least wins at the
end must in your
i did say that
kiara you said the person who has the
least wins
at the end must in their followers
upstream and with fuel in as many
sentences as possible
oh my god guys
[Music]
wow okay i believe you i'm a genius peel
that's not how i meant it i that's
that's not how i meant it but that's
apparently how i said it
interesting real scammed by yourself
it's okay i had fun
[Laughter]
but well kelly says she never agreed to
the trims but she also never said no
she's not doing it she just kind of like
went along with it so
thinking that she probably would not
lose that will
[Music]
well oh my god did you just send another
sweat one i'm getting there soon
i'm getting there
[Music]
silence is not consent yeah that's why
i'm doing this right now
she seemed fun with it when you were
losing blue exactly exactly
exactly we are but once uh she was
actually the loser
it does seem wrong though because like
mostly i lost
first so it's weird how i ended up being
having more wins than her it's kind of
weird
she did it at the end she said it one
time that's not that's not how
that's not how it's supposed to be done
you're supposed to do it at the whole
follow-up stream but it's okay
it's okay it's okay i did it i think i
i'm taking the fall because it was my
idea anyway and i enjoyed it for y'all
[Music]
thank you all the sacrifices aren't
making our job in legal easy for y'all
we'll do it because we love you but
someday it's just
real so i do have a legal team where
were my lawyers when that killer was
following me
for your love 67.00
hope you had fun playing with me that
was lots of fun
thank you for joining the game
that was really lots of fun i enjoyed it
i want to do it again for y'all but next
time you got to follow the rules guys
you got to follow the rules
but that game was maybe more fun to me
than mario kart
because like i was better at it
it doesn't require so much skill for you
[Music]
i like it for you thank you for your
support for your love 67 are you going
to change your name after this stream
you can keep it for a while
[Music]
didn't get to join due to works that we
know but hopefully next time
for you and thank you for the stream for
your water for your puyo ira
thank you for you next time i'm sure you
can make it in
ice ice cream for you and
last refresh hopefully
oh where are we there we
are cows kfb analytics division
potential i have a riddle for you brian
a taco
a reaper and an orange onion walk into a
bar
ha when the detective looked through a
window she only saw an orange snake
wheel
what happened for you
well the onion ate the reaper in the
taco boil
[Music]
is that correct foil
i think i'm correct for you i can't
solve it
[Laughter]
i think i'm correct for you
i think i'm right for y'all
bloop the shack for you for yourself xp
your
don't you feel safe in this bubble isn't
it nice being in that bubble stop
complaining
stop complaining bloop
at least some pre-chatters agreed that
if you propose ending with wheel they
wouldn't be
they wouldn't have been able to resist
the cuteness wheel
but i don't understand the meaning of
that sentence but are we agreeing that
saying puyo at the end of each sentence
is cute for you
yes i agree we are looking for the blue
thank you for the red super chat thank
you we offer y'all for you for you for
your
i haven't done anything bad but can you
pretend to roast me like you did so do
you have less time for your
that was fun and don't forget to blow
for your ah
you want me to roast you well that's
just
well that's just disgusting that you're
into that kind of [\h__\h] brian
[Music]
and then you forced me to do that to you
please it's disgusting
yeah i thought you were like uh someone
with like politeness
and manners and respect for young
unbelievable
[\h__\h]
we are well guess what matters for you
and then come back to me for you
hmm
can you recommend me where i could add
for you in my name for you once again
thanks for the really fun stream for you
how about one year puyol
[Music]
you're making me emotional now for you
oh
please stand up spend time with us and
enjoy every moment we all love you and
messing with you
me emotional too for y'all
i love you for you i love you for you
so she knows here's some money to pay
for the new hard drive you'll need to
hold all of the
until you're rising screenshots
i just got a new pc it should have
enough space but thank you for your
opinion
tn250 are we gonna pull them out no
because after today
[Music]
no one will ever talk about this ever
again
[Music]
unless we play puyo puyo tetris again
there will be no appeal until the day
when the game comes back to us
[Music]
no more puyo i told you that's only for
one stream for you
why why would i make a pool emote when
i'm not saying puyo
you'll just have to get me to play puyo
for your tetris again
put your is banished for your yes
that's going to develop your own tick i
think it's too late for that for y'all
for you forever no no no
no no no no i can't suddenly start
talking like that forever that would be
so weird for y'all
[Music]
ever thank you love you guys please be
happy for you your kisses will always be
special so embarrassing
thank you for you oh bronx sent another
one
another one bronze
bronze player
[Music]
long super chat time for y'all you've
been my favorite since day one i
love you please and every stream i watch
i have a goofy grin on me
your bright energy and perseverant
person forever
use words that i understand i know i
know what it means but i don't know how
to say it
person percept the reds
pers i said
you know what i mean draw us in the best
thing you can do to repair us is have
fun and stay strong we all love you so
much not a cult for you
but but i know we all
know for your first surveillance i'll
get
real nope no
i i don't think i don't think it's
enough real
i don't think it's enough for you
you know you have to imagine like
ima you guys imagine like people
like you you live the normal chill life
and then suddenly you have hundreds and
thousands of people
like cheering you up and and
complimenting you and all that and then
there's like
hundreds of people sending you so much
so many super chats like
wouldn't that be like over overwhelming
wouldn't you want to thank them properly
like if
that's not something you're used to it's
hella weird like
it's just like i wish i could write
everyone like a letter or something
or like give them a hug or like i don't
know
and take them out for dinner
it's just uh
i mean first of all because of the
amount of people i can't thank you as
much as i want to
and second of all because of this you
know wall
of uh virtuality
it sounds pretty crazy right for you but
yet
yet again you sent me a red super chat
thank you so much for your
dinner i'm kind of hungry for y'all let
me take you out but yeah
please dinner i've been living off
crackers and ramen for moms why
why will
see i wish i could send you guys some
money
i wish i could donate some money to you
guys
for you dinner is on me for ya
[Music]
i mean one way maybe would be like
giveaways like the after the
rise at least i'm giving something back
to you guys for you
but that's only six people that i can
give something to
that's only six people who get a code
that's not enough i want to give uh
10 000 people atelier riser coat
for you
[Music]
voice pack yeah but that's not free
thank you bronx once again thank you so
much for your
i love you
[Music]
guys
i don't know what to say but you did
follow up with another red super chat so
i can react to that one properly
and only only oxen free thank you
i'm getting confused again for you
nathan prayed with another rent of the
chat thank you
[Music]
okay let's see what you say oh
f worded this up the first time wait you
didn't want to send an
empty one oh god
so you follow up with another red one
oh man that that hurts
uh i appreciate it i appreciate it
though
i wanted what i wanted to say was if you
want to thank us keeping working hard
and improving yourself enjoy your
honeymoon trip with kelly tell us all
about
once you're back i will and don't ever
stop rising from the ashes we are doing
you
oh my god you guys are so sweet
i'm crying for you
i'm gonna cry off
nathan is based for your frogs shut up
we are your base
too brian
shut up we are you are all based for yo
i don't i'm still not sure what it means
for y'all but you're all based
[Laughter]
thank you nathan thank you so much for
you
i will try my best to continue
delivering lots of content for you guys
you guys make me happy so much that i i
completely ditched my my lazy habits and
actually go go here to stream every day
it's just you guys make my day every day
i love it i love you last refresh made
me
let's see
where was i invited to keep getting more
and more and more i keep on refreshing
because i reached the end and in that
time you keep on sending more and more
and more
doctor jonathan i don't have a favorite
tetris piece i
don't like tetris because i keep on
losing
who you feel was easier crystal azura
club arrow
[Music]
at least i'm still respectful i'm
definitely not a cringe fan
no you're not you're not you're not a
cringe fan
that we are
[Music]
oh you once again went to stream snipe
and then destroy me
in another game do this i would have to
find a game that you're not good at
good at so that i can destroy you tell
me bryo
is there such a game for young
tell me i want to know is there a game
that you're not good at please i
wouldn't destroy you
i want to destroy you
no he's good at chess i'm sure of it i'm
bad at horror games
well me too bro
[Music]
thank you so much it is very crazy but i
appreciate your support very much
thank you so much for your generosity
for you
thank you bryon
save some money to make yourself some
christmas presents it's oh my god in
eight days it's
christmas breal in eight days it's
christmas
[Music]
in eight days it's [\h__\h] christmas for
you
holy macaroni for you
eight days until it's christmas can you
believe it for you
oh my god
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat just
saying just be yourself
real thank you we are trying for you i'm
trying for you
love thank you for your view
[Music]
thank you
also evil hintsu was writing during
super chat month ago a month ago
you wanted to get invited to invent so
how can we invite you
and you contact uh
[Music]
like conventions in your city who are in
a city that's
somewhere in your country yeah and you
tell them you want
the whole life english girls to come and
be invited
to that convention boy and then you tell
all your friends as well
to write them the same email for you
so that they know that there is a lot of
people who want that to happen for you
and i think it will work for y'all
because uh
youtubers are getting really popular and
i think
the conventions would see it
uh as quite the good possibility to
bring
in new customers i think we hope you'll
i i think it could really be a thing
in the future that youtube has become
guests at conventions i mean
luna uh was also a guest at uh some con
like it was kind of a online thing only
but
maybe in the future when when
conventions are
um normal again and not online
then we could actually like go i mean we
would probably
travel to that country and you can meet
us there
probably still over a screen but we will
be there
and maybe we can do like you know how
um uh holy life actually
uh whole life japan did something thank
you for the red superintendent thank you
whole life japan did something in japan
um
i think up until now only one time
though but they did something like where
you
um go
it's like it's like a handshake event
for idols for you
so how to explain that event
it's like you you you you buy a ticket
basically
you go there and you get into room one
one-on-one with uh for example back when
i send by
and they are they are on the screen but
they are there and they are talking to
you directly so you can actually like
have a one-on-one talk of them
so yeah that actually happened
they're doing it again uh soon i think
um ain't that risky no it's not risky i
mean there's obviously staff there and
the pers like we are we are in like on
the screen
so it's it's not risky or anything
but it's cool like you can you can
actually like have an actual
conversation with us
so i feel like when we would be guests
at conventions that could be a thing
um like a a virtual meet and greet but
we're like actually there
and we're gonna actually have
conversations with you one-on-one isn't
that awesome that would sound awesome i
think
i i wanna do it i wanna talk to you guys
one-on-one
i want to talk to you guys i love that
idea
i wish i could do that one time i want
to go to conventions all over the world
see that's
that's that's something where i feel
like i could finally thank you properly
in person like
one-on-one so i want to travel to lots
of conventions and be guests there and
do that with all of you i wanna
i wanna have meet and greets with you
guys
i won't be too scared what why
don't be scared it's a
once-in-a-lifetime chance probably
sounds safer than when guests mean means
friends in person i
agree with that i agree um
i have lied to whatever convention this
happens at for y'all
okay i'm waiting for you for you i want
to thank you properly please give me the
opportunity to thank you guys properly
awkward sounds from being shy you guys
know me
i want to make it awkward i will help
you
i'm the entertainer i'll make a i'll
make the conversation don't worry about
it
and you guys know you don't have to
worry when you talk to me
you know me you know my streams
i'm i'm the host of holotalk i'm a host
i can do this don't worry i'll i'll i'll
i'll leave the conversation for you
anyway i missed you thank you so much
thank you it's cute that we are real
grenades to your clipper next at least
then
well actually i've
been thinking of something regarding
that real
[Laughter]
wouldn't
[Music]
shall we make a mass picnic days just
tell us the time and place and we'll
arrange 600k
people to meet up i'll buy the drinks
you bring chicken for you
all righty for you all let's do it for
you
nathan pray before you
thank you keep flustering cali and we
good
i'll do my best for you
for your love 67 for you for you excited
for you
keep sleeping at good times um i've
i have uh the past few days i've slept
um before four a.m
around three a.m maximum at the latest
so i would say that's quite an
improvement i've kept that for quite a
few days now
um
i think i speak for everyone when i say
that the experiences you provide us
are worth more than gold if you want to
thank us properly then keep letting us
be part of the life
of an awesome verb i love you for you
thank you
thank you for your time
[Music]
for you thank you for the red super chat
you know tony has become one of my
favorite songs i had so much fun
learning how to play the guitar solo oh
are you playing the guitar nice that's a
really cool guitar solo right
i like that that part for the guitar
solo
really looking forward to any future
music you make thank you
the the guy who made the song go
he pretty much always puts in guitar
solos into his songs
pretty much always so i think if i make
a song with him again there's probably
gonna be a guitar solo again for y'all
look forward to it for y'all thank you
for your support roxy for you
thank you so much i'm glad you like the
song really i'm glad i'm happy
for your nexus for your video thank you
for your
thank you
thank you for the red super chat for you
kiana you're so funny oh thank you
and i love you and you make me laugh so
hard every time i watch you really
i'm funny i'm funny
i'm funny you hear that guys don't worry
about giving back the kfb benefits
package is plenty
right no complaints no complaints merry
christmas denture that's too early
are you guys in canada already
celebrating christmas for you
they celebrate thanksgiving like a month
before
america and now they celebrate christmas
like
eight days before america weird people
in canada
real thank you
merry christmas for your you weird
canadians
[Laughter]
i wanna go there now and celebrate
christmas early
y'all i love christmas for y'all i love
it
yes i'm seated up in my tree
very canadian christmas
oh canadians funny
merry christmas leaf boys
how can someone thank someone and roast
someone in the same dance sentence for
you
i wasn't roasting anyone
canada just feels different
canadians canadians are nice people i've
literally never
heard of a rude canadian ever before
canadians are also like in in like
netflix series and movies and stuff
canadians are always like depicted as
the good people
and the polite people isn't that great
for you
[Music]
there must be a reason why that is that
way for you
can canada too nice to be legit for you
[Music]
it can be polite and so nasty not not
not canadians are not nasty please
[Music]
now skyrim for your
thank you austin reynolds for your video
thank you guys for the sweet messages
for you all
swan fork for your boy why is this super
jet reading not over yeah what the hell
i have to refresh again last time for
real now
[Music]
just from being here and giving us joy
but if i make a personal request i would
like to get strangled and fake chicken
ties
[Music]
you can thank us once we take you to
your live stage yeah
one day for you
almost transformed a transparent blue
bouillabrillo first celery received in
my life this is my christmas present i
share to you
thank you brio also the christmas
present to myself well
thank you
jacqueline as long as you stay someone
who thinks like that i will support you
i wouldn't support someone who didn't
appreciate it
i love you for you okay that wasn't a
red one but you got kisses anyway
[Music]
it should be parallel if it's that close
to christmas it shouldn't be for you it
should be part of
that's kind of true
[Music]
he's having a surgery on christmas well
that just sucks for you
good luck for you oliver right thank you
for the red super chat boy
super saiyans are us thanking you for
the meaning you bring to our life so
just being you is definitely thanks
enough for you
no it's not for you no but thank you
thank you brio thank you so much for
your support for you
thank you thank you so much
i really really appreciate it thank you
with all my heart for you
chill santos for your native pride for
you for you
looking for the another red one whoa
whoa whoa whoa
is christmas already
[Laughter]
you've been in our shoes too wouldn't
you want your favorite idol to be happy
yeah but no
no need for so many super chats to make
me up happy i'm just happy to have you
guys watching me
for you want you thank you anyway i
really
appreciate it for y'all
well that's what kfb wants from you too
if you want to get something back like
live healthy that's not that's not gonna
happen
give you all singing streaming and i
hope dancing in 3d model soon yeah
looking forward to that day for you
thanks for the roast you're welcome for
y'all
thank you for your i'll do my best for
you
i think i think if i go back to
australia
real then i might cook more often i
think for you
and i'll probably
i think one reason why i order so much
ubereats at the moment is because i'm
not really close
to any like i i have to walk a little
quiet a little bit i mean it's not that
much but i'm so lazy like
yeah i have to walk a little bit if i
want to get to a restaurant or to a
convenience store
and cooking i
i don't know i'm too lazy and also i'm
like it's just
at the moment i know it's kind of weird
i'm probably overreacting but it just
creeps me out like
i don't feel very safe in my own house
right now
because i feel like the mice are like
eating everything
and um i feel like it's just not
hygienic
i don't know i don't like it and i'm
scared of um
i'm scared of using my stove because
it's a gas stove i know this is all
ridiculous it's just ridiculous
and i don't really feel comfortable here
it sucks
i want to move out i want to move out
but it's
like it it doesn't make sense to move
out for like
two and a half months when
like like i would have i would get
problems like
internet and stuff it took me it took me
a month to get internet working here
and i just recently moved here
and it was quite a lot of effort to move
here so
[Music]
moving with kelly no i don't want to
bother her for two months that's a long
time
we need our privacy as well
just it's just i just don't feel
comfortable here and that sucks i
one reason why i probably don't feel so
happy being here is because i don't feel
comfortable in the place where i live
and no one was gonna start crying
[Music]
and just two and a half more months
i'm just trying to get each day to end
soon
it's also sad because i feel like i'm
wasting
like i i could use each day so much
better but at the same time i want the
days to end quicker it sucks
[Music]
oh man it's okay we're gonna i'm gonna
go home soon
hopefully
[Music]
i forgot to mute myself
a bit more just a bit more just a bit
more
just a bit more
chicken snot
[Laughter]
there's a bit more
i usually the thing is like i
i i i lived abroad before
for like a long time longer than this
time
and i didn't feel homesick at all but i
also was just like
feeling um and like comfortable at where
i lived and
i just i didn't feel the homesick and
i'm usually not the type to feel
homesick
ever but this whole year i've been
feeling homesick
constantly because of the circumstances
i suppose but
yeah i i just always felt like i can't
go home early
because then i would waste the visa so
i've been pushing myself to just do it
until the end
even though i feel so uncomfortable here
sorry guys
sorry i'm i've been trying to just
ignore
like that state of mind
because i it's just really not much more
time left and i feel like i just have to
push for it it's not there's really not
much more time left though
i just i just have to like move forward
mm-hmm
[Music]
final fight oh wait this stream was so
much fun i don't want the archive to be
depressing
[Music]
thank you guys
now i yeah
thank you guys i'm reading the comments
thank you
love you too guys
it's just a bit longer
[Music]
just a bit longer ah the crowds are too
quick oh my god
oh my god thank you
i love you boy y'all i love you
will you
uh soon i will be back and then i'll
i'll reach
the perfect fulfilled happiness with my
cats
and and feel an amazing job and my
beautiful cats
that will just be the best i could ever
be
thank you guys for cats
i'm very young
[Music]
yeah and like
i guess i if you don't feel comfortable
in your own home but it's literally the
place where you are
24 7 because going outside is not much
of a thing and a work from home as well
then that can be a bit stressful
um oh my god the comments are so fast oh
my god
oh
put up more pickles i have a pick of the
wall scroll
on my on one of my walls which makes the
wall
look a little bit prettier yeah
thank you guys i love you
[Music]
lots of off collabs after the concert to
get out of your house
i guess i can do that i don't know it's
some
off collabs are quite a lot of fun but
and i just genuinely don't enjoy going
outside either
i don't enjoy being in here but i also
don't enjoy going outside
this is difficult
but the off collabs do take my mind off
i guess
[Music]
stop being hikakomori for [\h__\h] sake
i like being hikikomoni but the best
thing would be being hikikomoni with
cats around me
meowing constantly asking for food and
uh scratching on my chair and sleeping
on my keyboard
just annoying me the whole time oh yes
yes yes yes
that's the life i want to live
[Music]
okay let me continue reading those super
chats otherwise we'll never get done
here
claremont more real game for you
kill santos for you for your mood out
why did you change your name back the
stream didn't end yet
[Music]
mv737 you said i told you to stop
sending super chats with no text got
that and there you go again
thank you mb737
[Music]
guys i'm turning off the super chest now
because you guys don't stop
[Laughter]
and turning off okay
[Applause]
you guys just don't stop i'm turned off
done
[Laughter]
thank you all for your support guys
thank you
i feel the love i feel it
[Music]
oh what what what what what what what
what did i miss what am i missing
where where did i stop when did i stop
okay mb737
[Music]
next time you send a red super chat
would you be so kind
to add some kind of text there like
something you always wanted to tell me
or a question you always wanted to ask
me just so that i can have a
proper conversation and thank you
properly please
i love you very much thank you for your
support
[Music]
also nothing much i can reply to in that
super chat but thank you i appreciate it
you're very generous thank you
thank you i'm so blessed to have you
guys what would i do without you guys
i'm moving soon and maybe i'll miss my
old house because i lived in my house
for 12 years
that might be but when i moved out for
the first time
i felt very happy in my new place it was
exciting
it can totally be exciting but there are
can also be a case where it's not so
exciting but i think you got to be open
to it and i mean as long as you don't
live in a in a house that's falling
apart and
filled with mice that uh
try to eat your food then you might be
fine
[Music]
adam rivera for you thank you for the
membership
coffee make alright you just renewed
thank you you hatched
congratulations well there i put you up
for young god i just want to hug you now
right i want to hug you too
all of you i hope our love can make your
days a bit more comfortable it
definitely helps me
to get over that period of time
it helps me a lot because it keeps my
days filled otherwise my days would be
so empty and i would just like
hide until under my covers like 24
7 and hope that it's all over soon
so you guys are definitely the reason
why i'm
keeping my sanity
for y'all really thank you so much for
being there and giving me a place to be
for you
thank you for you
[Music]
thank you for the membership welcome new
egg boy
[Music]
thank you you also changed your name for
you
right patrick chen
for you for you have a tissue in the
hook thank you you've been constantly
pushing yourself to do your best but now
you're seeing what's truly important to
you
my cats but i already knew that for
y'all i already knew that
what are you talking about talking about
something different
are you talking about something else
am i supposed to say you guys are truly
important to me
[Music]
no no no four cats that's right that is
truly important to me becoming the
ultimate cat lady that's that's
important to me hats no cats cats not
hats
hats are important to me as well because
otherwise i feel naked yeah that's true
[Music]
ultimate hat lady no ultimate cat cats
and hats well that is the ultimate
combination
oh thank you guys
cat hats lady hats and cats hats and
cats cats and hats
[Music]
brandon
a hotel nah because like
like i would probably feel more
comfortable in the hotel than in my home
but like i wouldn't have stable internet
and i would have to bring all my
equipment over there usually it doesn't
have as much space as this house has
blah blah blah so yeah
it's just like i couldn't i couldn't
really do proper work
in a hotel just has terrible internet
yeah and also then i have the problem
again with noise
because um they can kick me out if i'm
too noisy especially at night
they can just kick me out like that it's
not not not really a solution i guess
real
[Music]
i mean i've i've been in i've i've been
in quite a few hotels in japan and the
walls
in hotels and the ones i stayed in
seem a bit thicker than normal
apartments in japan
but still at the in the night it would
probably be a bad choice
book a study at cover corbin two months
and lived there ah that's not good
that's not gonna work no
no no no no no the studios are busy busy
busy
men's
oh you know when i when i lived with my
cats before i came to japan
i was uh i had the struggle of uh you
know
like having cat hair everywhere so when
i wash my face
and wash my hands five seconds later i
would have
hair everywhere again like in my eye i
would usually
sometimes i have cut hair in my eye and
that
hurts so much and you try to somehow get
it out of there but
you have hairs everywhere in your on
your fingers so i try to wash my hands
again
and there's always hairs on the towels
always you literally can't get rid of it
you wash the stuff in the washing
machine
you get it out and there's still hair on
there and you try to get rid of it with
those like
with those rollers uh the the sticky
rollers and stuff
but it doesn't get rid of everything
completely but you know what
i accept that kind of life i accept that
life it's okay
i i like it i like being a hairy cat
they're both short hair ah okay probably
for short
short fur cats it's not that bad but
mine are both uh
long hair cats and they shed a lot
they're so fluffy they have so much hair
it goes everywhere it's everywhere
literally everywhere
it's an added layer of warmth exactly
sounds fluffy very fluffy bald your cats
no
i would never do such a thing i love the
fluffiness that's why i love cats
fluffy cats bad cats yay fluffy cat
you make you can make two cats out of
every cat's fur
you gotta brush them i do i do
oh man i remember brushing my cats
one of them doesn't like it so much but
the other one enjoys it very much it's
just so much fun brushing her
she goes like
she goes like that
[Music]
did that sound like purring to you
it's a good furry noise yay sounds like
a motorcycle
well yeah my cat does sound like a
motorcycle sometimes
i've been totally like slacking off of
slacking on those pools
[Music]
for you yeah thank you typhon
i said it before these real moments are
what makes your connection with
us special oh we love you
we love you keeping you and we'll do
what we can help
thank you for your thank you just just
stay with me
stay with me and watch my streams so
that i
have some company until i go back home
and then after that i would appreciate
it if you say it as well
they do take my mind off of it yeah
thank you
for making your pure love 67
for your bro thank you for the red super
chat
we're all here for you and if you need
to rent go for it we can't do too much
but we can listen thank you for you
thank you thank you i love you for you
you trevor jim for you
go visit some cat cafes oh but it's just
different those cats there
they are so used to so many strangers
coming in
every day and leaving after a few hours
they're so used to it they don't care
about the people there
i gotta make friends with some whole
life member that has a cat
[Laughter]
they are like normal cats not the ones
in the cackle phase they are much more
open to interaction with humans
a great tangent stream this is not a
tangent stream
this is nice
[Music]
senpai already offered me to visit her
and then check out her cat
she already offered me she told me that
her cat is uh quite open to
strangers so i might want to do a half
collab with fubukki soon
very soon thank you for bookie friend
senpai
i didn't want to say this but i feel
this is relevant i got to see recently
recently i can't read the cr that scene
recently so i'm off healthcare awake and
in quarantine i find by the way for
christmas so i understand where you're
coming from
oh damn i hope you'll be
uh healthy again soon but since it's not
so bad for you apparently
that's good that's good
[Music]
oh man gotta be careful right
everyone seems to be getting it please
be careful and um
take it easy while you're in quarantine
keep on watching my streams
it's actually very good daddy that you
have so much time to watch my stream so
you can't miss them
but i hope you get better soon
[Music]
and i think that's it
yep okay okay okay that's it okay okay
we're done we're done we're done
this was supposed to be a short stream
what how did we end up doing three hours
one hour gameplay two hours super chat
reading god damn it
[Music]
will i be productive today um
i don't want to
[Music]
i should be productive
but i feel like like one if i stream on
one day i feel like
my brain goes like okay i already was
productive today
i can't do any more so every day i
streamed
that's all i can do for that day
i need a full day of no streams in order
to be able to actually do
anything of my other tasks i mean for
you
sleeping is productive rest is
productive yeah but i got other stuff to
do for you
take more days off from streaming for
you i can't for you
i want to stream more i want to stream
but i also need
i'm basically by streaming i'm basically
procrastinating from doing the stuff
that i have to do
as well so i'm procrastinating right now
but it's a good it's a good excuse i
mean this is my job now so it's not like
i'm procrastinating i'm being product
i'm doing my job okay
i'm doing my job it's not like i'm
procrastinating
not at all i have to do this oh i just
don't have time to do the things i need
to do
i don't have time because i have to work
i mean i have to stream i got i got so
many streams
i mean i'm making the schedule by myself
but i mean i
i have to stream i i have to i have i
have to
looking for excuses for my own decisions
in life
[Music]
foreign
what do you stream tomorrow yes i have a
fire emblem stream coming up tomorrow
translated to yes i basically just said
what i said in english in japan
a japanese song i just said the same
thing
is
all right guys
yeah i also thought i'd just do a quick
one well there we go it's been three
hours
a quick stream doesn't exist in my
universe unless i
i could have done this stream without
super chat reading and then it would
have been a short one
alright guys thank you so much for
watching today thank you for being by my
side
i love you all very very much
please everyone come to the fire emblem
stream
thank you everyone and enjoy german we
say afrida
[Music]
i don't want any of you to use this word
ever again after the stream unless i
tell you to do so
no more after the stream
bye
[Music]
i love you good night i'm not gonna
sleep yet but maybe you're gonna sleep
good night if you're sleeping
happy nothing of industry
i love you mwah i love you
oh
i love you
[Music]
love you love you love you love you love
you love you love you love you
love you
[Music]
so much love in here
see you soon
[Music]
you