[Music]
R feel it right me
B
[Music]
oh honey
feel it
me
intoxicating DJ keep playing
[Music]
dancing so
OT B
[Music]
B feel it rush through me
feel
it feel it through me
[Music]
honey I'm so badly
prepared because I had no time
I'm
sorry but we're still going to have fun
I know my echo is on because I'm just
going to going to going to start and
sing uh right away but
my I currently have my gloves off
because
they need to charge a little bit more it
seems which is okay we'll give them some
[Music]
time oh my chat is not working up the
wall wait the usual trick how are you
guys but
wow
really this is not window
capture
whatever yeah you're diagonal you like
it I'm just going to leave you there it
look so
stupid
why somebody put a
CSS into my hashtag on Twitter
yesterday I I didn't try it but would
that fix it tilt
controls is what even is that is that
just the same CSS that I normally use
It's A New Perspective I like it well
fourth anniversary means New Perspective
I
guess okay may maybe I'll try that
CSS if I can find it right
away Moo Can you send it to me on
Twitter one more
time chat is breaking Dimensions not
quite a a new point of view
well well well let me turn this off come
on come on my my arms are my hands are
connected to a cable and they're in
gloves so turning this off on the touch
screen is really
difficult oopsy I accidentally muted
myself that's great we love this
SCU love the SCU you hear me now and the
Reverb is gone that's that's better
maybe for the beginning why why do I
keep on moving over there hey did you
miss this fever Knight version of myself
did you miss that I put on the
freckles I put the freckles
on I'm refreshing my Twitter but I'm not
seeing the I'm not saying the freaking
CSS moon
dog where
why is it not refreshing or is there's
just nothing there freckles killed thank
you your hands are
wrong no they're not but they're just
off right
now there's nothing wrong with
them don't hate on
them was was my was my was my request
not click can you send me the CSS if I
want to see if it does something or is
it just useless
T-Rex
hands no they're not that small they do
we wrong
e no they're not wrong the thumb is on
the inside I mean it's kind of it looks
kind of long but no it's not wrong
they're just bent towards the inside
right
now
Italiano Italiano oh sorry I'm squeezing
my boobs so
hard uh okay thank you how come how come
Ari sends me this and not moon
dog what is this though is this going to
like hack my
OBS what is
this I've been sent a chat SS CSS let's
see let's see if it fixes
it is it just the same
hello chat it broke it even
more it made it
invisible well was that on
purpose
ah is the color wait is this the is the
is the font color
transparent I I don't know I can't
tell well I brought you back at least in
this form
whatever this is
fine ah the [\h__\h] did I just do oopsy
H yeah okay so at least you're behind
the at least you're behind there you're
breaking
dimensions a little bit here I'll cut it
off there
keep that that was funny that's not
funny nothing's funny okay so sorry I'm
like a total mess right now but uh we're
doing a little bit of a k okay uh I'm
not going to dance Too Much I'm sorry to
kill your expectations but I don't have
Wess mic or headphones right now and um
yeah it's difficult to do it without and
but I'm going to stand up maybe a little
bit and then you see my twerk skills
once's again it's going to make you
happy and we're going to reveal
the color
variant of uh this outfit and then and
then we're going to look at things from
from you guys that you sent
me uh and then I'm going to read a
letter that I didn't couldn't finish
writing so at some point it will become
freestyle
probably but yeah let's just uh sing a
little bit for now otherwise I'm going
to lose my mind from the stress right
now I'm sorry I'm really stressed out
but one thing I want to say is that this
is not really my anniversary
stream well it kind of is but not really
I don't I will have a better proper
3D uh concert it will be like a little
bit late but it's on its way it has been
recorded it's currently in the editing
uh stage so yeah so I was thinking I
haven't sung a remix version of hotor in
a while so I was wondering maybe I
should do that also do you do we want to
save my hands are ready to I mean they
definitely not
full they're definitely not
[Music]
full but let's turn them on again cuz
you guys are making fun of my T-rex
hands it's not funny it's not
funny just one of the hot remixes
oh this one started oh okay ah there we
go yay yay y
yay now I can
sing here I think this might be the
least appreciated one even though you
should appreciate it so let's sing this
one let's see if I remember where to
sing
ah think
[Music]
now
to tell me I can hear it clearly tell
[Music]
I will live to keep on fighting
till
[Music]
the I love this
remix my mic
[Music]
answer don't break I will never give up
and
TR at break of day I've been trying to
find my
destiny but they keep pushing and
pulling me
astray if I go wrong with the wait me in
the could you tell me please where I
need
to do I sing in this part don't
remember it clearly
[Music]
and flam show me thep Lance and in the
next I promise I will find
you cat H in my mouth but I got I got
freaking gloves
how am I going to get rid of
that think
no
e maybe it's gone is
it h should I just r drink some water
and then pretend it was never there oh
God I don't like
knowingly choking down CH chugging
down cat hair I don't like to knowingly
do
it which might callor you surprised but
I I don't usually intend to do
that but it is time I'm going to do
it m
M
wonderful who said who said who said oh
my God she's so
cute you said that oen I squired up
because
that thank
you well let me I haven't stood up yet
well let me show you where all is a
reminder a grim reminder about how cute
I
am
[Laughter]
cable sorry you will you will not mind
that will you
yay she's back with the booty she's so
back yippe why am I like all the way
over here
always Maybe like this
hey look at those shiny FS
Yahoo y let's work
out squat how's my
form is there a form at
all but I I look I look like I got a bad
form but I don't even know it's a good
form my my eye tracking won't hold up
there keep back straight right like it
looks it doesn't look that but but see
what happens when I just stretch out my
arms
something's just
automatically leaning
forward even though I'm not so don't
trust it completely my form is incorrect
[Music]
sorry I'm listening to cat's ey these
days a cute new K-pop ey group made up
by by people from all over the
world they have this
Coro where you do this crotch
movement and then they do
[Music]
this which I don't understand but
there's just so many crutch emphasizing
movements and then they do a kiky kick
but this doesn't work with my
trackers Hips Don't Lie thank you they
have this cute coo How does it
go they kind of like Lean
Forward does this and then they they
step they
stomp which one maybe I think the outer
one but it doesn't translate so well in
this motion tracking T and
[Music]
then and then they do this they stand
next to each other really close and then
they have uh another member's face here
and then they they all like the next the
person on this side will have their hand
like this for me and then they go like t
t t
that's yeah okay sorry I really like cat
eye you probably are not even listening
to what I'm
saying should we s sing another song but
I'm not going to dance cuz it's going to
kill
me
yeah I'm just gonna I'm just
gonna
Vibe I just need lyrics Here Sparks
K
Ki
lyrics okay here we go uh let's turn
this on again DJ Turn on the Reverb go
Mr DJ Turn on the
Reverb Wrong
song I hope it's not too loud or
so hey
I don't
remember L down on the floor L and you
don't know don't know don't know what to
do how you tell what's wrong what's
right if or no don't know don't know
what to do the storm hits and you losing
the way just take a chance and dance on
the rain cuz you got the king throw it
away don't forget don't forget what I
said get out of your head life is only
what you make it you're going to be
okay so go ahead and do it do it if you
want it let it
[Music]
everybody
night just your own way don't be afraid
just High your head and again keep up
keep up and never be afraid make
it it up
against the flam the fire
to just your own way looking take theane
now the driver seats they
just going so bad that it shouldn't beow
how we like it heard what I
said out of your head only what you make
it
[Music]
just just go your own way so don't be
afraid just to high your head again up
keep up and never be
afraid let go of the past tonight choose
the future we
Define to you from thees
[Music]
[Applause]
don't your own way
be
head keep never be afraid make
[Applause]
it the table to theet of
your the
fire today go go just go your own
[Music]
[Applause]
way
SP I have lit a
fire someone called the the fire
department
pleas oh no Tak the fire starter did it
once again
oh Reverb
okay
microphone sorry
sorry yeah even bouncing around a little
bit while singing loudly is
difficult can you tell
YY it's so hot in this
outfit so hot I should take off the the
sweater right and the leggings and
everything invisible chair
so y
guys only W songs by the way I have
decided the the the theme is only
takanasi Kiara song sorry if that is
disappointing ah sorry I'm moving the
microphone around a lot and it's not
liking
it freckles cute yippe I'm glad you
think so only W retrospective you want
to hear
Retros
but that's fine that's fine but I think
retrospective perhaps color-wise
suits the other other color variation
was so shall I show
you the other color
H well if you are a curious little
potato chicken then you might have
already seen it it's not
like like hidden
secretly in some kind of Bunker no no no
no here let me get it for you ch
[Music]
oh I'm going to get copyright strike we
wouldn't want that when I load this
model by default it is not wearing a
jacket let me just put one on really
quickly boobs bigger toggle boobs
smaller toggle mm interesting honestly
maybe
yeah f b
toggle mhm thank
you jacket on
toggle freckles there's some other
toggles like a butt a bigger toggle but
I'm not going to turn that on I think
it's already pretty big are you
ready color variation time taada
[Music]
okay it's the suit is now shiny H the
the leotard it wasn't shiny before and
we have instead of shiny leggings we now
have
um can you
tell fishnet fish nuts let's [\h__\h]
go which is something I did want for the
live Tod version too I'm working on it
they didn't accept my request before but
now now we have it oh my God where's my
mouse
here oh actually I don't really like the
I can turn those off too I saw them
somewhere
[Music]
um where are
they where' they
go eyes BR jacket uh it's
gone dar
what's this
oh well now I can't find it so I guess
this is fine the shiny the shiny
socks they're like
jelly but yes do you want to see the
difference okay here here is my butt uh
here is my butt toggle let me just show
you the
Butt YouTube Don't ban me
off
[Laughter]
on I think we I mean come on come
on come
on we don't need that right Chad yeah
I'm talking to you do we need this I
think it's it's
no it's fine without I I like it it's
cute it's cute but this is without um no
it's with with a thigh um enh hands here
look before after
see
before
after I like this
version and then
there's look
it's exploding like I can't even wear
the
sweater the boobies
normal big big
tatas they're already big I actually
have the Boop smaller toggle on oh yeah
wait if I turn that off is it even
bigger I no
holy if I turn the small toggle off and
then turn the boobs bigger togg on then
it doesn't go through the sweater oh my
God
balloons no no no no I don't wish to
defone crony I I'm I'm I hear
this they're still big even though the
smaller toggle is
on okay and
then okay yeah
y
y this is
[Music]
y oh they're kind of pressed in maybe
it's better if they're not
smaller what do you
say I don't know why I'm even asking you
I don't know why I'm asking
you but yay Black version Look at that
here I can see my belly
button nice belly
button you
happy
what bunny ears yeah bunny ears would be
cute right like shiny leather bunny ears
but I mean this is kind of you know
bunny ears ribbon a little
bit jumping
Jacks jumping jack jump [\h__\h] jumping
jacks he wants [\h__\h] jumping jacks all
right you'll get some [\h__\h] jumping
jacks here I go how do you do them
again one two three four 5 6 7 8 9 10
actually 11 cuz I I didn't count
one well let's
sing invisible
chair
[Music]
y
yay
okay we will now sing a very deep song a
deep insightful song
stop moving should I put my sweater on
you're probably going to say no why am I
asking
you celebrates takana 4 years
anniversary celebrate or cry about
it in
retrospective all right
oh baby I'm looking at what remains I
couldn't tell you the same I guess
that's
alive if you couldn't tell by now I'm
hopelessly waiting begging all night to
break
through stuck in an endless loop I'll
deny the truth asking why
scream I can't
redo the past and PR calls me to truth
and every part of my being doubts the
best feeling so tell me what am I to
you I can't
renew the part of me I lost it
The View hooked up on all the way ring
eyes leads me
paral taking two steps back I keep
moving
[Music]
on concern is filling up your lies once
again I'm mobile broken now save me
if I can let it go let it go Brea again
tell by now I'm hopelessly wasting away
to the core
inside it keeps
eating away at me every day asking why I
scream I can't
reduce the past and present call me to
true love and every part of my being
doubts the best feeling so tell me what
am I to
you I can't R new H me I lost it the F
hooked up on all the waving eyes leaves
me
paralyzed taking to
but I keep moving
on and I tried to change me but my mind
can just eras me anym than I have
already done and looking back I'm ready
to admit that it was all me who
destroy everything I
am caught up in Mighty mind
the doubt puts out my
life I can't be sure of who I am or when
I'm a
lion I can't
redo the past and present calls me to
[Music]
oh my H is going to come
up you got cat
[Music]
bang where are we right
now turning
[Music]
that
was uh
retrospective very
dramatic yes
yes did you like that that is a song
from my album takanasi Kiana point of
view POV album I think link is in the
description um so ooh
I
see sorry I got
distracted
stpv
yay y it's just uh testing physics if if
I can carry
them not with these arms I guess just
with my
elbows kind of but
[Laughter]
[Music]
I can carry it myself no FK you I carry
my own groceries my own
milk all right let's sing something more
uh like something that will clean us
because um we we are all just
no let's just sing something that will
cleanse us
[Music]
come on out oh it was already
on should I walk while I'm singing this
but the mic is so
low I'll try the
[Music]
along passing by
Heroes I couldn't
find the reason why
who I am you could have known stack in
the
ruins my disillusion
scrr in between the
reality my own
desire Keeps Me To
You O moving faster than the
LI I'm in the absence alone looking
back did I lose my way I can see the day
when I can reach you again then can I
let go I can hear your voice leading me
through the fade
away to the
bra it's just I'm walking by the Light
FL before my eyes alone the silence
steing still I'm reaching out to you
come surise to lie I tell myself so
ivive one day eventually the it will
lead me back to you see
me I am the
[Music]
Wonder I am
faith is gone the well is
dry no more
believing just
deceiving ooh feel the daylight on
theed I can't feel that fall back I'm to
deep I lose my way can see the day when
I can reach you again then can I let go
I can hear you Bo living through the bo
fade
away to the
gra I'm walking by the ls are Flash
before my eyes alone the sounding still
I'm reaching out to you
the the I tell my so I survive one day
eventually the light it will lead me
back to you'll see me da da da da
o I am the
[Music]
one I am that Wonder
uh I know
[Music]
man
awkward
[Music]
sorry Ollie's laughing Ollie hey what's
up ol
live she kept me she kept me
spending spending all your money on
spending on say it ol say
what say my name my
name what what the hell did she
say I I didn't see her coming no
balls what why Ollie
what is she
saying what Ollie is say so excuse
her sleep
[Music]
talking I didn't I I'm looking at the
chat I just can't see her am I missing
it or is she just not writing right
now I want to sing sleep
talking if I say what's on my mind well
tell me what's on your
mind am I on your mind I mean if
anything I'm on your mind right and
that's okay to say I'm on I'm on
everybody's mind who's here right
now say it say it say
it I shall sing this for you
guys this is for you it's been a long
day you call me you got me sleep
s don't know what to do don't know what
to do for me boy I'm up late already H
midnight convince myself I'm doing all
right but you know taking one step
taking one back when you text me saying
no way no fair no fair no fair your eyes
they telling me come here now I can't
wait your body got me talking breath as
you got me one
oh baby don't you know got me I'm hooked
I breathing you in I just can't Forget
for you got me stress I'm just wanting
[Music]
in you got me sleep talking in my dreams
I'm sleep talking all these nights it's
you no more hiding it not not caught up
in your B sleep talking in my dreams I'm
sleep talking all this night to you you
getting me sleep sleep
[Music]
you got me all day I'm sleeping in my
dreams I just hear your voice I ain't
got a choice that yeah just like that
baby you might never know hey don't you
leave me alone I'm waiting head on the
phone so baby you just going to make a
call and I know if you really all in it
give it to me now boy your body got me
talking breath you got me wanting oh
baby don't you know got me a hook to go
God this song leaves no room to breathe
I oh baby that's what you
do you got me S sucking in my dreams I'm
sleep talking all these night it's you
no more hiding it n n CAU up in your bit
sleep talking in my dreams I'm sleep
talking all these nights at you you get
sleep sleep talking all day talking in
the night yeah sleep talking oh that's
right yeah BM BM BM
sleep talking in the night yeah sleeping
all that's right
yeah you going make me sleep every day
hello baby who are you talking
to yeah if you want you got to do you
just so don't
pretend
hello baby who are you talking to ooh
it's the moment I can't
escape I can't deny
oh it's
you who made me this
way in my dreams I'm sleep ducking all
these nights it's you no more hiding in
C up in your B sleep fcking in my dreams
I'm sleep fcking all these nights it's
you you me sleep sleep talking all sleep
talking in the night sleep talking
that's right
now you got me feeling so sleep talking
in the night yeah sleep talking oh
that's
[Music]
right you make
S why do they write these songs with no
breathing room
Mama Mia can't [\h__\h] breathe
y sleep
[Music]
talking I [\h__\h] love the song I
freaking love
it thank you
chat it's my song yeah so
what it is it is quite
the heart challenge
nostalgic heart
container let's go my second original
song from what 2021 Valentine's Day
remember it's
[Applause]
[Music]
y all this hand's broken
oh both hands are de now
[Music]
[Applause]
me
[Music]
w
wow okay
[Music]
I realiz it was still loud
hold is this the r
[Music]
[Applause]
letter for
[Music]
[Applause]
I need to tell you that I love you
[Music]
and there's no one else in this world
that I would trade for you
get it get
[Music]
it
fore
[Music]
speee yay
okay I so
fun her
Challenger is so
fun haven't challenged your heart in a
while all right guys we're gonna
take a little break
to play some
bgm although maybe not bgm yet because
I'm going to well I'll I'll put some bgm
just in
[Music]
case which one which
one which one which one it's going to
be it's going to be time for
M some gifts although there's one really
long one I'm not sure if I should watch
the whole thing on
stream
but
maybe maybe
um how about this oh no that's not
that's not at all what I
expected how about this
[Music]
oh
yeah okay so I asked manager
Chan to put it into a
folder so that I don't like Pro like
immediately see it so I got a couple of
videos um one of them is like a big kfp
fan
project video I think
and the rest I think are smaller
videos so I would
probably start with that the smaller
ones yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah here's
here's the one my downloads folder
always loads so slowly unless I like
type in something that I'm looking
for what's the folder that I downloaded
called oh I don't [\h__\h] know
I don't know but I'm going to throw them
into OBS and we're going to watch them
together but each time I'll have to
adjust the audio for it cuz I didn't put
it in there yet because I didn't want
to didn't want to spoil it myself by
accidentally playing
it which just always automatically
happens why the hell is this did I
not uh unleash the videos yet here they
are okay
oh what is this what is all of
this okay okay okay we'll start with
this one where I already kind of saw the
face but like I'm not sure like I just
saw it for a moment and I wasn't 100%
sure what I was
seeing stop okay this is one of those
videos you know that you get like you
know from cool
people um thank you Doug hood for
getting this
one I wonder who this is a cameo yeah
yeah yeah that's what I mean that's what
I mean okay we're going to do monitor
[Music]
only who is this who is this going to
be
right sorry my hands are broken now but
it's okay let's go
there's a pretty long like spoiler
thingy so that I don't get spoiled
immediately but I I got spoiled by this
one
anyway that's pretty long
now that's it's so
long
um that's that's pretty long
is it is it going to be like one minute
in let me
skip okay who was
that I didn't
look it's coming it's coming it's like 1
minute in I
think hey Kiara it's Jordan CLA Robbins
from the Umbrella Academy Doug reached
out and told me wait is she the all
about all the amazing work you're doing
uh with your streaming on YouTube and
all of your kfp all of your fans um who
enjoy your content um and I just wanted
to send you a little note to say happy
fouryear
anniversary um very uh that's a lot of
work a lot of devotion and dedication
and time and
energy um I know that I struggle so much
to make content all the time so um to to
have the
consistency and um the passion to build
something like this and show up for four
years and build such a a loyal and
dedicated fan base is no small feed it's
a very big deal and it's um very much
worth a celebration so so proud of you
so excited for you so happy for you
congratulations happy
anniversary um I hear that you have been
very busy traveling for work which is so
exciting I love when I get to travel for
work um obviously it's a sign you're
doing all of the right things and all
the opportunities are coming and will
keep coming um and that you have to
start watching the latest season of The
Umbrella Academy on the plane that is
amazing I did I finished it already um I
personally love watching movies and
shows on planes um something about being
up in the air makes me feel really
connected to it and really emotional and
and really um present I guess
from the other type of technology or
something but I think that's actually a
really fitting way to enjoy it and makes
me really happy um that you found the
time and found the moment to to be able
to take it in and I hope you've really
enjoyed it um it's been such an honor to
get to be a part of the show and um it
means the world that you supporter of
Umbrella Academy that you love it um as
much as we loved making it that's the
only reason why you're not getting me
grateful for your support in general um
congratulations happy anniversary keep
up the good work you're so
incredible can't wait to see all the
things you accomplish in your future
this is your fourth your fourth
anniversary of many many many I'm sure
um kfp loves you and uh and they're
lucky to have you and uh just sending
you all of the happy Vibes for more
success in your future lots of love
she's a yapper Jordan Claire Robins
gorgeous
she yapped a lot didn't expect her to
Yap so much thank you he
y'
y'all just like me I wasn't sure because
like in the show she looks quite
different cuz she wears a a a blonde wig
and all that um and she wears like
completely different kind of clothing so
I didn't recognize her right away but
when she said Umbrella Academy I was
like oh wait she looks like the she
looks like the mom the Android
mom a I just finished watching the
newest season it was really good I wish
it was like one or two more episodes
but yeah that's so
cool yeah I did really like her in the
show she was so
rotic kids please do not turn me off yet
please
or
else I love you very much in my
heart I keep on zooming over here
today A well thank you so much for that
one there's uh a bunch more uh there's
one two three four in total of these
cameos can't wait to see well that
is Shakira wait what why Shakira but the
fun makes me think it's another Lord of
of the Rings related one I'm going to
die I'm going to
perish okay are you ready for this what
what what you you you probably you guys
could have already watched it if you um
went on Twitter for the
hashtag sh Wait it's not
Shakira there's no [\h__\h] way like what
what okay let's skip two a minute or
so wait did I I don't remember did I
just switch to audio or did I not do it
yeah I did
okay who is this help me out right away
if I'm not recognizing them because
that's
embarrassing just Spam it in the
chat and then I pretend I I knew
already what if it's Shakira if it's
Shakira I will recognize
her it's about to start it's about to
start
it's
Kira Kira is your
anniversary very important very
important day it's me by the way it's
Billy boy p pipp and to here to wish you
a happy fourth anniversary anniversary
of your um your your you streaming stuff
he always talks like this amazing not
very up on the words St use
anniversary very important very
important day it's me by the way it's
Billy Bo pip and here we wish you a
happy fourth anniversary of your um your
your your streaming stuff sorry I'm not
very up on the words to use that's okay
but I hear that you've already had some
wise gamji and even the ring bearer but
this year you've reached the very top of
the mountain as one of the tkes tell you
happy anniversary we' had four years yes
what about the second four years well
they're coming up and they're going to
be amazing I tell you who send you lots
of love Doug who says you are absolutely
amazing amazing person incredible singer
wonderful dancer seems like you've got
everything going on anyway k I just want
to send you some love and remind you
please as a little gift to yourself have
a lovely second breakfast for your
fourth anniversary a second what could
be nicer anything you want in fact I get
Doug to organize it if he's not around
they could send you the money what or
get it delivered I would suggest having
mushrooms in it no delicious I hate
mushrooms anyway happy happy anniversary
Kira I hope this year is your favorite
ever and I hope you get that second
breakfast Doug is sending you so much
love and so is a full of a to have a
great one happy anniversary anniversary
anniversary I'll remember that Billy boy
wow those hits are freaking everywhere
maybe it's maybe it's the accent I mean
of course it's the accent
right I mean
it's like he he just deleted the a in
Kiara kiar K Kira Kiara I think there's
there's people called Kiara K
Kiara like on that island there right so
like it's not such an uncommon name I
think you don't say it
Kira I don't believe it
That's funny
though for
Shakira yeah Kira is short for
Shakira oh my God
can't did I not get this be is this a
second I just like looked at the
thumbnail of the next one and I'm
like didn't we get one from him before
that that isn't that font already giving
it
away isn't that gimma girl's
font but didn't we get one of this guy
uh last year maybe it's a second one
maybe he wanted to say hello
again okay well anyway I'm definitely
collecting my load of the Rings actors
is there is there more on Cameo we got
to catch them all thank you so much
freaking
Pippin all right let's go where are
we uh one minute one
minute it's about to
start happy birthday to you happy
birthday to you
happy fourth
streaming anniversary my
dear that's
exciting isn't it you don't mean it
however Doug reached out and asked me to
wear a chicken suit and be a background
dancer in your music video I'm sorry
dear but that's a hard pass of course it
is there's not enough money in the
world for to do that but happy for
streaming best thank
[Music]
you yeah this one you know I love gim
girls so that's that one from gim girls
Michelle he's the um like Hotel
receptionist who is not in a mood for
work at any day at any given day it's
amazing amazing character amazing
actor yeah what what what did he
say happy fourth
streaming anniversary my
dear that's
exciting isn't
it however Doug reached out and asked me
to wear a chicken suit and be a
background dancer in your music video
I'm sorry dear but that's a hard pass
there's not enough money in the world
for Mich to do that but happy fourth
streaming all the best Happ for
streaming nah 100% understandable thank
you Michelle I love him he's so in
character he's so in character he's just
not in the mood happy for
streaming indeed it is to I have been
streaming out
take I'll take for special ah for the
same guy I did not make it clear that
birthday is different from streaming
anniversary ah sweet person R did the
message for free for free so so sweet
what a deal this is the original message
oh ah oh you must have wished me happy
birthday well wish I'll take that as
well
go here we go again fourth birthday
isn't that excting
what's up here he references that he's
talked to me before I suppose he
realizes Here We Go Again fourth
birthday isn't that exciting what's
happening today live from Portugal
Michelle is traveling the world yes once
again I had to refuse
Doug to wear a chicken
suit and dance in the background on your
music in your music video you I'm sure
you understand this is just not
possible you know as much as I love you
this is just not going to happen but
yeah have a wonderful birthday much much
love thank
you for the second time ah so he
rejected us twice he does not want to be
a backup back dancer that's okay that's
okay I understand I will give up
okay a Michelle well thank you so much
we got Kil girls we got Umbrella Academy
we got Lord of the Rings whoa damn okay
that's exciting I love getting Cameo
videos even though they're getting paid
for it so you know how genuine can it be
but it's still makes you happy
right but honestly like um I feel like
Pippen he's he's pretty pretty he's just
confused he's genuine but he's confused
and then the
lady she was
like yapping so much so she she takes it
seriously and Michelle he's just in
character so that's you know okay what
is this but what is
[Music]
this don't tell me I'm coming out of
that one don't tell me I'm in this
[Music]
egg where you going
it's so
loud
[Music]
oh he's on such a journey
or a the cuties a saying goodbye to
everybody where are we going go back
into the tree makeing New
Egg a I'm
your
oh that's cute
a what's this one happy 4th anniversary
takanashi
kiar you're talking to me talking to
me embarrassed I'm
shy
happy I I suppose we're going to watch
that too
um wait where is the
button hello herb welcome welcome
welcome all right second video same
person apparently aniversary takanashi
Kiara you were the Sparks that changed
my life I've been a kfp member since
your debut oh in my retrospective it's
obvious that you mean a lot to me
retrospective I studied art 4 years ago
it quickly became a love a rush there
were ups and downs where I thought I
wasn't good enough to stand next to all
these great artists but watching you
again and again gave me the strength to
challenge this doubt in my heart I was a
Lonely Wanderer until I entered the
hollow live Community Wanderer thanks to
you I found my lifelong passion great
friends and many others I would have
never known
about if this is all but a dream where
I'm sleep talking I'd never want to wake
up as I love this fantastic Kori I hope
you like this silly little message my
dearest Wawa my one and only
Koshi yeah thank
you I knew it he was implementing them
but did you hear all of them I'm not
sure if I heard all of them at least not
fully thank you for the message it's
sweet okay what is
this um
it's takanashi Thurs
[Music]
day just betray
love is just a game we play hat and
[Music]
betray
uhuh is that that just that's just is
that an anniversary video it just looks
like another first day takanashi first
day
video oh thank you okay we're going to
we're going to watch the there's
apparently a chicken Awards
video this is very
interesting but it's very long so I'm
not sure how committed I am to this or
how committed I should be to
this let's let's watch and then
see if if we should watch it fully or
not how long is long 27 minutes
let's
[Music]
go W SW for
get
again kfp myth fans lurkers and everyone
in between welcome to the chimin Choice
Awards a show dedicated to none other
than the ruler of chickens CEO of kfp
Phoenix of hollow life and tangent Queen
takanashi
Kiara I'm pudding and in tonight's
ceremony we'll be celebrating four years
of Kiara
and looking back at some of the things
that we' known and loved abouto we will
unveil what you the audience have chosen
as tonight's winners there are a total
of five categories ranging from the fan
favorite Kiara ship to her most popular
outfit and with 400 votes this is sure
to be an interesting show V so get your
popcorn pot wrap yourself in your Wawa
blanket and reschedule your ridal
meetings without further Ado let's take
a PE get our award categories let's
go oh mzo I haven't done an mzo video in
a
while a favorite Keo
[Music]
ship favorite K
outfit favorite stream style oh this are
these all new
illustrations oh wo wo from the have to
chunes you can turn up to 11 these
categories are only a few of the great
things we love Kiara
forat to a single awards show would set
us up for breaking 10 Show streaming
records but that's just how much kfb
cares with that grab your slice of
pineapple pizza and dig into our first
category amzo in this category we have
invited a special award presenter who
needs no
introduction Kik freaky Amigos I will
start off by saying that I am way too
comfortable in putting on and I know
this because while I was putting it on
my mother came downstairs because she
was visiting what and she said that's my
girl you didn't even need your fiance to
put this thing on did you anyways Kik
riy everybody today I have been asked by
the kfp to present to you the amzo award
they said do it or we will find you
needless to say they found me but before
I give the nominations for this amzo
award let me tell tell you a little bit
about it the amzo series started as a
small little thing that Kiara could do
back in November of 2020 when she said
that she could do a frog noise I thought
frogs would go Ribbit Ribbit and she
surprised us with a realistic frog sound
after a while during the new year's
Super Chat reading stream a viewer asked
her if she could make some popping
noises and she tried to but she couldn't
instead she made her legendary froggy
Wawa sound with Reverb this time 3 days
later the birth of the amzo series
showed up as she posted a video titled M
frog I mean look at this look at this
look at that is look at her I'm going to
show this to my kids and tell them that
this is the PBS channel an frog was such
a success that it turned out to be the
15th most viewed video on her Channel
now that's pretty impressive considering
the fact that she has music like do you
Sparks Cima that are bangers and in the
middle of that you have M frog it's
pretty impressive I think it's safe to
assume that frog is very beloved by the
kfp now after that she gave birth to
many other amzo videos such as M Dog M
owl M Crow M shark is my personal
favorite and for the true kfp members
you guys should know that there's a
secret amzo video in Valkyrie connect M
penguin now I said that the shark one is
my favorite but my actual favorite one
is missing from the F that information I
need you to fix this where's M Raptor
somebody cue the clip
[Laughter]
easy
easy that is my favorite amzo video and
now that we finish our course in amoo
history let's talk about our nominees
for the amzo that's my
laughter am sheep
sheep am RoR no what the [\h__\h] that's not
am frog I like frog the winner of the am
Zoo award is what the [\h__\h] is rap don't
make it win don't am frog
congratulations to am frog I'm not going
to be trying to repli that sound because
do that however congratulations to
everybody that voted for M frog and for
Kiara for winning this award I want to
give big thanks to the people at kfp for
allowing me to host this award and this
opportunity thank you to Kiara for being
so awesome as always and of
course shout outs to the person that
made this
costume people are getting a real kikiri
kick out of
it that's that's a good one I'm with
that that's a good
one thanks Co it's a pleasure to have a
wonderful member of the community stop
by to kick things off for us now that
the Menagerie has been managed it's time
to move on to our second award I want to
watch this whole I want to see who the
comment the moderators are throughout
her time as a member of hollow life she
has developed close relationships with
many of her fellow members who's your
favorite have laid the K and built
romantic ships pairing Kiara with those
members we'll discover if the seas are
calm for smooth sailing or if a rough
night is ahead on the stormy ocean we're
about to find out who gets to be the
Lucky Gal that wins The Fan Favorite
Kiara sh going to announce it here are
your nominees
t h and difficult to
beat see
y I thought he made it it's
reala we need a better name and the
winner of the Romantic Kiara get uh oh
sorry wrong
ceremony favorite Kiara ship goes to
takamori wait is there no commentator
for this one I
[Music]
love oh
no
huh
what who whoa
what a digital
sh huh you asked your car printer to fix
a wooden bridge Carpenters make carpets
it's so obvious oh my God I would put
flat Earth versus global Earth First on
the same level as people who believe
Carpenters make carpets and people who
don't believe Carpenters make carpets
I'm a glober but also I believe in
Carpenters making carpet and if you
don't believe that then maybe you're
also a flat earther who stole this word
from the carpet layer who had a personal
vetta against the carpet layer and was
like [\h__\h] you [\h__\h] carpets people should
walk on bare wood dust I steal your
carpet by stealing your Carpenter name
now you're naked now I'm the Carpenter
and people will be confused cuz they
think I lay carpet but in reality I
don't and then I transform them from
carpet lovers into bare wood lovers and
they will walk on the wood they will
ignore carpets forever they will hate
carpets they will burn carpets they will
rip out the carpets of their homes and
then burn them and say [\h__\h]
carpets superiority to hardwood floors
hey don't you put me on the wheelchair
and roll me to my bed don't you what
don't you give me my meds what's wrong
with this
woman what's wrong with this
woman
amazing she's
crazy let's roll out the red carpet for
our next category and dress to impress
our fashionable Phoenix has quite the
Wardrobe but which stylish sophisticated
sharp spiffy snazzy Sleek outfit did her
employees love the most our third award
is the favorite outfit category and here
are your nominees is Fever Night in it
Hello nice to meet
you good one it is me mature P the
Empress The
Majestic armpits nice it's
me Bally my default outfit at this point
the button yes it is a straw
hat this isn't even my final form can
you imagine this oh my God my
boys with the last s down the runway the
winner
goes to I say casual armor
outfit epic
video epic video let's
go I look pretty cool in that one right
herb is your favorite too it's pretty
sick I love it also in our survey we
asked for kp's opinion on a highly
debated topic is Kiara a gamer excuse me
400 chimpin voted 69% of chimpin voted
for option one nice the remaining 124
chimkin voted for option two to announce
the results for this chart we have a
special guest the maintainer of Kiara's
game completion list no motion motion
mtion if you would please is Kiara a
gamer
yeah yeah
thanks of course I am put down
controller and tune in to the live
stream of your choice to see the next
award from a hot glue infused
gingerbread Masterpiece a multi-art
jrpg a Hing good time with our favorite
FR or just sitting back relaxing and
enjoying a comfy zedan which one wins
the fourth award for the favorite stream
style here are the
nominees whenever I went to an arcade in
Japan the only thing I did was take P
she is making my brain react or my
uterus I was trying to know stay alive
cuz it was really really painful I could
not breathe
well and I was I thought I was
dying I cannot understand English so I
that was fun
that
was you little [\h__\h] I'm are you
challenging me is it f
God the scen oh no oh no this is R8
content gas gas gas gas gas forging aead
to make a saga all our own whichever we
TR Sparks like the
[Music]
flame
togic oh I feel like it's kind of like
yeah yeah yeah yeah I mean gaming
streams are my fire
and wa bre
and what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h] fu the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h] what I do all the time the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] what the
[Music]
[\h__\h] bread and butter
[Laughter]
not sure if I should have shown all this
on stream though with all these
copyrighted and take a look the winner I
shall be forgiven is z
that's you don't really believe that
though I don't
know so you're just saying you like me
talking anymore he kept on
yapping and with that every day as he
yapped for the ypp just doing like
simple dat streams on its own rather
than D you were enjoying me talking even
with gaming
stream I think that's what you're trying
to say yappers who yapped less than him
and asked him what do i
y cuz I just on we'd like to introduce
our next special guest with a crash his
rhythmic talent for live streamed
improvised drum performances is a sound
to be
heard let's go
dude when a new song or cover drops the
fans all rush to request that he add his
own special flare is he going to
[Music]
us please welcome I haven't seen him in
a while
drummer for real hey everybody it's the
8bit drummer and I have something really
special for y'all I was reached out to
by a member of the kfp uh and was asked
if I wanted to play a song for Kiara's
fouryear anniversary go and I'm like uh
yeah absolutely especially when it's a
song as good as the great Wanderer so
let's go ahead and get that started once
again congratulations on the fouryear
anniversary Kiara perform in these
Awards let's go ahead and get it started
oh my God
let's turn that up
guys let's go musical
[Music]
performance
oo I feel like wait he's going to watch
this
wait he's going to probably watch us
let's
uh I need
to uh where is
a let me just put on my jacket cuz
this once again congratulations on the
fouryear anniversary Kiara I wish you
nothing but the best in the future let's
go ahead and get it
started that's
[Music]
why out of respect
let's
[Music]
go
the I am you could
know in the Rion
in between the
reality my
own me
[Music]
you
look I can
see when I can reach you again I let
go I can hear voice leing me through
the
away to
[Music]
the will me
am
beleving just a
saing o
the day on
the I can't feel the fall
[Music]
back
go I canar
youring through
[Music]
the I'm walking back
my
[Music]
eyes you
once again kfp thank you very much for
having me on at as a musical guest for
this wonderful uh celebration
congratulations once again on Kiara's
four years of streaming anniversary and
once again I wish everyone of y'all all
the best thank you all so much for
joining me and uh again God bless take
care you'all have a wonderful one
bye-bye stop stop stop thank you so much
for doing that that's so cool I'm pretty
pretty pretty pretty sure that he
already did uh uh the great wander cover
so to say before but you know that's
like it's usually like first listen
first try uh so it was like spontaneous
yeah this sounded very different from
his first attempt but it it was like you
know it was obviously like more planned
and thought through and it was amazing
really really cool w i remember his
first attempt that was also really
really like I think I even tweeted about
it or or I talked about it on my stream
but yeah amazing thank you for doing
W that's so
cool freaking musical performance you
guys there's only 10 8 minutes left of
this these 20 minutes passed by really
fast holy [\h__\h] and to conclude tonight's
festivity I'm so sorry like I I changed
um out of respect and also in case he
wants to react to it because like I he
he sometimes doesn't show music videos
if they're too lud and all that but then
I ended up showing my legs in the end
and those are pretty loot so I might
have ruined it I'm so sorry um I'm so
sorry we bring you the final guest she's
The Mastermind behind the moves of
Classics such as do
you let's
[Music]
go Fever
Night me underneath
the move my through
as well as
[Music]
[Applause]
Sparks through her incredible dancing
and choreographing she's helped Kiara
bring her music to life so please put
your wings together as we introduce to
you Kiana let's go heyo hey heo hello
kfp my name is Kiana and I'm a dancer
choreographer in the online Oita and
K-pop in public sphere as well as a
choreographer for artists who are mainly
in the idol and vtuber performance genre
and I can confidently say that Kiara is
one of the first people to introduce me
to vtubers so I wouldn't be here in
front of you in this 2D form without her
so I'm very grateful grateful for that
yes but before I present this award I
believe I have two questions that I am
to answer for you all and that is
mention your favorite Coral that you've
worked on for Kiara and talk about your
favorite original song from
Kiara um I'd have to say my favorite Cho
that I've ever done for
Kiara is probably fever night I think
that out of all of the choreo I've done
so far that one matched the image that I
had in my mind before I started
choreographing so it was very satisfying
to be able to bring um my imagination
into life and I believe it's also the
song that she enjoys dancing to the most
so that was very very satisfying to hear
it as for favorite song honestly it
changes day to day depending on my mood
but I think that since it's getting
warmer outside pineapple has been on my
heavy rotation list
lately and
now the award nominees are
do you do
you
go
[Music]
Sparks Your Own
Way
[Music]
retrospective and the great Wanderer
noima Chima
do
biased and the favorite original song
from kfp no you guys going to say the
great wonderand you guys going to say
the great
wonderand the great
[Music]
wander I can read you too
well ooh
[Music]
W it's a Godly song this is the first
time we're hearing it
today the third
[Music]
time this is amazing I like these
chicken the wordss
[Music]
nice thanks for appre conratulations to
the winning song and thank you again
Kiana for joining us at this special
event kfb appreciates the expertise
you've provided to help Kiara be the
best that she can be throughout this
very special night we have presented a
total of five Awards and have three
guests this award show has been in the
making for 10 months with contributions
from the entire kfp community ranging
from artists to musicians from the
loudest members to the quietest lurkers
we would love to thank everyone involved
with this project and
kfp Kiara thank you for the great you
have n that me and a great four the goat
let's all have fun for more years to
come I have been your host please hand
me those artworks thank you everyone and
good
night I'm
amazing it's me do I take my Awards
home hello everyone
I'm and
I'm I will
wish the fourth anniversary we just want
to say you're loved by everyone around
the
[Music]
world I love you what's kelly doing
there
[Applause]
though happy anniversary
a look at
them [\h__\h] Australia
mate oh my god let's
go
dream
[Applause]
again oh my oh my God
you are caring kind
inspiring was in the middle of a stream
huh more years four more years
anniversary oh that's that's oh and
F creative passionate funny and make us
happy
come come why you hiding why you
hiding happy happy fourth fourth
anniversary anniversary we love
[Applause]
you oh thank
[Music]
you Ty let's go I
[Applause]
love thank you watch so many
people these are only few words that
describe you we love you and let's have
more fun adventures together dang it I
messed it up let me try again there are
only few words that describe you we love
you and let's have more fun adventures
together oh this okay
who
whoa how the [\h__\h] did you do
that how' you do
that magic I made up of
words a look at
them look at
them perfect credit let me go grab my
phone
[Music]
okay
I kind of want the
archive I kept on holding my my strap on
my leg up because it felt like it was a
falling down so I was running weirdly
[Laughter]
maybe okay damn thank you that was
really interesting I hope you guys do
that again next
year you have to do that again next year
get it okay I'm counting on you I love
that thank
you oh
[Music]
cute okay well I have sung I have
watched gifts now is the time to read my
unfinished speech speech speech speech
speech
speeech I will I will um freestyle out
at the
end okay speech
[Music]
okay I'm
try it's my 4 year anniversary
guys 4 years sounds like maybe not the
longest time generally but it's an
eternity in V2 my years I think never
have I kept a job for this long before
when myth debuted our oldest senis
weren't there any longer than 4 years
maximum and I looked at them with this
awe like they've been doing this for 20
years or so it felt like a time that
would be impossible for me to
reach I really didn't think that I could
make it this long but oh I glad that I
did joining whole life has changed my
life in unimaginable
ways of course it helped me financially
so that I can support my family and
myself and enjoy life by traveling while
working I even bought property that I
moved into at the beginning of this
year but also it changed my life in a
way that I can really be proud of my
achievements and the journey I had to
get to this place I'm proud of that too
it's hard to scroll years ago way before
whole life when I talk about wanting to
become an idol people didn't believe in
that succeeding at
all and then if I told you guys
before oopsie if I told you guys before
there would be times if and then I told
you guys before there would be times
where I'd perform in front of just one
or two or even zero
people and I always dreamed of having a
bigger stage a bigger
audience look at what I have
now what I had in New York what I had in
Japan and so
on being a part of whole life really
feels like the payoff that I always
hoped for and that I think I do
deserve and then out of all people I
have the honor to be a member of the
first generation of a new branch that
broke boundaries and expectations and
influenced so many people to get into it
too we shaped the culture together and I
know how I privileged I am to be in this
position I'm honored and proud and I've
been fully committed to this since the
beginning interestingly
enough the previous years I felt like I
was celebrating my
anniversary this year it feels like I'm
celebrating our anniversary as in myth's
anniversary I love the history we built
together and I treasure
it there will never be a replacement for
us even if an if new vtubers show up
every day I always know that myth is
myth and nothing can take this away from
us well there were again many ups and
downs in my journey of these four years
that often drag me down into a hole of
depression you won't get rid of me that
easily don't
worry because there's still so much I
want to
do K solo life when kid
when collaboration with capup groups
when song used by game or anime when new
fre the outfit when F cat win oh wait
that's
unrelated but yeah it's a bit a shocker
to compare myself to four years ago my
voice was squeaky and weak Minecraft
objects breaking scared me I didn't have
much confidence in myself in a lot of
ways and I was just
like
mentally yeah very weak in the beginning
to I think I've grown and kept on
evolving into who I am
now and for all of these versions of
myself kfb was by my
side even in times when I get a lot of
hate or when I'm away being busy you
stay there so that that we can also
enjoy the high
moments a new song release a banging
Fest performance a 3D YouTube live a
dream
sponsorship and so on and so on all
these Great Moments we share
together so thank you for never giving
up on me for still being here for
finding me in the first
place I'm not perfect and I might never
be but this time we have together is
perfect to
me that's uh all I
wrote
yeah I
really find this fascinating to me
like I've been I've been so proud of
like myth as a
whole like previously I really always
when I was like celebrating my
anniversaries my first second third I
feel like I was just like which I think
I I I have the right to be I was proud
of myself and I was celebrating
myself now it's
like I mean I've always been proud of
myth as a whole too but now even more so
I really feel
like it's Smith's
anniversary
and I hope we will have many more
anniversary so
guys thank you for letting me be your
oosi if I am your oosi there's probably
some people watching who I am not the
oosi of but thank you for still giving
me the time of your day um you're
welcome to come again uh people are
always welcome in my streams I always
strive to make people laugh I always try
to make my content interesting and funny
and entertaining I always try to choose
um interesting content try to make
unique content new stuff new kinds of
streams that are maybe not so common or
usual I play games that I like rather
than games that bring views which
sometimes or not sometimes always
definitely has an impact on my overall
statistics but um I want to do this for
a long time and I want to be happy with
what I'm doing
so I for myself I I mean I could do it
differently too but for myself I think
the right way to do it is by
choosing the things the games that I
love and also surround myself with the
people that I enjoy the presence of
which is you guys but also any collab
partners and so
one so I'll continue to work on my
projects and hopefully you guys will
like the
results and 4
years
felt like this last year felt way too
fast four years overall
felt honestly just like four
years but it's it's
crazy it's crazy that it's been 4
years I
think
um I think we all sometimes think about
quitting but especially for myth it's
like we when we started out we didn't
know what to expect how how successful
the branch would be how people would
welcome us how people would receive us
and honestly we didn't think we we could
make a living from it um the Japanese
Branch was already very popular but yeah
it was really up in the air like how
things would go so we all weren't sure
and and we all all thought that I mean
this I don't think any of us thought
that we could do it for 4
years I thought like probably after a
year one way or another it's going to
end if if somebody's going to end me or
if I'm going to end myself who knows but
one where another for sure it's not
going to be longer than that
right but here we are now 4 years later
and I feel like I'm running on this
treadmill andless ly
breaching for things that are there and
sometimes sometimes there's people on
the sidelines who are throwing water at
me and maybe a little snack or so and
maybe they give me a towel and they're
they're motivating me to keep on
running and I keep on
running I keep on running and I don't
see the finish line
yet I might be tired
sometimes and sometimes maybe I'll walk
a little bit rather than
running but I
hope that when I reach the goal one day
all of you guys will be waiting for me
at the finish
line and perhaps we can run through it
together
even but until then it's still still a
long way to
go so with that I say thank you so much
for 4
years um there's a proper 3D live that I
worked my ass off
for that was so [\h__\h] stressful to
record and prepare um it's coming soon
it's going to be labeled as anniversary
life because it is still like somewhat
close to it
uh that will happen in maybe two to 3
weeks I will announce it properly when
it is
time uh on this
weekend tomorrow on Friday I will
release a video on my channel which is a
little Vlog which will also have an
announcement in
it little Vlog tomorrow on my channel
then Saturday and Sunday h on each of
these days there will be uh exciting
full official fun videos such as on
Sunday it's going to be the myth
anniversary live of course I think the
Saturday one isn't announced yet what
what's going to be there but there's
going to be something really nice that I
want you to watch there as
well and yeah and then I'll be gone um
Monday Tuesday probably and then I'll be
back and back to streaming normally
until finally my Fredy life is going to
hopefully
happen
yes um yeah I still have to pack because
I'm going on a little trip uh I know I
just came back from one but you will
understand I'm meeting with Nissa you'll
understand
uh
yeah yeah we're going on a little trip I
still have to pack and I have to clean
my my uh my home and and also uh cook
probably some dinner uh yeah lots going
on well in any case thank you so much
for supporting me um I hope to get to
read those super chats soon after I'm
back from my trip also finish those
Polaroids don't worry I haven't
forgotten about
them I am so happy to have you guys the
ones the ones who are here with me today
are the real ones thank you for
supporting me I always cherish my time
with
you you guys are the best I love you
guys thank you for giving me a
chance thank
you and J
[Music]
bye-bye
oh I forgot to say merchandise I will
have solo Anniversary merchandise but it
will be released when the fretty life
happens
please don't forget about it
[Music]