[Music]
so
do
[Music]
sorry youtube was being kind of weird
there
hello
[Music]
yummy everyone hydrate yourself
how's it going guys
how's it going
[Music]
hello
too hot
too too damn hot in it
i'm dying from a virus oh no get better
soon
how are you me
[Music]
i don't know i'm good thank you
i prepared some
8-bit music for today well once again
playing for the second time actually um
hold up here so i hope you guys are not
sick of it yet because it's just my
second time playing
i want to i want to um
you know get a bit more
taste of this game uh
yeah yeah
oh sure
ah there we go
nice to see your stream live
usually working oh
well hello there on the tuesday
welcome to my stream
oh still sad oh yeah i already slept one
night over it so for you for a lot of
you guys it's probably still the same
circle of day but i already slept one
night of it so
yeah yeah but i don't know we can talk
about it guys if you need some kind of
therapy session i can i can talk about
it with you guys
uh hi i'm here hello welcome thank you
[Music]
yeah yeah in the morning
no wasn't it in the evening
don't know early
for n a i guess it was like afternoon or
so i don't know
i don't know hey what time is it now i
don't know it's morning huh no it's
morning and n a right oh maybe you guys
slept as well maybe you guys slept too
maybe we all slept
did we sleep
ah
all right so uh we're gonna play whole
kyodo um i will cure
your sadness with whole cure haha
yeah
i will try
what even is sleep yeah right
[Music]
same tbh
yeah well that's [\h__\h] sad um but life
goes on uh sadly
wow wow wow
what
no no
oh
secret stuff
secret
oh sure
let's let's go
hide all that secret stuff
no no
no no distraction allowed
nah
just woke up after the news that's you
know that's really
something
shocking to wake up to
a certain previous announcement also
happened while i was sleeping i think
and waking up to that was also like
really like what the actual [\h__\h]
it's it's kind of a little bit
less confusing when it happens while
you're awake but if it happens while
you're sleeping it's like oh nanny the
[\h__\h]
nah need the [\h__\h]
yeah
all right uh let me open the game i
already had it opened in the closet
again because it makes so much
so much music
hold on cure
here we go
and uh
let's hope today it doesn't lag so much
i don't know man um last time it lagged
enable enable hyper chat how about that
people just got to go first oh is it
always this opening or did it lose my
data
it's normal to lag well somebody else
told me um i don't know why yours lags
so [\h__\h] much something's wrong with
your pc
i don't know what would be wrong with it
also i'm not uh oh you don't hear it
there you go
i'm not so
oopsy that was too
loud i'm not
um i wasn't gonna say i'm not wealthy
today unless you want me to be wealthy
should i be wealthy
[Music]
i don't know if i should be walking
but
this one has more emotions you know more
more detail in my face
[Music]
i like this kiwa
okay okay we'll keep it like this
oh yeah this doesn't work with the mouse
huh okay uh now let me change the music
we'll turn it off cause i have uh 8-bit
music today prepared the rest i guess
we'll keep on
oh yeah yeah um
confirm space enter
oh yeah okay
but
1280 x 720p you know back in the day i
thought that was huge but in my
and my screen is so [\h__\h] tiny it's
like
the size of
if i line up my two palms of hands next
to each other that's the size of it
why is it so tiny
hasn't it been bigger before
i think it's the resolution right the
screen resolution i don't know what the
dps no that's dps wait dps
damage per second no i'm talking about
you know the for like photoshop and
printing size and all that wasn't that
also dps wait what was that again
go full screen nah
dpi
[\h__\h]
dps is not dpi different thing
okay
let me um so i have like a couple
different tracks let's see what what
should we start with
this is maybe an easy-going
one to start off with what do you think
[Music]
yeah i went audio stock shopping yeah
yeah i have some more dramatic ones and
so on later
okay wait how much do we currently have
564 okay but godzilla was a thousand it
was a thousand
okay we previously we haven't played
with guda yet so let's play with good at
once but my ultimate goal today is to
clear it with me and with sana at least
because
[Music]
we didn't do anything with her
and i hear she's uh pretty easy
i forgot how to play though oh [\h__\h] uh
how do you
how do you lock
the direction again
[\h__\h]
mouse doesn't work at all in this game
right
[Music]
i'm so in character can i change it he
binds
cancel special
is x
is it space did i do
[Music]
and it says in the space right of the
screen oh oh
space then okay and x is the special and
the rest is self-explanatory
did i say that correctly
self-explanatory there we go
all right first time with gooda how do
you make that good attendant
did i tell you guys
uh
[\h__\h] okay i need to get used to this oh
nice damage
did i tell you guys i
never mind tell me first what to do
i guess for gooda
these are the her her thingies grant's
chance to dodge an attack
too okay so first you want me to like
get the trident going
increase movement speed my family
[Music]
okay
so
when i was in oh
cool
that looks like a candy
shark bite attacks have a 10 chance
i'll never finish my sentences
two place uh one bite mark maximal five
perc per stack target takes six percent
more damage
wait
am i placing the bite mark on myself or
on an enemy
huh
this is like a dot for stack target
takes six more six percent more
dimension
twenty percent chance to heal you
one percent when defeated on the enemy
uh-huh
let's go with this oh i'm red what the
[\h__\h] why am i red
evil goura
[Music]
what happened what did i what did i do
to make myself red
oh my god i'm not good at this anymore
oh sheesh
[Music]
let me just get those thank you
ah
when i ultimate
it stayed ready to do for quite some
time
okay powerful line this was every 10
seconds create a whirlpool that draws in
targets and takes 15 more damage
lasting six seconds
well i hope gouda doesn't fall into that
whirlpool and only the enemies [\h__\h]
i need some food
ah i'm running too much into them
i'm also so slow
let's go here oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
give me like
oh yeah
oh it sucks them in nice and that's oh
[\h__\h] i okay
i'll kind of wasted that
it's nice that it sucked them in though
oh my god oh there's a coin
[\h__\h]
oh my god it's kind of tough got it
i need to get the feeling in my fingers
again
oh my god help
i can barely pick up the
thingies
[Music]
oh my god
but i i see my health is getting back up
i guess that's uh one percent
healing one percent healing i thought
that was like nothing there we go
burger drop dough
okay we have tried and personal free
or we want an extra weapon okay i'll go
for an extra weapon
i need some more like
something surrounding me to take care of
these [\h__\h]
oh
[\h__\h] i should have done it at a lower
spot
oh
wow
hell yeah
okay so i was gonna say when i was in
uh
in america i was looking up
i was in a shop a cold called daiso you
guys know daiso i love daiso
[Music]
it's like a hundred yen shop and they
have it in
sorry i just really want a good coin
they have it in l.a
uh so cool if you don't know about daiso
and you're in the area
you should check it out
i really love
daiso because it has actually pretty
high quality stuff
surprisingly
[Music]
yeah dice are so good
uh didn't know about it oh my god yeah
they have kinokuniya yeah i went there
too i think but the kinokuniya you mean
the supermarket ride it's kind of like a
mix
of kinokuniya and don quixote which is
fascinating
[Music]
okay there we go
nice
[Music]
nice so
and
holy [\h__\h] holy [\h__\h] oh i'm gonna die i'm
gonna die i'm sorry it seems like i'm
going to die right now
or i take the body pill now you think it
will immediately help me no
okay don't die
don't die
there you go hallelujah
okay i thought this was going to be
easier with guda
but she was going to be buff
[Music]
there's the whirlpools triple
oh now i can pick up these things
let's go oh yeah exp hello
[Music]
okay so
you know there's some things that i
always buy in a daiso
there's there's one item in particular
maybe it's kind of weird
um i guess i guess maybe depending on
the
on the um culture
on the country oh the culture that you
live in
maybe
it could be considered less weird
what do you guys think about toilet seat
covers
do you like your toilet to be completely
naked or do you want something on your
toilet
[Music]
what do you think
[Laughter]
[Music]
uh
never had one
i mean i mean actually not the not the
the the top um
the cover of the top just the top not
that but like actually also the the
cover of the
where your butt is placed
i'm gonna go for this one
what do you think about that huh
[Music]
i mean there's fluffy ones i guess and
then there's less fluffy ones so
uh it depends i would say oh holy oh my
god okay
nice oh look at that jumping down whoa
holy [\h__\h] i'm gonna go up there to get
those esp
okay get out of here [\h__\h]
oh i'm faster i'm faster
oh my god
okay okay good chance oh there's a box
here
[Music]
you like
them
wouldn't that get gross no you can wash
them and um yeah you can wash them
[Music]
increase all attack power by eight
forty five percent chance of dodge
hell yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah okay
oh [\h__\h] round of space i wanted to go
lower
but wait did that just
where does that land where does that
happen the special
[Music]
above me
because it looks like it takes place
right above me
[Music]
no i currently don't have one okay
i currently don't have a toilet seat
cover but anyway
i uh when i lived in japan i would use
it i mean i wouldn't use the toilet
obviously i would i would just use the
cover just because it looks cute you can
decorate the toilet but i don't i don't
obviously doesn't use the
toilet itself
why would i do something like that
[Music]
um
so anyway that's one of the items though
that i would usually always buy in a
daiso because they have not so fluffy um
but washable
it's just relatively flat toilet seat
covers that are they have cute cute
patterns you know and then the toilet
seat isn't so [\h__\h] cold when you sit
on it in case you don't have a heating
toilet seat self-heating toilet seat
yeah
um
but that wasn't even what i was trying
to tell you
oh my oh nice dodging
[Applause]
game doesn't count that as real dodgy no
does it
i don't quite know about this special
skill
confusing
[Music]
i would say trident
i feel like i'm not getting really so
many good thingies here but
[Music]
milk okay increases attack range yeah
okay and pick up radius yeah that's
that's helpful
because i'm having ooh look at all that
xp i'm having a hard time too
stay
close to the enemies
[Music]
i would say we tried and fresh
okay
and anyway so that was one item i found
was some really cute stickers i love the
stickers and daiso so much but like it's
not like i really use them when i buy
them like i would buy them like maybe
maybe at some point i don't need them or
they make a nice gift so i buy them
buy them
and then i usually don't really
really use them just i just hoard them
and then i'm happy
just to have them to process them
[Music]
i dropped some bombs
and
anyway so i saw
i saw some kind of shot really cute
shark stickers
and i was like goddammit i even would
want them for myself that's how cute
these are
[Music]
i think i want a new weapon
so
and i had to think of buddha when i saw
those so
what did i do
i
i bought the stickers for gouda
i kept some for myself as well
[Music]
um
fun be more always good isn't it
because then we could uh what was the
combination again
but you guys want to okay
okay i'm gonna die i think i might die
oh
get out of here
[Music]
that doesn't really heal that much
[Laughter]
[Music]
health baby
doing pretty well
it's just warm-up space i'm doing pretty
well
so yeah um
what was i talking about
i think i want the nightly milk
[Music]
no
okay apparently i want this one
i'm so slow again ah it hits so hard
when you get slower again
[Music]
i got some stickers they're really cute
but actually it wasn't even a real shark
it was like a whale shark um sticker so
it barely even looks like a shark but
you know then i was looking in the dice
so i was looking for items that are
maybe a bit more sharky more sharky than
that one but i couldn't find anything
else so i was like okay i guess i'm
getting these stickers
yeah she likes them
i don't know if she's gonna use them but
she likes them
it doesn't look like a shark at all it
was like i thought this was a whale
i thought it was a whale
i know
the great
oh well i'll survive
maybe not
escape sometimes you need to make some
smart choices aka escaping
just get out of here there we go
we can try to go back up again to
collect all that extra there we go
they're gone
[Music]
i look different today i look like put
out today but it's me it's your boss
don't hurt me
i didn't realize there was a box there
i'm taking that
uh but also i think i'll take cycloacs
[Music]
maybe study glasses
one two three three three one
yeah i think a lot of people agree with
the glasses
oh baby
honey
[\h__\h] nice
[Music]
love those i love those choices
best choices ever
hey maybe can we clear this
when you go in without even thinking you
could clear it that's when you clear it
oh my god so many burgers
[Music]
headphones
15 chance to negate one hit
i mean there's um you guys are saying
everything basically i can't take
everything
[Music]
oh fubazilla is coming oh [\h__\h]
yeah right it's 10 minutes oh [\h__\h]
okay focus
[Music]
oh yeah on the rabies right side i see
her now
poo poo stop
[Music]
yeah yeah get sucked into the whirlpools
let's go
oh oh that's not that's not cool
that's not cool
oh baby yeah
i would say bump
i think
[Music]
i want my bum to be
bigger faster
[Music]
oh that's so sweet
i will probably read your super chat
properly in about five years when i
finally catch up i'm sorry
[Music]
now we're in the second half
yeah movement speed would be nice
actually
[Music]
i actually i would
i appreciate her being fast but um the
others are really good too
it's hard to choose
[Music]
but maybe
these are all good
god damn it i'm gonna go for this one
whatever
[Music]
maybe we get something nice here too
okay and we can quickly level up the
body pillow huh
okay well it's so fast yo
a book or
probably
i'm gonna ask for something else but i
would say
one of these yeah
get that book up
again
uh where was i what was i talking about
just talking about getting good at the
stickers besides dabs i don't know i
don't remember
[Music]
we can do two to three five six four to
five
three two four
uh
yes
the axiom
rats are back oh and now here we can
already max it let's max it all right
then we can start working on other
things
[Music]
i love it when it collects everything
okay
because that one's also pretty far now
um
boys love
[Music]
holy [\h__\h] those everything collecting
thingies they spawn so much more often
than they used to be also i'm not
lagging at all today huh
something
something was wrong last time then
yeah yeah it hasn't lagged a single time
so far
maybe
maybe something like some process i had
opened in the back last time
[Music]
probably
the damage numbers i already had them
off last time
yeah yeah it was just restarting happy
chat turning it off and on again
that's basically i guess what i did
music we mean music
turning off the game music i don't think
does anything
but maybe having my own bgm
helps me focus
right now i don't know i took the bgm is
a chill one
isn't it
[Music]
oh
i feel like
his
block looks so cute i feel like he's too
cute brownie needs something more edgy
a little bit more edgy and
dark oh why did i run into that because
there was a burger i thought that would
survive that uh will we revive
where was superb
i would like to survive it
edgy not etsy
[Music]
is this an instant recovery
the hamburger consumable
we want to go for four
let's see if we survive that
oh my god oh my god
oh my god
there's a food up there but i can't go
there right now
toho time yeah
chill chill chill oh yeah boys lobo
i'm scared i'm scared to go back into
the cave
nobody i don't want to die
where do i go left or right or up and
down oh man so many choices
[Music]
going back
oh yeah
[Music]
oh
oh my god so much so much xp i'm gonna
pick all that up by going down again
don't jinx it uh huh
i'm
[Music]
thanks
yeah thanks rng
oh i i do know some secrets now about
the game
but i ain't leaking it because yesterday
for when i was making the thumbnail i
was once again asking for a sprites like
png sprites because like on google i can
like find nothing
oh my god
it's cute all over again
[Music]
help me
okay you know i've been i've been
like neglecting this one for so long
let's let's take it for once
it's kind of like a not so much
noticeable thing
maybe but hopefully it won't help
without me noticing it
i need to [\h__\h]
[Music]
they're gonna kick my ass they're gonna
beat my ass uh
with this bat
i really don't even need to move that
much i would like to go back up again
though because i see a lot of food and
the speed dropping up there
it's gonna be over soon it's gonna be
over soon it's gonna be over soon
over
i think they died i think the big ones
died
that was that was risky
running through that was risky
okay
that was risky that's very risky
[Music]
i think bomb
i think we're gonna bomb no exp
we want new attack ah i'm gonna go for
oh
then we can combine with it
wait why haven't we gotten the golden
anvil yet
[Music]
aren't we do we have don't we have the
acts and the boy's lab book max
is it just being late again
[Music]
i will soon okay
yes what's it gonna be
okay cool thank you now i'm gonna go all
the way back up
oh yeah um
i like this new strategy i have evolved
going down and then going back up
running away from everything by going
one direction and then once you're done
with that you just run all the way back
up i know you guys may have already
figured that out but if not then you're
welcome
pro gamer
thank you
[Music]
you see i'm going across northern europe
amsterdam copenhagen
and ending in berlin
hey i have not not been to
any of these cities besides berlin
so uh even in berlin though i don't
really have
many recommendations because i used to
go there uh for work only
um every time i went there i went for
work
[Music]
um
didn't really see much except for the
sports cafe
that i would like to recommend you
because that's what i love that
chocolate and they have a cafe
where they make i guess like they also
make like chocolate drinks and all of
that it's like the lint cafe but it's
what cafe
yeah
ah anyway um
[Music]
20 hp
i guess that's quite a lot if we're
currently at 85.
[Music]
now i'm going to upgrade the headphones
i heard that
some people i want that i want that
i've heard that some people just stay in
the same spot all the time and because
they have the perfect skill
like
set up
and go south oh oh then i have to go
south anyway okay
don't get greedy hi
four minutes left
uh anvil down okay you know what yeah
we're gonna go for hp now okay don't die
trying to get some distance
they're all right there in the corner
[Music]
let me give me a second we'll get it in
a second
um
let's put we're like one centimeter away
from one millimeter literally
um hi and hi
was that was that the good one
the boys level and axe
was that the good one
[Music]
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
is that what we're going for
spider cooking time for a new skill huh
okay
[Music]
that referencing to
i feel like they should make it a bit
more
to look like tnt because i i watched
piccolo and i still didn't get that one
machine
[Music]
and yeah the miasma is uh
the cook not the spamias but the spider
cooking is a hatchimal right so
copyright uh well tnt is not copper
either that's just piantino
[Music]
well you don't have to make it look
exactly like that
oh my god i think we're actually
clearing that this time even though it's
my first time and i thought i was just
going to warm up
first run today
first try with good having like oh
forget to use
have hats i had to get to use what i
can't
what english
i'm making
everything's twirling
i think that's why i can't speak english
right now
have a good run man
lots of things going um pretty well in
my favor save your favor
oh i wish i was faster right now
yeah [\h__\h] off go away big sapling
pull away
angry big sapling
oh my god i need some food
you do a lot of damage with the artist
sound things that strong what the hell
oh my god
oh thank you food
we're in the last battle
did you guys know in japanese they like
to just say that a lot last rose
last spring
and i've literally never heard anyone
use that before in english even though
i'm sure it's being used but
only time i've ever heard that was in
japanese
and then i got so used to it that it
feels so wrong to me to say it in
english pronunciation i don't even know
if that's correct
that's good
that's the skirt just sounds wrong to me
i'm so chill right now everything's like
chaotic on the screen but i'm so chilled
[Music]
um there must be so much exp up there if
i could only go up up up but i'm going
down down down
oh hell
oh oh lord save me i'm going
i'm i'm just gonna run i'm just gonna
run i'm just gonna run
oh my god i'm almost done
almost done
i'm almost done
gg
[Music]
okay
is there something at the end i forgot
wasn't there like one big boss like
small ammo or something like that
[Music]
[Laughter]
i could decide immediately for a
direction and then holy [\h__\h] i panicked
she dead
[Music]
i'm like what the [\h__\h] is going on and
then yesterday in minecraft distracted
like
kiss me in the game
i'm so confused
nobody has ever shown me this bunch of
affection before
so happy i couldn't be happier
but i'm just gonna say okay i don't have
a romantic interest in ame okay before
people are gonna be like again like i'm
good who aren't you poisoning it
i'm not forcing anything okay we're just
being friends stop being a little [\h__\h]
you're just jealous
jealous
you can't beat besties with amelia
watson the announcer from paladins yeah
but i really think it's like it changed
a lot since the the
offline meeting like we bonded so much
for the whole recording you know
by like working so hard together for
a a period of time
it's like
yeah we definitely bonded and made
memories
you're so strong
strong
she i don't even see her shadow anymore
sometimes like
it's hard to see her
i feel like i'm barely getting making
damage
um on amazon because i run away so fast
or is she just really bad but
i hope she's taking damage oh my god
[Music]
first try today okay i'm out goodbye
just kidding
what is my first try today
[Music]
that is so satisfying i did not expect
to win
what's going on
i didn't use aimbots
first time using gouda first try it
today overall
oh my god god gamer
i can get to 30 now what does that mean
oh 30 minutes
oh that's what they mean with 30 minute
runs i was like oh aren't they 20
minutes
[Music]
oh happy
okay well we got a lot of coins
okay we still are missing some from
council and hope so let's hope we get
something i hope we got something new
[Music]
i think i already have bales damn it
yeah i already had bails
i can do one more time right
i'm gone
hi this is
oh i'm curious
[Music]
and maybe upgrades
the remaining
money
what do we want i want to do the next
one with
sana
i think
maybe there's something good for her
xp upgrade um
four percent per level
okay
or
four coins
twenty percent wow i can't afford that i
can't afford evil dad [\h__\h]
i can go for a cheaper one
[Music]
ihp
huh i can get a couple of those
words regeneration here's one hp every
five seconds plus one hp per level
oh but the next one is really expensive
okay okay and let's
yeah let's get some
[Music]
hp okay okay
and then next time maybe i don't go for
the gacha but i just go for some good
upgrades
[Music]
maybe maybe maybe
okay
[Music]
i've tried her before but i have yet to
win something with her
no i just want to go for the normal
stage mode for now
okay
so
i guess
now we can talk a little bit about
the truth is
that
i didn't really know that she's really
quitting
graduating until
the meetup in america which is
really recently
yeah i heard it
pretty recently so i was pretty shocked
like
yeah
[Music]
uh
already getting such great attacks
here but maybe i want to go for orbit
first yeah
um
[Music]
and i'll be honest like
i
i don't think it's my place
[Music]
talk any details
oh
i'm gonna go for
a buff giveaway
[Music]
speaker space
yeah um
it's it's
you know
this is the thing with like
graduations or maybe not graduations but
just like these kind of announcements in
general they're really vague and
um
there's like a lot of things that can't
be talked about for like well business
reasons i guess
as they like to say in japanese
[Music]
um
um but
you know i i really
i was looking at the pre-chat
and the chat like i was watching the
preacher the whole preset and the stream
itself yesterday of the graduation
and hmm
[Music]
yeah i think i want spider cooking
attack
[Music]
where am i i can't see myself
where's the small sana
i'm trying to collect there we go
trying to feel like these things
[Music]
um
but yeah when i was like looking at
[Music]
oh no
when i was looking at the
chat
looking at the comments from everybody
you know it broke my heart especially
for the satellite specifically i mean i
think it's sad for
every holo fan when someone graduates
but
[Music]
i think it's obviously
the most saddest for the satellites and
looking at them oh my god it [\h__\h]
broke my heart and already in the
pre-chat people were like
oh my god i'm so worried what is this
and then others were like don't worry
it's nothing stop being such a drama
queen but i was like oh [\h__\h] well it is
it is what you think it is
ah those poor satellites
[Music]
yeah
i mean
[Music]
it was just heartbreaking to watch the
reactions and i was also like thinking
of her artist papa buckle
must be like really really sad for the
artist as well
like because papa paco especially
was such a
incredibly
supportive and loving supportive
papa artist
i would say out of whole lives
i feel like
you know there's other really supportive
ones too but i feel like papa paco might
have been like the most supportive
he like watched every freaking stream i
feel and
like also really supports the whole
console generation
so sweet so cute
[Music]
that's it's so cute to look at that how
he's like with his
um
that perfect english on twitter he
interacts with
with sana and council
like as like a
real papa taking care of his child and
you know trying to
be good with her friends too
that's really cute
yeah
and um
what was i gonna say yeah so since it
breaks my heart so much to see it
these reactions
and this time it felt even more a bit
personal than previous
[Music]
incidents because
just like it's whole life english it's
the first time
someone leaves from whole life english
and that's kind of more affecting than
when it's from a different you know
department
i guess
where am i
i don't know where i am it's hard to see
where i really am i would think the
middle of the screen but it didn't feel
so
i didn't feel like that
um
so that's why
that's why i
generally
it's it's not only because i'm your
european hahaha so direct so rude it's
also just because
i feel like i owe it to you guys to my
viewers
to be honest and open and transparent
[Music]
of course there's times where that's not
possible
[Music]
um
because of you know whatever
reason
but generally i just really when
whenever possible
i want to be as honest and as open
as as i can
to you guys i think i owe it to you and
and even if you know we can say i don't
owe it to you maybe i don't owe it to
you but um
i don't see why i would not be
you know
it's open like this because
i don't want to lie i don't want to hide
things if i can
it's just
i i think it's more comfortable to
let it all out
then you guys can be more understanding
too
and then you guys don't crack your
[\h__\h] egg brains
over
you know all kinds of things i don't
want you guys to be like worried all the
freaking time i'm invincible when i'm
big right
pick up this
oh wait the base of my feet when i'm big
that's where i collect things okay so it
is lower than in the middle okay okay
okay now i noticed
[Music]
yeah no not only kfp i think like
this whole community
it's full of worry warts i don't know
how to say that word
[Music]
ah
okay and i guess i understand like
a lot of a lot of the viewers are
who can already awaken the orbit
[Music]
should i should i
should i awaken the orbit yeah okay
what was i gonna say
a lot of people are really really
invested in this and i guess i would say
maybe that's too much maybe
some people need to be
less invested
um but i also don't
want these people who are so invested in
it
to break their [\h__\h] minds over every
single [\h__\h] detail
um
[Music]
yeah so whenever possible
i want to share the details i know with
you guys
[Music]
just in this
case it's first of all not my place
second of all i don't even know much
in this situation
i don't even know that much surprisingly
i know we wanna aim for a lava bucket
with spider cooking huh that's what you
guys are trying to do i see i see you i
see you
i see you there
i see what you're doing
and the thing is like um
[Music]
the thing is a lot of this
like
happened i think between council
i
for the longest time i didn't know like
what was going on
uh
yeah
so
i mean i know i guess i know the reason
but yeah
it's not not my place and yeah um
i don't really know much anyway
no and i know it's tough for you guys
especially the satellites
to see someone go and not really know
clearly what the reason is like that's
well i feel like that would maybe
really
make my mind occupied too
[Music]
so i get that i get that definitely
like if i have an oshie
and she just okay let's say piccolo
senpai suddenly
announces
knock on wood announces you know i don't
even want to say it
i can't even say it
if i don't know
if i only if they only say okay bye-bye
i'm out of here oh my god i think that
would be so
that especially for people of ocd
oh man
oh no yeah no no oh that doesn't feel
good at all ah no yeah no i didn't say
it i didn't say it and i knocked on
i know i'm knocking on wood it doesn't
sound much like wood but it's wood
yeah so i get it
but yeah it is what it is and that's
what it is
it's just like you know this is this is
the thing i guess with
big corporations
[Music]
yeah can't really
ever
ever go into too much detail
[Music]
[Laughter]
are you guys okay
[Music]
but
yeah you know it was weird like watching
the stream because it starts off with
that loading screen that she always had
but when knowing what's coming that
loading screen is even sadder because
she's like in the loading screen you see
her back like she's facing
away from the audience
so already with the loading screen i was
like oh
and then the calm music that she always
uses the calm or guru or melody
what's it in english i mean the word is
english anyway i think but in japanese
it's
sorry i thought we're gonna have a
therapy session here
you never thought about
sad right a music box yeah
let me box this now
papa please
what are these
[Music]
and she likes bread
let's get the full meal hell yeah
santa needs food because she beat she
soon
got more food
[Music]
mom
oh and then the ending too
the ending screen
felt like a dream you know that she
places this sparkling sound in the
ending screen
it's just it feels like her whole
existence feels like a dream to me she's
like a
fairy like a fairy tale she said
something about you know can't can't
leave a fairy tale forever or something
like that
but
oh my god
it just feels like a fairy tale
the princess from outer space
this is nice having them having that
shockwave
yeah
i love that chocolate
but i'm kind of getting scared and
claustrophobic uh oh my god
i'm gonna die
ah
thank you
i run into poodle is that something else
[Music]
yeah i just want that ears
ah how are we already is almost 10
minutes i feel like i have nothing to go
against
purple key
my skill heal you nice
nice yeah we need something we need
something to work with here oh you guys
wanted four i'm sorry
ah yeah but i'm scared of fabulous
but if i become big then
it's big versus beef
one two two two two three five to six
i say um
[Music]
spider cooking
the sad thing
is like
i feel
kind of like regretful
um
for not you know
hanging more doing more osana
it's kind of like a visual
oh i can already just
max
[Music]
maximum i'm going for that
yeah stay away from me
but you know sana was like i don't know
she was on breaks and
you know i was busy too but mostly sana
was on breaks and it just never felt
like the right time
and also me not really knowing how
how like what was going on didn't quite
make me feel like it was so urgent and
all that hmm
[Music]
now that's something i talked
with her about
and
i was really considering it
[Music]
speed decisions ah there she is already
ten minutes will not need to [\h__\h] am i
just gonna win every time today
[Music]
don't don't don't be too hasty
i really think i'm not doing much damage
but maybe it's just my imagination
uh
you know the thing is that she has this
gap between the 21st and the 31st
um
[Music]
so it's really only this week
and
oh my god
not nice
[Music]
one shot with big sana [\h__\h] nice
what do you think i'm twisting what do
you mean what do you mean i'm twisting a
knife what does that mean
[Music]
that looks like popcorn by the way
um
yeah so
i discussed it but like time wise it
just does not work out with holo talk
i'm sorry
i wanted to
i wanted to revive whole talk early to
do korabu
korrabu
yeah
but
i feel like if it was like after this
week i could somehow implement it but
whole top needs planning too
and i didn't realize that you know
it was really
like i i i didn't know that it would
only be this freaking week that that is
something i didn't know until you know
even after
america just very recently a few days
ago a few days ago i heard about that
but at least i got the
the aussie collab going finally
the aussie collab that's gonna be a lot
of fun i think
and
um
the snack box thingy
ended up being a pretty long one-on-one
collab with sana nato
but then and that
whenever you know i felt like oh man me
and sana
we kind of do get along well i just
didn't have
much chance to bond
yeah
i'm sad
just do whatever you can with sana yeah
well the good thing is i can i can still
you know talk to her afterwards so
um nice that's a lot of lava that's what
i like to see
[Music]
why if i just stand here
cooking with lava
yeah
that's true
[Music]
why am i going north what's up there is
there an anvil
oh my god look at that makes purple
[Music]
[\h__\h] me up
i'm not affected by my shockwave
[Music]
and angle from before
oh okay okay okay
um i think yeah we're gonna work on the
axe now
and i'm going there i'm just trying to
pick up some xp at the same time
so yeah um this is the thing man there's
just not enough time i have regrets oh
man oh this is what i was going for okay
not an anvil
[Music]
ah man
she's such a sweetheart
i'm gonna miss her
i'm so sad oh man
i rarely ever see the socket
[Music]
yeah there's always not enough time
always like that
would like to have seen a lot more of
sanami too
me too
i really you know recently was like
oscar girl
well hell yeah
sana makes music now and it sounds so
good it's really addicting
i love that
genre that she went for i hope she's
gonna do more um
[Music]
as i just said uh we have if you check
the schedule we have a collab coming up
um on this saturday
it's with hachama and bales
uh the australians collab
hatama because she lived in australia
before
and uh
males and sana obviously
you know and then me because i'm also so
obviously all
australian i'm stuck
so we're in the aussie group
[Music]
ah interesting choices i think um
we might wanna
you may wanna go for something new yeah
okay so we're having that wave again
that's gonna be [\h__\h] stressful
what's up with that oh i'm invincible
that's just standing there
a moment ago was actually working pretty
well maybe i should try it again but i
think just now something big dropped
um
would be very polite and be like what
would santa say what was that
hannah would be like
uh
i don't know what's
a really bad
impression
would you scooch a little mate
oi mate
she would you think so
do you want me to step on you
[Music]
oh so much going on
yes yes yes what could it be
alright
looks good thank you
oh and another one
oh my god
i think i'm winning again we're already
in 15 minutes why am i so good today
thank you
[Music]
was i just unlucky last time
maybe wolfy kiata is just bad at this
game
[Music]
maybe we could blame a little bit on it
on the leg last time because it was a
lot of lag and i was saying
i was saying that it's helping but
but
maybe it wasn't helping
[Music]
how'd you fix the lag i don't know i
didn't do anything maybe just restarting
a pc now
[Music]
yum yum
so anyway sana will be missed but she's
not gonna be an ng topic or anything in
the future so we can still talk about
her all is good
i mean not really all is good but it's
as good as it can be under the
circumstances that we have been given
[Music]
i wish you all the
best and we'll continue being friends
and i'll visit her someday and she'll
show me around
in the land of the down under
how about that and i'll tell you about
how it was okay
i'll hang with bills and sana
and i will bring you some stories
even even afterwards okay
you'll hear from her
adventures no matter what
no matter what
yes
i always wanted to go to
australia anyway
maybe maybe someone can teach me how to
surf
you think sana can serve
she could do anything right if she
wanted to
sure she can
serve isn't this enough for austrian
it's like every austrian knows how to
ski or snowboard one of those things
an austrian 100
is able to do
[Music]
how is it for australians maybe one of
the one of uh maybe australians also
have like one skill like that definitely
[Music]
my back's [\h__\h] too but
sure she can see her come on
come on
spiders
those fighters
skill
spider this is pretty useful
[Music]
alligator
ah
spider-taming
poison resistance
christmas christmas time
[Music]
you know i remember the other the that
situation from the other day where i
told you that someone in america
uh
was uh like
asking me if i'm like like
you know that under 18 story i
remembered the background story
i forgot but now remember
it was at the airport
uh
when going home
a passport check thingy when going
inside
was like they were like
are you alone
and i'm like yo
no but you're under 18 right
they were like worried where my parents
are
no how did i forget that last time man i
wrote it down so yesterday when i was
checking my notes i
i um i found the notes
[Music]
my parents hey what the [\h__\h]
oh my god oh my god am i gonna survive
this um uh
should i make my way out of this they're
gonna disappear right
uh i think i'm fine i think i'm wait i
can be big i forgot
oh [\h__\h] that's bad you know what i'm
gonna stay in the middle i feel safer in
the middle right
yeah i think now safer here
they're going to disappear in like a few
seconds
i've never been in a situation before
it's again coming
again
oh my god
oh my god i'm making way for the space
princess
going down anyway though
oh yeah
when's zombie coming when's on the
coming
oh there she is
oh
hello
[Music]
so i didn't watch her stream yesterday
until the end uh
did she give up
what happened did she give up
she found the
frog she found the frog
did she did she uh
breathe um i guess she couldn't break
because she only found one
she brought back
i wasn't sure if i would be getting back
my elytra
what if i hit her when i'm being oh
she's just
bouncing off of me guys
assert dominance oh
okay uh [\h__\h] wait
okay
that was kind of close
oh
oh it's about [\h__\h] time i'm waiting i
want my
i could get a golden animal where's my
golden anvil huh
[Music]
oh
i passed the gold medal whatever
what
i was such a gay mate today
i'm such a gamer that's cool
[Music]
this [\h__\h] girl
i can't believe it
[Music]
i clear that osama is good on first try
today
i'm on fire
whenever we try key i don't know i feel
like i'm not gonna make it
okay i got too weak in this game
buff me
[Music]
okay that's the question
am i gonna be able to clear with kiwawa
no pressure maybe if i don't put any
pressure on myself because like with
guna and sana i wasn't really expecting
anything you know
hmm
yeah it's harder yeah but with the ride
built
we just need those those weapons again
that we had last time i think those were
pretty
based dope super lit
maybe some upgrades
how about
exp
so we get stronger faster
[Music]
because i can't afford that anyway
huh
slightly harder than goober
[Music]
random kiana build what do you mean
random kyoto build
let's go for xp gain up
and we can
do something else maybe maybe on
increasing damage by six percent
or speed
[Music]
taste
attack speed by four percent
i guess we could get two things we could
get attack speed
and
something else
attack yeah okay i agree
okay let's see
i mean overall we're already better than
last time
[Music]
okay come on
you can do this
i believe in you wawa
[Music]
we will see if this is the day where i
am finally so far i'm staying pretty
true to the title i thought
you know when i wrote that stream title
i did not really
you know i thought i was gonna be made
fun of later ridiculed like hahaha she
wrote this in her title but it's false
advertisement because she only lost
everything
oh there you go
maybe not so bad after all all right we
gotta do this right i'm gonna do this
right
[Music]
so far i've been only winning
now i feel pressured
okay yeah we
can start with a nice weapon
get it going
asap
[Music]
and i would say phoenix sword or already
boys lava
[Music]
i feel like the bgm is bringing me luck
so i'm actually gonna keep it for now
i hope you guys are not sick of it
[Music]
oh
pretty good
stuff to choose from
[Music]
yeah i like the trailblazer
oh they're cheering for me they're
trying to support me let's go
thanks kevin i love you
we just want to get
as high leveled as possible as soon as
possible is the phoenix shield worth it
i wonder
in general
[Music]
oh
yes
yes but not now okay
[Music]
if you say so
then
at the moment it's looking pretty good
that we're gonna get voice level and
cycle x uh
combined very fast if that's what we
want
[Music]
wow
a full meal will be very helpful later
on though
yeah
ah sword yeah i can't forget about the
sword
i forgot about the sword
but i hope the full meal is an option
again later
there we go
the choices are too good what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay
you know speaking of amen
you know
she said that too she mentioned that but
she made us like
she cut some really yummy pairs for us
right when we were at her place
and now i'm kind of on a
on a pear
trip
i'm i ever since i came back from
america now i'm really like into pears
i've been i liked paris before that but
now
i really want to eat as many pears as
possible
i ate a pair last night too
i really like pears yeah
pears got
pear craving
thanks to amen
[Music]
why do i keep on calling it that
i want the spider cooking
[Music]
yes i do yes i do listen to your heart
chihuahua
we're gonna go for that and combine that
with the lava bucket right
okay okay the usual
menu please
eat a pear what are you laughing about
what's so funny
are you saying you and emma make a good
pairing
yes
no
i'm not saying anything
not without my lawyer
[Music]
nothing going on here
it's only been three minutes huh
[Music]
i also think looking at amy playing
minecraft yesterday maybe it's just
yesterday in particular
but i feel like
i'm
i'm better at minecraft than ami right
now
maybe i'm getting a little bit too cocky
sure sure
but judging only by yesterday
i fly better than her i knew more about
frogs
and
you know
i'm better at the
uh
what's how do i describe this
adventuring
around she kept on going like flying in
circles
just you just gotta go straight girl if
you want to find a swamp just go
straight just go one direction
fly up high
and then just you know eventually find
the swamp
exploring yeah exploration
yeah yeah
she's sick you're calling that a debuff
on her right now
we need to have a
minecraft battle
we need a minecraft battle
[Music]
i was i was so close to writing to her
let's go minecraft collab soon i still
want that but i didn't end up
writing to her i'll hit her up sometime
soon maybe she wants to do a
minecraft buckle
or like any kind of minecraft product
i don't know what we would do but like
now now watching our play and me playing
the other day or getting those frogs was
so much fun
finally dancer what the [\h__\h] only took
you about
half a million
years
okay way too long
[Music]
i need those dancers
i don't know it doesn't matter if you're
gonna max out both anyway
maxing out both let's go
i hope you guys are
interested in seeing a little bit more
minecraft again too
i'm gonna revive it a little bit
i don't know i'm not maybe me and amy
can kill that um
that dude
[Laughter]
what was he called again the new dude
the new dude
the warden yeah
the warden or in order river when i
still haven't killed the weather
it's okay to max out the sword right now
or should i go for something else
who
then gonna yeah i'm gonna go there and
do some critical damage on his mind by
saying who the [\h__\h] are you i don't know
who you are it's gonna be like
existential crisis cry cry cry
wow
three two four three two four two three
two two three
or
awaken awaken the sword
wake hands
[Music]
let's go
you know
wow those slashes are huge oh another
anvil
[Music]
i wish i could have that effect on my
sword in my life today
blazing sword
fire effect around it
i wish i could have that
[Music]
wow there it is
hello again we take it
should we take it or something else
yeah okay
nice thanks guys for
helping me out there
i wanted to go for it but i wasn't sure
if it's the right choice
i feel like it's already going so much
smoother than last time though
[Music]
i have a good feeling
so oh yeah did you see the schedule for
this week there's a questionable
question my question mark on there what
could that possibly be
what could that be
stop jinxing what i'm not jinxing so far
i've cleared every [\h__\h] stage haven't
died mr manuel schneider
huh
[Music]
oh so far i feel like i really haven't
seen any correct guesses
[Music]
oh my god i'm so sorry that i did that
unmuted
would have been more acceptable if i
didn't mute it
the director's cut is not ready yet
[Music]
um
i don't know when it's gonna be but i
wanted to be an asap so
oh
but i think i think canada is ready to
work on it um he was kind of busy so
[Music]
taking over twitter aren't we already
doing that
should we improve trailblazer
[Music]
they're surrounding me
i'm getting closer
but i don't care
[Music]
they're weak as hell
nobody can touch this dude
[Music]
beautiful
a little bit of a break because uh i'm
working on renewing it basically
the whole studio i want a new look
the whole break was kind of originally
not intentional
um but now i'm like all right how about
we just you know
mix it up a little bit
mix it up so it's fresh when we get back
home
yeah
i mean one thing i like about
i feel like gives gives you like a
feeling of
certainness with talk shows is that they
always have the same set they don't
really change even after a lot of years
today
but i don't know
i feel like i wanna
have some change
it's a good it's a good timing for it
merch guys
[Music]
wait can we maybe have that too
this year would be like two year
anniversary right in
[Music]
october november
i wonder if we could do that
[Music]
november
that would be interesting
[Music]
studio diorama
oh that would be so cute
i don't know i can't promise because
like that's that's kind of like very
different like normally you know
anniversary or birthday merchandise it's
totally possible but
uh or even like milestone merchandise
something like that like somebody's
personal project
i i don't know if there's like even an
example that's comparable
so far
in homeland
[Music]
we could make the studio if it's like a
studio diorama we could make it so that
on the sofa you can place uh like
already existing uh acrylic stands that
you already have
like make it so that
different ones like older ones would fit
there so if you already have like a
whatever gouda standy or suicide
standing or so you could like pop it in
there
[Music]
oh now i have ideas
do they have merchandise
[Music]
i don't recall
they do have oh
okay that's interesting
interesting
let's go
oh [\h__\h] should i get out of here oh god
um
[Music]
it's going pretty well though
not anymore not anymore
i survived that didn't i but did i turn
big i don't know it's okay it's okay i'm
okay i'm okay we're almost at 10 minutes
all good
survived it
can literally not die
[Music]
this woman just invincible
thanks for the inspiration guys
all right let's do we have five to six
five to six okay uh what boys love with
uh x right let's go x
next is now one
[Music]
let's go let's go
shall we start working on the shield or
not yet
one free free free free
[Music]
okay let's start working on the shield
oh i've been thinking guys
what would you prefer me to play um
next uh as a serious
cat friend
or
persona 3 or 5 because
i'm not sure
what to do
because now you know i want to make use
of those firms oh it's pretty mixed ah
damn maybe i should do it full
give me a community pool persona
california it's pretty mixed
here ten minutes
[Music]
get into position
and start blasting
so anyway i started blasting
[Music]
so cute so freaking fluffy and adorable
oh she's walking on my train laser pop
wait so fast
wow i must have done a lot of damage i
felt pretty [\h__\h] strong here
yeah let's go
[Music]
oh box oh it didn't seem
hey
[Music]
sorry i'm excited
i'm excited
[Music]
start a fire today in it yeah
sorry i'm saying it a lot today now
i'm very much in the let's go moon
let's go
[Music]
ah tough choice maybe just finish up
spider cooking and then we can work on
the shield i don't know
yeah
okay
hello let's go
um we're gonna go for these ones
[Music]
there's not enough of them
it's actually pretty rare isn't it
oh
[Music]
but then that would mean there's no
marine reference i don't i don't i i
feel like that's not
[Music]
yeah
i feel like that's so unlikely
yeah i think voice level is funny it has
her hat yeah that's right that's right
that's right it should be my i don't see
them like no why would there be like two
who's we say
[Music]
definitely
okay here we go
[Music]
almost there almost there
i want to try standing
[Music]
running around is more fun anyway
wait dancer
oh i lose that oh [\h__\h] it no you're
right okay okay okay [\h__\h] i forgot about
that no standing with me
[Music]
that's right
i just wanted to flex you know
no flexing today i guess
ah the clocks are ticking
oh
[Music]
now we have more space for weapons too i
just realized ah
now we can do fan beam and glow stick
was that the one
[Music]
holy [\h__\h] i was so good today
oh my god oh my god
[Music]
oh by the way
because a lot of people have been asking
i just want to quickly say um
i i talked to reyna about
uh korea
but we're not going together okay
and it's because i already have like
some plans elena already has some plans
to
um
and with my current plans as well it
would be a little bit awkward because
like some days i wouldn't even be able
to like be with
reyna
but
[Music]
the good news is
she told me pretty seriously she wants
to come to austria this year
so i'm excited
already level five what the [\h__\h]
should i maybe
also take the headphones
[Music]
i feel like i want to pick up the
headphones
oh what a shield ah
oh should we go quickly for the beam
103. okay
[Music]
okay let's work on the shield
it's my my precious shield after all
[Music]
so yeah she's gonna come to austria and
i i recommended her a time to come and
she's gonna consider
coming during that
time that i recommended her but yeah she
seems very serious about
coming over
and i'll also get some
get the keyboard to sometimes zoom i
don't know how fast it will come but
she's gonna send it to me
yay
make that really cool keyboard for me
let's go
[Music]
i could get the xp
yeah my current keyboard is pretty
loud it's not as flat as like uh
not as flat as one of those i don't know
mac keyboards for example
uh but definitely flatter than those
clicky clackady i don't really like
those quickity clock at the keyboards
but
uh
oh we could do
what are we doing asaku plus fan beam
not glow stick post family because i
guess this works good too isn't that
what we had before
two
[Music]
though
i personally prefer um
yeah so something in between you know i
don't like the completely flat ones
because i feel like they're a little bit
hard to type on
but i also don't like the
really big ones
but the ones that
uh uh
elena used
whatever
the ones that laina used are the thicker
ones because like i told her you know
that i don't like them so much
but she said you know when you make
keyboards yourself there's like really
most of them seem to be
like that like the thick ones
yeah
which i understand i'll probably get
used to it
i mean back in the old days you know
when when computers were still
uh not so common as it is today
most keyboards were clickety clackety
keyboards
cherry red switches of bronze
good for what i'm talking about
you know honestly i'm just oh god
[Music]
about you know wow i need to have this
special save my self-made keyboard but i
was happy about
um
dana making one for me because that's so
personal and so sweet and such an
original present idea
yeah i think we want some food maybe
yeah for safety just uh
secure our safeness give us a safety net
after all
[Music]
we're almost at the end again
huh
it's almost 17 minutes
what
now i understand why they made kiada so
weak because i'm just too much of a
gamer and i needed to somehow like
debuff me
i'm on the road yeah
[Music]
one yeah let's pull this nest
that was so cute
guys i saw maybe you guys don't care i
don't wonder if anybody watches out here
um i saw that the new season for
umbrella academy has been out for quite
some time
i was very surprised i'm like what
that's what has happened out and
apparently since last month but i was
too busy because that was i think it
came out when i uh when i was in america
or like on my way to america or like i
don't know in the middle of practicing
for america i don't know
very busy time
[Music]
so i didn't realize man i missed it i
totally missed it didn't like season
three much
yeah i also i think i didn't like season
two that much either
or or season one i'm not sure one of the
seasons i was like kind of like
what the hell what is what is this this
very dramatic
it gets so dramatic holy [\h__\h]
i wish it didn't get that dramatic
maybe you guys know what i'm talking
about but at times it's just a little
bit like
a little bit trying too hard
i feel like
my drama is wild
oh thank god
i've got so many of those during the
gura run and this is my first time i'm
getting the collecting one
in the kiara run
[Music]
finally
oh my god
how much am i getting
uh
over sheep level two i would say
in this situation
[Music]
hey
there we go and then on naruto we have
to work on the fan beam
[Music]
so close to the end but maybe you're
triple
you're not giving me a fanby for real no
wait family mismatched
oh i thought it wasn't for some reason
[Music]
what do we want
this is the run of course it is golden
ammo below okay i'm going there although
it's almost over
but but we still have to fight against
amen
okay
oh invincible kiwam
[Music]
dragon fire is back
i think that was finally the time
that i can do this
which i always wanted to last time
i think finally
finally
[Music]
hello
oh
[Music]
oh my god
[Laughter]
i've got so much power
i've got too much power oh [\h__\h] i'm
scared oh [\h__\h] i'm scared oh [\h__\h] i'm
scared
[Music]
is better
[Applause]
can't get
me look at the casual neighborhood
minecraft nor here
but i will pick up
the items that you lose when you die
oh my god come on ammon don't run away
from the hot hot fire phoenix
don't run away run away
[Music]
touch this spicy phoenix legs spice
don't you want it too
don't you want it
too bad
[Music]
holy [\h__\h]
[Applause]
[Music]
what
explain this to me kf why am i so good
today
easy clap yeah easy
[Music]
oh my god
what else can i ask for
oh
[Music]
ah
amazing so many coins too 951 bonus
hey yo
got your time baby
we're missing
[Music]
are we missing fauna
oh no
ah okay
yes video game bird yeah yeah game of
bird fallen okay you know what we're
gonna do another run um hopefully we can
do it with iris or with whoever we're
getting now
[Applause]
no okay we're already one of sana once
i'll go
i'll go one more
come on
goddammit
okay hard to get playing hard to get i
see
okay now
can i buy something with the 800 it's
getting tough now
haste maybe haste
haste
huh
iris has unlockable weapon
uh-huh
oh
crit
quit for iris okay
all right can't get more let's go and
try island so we're on i'm really
interested because like she's such a
cool character like from the design you
know the whole concept
okay we're gonna do endless mode another
time not today that's not what we're
here for today
interesting attack
swoosh swoosh she sends out two
sparkly balls
i see
ooh okay we have half angel half demon
when landing a critical hit on a target
there is a 10 i need to turn on bgm
again yeah
how about something else
[Music]
it starts like pokemon but
it's not as chill as the other ones it's
a bit more happy go lucky
[Music]
we can go with this for a while
let's see how it goes
i need some water
kirby music
excuse me
radius through carefully okay when
landing a critical hit on the target
there is a 10 chance to heal one hp
there is a 0.3 second cooldown between
each heal
and then we have
increased
damage right
increase damage by 3 percent up to 40
percent
for 5 seconds every time iris heals each
heal resets the timer i understand the
thing that's written here
[Music]
said hello hi junkers
they work together okay but still most
people seem to want me to start with the
nephilim blast okay twenty percent
sounds acting good
i will take that
[Music]
oh cute pretty i'm cute
oh she can only go sideways like i was
like aiming downwards but okay i see uh
oh that's that's tough
but maybe that will become bigger too
okay
[Music]
so should i start with half angel
no four one four
okay we want xp alright that's fine i
know i can see you
i see what you're going for
let's see are you guys saying iris is
really strong
she's one of the stronger ones
i like how her wings flap oh let's see
her special
wow nice flowers oh
well they're like bombs wow
she's tanky she heals uh-huh
is this tanky nice
yeah i mean her hp is pretty low but i
guess she heals so
[Music]
the ulti is very pretty
kind of expected something else but does
surprisingly girly
[Music]
okay sweet
question my question my flashback i'm
not sure guys if i
i have quite some freedom with this i'm
not sure if i should like announce it
beforehand or if i should
just surprise you guys
i feel like in this situation the
surprise would be quite nice
[Music]
[Laughter]
surprise
yeah i'm very surprised yeah
i'm surprised
a nice surprise very good surprise oh
worth staying up for a surprise maybe
maybe if you like kiwawa
oh nice
if you like then i think it's worth
staying up there
[Music]
any hints no no justin it's a good
surprise
oh nice
well probably this this i like the icon
the logo upon being hit there's a 20
chance to heal 50 ooh
that's that's [\h__\h] high
i see it but you guys are saying one for
now
that but that's what heals her see
that's what makes her so tanky
so there's so much food
okay
so far
he comes
in we even need the nurse's horn when
you play iris
oh
apparently yes
even more healing let's go
[Music]
i think it's about time that we get a
weapon an extra weapon
what do we want to go for
[Music]
i don't need glasses though
wow one doesn't need glasses koala has
very good eyes people always like i have
this thing a lot where like i see
something in the very far distance and i
point it out
and my friends around me
are always like
naughty the [\h__\h] kiwama
you can see that and i'm like yeah easy
easy
you can't
even like glasses wearing people
they can't see what i
can see
yeah my vision is really good which is
surprising because like
i've been
constantly
on the pc for
who a long long time
my mom gave me a
pc
so early now
so early on
i was really young
when i first got you know
a proper pc
none of my
school
mates
classmates
had a pc
a weekend already
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] i can't go up i can only go
sideways yeah yeah
oh
can we get them come on come on yeah
yeah oh that hits them nicely
oh [\h__\h] too late
this is bgm oh it's just some audio
stock 8-bit bgm we i use all your stock
for my bgms all the time
uh if you
want to look it up on all your stock
japan the number is one one zero zero
eight four nine
one one zero zero eight four nine
and you should be able to find it
i knew stuff
i'll use
okay so far
it's pretty smooth it feels pretty
smooth
pretty easy
you don't use crt monitors for decades
now so computers are not so i don't
mention
i don't know anything about that
but still like i don't know 10 hours per
day or even more in front of the phone
pc and tv
i don't think it's necessarily the most
healthy way of living your life for your
eyes
[Music]
f eyes yeah
i know my eyes are just too buff
oh [\h__\h] i'm stuck
[Music]
next
game beginning sounds so much like
pokemon
wanna play pokemon makes me want to play
pokemons
[Music]
muscles on my eyeballs no i don't have
muscles on my eyes look
eyeballs that sounds disgusting
i'll leave this one up to you guys
oh you really want to buff her hp so
much huh
really relying a lot on the hp and
healing items and all that
what about what about fighting items huh
are we getting any
adam's good
later
there you go i just saw the chat that
this one is mandatory so i'm getting it
i hope that was okay
so much fun
still even though she only goes sideways
i'm still like automatically trying to
aim up and down and all that
uh
jackman plush in otaki oh [\h__\h]
oh well
oh wow
[Music]
oh
we already have this one awakened so
let's improve some stuff here
[Music]
what plushie yeah i don't know what you
guys are talking about i don't think i
have that
[Music]
i don't have access to it
oh babe for 10 minutes to unlock plus
you oh
i guess i never played that long with
bay before
i think did i i played with babe before
but i don't know if i reached 10 minutes
if would it would it have told me that i
unlocked something
because
i don't remember anything popping up
like that
oh by the way speaking of bay
after the snack box room did you all
watch the snap on stream
so snap australian snack box streams of
snacks that they got me did you all
watch it
yeah yeah yeah my fruit hurts what is my
protein let me let me take
it that a blast thank you yeah yeah but
the thing is
there was like two things that i
couldn't eat right away right it was the
salt
and the the tea
i tried both out later that day
now the salt i actually
i wanted to be careful because i didn't
want to it says chicken salt so i didn't
want to over salt it
i didn't want to over season it so i
didn't put too much but it turns out
pretty good but just not too noticeable
so next time i wanna
um
try using it again with some more
more and more and more just completely
maybe
don't put any normal salt that's the
problem i i i was making some more
potato fries
self made
and i
i started seasoning seasoning them with
some salt
and then i realized wait i have the
chicken salt i should try that but at
that point i already had some normal
salt on it so i didn't want to put too
much chicken salt on it you know
yeah yeah
[Music]
m
okay
[Music]
i like how the sun
shines from the top
is there a reason why it's those flowers
i'm i'm sorry i guess i don't know much
uh that much about
iris but is there a reason
ah the light is the uh from her debut
reference i guess
uh i was flowers oh
that's the name of the flower ah i
didn't realize
open up open up let me out
was that literal yeah
she's a flower symbol on her waist
hmm
i know i've looked at her design a
million times i don't remember the
flower i guess so
i really love irish design it's so
pretty
i love you know that's purple
kind of absolutely color
i wonder
we haven't talked about this before one
of ours on purpose like giving her that
color that's like
resembling to azuki
[Music]
ah wait i'm not done talking about the
australian stuff
got uh
distracted so the salt so far i like but
i feel like i didn't quite get uh the
most out of it so i'm gonna try again
and then the tea yeah it was fine it was
just basically normal
english breakfast basically
i didn't
i don't drink english breakfast tea
normally um so i haven't drank in it in
a long time so i can't really compare
that well i guess
[Music]
i haven't tried yet maybe tonight maybe
tonight maybe tonight i wanted to do it
yesterday but then boom got too late you
know
yeah because i was i'll i didn't expect
to be watching ahmed for so long
i was so worried i couldn't leave the pc
because she was flying around with my
elijah like a freaking amateur
[Music]
glasses okay
i don't know if i'm being lucky in this
run with the build of the items we're
getting i feel like it's kind of uh
could be better but whatever
i get here and a large riser gift wait
so she's still sharing one of buddha she
never had her own
did she never have her own oh my god get
out of here i don't want to be part of
this i don't want to be part of this i
don't want to be part of this
no i'm not going to be i'm not going to
be part of this no no no
but now now i will be part of this party
that's so strong no did that just
disappear because they were going to
disappear anyway or
i don't know anymore
it's called our live stream for a reason
uh-huh
well okay i do have a leftover elytra
i'm giving it to him i mean but maybe
before i give her my last leftover
elytra i might as well i might want to
go looking for another one so i do have
a backup after giving away the backup
you know
um
i'm a totally lightweight trip oh
we could do that too
she wants to get one for herself
all right i'll just join her then i'll
i'll babysit her
i will babysit her
now she seems to you know want to do
things on her own so i don't understand
the book
i will
i will um
respect that
yeah i gave her two tadpoles so she can
make frogs but when i gave that to her i
was already thinking you know she
probably wants to
explore herself and get
the frogs herself first as well
you know she likes nature and
those kind of things it's really
fitting to omit anyway
[\h__\h] i get that
that's before i didn't mention that
everyone didn't even get their own
alignment because
[Music]
but that doesn't matter because we still
are all gonna have our own
end
the end and and japan ends are different
so
when we merge it's not
our our cities are not gonna merge oh
[\h__\h] she's already here
i only fight sideways well that's [\h__\h]
up okay that's gonna take a while bro
that's gonna take a while how am i
is that doing any damage to her
to rely on
my my
spider cooking and
my lava buckets
make her walk over those
come on come on
it's already 10 minutes y'all
[Music]
that was relatively fast
thank you
i'm glad you liked the minecraft stream
incredible
i didn't see oh yeah it's up there okay
okay again
i'm gonna go there
thanks guys i wouldn't even notice
myself probably
uh one
let me get all those exp and then i'm
gonna
[Music]
i'm not sure maybe bomb
because it's only level one
no one
three
has made a million clones of herself so
she can love iris from every every every
little centimeter of her body
[Music]
child support
okay
[Music]
oh my god
it's okay
it's okay various
we see you
collect them all gonna catch em all
let's go ah milk
milk
[Music]
with the bomb
is that the plan
[Music]
okay
i'm feeling it
i'm not good someone gets me laying
around we are at 12 minutes almost
i think i'm once again first trying it
no doubt
[Music]
i'm just going for this one
i'm just gonna go for this one oh is
that what's happening out of the clocks
is it the clock face again
the clock face is one of the most
stressful ones to me
yeah oh [\h__\h] yeah yeah that's what's
happening
if i just stay in my
uh
spider cooking hole
and i should be safe
guys
oh by the way i had some friends over
yesterday
[Music]
too similar to australians
i gave them the same time to try also
gave them
the some of the potato chips to fry stop
stalking me
there we go
go
[Music]
yeah
i want the piggy piggy p man oh sorry i
didn't know
oh no oh no
um
[Music]
next time next time i'll remember but
we're going to win anyway don't worry
anyway
oh we shouldn't do the same time slam
now i think i also yeah i might have
also let them try the popcorns too maybe
i'm not sure
run is going well so far yeah i think
we're gonna throw some bumps
have i combined the bumps of other cocoa
before maybe i have
should be good though
[Music]
did they give you any meal no
that's something to drink right
probably didn't send it because drinks
are kind of yeah difficult to send
yeah if you don't do it right there's a
big chance they'll explode
and then you're [\h__\h]
everything will be drenched
never had that happen to me before and
being the recipient
yeah it's the right time
[Music]
that came at the right time that one's
really helpful
[Music]
now i'm a little bit in a difficult spot
nice dancing tangible oh thank you
i am the dancer after all
i hope you and bay can have a collapse
and it's been a while it has been a
while yeah yeah
i think when i send her my snack box
then uh
i'll try our best to call in
we'll we'll this time we will
sync it up better
i'll be there when she reviews the
austrian snacks or like this i'm
probably gonna mix a few
non-austrian but european snacks in
there too because you know
austria doesn't have so many snacks
that are like
uniquely austrian
so i think i'm kind of forced to
i'm kind of forced to make some stuff in
from italy and germany and so on
you know
i think she'll
like it there will be a lot of new stuff
that she hasn't eaten before i'm sure
nice
oh my god
hula bump is max we're waiting for asaku
oh we're getting some milk
[Music]
nice not bad
not bad good
stuff not to be experienced
and now we got the fan beam too
max okay golden hand will come at
here we go
[Music]
it's time baby
oh yeah no i see that for the first time
collaborations look plucked up as a coco
and hello bomb limited time only for
5000 yen
[Music]
oh what holy [\h__\h] it's a minefield
okay that will protect me well from the
saplings
yeah that's from the asakukunusu i
remember
nostalgic
very nostalgic
oh my god what a deal
i i need to go to an idol meeting by the
way so after this we're going to the
island
i am going to an idle meeting you are
not joining
now we have like so much choice
uh because we're like invincible already
i'm going to announce
[Music]
glow stick all right
i don't know if we can get that part
like combine glowstick and fan beam but
what we'll see
the fact that her own special is like
bombs combined with this bomb that i'm
throwing out
oh my god
[Music]
oh
there it is crate by 10 for 10 seconds
[Music]
should i take that now okay
kind of late though
but it's never too late never too late
for more power
[Music]
almost done
just running away from them
oh maybe maybe we'll stick
[Music]
when did you become so good you're doing
so well today it's incredible i know
right let's go
oh
this game's got nothing on me what a
baby game
a walk in the park is what this is
easy
[Music]
did you see
the during the graduation announcement
she
showed a teaser for some things
actually sana showed me the non-blacked
out version
so
cute so [\h__\h] cute that's all i'm
gonna say
so freaking cute is all i'm gonna say
ah we're so close to the end don't you
fan beam or
i need to
[Music]
today because this will be the what
fourth time today
but um
giving her an aspect but i guess she's
enjoying it she's for some reason she
keeps on
saying that she likes to be
beat up
[Music]
why does she like it so much
don't change it stop saying that you're
jinxing it by saying don't jinx it
i don't know what you're doing
[Music]
um
come
well on i was thinking about that too
because now a big wave is coming
the shield would be good
tiny leg no problem
oh wow oh we can
do it again one minute left guys
should i do a body pillow again
i think i'll do
but people again maybe
two
three one
okay
[Music]
i don't know where to go
okay
[Music]
chad was dead for a second
stink will protect you don't panic i
don't know man it's looking so scary
she'll she doesn't die okay okay okay
okay
bearish
tank chris can take it yeah yeah okay
i was immortal risk
[Music]
well i didn't turn off hype which i have
still there ah
okay we will go for
inside
[Music]
oh
is
i'm so relieved to see you to be honest
oh dear lauren you know what just for
fun i'm adding another uh attack item
[Music]
here
yeah hitbox too big amen
so much for being small amen
yes
i'm going aggressive mode right now
i'm not running away
this is fun i like this boss oh
baby
oops i did it again
[Music]
no let me change that i am the
gamer girl
magical music notes that float
vertically in both directions oh
we got a new thing here that's four wins
in a row not a single lose the title is
so accurate
let's go
okay now i need to go to an idol meeting
i don't know
please give me a moment
[Music]
uh
so
you know
we played for like three hours we
cleared four uh girls
and even though i would wouldn't mind
continuing to play
i think so the 30 minute run and all
that we're gonna do next time if there
will be next time i think i might wait
for some kind of update
uh to play it again because i need to i
need to start reading super chats to
catch up because i got so many super
chats to read
yeah um
so if that's okay for you guys
thank you thank you thank you hi
any chance continue my research oh i
don't wanna yo hmm i probably will
forget
but at some point i do want to play it
again yeah
thank you guys for being here now
of course
of course update around august oh well
that seems about
right that's okay
gotcha time ah
i know i want to keep the gacha what if
i don't i really don't know
like when
the gamers still coming but if they're
coming in the next update then i want to
have the gotcha money ready
um
[Music]
there's an image on the whole of your
game twitter
oh okay
and now then i want to wait for august
and then we will learn the new
characters and then we do a 30 minute
run or something like that
um kind of read super chat now so much
to read from the from the birthday
yeah
okay hoping for august end of august hmm
okay if it takes so long and i need a
villain game then i'll play it again
before the
update
yeah
yeah i hope you enjoyed it thanks guys
for joining today you met you're welcome
to stay for some super chat reading i
need some company
[Music]
but i think i'll go make some tea before
that because my my throat already hurts
already
thanks for the fun tangent are you
welcome i tried to dig up some more
tangents yeah
okay well then um we'll go to the office
but
actually we'll go to the intermission
and i'll play a different music though
i'll play this
oh [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
okay
i'll see you all in a few minutes i'll
go make some tea and then we'll read
super chat does okay and you had a great
time thank you soon yeah crispy fry
fried party i don't know what the hell
is going on there
it's uh
been sent into the
oblivion i don't know
mama i see you in a moment thank you
thank you
don't miss the stream on saturday with
the question my question my question
mark
okay
[Music]
yeah i want this one
okay see you in a moment
so
[Music]
do
so
[Music]
yum
okay i'm back i made a big
big jug
[Music]
undefeated yeah
i am undefeated
[Music]
okay
thank you for waiting
welcome back chad
[Music]
papa
oh
[Music]
you know just today i was thinking about
that that i should revive the idea
sometime soon
the rap tournament yeah
i haven't gotten to it yet
maybe in the summer time which is now
but summer is long so
i bet you would win no no no no no no
come on maybe i should be the judge
because i don't trust myself to write
something decent under pressure
i mean it's my idea anyway so
man it would probably be me and callie
give you some confidence kelly sucks at
freestyle rapping
hmm i mean i've heard her sometime
sometimes
restyling a little bit which was mostly
it felt like she was just messing around
but
yeah um
yeah
nice you say that but i feel like i need
to be in a certain mood and and yeah to
actually be good at freestyle rapping
like decent
i just can't think of words you know in
english sometimes if it's german then
maybe i would have an easier time
definitely definitely
she says she's terrible at it
she could use some work well okay well
then yeah there you go
we should we should be the judges
don't tell the participants that it's
because we suck at freestyle
tell them it's because we're the most uh
skilled at it and that's why we will be
the judges
yes
give us a german freestyle right now
then
[Music]
um
right now
[Music]
is
i don't know i can't impress you right
now i'm not inspired
okay don't don't clip that because it's
crap i'll be better sometime
now we're done with the 8-bit i think or
i don't know actually it's pretty cool
pretty cute
we didn't listen to this one yet i think
[Music]
no it was nothing did you just say that
because you don't understand german
i couldn't think of rhymes
remix sure okay
try to try to make my
uh
shitty rap into something that's
acceptable
you guys remember the number for
superchatos
what
[Music]
okay thank you
let's see how far we get today actually
i'm going to turn off superchats right
now
um
[Music]
catching up always
stop tough
[Music]
here we tough
at least we already have the collins
behind us yeah yeah i'm 292 went how
much is this looking in total
1400 okay great
but you know not every number is counted
so
[Music]
don't don't see it do you have to see it
as a half as a group how glass is
helpful kind of situation
yeah
bro doing okay
it will be not okay soon
wow
oh
super tight only are only 801 okay i'll
get all that
520 okay
[Music]
i never read the one from ever i think
not
or did i apple
did i
[Music]
we will read these ones here
i did okay
you guys know everything you guys
remember everything
[Music]
john newsom thank you for the red super
chat
[Music]
[Applause]
rainbow
it is i already read that one if i
remember correctly
silver razzle thank you for the red
super chat wow
seem to memory too good yeah you guys
have good memory
thank you for helping me out with that
kind of stuff
everyone's attention thank you for
bringing me more joy into my life and
for all your hard work i hope you're
having as much fun as your chickens are
and can't wait to see what you're
preparing for us next oh yeah i have
something in preparation that
um i was thinking of revealing it for my
birthday but then i felt like it was
already like so much going on anyway
with the concert and the collins and i
thought
it might be fine to just leave it for
later so actually i have something
you know even you know besides
a certain thing that's uh this question
my question my question mark this week
i have another thing
and i guess the other
original song
you know i wonder originally wanted to
release that around my birthday but
that one's probably still gonna take
some time yeah
um okay i have some things in my sleeves
now
[Music]
happy birthday again kiwawa and may the
coming year bring you exactly as much
happiness as you can handle and a tiny
bit more
oh thank you thank you thank you
hopefully more yeah you know there's um
a lot of tough things going on behind
the scenes but uh like
last year too
um
but
you know you guys make me so happy and
i'm glad i can do
you know stuff living whole life that
um uses my skills
and my talents
so that makes me happy too
i'll continue doing that
thank you
again silverado thank you so much
[Music]
worked so hard for this moment and we're
all so proud of you looking forward to
the day i can share you on stage with
all of kfp now go kick in the kick ass
away with your performance and have a
blast thank you
thank you thank you thank you
thank you
that's really sweet yeah
i hope that you know we can have a real
venue sometime
you can as you say cheer me on stage
with kfp
and
yeah i would like to give a performance
for you guys to see with your own eyes
with an audience around you just like
dokomi but next time in pretty would be
amazing
i saw that but
i thought the griffin one i already read
maybe i didn't
sorry did i not i thought the whole
rainbow i already did range
[Music]
i thought i already write the whole
rainbow
yeah yeah yeah that's because the last
one was i'm the real growthed in
[Music]
thank you for the generous donation i
appreciate it thank you
thank you for the pinky happy birthday i
still can't believe that the day has
come for your pretty debut yeah it's not
though but that does not mean i was not
ready for it i will always be proud to
call you my oshi and i'm positive that
nothing will ever change that love your
buzz
so sweet thank you
well you already put it in like those
marks thingies
it was not a 3d debut even though i
showcased a lot i know
and i was so long i was against doing
that but i could not miss out on
the opportunity of doing a 3d birthday
again
i couldn't wait anymore who knows how
much more often the 3d debut is going to
be delayed so
i have to do it yeah but um
i hope you guys are gonna once we
actually do have a proper 40w i hope you
guys are gonna treat it as special as
it's supposed to be otherwise i'm gonna
cry
[Music]
oh lower bgm is it that loud
i lowered it a tiny bit
still an amazing stream thank you
but you know uh it can get even better
so during the 3d debut i think
everything will be you know perfect
perfectionized idealized everything will
be
as perfect as it possibly could be
um
[Music]
course what you mean of course could be
austria too
it could be austral or late stitch time
i guess
oh my goodness
last month
[Music]
mmm
[Applause]
thank you and today's a glorious day
phoenix boss lands to this world we will
always love you and follow you i hope
you're always happy viva la wawa
no problem
no problem papago is always happy to
help
with our communication problems
thank you thank you thank you
[Music]
i do sometimes wonder how it feels to be
eternal plus two years old
but maybe i should be glad to not know
i hope you have a great time with all
the presents made by caspy
oh thank you thank you thank you thank
you i'm still waiting for the uh for all
the birthday messages for the the ones
that you um collected and i'm still
waiting for the
letters as well
yeah so much to check out
and it could keep me busy for
months
[Applause]
[Music]
using my
really cool pikachu cup today
i'll add some honey
[Music]
that doesn't come out properly just air
coming out even though there's still a
lot of
a lot of honey in there
what's that
shake it shake it
like a ketchup bottle
hear that
[Music]
it's like that ketchup bottle incident
okay there we go
ew don't make these disgusting sounds
[Music]
it's not me
enough honey farts
[Music]
[Applause]
attention following this journey and
seeing all your hard work to create your
very own concert with nothing short of
inspiring big love
thank you
i'm always very very flattered when
people say i inspire them that's very
very sweet good to hear that
i hope with that inspiration
that you're gonna do something great
with your life as well yeah make good
use of it thank you so much bruno
[Music]
i've been waiting for this day ever
since you first mentioned getting
koreans for your originals yeah i can't
wait to see the fruits of your hard work
as uh well as everyone also support in
the background thank you
yeah actually the choreographer is so
cute she was like you know she did corey
was happening around for a while
and now finally they all got revealed
properly by me
and she was very very excited on twitter
for days after
yeah
she's she was like
so proud and like praising me too
i was under a lot of like debuffs like
the circumstances of you know the
environment where i was dancing and then
you know the amount of time i had to
learn the dances
and the equipment that i had on my body
how hot it was like
and then the glitching and
some things not being captured as
accurately as they should be and hands
and all that yeah so there were a lot of
debuffs and despite that
it ended up looking pretty good and then
the choreographer kiana she was so
so
happy about it seeing her
her work come to life like that
oh yeah that's so great
i'm glad she was so happy to see that
[Music]
and i
will continue working with her
for more
personalized
choreographies yeah
[Music]
oh
thank you thank you guys yeah she's
great she does good work
she's also very receptive of my feedback
when i say like i don't this is not
really like what i imagined and i don't
like this move this this one
specifically i want to be switched out
and all that and then she quickly comes
back with some new ideas yeah
chad asking someone a single joke yeah
yeah yeah yeah someone or something you
guys are going a little bit too far
these days
anyway
wow
[Music]
thank you
you have a ton of superchats to read so
i'll keep it short yeah i hope all your
wishes come true and you that you'll
have an amazing birthday thank you for
your hard work and for blessing us with
your radiance love you thank you i love
you too
[Music]
i am very
very
much working hard
also behind the scenes
things you don't even see but thank you
for appreciating it and supporting me
pushing my back towards the goals
[Music]
is the tea single um
no it's taken by me i'm
about to drink it
it's gonna be gone
[Music]
an orchestra piece from almost all of
your original songs and btns yeah it
also contains of christopher's box as i
promised before please listen to it when
you have time and i hope you enjoyed it
wish you all the best
thank you thank you for reminding me
even though this is a super chat quite
in the past now
i mean it's on
a week now
thank you for reminding me because i
have
still not watched it because i forgot
about it the past few days but you know
what i'll look it up now i'll open a tab
but it's long so i won't listen to it
now
[Music]
yeah
14 minutes okay
just i opened it
listen to it afterwards definitely
sorry
sorry but thank you thank you so much
it's just you know overwhelming with so
many presents oh but i'll make sure to
listen to it just play it in the
background i don't know it might get
kind of loud and dramatic
i want to listen to it without you know
having to read so many super chats so i
can focus on it
[Music]
i really don't like this tv
but oh well
it says it's good for your throat so i'm
going to drink it
[Music]
okay
bailey and duncan
[Music]
oh thank you
another brazilian super chat
i'm happy to see some brazilian fans
every now and then hello
thank you so much
[Music]
that by the way that reminds me of those
uh snacks what was it
uh
mcm it's not quite
what was it
let's see lclcms i read that uh it
doesn't mean anything
i looked it up and i read that even
though people
uh are making up some things that it
could mean
that lcm like they themselves they just
chose that name because it sounds catchy
but there's no official
uh reading for it
yeah but they they made a statement
saying that they enjoy seeing other
people's guesses
and they're sorry to disappoint that it
actually has no meaning
you didn't know
yeah because people were like oh lcms it
could stand for
uh
what was it
no wait was it lcm's mcl what lcs lunch
something with lunch no crunch
no it was mcmc it like crunchy munchies
for example right
crunchy munchies or you know
uh
lunch
crush i don't know i don't know what it
was anymore
lunch crunch ones
yeah i mean
i guess it is catchy lcms i guess
lovely cute mommy
that's probably not it nice try though
monty munchies i like that one it sounds
so cute
[Music]
thank you so much for being such a
positive and creative inspiration for
all of us at kfb
and i can't wait for more fun times
ahead congrats on all you've done so far
and enjoy your special day thank you
i'm sad it's over
ah that day was over so fast because i
was so like you know
i couldn't do much
just you know waiting for the file to
arrive trying to bridge the time and
then it was already so late i don't know
it happened so fast
[Music]
yes i won all four tries i tried i did i
did four runs each one with a different
character first try
did not die a single time i'm not even
joking it sounds like a joke but it's
true i know it's unbelievable
yeah i played so good today
so good holy [\h__\h]
yeah
pro gamer
so thank you for asset for us here's a
kiss for you
you learn so quickly too i did
thank you
i know
more details thank you for the red super
chat
this does not seem english this is i
guess a different language
[Music]
happy birthday birthday bird love from
norway
thank you
[Music]
that sounds uh
like happy birthday
is that happy birthday
sounds interesting thank you very much
love back to norway thank you so much
norwegian i need to visit norway
thank you
when i come to norway one day you gotta
give me like all kinds of tips and
advices okay recommendations
mwah
did i get forceful recipes
in case i didn't here's another one
your next issue fire
[Music]
happy birthday thank you for keeping my
sights and enthusiasm high despite hard
times past
and here's to another young viewer i
love you mama you're the best thank you
very very very sweet
[Music]
yeah here's your number here more
exciting things to come
more nice beautiful memories to make
together i hope you'll be part of it
thank you randall
casey gaming
oh
you're here so often these days thank
you for the pinky
it is a spark filled day the cafe will
stand at your back for any obstacle that
comes our way
oh good prime happy birthday and may the
stars smile upon your journey
rhyme triple
oh baby triple
viva la quieto
yeah thank you when i see your name it
sounds so nostalgic
it makes me feel nostalgic
[Music]
for being here
hope you enjoyed the birthday concert
and if you were watching proudly like oh
look at her
i used to be her general back in the day
i'm so proud
now she's able to do all of this on your
own without my protection
[Music]
thank you for the word challenge
can i simply thank you for all that you
do i always look forward to all the
projects and ideas you have set your
mind to thank you for being such a cute
and amazing aussie to support i hope
you're proud of all that you have
accomplished much love
oh thank you
thank you for letting me be oshie always
happy to hear that thank you so much
there's
quite some um ideas that i have all the
time but i can't do too many things at
once but i try to come up with some
ideas that are entertaining for you guys
some special stuff so
i hope you all are enjoying that thank
you nico no i will do my best
thank you much love back to you
your boy stephen adams down kitchen at
17b
epic zeros thank you
see ya
thank you for the red super chat
yes we did go there
we ign
thank you for being there on that
special important day thank you
[Music]
thank you for the happy birthday message
in the red super chat oh baby um a five
times poo
five times
a quintuple
oh baby a queen two ball
[Music]
um
i think that was five kisses yay
jackasses
thank you so much
way too generous as always guys you're
going crazy
thank
you hope you're doing well
[Music]
great man gray yellow thank you cat for
nford
i'm a katana thank you for the pinky
happy birthday kela i'm excited to see
the result of your hard work i'm sure
it'll be amazing
yeah my hard work finally has been
revealed
finally my skills
have been displayed
for once
i want to show off more oh but by the
way i kind of went back on the idea and
like genma also kind of said
no
no no
when i
brought up the anniversary concert idea
it would be too stressful i think so
um
we'll just do something else for the
anniversary and then
i'll
continue planning for
another concert another time yeah
[Music]
yeah
it's
i mean it could be possible but we would
have to make some sacrifices
and um
mental stability
for all of us i know how crazy you guys
go if i'm just gone for one [\h__\h] day
some of you not all of you
yeah yeah
you miss me already now don't you i'm
here
well you can really dance you mean
we've all been dancing all along what a
coincidence oh is that a reference to
that
because i think this is is this still
pretty chat let me look at the time nope
this could actually be already the
[Music]
that could be the beginning of the
stream
that's a real chat
not confident because it says two to
eight
just eight minutes after the hour i
think maybe that was loading screen or
not sure
so thank you for the rest of the chat
thank you
i wish you a happy birthday camera i
can't wait to see this concert i just
want to say thank you for all the
amazing work that you always do great
greetings from a kfb member
from the strange german speaking
neighbor country i'm sorry i'm sorry
switzerland is a beautiful beautiful
amazing country that
is so desirable yeah
i want to go there and i didn't mean to
like you know make fun of you guys in a
negative sense but you know we can we
can poke a little bit of fun at each
other right austrians and
swiss people huh right right
love you guys though love you i wanna i
wouldn't mind living in switzerland
yeah maybe one day
thank you for your support
nice to have you here
[Music]
thank you
for your understanding
switzerland
no i didn't mean it
negatively
[Music]
i thought it's cute i'm so sweaty she's
cute
[Music]
shark
you
hey look i'm i'm like already pretty far
i'm already at 631
oh we're going pretty fast i think
taxi thank you for the pinky
[Music]
that is a new account that you made huh
i see a different name and a different
profile picture
thank you thank you thank you
speecho yeah
v is for void thank
i hope you are having a great day and
thank you soon oh yeah this already
looks like it started yeah hope you're
having a great day and thank you for
alice
thank you steven
kitchen
thank you very much
yeah judging by the super chat it looks
like the concert started at this point
nice
[Music]
pinky go go my ticket purchase
oh thank you thank you for buying the
ticket to kiwamo concert it's a free
concert but i guess i'll take the
donation
i'll take you up on that thank you so
much
uh trista
thank you for the pinky as well you glow
birthday girl this is my first super
chat in my life because of time zones i
need to work tomorrow i'm so sorry i
can't join for join your first friday
stream wish you happened yesterday and
always the girl who loves kiara will
support you forever
thank you
ah thank you
bad you couldn't see it live especially
because you said that super chat right
when it started it must have been must
have been really tough to leave
[Music]
i hope you were able to catch up
and thank you for your first ever super
chat thank you soon i hope you can catch
my streams more often in the future
[Music]
ah this one
i cannot read
google translate
[Music]
i was just trying to check if that's
okay to say um i think it's probably
fine
i don't know it looks really
[Music]
you know
sometimes
i'm gonna worry
and something is hidden in there that
i'm not supposed to say
uh
i'll just say one part of your name for
security
and be it
what was it
[Music]
i'm sorry because i'm worried but thank
you for the rest of the chat it was
probably fun
but thank you so much for the support
[Music]
i appreciate it
sorry i'm too i'm paranoid about name
snow
thank you so much
i hope you enjoyed the concert thank you
sean for watching
vincent love thank you for the rent
thank you
happy birthday attention thank you for
your efforts and providing this
impressive performance
adoration for watching it was a lot of
effort put into it yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
what
i hope i hope you guys saw the effort
f
effort not f word
i tried my best i gave it everything i
could
under the circumstances so thank you
thank you for watching and waiting for
me
even when i was busy and not streaming
so much
you did great thank you completely thank
you
we're so proud of you
thank you
we could see your passion oh thank you
you delivered and then some thank you
i never use that
saying because i don't know how to use
it
another pinky with the sub account come
on
way too much come on
thank you
[Music]
thank you for the pinky happy birthday
to your attention we have been working
hard for this for a long time and this
year we finally saw you pretty i'm very
happy for you i always i'm proud of you
please remember to take care of your
health thank you for everything love you
love you too you should take care of
your health too all of you
very important
health comes first
hmm
comes
1.1.5
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you for watching and loving and
supporting me thank you so much
now thanks for the pinky as well
actually no it's not a pinky that's a
double red thank you
[Music]
happy birthday buzz you look amazing
you know my legs looked really pretty
didn't they
in 3d
the legs the legs look so nice
[Music]
so long
long long legs
hope you enjoyed looking at that
beautiful smoking hot body thank you
rangana for joining in live
and supporting me on that important date
i wonder where right gunners for you
donating in euros
i don't know where you're donating from
oregano
thank you so much european buddy
i guess we're sharing a similar time
zone
french oh
what bonjour miami
hello hey good to know here
i think this weekend
is japan expo
i think
not going but maybe you're going if yes
enjoy enjoy
weeble again
[Music]
yeah japan expo
probably not going oh man i i kind of
you know kind of wanted to go but
it was during a
busy time
so
unfortunately
i went like twice i think before
this year it ain't happening
but apparently this here is uh phoenix
edition so
please enjoy instead of me
everybody who can go
right it's phoenix edition such a waste
that i didn't go
it's like
it's like ah it's meant to be
next year won't be phoenix edition
though
i should have invited you yes they
should have
they should have
[Music]
so true
just kidding just because you're french
and i'm giving you a kiss
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank you for the rest of the chat let's
talk about something else i'll eat that
let's go happy birthday to the greatest
buzz thank you
yes yes i'm the greatest boss that you
could ever ask for right um
[Music]
yeah i would love to have a boss like me
thank you elena
[Music]
cutest boss too so true so true
get out of here chad
get out of here
take a break in the corner
here here take a break in the corner
[Music]
don't look at me look at the corner
and now you're looking at the corner
look in the corner
be a good chance
reflect on yourself
i know it's partially my fault but
your boss is never at fault
no no no
okay have you reflected
have you reflected
uh
there you go you're gonna
go back already
so generous so sweet
such a merciful boss
[Music]
wait
thank you
[Music]
thank you thank you i wanted to study
more korean
the other night two nights ago was that
maybe
last night i'm not sure anymore i think
it might have been last night
but it didn't work
stupid
on duolingo on phone is missing so many
options and i don't understand why
why you make it so difficult i want to
be able to
learn stuff on my mobile as well
[Music]
like the the tips the tips they don't
show up
and then everything was booked not only
in korean but also people told me in
their japanese duolingo
it's also [\h__\h] like you can't see some
of the signs some of the um test
thingies
it won't show it properly there's like a
display bug
[Music]
yeah
no i guess i'll try maybe on my ipad
i'll try maybe tonight
because my trip to korea is getting
closer i wanna i wanna you know be at
least able to read so i've been trying
to um remember the readings because i
forgot
a lot of them already
i need to learn again
hey but
pasta is easy to read i i can see what's
going on there
yeah
yeah yeah i can recognize that little
the beer
i can see that
yeah you got this
[Music]
[Laughter]
i'm not sure but thank you
[Music]
thank you soon thanks guys
several tv employees cannot handle
direct hits from this pretty sexiness
ooh
understandable requesting for phoenix
down i repeat requesting for phoenix
down
on yo
did i accidentally
eliminate some of you guys with my
beautiful
presents
oh dear
it's too late now is it
i could send some phoenix downs now but
i think it's too late
you gotta
not everyone made it
oh no
oh
but well at least there was a nice way
to
leave earth
wasn't it like one of the better ways
by watching kiwawa
[Music]
at least you saw me in 3d
thank you so much
cyril or cyrel612 thank you for the rest
of the chat happy birthday it says thank
you
thank you again for the sweet perfect
message thank you very much
[Music]
your dancing is so good it always blows
me away how cool you look oh i think
this was
during ladylike or even already during
full blood
thank you
i'm glad i could leave a good impression
with my dancing yeah
i'm very happy to hear some good
feedback
thank you thank you thank you arigato
thanks miyako i hope you enjoyed it
[Music]
jt mentions thank you an electric heart
thank you entity again with the
subaccount thank you for the pinky
your boy stephen adams
thank you for the pinky
you said we weren't allowed to say your
dancing is amazing until we saw the
concert your dancing is amazing but
those hips
hips waves are hypnotic
hypnotic
[Music]
i see i see i see you that is probably
very true thank you yeah
thank you for being patient
and telling me the truth
thank you
meatballs
functions
[Music]
it's my birthday mom too
and i want to give this gift to you as
thanks for all you do you lift my
spirits every time you stream i recently
rewatched your debut and i realized you
have already achieved all of your stated
goals wow
much love from texas usa oh thank you
oh i guess yeah i did i did but that
does not mean that i can stop
nor can you stop keep on going don't
stop don't stop just going your own way
and happy birthday i don't know if it's
already
been the day
or if it's still coming but you say it's
your birthday mom so happy happy
birthday to you as well
thank you james jackson
wow
it was very fun to make you aware oh
glad you enjoyed it thank you
but i need some new girls well i already
have them in my in my mind
they're already there
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat what
the [\h__\h] is that profile picture
what is that profile victim
well i've been following you for a long
time but i haven't shown up much because
of language issues oh
oh
it's part of the tuk-tuks project in
thailand hope you liked it ah those are
so cute i wish this year to be another
great year for you happy birthday also
your fruity life is very hype
thank you
oh
the toothpicks were so adorable the way
you guys were like zooming around town
was really cute too
yeah
thank you for doing that it was really
sweet i watched all the little photos
and videos thank you hope you guys had
fun with that
and please
feel free to watch me more maybe you'll
learn some english and there will be no
more language issues
smart
thank you
weird
[Music]
you're so beautiful
no you
[Music]
pencil i'm so happy i got to celebrate
our birthday together again this year
keep up your spirit cheerful attitude
and content here's so many more
birthdays to come oh thank you
yeah more birthdays please
[Music]
voltron 1001 thank you soon thank you
for the red super chat
oh everyone from brazil oh boy
i could not believe you could become
even more cute
your dancing skill is far beyond what i
imagined your happiness is all we need
happy birthday
[Music]
yo
you see 2d was such a debuff to me
should have been pretty from the start
how about instead of the singer
should have made me the dancer
that's something i haven't heard before
[Music]
okay pour it in some more tea
it's honey time
need some extra honey
don't be weird
don't be weird honey
the wind that comes out of the
honey bottle
makes the tea spill over
come on
oh it's coming
one more
come on
[Music]
all right
got a good amount
[Music]
oh man
you should ask if the honey ball is a
singer
[Music]
i think i may have not given a kiss
maybe i did thank you though thank you
for the sweet words
[Music]
thank you very much watching you finally
get to sing and dance game for me gives
me such a warm and fuzzy feeling keep
burning it up for another year
sorry i didn't get you a perfect card
with this oh no worries
if you would have sent me a birthday
card it would have arrived half a year
later so
this way is much faster thank you so
much
thank you
hope you enjoyed the concert with my
singing and my dancing
yeah
please be there for the next time too i
want to keep on doing more and
performing more there's so many songs i
want to perform like also like cover
songs so hope you will be there for now
those moments too
thank you contact
[Music]
notorious b and c duncaschen
friendly neighborhood lesbian there you
are
thank you soon
repeat vanity 1991
[Music]
ghost
[Laughter]
yeah i want to start it off
with a
german debut and then put some clips and
the eof collab and stuff like that and
maybe fairy tales
maybe even german song covers
um
look forward to that
thank you very much
or another german speaking one
question
[Music]
and
have you guys noticed i've been shaking
so much i've been like rolling
side to side swinging side to side in my
office chair
can't stop right now
can we clip the german channel or you
want to clip it for yourself
uh i was gonna hire someone to make the
clips
for me
you're welcome to do it and then send
them to me i guess
yeah that would be less
less work for me it's a little
distracting
[Music]
decent exercise not really i'm not
potential i teared up when i saw you
finally got to show up your dance was at
hollow fest but this time you turned it
up to 11.
the moves are so fluid the camera angles
are on point even the facial expression
did an amazing job thank you
could get better though definitely room
for improvement
in a lot of ways
um
yeah holofest was you know
higher quality capturing
so
i want to
i want to dance in that kind of
environment again
hopefully hopefully
in japan
don't
please be patient so i can do more stuff
like this please support me rosaline
[Music]
are you here did you catch that
i miss all that
probably in the archive but i'm just
going to say it again
and i said uh
the concert you know it was um
there's room for improvement and for
holofest it was higher quality capturing
so
uh i want to dance in that environment
again
hopefully in japan and yeah please wait
for that so i can
show
my best side my dancing from the best
possible side yeah oh you are here hello
[Music]
kiss delivery for you
fresh out of the oven
thank you imagine make a dunk
oh elsie love and i saw you you know
because i was looking at the chat i saw
your super chat in sana's chat saying
that she's your favorite from council i
felt for you my heart broke for you man
my heart broke yo
all the satellites man
is broken
[Music]
i hope you're okay
no gotta think that
sana will be
feeling better
afterwards
[Music]
thanks for the rainbow
what's up
rainbow time
happy birthday chad you've grown so much
for the past year even your dimension
has increased to free
ah
took me a moment and b
ah maybe we'll see 40 kiana next year
i'm just kidding i really like you i
like your interesting tangents wonderful
singing voice message mesmerizing dance
moves and so much more about you oh dear
but i hope this rainbow will make you
feel happy too honestly i don't know
what to wish you because you've already
accomplished many incredible things in
your life so i'm going to say the most
basic things
this is so sweet
you always do your best to give it to us
and i appreciate your hard work for me
you're like a bridge between japan and
western culture
i've learned so many interesting things
from you i wish i could send you a nice
gift in a pretty wrap
i wish you to stay happy healthy and
always find an inspiration for your
future projects and thank you for this
awesome pretty concert
i saw your birthday merch and ordered it
right away thank you this will be my
very first home merch oh if all goes
well it will be delivered around my b
day oh like in half a year or so a
little bit longer probably
yeah it's gonna take a while hope you're
patient you know the first time ordering
let me just warn you it will take a
while depending on where you live it
could take even longer
yeah
don't count on that down here yep yep
yep
just don't have too high expectations
okay and then you'll you might be
pleasantly surprised
thank you so much for the beautiful
rainbow the lovely support and the sweet
sweet words maybe one day you can give
me a wrapped present
maybe if i come to some
convention
not only digitally but like dokomi in
person then i can pick it up
[Music]
thank you
very much appreciated
yeah it takes a while because they're
you know
order made
yeah
but at least this way it doesn't get
sold out before you can buy it
it's just well one month
one month of
yeah time period where you can buy it
we have pre-order
tai chi thank you
[Music]
happy employees know you always did your
best and be happy your happiness is our
happiness
so much love here so much
kindness
thank you
thank you thank you
for the sweet voice
[Music]
[Applause]
happy birthday to you happy birthday to
you happy birthday to 10 show happy
birthday to you oh thank you very much
oh thank you very much for your sweet
and kind words and the red super chat
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
let's go
[Music]
too
thank you
uh i hope i hope i hope that it stayed
in a lot of people's minds
because you say it's legendary i hope i
hope it's kind of you know
something that made a good impression on
people also that don't really watch me
much i hope so
thank you so much ghost for being there
and being part of kfb thank you
i wanted five times so it will stay on
my mind ah
perfect carefully thank you soon
it will stay in my mind as long as my
mind exists
lovey-dovey cute
kt kfb welcome you egg thank you
thank you for the membership
that was my
hip
not even my neck i know if you heard but
i just cracked my hip
i
i admit i cracked my hip i'm sorry
i'm sorry
[Music]
i don't do it that often we'll let it
slide yeah please do
[Music]
no no i i can do that without even
really moving my body i just move the
sometimes i
you know when you feel a certain kind of
tenseness
in your body you can like move like
you know you don't really even move it
properly
yeah
and then boom
feels better
ah my hips are fine don't worry
chihuahua's hips don't lie
[Music]
hold on thanks for the pinky
thank you
morales
once again the pinky
thank you you crazy crazy little pikachu
[Music]
no i can do better
i can do better
[Music]
you girls did a freaking amazing job i
can't even more lol
oh my god you can't i can't oh my god i
can't i can't
i love that
i picked that up from
english language
you can't i can't we can't oh my god i
can't oh my god like i can't i can't
just can't
thank you
i hope you can again
it's not good to not can't
do
things
you can't even oh my god
you can't
when you're dancing is so good that they
can't
not
[Music]
i wasn't able to catch much streams
recently and even if i do i don't really
write anything anyway but i want you to
know that i'm still here cheering you on
and i don't plan to change that happy
birthday chihuahua
thank you
that's good to know
that you're here thank you here's your
heart
welcome to
savings
more often learn less
you caught this one hello
see i will miss you if you don't come so
come
okay
i
by the way
i'm gonna get up early for that one
[Music]
guess it's too 2pm for me
but still
yeah over 1 million now damn girl
happy for you congratulations gonna
congratulate her tomorrow in person i
don't know if she saw my tweet
it's too popular now she probably
doesn't even see my tweets
baby kobe growing up so fast yeah
i saw like i mean i didn't understand
anything but i saw
uh the when she called in and ollie's
olivia stream i watched the the archive
a little bit
just listening to her doing that boy's
voice
[Music]
and ollie being like such a girl
i didn't understand [\h__\h] but it was
really cute
[Music]
the drawing
someday
yeah rain wolf thank you
thank you
[Music]
wrong thank you for the pinky and no
words with it but thank you
thank you very much
alcorn thank you for the pinky
happy birthday lady kiara the concert is
absolutely amazing and so are you
thank you you're amazing too
thank you for the lovely support thank
you alcors
afterwards zero seven two seven nine
thank you
oh
aldo rodriguez
[Music]
concert glad to see that all your effort
pays off
thank you thank you for watching
also i guess your german speaking
dankest infrastructure
yeah
has fish bars for months dreams
[Music]
understandable have a nice day
thank you for the red super chat
happy birthday kiara you're amazing and
shining star i'm so impressed by what
i'm seeing
you're blowing us all the way here i
wish you all the best may all your
wishes come true i'm so proud of you
love you boss thank you oh that was
already at the at the 30 minute mark
i'm glad you enjoyed it so much
[Music]
very sweet
i'll continue doing my best you need to
chat
with you on my side my lovely chicken
it was so good thank you
stop
today
[Music]
yeah i wonder if you named yourself that
after that one stream
or if you just in general always had
that name
happy birthday
kiwama
this year's birthday is amazing for kfb
i'm so happy you finally make your dream
come true this pretty concert almost
made me cry you're always my aussie love
you ow
thank you
you know though the word oshi always
hits so hard
in my heart
it's like an arrow straight into my
heart
thank you so much
[Music]
yeah
i'm getting tired
can i snack on something can we take a
little snack break i'll just eat uh one
of my rice waffles my chocolate rice
waffles just on my cuke
i need this to survive
[Music]
do
the screen is so [\h__\h] bright
[Music]
um
mom
i'm tired
[Music]
huh
sent me
[Music]
eyes and heart emotes
happened no
almost an hour ago what did i say
[Music]
no not about the merch
i got a separate reply for that
ah maybe they'll talking me out the
concert thing
i mean
didn't necessarily talk me out of it
[Music]
but
she also
already seems a little bit
a little bit
worried about all the other plans i have
[Music]
actually we've been we've been getting
more and more
like managers joining our team
so
recently though
the whole lineup has changed a lot
and some people are like managed by two
two managers i don't know to like spread
still work and all that i guess
and i am currently the only one
that has only genma alone
i'm happy about that
[Music]
yeah no one else
yeah she probably doesn't want to give
me to anyone else
[Music]
either she still manages like some
others too
um
but like with the help of others and i'm
i'm like the only one that she manages
alone
yeah then my monopoly one day one day
i'll be her only child
[Music]
one day she'll be mined completely
i just gotta give her
a [\h__\h] of work so that she can only
focus on me
[Music]
i don't want her to suffer
oh i'm letting her breathe i'm trying to
already trying to not
you know put too much work on to her
i'm trying but there's also so many
things i want to do i'm already holding
back
i'm too considerate
[Music]
foreign
yeah i i can read the air i'm very
considerate
[Music]
release your full power
see that's the thing i haven't released
my full power yet
ah
i'm going at a
pace that's somewhat taking it easy
okay i finished one
one waffle
gonna continue reading maybe four maybe
we'll have more hour
yeah
and then tomorrow after portal yeah
that's a collab so i probably won't be
reading super chats
but
if i feel like it
i might read i might maybe maybe nah
probably not i don't know maybe i'll do
a super chat reading after that also for
like youtubers live on thursday
but i'm the one who originally requested
permission for the game
and i know good i've played it and i
know it's like kind of a
soggy
[Music]
but now that i used up pretty much all
of my tangents for the week
in honokia
i'm not sure if i can carry youtubers
life with my tangents
i might change that i'm not sure i might
change it
surprise you didn't play it immediately
yeah because i didn't notice that uh my
permission thingy was granted
and it went through i didn't notice it
in time
i hope good i enjoyed it though
i hope she enjoyed it
she she kind of hated it
really
this because i want to show you regrets
playing it
because i was cringing hot yeah
obviously it's a cringe game that's why
i that's why i asked for permission i
knew it was cringy
but you know youtubers live
youtube youtube
uh well just so you know that the plan
might change into something else we'll
see how i feel i i'm gonna decide um
yeah the night before or the morning
the noon before who knows
she didn't like the message of the game
really oh i don't know i don't know the
message of the game
i wonder what the message of the game is
a movie watch along you mean a public
one i've never done a public movie watch
long
i feel like hmm
that's kind of for me that's kind of
like a waste of a stream day
if i do it publicly like i feel for
members you know it's a nice cozy time
but publicly i feel like it's a waste
ah the cat one wasn't my i guess that
one was public
[Music]
wait it's honey time
okay don't make any funny noises
oh it came out straight away whoa that's
a lot of honey oh dear
that one came immediately
nice
[Music]
someone needs to confiscate your wallet
but thank you so much
thank you tai chi it's so supportive oh
my god
thank you
hi pepsi and thank you for the double
rate super chat
the happiest of birthdays my beautiful
bird boss continue shining brightly you
insanely tunnel timed phoenix love you
ps this college is beyond anything i had
imagined you and the team absolutely set
to stay on fire
thank you
yeah
i think yeah it was um it was i think
with a little bit more time it could
have been like even crazier amazing but
yeah
it's always like even with a little
amount of time he does
great work so
respect you know so many skills too like
i didn't know that he could even like
make 3d stuff himself like create the
stage
and then i heard that you know he's
making the stage himself i'm like what
are we sure
are we showing up we're gonna let him
make that because i didn't know how good
he was and suddenly
suddenly he shows me the draft
and i made some improvements i added
some things
like the ceiling originally there was
like no ceiling
and uh
some other stuff
yeah
we had that added and then it was
perfect i love the stage
kind of it feels like a waste to not use
it again
i think
probably gonna use it again
hopefully i guess it would be a waste
not to
maybe use it again and then redecorate a
little bit for the whatever
um
the reason
the concert is
and then for the next birthday i would
want a new stage because the other girls
also always get a new stage when there's
a new birthday
[Music]
i really like the zig zag shape on the
stage it's really cool
oh
no i don't think i can show the original
draft from my side
i think yeah yeah i was thinking maybe i
could show you but i don't think i'm not
sure because it uses for my original
draft i used like a
something
like a reference
uh
from like
management
and i'm not sure if i can show that so
i'm not gonna show but it looks really
shitty
i originally i did put like a
volcano
in because you guys you know you were
like volcano and i'm like oh that would
be amazing but in hindsight you know
when i sent that draft to canada i was
like you know what you can ignore
everything in my reference because
i know it looks like [\h__\h]
[Music]
[Laughter]
maybe one day i'll have a volcano but
[Music]
yeah
yeah i think it's good that there was no
volcano this time
[Music]
it looks so shitty
yeah it's very over the top
yeah
give this change your volcano no i'm
good i'm good thanks
thank you
thanks for the pinky once again thank
you so much
wow it's everything i hoped for you are
stunning and for the 2d too you're my
own scene every time
i hope your bro survives this super chat
it's like you can look into the future
i'm trying i'm trying to keep it
um
wet and um
warm
and
yeah
creamy trying my best here
thank you for
you know that's also very um considerate
of you to say to mention
thank you thank you soon i appreciate
that i'm glad i can be austin every
dimension that's sort of romantic too
romantic the monkey girl thank you man
[Music]
what
what i'm just
wet because i'm drinking tea warm
because it's warm tea
creamy because of the honey
do you want to stand in the corner again
kfp
i can put you in the corner again
no right you don't want to
honey isn't creamy this one's creamy it
even says be your blooten honey creamy
it says
bile
flour honey
creamy
it says creamy on it it's a creamy honey
there's different types of honey
there's the clear one this is not a
clear one this is a creamy one
yeah
you guys are just weird
[Music]
yeah um too lazy to put you in the
corner but you deserve it
[Music]
benny dylan thank you for the pinky
one of the two oh where's the other one
oh there it is
okay so it says
have a birthday canada the concert looks
amazing you know even though i've been
enjoying your streams and admiring your
talent since 2020
that sounds like so [\h__\h] long ago
until last month i was a little bit
embarrassed about the idea of being a
fan of someone oh
but after going to document seeing so
many people having fun in united thanks
to you i finally realized there's
nothing wrong with it there you go
today i have no trouble saying i'm glad
i choose to support you and happy to be
a fan
wow
well that's wonderful to hear i i think
i am i can understand
i mean i don't quite understand why you
would be embarrassed first but
um i'm glad that for dokomi you know
seeing
the people cheering loud and clear
seeing the other ones the other chickens
being so proudly so proudly a fan of me
what's up inspired you i'm happy to hear
that now
proudly say
i love kiwawa i am her fan she is my
oshi
there's nothing wrong with it thank you
so much since it was two pinkies you get
a kiss
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you thank you thank you
enjoy your time in kfp it's a special
time
you know being a fan of
something
it's always a lot of fun so yeah make
use of it enjoy have a good time
thank you
jonathan brown thank you soon jackson fb
happy birthday kiara congrats on a great
year i'm not sure i can say much that
everyone hasn't already said as well say
this instead first it's a honeyworks
song wait we're already in
the hollywood song oh a second big
absolute camera champion they know
what's up
thank you thank you thank you thank you
okay let's come out
[Applause]
oh yeah um
i chose that one even though i know a
lot of people
were like hoping for fansa
but i chose this one because i already
knew the choreo i don't even know if
fonza has a choreo
at this point it probably does but
yeah
[Music]
i already knew so it wasn't like kind of
a filler for me
but it's one of my favorite performances
in the concert actually because
everything went pretty well
the capturing went pretty smoothly i
mean actually that was
the one that i had to record the most
because like when we were still testing
out things when we fought we had
something going and working amen was
like okay what's the first song you want
to record and i went with kenyo in ohio
because i was the most confident in that
um but then you know that was on that
one evening where what we recorded ended
up in the trash bin
uh because it wasn't really usable so i
recorded it again on the next day in the
morning
but then that data also was not ideal
because of the floor that we had
and then i recorded it again after i
recorded all the other songs after 10
hours
um
at the as the very last song
so
you even though
it was the last song and i was [\h__\h]
dead at that point my
feet killed me
it still actually looks the most um
well danced i would say in the concert
so
just because i was so confident in it if
it's a song that you know you have
like even if i know the choreo of a song
the way you dance it really changes
depending on how often you
you danced it and you get like more used
to it and it comes more naturally
yeah
you don't have to put so much
tenseness into your body
i was just bouncing and popping and yeah
i really liked kenya we know ohio's
performance and then in that one
everything was so bright too
like the white
floor the bright white floor and the
like some kind of blue elements
it was really nice
really agalesque
no one can never take you out like
stamina
no i definitely do but maybe i will pull
like
ian
i don't know like if i go upstairs i die
immediately
[Laughter]
walking upstairs kills me
that's the way to kill a phoenix
yeah
and for the dancing you know i have to
take breaks too it was [\h__\h] hot too
and that was the fact that kind of
debuffed me
all your strength was in your legs no no
not much not that much
my whole life english standards yeah
different standards okay okay now we're
talking
thank you
thank you thank you for 10 hours yeah
yeah
it's not just you know dancing like
well well
i'm enthusiastic swaying from one to
side it's like
[\h__\h] choreographies where you turn
and jump and kick and all that
[\h__\h] workout
probably
uh burns
million calories on that day more
wait was it was worth it i want to do it
again
next time with air conditioning please
ah
air conditioning will help so much
it would go a long way
[Music]
next time aircon
air conditioning
[Music]
[Applause]
i'm eating the honey soy chicken potato
chips
from red rock deli
yesterday when i ate one of those
you know how i said i like to fold it
once yesterday i had one that i had one
that was double folded
oh my god
even showed it off to my friends oh it's
like look at this potato chip holy [\h__\h]
yeah like you know you fold it once and
then you fold it again it was like
four four layers
[Music]
yeah ssr potato chip
you know i also like
at the end of a potato bag i like um
just eating all the small
um remaining
little pieces of chips
[Music]
after the folded ones that's my second
favorite thing
[Music]
and with that we have an empty bag
yeah chips crumbs yummy ma
ma
[Music]
what was it again
it was delicious
i wanted to hear in korean
much much
[Music]
that sound i just made
reminded me last night i was watching
taskmaster i'm at season seven now
if anyone remembers if anyone watched
season seven you may
know what i'm talking about there's this
dude called
phil wang
comedian called phil wang
i think that was his name
you guys remember when he
did you know the best noise i had to
make the best noise and he just oh my
god
they did a close-up of his mouth and he
made
this basically this
but it looked even more
weird when he did it
[Music]
okay probably a lot of you guys don't
know what i'm talking about
his whole presence is yabai in
taskmaster season seven
[Music]
just gonna say yellow
yellow that's all i'm gonna say yellow
yellow
oh where was i i've been slowing down
[Music]
okay someone understands
there's no region varying don't ask
myself
what
[Music]
yeah
okay
so um
akb akb dankeshan nishiki thank you for
the pinky nishikim
happy birthday kiana john can't be with
you together forever
yes eternally nishikin
any
it's a it's a promise pinky promise
thank you soon
thank you
[Music]
honey
that's probably
the first one is
[Music]
thank you but i should change it because
i actually have been listening to this
for too long now i want to change it
now i want to change it
um
[Music]
what are these
unsorted bgms that i have
oh
i used this one before it's amazing
yeah it might be one of my animal
crossing videos
[Music]
oh my god
yes
benny dylan oh that's the second one
thank you
for the pinky
thank you once again
you deserve kisses for all the pinkies
thank you
seaweed
and tall merch and thank you for the
pinky
happy birthday pencil i can't stay awake
for much longer because if i drink more
double expresses my heart will pop like
a water balloon also because of the
cuteness i swear i will watch the freak
out of the vlog
oh thank you oh my god
sorry you probably tried to stay awake
and because
of the delay and it was too long oh my
god i'm sorry
thanks for trying no you made it like
halfway through or so
must have been really really really
bad then if you had to if you felt like
you had to leave midway through
thank you doll i appreciate you trying
[Music]
the glorious lady kiwawa i wish you a
very happy birthday me and the rest of
cafe are so blessed by your presence and
i hope you can keep on chatting for a
long time thank you
very much
i hope so too
yum
i know you guys are currently very
sensitive
and uh maybe some of you guys were like
worried about chihuahua leaving but
don't worry
don't worry still so much to do so i
will shine long and long and very long
i'll do my best
so many things to accomplish
and reach so please follow me and
support me while i'm doing my bestest
you guys can proudly look back on
everything i've accomplished and say i
was part of that
yeah
counting chickens thank you for the red
super chat holy thank you for the
concert concert kiara you've worked so
hard in the face of so many obstacles
but always found your way
around or through them the fact that
this is a myth production
makes us all the more special we're so
lucky to be fans happy birthday
yeah yeah yeah
it's it's quite impressive what we can
do once again especially with
with um ami's help yeah
so glad we have her without her
we would be lost in so many situations
yeah
yeah yeah
i tried to do my part though
what was possible for me i did
everything i could hmm counting chickens
thank you so much for supporting
[Music]
tango and template
thanks for the pinky
again
[Music]
phoenix 2612
thanks for the red super chat happy
birthday enjoy your pretty concert is
beyond amazing seeing you in your
element on stage fills my heart with joy
i'm proud to call you my auntie and glad
to be a member of kfc
i'm so sweet
thank you thank you thank you thank you
some hearts for you
thank you for the sweet words
thanks for
washing me did you know that actually
the word
um comes from the japanese verb of
pushing
someone so it's like you're pushing my
back
that's i would say where the word comes
from pushing an idols back to support
them
so push me but don't push me too hard
otherwise i'll i'll fall over
just a slight gentle push thank you
phoenix
i think zombie tank is
[Music]
oh thank you very much hope you enjoyed
the concert thanks for the support
very generous
[Music]
pushes gently soft push thank you not
that you little chimpanzees have that
much power in your wings anyway
could push a
phoenix over
raw root
now
you want to shut up mate or mate
sakana she could
yeah she could yeah
but he wouldn't
he wouldn't still
never
because he's not as cheeky as you guys
are
cheeky little chickens
[Music]
okay
i really appreciate your wonderful
fruity concert you did your best and i
hope you were satisfied enough happy
birthday kiara and then a little bit of
korean
um
[Music]
thank you i hope i can give some
something back to all the lovely support
from the korean fans
i will do my best thank you so much
optimus prime the audition for the pinky
wow i'm from honda i can see and feel
how much hard work and love went into
this just breathtaking i'm just smiling
and vibing non-stop watching this
evening
thank you and everyone for this event oh
thank you
i suffered for so much free it so you're
saying you're proud of me makes me very
happy done cushion
thank you thank you for enjoying it and
watching it and always being there to
support me and push my back
thank you
[Music]
again thank you very much for the pinkie
thank you
davos thanks for the resume chat
holy [\h__\h] girl you've got the moves
i've got the moves like wow i got the
moves like wow i got the
moves like
they should change the lyrics officially
to me
[Music]
i know you're amazing what you blew it
out of the park with your singing and
dance skills it shows how hard you
worked on this
i bowed down before your greatness i
almost forgot happy happy birthday thank
you
i'm praising me so much what am i gonna
do with all this praise
thank you so much very very sweet
[Music]
thank you so much
see now i have a problem again where i
don't know how to say thank you anymore
besides saying thank you
well thank you though
a kiss always works right
spider thanks for pinking go attention
go
yeah
i did go
i went off i popped off lancashire
[Music]
very happy birthday angel what an
amazing year it has been really enjoyed
the pretty concert you have moves that
sets the dancefloor on fire
now one day we'll really set it up set
it on fire
you are our legendary feeling some ukb
employees are immensely proud of you are
you are young
yeah thank you
thank you soon i'm proud of you guys too
okay
[Music]
red super chat thank you
thank you so much
[Music]
you mean like a dictionary thingy
yeah would be helpful the next one i'm
not sure how to read this
name it's probably not japanese
[Music]
so
probably otherwise maybe shoot
that
for the red super chat
thank you for the lovely big hearts be
granted mama big red heart thank you
what
i don't know
[Music]
oh i feel like i haven't heard from you
in a while thank you for the red super
chat
thank you
nice to hear from you peter lee
extension
what really feels like i haven't said
your name in a while
thank you thank you for being here
[Music]
yeah i hope you still watch my streams
yo
you do right you do
hope you do
now next one is something with
i think m and then that one what i think
[Music]
that means i don't know either i should
remember that when someone asked me
where where's the toilet
[Music]
it's a great pleasure to meet you i
can't watch your stream but i've seen a
lot of your clips your effort oneself
your love for your fans i hope today is
the day when your people are born
beautiful again
they're always beautiful
of course including you happy birthday
and that was a little bit of a weird
translation there but i think i
understand thank you
thank you
yeah you're watching clips huh you
should watch more of my live streams but
i understand it's probably hard to catch
when you live in korea but thank you for
coming by on this special occasion
[Music]
once again all the lovely heights here
i'll send them back to you
there you go
log082 thank you for the pinky happy
birthday the concert is amazing
thank you thank you thank you thank you
i appreciate it thanks for watching
[Music]
eight four five three four what a name
happy birthday thanks for the pinkie
tai chi to danger
that's a second
that's the second sub account thanks for
the pinky tai chi
too thank you
afterman's prime time
another pinkie thank you lovely lovely
lovely love
[Music]
i'm speedrunning this now
brutally
[Music]
this is where i'll stop lord evil i'm
sorry
you're where i'm gonna cut it up
1018 i'm over a thousand now
a thousand eighteen
it's over a thousand
[Music]
i think that's a good
good good point to stop i went i got
pretty far
so we have
according to this list is 1 400 free in
total
but you know the numbers are not
really
accurate so it's less less than that
i went for 700 supposedly supposedly not
really but yeah
oh
[Music]
okay
all right
now i can go eat some food
and make a thumbnail and try oh my i
should make a thumbnail first you guys
want to chill with me while i make a
thumbnail
[Music]
ah
if i look for like
fan art from both of us i
the only way i can think of doing it is
using both our hashtags all right
fascists aren't the fascists
arts of ashes i think
oh cute there is some cute lauren
[Music]
i wanna use some art oh
that one's cute too what the hell i
don't remember this one
cute
[Music]
look at some of these arts i haven't
seen yet
[Music]
wow
you know what i might go with this one
this this one doesn't even have art
hashtags
but this one's good too
maybe
one of them
one of them for a different colorado
like i have this
i could like put this like on the left
side and then extend the white thingy
and then put portal 2 logo
or or this one it's cute
[Music]
they're both cute
but the right one is more saturated
which you know is actually good for
thumbnails
[Music]
i'm carrying her in the game
okay i'll try i'll try to carry her
again but this one i must use at some
point too
that is cute right
okay okay i'll use this what it's called
i decided four or four all right all
right
[Music]
some of the time
some of the time get some work done
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] oh no that's fine okay
where do i have the portal logo
i saved it before but
[Music]
i'm going to make the background
transparent by deleting
my stuff around it
[Music]
porto
all right then let's
take this
bring it over
[Music]
stream preparation happening now
i don't know i don't like this image
from like portal
let's find them differently pour it out
porto
images
size big
[Music]
tough choices man
open image in new tab
copy image
paste image
memory this i don't know
not the best thumbnail
[Music]
uh
placement of logo
[Music]
muzukashi with this art i don't wanna
overlap too much but i want the logo to
be big
i haven't uploaded the schedule on the
youtube comment ah somebody tweeted at
me
i need to do it afterwards
i'll try
[Music]
i don't know what to put maybe here
i should show you guys what i'm doing
[Music]
uh
what is that capturing
[Music]
i'm not sure what that would be
capturing so i'm kind of scared to do it
even in studio mode it doesn't show me
properly
let's go back you'll see it in a moment
you'll see it in a moment
i don't want any oopsies
no oopsies allowed
[Music]
basically the stream is already over i'm
just
letting you
bathe in my sunlight a little bit longer
dear chimpkins i hope it's warm and cozy
[Music]
okay
i don't know if i like this
it doesn't look so well with the art i
think hmm let me try the other one
let me try
if i use this one
[Music]
i still want to use the other one but
maybe another time
[Music]
i need a book
[\h__\h]
[Music]
don't look directly at the sun
i want your chicken eyes to be hurt
[Music]
all right signed
i can't help it
ah your chickens are out of control
[Music]
yeah that's fine
fine
now give it a
outline and a drop shadow
[Music]
maybe here
maybe if i move this a bit more like so
[Music]
i'm just too beautiful
thank you you guys are so charming why
did you learn all these
ways to be so charming
who taught you
[Music]
giving you guys
such intricate
lessons on how to be a charmer
[Music]
nina you know was a big influence
i can see that
okay
looks better to me than yeah
you know saturated images just really
help
with making it eye-catching and also the
composition
works better this way i think
[Music]
yeah
all right it's simple recently i don't
like putting too much text on my
thumbnails anymore i like to keep it
simple these days
[Music]
thank you for streaming oh you're
welcome
it's basically my my job i like this one
but that's me loving modoki yeah there
are things so sweet so
ah
the art style is so fluffy and so soft
it's so pretty but they always draw me
with these huge padankas and huge hips
mmm very curvy i'm not complaining
but yeah curvy
curvyness net
good stuff good stuff
so this is the portal two
two two two
okay nothing too special
but that's it
[Music]
it works
okay then i at least already got some
work done now i can put up the
reservation let's go i'll put it up
immediately
oh
[Music]
all right hope you guys had a lovely
evening
have a lovely day if you still have a
lot of hours left today then make the
most out of it
thank you so much for watching
tomorrow is kona with portal reporter
lukova
i hope everything goes well tomorrow
i haven't played portal in a while
yeah i still remember i mean yeah we'll
be fine hopefully
hope we can continue where we left off
last time properly
[Music]
i haven't talked to her in a while
ah such a sweetheart all right so see
you there it was a rough day but i got
to cut your stream i hope you feel
better
[\h__\h] rough days
[\h__\h]
point the middle finger at them
stupid day
you suck
[Music]
wonder if she remembers momentum i
wonder if she remembers europe
uh
also hey i saw you know in clips and all
that uh of the the new incident of uh
from portal
no not from from the birthday stream
whereas like a number from one to six
and you know
there's no reason to be like so
serious about it but in the comment
section some people are like uh it's
kind of kiwama's fault because she says
one two six and the intonation you know
it's yeah it's her fault
she should have said one through or
between or so
shut
up shut up
[Music]
complain about everything you complain
about everything oh my god
oh my god
[Music]
yeah well i know english is not my first
language
excuse me i'm trying though i'm trying
and i feel like you know other people
understood
and oh my god i hit the comment no no no
no no
[Music]
yeah i i thought it was funny it was
such a deja vu oh my god
let's see what we get tomorrow from kobo
hopefully communication goes well
tomorrow
[Music]
goodbye
and in german we say auf wiedersehen
cozy bed is waiting for me like my cats
and tusk master maybe maybe umbrella
academy if i'm in the mood also watching
a lot of sims 4 gameplay again recently
i haven't in a long time but recently
i've been watching like there's there
has been oh [\h__\h] am i going on a last
minute tangent
there has been a
um
a game pack or whatever um recently
that's about werewolves and you know i
think it's kind of cringe like it's
basically just a furry game pack
sims gold fairy
um
i feel like i don't know i don't really
like it but i'm watching a whole
playthrough on it and
yeah
watching it is okay i don't think i
would want my sims to be werewolves um
they look kind of cringe in my opinion
but there's a new um
pack coming out soon
uh i don't remember when but i think
maybe maybe even this month
uh it's
uh about high school live
yeah there was university before but
this time they're adding like high
school lives so you can go into the
school and all that and yeah they're
yeah
adding high school life so we might
check that out
when it comes out but i also want to
play sims one because sims one i had i
bought the whole collection
yeah
horizontally academy at home tony in
school yeah back to school
we will see we'll see
sims medieval i played that a long time
ago outside of the stream before hold on
yeah i like it
i like it
it was fun anyway goodbye
[Music]
lucky
do
[Music]
you