[Music]
come down
what's up
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
ah
heat oh yeah
did you guys notice
did you
I saw I think I saw one person noticing
after the fourth Loop that perhaps that
was pre-recorded
um yeah um cow carrot put together a
better higher quality version
with my looping singing voice in the
background
so I don't even have to do anything
but it was funny
I was laughing at myself
oh man
yeah hello everybody
it's been a long day already uh
you're tired
some of you may have seen me
45 minutes ago on the switch
Channel
of dokumi
uh uh-huh I was there for one hour
before this stream
uh talking to with the organizer of
tokumi and with Iris
and then before that I had some
appointments
or one appointment that I'll tell you
about but
I'll tell you about but a little bit
later
um so yeah I've been up since 9am
and haven't slept that much maybe like
you know for Kiowa standards it's just
not enough
so actually no I mean I wasn't that
tired in the first part of the day but
I'm really used to having
a nap in between by now so I think my my
body wants me to sleep less but also
wants me to take naps like I think I
think my body noticed kiwawa you take so
many naps these days
how about you just sleep less during the
night and then you'll get a nap for free
extra
so recently I've been able to
get through part of the day even with
less sleep than I used to get you know I
used to prefer to have 9 to 10 hours of
sleep nowadays
I wake up even on my own without an
alarm clock after like seven hours
but my body will demand a nap
later on
now today I have not had time to nap and
um
I feel it I feel it it's gonna get
stronger later
so I don't think we'll be doing too long
today
[Music]
I also have to get up early tomorrow
again probably
uh because I have to do something
tomorrow
yeah okay so hopefully I we still get
one dungeon done today my goal is yes
I want one dungeon and then I'm happy
as long as long as you have one dungeon
uh then I'm happy and I think it
shouldn't be too difficult
uh oh dear I do
no wait we already had some kind of lava
dungeon I wonder what the next one will
be maybe a water dungeon the whole game
is a water dungeon I wonder what it will
be we had some kind of lava lava flying
Earth Dungeon and then
a grass tree dungeon
yeah thank God I don't really like lava
dungeons so I don't like the atmosphere
I want something more refreshing today
let's see what we will get
what there's other things in the normal
mode that I can choose
oh but [\h__\h] no
I can choose hair mode I thought that
was something you only get to choose
after you you've played the game once
okay
there you go
what was that sound
thank you let me look at my capture card
let me look at that really quickly
okay
weather orb oh maybe it really is a lot
of dungeon I mean it would kind of make
sense
[Music]
time
down
[Music]
good morning [\h__\h]
what do the birds mean again
oh
everybody
bye bye
[Music]
is this where I need to go
don't stop my music
[Music]
that must be that one down
foreign
[Music]
remember this place so well
what is the meaning of this
the island it is
we are too late
I knew we had precious little time but I
never suspected how little
a great water spirit named once lived
here but no sign of him remains
what's up above are you hello what's up
what's up yeah I guess I think I
remember
oh this is kind of like
the Turning some kind of a turning point
it's like oh [\h__\h] where it's late
oh so you're here I've been looking for
you are you by chance seeking the great
spirit jaboon
I'm sorry to report to you that jaboon
can no longer be found here
just look at how this place has been
torn to pieces I suppose this too is the
work of the shadow in The Forsaken
Fortress but fear not jaboon was able to
flee this island before it was attacked
he is in a safer Abode now
would you like to guess where the other
boat may be how the [\h__\h] would I know
[Laughter]
at the moment I said how the [\h__\h] would
I know I remembered and then they turned
your own Island into a dungeon
[Laughter]
don't tell me before I tell you
on the island where you were born on the
outset
I like that name much better
yet even if you were to go to outside
now you would not be able to see jaboon
for I am too weak
the cave where we are just sealed with a
mighty stone slab that repels all who
try to pass it why not even the pirates
with their Mighty ship could get in
I must apologize kiwawa I thought if
anyone would know of your whereabouts it
would be the Pirates
oh
I told them this tale without so much as
a thought for their consequences I don't
know what they hope to get but they
immediately set sample outside Ireland
and tried to break into the cave
it is lucky they could not gain entrance
I've heard that they were last spotted
on Windfall Island but doing what I do
not know
do you wish to see jaboon I think you'd
better search for the Pirates on
Windfall Island
is everywhere else boasts clear skies
and calm seas but this place suffers in
the dark clouds and rain
what will we oh probably the answer is
yes but I wonder if we'll get
um a Melody where we can change the
weather
eventually Baloo must have been right
when he asked me to bring word of jeban
to you
we call this island cursed
chat is like dude
I would counsel against staying here
longer than you have to
hmm
dude you are so dead are you more tired
than I am wake up
[Music]
enjoying the story okay I forgive I
forget yeah we're just listening but
that is your decision I have told you of
jabun so my task is complete my job here
is done bye-bye
yeah for a lot of you guys it's early
what time is it for you guys
um
oh damn
10 a.m 10 a.m 7 A.M 7 A.M is PST right
not many of you guys here mostly 10 a.m
I think that means EST right and am
probably ESPN
yeah because I I like how uh most of Ian
kind of has PST Prime Times in the focus
so their viewers as well are mostly that
but PST is like
they have a hard time watching my stream
so if anything is EST watching me but
even for them you know it's always
Mornington but at least you get a
healthy sleep schedule you're welcome
okay if I can glide too for a piece of
heart here all right you know a lot of
uh the windbreaker huh
let's go
okay if I can glide too from here
I'll be on the lookout so I guess I
would have to go to the top
of some high point
uh wait how do I
we need to climb up somewhere
but wait is that the cape that I just
saw up there yeah yeah that I see the
cave okay but
is there something for my hook shot
those trains don't look like I can grab
onto them with my hook shot
yeah the question is can I get to it now
oh wait I if I get honest can I move it
with my leave
too heavy
yeah I thought so but okay
[Music]
Maybe
can I get on this one no
later maybe
later
you've got to remind me again
and I have a boat yeah but
when we go around a little bit with my
boat
and see if we can hello
survived the Sea Spirit has lived
through the trials of many long years he
must have caught Winds of ganon's attack
beforehand if we are to believe the
words of burrito Postman then the
Pirates know something about the cave
four jeboon hides
why don't we go first and then search
for them there
uh she's my dad
spiral Mountain starting point
wherever that is okay
I don't think
[Music]
oh well
um okay oh I just thought he was on fire
his boat looked on fire all right we're
going to Windfall Island
it goes on the weather is so shitty
let's get out of here
sounds dangerous though the music right
now A Dangerous version of that happy
music interesting interesting
oh do you hear that
oh is it gonna be like this the whole
time now because um
I need to urgently go to Windfall Island
the game is urging me
wait Windfall Island was that the oh
wait I'm going somewhere else
was that the one
well which one was that
that's not my home island is that the
one with the birds or the one with the
castle
or the town
oh the city okay
they need better names
oh just this
is this for later also I just remembered
we missed the the fish in the other one
now maybe there's one here
fish
interesting oh I need bombs here though
yeah definitely need bombs
don't see a fish a fish foreign
[Music]
is he gonna come here
yeah okay items
this fish eats so much of my bait
and take this
tell me something interesting
your original song because it's
happening in six days
like on like what Sunday
nah way too busy can't no no no no no no
no
if I wasn't so busy then maybe
but nah
um
Saturday yeah even on Saturday on
Saturday on Saturday I want to do the VR
stream with Raina
I don't know I think I'll have my hands
full
hmm
depends on the time though how long I've
never actually watched the Eurovision
song contest live
I've just seen some of the
uh performances one by one
cut
what it was quite going to tell you the
way the ray of light Shone out like a
shaft of gold for the cold Darkness I
used to kiss a little Jillian anyway I
bet if someone could shoot a powerful
spark into the top of that Lighthouse it
would light up again
of a spark
scream it
[Music]
oh thanks for that
how long does the numeration song
contest usually go for
I really don't know much about it
three to four hours starts nine PM my
time peace
9 p.m my time
well no I don't really have the time for
it
[\h__\h]
is it because I already have them up no
no no no
[\h__\h] what's the problem with him
now I'm just having anal
there we go it was not too far because
he's eating it now such a little shit's
head
I don't [\h__\h] Mommy
yeah
yeah uh-huh
cute Island
okay
they say that inside the ring of rock
that makes up the parameter of that
Island
it relieves an incredibly beautiful
fairy
the thing is nobody's ever met her
probably the only way you'll ever meet
her is to take a ride on the Whirlwind
and droppings well I can do that now can
I not
is that the one I can get now
stick around in the world one I can do
that
in here
but was he talking about this island
no you can not get here until later oh
okay
oh
he means generally a huge ass one like
that one and they will bring me to the
ferry
many questions
no answers
it's 42 and that one doesn't really help
well okay anyway we're going to the
Windfall Island
mm-hmm
I need items that I don't have for like
everything oh man
oh man I saw a fish there
I think a little while
I'm not gonna go looking for him now
oh treasure treasure
that is
[Music]
and breakfast breakfast was just a
chocolate croissant
and then later on
uh today later today of course today oh
oh sheep later I had
right before the stream a second
breakfast with some cereal kind of stuff
it is oh it's just as the postman told
us the pirate ship has stopped here to
avoid drawing attention of the townsfolk
are you serious the ship is so huge no
matter where on which side of the island
you're standing everybody will see the
[\h__\h] ship
yeah this is not gonna draw any
attention at all no no no don't worry
about it you totally hit and I can't
feel and then
[Music]
Hey where's my snack
[Applause]
get out my snack
my salami snap
[Music]
hmm
should I get into the boat into the ship
no
I don't know because I don't know how to
get in there maybe I jump from above oh
let me change this and oopsie
and let me change no no okay
now
I've got mail
good evening
one letter
and find some nice crests and return to
me orca
okay Orca I already have a couple but
I'll come back to you when I have way
more
so I wonder can I
it's perfectly placed right at this hill
sounds like a yes
sounds like a big yes
YouTube you're good
you're good that was fast
I just had this genius idea to jump into
the ship from here am I a genius or what
open
oh Queen's Pirate's ears is that like a
question
to get me in
the Wind Waker obviously it also cleans
my ears
oh but wait I have to find out the the
password first
is it not the Wind Waker
uh
take a guess
um
[Music]
okay
oh where do I find out the password
though
are they currently in the city and I can
find it out for being in the studio
[Music]
oh I was wondering why you guys were
saying fauna I suppose because she does
ear cleaning ASMR okay
sorry for snacking
I only had like two small breakfasts
no proper
lunch or so
hi YouTube
hello YouTube
why
what's happening
YouTube are you drunk
no my PC is fine
should all be fine
streaming cool
what do I go oh can I still do an
auction now it's okay though I don't
need it
I hope this won't uh continue
uh let me see what's in here maybe we
find some Pirates and some hints for the
password
what
I have another
been in here before or is this just a
shop that works at night time it has a
potion which comes with a bottle
oh hello hello
you are stronger and you're wrong and
totally true shall we Juice Shop
you must have heard our potions are the
best I'm telling you they're too good
I mean [\h__\h] they're absolutely
incredible
hmm what
what's true jelly you ask looking
somewhat bewildered
oh sir you simply must be joking you I
don't know what sure jelly is
just ask yourself this could sir what is
a robustly nourishing element
what is a mystical substance that is
good for the body of the Mind ask
yourself
um
uh
uh burgers
the worst chew jelly we're out an answer
to these questions proclaiming
themselves to be true why it is the key
ingredient in the most effective potions
around
okay
Empty Bottle
ah don't need your stuff
you won't give me an extra Empty Bottle
that's sad
Sunday
foreign
let's continue looking even further
[Music]
what about nah it wouldn't be the camera
the one place I've never ended before
was this place
I mean at least not in this play for
let me go yeah oh wait you say there's
Pirates at the bombshell why are you
telling me that
let me go from the side then maybe I'm
supposed to enter from back
or maybe not
mini game
oh
me oh man I think I remember or
something like that
link no no no no no oh
you can't climb up here is there
something special oh
yeah oh yeah oh yeah small
like a baby link
oh I hear them Pirates
oh was it right for me to enter from
here
I went past the battleship minigame oh
no
look don't be mad at this it's not our
phone that we absolutely Gotta Have
bombs to get the treasure way after how
about you just think of it as a payback
for the national Monopoly you've been
running here yeah
I couldn't think of a monopoly joke
right now
so I bet you're thinking it was
foolhardy Jazz Pirates to pay such an
outrageous Bright House yeah I bet you
huh
you know Gonzo I still can't get over
that beat up by stocking you put it you
pulled to get that information out of
the postman
who you do is movement who was this
they're telling me they sent my ass on
that quinoa I just knew he was hiding
something back about that yeah so when I
started Postman I just pretended like I
was all worried about that hidden stuff
and Blasting away spilled the beans
wait who's Gonzo and which one who's her
good way ganja really just Top Notch you
know if you're cunning and Miss Tetris
smarts if you two got married and had a
kid wait who's saying that I need name
tags
Gonzo is the big guy
that came with me the greatest pirate do
you ever stand the Seas yeah the
greatest
now he's talking maybe
you idiot keep him up should you don't
be so stupid he's flashing
Miss Kate were you listening to this
network can you dark him some paper or
something
quit goofing off both of you
keep your childish jokes to yourself and
get those bombs back to the ship
the second you're downloading them up or
setting sail for outside Ireland
Miss we have to leave immediately but
it's been so long since we're weren't
sure
we need you for little bellies with some
good eating yeah how about we grip get
some grub going free cheese pizzas and
stuff like that
and we know that I'm fine either way of
course whenever you say is fine Miss I
what I mean to say
is he still he talking yes it's just
that the boys were so excited to come to
town yeah and I came up to think it
would be awful hard on them to live so
soon without the proper layout but
so what do you say we sell tomorrow yeah
what do you say miss the treasure isn't
going anywhere
[Music]
you're right with me right boys who's
fortnite of fun
oh they don't really seem to want some
fun
you're all fools do you know that you
sounded the most Island you saw the
senseless destruction
you have to hurry on to asset or the
same thing could happen here
sounds like they're uh trying to do
something good though
not to be just disrespectful but by the
sign of things you're worried more about
that Island than the treasurements
[Music]
I overslept what
YouTube room five hours
don't be up after the stream is over
don't be ridiculous ah don't don't be
ridiculous I want you know I want the
treasure
[Music]
oh
winky wink
all right fine how about your way we can
leave town tomorrow you big babies
oh
hmm
[Music]
today's password listen up care of him
Swabbies
[Music]
that makes a lot of sense cotton swabs
yeah okay
swabby
[Music]
flappy
it's a cute word
[Music]
zombies when I missed the game
could I have won something
besides money
[Music]
um
should we free the guy
should we yeah
we should take the bombs
oh you can jump up jump
[Music]
my free ham how about that
he won't mind right
[Music]
he's loaded
I say it but then I jinxed it I jinxed
it
[Music]
I can always play the game okay
um
I want the Buns
[Music]
not bad
Let's help him
I can't
I'm going to tell them
[Music]
I don't think I can help him
I'm sorry I kind of wanted to
okay swabies
oh before that let me quickly buy some
more
um
Banks because I'm running out of it
running out of bait
oh gosh you still haven't okay
brother it's really bad isn't it
how's the weather
I'll buy them
you have any more
yes you do
[Music]
[Applause]
the soundtrack
coming yep
coming
hi hi both
hi Boat
I remember when cam did a cute dancer
song did I
you mean to a different version and a
different cells again
yeah I don't remember doing a dance to
this
[Music]
time in America I don't live in America
here it's a 4 P.M 44. yep
in Austria not Australia
Swabbies
[Music]
but
I wonder what what Tetra what
uh was like trying to tell me
so she realizes I'm like I'm following
them
oh nice bedroom
[Music]
oh hello
didn't expect
so I clean your ears out wanna clean
your eye a pirate's ears
um
I'm alive very much on the other parents
then you got done in by that bird
monster in the Forsaken Fortress so I
thought never mind what I thought you
were alive I want to get it now you came
back because you missed me so much I had
no idea you wanted to be my swabby so
badly no no no
no it's pirates for friends wait really
really it sounds way too cute to be a
pirate word it should be yeah more like
yeah mate
[Music]
right after you left I went back to
being the bottom rang on no matter which
is why I'm stuck here while everyone
else is in town having fun eating oh
you're the only one left on the ship
right now
oh
that is not how you do a pirate I [\h__\h]
you that is how I do a pirate pirate are
whoops
[Music]
undermining me again and again and again
these people
yeah but that's not how you're supposed
to say Kiana
more like Japanese pronunciation
[Music]
oh
I know we set you to your next test okay
yeah okay
we'll be easy as well I hope you have
some treasure for me
[Music]
that treasure chest looks kind of
special
foreign
okay okay
[Music]
all right
oh yeah
there's the volume here a bit
okay
sweatshirt opens the gate is in the same
places before so go step on it if you
get all the way to this side before the
time runs out I'll give you bombs
sure you're supposed to do that dude
give me bombs okay can we first try it
yeah maybe I'm scared
[Music]
uh where's even the timer
I'm not supposed to be on the ground
right
I don't think I'm supposed to land on
the ground
I think I have to redo
no timer
Papa
watch it
how do you stop again all that like this
okay
ah instead of falling down I should go
from here to here okay
hi
[Music]
oh but wait how do I get I shouldn't
have done that I should have gone for
long
[Music]
reflexes want me to land on the box but
I'm supposed to land on the on the road
um
okay so much for the first try
[Music]
not only to go so high
but maybe later but here no need
and swing and swing and jump okay
okay we can already I think go to the
middle one no no no no no no okay wait
[Music]
and down down can we make that jump I
feel like we can if link stops being so
weird
don't don't go down okay yeah
[Music]
maybe not
no I think we can do it
yeah [\h__\h]
okay
fourth try fourth time is the charm
foreign
I'm going next go next go next door
stop
turn and go
back
[Music]
wait wait wait wait wait oh yep okay
okay that one works okay okay go down
okay from this one I think we must be
able to reach the next one
but wait a little bit because I'm
worried about the hitbox
I jumped too early yeah I'm so impatient
[Music]
I was so impatient
it was so close yeah the ropes are
moving I see that I see that
uh
[Music]
I like the music in here though even
though I don't I don't think it quite
fits perfectly
no go down
okay
and more and jump
oh oh I'm up so high
down and it's coming
I'm not ready I don't think I'm ready
don't jump on the wrong one
now let's wait for it again
hope that the timing will be right oh
[\h__\h] ah
yeah okay
[Music]
I guess I can't skip that one right now
so I will oh
[Music]
I wanted to jump to the other one and he
jumps away from it
[Music]
why do I even keep on refreshing this
when there's no timer anyway do I even
need to do that
oh
remember stop
no stop
[Music]
you go
depending on where the Rope is going oh
okay well I mean
we're just gonna go like this or like
maybe like here okay
oh that was close
[Music]
okay okay no messing up no go down go
down why you go up
[Music]
there's a silent timer really
I have yet to see it go off
okay
I think this could be
[Music]
yes
I hate
no no
[Music]
wait once you're here and how much time
is left
[Music]
[Laughter]
it was like already
and I thought I have to jump now but I
wasn't sure if that was really enough
momentum but yes it was really close
[Music]
oh my God I'm getting the bombs
dude you're not supposed to give those
to me
foreign
[Music]
well now now there's so many
possibilities oh
oh Ted try you've been watching
That's mighty courageous of you trying
to steal treasure from Pirates
you connected with my phone again huh
I suppose I should be shocked but I'm
more amazed that you managed to survive
after being tossed out of that Tower
from the look on your face I have to
guess you haven't saved your sister yet
huh
you don't give things much fun do you
just rush in never thinking how badly
things could go for you
like just now the only reason you got
what you did was because we left so
simple-minded little rat like Nico
behind to look after things
no one else would have played it with
our treasure so easily I assure you
but she knew I was around she wouldn't
have let Nico stay here alone if she
would have really cared
about me not getting the treasure
she likes me
H because you wanted me to have it
foreign
and just how do you intend to use those
bombs anyway don't tell me you're going
after jabun's treasure too
right now Japan is hiding in a cave at
the back of the island you are going to
where there is a big Stone in front of
it that I have to make go boom
and she even tells me all about it we're
going to relax in town and eat our fill
up whatever this town has to offer but
we'll be leaving for outside first thing
in the morning
okay if you take too long we'll come
sailing right by you tomorrow morning
and believe me you didn't get all of our
bums you'd better be quick kid
[Music]
that seems like a very obvious
invitation
for me to do exactly what she hinted
towards
lock him in oh
was he standing outside or inside
in any case
we have bumps
and I shall go use them
wait I even have them filled up it's not
only space so funny moms I also have
furry bombs okay another male
check her room oh is there something
there
Beatles shot ship oh
ah because now they have bums okay okay
okay
[Music]
I will always tell me where the the
ships are oh
[Music]
just Lord ah okay no never mind
I like lore sometimes but right now
right now I want to go
got the Pearl before they arrive okay so
all the whole dungeon within one night
okay leave it to kfp
uh where's my map OSHA uh where is
here no that's dragonairs
forsaken Fortress
in here and then there's very far
okay
not really a dungeon about that dungeon
eh
oh well I'll probably understand soon
enough
I cannot shoot on my boat as well
[Music]
um
stop stop stop stop I want
I want you I need you
oh thanks for coming here fish
cute there you go
[Music]
here's my here's my map draw on it
whatever you want
I feel like we've seen that before
it looks exactly like a different map
that I saw
hmm
oh I'm sorry I wasn't reading
uh well climbing on three and one
wonders averages
somebody's gonna scold those countries
and set them straight for the sake of
the poor teacher all the kids on the
island
eh
you want me to scold them
okay
well another time perhaps
another time Oh wrong direction
[Music]
yeah baby
you know what that that hurricane yeah
okay I didn't want to go in right now
but I was about to say that it might
actually get me closer oh I can shoot it
now but I don't know man I don't wanna
just just eat me up
could get me closer to where I need to
go don't
what I don't shoot him yet you mean
don't get I thought you meant don't get
eaten enough
I finally I couldn't can fight back now
why not
my
after arrows okay okay okay
[Music]
foreign
direction again
okay now we're about
about the right direction
money money money money money money
money money
keep your eyes out for flocks of
Seagulls when sailing okay
you'll think they'll be out here in this
weather
I kind of think no
what is this
a fish damn it
looks like a goal
for like a a race
um
how far along I am I've just had um did
the the three dungeon last time
now we are going to my home
Island oh hello there
[\h__\h] I'm too far
oh shark I can't
deal with the shot 's here
please
maybe here I don't know
ah
oh she did it again
a boomerang oh
[Music]
yes
I'll leave
oh maybe let me try
wait how oh my God
oh they only dropped one coin but they
they give it to me okay
hey
I killed the whole group of sharks
what do you call a flock of sharks
what do you call them
that is cool really
even with sharks because I know it's for
some fishes like that but maybe not for
sharks
a shiver really that's cool
that sounds pretty cool
a shiver of chefs because they make you
shiver
what the [\h__\h]
I have to kill him before it sucks me in
are you [\h__\h] kidding me
oh my God
um excuse me
[Music]
I don't know if I can do that man
I'll try
hey
I keep on getting closer
ah
oh oh
maybe maybe there's one at two eyes
already glowing
is
there another one here
no
only one left
[Music]
[Applause]
is it is it done
it's done
well that's very threatening
very scary
oh
[Music]
oh oh wake her up
thanks to you I have been freed from the
beast's spiral grass
and thanks I shall give you just a
little of my power
[Music]
foreign
twice
damn oh good that we got that before the
next dungeon
May the Winds of Fortune always blow
across your bowl
I don't even have a bow
okay
wow
I feel very blessed
okay I think I just saw uh sharks but
what did that or maybe it was the
Shadows
well
we did that
oh my front of the ship okay
um so are they in fixed positions and
this one I got now so I don't need to
look for her anymore here I suppose
yeah okay
nice son
nice
that's double the amount is pretty damn
good
not that I felt like we needed that last
time okay never mind
jumping out of the boat in the middle of
this huge deep ass ocean no thank you oh
thank you
this is the only fairy in an October oh
oh I see me was that the one that I was
told last time to get
and that I was supposed to be reminded
of this time
was it this one
oh [\h__\h]
okay well done good
um
have you noticed Chihuahua Morning has
not broken since we arrived at great
fish Isle the land that was so ravaged
by monsters it is as if time itself is
Frozen
[Music]
um
perhaps this is to curse that while you
spoke of
whatever the reason if this night does
not end then we need not to worry about
the Pirates overtaking Us in fact it
might not be a bad idea for you to visit
your home town and family again
that's a flag
after such a long time away
uh
we can speak with javelin after you do
I have a feeling
that my grandma is dead
uh
let's see them
[Music]
grandma
are you alive
[Music]
oh my God
oh
[Music]
about me
okay wow our real don't go oh she's
dreaming don't leave oh don't leave you
poor old grandma hello
[Music]
foreign
okay but at least she's alive that
really
relieves me
not the time I'm sorry
but I love the song should I visit
anyone else
the light is on up there
oh no should I say hello
I'm Gonna Let You Go oh oh no never let
it go oh oh oh oh
is that your Cuba well look there's
still your state
it's good to know your grandmother has
been having a terrible time of it ever
since you left
she rarely leaves the house and as far
as I can tell she just spends her day
sleeping she hardly eats
thus is the life of a grandmother of a
hero
I've actually come here to see if my old
grandpa knows of any medicine or
anything that might make her feel better
so does he
oh okay Lola you've come back and in one
piece too gracious my granddaughter
tells me that your grandmother is in
poor health these days I'm certain that
a little fairy dust would provide all
the lifts her spirits need but well the
problem is I haven't seen any fairies in
these parts recently I met one just
recently
fairy fountain
you I have a fairy wait how about the
fairy we can like put it through the
cheese grater and then we have fairy
dust no
because I have fairies just don't have
the Dust
I can use my favorite oh okay cool
but he wants dust
[Laughter]
there was a time when I used to like
playing with fairies
but now
they don't like me anymore
they prefer kiwawa
in any case ever since the fountain was
blocked up by that huge Rock I haven't
seen a one
oh it's not a dungeon it's a fairy
fountain
but jabuna's there
two
okay
but I have a fairy and someone said that
works too but I should go there anyway
because the story tells me to do so
oh my God
and we reach from here wait why don't I
just go with the boat
is that what I'm supposed to do
maybe not
yo
I think I need to go around the island
like this oh maybe maybe not
what
okay I shall go
give Grandma fairy first
okay
all right we'll do then I can pick up an
extra fairy when I go to the fairy
fountain
okay
those [\h__\h] trees how fast are they
growing oh my God
grandma grandma
[Music]
do I just sprinkle it on top of her
where's the cheese grater Grandma yeah
or I mean the knife maybe worst case
I'll use the knife
but she's great I will be better
or something like that oh maybe one of
those uh graders oh [\h__\h] sorry that I'm
like a bowl and you stomp stomp stomp
stomp stomp
now
[Music]
oh take it
okay oh my God that was gonna be so bad
if that didn't work
[Music]
grandma
oh
okay Wawa is that you Grandma is always
happy to see you bright shining face oh
wait a second I need some ice tea
no
[Music]
um
oh my God
oh
this is so cute
I don't have a grandma anymore never was
really
much involved in my life anyway
[Music]
but this is so cute
that's so cute one day I'll be a grandma
like this
um I'll make someone I'll need someone
some sweaters even though they'll hate
it and I'll I'll make them
worst case it will be my cats
and uh I'll make cookies oh no no no
I'll make I won't make cookies I'll make
I'll make a cake but in the cookie box
there will always be suing
um materials
you were safe that's wonderful just
wonderful
I'm so happy that I wait is this an
optional thing
can you also choose to not do this at
all because I feel like it was optional
but that's so cruel why would you not do
it
is oh
did you do this did you heal me oh
you're such a sweet child yes it was me
oh that's right you and your sister I
really are trying to so hard to be
strong
and I've just been sitting here moaning
and worrying it's okay it's only
understandable like what the [\h__\h] you're
you're super young children are like
gone and and you're old you can't really
help them
you've not even move much from your
chair
um
I'm your grandmother I'm the one who
should be taking care of you I'm so
sorry kilo I haven't even considered
what you must be going through
foreign
it's Mother's Day
so it's also Grandmother's Day
Grandmama
[Music]
I tried to call my mommy but she didn't
pick up
maybe later maybe later
it was sure what's up
all right
ah so
grab myself and now I can always uh get
it from her right
nice
all right attack power also doubles
until the first time you take damage oh
now that is one hearty soup damn
okay there's two helpings
damn
damn there's usually never two helpings
in these shitty bottles
you and your sister love this soup don't
you if you run out that can make it for
you anytime you like thanks very super
chat
[Music]
grandma's going to try to be strong why
did it why did it Skip hello I wasn't
done reading
no no well at least now we have the soup
so uh should I use the boat to get
around the island
hey
why can I not manage to jump into the
boat anymore oh yes I am ready
as I'm ready
go up first
but I thought that's where I'm going
with oh
up
up where what's up
dog
okay
[Music]
I suppose so is he gonna teach me
something new
nothing much
what what
are you doing
oh okay Laura you are all right why did
you not tell me about Ariel that was
faultless of you
um
sorry
you're so interesting hard times ever
since you deported
I do not know what you have been doing
on your journey but you seem a little
more daring these days
that look in your eye is not the one you
left here with
possibly
okay
bye
just like that
yeah
does this Calendar's hits
[Applause]
does that count as one hit
haha
baby
I'm gonna fail this
[Music]
oh
press a I know I know 40 times
that's the answer that was on purpose I
counted every single hit was calculated
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Laughter]
[Music]
I pressed a you pressed
[\h__\h] you one more
mama
[Music]
you do press a at the right time
foreign
whatever
a button shows up that's a sign for me
to press a to scream a I mean ah
what was that
oh my god um
[Laughter]
[\h__\h]
I [\h__\h] hate you 65 oh my God this is
actually a little bit difficult come on
[Music]
what's that
um
you need to press a not screaming yeah
what oh I misunderstood okay
okay let me let me uh do it that way
then
I think there was a misunderstanding
we have to Brute Force this [\h__\h]
oh God I'm not ready
oh man
yeah hard time worry
wow
yeah
don't get coffee
don't get cocky
[Laughter]
I can continue oh
they get something special if I do more
spam chat if yes
okay
how much how much
how much 200
oh my God okay really
I didn't even look at this one and still
got the A1
and again holy [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
my fingers are like so stiff now
can't do it as much longer
300 but don't please oh my God I'm
getting the 300 this will take a while
though
they might go insane while doing it
okay I'm not gonna need a 300 I'm not
getting the 300 sorry guys
I did too many mistakes
sorry
about that
getting better though
oh my God
okay
[Music]
wait how many
how many okay
okay I mean 300 is definitely not
impossible for me
yeah
I can see it I can see it happening
I guess it was wrong of me to treat you
like you were still at a lowly page you
are a page no more what does that mean
make more music I'm on it releasing this
month
guys I've been talking about that so
long please support the new songs coming
soon
my goal is to uh have it out by the end
of the month
um no exact date yet still close I don't
want to decide until the MV is done I
don't know how long it will take
what am I taking with me
[Music]
dude that's a joke right
that's a joke
it's joke
500 for heartbeats really because
everybody's had different numbers no way
500 all right I'll be doing that
sometime
sometime much later
bring him Knight's crest for real press
how many does he need I don't have so
many I have
oh where do I see them
I have two
that's really not much
okay we need to go up to the ferry now
wasn't over 999 fourth wall breaking
really what 10 night Chris okay I'll
remember that
[Music]
I know
I don't know
you're just making things up 69 420 for
a piece of traffic what kind of [\h__\h]
is that
ah
yeah
I don't believe that kind of stuff you
can't fool me
no way that the game developers
are that cringe to put something like
that into the game
now
let's just cringe I'm so am I supposed
to fly uh from here
easy I remember that oh hello who the
[\h__\h] are you
oh it's so cold I could fly to the top
of that Hill if only is that
a hint when you've got rocket to try
a newly spoke a lot without thinking
it's a secret that's quite a secret
which Hill what is he looking at oh over
to the Head
that's why Triforce is are you kidding
me
a Snapchat
[Music]
he looks like whatever is called in in
English
someone said in Japanese it looks like
snuff snuff cooking
moving moving
probably
yes
did you guys
think there was a resemblance too I
think so
is that a hole
I know it's just oh my God it's a stone
okay
um
should I tell you guys no do I have do
we have enough time
when are we not getting a dungeon today
yuck
now get off of me
hi
maybe I might tell you during the
dungeon that's probably better
what's this I see you
what's that light where does it come
from
I guess I was just more like more like a
like a bug
okay how about we place a bump here
and that's probably no no
that's where can I not just put them
down
oh my God
okay
that's probably what a fairy fountain
will
okay okay come Adam
set R to drop oh okay
[Music]
I want a heart
wow
this looks this reminds me of uh good as
we are chat world
not that it really looked much like this
but still
[Music]
Young
allow me to Aid in your quest
[Music]
let's go
oh would you look at that number
the fairies in this Fountain shall ease
you wearing it
when you grow fatigues from your battles
come here to be refreshed
[Music]
oh I'm covering it up
I want more but I only have so many
bottles and the other one has soup in it
so why you look so sad pomu
don't look so sad
she should be happy about it
but I'll learn from this if I ever meet
pomu I will try to capture her in a
bottle I'll legit bring a bottle
in a jar
Isha alrighty uh we did that what's next
ah we go with the boats to jab jaboon
what's whatever his name was
oh hello
you guys protect something special here
here
oh my God
[Music]
I didn't want to fall down but here we
are
okay the battle that we had with that
old dude actually might have helped me I
say while getting absolutely wrecked
sorry but I think my reflexes are could
be better now and some I might have some
some strategies now
wasn't there like a special item there
no
no so fast what the hell
[Music]
yeah
I've been robbed
I have been robbed
unfair
I not buy a light Emma
and the aprams I'm ready for them
I've Got a Feeling for them now
okay anyway now we can go to my my boat
right yeah
he's kind of feeling
that tonight's gonna be a good night
that tonight's gonna be a good night but
tonight's gonna be a good good night
feeling
but tonight's gonna be a good night but
tonight's gonna be a good night at
night's gonna be a good good night
I don't really like the the song the way
it's arranged in the official
release am I supposed to go in there
uh but I should bomb it under my bomb
bit then the thing will disappear
but I like you know uh how do I okay
I like it when it's sung like kind of
like a
capella you know
uh like this okay okay
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] okay ah
mean
I have a couple left oh this one might
have gone ah no that one was still fine
okay but now we're so far away I don't
know man
[Music]
that's kind of difficult to see with all
those dots
oh no we need to get closer
aim for the glowing part oh okay
oh sure
yeah
yeah top part gone
okay now we need the lower part
oh okay okay easy peasy
is it because I already hit it a couple
times no the little one
oh
fast
original hat no Crosshair really holy
[\h__\h] that was
a big Improvement then
nice
nice that's pretty fast oh pretty
so glowy
oh
[Laughter]
all right
um
uh
[Music]
we'll meet and deep trouble I'm pleased
to say that you're safe
[Music]
yes it seems goggle has returned there
can be no other explanation
[Music]
unfortunately that is not so
much
I didn't mean to stop working of course
it's working
but
you'll hear these voices and effects
right
foreign
the one I have brought with me has no
connection to the legendary one
and yet I sense great promise in the
courage that this one possesses
[Music]
I do it is the only way
thank you
[Music]
well the water spirit dabbing was kind
enough to give me this journal a
treasure of one of the goddesses oh
so I kind of get it before the dungeon
or do I also get an extra one in the
dungeon
so that foul rain and Endless Night were
indeed elements of a curse brought on us
by Ganon he must intend to cast this
land into pure Darkness for all time
[Music]
I believe I have
this is too stupid
they did not give a [\h__\h] about me being
in the room no they just had their
conversation there
foreign
that's it Free Press oh
are you ready Chihuahua
everybody
oh just remember there was one dungeon
where it's kind of like all on the water
like partially not all just partially
and then you kind of go through with the
boat oh no you swim I don't know I just
remembered one of them but also was it
was this about was this a statement
about this game that is kind of lacking
dungeons like there's not enough
dungeons oh that is the next one okay
is that about this game was it about a
different silver game
yeah
oh is it is about this one
only five
oh we already did two
they cut some dungeons here and added
them to Future games
so some tons of mini dungeons okay
lots of side quests yeah I guess so yeah
yeah but I don't know you know you have
this big ass Water World
I think what it definitely lacks is
Islands more more Islands you know
I'm ready Mark the place where you must
set the pearls on your seat truck I
already said one yeah I already did some
of the homework let me know
certain that the perils ahead will be
greater than any of you have faced so
far oh
you should finish any business you have
here and outside right now so that you
shall not have any regrets later
I think that's okay like we did
everything right we had uh we talked to
the the grandma we talked to the swords
dude
uh we talked to the
to the people who gave me the hint about
Grandma
um
visit the pig
they're Racing for this game I'm not
really trying to though it's I don't
know it feels very fast paced though
doesn't it
foreign
well I mean once we have like all the
tools we need well we can go more like
island hopping like looking also for
Treasure all the treasure maps so all
the treasure maps that I have
I want to actually go and find
the treasures
so yeah
um whereas is pretty much just the
beginning of the game oh yeah yeah yeah
I'm aware too like this is not
it
it's always like this kind of
they gave you they gave you this big
first Quest but
you know that's far from
far from like yeah the end game
uh fish
feed still fish here
foreign
this version makes everything better and
shorter making uh something shorter oh
fish Island I don't think that makes it
better but I've heard that there were
some improvements made yeah
I guess like shorter as in certain
things that were really really annoying
to do are not part of this game
[Music]
um
as long as they don't cut uh
the good quests and the main story
all the time wouldn't that be nice Oh
you mean teleporting
don't you have a weapon that can Pierce
things from a distance
no not yet not yet
okay
bye-bye bye
[Music]
I always lose the direction here this
way oh wait was all those Treasures oh
why is there five
are they all 50 rupees 50 rupee dollars
foreign
[Music]
but the other ones will be hard to get
because I can't see them anymore
yeah and I'm not good with that oh
okay
that one I can get I think yeah
Bubba
now they're all purple rupees huh okay
never mind uh I can I can keep some for
later when I need some more money
uh next up
almost there
[Music]
no way yeah hey do I need to waste my
bombs on you now for real
I don't wanna
okay yeah
so where am I where are we
oh we're supposed to the other one
okay
it's not out it's not this island right
no but it's right
right over there
on the next tile of my map
so no problem oh that was tingle Island
ah
almost there almost there
is either that Tower or that flat uh
thingy
oh
please did you see that
is that not the one that we already
filled
everybody
let me get off
because I only have two markings on my
map so
I would hope it only shows me the ones
that I haven't filled yeah okay
they just all look the same huh
[Music]
one Pearl remains
okie dokie
now we just have to go straight down no
don't talk to him
so damn want to go okay now let me tell
you about what happened today
it's so stupid oh man are these the same
people here
um
no hey
[Music]
hey no why foreign
just eat me up
[\h__\h] you
oh
where are we
okay
at least the weather is nice here
okay let me tell you now I have more
time to tell you so
um I woke up very early today like
around 9 00 a.m I was pretty tired but
uh well I had to go to an appointment
which was pretty far away
um and I calculated enough time in
theory I asked Google Maps how to get
there okay
and so
I went pretty early I even was able to
grab a croissant from
uh from the shop
yeah another appointment
not a doctor's appointment though
thankfully you're here no no no no
and
[Music]
um
now I took a train
and then
I was like Google Maps told me that from
the Train on it was not the only way to
go but it told me
okay okay
oh okay
it told me to take
um
uh Tom told me to take the an Uber or a
taxi or whatever from there on
um
it's kind of distracting okay and it has
yeah
man
is it easy with bombs do I still have to
hit the eyes
well
I'm still more damage
yeah oh well
the aiming seems more difficult
ain't got no time for your [\h__\h] right
now
please no
okay we're doing pretty pretty good
oh God we're getting so close
[Music]
[Applause]
is that all is that all go
okay
that's not another fairy is it
did you guys said that that's the only
one inside uh
the inanis
[Music]
okay ah gives me a treasure
a good one I hope
[Music]
not money come on give me something
special
okay hundred okay
it
are these like once I killed the one in
this spot is he never gonna show up
again either
[Music]
one gives you a heartbeat no they don't
worry they stay dead Okay gone forever
okay okay okay good to know uh wait
we're almost at the island
let me tell you the story when I have
more time
because I think after putting in the
last Pearl
will probably be told something
that I have to read
we'll get there guys we'll get there
story time today
get up there
shallow fish
I do need the map piece but oh well
[Music]
oh is that my boy boy
is that my Yakuza boy Ichiban Ichiban is
a new
calculator no no I'll try to tell this
one in one piece okay this is not worth
a whole
um compilation
it's not worth it
oh
oh wait it's moving it's moving it's
opening up a shrine like a dungeon from
below the water surface right
that's what we just heard
probably in the middle oh my God
[Laughter]
oh my God what the hell
oh yeah okay
he was like first very cautious then he
gets back and then he gets shot
unbelievable
and in the middle of that will be
oh a Triforce and the dungeon
and there it comes oh yes
all right I remember the tension but I
like a little like let's just remember
the existence and like dance with water
and all that but I don't remember
if it's difficult or so
why does it look like a paper dungeon
looks like it's made out of paper
or in Paper Mario
oh thanks for coming over
pick me up
or a link now
[Music]
wow
I I like the architecture
hmm
this Tower which the pearls of the gods
have caused to appear is a place that
the gods of the ancient world prepares
and amend it so that they might test the
courage of men
only one who is able to overcome the
trials that will wait here will be
acknowledged by the gods to be a true
hero
only then will that hero be permitted to
wield the power to destroy Grant evil
the master sword oh Chihuahua that which
you must obtain Now lies before you
You Must Believe In your own courage
which has led you to triumph over the
many hardships you have faced and you
must Triumph once again
you must rise above the trial of the
Gods wow
oh here we go
popsicle sword is still about it that's
our Master Sword
and in we go are you guys ready should I
buy bums that they will give me bombs
right
the grass will drop bombs surely
the Tower of the Gods oh dear huh
was it with raising and low wearing
water I think yeah ah there it goes
oh
oh hell no man
do you guys like this dungeon
do you like it
I don't need to get it oh is that
optional well I want to get it
uh wait I'm really bad at turning
I like it it's pretty
it's a bit long
and where do I go over there
but the fast one doesn't help in here
does it
there's no wind
okay both I'll leave you uh here
[Music]
great timing
great timing hello
raise it
oh [\h__\h] there you go Seth
don't worry link I wouldn't let you die
like that
bombs nice okay
okay
more bombs no okay Hearts is also
something I need what is this
or try it out in a moment I'll destroy
some more of these pots
[Music]
wait do I need to do I need them
maybe no
what is this
okay oh no no I understand
I put one of them on here
maybe the other one
on that other spot
I
here we go
and the other one here I don't know for
what
or if that even works because it doesn't
seem to have the same shape but there is
two so
Maybe
foreign
we'll just leave it there
but okay
first room okay it's dungeon time now so
let's see
okay
it's dungeon time now so I can talk but
let me also take a fruit candy
[Music]
before I talk
I wanna Rising here too
oh
aha
oh can I
can I not
get up to the other side
[Music]
I don't think I can do it even with
flying because
but what if I put a box
[Music]
oh
don't break the other box kiwawa do
yourself a favor
okay
so okay I woke up early right and I took
the train and then I was supposed to
take an Uber but I had like pretty much
enough time even if the Uber would have
taken let's say
um
damn it
let's say even if the Uber would have
taken 15 minutes to get to me
oh thank God
okay when it goes down it will be in the
same position
I arrive and I call an Uber
and there there is an Uber accepting but
it would still take a lot of time but
I'm like okay well I'll wait I have
enough time
but the Uber was finishing a drive
somewhere a drive for some other
passenger
at the moment he finishes the ride for
the passenger
he cancels my ride even though I already
waited like pretty long so I'm like okay
[\h__\h] you
so I ordered another Uber but for some
reason the area that I was in apparently
just didn't really have many Ubers so
the next one I
huh
the next one that I accepted
I see that I need this outside
[Music]
the next one that I got
also would have taken 14 minutes or so
to come to me but at that point I
already waited so long that I couldn't
afford waiting another [\h__\h] 15
minutes for an Uber this is not normal
here okay
um
oh [\h__\h]
don't don't throw it down there
okay
no I wasn't even traveling that far
um it wasn't even that far
but still
yeah
um so when I saw that the next one it
would take 14 minutes as well I was like
[\h__\h] I need a different solution this is
not gonna work
so I canceled that one myself
and I think I was charged for that one
because he was supposedly already on the
way to me but I think that one was about
to first uh
am I supposed to go in there
or the other way this way should I check
out the other one first
this one
I think um I think he was gonna finish
another ride as well that one too
yeah so I don't I don't think it's quite
fair but okay
14 not 40. still it's too much
normally I wait like what
free to 10 minutes maximum maximum
oh yeah well
so I looked up on Google Maps what my
other options were and there was walking
for like
whatever how long 30 minutes or
something like that which is
way too
way too long I would have been like
20 minutes late if I would have done
that
um
so figure this one out guys can I stand
here
oh [\h__\h] no just put it there okay that's
good that's good
yeah
I can stand on on this one too
yeah they shouldn't charge me
if I see if I order an Uber and I see it
will take that long
I think it's pretty normal
for some customers to be like okay I
don't have that much time
so I'll cancel that one
so uh any other like buses or trains or
whatever wouldn't have really worked
either
do I need this for something
ah I see I see I see
I need to move the box over there
probably so I can make this one explode
too maybe maybe I'll try
now I think it's kind of unfair anyway
what do I see right in front of my eyes
[Music]
oh
the thing is
I've never
used an e-scooter before at that point
can I move it please
um I didn't have the app or anything
either but I figured this was my only
choice to be somewhat on time
so I quickly I scrambled and I tried to
quickly download the app and register my
payment method and all of that and that
took me like five minutes I think so I
only lost five minutes for that stupid
stupid process okay
then I put my phone on the they usually
have like something where you can put
your phone do those come with helmets no
they don't and I didn't have one
but what was I supposed to do
what what am I supposed to do now
I'll just stand here
[Music]
if it works it works what oh that was
not worth it
that was not worth it
[Music]
it's not worth it
thank you
one way to do it yep
and now actually let's go in here what
the hell
maybe the map will be in there
although maybe the chest is not too not
special enough for that
Michelle
um
[Laughter]
it is the map again
we got the map yay there's four floors
okay
and can't leave the room now oh my God
where did you guys come from
looking forward to seeing five of you in
the scooter me too to be honest I was
thinking about that because
um I was having kind of a hard time
on the scooter
ice
anyway so I finally got everything set
up and uh I put my phone on there and
and put on Google Maps and tried to get
to the address but
um I had to put my phone sideways and
and my my new phone kind of can't keep
up with Google Maps and also can't
correctly show me which direction I'm
looking in most of the time so
it wouldn't update
when I was moving like it would update
like way later and it also wouldn't show
me the right direction so it was really
confusing okay
I tried to navigate my way through
this place
while being super in time stressed and
also trying to control an e-scooter for
the very first time I had no idea what I
was doing
I also didn't know if I was even allowed
to drive on the on the um
on the pathway for the normal people or
if I should be on the road I don't know
I did both I ended up doing both
uh yeah actually I did a great job at
following the map without it even
functioning properly
properly but I made one one mistake
I still had the roots set to
um
as if I was going by foot
So eventually it led me to go through
some kind of Muddy grassy path
and when I came to that point and
realized that there was not really any
going back and I was also like if I
change it now and I'm already late I
need to go through this now I need to
try
um
it was also kind of hilly so I I go I go
up the East Coast it's really shaky the
path is like so as never or less the
tire and it's muddy and grassy and
there's like three old ladies on a walk
looking at me and I'm like hello sorry
it's me with the e-scooter in the middle
of nowhere
free old ladies are probably like oh
these young people with their technology
these days
yeah
um so that was really awkward oh I see
fire you want me to jump
over there on the boxes ah but maybe I
should make a proper path first not a
little okay okay okay
[Music]
um hmm
let's start with this one
okay
um
uh finally I was done with the Grass Pad
but I noticed that the tires of my
e-scooter were completely covered in mud
and grass
are you scooter company I'm so sorry
okay
[Music]
you know
laughs
yeah
I was also getting really sweaty and
controlling the the e-scooter when it
was so shaking
it was really difficult it was really um
using up my my arm and my leg strength
to try to control this thing out
can I still do it
maybe with these boxes
[Music]
you have to go outside
okay I can do that jump maybe if I put
the
maybe if I space them a little bit
should be fine okay yeah
the small one should work too so let me
put
this one here
I think that works
thank you for the Super Chat
okay so uh continuing
um finally I arrived after
many many
um
problems
[Music]
uh I was I was 10 minutes late but with
the Uber I would have been if that Uber
would have actually came and not
canceled on me again I would have been
at least 20 minutes late so I saved some
time okay
it oh
I can make it
out there
oh it's too late
I also cut down
okay I shouldn't hesitate I guess and I
don't know if this
is the last jump
um too much
oh God
I wonder
yeah save 10 minutes no the story is not
over
that was 10 minutes late to my
appointment the person was waiting for
me there
um I was like hello I'm like sorry I'm
late I'm so sorry yeah [\h__\h] and
I'm like sorry I this is my first time
riding an e-school I don't even know how
to park this thing so he he teaches me
how to park it
I think it was already looking at me and
thinking what
what is this child doing is this because
I just touched the water a tiny bit
is that why that happened
[Music]
ah so maybe the I need to space them out
differently
okay wait a second
ah it's really annoying oh my God
I'll space this one but I always land on
the small one and that [\h__\h] it up so
the small one has to go I think oh I can
move it uh-huh
move it move it move it and then space
this one
like this maybe
um
but I can't land on this one no
sorry
[Music]
I'll space it out a little bit
differently
am I am I done now do I should I reset
let's do it like this
how about how about this
this could work
I think this works let's try you got the
meal
but uh I'll wait for the next time
okay yeah the small one's gotta mess you
up I think so too
so he looks at me
probably thinking what the [\h__\h] is this
child doing
and also helps me to park my stupid
e-scooter
and I try to explain to him that I'm
late because I was waiting for an Uber
Uber I was gonna be on time but then one
cancels on me and you know everything
goes wrong of course and I apologize and
all that seems understanding and fine
with it
oh
it needs to be a bit more in the front
Okay and then we have it I think
having the middle ones connected was a
good idea I think do I need a stick
spell am I running out of sticks let me
tell you this one
uh or do I have to can I bring them
is that my last chance are you kidding
me
okay I'll wait I'll wait I'll wait
matsum matsumatsu
[Music]
um where was I oh yeah I explained to
him and uh
yeah
um then he actually scolds me
like I said it's my first time riding in
these scooter so I didn't really even
know what I was doing and if it was a
lot of what I was doing you know driving
through that path in the rest and then
he's like didn't wear you didn't wear a
hammer did you and I'm like no I didn't
bring one I wasn't planning on going
with the e-scooter after all
we won with an e-scooter wearing a
helmet I know you're supposed to wear a
helmet but I don't ever see anyone
wearing a helmet
no one does that with an escoin and
maybe with a with a bike oh my God these
[\h__\h]
[Music]
[Applause]
oh man what did I just pick up which are
them did I pick up
I forgot
but we're done with the room right
I got a key
[Music]
yeah
oh well so the story is not over
on my way
um no no no oh yeah when I when I'm
parking the thing I realize it's it's
telling me
I am outside oh
yeah I am outside of the territory where
I'm allowed to put it uh where I'm
allowed to park it
so I'm like [\h__\h] I need to park it
though and since I can I can pause it
for uh two hours
so I'm thinking okay well I guess I'll
just bring it back to where I came from
uh maybe change the route a little bit
where am I supposed to go
change the route a little bit so I don't
have to go for the grass anymore you
know
where is the door where I need the key
let me look at mine oh and there's some
doors that I can't even see
hmm
oh I need to bump them ah yeah
I think
fire
ah thanks map for telling me
okay there's one more
okay
yeah series of four Unfortunate Events
exactly
I felt so so stupid going with the
excluding through that grass I felt so
stupid to be honest
okay both I'll leave you here okay I
need to go to that side
oh I hear you guys
want to hear you
oh this door doesn't even need a key
uh
should I need these for underground
oh that one needs a key you went there
damn it
can I go up first
I don't know where to go
foreign
my shoes were fine I suppose flat I had
flat shoes on yeah yeah
making an interesting story exactly that
was that was also what I was speaking
like I'm looking forward to telling you
guys this story
is there water here too
I mean yes there is yes there is yes
there is
do I need to Kill Them All
is it a requirement
I can't fight them now
[Music]
of course
one second one more
[Music]
South
I paused it and then after the
appointment I was planning on using it
again
so appointment over
I go to my e-scooter
I unpause it
oh I go
I walk like I go with my scooter for
like 10 meters
by the way it said if I just leave it
there I could have left it there but I
would have gotten a fine
so I said I will pause it and then bring
it back
but what happens
I go a few meters and suddenly the
scooter stops working and I'm like what
what did I do wrong now
this is my first time with me scooters I
didn't know what I was doing I was like
I tried to move it I'm like hey what am
I doing wrong
Michelle
but it just won't go on anymore
foreign
I suppose maybe the battery ran out but
the east corner didn't like have any
display or anything that told me the
battery rays were running out it just
suddenly didn't want to move anymore and
then I tried scanning the code again
because they have a like a code on it
that you have to scan before starting
and uh
when I scanned the code it said this
this vehicle is not usable anymore
no
so what happens Dell is
the system
now said I left the vehicle outside of a
parking area and got to find any
I got the [\h__\h] fine anyway I was
about to bring it back but it's just
something around how the battery or
something but to be honest I didn't I
didn't think that it was the battery in
that moment so I thought you know
that it realized that I was [\h__\h]
around so much with it that they they
wouldn't want me to control it anymore
oh my God what the [\h__\h] is that
what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] how do I
fight you
like that
I'm on fire
yeah I thought they were just like girl
girl all that mud and grass on our tires
and that routes you took we were
watching all of that and girl this is
your first time using e-schoolers but
you already banned for life using our
company's e-scooters [\h__\h] you get out of
here
and here's a fine to go with it
that's what I thought it was
but look I I understand you know I
really treated it badly but I was like I
was I was desperate
but I really messed up man
I really messed up didn't I
had with humor though when my when my um
when my scooter finally ran out and it
wouldn't let me drive it anymore and I
saw that I got the fine
I just I just chuckled and then walked
my way to the closest public transport
option
yeah
I want to shoot this one
no I wanna I just want to shoot that one
can I not is that not what I'm supposed
to do what are these things for it's so
sauce
not at all it up
ah wait does it close its eyes when I
don't look there
was related okay okay
wait but did I do the key room already
I did didn't lie
what did I get I got the statue and I
put it there
what's next
foreign
on the bottom
and ah because the water oh yeah right I
forgot about it bird brain excuse me
yeah yeah
thank you for the thinking thank you
thank you
appreciate it
okay
yeah so
um I
I always was like
like there were times where I was like
oh if I had if I knew how to use an
e-scooter right now then I wouldn't have
to walk so far wouldn't that be nice but
I never really used it until now because
I just felt like well I don't know I
don't know how to use them oh
nope
foreign
sorry
uh but yeah I kind of
I was kind of in a situation where I was
forced to use the
I
the East Guru today for the first time
which
I was glad I finally learned how to use
them
but
foreign
yeah
it was an interesting experience
for the very first time
or some lot of stuff I hope that
I hope that I mean at least there's a
I don't look cute at least there's a lot
of other
[Music]
s
scooter he's good at companies
oh I want to use them again but I'm
scared
I'm scared mommy but they're fun they're
fun to use
[Music]
definitely are fun to use like they go
so fast with no effort yo when I was
younger I had a normal scooter
and I loved cruising around with that
um
[Music]
foreign
thinking of getting myself my own
e-scooter one one day if I need one
or an actual real bike one day but
at an e-bike if anything I'll get a
proper bike I think what are we doing
here
let me look at this room
ah that one is open okay go into this
room first Kiwa wow okay
I hear you I hear you
you bikes are proper box can you use
them without using the electro function
oh am I supposed to bring one of these
foreign
I'm impressed by link being able to
uh
run at the same speed even while he
carries one of these other
stuff okay wait I'll kill these monsters
then
[Music]
here we go
ah wait the door is just open anyway
oh but do I bring them can I even bring
them from outside or does he leave them
there
they're pretty heavy to Pedal compared
to normal bike if you run out of battery
oh dear oh I can't okay
um
story anyway but I worried that I left a
bad impression with uh
the appointment person
uh check speaker of the goddesses god
post press said R to call me and guide
me to my place of Truth ah you're gonna
follow me I remember that thing is gonna
follow me and it's gonna be so annoying
press said r
wait while I'm on the bridge
[Music]
that r
I said I'm pressing that
what it said president R right
targeted
hmm
just walk up to him
oh
[Music]
come on
I'm a new friend
[Music]
did you learn the song what song I
didn't learn a song
not yet at least
all right we gotta be patient here we
can't go the top path we need to give
this body some time
lead him through a safe path
oh do I have to I have to throw him
right
I think yeah
come here
[Music]
you killed what huh
what
how else am I supposed to get him over
there
[Music]
oh wait I'm supposed to jump with him
oh
come here
okay
he has to come with me through here
because that bridge will otherwise throw
him off
okay but then then afterwards
here I can go with him
okay okay now we have to
help two things out you know
you tell me I can make this jump but I
can't throw him that far okay where are
we going with you
that way
it was too slow go man not sorry
sorry
at least it didn't reset us to the very
beginning
or no what is that eye for it so sauce
we have to shoot it later I think
ah
[Music]
mode oh
and now we get your friends
thank you for the Super Chat though
thank you acknowledged
next one is where
you're not open
you have to do oh I saw
a song
okay uh um
no no
wait I don't see it I don't see it uh
left middle right middle
I remember that
that would teach us me
left middle or right middle
I know how to do that cause
I am
I know how to use this wind waker what
gave you the impression that I didn't
know how to use my Wind Waker huh
unbelievable
[Music]
I can control them now ah
oh you won well I don't know what you're
talking about
I don't know
[Music]
guys
that's what I was hoping for
[Music]
oh dear hello
I blocked him and for what
I got burnt anyway
[Music]
and if he dropped an item it disappeared
in the wall oh well
um
where is that thing that I need it's not
here but I see a hook shot uh thingy
foreign
the dungeon is okay
don't put it here
but can I oh I think I can hit them now
what no
I thought I could
[Music]
maybe that was something else
what
people what's up
oh this works
[Music]
bye
um I am on fire ow oh my God ouch come
here
and you don't wanna
okay
almost fell down ah [\h__\h] I need one of
those over here
but I can't make them go with me
wait how about I just open the door and
sometimes just assume that every door in
front of me is automatically closed
okay
uh how do I even not need to go over
there I guess yeah
God damn it
foreign
[Music]
oh what's that motion control oh
I didn't realize that I keep on
forgetting that the Wii U gamepad has
motion control
I leave you here
Maybe
ah wait
no I control you make you go over first
and then I follow with the hook shot
okay okay
left middle right
left middle right middle
well look at him
link he's so into it and I am I'm
stature
I'm ready
you can come now
all right
if you say so
oh wow
[Music]
come with me
open
a good statue yeah
good boy oh who's a good boy I'll drop
him I probably need to go on this one
again uh oh
no this time you have to go there okay
foreign
[Music]
statue video coming soon
you got any Zelda game oh you played
literally every single one really even
the really old ones
the DS ones or so for example
[Music]
that's sad when you have played
everything like from your favorite
series
there's nothing
you can do that's sad oh oh dear hello
do I have to take that sword off of you
[Music]
yeah I remember that kind of
oh now I wait for the a button and
hopefully that ever turns up
when does that show up
[Music]
or can I attack you normally no oh wow
there's a boxer now but
holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
gamer gamer moment
wow
I was surprised that that went so well
great enemy failed
foreign
[Music]
well I didn't even use it
it's so strong
I'll grab a hook to steal I tried that
before but didn't work on the other
enemy so I was disappointed but here we
have the heroes Bowl
with 30 arrows
now we can shoot the Eye of the Tiger
The Thrill of the body I have the temple
oh
okay let's see how to use this where
where do I have to aim the middle of the
screen or
it has no
aiming thingy so I don't really know
where to go for
oh no it does what what just happened oh
no that's the hook shot
habit but not the ball
I don't know that that is a little bit
easier okay I'll shoot the idol
I'll shoot that thing then
oh okay okay go go go go
okay
I'm supposed to shoot this right maybe a
bit lower
there we go
foreign
[Music]
I like that might be a little bit
difficult to use sometimes but
we're gonna get used to it
what
it
Erica
need to go get the statue and then
with him together we will go over these
platforms you
yo
I am back thanks for waiting
my Uber is coming
what
was that it
okay
sorry
um moment
what's up
oh
[Music]
you
so slow
okay I'm not gonna mess it up again
[Music]
are you gonna attack me why the [\h__\h] are
they following me now
remember they following me
why would I reactivated
why why why why why why scary
very scary
[Music]
huh
because this is their leader
that makes sense
okay the last door is open
uh wait which one which one
that one
a glowing one
yes
okay
first of all please let me get rid of
those [\h__\h] pets but they move so fast
but it still follows them
it can
[Music]
we really get them with the boomerang
oh my God maybe just focus on one
wow
[Applause]
Boomerang oh for power no way
if I stand on them I see I seriously
I already understand without even giving
it a try
one more I think one more because
otherwise
or even maybe even two more
[Music]
oh maybe not maybe not necessary
I thought that if I would jump on it it
would change again but there we go
I don't have a key do I do I
or just one key work for them all no I
need a key
[Music]
down here
I think
out of all the Nutella games I've played
so far
my channel
I feel like
um
which is Skyward Sword and
[Music]
Skyward Sword and uh uh uh Lynx
Awakening
hard to say where he's going
yeah
ah wasting
I think this is the one I'm doing the
best in wouldn't you guys agree
I'll stay here I would agree
hey
yes partially the reason might be um
because Skyward Sword had those shitty
motion controls
I don't know what my problem was and
Link's Awakening though
Emily
finally
uh there's a chest here
this looks complicated it was probably
not that bad
what the [\h__\h] was that the name
can I even hit this from here
I have it
[Music]
can I
oh I can
where am I going to the chest ah okay
jump on that one jump on that one
what is this
okay
yeah I of course of course it's the key
what else would it be
oh anything else oh there's another one
another one
nice
[Music]
now let's shoot that stupid skull as
well
um
oh wait I can shoot like that oh okay
that makes it much easier I was doing it
with the joystick okay in this case the
door uh the the motion controls are
actually helpful
uh
ah should I go on that one
okay
[Music]
foreign
indeed
let's try this one
oh there's an apple one here okay I
didn't realize
why am I going here
what is there to see
yeah
oh another eye oh
from here
I think I have to do it I do that while
I'm on the platform
okay
nice shot
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
just money probably
oh no Enjoy panelokai hmm
let's get take everything we can get and
now what's the best way to get back do I
really have to go
from platform to my phone oh okay lucky
[Music]
wow
pakura
on The Deco Leaf oh
never mind this is a pro move
everything according to keikaku once
again
at your shop
you know I don't know if my mom is
watching the stream now but there was
actually another reason why I wanted to
call her
oh gently oh
I know what to do
urgently before
My Stream today
um
I looked at my raspberry plants
oh damn it the other way around uh
oopsie
I was looking at my raspberry plants and
I noticed something
[Music]
um
they are growing
like real legit
mushrooms
so confused
why are they growing mushrooms
I forgot the name now but it's
apparently even an edible mushroom
[Music]
a white edible mushroom mushroom I
forgot the name if you guys would say it
I would probably recognize it
too much water no I think
um you know because I got all these
um roots from my mom's Garden she said
that there might be like mixed with that
something in there
you know by accident and then you know
because
maybe I don't know
[Music]
they could just there just could be
something else there
for whatever reason
not on purpose but just
it some kind of
I'll throw it then I'll try to time it
[Music]
why does it not open
Sports everywhere they may have just
well floated in yeah either dad or it
was in the soil for some reason
um but the story was bought from the
store I don't know but from somewhere
for some reason
no it's not just pills it's a specific
type obviously
um I have some kind of what do I do
the mushroom
s
with my raspberries now but I don't like
mushrooms you could it said that I
Googled it oh [\h__\h]
I Googled it and I said
I could eat it you know but but I don't
wanna
oh my God
um is there something important in there
because I can just for the life of me
not figure it out
no not Champions no no
[Applause]
let me get on the platform
too late for me to me it just looks like
I'm throwing too high
but okay
[Music]
I'm throwing
sorry link
um Pro a
[Music]
okay there we go
that was annoying
[Music]
the measles kind of stages
I don't know
the ones where I have to throw bombs
into their
mouths as I remember
no way I can I was supposed to control
one of them
should I stand here
it says check let me check
designs that reflect window drawn here
wind
the wind
do I need my blowy thing you know
[Music]
I thought you make them open their mouth
mouths with wind also why do they have a
nose and a mustache like Wario
well I'll wake the wind
which one though the controlling one
left middle right
[Music]
okay
um
left right
up left right
no win for me
do I have to stand on the platform oh
yes
I couldn't see it so I wouldn't feel the
effect sure sure okay okay
foreign
[Music]
they grunted like a pig
you're not gonna give it to me yeah
uh oh yeah okay
uh hi uh oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
I got one
[\h__\h]
[Music]
[Applause]
okay I needed those items thank you good
ah
[Music]
okay okay okay
and I already opened the chest actually
no okay
we got
him wait isn't that the master key just
are we already that far
the boss key I mean not masuki
oh
no ah it's a [\h__\h] treasure chart
foreign
okay well you got my hopes up there
treasure chart really
really
huh so that room was kind of optional
because I got nothing
in there
[Music]
was it optional
I mean I would understand if it was
optional because the wall honestly
I could have
maybe if I wouldn't look at the map I
may have not seen it at all
okay uh I have to go ah over there do I
have a key
[Music]
I don't think so
um
did I pick up a key somewhere I don't
bottom right I was looking at my screen
my map my item thingy but it's written
on the on the main screen
yeah I was looking at the other one damn
it
one more one more one more one more
looking at my items
you're sure
oh yeah so um
I got mushrooms now
I'm not very happy about it because it's
confusing me
I hope they don't take do I should I rip
them out I need to ask my mom mom pick
up the phone
[Music]
no the bottom screen doesn't say it no
no I mean on the main screen yes but not
in my item thingy my Wii U pad
[Music]
box
Move the Box through the laser
if I can
is it not movable
ah am I supposed to fly over there
no way
foreign
[Music]
I got that without you Chad
you guys honestly don't need to back
seat me on this game
most of the time
I completely understand
what I need to do
except for now but just give me a moment
ah I let him go first
[Music]
um
yeah
I don't mind you guys back sitting
generally but
for this game
The Riddles are
pretty
easy to grasp
no backstabbing
please knock back stabbing especially
not with the Wind Waker because that
looks like it would hurt
now what is this for ah just for me to
jump down from and fly over okay well
now I just bring you outside
really that's it that's it
oh
yeah I don't need any help me
why is there new enemies now
which weapon are we going for
shoot me
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
okay
[Music]
yeah okay okay
another new enemy and
wait ah I first have to set the platform
otherwise I don't think I can bring him
over
[Music]
let me do that really quickly but I
might have to put more than usual on it
because with him I have more weight
right
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
normally normally I think two was enough
now I might need three
I think meet today
we can also just put four on it just on
just in case
nope
I asked that's too far
don't want to regret anything after
wards
[Music]
okay it's okay it's okay I already did
they respond immediately when they fall
into the water anyway okay yeah free was
enough I knew that I knew that
[Music]
laughs
there it goes number three do we get the
boss key now is that what spawns there
when I have all three of them collected
I think yes oh Triforce
oh
it's a teleporter
One Dial
wait a second let me try to get some
materials
on it
okay
I'll take that
oh hello Kiara hello welcome thank you
it's a material world yeah yeah yeah
yeah
oh I always pick them up I can just
break them with a sword I forgot what is
this room where are we we are on the
third floor
there's not much here
oh I think it's literally just getting
the key and walking into the boss rim
according to the uh
I'm going to the map never mind that
might not be all of it
uh-huh
one two three uh-huh okay
I think we need these ones and me
because there's only two
oh
[\h__\h]
okay calmly
[Music]
sure did you see the food on Twitter
than the name yesterday it was really
yummy yummy I thought it didn't look
look as aesthetic as the other ones that
I made because it's basically just
potatoes
sausages and salad it doesn't look so
special but it tasted so good
thankfully I have once again some why do
I go there oh some leftovers
oh
so I'll be eating those today
um they were supposed to be made with
shrimps and with shrimps it would have
definitely looked a bit fancier but I
don't like shrimps so I I had some some
bacon wrapped cheese sausages
in my fridge since a while ago that was
actually perfect I have four more so I
can make the same portion another time
what the [\h__\h]
what
connected
wait why is this not open
do I have to kill them
oh okay
with the bow
uh wait turn around
uh uh okay are you dead
wait turning around is kind of difficult
yeah
I might have to hit him on his butt
monster
cute it's like those uh those those
monkey buds
[Music]
okay come here in your face
hi hi
don't get hit don't get hit
baboons yeah
there it is
and here we go guys it's boss time
oh bird hello
oh
no
ah
just run fast no wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
uh oh
[Music]
wait I want that oh wait wait let me let
me pick it up
go before it disappears okay now what do
I do with you I don't remember being
able to hit you like
but let me try
oh really
oh
okay
ah
you can't
I know
wait out
what
happened
yeah very stressful right now
I want that but I don't want to get
close to that pink one anymore can you
come back please
made a mistake
that was close
okay okay okay
now we need two of them does it work
like a boomerang too
oh
I need the heart and this heart okay
oh no not pink ones
and what do I do about the pink ones
shaking
hey
maybe nothing maybe just walk past
bye-bye
you guys say run two but whoa
I don't need you
guys it feels like such a waste when I
don't need them
okay you also just walk past them
I didn't save uh we better win
guys
yeah
um
can I save now yes I can okay
thank God
[Music]
did I say
okay
[Music]
well but if it's uh
even
as long as it's not a million times more
difficult than the last one if it's just
a hundred times more difficult than
where we have no problem here
let's let's go
22 arrows I hope that's enough
um hello
oh
um
[Music]
GameCube
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
yes yes
oh no don't clap me please Don't Clap me
Please Don't Clap me no that's so scary
how do we do this
is that it
[Music]
don't don't don't spam them
and now do you eat bombs too
baby
[Music]
I wonder if I run out of arrows
okay I got that
one more
oh
it doesn't give me enough
[Music]
we only have eight left
what the [\h__\h] do I do
but she moves so fast
oh [\h__\h]
you'll see some oh okay okay Hallelujah
here we go
there we go and now you want what bumps
[Music]
oh yes
well then I'm not worried anymore oh
can you not
[Music]
one more error left
Make It Count there it is
we have more arrows thank you how many
10.
uh where am I shooting to
[Music]
I'm just gonna spam them now
I don't care give me more give me
hello
thank you thank you
you're gonna do it endlessly right
foreign
[Music]
okay the hands are down I'm getting some
more arrows
now we take the eyes
so the [\h__\h]
[Music]
hey
oh my god oh oh my God
[Music]
if he gives me arrows he resets oh [\h__\h]
it puts potato
[\h__\h]
okay I really have no make it
oh my god oh
[Music]
can I just go straight for his eyes wait
he doesn't reset I only killed one more
hand
didn't reset
[Music]
no no [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
uh
[Music]
oh for [\h__\h] sake eh
okay he did reset
well I'll just go for the eyes then
not those eyes not those eyes
okay no
ah okay we have one eye we have one eye
we have one eye it's fine it's fine it's
fine it's fine
but I don't like it when he
um focuses on something he shouldn't be
focusing on
[Music]
yes
he's down
[Music]
how many attempts we have to do this is
the second time
[Music]
oh you want me to do the hands now okay
wait I only have three left will he
reset
please do not reset
stop moving like that
[Music]
okay one hand down two arrows left
rule of three well last time it wasn't
free was only two times
time Limited
[Music]
no please don't reset okay he didn't get
his eyes back I think we're good
okay no
one more okay
[Music]
for time for time
hit him
yeah
now you're gonna make me reset again
[\h__\h]
not fair not fair
ly like difficult to figure out but he
is kind of annoying
oh now he's got him really fast or am I
just imagining this
he doesn't give me much time to work
with
okay one eye one eye done
foreign
[Music]
I need more arrows please sir please
thank you
[Music]
is there a way to not happen
um focus on things that I don't want to
focus on like can I switch
and I control it more
I don't know
better
oh well uh
what's up doesn't matter we're done
[Music]
why don't you talk so fast
yeah go back you go back
go back
wait where's the master sword
am I getting that one too
am I getting it too
oh yeah
what
mother
but then the my boat says something
about
getting the master sword what the hell
did I miss interpretate that or am I
getting it here
and we're gonna pull it out of the stone
like Arthur
out of the
Triforce
no on it
there's nothing up here yeah
big bell bell
didn't see a bell
[Laughter]
right
[Music]
do I get the master sword then
huh
what is in there it's a monster sword
the the thing that makes the Bell go
ding dong
I'm done
I'm done both son
oh that's a teleportation thing
to where I will get the master sword
surely
and bound
uh
you have done well kiwawa
it was seen the gods have acknowledged
you to be a true hero
but this does not mean your trials have
ended here
once you take your first step into the
world Beyond The Ring of light you see
shimmering in the waves before you
your Trump trial will begin
are you ready kiwawa
is that
the World Behind that kind of black and
white or was that a different game
wasn't there like a monochrome
well
is that something else
it is old his face he has really two
link has really great faces
[Laughter]
[Music]
link
should be a YouTuber
where are we going uh he realized he can
breathe normally
oh they're singing the boat
[Music]
that's a Hyrule
oh
in the past right in the past I think
the past
and I think we'll see in Zelda
[Music]
I think
nice
you are probably wondering where we are
aren't you hi
unfortunately there is not enough time
for me to explain it to you now
don't worry I already know
once you're able to strike down Ganon
with the item you obtained in this
Castle
all will be made clear to you they make
it sound like we're already at the end
of the game
what's happening
but we're not right you guys said we're
not
but like are we past 50 percent
Albany
that's the point oh yeah all right okay
but it is basically 50 okay okay
trust in my words see what awaits you in
the castle
I don't really remember
what came after this
when I see them happening
so but I don't really remember what what
happens like what awaits me in the far
future so that's good I can still enjoy
it without spoilering myself too much
that
yeah yeah it's nice to see these things
again these scenes hmm I really enjoy it
normally I don't like replaying games
but I don't really as I mentioned before
I don't really consider
me like this me being having having
being played it before
[Music]
you know what I mean ah
oh it's me yeah
yeah I don't think like I ever really
completely finished it from beginning to
end I just
played some itsy bitsies here and there
is also ages ago
Zelda so which high rule is this
which um
which game is this
is there like a
which do we know which one it is
[Music]
I'll meet you to listen to me for a
moment
the item you seek is hidden somewhere in
this Castle to find it you must find the
entrance to the basement
but that entrance has been blocked by a
mighty threshold firmly sealed to
prevent evil from ever gaining access
do you know where to search and what you
must do to open the hidden way you will
find a clue in the shape of a heraldry
near where we arrived the castle
well I don't know what you're talking
about but what I know is I need to put
these things together to look like a
Triforce no
are we missing a piece
wait what
are we not playing puzzle right now
why can I not move it oh
I'm supposed to do this now right
I was about to say can I not move it
because the time has stopped
but that is not the case there you go
one down a couple to go uh
oh dear oh dear
uh
okay the first one was easy but it it
is
it what
I can put it pull it over here
okay I can pull it not only push it
well then that makes everything a little
bit easier and here's your second piece
there we go
one more it's all the way over here
hey is this the second dungeon
I don't know how much awaits me like
when is a good time to stop we've played
three hours 30 minutes I can do some
more
I'm not gonna do some more it's uh not 8
P.M yet I'm okay I thought I would feel
more tired by now
I might just not rate super chats but uh
what if yeah
but I'm okay not really a dungeon oh
okay ah [\h__\h] I'm in the middle
okay okay
[Music]
no I don't want a cliffhanger
I don't want that
foreign
[Music]
this is the third one okay
okay okay can I open up here
no damn it
I don't wanna come out of here and then
suddenly have to fight all of you which
maybe really be what I need to do
hello
why are you so cute am I am I
you've got good news for me
hello
excellent kiwawa to perceive such a
puzzle and December it is no small feat
AKA only a gamer like you with that big
bird brain can figure it out amazing
now take the sword that lies before you
it is none other than the master sword
that blade of Evil's Bane
it is the only sword that can banish
Golem from the world above
oh will they attack me
ikiru
are they gonna come to life
I wasn't ready I was not ready
oh okay
[Music]
oh what happening what's happening
what's happening
oh they're knighting me oh oh well done
well done
actually it's not monochrome it's Sapia
[Music]
do you call it Sapient English oh there
we go
[Music]
oh
what did you think it was happening I
thought they were gonna kill me
right at the spot
huh
um wonderful
this is no problem
so
do we have to escape
is that it or
wonder how much time we spend here
stronger I guess double damage Maybe
[Music]
wow
do we have to load up this master sword
as well with some extra power
was that just some other Zelda game
fees back oh hell no no [\h__\h] way
no no no no no
yes we have to load it up too okay I got
the master sword the Legendary Blade
with the power to repel evil once
wielded by the legendary hero himself
it will be continued by the to be
wielded by the legendary hero
wow how do you how do you shoot
how do I shoot them the laser
or can I not shoot it
oh
looking for a secret
is there a secret
no beam and 3D games oh okay
[Applause]
okay I mean even the Link's Awakening I
barely used it because I barely was ever
full HP
so yeah
I'm used to not being able to use it
um we're just gonna walk out like that
oh there that dude right next to me
oh God
[\h__\h] kidding me like what
okay first instinct run what did what
what's happened
okay the other ones are not paying
attention anymore nice
foreign
[Music]
absolutely obliterated what are we doing
in here should we just walk out should I
explore
and kill everyone on this floor
out
[Music]
um oh yeah you're with a big deal that
was a boss before actually I feel kind
of nervous about buying you
[Music]
oh okay
nice
[Music]
okay these ones are none that easy to
fight so maybe don't necessarily want to
clear the hole dungeon hey I didn't even
completely get him naked
like I did the other town
I thought you have to get them
completely naked first
yo I got the big
the bill oh with that can I not actually
damage them even when they're uh wearing
the armor
let me try
I mean you are different
does this do more damage
[Music]
let me see let me try
no more big armor guy up here
it would be kind of ridiculous if this
did more damage than the master sword
yeah
[Music]
the hero is bad
no time for Monsters I'm here to clean
up
[Music]
okay I cleared the second floor what do
I get for that
do I even
need to kill all these this is
ridiculous it would be a ridiculous
thing of them to ask of me right so
let's not do it uh where are we going to
up or down
up
almost ran into that
is that gonna disappear
I do have to oh
I
I don't have to
okay well I mean no problem for me I'm
coming here
no problem for a hero like me
[Music]
oh
out
[Music]
give me the prompt
[Applause]
s
[Music]
okay I'm really
feeling like I'm I'm massacring
these dudes
I want use this sword to kill one of the
armor guys
you see what it does but uh here
here we have one
oh [\h__\h]
damn it
and let me pick it up please okay
oh no
he uses his shield
useless trash
[Music]
oh I saw your back for a moment you
shouldn't show me your back unless
you're a quesada
then I like looking at your back
[Music]
finishing it beautiful
hey do give some nice drops ooh the
crest we need the crests
Pro Warrior noises you think you'll
notice are damn it could I have sneaked
up on him I wonder or do they always
know this even if I go from the back
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
oh [\h__\h] I'm such a broken
[Music]
I'm too good for this game foreign
like this uh
like this
especially if you throw a sword at them
oh nah that's too easy
we both play like a Pro Gamer
oh so easy
[Music]
oh I did it though even I didn't even
want I didn't try to
I
I'm sleepy
[Music]
I feel like I'm in some kind of training
camp right now
yeah come here
I feel like he just stopped himself
[Music]
using his break his inner break
eternity
I was scared about this in the beginning
but never mind it's not scary anymore I
wasn't even sneaking what's the matter
with you dude
I was not even sneaking
[Music]
wait let me
can I have the money
hmm
okay sorry
uh he wouldn't listen to me play music
for him cute
out
dude sorry okay
[Music]
the disrespect what
I just I don't disrespect other Warriors
if you can call this a warrior so we go
up or down now I killed everyone
think up
they better not respawn
and have me kill all of them again or up
okay
behind the stairs yeah what the [\h__\h] do
I need to look there
down to explore again
[Music]
oh that feels so good those hits man
with that sound effect oh there we go
feels so good
um
okay
I down to explore I mean that down to
explore it but if I go through and then
come back they won't uh
they won't respawn right that would be
like crazy normally
okay but with this amount
A1 okay
it'll respawn but I don't have to kill
them oh okay
breath of the Wild
by the graphics
I was like
it's kind of like
I've seen it before but
I've seen it with better graphics before
oh
oh yeah okay I can't go past that no no
but that's cool to see that yeah
they probably just use these Graphics
because you know they wanted it to look
like oot
not because
look at that water sorry for the roast
it's a little
damn it
let me go up
you don't want me to make fun of it
yeah this is just because
um oot you know
um they wanted to keep that feeling that
vibe
it almost looks like it's made out of um
what's that what's a toy
what's that toy that you can shape the
way you want
small link too small he doesn't even see
any of this
Play-Doh yeah
looks like Play-Doh all right I think
I've seen what I needed to see
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign I want to look at the picture
so there's Zelda would I know all of the
other people if I played oot properly
I mean there's obviously the king her
father
well I don't really know about the
others no
I wouldn't
but
uh is it obvious when I look at this
not really
I I did think there were some
similarities
[Music]
um
a little bit like as if he's the father
of you know who
and that could be the father of the
other you know who maybe
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
I don't know
very interesting are you yawning Are you
seriously yawning at me
don't worry can fight and kill so many
mobs and I come out here and you yawn at
me
you know what did I could be staying
there
that was disrespectful if anything that
was pure disrespect
but that he's Landing are we are gonna
go let's go
[Music]
are really just going really okay okay
okay
we're back
hey what now
there's nothing on my map
um
you're not gonna tell me where Ganon is
oh yeah
okay he just ignores me are you mad at
me did I do something to make you mad
dude
oh I talked to him okay I thought why
does the hero need to talk to the
underling the underlying should try to
talk to me
first ask for permission to speak and
then I say yes speak
and then he must speak to me
yes first you ask for permission mm-hmm
and then I give permission
sword I'm obviously the hero now my
status has changed
anyway
[Music]
oh that looks funny looks like one of
those candy rings
disgusting candy rings and you lick for
hours and hours
of those candy diamonds you know what I
mean
keys that control that fate are none
other than the lucky items known as the
Triumph Forks works there's some sort of
magical utensils if you want to learn
more about the tram folks actually that
guy tingle
okay
I mean it's disgusting because you lick
them for so long
the rain pops yeah oh but some of them
oh yeah right some of you can um dip
them in sour stuff and that's what
actually makes it worth it licking them
for so long because then there's some
more you dip it again and then you
continue looking and you dip it again
and then you continue licking right yeah
yeah they come with these you're these
sour dippy thingies the packages I
forgot about those
ah yeah gives you some variety of taste
oh man I need to check in the
supermarket if they still sell something
like that
um
Supai Sato
there is
[Music]
no
no no no
yeah
okay I'll take it back maybe they're not
that disgusting just just the thought of
you know
that you would have to probably I don't
know how long does it take to
lick that until the end
because I feel like he would take breaks
and then I don't know some fuzzy things
would fly on it and I don't know
hmm we could do a challenge buy one of
those and then
just you can't see it but I I'll
do a challenge try to lick it until it's
gone in one hour
[Laughter]
I wonder if one hour is actually a
challenge or if that's easy
[Laughter]
nah they probably don't even sell it
anymore I don't know I need to look in
that kind of uh section
can I talk to you only if I'm off of the
boat
why do you delay oh
we're going to the first second Fortress
oh dude why did you say it like as if I
should know
I don't remember you telling me that and
I was pretty like focused and listening
okay no never mind
um that sounds like it would take some
more time
um we can go
uh there and on the way check some
things out maybe
okay there is
wait wait wait wait uh forsaken Fortress
there is um on right ahead of us one two
three four five six tiles
that we have to pass through that I
don't have the map off yet so you know
what the challenge will be
I will get all the six [\h__\h] fishes
I will not leave this tile without
finding the fish first
but we're not going to The Forsaken
Fortress today
deal
you see the fish or is that stupid ass
fish I need to grill it
is
what do you want boobs what do you want
[Music]
basement I see him
no that's not the same mouth
that should be
so I looked away for a moment uh
fish
um
um should I try to kill this thing
take take him take him down on it
oh
they're bad
uh fish was scared of the bombs and
disappeared
let me kill this thing first then
uh
[Laughter]
okay okay me you were right in front of
me so
fish
look like you are closer
intense match
great that they have about the same
Amazon just even a little bit worse oh
[\h__\h] sorry I don't want to bomb you
I mean I could maybe I should
quite the standoff pirate I'm just
trying to get on their level
so that if they die they feel like they
died
by fighting
a proper fight you know
for their honor hmm
so that their soul can leave their body
who knows so maybe you saw the map now
I'm going left all the way to the edge
of the map and then up and getting all
the all the maps on the way
so oh I didn't read sorry I forget that
you tell me things
I look later what you said
I even have another Beach
I might not ah no I have enough bait
all right
let's talk a little bit about the dopami
podcast although there's not that much
that I can that I can say like I don't
know what to say but
yeah if you watch the twitch today then
you may have seen me and Iris on
Friskies channel dopami channel
um in preparation because the docomo is
happening very soon in like
a little like two days less than a month
wow so soon oh my God
um
so we talked a little bit about
all kinds of things conventional related
things
and oh wait
what I missed that was fast
no wait I have
wait what
I don't have this one ah fish is that
you
know
what
it's confusing
but I have this one
it doesn't show a white square oh
because I'm on it maybe
okay okay
sorry I was a bit confused there
ah yeah I forgot to turn myself into a
cat so I switched it Midway through and
that made me go blue but transparent
because they adjusted my green screen
um when I was wearing the kimono so I
was like whatever whatever as long as
I'm a cat
and I'm happy
so is that square fine now yeah okay
okay now it's white
hey
you have a nice background that that
background uh style looks familiar to me
it was probably the same one who made
the holotalk background I think it was
called omorphia
that person it's funny how you can
recognize certain creators Style
art style
looks very familiar I don't know if I'm
correct with the assumption
but I feel like I might be
yeah the Cat Cafe
background was really cute I didn't see
the fish
no
look closely
over there
no
[Music]
what
ah there he is
I'm on my way
yep is that really the one
is that not the one from the next map
no ah when they jump that high is that a
sign that they're new fish so I can find
them easier
oh he's like really on the edge of the
map
uh fish
a bit
take it quick
foreign
no I don't think Iris was left out at
all we spoke English most of the time
but physically sometimes translated what
we said to German he tried at least
one time I even translated myself
oh I see now there's like these maps
that have these numbers am I supposed to
go here first because it's number one
you've seen those weird rings of light
that appear on the scenes at night
haven't you
oh I don't know which Rings you mean
though
those things are sure sign that there's
a treasure in it oh those I'll kill cams
so wait those only appear at night
[\h__\h]
what you don't know
shut up I'm not delaying
I'm on my way
go fast
always with the upper hand
no but um maybe that made some of you
guys realize that translating so much at
once
it's quite the challenge
no
not something that anyone can do that
easily
yo I love those waves so
wow the waves are so fun too be boating
in
where's the fish
oh no wait I just got that fish
so confusing because the map doesn't
really turn white because it's red
because I'm on it
just got that fish I'm so confused
a fair Flex
thank you
yeah uh what else uh yeah
um
he mentioned something
special
foreign
they don't they didn't mean the thing
that was previously hinted at
if you listened closely then you know
anyway what it was
uh but it's a cool thing anyway
nonetheless
oh [\h__\h]
I can't I'm not gonna say it even though
it was already kind of sad but I'm not
gonna say it
um
yeah I think um
yeah they were there was something that
I was hoping for that was kind of like
it seemed pretty sure that it was gonna
happen but now it's not happening
and a little bit disappointing but
I still have some other things oh also
about the applications they said 30
people
um but originally I asked for having two
time slots for the meet and greet
I mentioned it again after the stream it
should be fine so it's probably gonna be
like I don't know how many people you
can fit in two hours but
it should be more than 30. but I don't
know if
I'm like 30 in one hour is
realistic to be honest
unless we extend it a bit
but I think it's more gonna it's gonna
be more like 50 maybe maximum like in
total
meet and greet cost 60 Euro no it
doesn't
they said six
Euro not 60.
did I miss her or did you miss here
I heard six I thought wow that's so
cheap
oh they corrected later
oh
oh 60.
I thought six additionally to the
to the docomo ticket
oh
oh sorry
oh that's quite a lot I'm sorry guys was
not my decision but you know I suppose
it has to be
um
you know
there have to be some Cuts made to
certain people
like maybe in whole life maybe and maybe
Me Maybe
I know and yeah if it was six Euro then
we would probably have a [\h__\h] ton of
submissions
hmm
uh
well to be honest
um I think
when you think about meet and greets
it's not even
that weird of a price I think it's quite
common
oh yeah the question is it if it's a
raffle and you spend 60
euro is it only going to be charged if
you win
wait did they say something about that
how it works
foreign
okay well thank God so otherwise I would
be like what the [\h__\h]
uh come around oh when the left half on
this side do you want the left half
um we had a right half
four two
um
how long I'm eating greets for well I
want to be able to meet as many of you
guys as possible
um so you know it will be three minutes
per person that may sound like not much
to you or it may sound like a lot to you
compare it to the idle handshake events
that I went to in Japan where you
literally only had five seconds I'm not
joking
compared to that three minutes is pretty
generous first of all and second of all
I had
um
the last time atokome when we did meet
and greets last year it was also I think
three minutes
and from my experience it really depends
on the person and and how how much the
person prepares and how fast you talk
and all that and how much you are aware
of the time because I am aware of the
time I have a timer right next to me
during the meet and read
um like I had the feeling for some
people
time went by really fast
and for some people the time went by
really slow
[Music]
yeah
so out there is the fish it really
depends on how where you are of the time
and how much you
um
you plan to be talking
[Music]
um
yeah
[Music]
um
I think we should be able to
do the whole signing thing again
like last year
yeah
foreign
sorry I didn't listen
I was that love gifts for you what
I have something running
what
you have something ready for that one
and we give gifts if we don't get picked
oh I'm sure you can yeah yeah you can
just give it to staff members but make
sure to do it
within Saturday if possible
um
worst case Sunday works too because I'm
around they'll bring it to me
oh it would probably be good that you
leave it
if you don't find a fitting staff member
actually don't even look for your staff
member it might be best if you leave it
at that mysterious
thing that fisky slipped his tongue
about
you could probably leave it there
don't give me books I mean
that don't don't completely hey maybe a
nice cooking book with about baking or
air fryers
no that might be useful
[Music]
hey
it could be maybe a special drop of
place especially since like we had that
experience last year but I think I got
everything that you guys tried to give
me I think I received everything
hello fish out there
I I was even there when uh
when they opened the gift's hand to
check for safety security so don't put
anything weird in there
what's to get a girl that already got
everything
well
it's always things that
hmm you just don't get for yourself
even though you would be happy about it
the bird people us who live on Dragon
Roost island east of here have invented
an incredibly useful device that they
call a grappling hook I know I hear you
can throw that thing at monsters and
you're okay
steal items yeah yeah okay ah get the
joy pendants oh I didn't okay okay well
I forgot about that yeah
Uber gift card
[Music]
um oh God uh oh hey I got mail did I get
the ferry on this island
a living chicken no no living things
also
you should not really be giving me food
unless it's you know it might work I'm
not guaranteering it but it might work
if it's packed in a way that there's
absolutely no way for you to temper with
it absolutely no chance
but I'm not gonna guarantee it so even
if you try that don't don't think that
I'm gonna really receive it
I don't know
but you can try I guess if you really
want to
yeah just don't bring food
uh two letters number one
how are you doing kiwawa do you have
enough of granny's soup where are you
now wait is that Grandma are you hungry
oh this is
[Music]
are you keeping warm you have an injured
yourself have you
always drink so hard you whoa do you
have enough herpes
your grandma doesn't have a lot but I'm
sending it oh
[Music]
as long as I have you an arrow I don't
need anymore
he's still gonna die I just wanted to
love you to return home safe we will we
will I'm going to Speed Run the game so
that you don't have to cry I'll remember
ski
one more
I'm sorry to disturb you with this
unsolicited letter if the following does
not interest you please throw the letter
away before the second thought but this
is your big chance oh
auction do you have a need of an empty
bottle a piece of heart or a treasure
chart sounds like an auction we have a
special bargain prices but we have only
one of each
oh if you're interested go to the shop
ship
near Roxbury Island ah
where's Comfort served I can't wait to
serve you that stresses me out but I
think it doesn't matter when I go to
those who took the time to read this
letter please accept my humble thanks
assistant manager Rock Spire shopship
um please remind me next time
why the [\h__\h] did you give me a green
rupee with that huh
what
[Laughter]
oh wait no I don't think we can
you still can't go here can we oh we
need a hammer
the next item will be a hammer
in the bucket
ah I understand
all right I remember the hammer um
okay we need one more map I think or or
this one and and another one do we have
the one on this map probably not but I
see the fish I saw the fish
where is he now
each
day you know
is that him
what
I saw a there he is
you
uh where was I you don't there we go
peace
okay
where was I what was I talking about uh
the twitch stream
anyway I don't think there's really
anything to talk about if you watched it
then you know it's really only important
if you watched dokomi if you're planning
on going to docomi
huh oh wait I already got him oh [\h__\h]
see this map thing really confuses me
[Music]
huh
playing with you
to be honest you'll be helping me out
see I've been having some ferocious body
aches that only acupuncture can come
here try it out I'll give you 10 arrows
for that bow of yours and I want you to
aim those suckers at me when I leap out
of the sea
yeah see if you can hack me with them
okay for each Arrow you nail me with
I'll give you 10 Rupees and if you hit
me all 10 times I'll give you 10 a 200
what
okay let's let's do it do you call that
acupuncture oh God
you'll be fished on a spike after this
don't be I'm a man fish I've spent my
life being toughened up by seeds rougher
than any of you have ever seen those
arrows of yours can't ain't got nothing
on me oh yeah and you probably also have
been munched on by many many gudas okay
I'm not so good
is there a time limit
okay
gonna be here
[Music]
no time limit that's good oh
gosh
kind of move to the right side
nice
close one
foreign
[Applause]
could not really see that one coming to
you
how would I know
is there a tip
[\h__\h] okay oh
what why not
why not
are you making fun of me
Rose day sticking on him like Minecraft
40 rupees okay well I'm not losing any
money so what the hell I guess well bait
costs how much again
I got three pieces for for 25 or what
was it
Freddy oh okay okay I definitely didn't
lose money
do you get a heart container from this
otherwise I don't care about doing it
again
do you
know 10 rupee profit noise
yes no
yeah
I know
uh fish no heart okay I believe that
therefore I will never play this ever
again
oh I I see you
I'm coming for you
where the [\h__\h] did the fish go and why
are you in the middle of that
[Music]
yeah
um come here
these fishies are really masochistic
being in a place like that just for fun
and like he likes to get hit by arrows I
don't know man
what a weird fish
he's the bait yeah in this case yeah and
here we have the last map that I wanted
for today it's slowly starting to fill
up my
my uh my big map all the rings of light
you're telling me about the same thing
are you for real oh you don't even have
any other advice
it's running out of advice
wow that's lame
foreign
first okay we will go a little bit
closer
and
stop here
and set
and that was four hours 20 minutes of
Wind Waker which even though
I said I won't be doing much today is
basically
roughly about the same as I did
yesterday well I think I did like five
hours yesterday
so yeah not bad not bad
[Music]
oh
no I can't wait to fall into bed I kind
of wanted to stream tomorrow but now I
actually have to do something tomorrow
and I don't know
um I need a doctor's appointment and I
kind of don't know when I can go I'll
call as early as I can but I don't know
when they will be giving out the
appointment so
um
yeah I still need it yep I still need it
uh so uh yeah unfortunately
without knowing that I can't really plan
a stream for tomorrow so I'll do a day
off tomorrow and also make a schedule
later
um but I think I can read super chats I
just need to go to an idol meeting
really quickly okay don't go don't go
don't go kfp my beloved
yo
[Music]
Kami Mamita
okay okay okay
good
then
oh god oh wow
[Music]
wait a second I'm just looking at
something's okay now I can go
in a second
mate
[Music]
I'm trying to leave with some kind of
nice face but even though I'm like
really far away it still captures me
foreign
[Music]
I'm back
oh thank God I didn't stop in an area
with sharks and all that oh
hello
[Music]
okay
shall we go to the Cozy place again
let's go to the Cozy place again
bye
[Music]
[\h__\h] I keep on pushing the wrong thing
cozy place
[Music]
uh but no I shouldn't eat too much
popcorn because I'm gonna eat dinner
afterwards
yeah
no let me close the game
let's play some OST from the ocean
uh Wind Waker ocean theme
I want to listen to that
Great Sea theme 10 hours
so loud
wait are you sure
[Music]
okay
thanks for the membership welcome
back
[Music]
it's like I'm going for an ocean of
super chats
wow what an adventure
[Music]
on thank you everybody
for watching my stream today and
tomorrow yesterday too thank you so much
for always thinking of watching my
streams I love you I love you so very
much
[Music]
spending my time with you
let's continue
[Music]
ending yeah
happy Mother's Day yeah
[Music]
okay okay let's start Super Chat so
I don't know why I have so much energy
it's weird
um I'll probably uh be very tired
right after ending the Stream
not the konani energy
[Music]
ah
baby dancing
[Music]
I remember [\h__\h] Legos
thank you thank you so sweet
I will Dominican Spicy Chicken Taco
Garden dungeon
Dominique
and Mr cats big thanks to the pinky and
the Lord states that you're our adaptive
mother I am along with our boss so happy
Mother's Day there are a few hello moms
in her life but with your 1.46 million
chickens plus Cobalt plus the others
you've impulsively adopted you got the
most children meaning you're the most
powerful homo Mom oh joke Society you
give us a lot of fun and a nice dreaming
environment I'm so thankful for that
even if you've often forget to say Vegan
I completely stopped saying that I'm
like so done with that but
you say I'm like the most powerful mom
hold on mom but
have you noticed that
people outside of kfp don't really see
me as a mom character it's because I'm
not considered a mom but you guys
because of some huge milkers
but that's because of my motherly warm
love for you guys which is let's be real
[Music]
the best type of mom
but that's why you don't know until you
get to know me that I'm like a mommy
[Music]
I just wanted to hatches when we were
eggs yeah and I did that gladly and I'm
continuing to do so
I mean I have some yes
but not that huge okay
like compared to crony for example holy
moly
holy moly that body naked I drew on that
body naked because Ina gave me a naked
base
for all of the
I asked Dina for some help you know that
we have some like a base to draw on and
in a in a Drew all the council and hope
members naked
I mean no it was just you know skin okay
no no you know details
but
damn crony's boobies
damn
I wanna use the boobies
[Music]
thank you for the pinky I'd like to wish
a happy Mother's Day to Mama Tony I very
much appreciate the adorable hatchling
she raised I hope that she has the
absolutely best day for everything she's
ever had to go through raising that cute
Luna chick
are you calling me a lunatic
all right that's not really a praise is
it not really a compliment this wise I
know what is
[Music]
it okay
copy crazy
it's more like insane crazy not just
crazy
well okay let's ignore that
uh
[Music]
and happy Mom's Day to you too care now
that you have a new blue child who is
your favorite child you've had so far
besides your cats
my favorite child who else did I have
who else are my children
I don't really consider good on my child
it's my child besides Kobo
I'm gonna consider him a child
she's like
that child from the neighborhood
that I have to sometimes take care of
maybe babysit
but she's not my child
no I don't have any other children
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh that's sweet it's fun at the taco
meat ingredients via Lottery you know
that's what's not Lottery I'm using
wonderful kfp supporting Kiara Dera but
I hope I win well I think I think it's
better this way
instead of making his first come first
serve because that's just stressful and
then
you know I don't know and I don't think
it's a good experience first come first
serve systems
I think it's better this way everybody
gets a chance
um
yeah
I mean I wish everybody could get a
ticket
and I don't know how many of you are
applying
um
let's hope we can get in as many as
possible
worst case maybe some of you can put on
one big sweater
and say that you are what do you call it
a joint twins
is that what you call it
I joined chickens
conjoined chimpkins now we're banking or
you know you know make one of those
chunking Towers yeah 20 timkins in a
trench coat
so many possibilities we'll get you all
in there somehow hmm
it will get a little bit sad if more
than one sim can talks though out of
those 22 kids
you'll have to coordinate yourselves
like everybody says one word but then
the top Champion that's actually visible
has to mouth every word and that takes a
lot of coordination
um
[Laughter]
Crispy Chicken Duncan hey Pacifica
jungle thank you for the rest of
potatoes
[Music]
it is my birthday today congratulations
can't be employing contract here is my
birthday bonus I shall continue
to Chef give me with much to tell cats
trying to head to him Handler serene you
so why am I singing it is
until my being as ingredient ends as
your command can I go to the usual room
now no you cannot it's not something you
can request for me
you need to be back bad
I don't look Christian
okay let's stop now
happy birthday
bye
wow
[Music]
wow one of the few birthdays that I'm
actually able to congratulate on the
same day as their birthday
feels nice
yeah
you can go to the birthday room now not
to the usual room
[Music]
foreign
friends
I sitting there waiting for you and and
they wanna they wanna blow into one of
those two things
online
[Music]
so
um
foreign
[Music]
I don't know
foreign
[Music]
thank you I will I will visit Korea one
day I'm already looking forward to it
Loki planning it already
it's not sure
when exactly to go but
um I'm thinking about it
[Music]
yeah I even have someone to guide me now
so
it's definitely happening
you're a mom no but you know still
foreign
[Music]
don't know if it applies to you but
happy Mother's Day thank you
Sam Point what is that thumbnail is that
your your profile picture oh
cute
[Music]
what do you call that thing again an
animal
a ferret
love parrots so cute hey boss today is
my second birthday with you oh my God
thanks for the membership comes
I just wanted to say that you helped me
a lot anyway have you ever considered
doing an original song in German I know
you say speaking German is embarrassing
but I personally think you're German
isn't adorable
um
um I have thought about maybe
translating
um like a vocaloid song to German and
covering it
or maybe just doing like a small part or
like some scattered German words in an
original song
but doing a full original in German no
not really planning on that
yeah
maybe who knows uh
what the future brings speaking of
covers though or did I tell you guys uh
that for
[Music]
um
for the Danish song cover I don't
like at this point it's very unlikely
that we will release it during the
vacation did I tell you guys
because of the translation I told you in
members okay so please don't expect it
during the vacation anymore it will
happen afterwards actually in June
because I need to space it out
[Music]
um the other one is happening
and my original song is happening and
then in June we have the song cover with
Elena
and in June I'm so [\h__\h] busy working
on other things too
like um
like many things such as birthday
planning
[Music]
learning choreographies I should maybe
I'll find some time in the Maldives to
learn choreographies because especially
if it's raining
I might have some time to learn some
choreos
I feel like you know I mean we've been
spending most of the time just chilling
it's relaxed yeah we will we will but I
feel like maybe I will have too much
time on my hands and I'm stressing out
about not having enough time
to be honest
ly
foreign
I wonder if I can really
get everything done that I want to get
done in these coming in these two months
May and June
um
I hope so
also because
um
you know being in the Maldives kind of
keeps me from doing a certain
amount of work
and then I also feel like I have to
prepare for that
so
do some extra content before I go and
then afterwards do some more content to
kind of make up for not being there too
yeah and it interrupts my work while I
am on it
on the Break
um it's kind of difficult but
um
I don't want to
push or pressure myself too much in May
and June because I'm like doing a lot of
stuff behind the scenes also probably a
lot of things that you guys won't know
for a while so please don't be mad at me
when you feel like I did yeah what the
[\h__\h] is she doing I tried to not make it
to noticeable I try to keep up my
my pace
of content as much as I can
[Music]
just want to get past these next two
months May and June
just want to get past this and then
after the birthday live
probably have to start planning
immediately
for an album and a concert
yeah
but but that's okay because I think then
I have enough time I'll have enough time
[Music]
yeah I said I want to put out an album I
mean I haven't really I don't really
know how but
I want to it's just me wanting to do
things and I'll do my best
oh yeah second anniversary oh [\h__\h] don't
remind me
well for anniversary I'm kind of hoping
that management will you know
do something
yeah at least for our anniversaries we
usually have merchandise coming out so
that's at least something where I don't
really have to do much besides
giving my okay and yeah making some
small decisions maybe and then uh yeah
retweeting
there's one more thing that
I want you guys to look forward to
besides
original songs
coming up very soon even right before
dokumi or right after dokumi
[Music]
okay let me read some projects before I
say something wrong thanks
foreign
[Music]
is the sweetest
and most amazing person
hope you feel better soon Robin the hood
dance and thank you thank you thank you
for watching my streams
the social artist
Dragoon Duncan thank you
one of my favorite games of all time
Emma
don't thank me this is more me doing
something for myself
the Louis Dragon dances and Jackson have
been dancing with the pinky moral of the
story is to travel with Kiana for
maximum chaotic Adventures
um
no don't say that that will make people
not want to travel with me
chaotic sounds so negative how about
more exciting Adventures huh
that sounds better
thank you
exciting
[Music]
and memorable
memorable
no need more positive words to describe
it
borderline criminal well
no no no no no I am beyond the law
no no no no no that was not not not not
criminal didn't I didn't do I don't know
I I
[Music]
thank you
[Laughter]
[Music]
can't be a trainee you're here okay no
problem then yeah I'm not part of the
system did you forget
[Music]
I'm gonna take that e-scooter and I'm
gonna throw it on the ground
oh
I have just received
super cute Artful the song cover with
Lena
oh cute
[Music]
oh
my God
oh my God
[Music]
mm-hmm
yes come on
oh my God
[Music]
it's very cute but I can't show you yet
guys look forward to it
Michael Jackson swim I'm just
I'm just to see cute things
thank you janma thank you
foreign
[Music]
Ty like
so good
[Music]
jenma is still awake she's always awake
what kind of question is that
[Music]
about but oh God stop stop
I should mute the music to myself and
just have it come through to you guys
so good ah lots of the things with the
pinky
uh wait did I read the one before
addressing happy birthday oh my God
happy birthday oh it's your special day
make the most out of it okay
that's another thing you put a pinky and
just a super support to our attention I
have no idea what I should write so I
just typed some random words here okay
that's better than nothing I guess
thank you very much that's a bill you're
still here
your name your name I know you've been
around for a long time too thank you
very much for thinking of me and
supporting me still
hope you're still enjoying the streams
as much as day one or maybe more even
thank you
okay okay
[Music]
looking for the top function
Foundation
[Music]
I am fanfiction thank you happy Mother's
Day
oh
oh I'm I'll be your mom
I'll be your mom
me I'll be your mom Sergio Crookston
thank you Dominique thank you you only
pay if you win the raffle okay okay yeah
tomorrow on docomo's Twitter if you're
planning if you want to be part of the
meet and greet from tomorrow on until
one week later you have the chance to
enter the raffle
don't forget it
don't forget about it
and then thank everybody for the flash
chat it's very blue indeed just like the
ocean in Wind Waker beautiful
I'll be entering it good luck Good Luck
Good Luck Good Luck Good Luck Good Luck
Good Luck
yeah I will fill it out okie dokie good
luck
thank you
[Music]
oh you should try
maybe this time you're lucky
[Music]
really surprised to see so many planning
to go it still like blows me away holy
[\h__\h] you guys are crazy
you guys are Luna chicks
celebrities
[Music]
thank you
after EU mind oh yes must take occasions
I love my vocations and as you guys know
I see the vacations as some way to make
some kind of content as well like like
get new stories you know and also
connect with other members
hmm spicy chicken taco salad
for the pinky since you're not streaming
tomorrow here's my early Super Chat for
my birthday
oh happy early
for you I'm not talented enough to
contribute to the community but I'm
hoping that a dokomia would be able to
leave you a gift of my making if it
survives to travel oh
I hope it's not food because that kind
of sounds like food and you know I can't
accept it but
uh I wonder what that will be
[Music]
I hope it survives too then
I I suppose it's gonna be a surprise
until I get it
but wrap it in a lot of bubble
bubble wrap
um
thank you for thinking of me and happy
happy birthday congratulations
stay healthy
and happy and thanks for still being
here
[Music]
and take some time for yourself tomorrow
okay since I'm not streaming anyway
yeah enjoy the day make the best out of
it
get some presents some nice food treat
yourself
maybe do some kind of activity
thank you for your support
I'm at work oh well I mean maybe maybe
they'll let you go a little bit earlier
then huh
well nice at work too
because London then people will take up
some workload from you maybe or they
will bring some cake to work
I've had that before
foreign
you always have to be close to that one
person at work that likes to bake
and I was I was somewhat close with that
one person at my job at my old job that
likes to bake and what did I get out of
it lots of cake so
absolutely win strategy
hey
I even got a cake when I am on my last
day of work the the that person she made
a huge cake
A Farewell cake isn't that sweet yeah
so sweet
and I think at that point yeah she
didn't even work at the same job anymore
I think if I remember
but she still made it and brought it to
my job
thing
[Music]
pretty sure that she like quit like a
while before me I think
[Music]
that's a surprising thing
crispy chicken
five chickens in the pretty dress yo
thank you for the pinky we tried to get
him but none of us could get a ticket
and you need to go there in one month
you probably tried to enter a completely
different event ah these dumb chickens
and Brew brains try again in one month
hello thank you for the Super Chat
Master I've been waiting to see you for
so long from your stature I estimate
there's a 71 gen percent chance you'll
consumed one of Mario's drinking
mushrooms
[Music]
smile
a smartphone
um but yeah 71 is too low
yeah no two link is just small because
he's a little boy
yeah
oh man fee was he was nice
at least now I have her informed
memories but did I hate her back then
uh
[Music]
I don't think this is uh yeah
thank you
Albion Crescent
Anton and thank you
I tend to I recently got a stylish suit
for being in kfb for six months ah I'm
really happy to be here with you thank
you for the fun streams and the unique
atmosphere and looking forward to the
next promotion wait what is it again oh
yeah yeah don't worry
don't think about it too hard
but I hope the uniform fits well
I took the liberty of taking your
measurements when you were sleeping
yeah
hope it didn't wake you up
but it looks amazing on you
wow you look so fabulous
thank you antonym will because for
staying a member for so long hope you're
enjoying my streams and my members
content even though it's not that much
but you know
um
thank you very very much
I hope to keep you for a lot a lot
longer
I'm getting really hungry which is good
because this is my last Super Chat Jake
Sherry charay induction
don't know what that means
okay everybody thank you for Wednesday
uh I had a long [\h__\h] day
so I'm gonna go now without further Ado
uh
foreign
imagara
name
is
[Music]
I think you know what I'll put up the
schedule tomorrow because there actually
might still be things that
um
might change tomorrow
so since I'm not staying tomorrow anyway
I think you're all gonna be okay with
that
I hope so I'm also not 100 sure if I'm
allowed to put a certain thing on my
schedule just yet
so I'll check about that too
um
[Music]
okay thank you for understanding
thank you so awesome schedule they must
happen again
yes
okay okay okay all the chickens say okay
so in sync
you can guess what it is or what could
it possibly be
hmm
[Music]
could it be
okay okay okay okay okay I like how you
so aggressively not only press OK once
but like three or five times okay okay
okay okay okay okay okay
[Laughter]
okay okay okay okay okay thank you
everybody okay okay okay I love you okay
okay okay okay okay
okay
[Music]
bye bye bye
love you okay okay okay
your answer to me saying I love you okay
okay
[Music]
kind of disappointing but okay okay
bye-bye
good night
bye-bye with me bye-bye
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
mwah