[Music]
foreign
Instagram foreign
[Music]
assistant
foreign
[Music]
kicking oh
[\h__\h]
ing
[Music]
oh
hello
sorry for being late
[Music]
does this work
oh what the [\h__\h]
um
[Music]
I
um
I'm okay
I'm gonna just fix this
[Music]
I'm gonna showcase
was really good
look cute
as expected
yep
okay
hmm
we're gonna continue
I emblem engage
I think I have a headphones on the wrong
way yep
okay
hmm
yeah I was also surprised I didn't I
didn't remember
that I had Pokemon Scarlet opened
recently
I did not update the game I think
oh but this was because of Elena's
little thing what was it called
what was it called
metronome something
hmm
um
yeah okay let's do it
uh oh
did you hear that
I'm not using a different mic why
I'm just
yeah
why why
sound different
I'm just gonna say microphone as always
I'll get there I'm getting there okay
okay now you should be able to hear the
audio
I think
in the moment
[\h__\h] controller why are you not
activating
the left side doesn't work
there we go
I have to use the
the one that comes with the switch
because Pro Controller is out of battery
I guess
okay
my head hurts
what do you mean I sound really low
should I scream
is it too quiet
what do you mean
so what was updated
what did they update
what was updated
it'll see maps okay
hmm I did not buy the new DLC though oh
wait you guys said I don't have to right
there it comes ah
shut up
I'm not an Austria I'm in Japan
Nani
um
okay well what
Hector oh there we go Hector has been
added they will each show in your group
when they respective Divine parallels
have been cleared
I need to get my [\h__\h] together
and
look I don't know man I don't know I
don't know
foreign
[Music]
get my [\h__\h] together
maybe if we have them talk to us the
characters
yeah
talk to me
no no
no no no no
no
I'm gonna stream fire emblem
whoa
oh
that's a lot of stuff
no
um I forgot how to play this game it's
been too long
uh
uh uh oops
Mr ping no that's also not what I want
this is what I want oh what the pink or
the drift holy [\h__\h] what is this
controller
okay talk just talk talk talk talk
so you're not just a prince you lead a
militia too
my father did as well you know your pops
let a group like my Sentinels pump he's
a great guy I'd love to throw a party
for him
that's so short why don't they talk more
do they hate each other
talk more
she's so cute
talk
[Music]
yes boss nothing beats an ice jaunt on
Wolf back you and I used to go riding
practically every night
what happened to those days War happened
the world has changed unfortunately
since those days what do you mean by
that
remember how we met you had a bunch of
Bandits tied to trees and we're about to
feed them to the wolves that was
literally to intimidate them I wasn't
actually going to and don't get me
started on the way you used to talk
you'd say things like feeling hungry
punks I got a fresh
sauce for you right here
why I beg you to cease this course
impression what the [\h__\h]
I love the old
the old the new YouTube the feeling is
mutual boss
you're Relentless teasing aside
wait
I think that might be the first time I
hear panette talking a lot
uh
[Music]
why is she like this
no not the voice it's like the the whole
she speaks like a
really sophisticated lady
that's not what I expected
hello Raiders hi she's pretending is she
faking it will we see her real side then
I think I would prefer it
um
it's a face
she's going out of the way to try okay
okay because I don't know I expected
something more edgy
she has two modes of speech oh for real
okay
um
let's let's hope we will get to see the
other side oh man it's been such a long
time since I played I don't I don't
remember like what we were doing
[Music]
oh how do I
oh there we go need to get a grip of
this controller
she is with other characters
oh Nani
I have an easy way to improve
relationship uh
in Game of that DLC update huh
I barely hear myself for the headphones
man
Recreation you can send like two allies
on the song you'll spend some time
relaxing at various locations
is this is this the thing that you just
told me about
you sound loud and clear well I sound
loud and clear over there that's good
you're unlocking this just I don't know
what was it supposed to unlock this
earlier
support points between the Allies you
select may increase as they spend time
together
you can do this once each and it seems
weird to unlock it now doesn't it
feels like something that should have
been around since the beginning
if you want a fast way to bond then use
this okay
free update oh oh it's a new thing okay
seems like something that should have
been around
since the beginning
what the [\h__\h] the
buttons are in such weird places on this
controller
okay so I think last time
we just arrived in the desert right
I think we just arrived
I had Recreation never bought the DLC
yeah I guess it's just uh from the
update
um um
[Music]
yeah yeah
um
I wanna use the things that blue made
for me but I I couldn't find them
[Music]
an idm'd blue
out of the blue
and I don't know if blue saw it
was kind of last minute
maybe blue
replied out of the blue now
I couldn't find it
[Music]
um
I want to use the ring is
I'm playing with English voices yeah it
yeah so yeah yes
yeah
English because whole live English
Mamacita
um okay
sorry guys
I I
I'm getting there
eventually
you know how it is
stream a bit
and then
and then yeah
I had for breakfast I had
a banana
that is totally unrelated to the fact
that there was a banana
on the crime scene at Amazon stream
I have nothing to do with that
hmm
but not a banana and some
slices of
I think was it an orange or was it a
little Tangerine I'm not sure
they were peeled though
so I'm not sure was it um
it's probably a tangerine
small omelet was framed when was the
last time you saw some
um
when did I see small Lama
oh no
I didn't I don't know anything about
small
anything I'm just saying right now it
doesn't sound
funny
to me and I cannot be genuine right now
I'm so sorry
I'm a monotone robot
I'm planning to
order some food during the stream
because I will be hungry I know it
um
but for now I only had like some fruit
for breakfast I'm good though I'm okay
my eyes are a bit tired now
but I'm okay
I'm not tired physically I think I think
maybe I am
maybe I'm not
how the [\h__\h] do I reach that place I'm
just looking at the whole time I'm
looking at the map because
get to know where I'm going yeah this
way this way
is it should I really every time I come
here
collect every single thing on the map
should I really is that worth it
yeah but it's really loud in my ears
let me try to fix it somehow
how do I fix it
um
um Maybe
oh [\h__\h] sorry that's loud huh
one sec
[Music]
wait I'm separating I'm separating
everything
uh
now I can adjust on obs and adjust here
yeah okay
I separated it I'm a genius technical
genius
yay
do you want it to be wait no right now
it's kind of quiet anyway
I know that's because I turned okay do
you want it louder
I can make it louder now
if you want
just get the iron from the dogs ignore
everything else
a bit louder okay
I made it a bit louder but a bit louder
I don't know how how much bit is for you
okay
I'm sorry guys
I'm so sorry
[Music]
um
I have some tea
you don't need to say sorry
[Music]
foreign
how are you
okay uh
help me out guys what am I supposed to
do what else I did bonds I did
collecting the items what should I do
before I go to fight
I'm just starting to it okay
I'll do starting to eat for tomorrow
thank you in a meal okay one sec
um
[Music]
um call guys good call
we have begun
late but
we are
Arena animal try Recreation okay
[Music]
Arena
Arena Arena Grande
Arena Grande
[Music]
ah cleaning the Rings hmm
want to give you a big hug thank you I
got a hug from Eno
I asked her if she could give me a hug
gave me a hug
thank you enough
[Music]
um
hug was prioritized over not getting
sick
[Music]
um doing
another daily training be done now
I am Boucheron what royal Knight
oh
[Music]
more
you're so motivated how satisfied
indeed
[Music]
about Anna man I don't know
I think I think I have to I have to
decide you know who to prioritize and
I Shall Serve as your opponent today I
think we'll we're gonna drop either
oh [\h__\h] you're gonna get
how satisfying
I did invest quite a bit in her huh
[Music]
oh
Clan basically that was him just being a
punching bag
okay he got this level up
[Music]
um
look at all these
units I dropped it why is she down there
why is portentias why can I not even
choose her if I wanted to
know hey
no no what what do you mean no weapons
uh inventory
so cute
uh or if I just optimize equipment she
only got a physique well what does she
need a book
what does the optimization not give her
a book
[Music]
do I not have a book
not have a book
[Music]
uh okay you can have this funder
um
wait
is there an L fire to spare you have one
[Music]
I don't use them do I wait is he new
I don't use her much either I tried a
little bit in the beginning
take it from the Abu dude yeah okay
isn't he like on a flying horse or so
normally can he even use the the book
he's new right
the guy that barks it so [\h__\h]
obnoxious
okay
that's uh I would say
good for now
if you want you can have the war
he's not mounted oh
[Music]
why are you spider are you saying that
ironically
she also doesn't have a ring we need to
give her a ring
[Music]
oh is there free one bile up is free
let's go
she'll get violent
[Music]
oh I got Bible from her
no no no no
I had the the three houses boys already
I thought they were kind of the same
thing right now I have a massive seat
for her that's a good question uh one
second
wait a second wait a second
what level is she anyway
19.
wait that means she's ready to
what isn't she ready to use the master
sale for quite some time
[Music]
uh
what would we turn her into
[Music]
she's ready
okay how did it change Quest
I don't have a monster seal I guess
I don't
okay let somebody fight once and let's
see if we can buy a monster too
[Music]
um
do you think me a worthy opponent
better be ready
oh
he's trying
it's not as
humiliating as the other 5-15 so they
can learn a lot really lucky I suppose
yay
okay
I'm getting there guys
while I was getting there
being curb stumps what
you're far behind on your own gameplay
you had so much time to catch up are you
[\h__\h] kidding me
that's how much time oh
that might be my favorite like
casual outfit that these peeps have
you do
it's about okay
it's cute
okay well then let's have some
you think Clan can cook
hi there
who we trust him to cook for us
I guess
let's go with how do I have I had Tamara
over yet probably not
let him go okay okay
[Music]
what crap seems to be his specialty
that's okay that's good
[Music]
uh no no veggies in the hot tub ew fruit
fruit
don't [\h__\h] it up I'll give you a chance
don't [\h__\h] it up
so I'm at this
chop it
wait
my home cooking oh yeah I could get used
to this one
it's decent
yeah I like it okay
what people say spicy
d
that's terrible
[Music]
get it
thank you oh
MBA thank you
okay she would sell the seals right or
was it the other shop
please tell me you have a master sale
yes yes poop
I thank you let's go I thank you
should I buy the second seal too
she has six anyway we'll just if you
don't buy it when she restocks does it
just add on to the stock or does she
just not restock at all
we'll add on okay good do come again I
give the membership yay
[Music]
they do get unlimited what
uh now
um
change class
what's she gonna be sleep near Rider
what is that
a knight who writes the Charming Pegasus
sleep near use powerful stamps and his
skilled with tombs
[Music]
best healer class
killer magic right well we already have
someone like that but
oh wait that's always like that
oh but she looks cool she's got like
some fancy stuff around her neck
keeping her in check
so she can't move her head too much
looks like it would hurt is there anyone
else
[Music]
who wants
oh
[Music]
somebody who's over level 10 and has
like a b rank right that's the kind of
people
oh
that okay that confuses me because you
guys are gonna probably tell me that she
could not change like upgrade can she
[Music]
can
that's it she already is
can she not go any higher
can we get much higher
so high
[Music]
so confusing I can change her
but I cannot promote her anymore so
that's what I was asking
hmm
well done seems like no one else really
[Music]
second steal when she reaches max level
oh
okay
okay uh we did food we did the arena oh
there's a like a bond thingy going on
oh
[Music]
Grill grilled and ready to go this meat
is so yummy it's gonna make your taste
buds dance
that seems like a lot of meat for the
two of us oh no this one's for me I was
going to do yours next what
how do you eat that much oh you know you
guys can catch up on the Lord of the
Rings watch long as we do before you
with all this Monday Tuesday Wednesday
you're really something Tamara
[Music]
yes yes and I'm wearing lots of
Priceless Jewels why uh is she talking
like this I've heard that this area
isn't very safe
you can say that again it's absolutely
crawling with Bandits that's why I'm out
here like a nice tempting Gunk of lamb
on a spit wait a minute
that was your plan to use yourself as
bait it worked didn't it look though
since we got here it looks like
oh my God
not if we pounce on them first come on a
piece of cake for you and me yeah even
though I'm not even but you know a
little heads up would have been nice
doing well today sorry thank you though
oh
thank you
[Music]
everybody wants to talk to Tamara she's
so popular popping a new chicken well
well if it isn't fogado my one and only
City
yes in the flesh okay to tell me why
you're in such a good mood oh no he's in
particular really I would have guessed
there was a song or a slab of meat
involved mine I'm glad to see you
looking so cheery always puts a smile on
my face well good because I'm happy as
can be
you tell me why
because they have another meaning that's
not good if you really want to know it's
because you're
yours
I'm always here oh hate to break it to
you but no thank you for all the
membership games and spend all that much
time in the castle but you you were now
you spend time with you at all huh yeah
you make a good point these aren't what
you'd call them yeah I never heard of
the stances but I'm glad I see you every
day wow you really put a positive spin
on things we're in the middle of a war
you make it sound like a family vacation
a membership party
membership gifting party I'm just happy
that you're happy
she's just quirky like that
yeah
okay I think I'm okay now guys the the
my favorite part of I'm a showcase I
think was the the hopping the whole pop
game of metal it was so good so cute
they put a cute Twist on it with the
ball
you cry when I say
soccer instead of football well how much
were you crying when meru said soccer
ball
wait what did she say
yeah yeah she said right
I think because it came right off the
basement so her brain was like um
forgive her
if it's a Euro you forgive her because
she's Japanese
what do you call this what do you call
this
two what's it called again
[Music]
double standards that's the word
you guys and your shitty double
standards
unbelievable
it was cute though how fair are you
today
but in German we say
much for inviting which is literally
football yes stiff I should try to sound
warmer but in English I don't know
something a Miss Claire I think I
learned in school to call it soccer
where did you come from
my apologies I thought I heard someone
mention my prince's name you heard right
Prince Alfred invited me to work out
with him today but I've never spent time
alone with him before so I'm nervous
about saying the wrong thing
a private exercise session for the two
of you
that's right America
could this signify I don't think it
signifies anything
but pay me no more to a long time so
then you are practicing your greetings
the cooler name I think to embarrass
myself by being accidentally rude maybe
primitive don't you I'll talk to you
like your prince Alfred and if anything
what is this
Stephen Fang oh I got it
[Music]
soccer is cooler now you must agree with
me I had perfect reasoning
um
football was originally any sport I used
well there you go that makes it even
more stupid that we call it footballs
so generic
nope you're wrong you're wrong
I am right
that takes Wallops
[Music]
it always goes low and then I won
gotta use the the cross one
the rest it just doesn't work it just
doesn't
work
um what else oh yeah somebody said
something about panette what am I doing
with panette
I'm changing a class
what
General somebody said General
[Music]
like our kisara waipu
and we have her double
no no Warrior my people don't have
[Music]
um
people are not on the same
what where is Warrior I don't see Romeo
what we want
where's what we want
I can't do wrong huh that's advanced
which means I need a master sale and
she's not ready for that anyway right
[Music]
keep her Berserker that's better for her
keep her physics
[Music]
you guys don't
you're not you're not on the same
page
hmm
here's what she would need a full
professional oh
he's already in with grandson oh his
second ceiling but need both proficiency
so
wait how do you do that again you you
how do you do that
reclass into a Healer
that would make everyone go like what
all the things you could do
train with Lynn
[Music]
hmm
Warriors of geography and upgrade to
Berserker in every aspect
oh it feels like you guys are having a
heat at this question about this
[Music]
he's built to be a Berserker stroke
unless you get a really good idea
keeping her into that class too I think
I'm gonna stay with that
it's interesting
but because there's so many opinions I
can't decide but thank you for like
um informing me about it yeah
[Music]
yeah we haven't even tried her as jeans
yet either
[Music]
give her give her a try
yeah
and
emblem Rings is there still some who
don't have one
uh no wait
[Music]
you can hands
um I don't know
which one you want
[Music]
don't I have any golden ones flying
around I guess not double
what's this one luck and Magic okay you
don't need that Dex and HP all right
take it
equip Ike for panette
okay but isn't is that combined with
making her that other class or is it
even good without that if she just stays
Berserker
[Music]
she goes to her dress if you were class
her well that might be good
regardless okay
my turn
well then
Tamara
let's see what could we do
oh
who's that who has idle God right now
what is that
[Music]
[\h__\h] is that
middle guard Count On Me
sorry we need our wings back
we need more rings
more more more more
how about drinking sex for you huh
best
I'll let some DLC braces then
I guess we're gonna do some DLC now then
I'm sorry for taking it away from you
Sarah
[Music]
okay
one ring per main chapter now
[Music]
how do I how do we go what was it one
more important thing I needed to do
cleaning rings
guess
I could do cleaning rings
[Music]
okay we'll do that
how long can I stream today forever
I think
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
we'll see how long I can go but also
you know gotta Read Super Chat huh so
I have to control myself
so we're gonna have an energy drink yeah
but just you know make sure to get some
sleep before the 3D collabo
uh
uh when when
and you know just in case we want to
change our mind I will polish with make
it Sparkle that spot really does I hate
when it gets dull thanks again see you
next time
streaming until pretty yeah well that
will not happen don't worry
because I need some sleep too
Ike
oh they told me who did I give Ike to
um
right oh I guess panette is in polishing
duty today cleaning the ring good we
like all right cool
it looks good thank you
you probably don't need to polish your
rings for a while oh okay play
so I'm guessing you answered my Twitter
yes
yes you did
chapter 13. I think we're in chapter 14
right oh yeah and right there's panette
makeup
yeah right
uh ooh should I do it with the wig or
without the wig
[Music]
I think I'll do it without the wig for
now and then chapter 13.
wait how does this look again
where's the
[\h__\h] and chip
munks
there it is really yeah I guess I do
have by love
okay okay okay transformation
thank you for the membership
[Music]
transformation time transformation time
oh my God
hmm
how big how big does it have to be
is that is that is that right under her
eye where do you place this
I forgot
uh
okay take a look at this and tell me
tell me if it's correct uh
uh
oh
and look at the other stuff does this
look correct
cute
[Music]
edgy
wow okay one more
I'm Pinette
I'm pregnant today
and Sheen
oops now I changed
[Music]
ah okay okie dokie
okay
perfect perfect
hello
wow
so much going on here look at all my
rings and bracelets let's go
The Bling Bling
yay I got the little
whatever that is dog cat thing
beautiful
perfect
okay what was I doing
[Music]
oops polishing rings
sorry about the hassle what the dog
doing
check out penet and pandrea support it
did I miss one
twenty
oopsie
20 gifted memberships how does it look
oh it's all shiny oh my God so many
memberships
[Music]
thank you
no I don't care who polishes these
stupid rings I'm kind of sleepy
I'm going to sleepy
wow
is it Australian to say
because the other day I watched a video
of the Australian member of new jeans
how she pronounces things very
australian-ish
no need to hold back
it's much better I appreciate it was
quite soft to the tea I thought it was
quite soft
okay
[Music]
um
um yeah whatever I want to go fight
let me go fight
unless there's one more bonding thingy
there's none
snow
let's say
vital
depart
Divine parallels
for now
your screenshots are pixel because the
stream is 720P
where do I go which one do I do can I do
any of them should I do this one
which one would be suitable for me
[Music]
first
try
of course that came from you
[Music]
Hector for finesse
that's the easiest one right now oh oh
hey it's not only you ran
where's Hector which one's Hector
okay we can do Hector Mickey
this one Hector Berserkers Hollow
left
okay
a bracelet has been sighted in a dank
dank
cave filled with miasma
all right wait can I just begin
I think I can just because we're good
[Music]
Camilla I've never timed it
the bracelet friend right over here
you're right
is this the bracelet or the brush
General yes I think Adam is asleep just
as I was
will you wake him up wake up as soon as
I laid eyes on it let's give them a try
emblem of strength
okay
[Music]
what a refreshing rest hey there I'm
Hector was it you who woke me up
hello yes it was greetings Hector I'm
the Divine Dragon good to meet you
oh
sure is nice to move around again
you must have had a reason to come
looking for you
this world is engulfed in a terrible War
we're trying to put a stop to it to that
end we were hoping you might lend us
your strength
well I've got a good feeling about
that looks like you've got grit just
like he did he
asked who you're talking about
my good friend elliewood in my world he
fought to bring us back from the brink
of disaster like you were doing our
fight was against a rotten Bunch called
the black Fang they were a real handful
for Ellie wood Lynn and me and all our
other friends it was the fight of Our
Lives
they must have been glad to have someone
like you on their side
Roy's dad
you need help that's enough for me but
first let's have ourselves
what do you mean
it's been a while since I've seen any
action I want to get the measure of you
in battle I understand
poor guy
brace yourself
okay
let's go who did I bring
um
[Music]
I guess he's on the top left
also big
can I like make some hot water real
quick
[Music]
eyes boiling
not not warm water hot water
worm not enough
[Music]
yeah I'm making tea
making tea
you know I miss I'm as like for the
office looks so good
all right
was so good
and she also just like me with femini
she also had like a disco functions
[Music]
can dance at night when you're done with
Detective work
phone
pick up the phone
yeah
because then Bubba Bubba was like picked
up he was like his legs were bouncy and
wobbly that was cute
so good man why is she so
it's a ball what the [\h__\h]
whoa
what how does she do it
stick man
hmm
oh
the dog treats one was really cute too
yeah cause like Bubba was running around
and they were disappearing rather than
appearing the
you know normally it's like you know
nothing much happens with these you can
make stages there
yeah I would put in this this one there
was interaction with football that was
cute
[Music]
and I'm a small woman that was funny so
othing part though we're taking
really shitty aim what the [\h__\h] was that
Stormtrooper and I wrote that in the
chat
[Music]
okay
Kitty honey
push
okay
which showcases I like the most that's
such a difficult question because we're
all like really they have different
vibes
[Music]
that was really different vibes
Amma was focused on like games and stuff
rather than
singing and dancing and Cali was very
focused on singing and dancing no no
they're not dancing I guess I was very
focused on Dancing
[Music]
I will not choose
you know what my favorite will be the
one that's tomorrow tomorrow
yes tomorrow
[Music]
okay tea has been served
or Channel
[Music]
what kind of tea oh it's um I've been
drinking some chamomile
chamomile herbal tea the whole time
okay
unit selection
[Music]
these are always such difficult choices
but we're gonna do this because she has
a fancy ring
um
no I did it last week did you not see it
tomorrow is
the one where we do all together with
all five of us
[Music]
um
so okay let me think we have our divine
dragon can I go without her enough
we have our alcrest
we have magic one and
magic too
now uh one cavalry
[Music]
oh cavalry
one one Cavalry I guess this is enough
we're at potencio
you're right
she was
ah flat okay perfect
but why is she still at the bottom huh
why is she at the bottom
[Music]
radiant bow for focado oh
do I have that
um
just because she's new okay
[Music]
let's see ah
perfect
she can't use it so can't switch
thank you for remembering that I did not
remember it all
whose arrows pierced with light
effective flying also I want to use this
one on flying units
oh wait they're all effective for flying
what's so special about this one because
it's magic
ooh so maybe like a oh
um a heavy armor unit on flying
is what this would be really good for
okay
we're probably fine right
[Music]
yeah okay
not spaces track map yeah I should do
that
so do we all together go up or should we
split
because up here there's a treasure
that is what you are there's also one
down here
I don't know if I want to split though
because there's so many if I go up and
then down here and I could go back here
a little bit
and then go
Squad go left you can have some go up
I guess it's not that many in here as
one on the side here two here two here
one of them
fabric
oh I was look at that weird purple stuff
around them I was like what was that
[Music]
but then up until here there's not so
many enemies but then here there's quite
a lot in in one pile
[Music]
that's the question
me asthma
it's like everywhere what does that do
but it would stay together along right
path
what what does that mean
there's no right
oh
[Music]
we have two flying units though they do
be quick
[Music]
whatever I don't know
[\h__\h] it
let's get started
there appears to be a fog-like substance
Eminem No you're not even here beyond
your guard
[Music]
okay
bye two
and he's always there he's cheering From
the Bench
itself split but
why are we only eight
all right really why are we only eight
[Music]
I hear you
all right let's do this
[Music]
fire
can't kill
can I kill the other one with fire
[Music]
no
that's how it is
[Music]
Curry
any Curry that you feel like
so many different ones
because you can do this map extremely
early as well
oh
I guess so anyway a Bunkie with some
fire
I saw and you know there's like these
three main convenience stores in Japan
uh
Lawson Family Mart and 7-Eleven I saw
one of them I forgot which one it was
has like a oh
has a
campaign a query campaign going on with
curries from all over the world
kind of cool
[Music]
I'm gonna try I wanna try but I worry
that they're too spicy
yeah my job I think it's fine yeah the
like drinking doesn't hurt anymore but
this I don't know something about the
inside of my
valve still feels kind of a weird sore
maybe I think it's still from the cold
who do I stand up
maybe speed horse
speed horse with
[Music]
from only eighth and maybe free app and
and four
what can count six plus two right
it's eight
yeah how about
five to the left three up or just four
four
okay I'll do four four which means yes
ow Chris
you
go stay here
and then the other one on the horse
scene
I'll bring the faster looking ones up I
guess
handle it magic
wait isn't that where the the stuff
comes out is that no one before that
okay
[Music]
then we're good
yeah I don't know why I have no longer
but I was looking for it there
no longer
yes
no not too many just ah wait I do have
three Mages with me
oh
why did you guys not tell me to not
bring three Majors with me I mean I love
my Majors but
I will I will bring the the other flying
one up instead next turn
so then we have one two
and then you can you
can't hit from here okay
it's a dangerous zone for him I wonder
[Music]
hmm they'll be right okay one more huh
oh on HP again
for real
with the hand X
free HP
[Music]
triggers me
it
what do you mean we never put the radio
no we did
I remember doing it
[Music]
hmm
I did do that what do you mean
[Music]
okay well I did I did gaslighting me
or tangents aren't the money today any
any that you want
[Music]
what do you want
which one do you want to hear guys
what oh my goodness slay girl yes
didn't she only have a place
[Music]
foreign
you can't get much more out of those
three days
[Music]
had to be there
can I not talk about that before
we really
um basically you know I came a bit early
to the studio set up eventually lots of
myself I came and like we were we were
like chit chatting about potato chips I
guess
technology
and then after the stream was over
oh yeah now before you know she was
witnessing the whole General please get
me a bathing suit a tantrum
but
nothing left however after the Stream
you know there were a lot of potato
chips left over so
um I was asking if there's like staff
who want the potato chips and like they
came in to like try taste test which
ones they liked
Empire's manager
was
absolutely addicted
to
some paprika chips that I brought
[Music]
and could not stop eating them
was so in love with those potato chips
and I was like please please take them
home I'm so happy someone's enjoying
them
yeah
and generally so everybody got potato
chips from the aftermath so
quite quite satisfied that they were not
wasted you know because that was
obviously too many for us to eat and and
then I I took some home too but
I was gonna eat them
I I brought like free open packages or
so from you know my chips
uh and oh no one one of what damage
chips too
but the next day
you know that's where I started getting
sick and I noticed a tingle in my throat
and all that so I was like I better not
eat chips right now
um
so I haven't even I think they've gone
to waste because they've been open for
like a week now
[Music]
I don't think
they're good anymore probably
my beloved
[Music]
but you can't use a steel blade right
let's uh replace
[Music]
you didn't get strength yeah is that
unusual for her
um
it'd still be perfectly edible but they
wouldn't taste right yeah probably like
um
stale yeah maybe I'll try I like I have
to check because now
I guess I could eat potato chips now
I was looking forward
ing on them and the following days but I
got so sick still I was trying to eat
soft food
[Music]
my last surprising and Long Island you
think
our potato juice is bad for when you say
no well when I had bronchitis laryngitis
and a sinus infection
the other day uh you know I I was told
to eat
um
[Music]
stuff that's like
not acidic and not like soft soft stuff
you know and there's so many things that
I was supposedly not supposed to eat
[Music]
so many things I wasn't supposed to eat
you know
[Music]
and I thought well this case is really
similar I guess I mean I just have a
cold but I would assume that if your
throat really hurts and you lost your
boys
I don't know maybe maybe not eat
[\h__\h] ton of crunchy and spiky potato
chips don't you agree
that that would probably be smart
salty too like the problem is also that
they're really salty right
I just thought it makes sense so I
didn't eat
salty Breezy
[Music]
hi what the [\h__\h] I'm not gonna microwave
potato chips what
[Music]
Skye
I was gonna send you yes yes
[Music]
I'm scared
good
[Music]
does she have the one with the long long
no no right wait Astro storm is still
the one that can shoot from really far
away
emblem engage
yeah
can we hit oh baby
[Music]
no
let's go
[\h__\h]
a good win thanks
okay so we got that one out of the way
are there any charging oh yes
we were up there one two three four okay
um
what are we gonna do with you man you're
not gonna do any of them dude let's go
up and let's if I go up here then I
think he will run after and then try to
attack panette I think that'll be fine
unless
take him down with Lucina Lucina Lucina
Lucina
hallucinating
let's do some hallucinating AKA
hallucinating Lucy now because she's not
real look at her that's obviously on
hallucinations
[Music]
mm-hmm
announcements
no no
I don't think there's anything else
tomorrow
I don't think so maybe I forgot no
I mean
we'll see
I'll see
ah he has the chain Attack One
[Music]
kind of useless Now isn't it
um
good ideas but that's the tangent that I
want to tell yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
oh my God
okay nevermind I'm going back here after
all
um
so the other day uh I was
uh
somewhere to do something
work related
and hmm
I did not expect
to meet Aqua Senpai it turns out I did
well first uh I saw
[Music]
first episode
no you know what I can take them down
with combined
combined forces uh yeah and we were like
hey
thank you
I was really happy to see her we talked
quite a bit
um
sorry brain slow when I do tangent
[Music]
seven that's probably fine
yeah
and then I realized
[Music]
we'll be coming
she she arrived
and
[Music]
it's exactly like how I imagined her to
be
exactly
[Music]
she had the typical
famous Aqua
um like undercover hat
on
she was so tiny
yes she was a cute mess yes she was so
tiny and and
um
[Music]
she was looking down and she was wearing
a mask too so I barely I didn't even see
her freaking face because you know she
had the the hat on and the cap the front
of the cap was hiding her eyes
and the rest of her face was hidden by
the mask and I was like huh
it was like reading her really excited
and I I immediately know this from her
like body language and everything and
she was like
she was having
um she was struggling to
exist and
she she was like really shy she couldn't
talk
um but I was like I'm I'm gonna I'm
gonna get her
like in Hollow talk I'm gonna get her to
like talk to me it's okay I like
um don't don't worry you'll you will
warm up to me whoever you want it or not
hmm
[Music]
um
so yeah she sat down and I sat down and
I was like trying to make a conversation
and the whole time ah
the whole time
she was you know
she was like really
what's the word
what's the English translation for today
oh that's great I was in curses upon our
enemy
not not flatter bashful yeah she was so
bashful
[Music]
it's so small and it was like
and she was even more bashful than
yeah I wouldn't win like we were not
together for too long
wait they all get poisoned around there
the reach is so huge what the [\h__\h]
yeah bent impossible
[Music]
um
yeah anyway like it was just so funny
because it was
it was so
so clearly simply
she was small as expected she was
wearing the kind of clothes that I
expected to know the Hat
she was acting the way I expected you
know from all the stories
and I cracked up so much at that because
it's exactly how I imagined like when
you hear those stories about Aqua Senpai
right from like other people
[Music]
to meet her they're all kind of talk
about her the same way I feel like
[Music]
relax yeah so introverted so cute
I'm so glad I could meet her
very lucky lucky me
oh yeah Senpai apparently was worried I
I saw that I saw that clip apparently
she was worried about
her hoodie being stinky and if I noticed
it because I hugged her no I did not
though this is such a thing
at all
I think it was uh I didn't notice
anything
talk about a good time
so please be relieved I would not have
known about it at all
[Music]
[Applause]
no at this point I was not sick yet I
got sick the day after
[Music]
antitoxin toscato I might actually
replace it with the Wolverine
kinda needed
so she's kind of dying
[\h__\h]
is it safe anywhere at all but she's not
even no she's poison do I have an
antitoxin on there
of course I don't
but I do need to heal
okay
uh
[Music]
let's get moving
the other like shy elusive member that I
still need to meet is I am missing but
eventually
[Music]
needed true true true
I think I've done that
uh when I last played privately I was
using the doubles
which is going quite well it was pretty
useful oh my God wait there's so many
enemies here
why does this one have an exclamation
mark
[Music]
I'm scared to walk over there we're
outnumbered
[Music]
an item kill a weapon oh
okay I will open up
[Music]
what's inside
your water
[Music]
wait I should just [\h__\h] use this
already why did I not use this already
this
bring to ground resistance plus seven to
use her bonus strings fight one extra
well I think I'm just gonna send it to
the Convoy
Subaru and Nana tangents Oh
was there something specific
hmm
[Music]
how long have you been rehearsing really
not that long for Subaru Senpai I sent
her like what I want to perform with her
and
what
[Music]
which part you know that and which
choreo sent her that like
thinking
I think in December or so and
so for nanity we did it with dance
lessons and a teacher about the poster
but we stand by we did it like just
learning it on our own mostly
um
yeah super sample was fine with that
so I'm I'm used to learning things on my
own as well
y'all
I learned it so fast like when we met
at the
beginning afterwards
when I met her for the the program the
New Year's program
[Music]
um
and she told me okay wow by the way I
already learned to dance I'm like what
[Music]
I
didn't even learn it yet
oh
just sent you to Gloria you already
learned it what the [\h__\h]
yeah
I was like yeah I gotta
obviously
I gotta be fast and do my part ASAP
[\h__\h]
terrible spot to be in
[Music]
um
is he gonna get killed if I put in this
far from the front I don't want I don't
want um her to be all alone there
he lived
more poison
ous
I am the Divine Dragon well we got to
attack first
oh my God
sakini
critical Jesus
[Music]
unbelievable
okay
my Chris is still alive
okay okay why is that one going oh
[Music]
that's weird
oh yeah I'm on hard casual oh
uh
didn't I have that written somewhere
before
[Music]
let me write it here
playing hard casual
okay
[Music]
I go Pete treasure box he's going for
the treasure box
I gotta get there before him
huh
that little [\h__\h] no way
ah Crystal okay right right once he gets
it I can still get it afterwards if I
killing him okay
okay
just a scratch oh you can't move
[Music]
yes I will
like learning it on our own and then
yeah we just did like rehearsal together
to like match it up
but
I don't think it was anything really
to mention there but we had a lot of fun
doing it together
I'm so glad I got Super Saiyan 5 for my
showcase
I really love her
it was definitely a nice memory to make
together
I'm glad that I could once again
do my wagamama
I mean it's my showcase so I can be
selfish right
so I got
I got to do another hell of a project
song
and I originally I gave super Senpai
some choices like which one do you want
to do this one or this one and then she
was just like oh whichever you want
I I chose the Tomodachi because
I think it's just you know the perfect
friendship song from
my beloved Idol group
can we get a crit I might get a crate
out of this
and it's still cheerful and happy
I'm getting sleepy
and the aquarium is so Dynamic and
bouncy
I'm quite happy with it we I don't want
to go down there they're gonna slay her
oh Chris
I'm just gonna chill here
[Music]
um
it's perfect for you too right yeah
and then she prefers to learn with a
teacher
and oh how did I do that no undo undo I
don't want that
so you know for me it's been a while I
think since oh oh wait that's not even
unit for me
it's been a while since I learned
tutorial with a proper teacher I mean
recently I've been doing that more
because like also
some other dancers I've been learning
um
yeah so it's it's quite nice to
have a teacher hammer it in your head so
you don't have to think as much
I think we both picked up tutorials
pretty well so the thing was for this
song if you look at the original
um video
for this one we were able to use the
original choreo or allowed to use it and
um there's like this consists of five
members
but for some reason for this song they
only let
they only let
they only let the two like kind of main
singers
sing for this song
[Music]
um so I did think it would be actually
quite a good duet song even though it's
from a five members group
and the other free members I feel kind
of bad for them
because in this song no just being
backup dancers even though they're
full-fledged members of the group who
can also sing
but it makes for a really cool
harmonizing duet song
thanks to that
so the free in the back they're like
hardcore dancing
and the two dancing the two singing in
the front are kind of
only really
dancing in the intro and the outros and
the dance break and so on
so I thought I think it's fine if we
just take up that role since we're
singing anyway
so you may have been thinking while
watching that we were just like vibing
randomly and yes that's what we were
doing because that's what the two
members who sing in the OG were also
doing
and then we were trying to
you know
really break it down whenever it was
time to break it down
[Music]
no I don't think I tell you told you
about the hello project PowerPoint no
oh that's cool
I just read the comment that says poison
their Kiara
oh well
unit near her oh well nothing happened
no
yeah yeah yeah
they didn't go for the attack
where is the bow unit that you're
talking about I don't see one
no
and
yeah in hindsight you know I did want to
do like a full-on dancing too with Nana
C just because we can
uh but
I think it's it was a good like contrast
to the Subaru one where we were full on
Dancing we just have one song where we
focus on singing properly
it came out really well the harmonies
were so nice we just gotta say big thank
you to cute Who besides the you know
official version of the song where the
harmonies are overlapped
um they actually officially released
the separated versions of each member
singing it alone which made it really
easy to copy it because otherwise it
would have been really hard for me and
probably foreign
uh the differences
um
so we were using that to learn the song
[Music]
[\h__\h] that can't [\h__\h] reach it's
unbelievable unbelievable
I guess it's time to use an anti-toxic
does it happen often no but cute was
just based
they're cool so they do cool things
[Music]
that is stupid
um
based on what you're stupid
[Music]
just base things now they have so many
good songs they don't
we're out of enemy Ranch you're squishy
okay oh she can
does she have a sky remote so I guess
it's flying okay it's just like how the
[\h__\h] does that horse get up there
she off of range
see the other range here
okay
yeah
[Music]
I hope you liked me and Nancy dancing
those Dance part they may have been
short but
we worked hard on those
to make them look cool
then itchy was like a little bit
um how to say
she was unsure
yeah because she was just unsure of
like how to move her body during the
freestyle parts and honestly like in
general if we like talk about clubs or
whatever I don't go to clubs partially
because I don't know how the [\h__\h] I
would move
like in a scenario where there's no like
choreography I can only really function
with a choreography
yeah then she was like looking up stuff
to get inspiration on how to move
for those freestyle parts
I feel ya I was just trying to copy
you know
[Music]
how they did it in the OG and just
vibing
um
one thing that you know the um
the studio director told me after the
Showcase oh
yeah you're so good at dancing huh I'm
like well
thank you but
I do still
very much
like
I don't know I'm not quite satisfied
I guess we haven't talked about my
showcase properly at all yet anyway
right I am not satisfied
I know I was like hyping it up to being
like proper tracking and all that blah
blah blue
and we're all looking forward to that
but I'm not satisfied with the tracking
I still think it dampens
my movement
[Music]
Chihuahua I was hoping for more you know
what this is once I will
[Music]
because I didn't think of that
like especially body rolls and like
the one YouTube short I uploaded there
you can see it really I was doing hip
thrusts in that one movement
and they're like not visible at all same
thing goes for fever not people not have
some hip rest that I really feel very
embarrassed about
be quite honest with you
Mrs choreographer piano son
oh oh I get poisoned there well [\h__\h] it
we have to like make
um
yeah it will be like that that's okay
so what do we do here
and attack
you can't do [\h__\h] then I I'd rather go
up and do something but I can't do
anything up there either
oh how shitty
and I can't even stand on here to charge
in the next turn or so
oh this is really stupid
[Music]
why is this so stupid
no but I was already trying really hard
to exaggerate oh yeah Revival okay I
will do that
it's trying really hard to
exaggerate my my movement
[Music]
like constantly that's why it's even
more it's gossiping than just dancing
normally
I have to dance
[Music]
and then one thing I've noticed you know
yes you may see body movement clearly
with my default outfit because it's
tight and there's not much like stuff to
it there's no Raffles and like ribbons
in this and that all that a lot of the
other members
in general have
and I always thought you know that looks
cute and then I was telling myself well
it's okay for me as a dancer
it's it's good that I don't have all
these extras to my outfit because this
way you can see the movement more
clearly
but now now I'm again on the side where
I'm not happy with that because I see I
see how ninja she dances let's see how I
dance when I see it in 3D and foreign
energy looks so much bouncier and bigger
because she has so many ribbons and
flowy elements in her outfit
that will make the dance look much
bigger
now I don't have that
I'm already trying my best to dance
really big and exaggeratingly
[Music]
and I said that to the studio director
like yeah well thank you but
[Music]
um
no matter how big no matter how strong
how much power I put into my dance moves
it's always like it always feels like
kind of dampened and and I feel like if
there was more flowy elements in my
outfit that would move along
bounce around then it will look bigger
too
so that's just something that me as
someone who's really like dedicated and
a perfectionist in terms of like me
wanting to show off my dad's skills
she's not happy about
sounds like you'll be using your shiny
for red outfit a lot more when you do
free yes I think so too
I think that will be like I'll be using
it all the time
yeah you're right with that
you arrived at
I mean like it's it's especially I think
you know the limbs the limbs move
um accurately but it's the the body like
upper and lower body just you know
without the limbs without arms and and
the legs just that part that square part
right
that's what's
hmm
difficult because it's just it doesn't
like the Torso yes it doesn't show
properly what I want to show
[Music]
thank you
being happy good enough isn't the best
attitude always striving for
professionalism well but that's one
thing I can't really do much about
and that's that's frustrating
can't do anything about it because you
know that's just how the and that that's
already like the highest quality
tracking it doesn't really get better
than that
I think
look me should we go up or down I count
the size but I guess
uh we're going nowhere I don't know
go down
I'll just stay here
[Music]
double pointed
oh
he's worth it
[Music]
one thing that I feel like they could
still improve on I'm sorry
in my opinion and that's face tracking
in 4D
uh but like a cloudy wise I feel like
this is like
As Good As It Gets
which is so frustrating me
[Music]
let me swipe the dragon [\h__\h] you
maybe I've been thinking like I want to
do more stretching and stuff to get more
flexible because that's the one thing I
think that I could still like do
that would make my body move even bigger
to get more flexible and surely my
movements will look bigger
I would hope so
are there any benefits you see with
sleeker app is like a restaurant it
looks smaller
no the only thing that is maybe good is
that there's not so much of like scuffed
um
what's the word
[Music]
oh
like things
what's the word clipping yeah clipping
that's the only really
good Advantage I am I see and I guess
you have a nice silhouette but I do also
like the nice Silhouettes with outfits
that are more like cool
cool
fluffy and all that
oh well it's not like I can change this
it's not like I
look it's not like I I am ever gonna get
out of this so
um I have to accept it that was not
worth the detour
that was not worth the [\h__\h] detour
what the [\h__\h] 2 000 gold
[Music]
you're the only man who has a hip and
the ultimate quinoa
just looks simple it just looks so
simple
[Music]
I feel like especially with like Iverson
Council
I feel like miff still had some like
simplistic designs right like me and
Kura
and in a way Amit too
but then Iris and Council come out with
these super intricate designs
beautiful intricate designs
yeah
well it I think you know there's
preferences to
that kind of stuff and I don't know I
wouldn't say there's like
it's better to have intricate one so
it's better to have simple ones
I wouldn't say it I was like
something like that
I'll do my best it depends on what
you're looking for really what you want
to achieve
nah
[Music]
you know that's I'm really regretting
not asking for did I ever say this I
regret not asking for a Freddy uh outfit
for my 1 million wish
the only reason why I didn't do that is
because I didn't think that would be
possible
but I I I didn't think that was an
option
and also I guess because it was so far
from being able to use my 3D I also
thought well I will have more use with a
live to the outfit
in theory that's true
but now I really wish I had a me first
another 3D outfit
is it two million milestone
which is let's be realistic I see my
growth it's so far away
uh definitely not happening this year
or a concert real life concert not just
like 3D birthday or whatever
which
as we know because everybody's at all
the members are asking for it and being
put on a magical mysterious waiting list
that I haven't seen
um
that's also not gonna happen anytime
soon
at the time Freddy wasn't looking as
promising so going with life today made
sense that's what I thought and I also
kind of wanted to Doodle yeah because I
also I think one more reason why I did
that was because I thought you know at
that time myth was always going with a
theme together it seemed like you know
management wanted us at the time to
always have a theme together there was
absolutely okay which theme do you want
this time etc for new outfits and I was
like well dildo doesn't ever match these
themes so I'm not getting a deal but I
kind of want to deal because you know
you know it's cute and then
wanted something to represent that side
of me
yeah
so I thought that was the only way of me
getting a candle
no 1.5 is not considered a milestone
with a reward
[Music]
um
but for me it's definitely a huge
milestone that I'm looking forward to
I'll reward myself in other ways
it's a milestone for me maybe not for
them but it is for me
I will celebrate this this [\h__\h] out of
1.5 you can bet on it
I went
yes I will
and we're getting there we're getting
there sorry I'm just like so slow can we
like focus on the fight a little bit
uh uh I think can I do something like of
meaning
[Music]
I could heal this person
have a physique oh that can do another
distance
here we go
[Music]
I'll celebrate by ordering a bucket of
KFC thank you
anyway all these things I've been
discussing now it's no things don't
that's just how things are and that's
okay I can accept it but just you know
it's just
things that
are not the most ideal should I go down
here now or afterwards
they are gonna come for me
[Music]
I didn't wait what am I doing um please
miss please miss on the other side to me
hey
and I just also kind of want you guys to
have like an Insight of how things work
and how and explanations and weavable
[Music]
you know always try to share things with
you so you guys also have a good idea
and an understanding
[Music]
emblem
okay well she's like purple now
oh
should I do this
[Music]
atrocity
uh-huh
she looks cool
14 that was bound to happen it looks
cool when she's engaged with that emblem
so purple
Aquino
design
what
what continuously when I look at her
design all I can think of her original
design all I can think of is just
Pokemon
was there like a Pokemon character a
trained Arena trainer or so
[Music]
Jim
Trina who has a similar design because I
always feel like that
no not but maybe like a mix
no I'm thinking of someone who had like
the same kind of like bounciness and
like like similar outfit Iris
[Music]
Pokemon Iris
no no
that's not never seen never seen that
person before I guess I don't know I did
but no
you know
[Music]
oh that definitely has like similar
Vibes because the pose and I don't know
it's the tropicalness about it
but I feel like there was a trainer who
had the same maybe I'm just imagining it
the same kind of like outfit but like I
don't know
Olivia
[Music]
no
what
[Music]
oh cute but no
no
it's it's not about the skin color
I'm Legit oh these always
[Music]
trying to say
look it's the clothes
[Music]
oh man
okay whatever maybe I'm just imagining
it because it's like a design that you
can definitely imagine right in in
Pokemon
gloves
clothes clubs
that last one I'm looking up
clubs that just brings up gloves
blogger is a clover
no that's what Pokemon clover
oh Skyla
[Music]
no
oh no she looks like I don't know from
like Winx Club or something like that no
that's not what I'm thinking about
that's also my little thing
[Music]
whatever maybe she doesn't exist maybe
she only exists in my brain I'm
hallucinating
[Music]
I'll I'll go
oh
go and attack
show you the algo rhythm
[Music]
yeah it's just listing female trainers
so many
attacks we're gonna expand by anti-toxes
I don't even need that many in what
world do I need so many anti-toxins not
even here
that popping out
come come and get him
to be one
well if I keep on standing in the
[\h__\h] poison
then I might need all those anti-toxins
nice man
[Music]
I forget you
I didn't have to be scared to stand in
the middle of all that
hello
[Music]
clean the cookies
she gets so many crits yeah
did you use a different marker for his
shrimp of course I didn't but I was also
sick
oh but I was wearing like a pin like
ready but I was listening back on the
stream and it really didn't sound as bad
as it felt to me it had to stop me I
actually had no voice and it was so
painful to speak especially the more
time passed more careful it was but of
course you want to be like hype like
it's a showcase so I didn't want to be
like oh hi everybody sorry I need to
speak quiet because it's my show yeah
because I I missed a mistake
of course I can't do that like it's a
really important event right
didn't sound so bad right no it wasn't
even that noticeable well it got much
worse after that anyway
I guess it's good that it wasn't so
noticeable because
and it's not so terrible
oh one more thing about like dancing
there that kind of restricts me a little
bit I feel like
you know the
there's like all kinds of camera angles
right and there's like one that's like a
like a hand cam right there's someone
controlling a hand cam
and a person is like with me in the room
controlling it
and
and yeah the camera does tend to get
very close to me and of course they
don't know the choreo so
some like when I have to like
punch forward or so like
it's difficult
and it also makes me feel kind of
embarrassed I feel like if I was dancing
all alone in the room I I would be able
to display a bit more power
[Music]
um
cheers I should have unpoisoned myself
oh well
I genuinely feel
I feel about
dancing like I have to say respect to
the to all the other whole numbers the
same place and so on when they do it
they seem like they don't they don't
like
care about it at all like there's no one
else there that's like nobody's watching
right but I definitely feel like
someone's lunchroom
so embarrassing also during MC and stuff
I feel so awkward
for the actual showcase the camera
wasn't the only person in the room that
were like you know some helpers who
would like help me with the items that I
have to
use and all that
um
they did however
uh I think helped me
um
I mean the whole time you know during
transmissions and so on I was like like
right before until the one second when
uh
like this one second before the stream
started I was like screaming like
[Music]
yeah
I was so nervous about it
ah
so so so so so terribly nervous
but kind of not being all known
in some way while also making me feel
shy oh [\h__\h] also helped a little bit I
guess because it gave me mental
stability I'd be terrified I do not
blame you
you know that makes me think you know I
had like some staff members in the room
but
during Cali's reveal
[Music]
the whole time we're in the room when
she was like you know doing all those
sick performances right
they were like uh because me and gouda
were uh from Discord right
in on Discord and and I was watching
until it was our turn
uh and we were like chatting on in our
Discord group yeah they basically got a
live show for real for real
and and we were like holy [\h__\h] this is
so fire me and Kura in our in our chat
and then uh I mean you never replied
right yeah we're watching it like for
real for real life like for real real
she's like so fire holy [\h__\h] it's
amazing it's incredible
hahaha
yeah and she I think if if I had members
in the room I would be even more nervous
about doing my stuff
there if they were watching me while I'm
dancing I would feel even more
self-conscious about it
oh
[Music]
yeah but they were watching Cali
and I was like how the [\h__\h] are you
staying quiet how can you not scream and
be like
oh
holy [\h__\h] like that's so so on fire with
a rap
you know like yeah it's hard to hold
back
we're going crazy inside
hmm
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah and I guess so now when I
was recording at amma's place like fauna
you know they would be watching me
[Music]
um that was a bit embarrassing indeed
but I got used to it because we were
doing that for three days straight
from morning till night
as all we were doing So eventually you
know what I was really embarrassed about
and during that time was me being
incredibly stinky
[Music]
that was so sweaty hi Raiders
I was incredibly sweaty during that time
yeah what was I trying to say oh yeah
that I just ah
hey Kelly's like I guess she really
doesn't mind
having those eyes on her and having the
camera in the room and all that but yeah
I did feel like it was holding me back
for some movements
um a little bit a little bit just a
little bit
in terms of like physical like how far
my arms can go and stuff like that but
also just because I'm embarrassed to
do some sexy dance moves or so
I also poses like you know
oh man
[Music]
very sorry and you get used to what what
do you mean DC what are you apologizing
for for me
this
is probably not this
but this we should be apologizing for
mm-hmm
I mean the tangents that I'm not
properly playing the game well there's
so much
also want to hear it
I know you do oh man my team's already
cold
ah
sounds like she's drinking a slushie
now I need to close it out now let's
finish this Pokemon
Get Back Spin two and a half unless
actually decent that's okay okay no it's
not okay don't don't
say it's okay because it's not okay
guess we're waiting
where's that feet there there he is but
I'll go for this one first
[Music]
president thingy
they were talking about who the hell she
is so funny but yeah
[Music]
and of course
it was funny that Obama
does not only have me as an Oshi but
Ahmed too and I just gotta say excellent
taste
excellent taste
that was really funny I want more of
that more and more and more more more
and more and more
Cali enjoyed it too
or more
yeah one too I was listening to the
whole thing it was so good
[Music]
no one
uh
the part that cracked me up the most was
when
um Biden went like yeah like that that's
the one part where he gets like really
loud
I wonder how you did that how he how you
got him to emphasize it so much
[Music]
hahaha
yeah Biden goes like yeah
oh man
oh so funny
[Music]
oh
attack oh
let's go
allow me
oh
you didn't see it oh I guess because it
wasn't kind of like Underground
[Music]
can I don't think you can post links in
my chat right
if you're in the kfp Discord maybe
someone can send it to you
so hear him say a word so accurately
yeah it was so good
I don't know how you do it so well
[Music]
there's nothing I can do right
engagement a little healthy
foreign
[Music]
all right we're going to meet up
with the others hopefully
soon
[Music]
which timeline video did you watch with
the present I'm not sure which one or
just someone somewhere
I don't know which one it was
Albedo
Am I Dreaming Albedo is Captain
[Music]
hello
have you noticed there's like no flying
units on this map
didn't really have to bring up Chris
or the other one a little while
time to
charge
I can't do much with that name anyway
is there charging one down here no
he's that smart or is that stupid
I don't know let's see how far we can
get with the others um
or we can shoot with her she's charged
again
[Music]
I should engage
it wait huh no that was Tiki
ah I was saying that Tiki is the one
that can shoot fire
[Music]
[\h__\h]
yeah I guess I'll just wait down here
for the others but then there's these
reinforcements coming too man
hmm
but okay that might be the best idea to
wait for the others while
um Gathering here going a step back and
charging with this one but she can't
reach this field that's the problem
no okay
um
ah no antitoxins do you have one
you do but you also wait I'll make you
use it first
and then you can trade it with me
but ideally not while standing in one of
those poison Fields right
here should be safe right
[Music]
you might want to catch the thief with
the bottom gang yeah
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
ah
well I mean
it really makes you think
it really makes you think when you have
all these ooshies
[Music]
hmm
what does that tell us
[Music]
foreign
get that out of the way
ouch
not nice
see it
kill him kill him kill him kill him
um
[Music]
okay
is there someone who can one hit one
shot him
no
okay
ah
interesting situation we got here let me
just move these ones down first
[Music]
president medieval one I don't think I
saw that one
[Music]
Lakers has no business taking damage
that a lot of Archer class
doing quite well oh look
wanna go to sleep now good night thank
you for coming
[Music]
oh she'll get poisoned here
she sounds like a step back
for once I'm not making that mistake
are you proud of me
it's so often that I'm using IV for this
kind of stuff and she always lags behind
I had the same thing with her on the
tiki map
hmm
I feel bad for doing that
okay so now
[Music]
we
um
we will do what we have to do
[Music]
lend me your strength shall engage
we should have ai Kiara finally fulfill
the problem with the thing Old MacDonald
Has A Farm I'm not alone anymore I don't
have to
[Music]
did I never sing it before
old MacDonald had a farm
e-i-e-i-o and on his farm he had some
cows e-i-e-i-o with a moo moo here and a
moo moo there hear a moo there are moon
everywhere moo moo old MacDonald had a
farm
e-i-e-i-o old MacDonald had a farm
e-i-e-i-o and on his farm he had some
chicks
with a clock clock here and a clock
clock there here clock there clock
everywhere clock clock old MacDonald had
a farm
e-i-e-i-o old MacDonald had a farm
e-i-e-i-o and on his farm he had some
pigs
[Music]
there hearing oink there and owing
everywhere and oink oink old MacDonald
had a farm e-i-e-i-o
there you go
you asked for it I shall deliver
probably
thank you thank you
that was okay excuse me
[Music]
I need that on Spotify immediately right
thank you
give me the respect that dessert
I'm gonna go I'm gonna order some
[Music]
um
I already put something in my cart
beforehand
I know what I want
okay next
[Music]
brilliant performance thank you
9k on your headset setup what
what are we even sure it wasn't Kiara a
I singing it
come on it's me I'm real
[Music]
a mid version one day
okay Wawa had a farm
e-i-e-i-o and on her Farm she had some
dogs
here and a Bubba there here above there
above everywhere
yes
Drago [\h__\h] what does that do I spend the
red oh depth plus two to use it
permanently
[Music]
okie dokie
has potential
yeah use it on your highest defense hero
whoever that is I don't think he's here
right now
[Music]
what about the 11 sword
by 11 swords and also attack from
auditions
what about iron sword
[Music]
they create challenges
oh wow
wow
that's your sick sword
really cool
[Music]
yeah of course I heard a sang 99 look
balloons before
oh I don't know I'm fake no balance
[Music]
ah
okay
[Music]
hello now
we're chill I look alive
first I have been watching some videos
she keeps on getting into my recommended
quite funny
I think there was like one video where
she had like a mental breakdown that was
really funny
oh
yeah it must be fauna
I wouldn't mind either that could be
interesting but I don't know how that
would work
bird bastards
me first burn them to the ground
[Music]
oh I like how Lynn takes a shot too
right after the fire
[Music]
cute Joker music
I am sorry I'm sorry
sorry
[Music]
we have gabbard here today
uh
to get another bracelet so let's get it
[\h__\h] going
I trade with someone who has it you have
one Wanna Give it to me please
I want to keep all these things whatever
she'll survive it
right
I'm sorry to poison she can stand here
what about those uh units that are
coming from right sides should I worry
about them
[Music]
I'm still engaged
[\h__\h] my me
[Music]
that's what I thought I wonder if
they're gonna catch up with me
[Music]
okay
wants to go for Celine probably
[Music]
well
come at me bro
gets poisoned
they will probably catch up
oh
hey you were beautiful while you lasted
bring up a pair of armor units
[Music]
three percent crit
that's what they get for challenging my
favorite girl
[Music]
and they're catching up in the back
oh
of course go for it now
uh no I wouldn't kill them
um unless I engage probably
let me see what that does
emblem
oh greatly
[Music]
from there to hit iron ah yeah that's
like the double
punch
[Music]
engage and use grade eight for new them
really
near them
[Music]
but won't they move
if it takes one round
won't they be gone by the next one
[Music]
interesting Maybe
come on
foreign
[Music]
I can take one more down but I don't
think unless I
engage
then I should be able to take Christmas
strength and victory a clear another
line
okay
[Music]
surely I can with some atrocity
this is so broken it's so broken
engaging gameplay that I'm learning to
get over my like Jr RPG curse where I
don't use things that are useful
because I don't want to waste them I'm
getting over it
at least for the emblems
now
listen I'm getting sleepy did you just
say this ends now
[Music]
it sounds exactly
like in Tales of a price
[Music]
wait wait did we like previously realize
that they have the same voice actress
[Music]
didn't we like
right a bunch
[Music]
that's for Jade yeah but
uh
that sounded like
um
from Tales of a rise but she says the
same phrase and it sounds exactly like
how she says it this ends now right you
know what I'm talking about
oh my God
that's not even the same voice actors
right
and she plays silica Celica but we don't
have it right now so that wasn't true
[Music]
what a joyous feeling yeah it really
feels like for games and animes they
always use the same voice actors right
in English
if they need more variety and more
choice can hit me up anytime I would
love to get some job like that man I
would love to
oh
I guess you can help
why not
[Music]
[Applause]
Japanese clothes
I mean even in Japanese voice acting
there is often a lot of oh hey I've
heard this voice before I haven't heard
the choice before
so you know certain popular ones gets
reused I'm tired again and again good
for them very good for them
Unforgettable
[Music]
no matter the line of jail
all right
oh my God
she's hiking
whoa
that was so blue
[\h__\h] shush I only killed one of them
though
the rest was already gone
that was really cool
game's a bit loud okay
and I might go for an Isle meeting how
is this taking so long next next battle
we do today I'm gonna try to do faster
okay
really quickly the thing is about to
arrive and I want to go to an island
meeting
time you can you can also go to idle
meeting guys maybe
foreign
okay see you in a second
[Music]
kiwawa not here because she looks down
and hides behind her hand no wait let me
let me actually
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
okay
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
oh
snacking
[Music]
hey hey hey
hey hey
I got myself for some reason a hot dog I
felt like eating a hot dog
okay and some tea as well and it also
came with a little piece of chocolate
cake
sure
hot tea perfect because I just ran out
of the other tea like it got uh
um cold
[Music]
I need to put in the back by myself
apparently
see good color right
this one is not um chamomile though this
one is like some soup normal
English breakfast or something like that
I think
real hot afternoon hot tea hot dog Fire
Emblem really hot
ah you're cool
maybe oh
my dad's why I felt like eating a hot
dog again
God
[Music]
I pour some honey
into that tea
more and more and more and more we're
running out of honey again this is my
second honey bottle since I came here
I'm running out
putting it on the Mind y'all
so yesterday I was typing some stuff in
their chat
and then
she's like
let's go to Disney because we before I
was out because I know she likes that
kind of stuff for sure let's go to
Disney sometime and she said when I was
in her chat yesterday she said let's go
to this and I'm like
because the other day when I was in the
studio
I saw there was souvenirs
from her recent Disney trip of Zeta and
Lisa they've been they went really
recently
like what a week ago or so
or two a week or two
no I'm not gonna drag her to Disney
twice in one month that one probably
wouldn't be so special
it's okay
so
it's okay and we don't even have time
for a day of Disney with her
hmm would be nice if I can still see her
though before I go back
I wouldn't want to go twice a month
either
I don't think she would wanna
no matter how much you love Disney
look I think they went to Disneyland
there's also Disney C here
[Music]
you're telling to watch Lord of the
Rings now that you've seen Star Wars
kind of
she's aware that I've been watching it
can I take a bite of this hot dog
so this one is with a [\h__\h] ton of
pickles I wasn't sure if I I would like
it so we'll see
it has like
like really tiny pickle thingies all
over it
[Music]
I don't know if this is my kind of hot
dog yeah relish I guess yeah really
strong yeah that's what it is I've never
had that before
[Music]
do you guys like that kind of hot dog
ah
[Music]
radish it's still already chef
I like it
[Music]
the thing is it looks like it's so much
on there
but it's not so bad
[Music]
without the assets thank you they're all
my blue blue
has been making all these lovely assets
[Music]
I saw a blue mate it's a microphone for
me
I don't know if it's for me it didn't
say it's for me but I mean it's a
chicken microphone so it's probably for
me
maybe trying to get on my good side let
me tell you it's working it's working
it's really cute I love that microphone
I'm gonna use it
right now
[Music]
hmm
but I wonder because you posted one
version that has like a like a volume
thing going on
I wonder if someone can animate that
[Music]
um
it may have been a joke
but it broke my heart for a second made
me sad
[Music]
dle fly emblem so true thank you
playing with one hand but what was I
doing just now
what are we doing
I guess we'll wait
[Music]
foreign
who needs it
oh yeah
now we're good
[Music]
sorry guys I'm all I'm already halfway
through the hot tub
mm-hmm
yeah there's a dog in my arms too
[Music]
spicy mustard
we're almost there there's no enemies
here because I already baited them all
hey
[Music]
oh thank you
yay Cafe
do you add 3D collab tomorrow
[Music]
okay
it's about time I got moved oh
oh
I activated something in him
[Music]
okay
um
[Music]
mm-hmm
and future is
spicy
is that kind of spiciness that makes you
nose tingle
[Music]
this makes me miss
um Austrian German
sausages like this sausage is okay but
there's better
[Music]
thank you
it's a hot dog
the bread
bread is okay Japanese bread is very
different but it's very good
[Music]
oh
I'm done
[Music]
yeah because people think
that all Germans do is eat sausages
which is not true
but I guess that means that we have good
sausages
so
laughs
and the verdict is
it looks good
it looks good it was good
that's something stuck in my teeth
though
good that you guys can see
[Music]
yummy
okay focus
[Music]
all these blue haired emblems I barely
used them this fight I don't use them at
all what the hell is going on
let's go let's go
that one's so far
[Music]
Hortons just did it
oh oh
oh
I'll pull back for now
but the time is gonna be different
should we reverse time
we're almost at the end when we are at
the end so maybe not
[Music]
I could but um
yeah okay
it hit
fabrication away the fabrication away
the fabrication weighted fabrication
waited
okay so from here
Just Gotta Stay
here
apparently
[Music]
um
emblem
so this time hopefully no deaths
he takes his shot at Celine
and another shot at Celine
have a good night
very dangerous she's she's in big Danger
let's hope she doesn't die
no one else is gonna go for her right
okay okay okay okay okay
and we're gonna level up out of it yeah
good one
[Music]
what are we gonna do about that she's
gotta heal herself
the other one who could heal her is
quite far
she have the
oh all right
teachers amazing
[Music]
Hector's range
no I don't think I gave potency or
healing stage did I
minute
it's okay it's okay
I know I guess one of them is the
breaking one one of them is the warping
one
of them might be a healing one
[Music]
a good night
Alia's dragon breath to hit all three
dragon breath
oh and was that the one that's not the
one where you have to stand in the line
right
me too emblem engage
[Music]
how does that work
you mean the fog breath
uh
how would I hit all free
doesn't look like it because it's all
free
no never mind it does
[Music]
uh
that's the same kind of
what are these patterns
and I think standing in front of him was
actually better
don't you think
[Music]
no only two
see that's okay
I guess we shall do that yeah yeah yeah
yeah okay okay
relax
oh
God
or is that a thing like not only for her
are there more like these
[Music]
and the second pattern is oh where the
[\h__\h] were that interesting
avoid Plus 30.
I want to stand here and get the chest
maybe more than attacking right now let
me do that I guess
unless
[Music]
I don't know
Hill first
will take a little
[Music]
okay it's not like I think oh never mind
I can kill
anything
let's take a sip and then that's how a
princess does it
a throat Hort
um
[Music]
it's a thing for strong dragons in the
series usually dealing penetrating
damage well this sounds strong
[Music]
oh
okay
[Music]
um
oh that looks good to me yeah
uh I won't get damaged back because I'll
break him it hit me first
thank you guys
I can't believe I did that
[Music]
new Mario Kart DLC is out next week uh
you mean there's another wave
I don't really care about these waves
but
cool I guess
are there more archers up there
no not really okay
[Music]
um I wonder how dangerous Hector is for
us
[Music]
there's more tracks I haven't played it
in a while
but
did you guys play them are they good
[Music]
talk about a good time line up to create
a Killzone they will come along with
tanks
oh nice
more DLC for find them but don't worry
I'm still playing fire emblem for a
while so
I'll definitely experience that
[Music]
kills all you
use calzone
[Music]
if Yakuza brings out a new
game
that is not a remake or so
like a what is he doing is he doing the
thing that I did what he charges
yeah I'm just waiting for a new release
at this point and many other games I
need to play but
yeah eight yes I will play that
[Music]
what is he doing
oh is that one coming out next year oh
yeah they announced it like really early
right
I heard about it but it's so early
can't even imagine
[Music]
let's move let's move the Chihuahua
first
um
[Music]
let's claw him like a kitty cat meow
there's a prequel I'm getting sleep
seven coming out this year
hmm well I'll look into it when it comes
out maybe I'll play it I might
[Music]
can you talk in a British accent well of
course
oh
anything for you darling no that was not
for ish at all I can't I can't
I admit it I can't
I shall admit
I am
I am just ashamed of my existence I'm
sorry
lost judgment nah I don't think so
how do you listen to it so much right
right because I listen to it so much
because I'm a right she's totally
British that's where I I get it from
yeah yeah yeah
wait should I they said I should make a
Kill Zone
but he's all that's left over
can I just move over to him now
cornering him
is that bad
the treasures I took them all yeah
[Music]
okay go get him oh all right
I could even make a fire here or attack
normally but I'm I won't even do damage
about that normally so
I'm gonna do a flame Gambit hey wait
hold on
no thank you I changed my mind
Taxi
[Music]
hmm
wait oh wait there's one more left here
I guess
[Music]
oh yeah I know I know don't worry I'm
getting it all flowers eventually will
I'll get that one
[Music]
I'll get Outlook
tomorrow so she needs to charge anyway
smart good thinking well it's just
there
hmm
[Music]
well
as I'll wait
more basic action
agent blocks I don't know always like
emblem is that well I'm like the only
thing I know that that one can't hit
from a distance and so I waited
[Music]
to the Clone one
which one which one has the Clone one
okay okay okay I'm getting there
I'm getting there oh survive please
oh 43 that's so bad Hector what's wrong
is it because I'm on the horse flying
well you chose The Wrong Enemy
[Music]
damn oh my God so many reinforcements
oh
Chihuahua is here parties over baby
[Music]
which one do you want
um
what the [\h__\h]
do I need to break him first
what what the [\h__\h] is that
what the [\h__\h] is that
so much for it being overpowered
I guess I gotta do magic right
now
oh that looks good yeah yeah
[Music]
let me take one of his lives
All In The Name Of Peace
[Music]
I'll be fine
the fog wrap still does the most but I
would die
[Music]
no no no let the Mages do their job
how far can you go
not close enough just one tile
honey
no never mind I can do some stuff with
my father
oh sorry I skipped his dialogue
[Music]
going well
um
if I engage with you
what can you offer to me probably a zero
is it a zero
maybe I should do this for the children
or
well nearby means I saw it previously
they don't have to be right next to me
right
what if I pull an all for one
oh that's pretty decent
[Music]
Jason no this looks like
we've been through spaces
[Music]
wait let me do someone else first then
oh okay
one more
HP bar down let me help
yes you win
no need to engage her in your situations
foreign
[Music]
because I only have one turn left
or no no wait we saw that I'll die if I
do this
[Music]
the final final ones yeah yeah yeah yeah
probably gonna kill someone next time
yeah I guess that's all right
he didn't really do much against uh
Hortensia so I'll give it to
um
oh no
who could he do a lot of damage to
who do you think he'll kill
him
[Music]
you were safe with me
for SP and bonds
he won't reach the interviews that's
also true
well I want to engage
yeah oopsie I want to do something with
my engagement
[Music]
one second
I have to think of every option
[Music]
what happens again if Tamara comes over
nothing right it was do or do or do it
right
and with these things just a little bit
and it is
so ridiculous
okay I'll go here
[Music]
I'll do
even Fallen star or I'll do a shield
Gambit
no
[\h__\h] it
don't care
just did this to get one more person
closer basically
[Music]
so that this would make more sense
four times four
yeah yeah
who has it
wait forgado
well
would he have killed with it I don't
think so
[Music]
interesting idea
people
[Music]
interested
we're doing it I did in that one turn
free HP bars
[Music]
not sure if that was that bro would have
done the whole HP bar but this way
was of course always the way I plan
doing it
oh my God
get that young
boy
I don't understand how could so much
growth happen to someone like me what's
happening well well you did a really
good job there
[Music]
thank you
thick
yo yo yo yo
actually managed to beat me
I'm impressed
I take that to mean you're happy with
what you saw
no doubt about it one glimpse of your
fighting Spirit was more than enough
took all I had to hold my own against
you you'd be fine even without my help
I'm sure no we need all the strength we
can get and you've got plenty of it I
couldn't have gotten through your
defenses without my allies at my side
treasure that feeling
I used to think I could protect everyone
I cared about with nothing but My Own
Strength I couldn't have been more wrong
it was only with the help of trusted
friends and allies but I survived the
black Fang your friends must have been
really good people
talking about them fills me with pride
even now I appreciate your determination
and desire to forge ahead does that mean
you'll join us
for as long as you need it my ax is
yours thank you emblem Hector I'm
looking forward to letting you learn
something that's what I like to hear
[Music]
good match dozed
I was half expecting you to ask for a
rematch what's on your mind just wanted
to make sure you were all right I got a
little carried away in that last round
thanks for your concern it was a heavy
blow but I'm fine actually I'm really
happy you're happy to get hit with an ax
not exactly I'm reminded of all the time
we spent together you me and Allie would
we trained hard all I can think of is
Elijah but those days are full of happy
memories for me seeing you fight with
everything you had just now gives me
that same feeling I understand
completely I'm more relaxed going into
battle
because I know you'll always have my
back and because you're a cherished
friend
I trust you with my life good I hope
you'll let me protect that life now
instead of charging ahead by yourself
don't worry I won't ever leave you
behind
yay
we did it emblem had the most high
defense
four and a half hours definitely would
normally not need that much time
[Music]
um
but you know
the sing skill quick reproached
your post there repost a let's counter
attacks follow up while the unit's HP is
above a certain threshold
well
interesting
the engage weapon wolf Bale deals bonus
damage against Cavalry and armored
enemies
thank you skill impenetrable increases
the Union's defense and resistance when
attacked by 30 damn the engage attack
Storm's eye prevents foes from following
up or inflicting the brakes at us is
that what he did that one time
it also lets the unit's counter attacks
follow up
uh-huh
man na
sorry guys it took so long
Vengeance be holding me back
[Music]
um
let's focus a bit on the story
hi Anna what you doing here oh look at
that it's a
cat that looks like a tiger
wow it has glowy green eyes
very
[Music]
iron ingot
I don't think I need to like adopt any
more animals though because I got enough
dogs right
don't really need them
[Music]
nice fight good night oh good night
thank you for coming though
those animals need a home
okay now you make me feel bad
[Music]
okay
I can adopt the dog I think
where was he
there you go
looks like a labrador dog I think I
think that's what they're called
cute
cute cute cute
and I'll talk with him
finger skills up close inspires me to
push myself even harder
that sounds great let's go then
insomnia
I'm going to leave the animals in
settlements since they're better off
being friends with the villagers
uh
what
delicious
elements
time to do the dailies that's exactly
how it feels hahaha
can't get over emcee's here she looks
like a YouTuber
hmm
isn't that discussion we already had
where we said well I think
things like that will look like that to
us only because now we are just you know
I don't know
it makes me so
we found another Divine dragon
we have so much to talk about I look
forward to chatting as well
I'm sure we'll become good friends tell
me about yourself
[Music]
yay level five
right
I just realized
come out for a second to remind me of
nudity with that
that outfit
huh I guess the bright hair
all right let me collect the items let's
go
oh we should try that thing that helps
bonding okay so the membership gifting
thing oh and I should do this too
[Music]
feed uh what was it eggs or milk
what was it the good one
um
you guys will show me surely tell me
milk egg
beans fruits fruits still fine too
oh
any of them
I shall give an orange
better be true
oh that was decent oh okay
he likes oranges
just like me for real for real
okay I think
can we get the bar full
can we
don't give him nuts yep yep
which nuts
do it
[Music]
I did the bump not increase
oh those nuts
ah
thank you for the membership gifting
hey I didn't say it you guys said it
foreign
I got them to say it got him
hey I'm not gonna fish I'm not in a
fishing mood
and one step ahead totally
big brain move
true
it's downstairs
oh my eyes are so tired man
oh by the way the collab tomorrow the
Friday collab tomorrow
[Music]
I just want to say ahead of time I mean
you guys would probably not mind but
other
s maybe
um
management basically asked me
to
kind of be the
emcee
um
but that means I might be talking
maybe generally more
I just I just want to say that before
people are like why the [\h__\h] is Kiana
talking so much because my husband wants
me to
be the emcee
so so people know
um and you guys don't mind
but others might mind
so just so you know
that's what's happening
I have been the chosen one
I'll try to do my best I feel Under
Pressure now
pressure
[Music]
doing stuff like that at home and like
collab or so
Like official program or so still feels
kind of okay because like I feel like
you know I'm on my PC so I can look at
the script and all that and scroll
through and like do this and that
you know what I mean but then
doing it there in the 3D stream I don't
know how how that will feel
like like full book you stand by doing
the MC at the New Year's
um
stream that where I was part of where I
felt like damn I had so much respect for
her because I always knew she was a
great MC
but it was so so noticeable once again
this time I saw it in real life
so I do that in real life and Bam she's
just so good at it
she doesn't feel like no she doesn't
seem nervous or like
I don't know worried about anything
no
I don't have as much experience with
that as she does
we'll see how it goes
[\h__\h] my tea is already cold
oh
it's because it wasn't in the furnace
which is why you guys should buy my
famous merchandise tomorrow
and then your warm things will not stop
being warm
[Music]
good marketing I know right
I think besides my thermos
the other merchandisers Kelly had a
necklace right I may have a
a cap
in a
[Music]
I had the ramen noodles topper thingy
gouda has a bag
I know the bag is kind of girly so maybe
not for everybody but I think my
favorite is actually the gouda bag
I must have it's really really cute too
and I guess Callie's necklace ah the
necklace is pretty there's a lot of
girly supposedly girly things there
I really like the back though
I mean I don't think I would get it and
wear it because
well
it will be difficult to use it
in my position you know what I mean
Prince fogado hey I guess my favorite
merch item would be my furnace
like the most usable one I feared my
presence might dampen your mood right I
think you're being a little hard
definitely something unique we actually
have a lot in common
you're the second Prince of a kingdom
I'm the first prince of a queendom
tomato
I suppose you're right
um why the Sigh we do hold similar
positions but if that is the case why
are we so different you're so carefree
and sociable and I'm a dismal burden on
everyone I meet an afternoon
I guess not that I'm on your downward
attitude it's actually one of the
reasons I like you
you find me likable but that's
impossible I don't deserve such kindness
bad if you continue I may find myself in
a dangerous spot wow what's so dangerous
about me
the stuff he says is even more
concerning when you look at what he has
in his hair please don't look at me your
pure heart is shining a spotlight on me
he'll reveal me for the waste that I am
oh God I have to go I'm sorry I'm so
sorry
oh God ah man that guy really knows how
to make an accent
why
[Music]
why Fire Emblem
you concern me
[Music]
greetings princess Hortensia
princess Saline
[Music]
princess versus Princess tough but I
won't lose pardon what what are you
talking about
oh you're good we even be evenly matched
but you won't catch me admitting that in
competition is it about boobies eyes
[Music]
we are battling then is this yes and I
will ignore whatever I need to
to Proclaim yes
you are no
I will defeat you in cuteness
okay sorry everything else
what cute is yes I think
so that's what you were raving about
Selena's prettier
while you can I'm gonna fantabulize you
into the ground might as well get it
over within surrender
the lover
is she leaving so soon
I had hoped to invite her to tea
[Applause]
I wish I had a younger sister as
adorable you and your team yes while
gone
[Music]
that reminds me
[Applause]
[Music]
that reminds me of something I wanted to
do okay keyword T can you guys when the
stream is over
you write me a stream over tweet just
use the keyword t a lot or tell me
kiwawa
tea time
please thank you
oh man
[Music]
[\h__\h]
damn it
t-e-a
and
oh
I think I did them all
okay next winner comes to mind is food
[Music]
I've grown fond of life in your home
blue blah blue now can you cook
sweet edgy child
and who to cook for
you know
papaya
[Music]
haven't used Chloe in a while either I
think
does she have no specialty isn't the one
with the Sparkles to ah wait never mind
it's not on top this time she likes
risotto she makes rizondo
meatballs and beans
that have been stewed alongside onions
and other ingredients
[Music]
potency doesn't like it though
oh
I think I'll go for someone else that
likes it
wait it's a risotto is that what they
both like
okay
It's gotta be the risotto
I only have one spices
here we go
oh my achievements
oh yeah right
so true so true please
supposed to go
thanks for reminding me I forgot about
that maybe go ah it puts the foods that
both like at the uh
I dare says
[Music]
a hearty meal uh
their hair looks so soft and fluffy
good job
okay
Baltimore
achievements
uh claim all
2100 we are at 25
000 Bond fragments now
what could I do
that I use a lot on
inherit skills ah yeah
foreign
[Music]
not only that
um
tell me what you got
I'll be your opponent
might not be so bad though
oh okay okay
oh [\h__\h] can't get another hit there
should have missed there okay well come
on give her a break
damn it
was a pretty good match though
one more one more
emblem training here
ah yeah that's right that's maybe what I
was thinking of oh
38 hit chance for him he has that note
or take it back I'll take it back I
didn't even say it yet so we're good
nice though
oh yeah he got the killer lens hmm
you were saying nothing that's a bad
level up though only free
one more time right
how about
anybody really close no
[Music]
all right connect
I am peanut Royal soldier of soul
her skirt looks like she was playing a
little bit too much Splatoon oh [\h__\h]
whoa whoa whoa whoa
oh so sorry are you injured let's go
that was a
damn what what's with those level ups
only free again
okay but the excitement made me uh
made me cough
cheers
[Music]
um
the meaty flag them don't say that's
kind of embarrassing
it's a really good level though she was
only three stats up
should I do some emblem thingies
I don't know which one I would want to
do
[Music]
um
only the only stats that matter well
okay then
[Music]
I could
rap
okay
we can get them straight to level five
[Music]
that's cheap crawling one on one is not
for the week of heart
I'm I'm sorry
greetings and salutations Ike I say you
look quite Splendid this very day you
have a big way of talking
I wonder where you picked that up from
exposure
[Music]
and reposition used to move an adjacent
Ally to the opposite side of the unit
oh
uh-huh
tax power
[Music]
okay
after I do more
do I need more for that one skill
you need to get a unit out of a bad
situation
should I what are we aiming for though
um
[Music]
go to 15.
fish
I am pennette Royal Soldier first time
you see someone one shot if you've no
need to hold back
that's on me oh
that wasn't the one shot but still I'm
so sorry are you injured
easy
no struggle there
hmm I hear you were in the service of a
royal family I imagine they were quite
strict about etiquette my friends told
me I missed up sometimes but I never
noticed any problems
boy why are these conversations so short
all these Cliffhangers man
ax proficiency Max Power Defense sword
perfume Urban
yo
and somebody did say I should go to 15.
what do I get for 15.
[Music]
that's Max
ah I have to finish this parallel first
[Music]
did I not oh no that was Hector
oh okay
we could go to his paralog
I wouldn't mind is it difficult
[Music]
where is it where is it where's our
course
[Music]
oh there we are
and we need to buy a long bow for our
crest
oh do we have one probably not
[Music]
and that's meal
no okay I'll go buy one
[Music]
um
sorry energy kind of low right now
um come back to our energy local
oh I can sell it hmm
every country
for short no
I do not understand and I do not agree
give panette a killer ax
oh I can do that somebody that I don't
use has a killer ax right
I saw it just now
panette
get killer ax
Bender no what up
[Music]
oh was that just an ax that was given to
him randomly by the game or what
[Music]
origin refine it too
Diamond has one
[Music]
what will I use
Diamond much again I feel so bad because
there's so many nice units but I can't
use them all
[Music]
interesting strategy
and that I could kill her extra little
Mexican
yeah maybe we'll do the parallel no
story then today that's kind of sad
old dudes go on the bench
[Music]
you get flooded with good units until
this part of the game oh yeah I guess
because we are through the four areas
now the continents
or countries
probably there's not really much more
additions from now on huh
probably actually mostly God all the
units that you can get
oh thank God
this already is such a hard choice
Mr sorry you won't need extra parallel
skills for now okay I got one story at
least today would be good what am I
doing right now okay Lex
let's buy a killax
uh
uh who selleth the killer accent
[Music]
wait you don't sell off the killer
access
you sell of clothing
[Music]
hi
thanks
cute
hey Divine One what do you think of what
okay
empty sweet Charming use your word
sure you're good enough just like always
yes she is put a lot of effort into
being adorable you know at least you
could try hard
I had no idea
forgive me for not noticing that's all I
get
that's all you think about it
kind of shallow
people to be extra nice do you have some
kind of God training that lets you see
through fake crying Divine one God
training I don't think anyone needs
special training to see through and act
like that hey
fine then let me ask you something else
you're not fawning over me I'm
unimaginably cute I am but light people
differently just because don't get so
hung up on it kindness matters much more
wrong being nice is great and all but
cuteness is a huge Advantage oh that is
true everyone knows that I see it is
true try this again only I'll be even
cuter next time so you can't possibly
miss it
hahaha
I'll act as if I'm missing it
hmm she ain't really yeah there's
something like a huge privilege
what do I require let me see
do I require anything at all actually
let me
sell you
50 gold
don't tell her I did that
don't you dare tell her
dinner
tonight
[Music]
do come again more man steps
they had uh one broke as far as I
remember
um
she has four on her physic left
hmm
she has lost one I suppose
[Music]
a great deal of an HP LS HP but like it
has to be right next to you right
this one's the distant one
I'll take the man
I thank you
um
[Music]
and I'll just replace still
no I'll replace the anti-foxin
now you have two yeah physic
fracture and a warp that sounds good
do come again
well hey there
Mike stays she uses an avid plus one way
that's cool
nice skill
Okay so panette
you get
a killer ax
replacement
[Music]
she has what was that
hmm
should she even be carrying that
what was that
gives her HP but does she have to use it
in order to give it HP
[Music]
Sarah
ah permanently
hmm
um
I don't know if I would want to use it
on her
give it as low HP
[Music]
somebody squishy is she squishy
Celine
[Music]
uh this is so stupid this is why
this is so stupid
this whole system
because
I have to put it into her inventory
first
oh this is so stupid
it shouldn't even be an island that goes
to the inventory I should just
such a stupid system
welcome to Fire Emblem
oh man now I have to trade again
and I have to go to trade in order to
trade
oh it's so stupid what did we I at the
end okay
okay enough roasting well hey there I
guess I could use this from the combat
but still it's stupid
it's overall just way too confusing so
uh we need a long bow
[Music]
so something like a killer bottle yeah
there is
[Music]
oh Killer Bow too
here you go
because she doesn't have the radiant
ball might as well give him something
else
here you go I'll give it to you there
you go hope you're happy now you got all
the bows now you got all the bows yay
except for the silver bowl
[Music]
blacksmith's cheaper
oh well
I have I have enough money supposedly is
there something I can sell
oh what's that hurricane ax
why what
[Music]
what why can't I why did I not
I should give that to someone
that is not really good
it sucks
hating X
so many other books I don't use the
those classes at all
I have so many
[Music]
I'm gonna sell them all
except for the expert one
[Music]
also I really don't need so many
anti-toxins now
[Music]
wait what
I thought that was why
I thought that was from those characters
that
eh
the classes that dude that use uh I
thought
thing is
reset but I'm gonna have to redo all the
stupid things I did before that
[Music]
oh the unless the true series of skills
grants one fast hey at least I kept the
expert one
yeah I heard SPS I had to get
isn't there is there a buyback option
a lot of games have that
[Music]
it doesn't happen
you'll be fine without them
[Music]
you
um you can finish it
was DLC oh
I got those from the DLC
[Music]
the last save was right after the the
battle that I just did
and
[Music]
um
I know absolutely okay we'll play you
know the game is already too easy for me
anyway hard mode we play hard mode
self-made hard mode
um
oh let's we get another program
reviewing it yeah yeah yeah
um is that the
which one is that one is it the baby
which one is that
uh
I'm in another one yeah
foreign
[Music]
yeah I said no to the DLC gifts great
and win it okay I think that's the baby
one
[Music]
when are they uploading that one
uh yeah oh no yeah that's my that was
what I was thinking
oh
good night kotako
March 6 is that I think that's Monday
right take care
today
should I
go back
um
[Music]
it's kind of 50 50.
make me safe
[Music]
laughs
hmm
I'm kind of too lazy to redo all of that
foreign
of me doing stuff
no [\h__\h] it
yeah you wouldn't have used them anyway
you really think so
well if we ever get to a point where I'm
like [\h__\h] I wish I had more SP
then we will all be like well if it
isn't the consequences of your own
actions
you won't need them that much
okay that better be true uh so what else
uh I gave Longbow I gave killer ax I
gave killer this and that
is
we should do the the new thing
where do I do the new thing
a bonding thing
[Music]
allies to enjoy Recreation
I don't know who I don't care who should
it be
they were ivy
and Hortensia
let's see what that looks like
they swim
oh
Hortensia faster I can't swim like that
I swim like Ivy that's the only way I
know how to swim
hmm
I tried sometimes before to swim the
other way but I don't think I'm doing it
right because I'm quite struggling with
it
is that once per
you know being in the thumbnail
Yeah okay or is it once per area
for like recreational area
oh
once it seems to be once per week is
this like horse riding
oh
stable
um
Celine
Laura
oh they don't know right doors they
clean the horse
[Music]
you want to know why they can't bomb
oh why not
they feel refreshed only
Nani the [\h__\h]
well how do I know that
it will show a minus if they can
[Music]
magical
oh cute that one's cute
oh
[Music]
farmer approves
okay okay I'll remember for next time
[Music]
Hortensia something on your mind Ivy or
are you just here to admire my pretty
face
I'm just happy we've been through so
much but we're finally together again oh
you're my only family now
I want you to know that you are
important to me yes it's a relief to
hear a half sister counts as family that
has never mattered too I consider my hot
sister as family who is my sister and
you are all the family although there's
other half yeah
siblings that no I don't really care for
the family because I just don't see them
ever yeah when I haven't met in my whole
life you have your mother's smile and
the one that I've met when I was only
really really small and The Sibling was
awesome
place
I don't mean to dig all that up yeah my
husband is the one that I just usually
call sister when I talk about her on
stream my mother saw me on Reddit
several times
just remembered something I gotta do
somewhere sorry Ivy talk later
chocolate pound cake sorry Hortensia
the one the picture yes the one that
fixed my table
with me with my brain and her strength
hmm
y'all be like [\h__\h] you again she's also
quite the gamer
um
and she also loves cats
big cat lover just like me for real for
real
[Music]
hmm we didn't like
um since she's my half-sister like part
of my childhood we didn't spend together
and the other part we did a little bit
spent together like for some time she
was living with me and my brother and my
mom
and for the some other time she was not
living with us
so
yeah we did have some time to bond here
and there but also not really
we were I think lame she's a bit quite a
bit older than me older than my brother
[Music]
um
so I feel like you know
we never really connected
on the same level
I went to age Gap was too big
and we never had this like system
potato
um
I think we did fight
quite a bit
I remember watching her play
what was that game
she was also playing MMR pictures and
stuff there was this one MMO that she
was playing and I liked watching her
play I was just sitting next to I was
like can I watch you play
can you play this game so I can watch
you play
[Music]
I don't remember what it was called
yeah I really liked watching my older
siblings play games
rabbit and playing them myself
all siblings fight yeah yeah
um
[Music]
yeah but
um
and now it's family has their own
issues I think
[Music]
so let's not get too deep into it
most youngest siblings can't relate I
watch my own assimils play games back in
the day ah just like Maple Ray for real
now you get to watch play games what you
mean now I get to play the games
[Music]
couch Club no we never really played
college Club the only couch Club I
played with my siblings was tales of
with my brother but no that's not true
we have played like Mario party or
something like that every now and then
hmm well that's about it
probably I would known Daniel
would you control Symphonia
and most of the time I wanted to play
um Sheena or Colette
or Persia when we had persea I loved
playing persea but no boys I didn't want
to play the boys
[Music]
wait we have a new emblem right now
who wants the new emblem emblem ring
who should I give the new one to
switch around too
here we go
I don't know if I really liked Ringo
[Music]
Louis Jade or panette
um
post shade
we should have said kisara
yeah okay
[Music]
there we go Hector for you leave it to
me ah look at those two buff people
they they fit so well together
who's she
ctor my man leave it to me he says
so cool
you're gonna have buff babies oh my God
they're gonna be be breaking trash cans
from day one
after they're born
like all
polish no wait did I already do that did
I do that within let me see
does any ring need to be polished
oh yeah kind of
please clean it up is this so annoying
it's so unnecessary
thanks again see you next time
the more I do this the more I think it's
so unnecessary
Who currently has Ike
next
could you clean that up
I guess but I think it's really stupid
that I have to do that I worked hard
I'll repay you in battle
um
if there was a button at least that that
could like automate this I would
appreciate it
just polish all
please
give me a Polish all button
s Casino
sorry about the hassle
um
what are you doing yes I was totally
talking about Poland
that was nice of you thank you
you might let you'll be the only person
on the planet who does the pollen really
maybe I shouldn't be doing it
thank you for making us already also
from Poland
although you're from Poland and buy the
books
yeah I feel like I thought you were from
Germany
who here is from Poland
I polished the Rings too
didn't want to say I wake up oh it's
okay good morning
[Music]
okay it's Poland OH
okay so like Free People
let me tell you my next YouTube short
has something to do with cheeky cheeky
bum bum
makes you curious doesn't it will this
take long
you can't watch
you sure you know what you're doing not
the dance but later on I realized I
should have done the dance I hope it
stays this shiny maybe next time I get
an opportunity hey tomorrow maybe
there's some time tomorrow
maybe I can learn it until tomorrow it's
pretty easy
the chorus dance
just like the arms out
front
honestly if I learn it today before I go
to sleep then tomorrow it should only
take like one try like three minutes
like surely they can spare three minutes
[Music]
nah I don't think before only after
should be doable before everybody's like
you know in a scramble
what what are we doing I will guard okay
adult
no need to hold why are they all polish
maybe a different spot thank you for
taking care of it polish friendly
was poor polishes
oh
what
oh holes
that's how you say I just have never
heard that before
I guess in German it's also similar
the Poland
[Laughter]
which I just realized that now for the
first time
um I don't want to look into that
inherit skills [\h__\h] now I don't care
I'm gonna melt
so he also said that that's that that
this one's also stupid no
yeah
I want to do one got time
because we haven't had Ikea rings
yet oh cute
who is she
Mia leopard yo yo he's got all the cute
girls what the [\h__\h]
uh
oh God three years
money this one makes like everything so
special wind adapt hey hey
if you initiates comment with window
quit even May attack twice yo I got
something really special I think
yo SSR
en s
Sr
but it's me oh
excludes element and Excalibur
with wind equipped unit May attack twice
why does it exclude Elven at all
oh
sick oh she's cute though
oh my god oh
holy [\h__\h] these rings
yeah wind is kind of bad right oh
Missy
silver ring
Grill
wow what a pool
you guys
but as easy to charm as I am whoa
whoa
I got clawed
what's going on
oh these are all the free houses rings
free houses characters
all of them are aren't they
that makes sense
foreign
[Music]
I know I'm aware
more Ferdinand you'll do so many
characters why do you spam me with all
of the same ones
Ingrid ah
she makes me want to replay the game and
then choose different house so that I
can see more from Ingrid
so I kind of missed out on her didn't I
don't know English
[Music]
that's the fun part of the game I get it
on foreign
huh
foreign
[Music]
hmm why
oh
[Music]
lion
suddenly like
I don't know
[Music]
what doctor do I go to to have that
looked at
in Austria
actually let's give that one ring to
um
[Music]
Celine was it
where is it
[Music]
Sauron s right so there it is
thanks for saying it in German so
basically a dentist
because dentists usually
um
have that as part of their
specialization I think
no the teeth don't hurt but
hmm
I went to win oh yeah because she has
Elwyn
do I have a wind I don't think so
um
[Music]
I think I must have sold my wings
maybe I have one I don't care it's cheap
okay it's weird that I have to like
downgrade though
for it to work hmm
don't mention this people looks
yeah maybe I'll just get done and bottom
house
yeah yeah
yeah
okay here we go let's go sorry for the
wait sorry sorry sorry sorry what is
this Victorious at Zone Palace the party
six to ring of the crooks of Fate at the
northern Fortress
big
gie
my new moves are coming together nicely
just a bit more practice and I'll call
it a day
it was a spot it's perfect for rehearsal
so quiet and empty
it's the last unit that I'm getting
what is that
no good
trapped here
die like this
well I'm Such a Pity to be caught so
unprepared I don't think it was clean on
this one Let's Dance
who said that
you can hear what I'm saying can't you
call this I love my voice you can hide
in here
female emblem
he's our dancing boy
oh I wish he was a girl but okay
Cory is the northern Fortress that
frightening
yep my ancestors designed it that way
didn't want people to go poking around
the locals won't get near the place they
say yeah he's a dancer apparently wins a
haunted castle lately some have heard a
young woman's voice calling out from
inside
relax that's just the local lore then
why did you make it sound so real
sorry sorry I shouldn't be talking I've
never even been there mom always told me
to stay away so nobody would figure out
the Ring's location
there it is now the northern Fortress
for an abandoned Fortress it's awfully
noisy wait a sec
the corrupted they've gotten in oh no
you can't let them get the ring
all right let's go let's go no time to
waste we gotta go Gotta Go with haste no
[Music]
this place is swarming acid is a little
haunted huh hang on
to find one look
there's someone here pick it again
out in the open thank you Rick thank you
I was telling you to hide not come
looking for me
how could I stay away
[\h__\h] ring you really set off those
creatures as well I take it you're a
princess trapped in this unusual form by
a wicked curse
let me out really I'm no need to
persuade me your highness I'm not
wondering
oh Spirit of the Court Royal status
before us excuse me
dragon
the dragon may come from the gas
connected Source I suppose we'll just
have to hold on
he's kind of all right oh my God I can't
believe this map is so short there's no
way this map is really that short
whatever these doors
that nope
[Music]
wait wait what
for a second I was kind of Happy
it is really
what does that mean reinforcements or
[Music]
um
can I not actually enter after getting
him I can probably enter and then I'll
see what's under that ceiling and then
it goes like all the way around here
around here
this and that all the way down here
not as short as it seems to be
at least this time we can bring uh one
two three four ten units let's go
I shall bring my beloved
shade with Hector
um
and
don't care about the others and look
fine to me
two archers
free okay maybe it's too much Magic
might be too much
maybe you're not gonna
[Music]
no I haven't used her in the world
never too much magic yeah but I don't
know
I want to spice it up a little bit right
foreign
are they confused
but they got the spirit
hmm
okay looks good to me good formation
um
anything else I should do before I think
we're good Lynn on all Chris is great
here
Lynn who has got Lynn right now Ivy well
we can switch around
through our pressure
like mother how do I do this
I'll create
you are getting your honors up because
somebody said so
you knock a better ring okay let's
switch some rings
I'm here for you
and anyone is great
switch at an Archer there aren't any
pliers on this map
well then
uh Lynn let's go
well then I'm now bringing it on Chris
at all
bring Celine back or bring someone else
[Music]
haven't really used Marin except for
once when I had to use her I think
Italian yeah she's just
oh and almost all girls team almost
somebody said about yunaka's Ring being
weak that's true I guess
she is currently wearing the tiki c-ring
[Music]
well everybody who's in the team except
her has a cool ring
which one should I give her
one of the new ones maybe what about
titanium what does she do strength deck
speed oh
not bad I would say
okay
[Music]
I think he's trying to protect it
he's clearly no friend of the corrupted
she'll be safe let's give him a hand and
adopt him it looks like he could use one
like a child and then never use him
again unless well he's a dancer so he's
actually kind of interesting to me
the dancers can make others
get another move right it was like you
go next to them and then then you'll
dance and then they can do another move
right
I used to do that in free houses
all right I remember
[Music]
um
shitty positioning from the get-go
of course
ah
weird too
okay who who's got Lynn uh yeah
I could call Double still
I think I'll call Bubbles
um
[Music]
right a variable I can't get very close
this is as close as I can get
but doubles and great effort
would be kind of weird because then
don't who will they go for
the doubles are for the Aether on it
Violet can do the dance
the doubles got priority yeah only one
of them is a good idea it's what I'm
bringing too
oh wow I'll put it on the front anyway
[Music]
wait so buy little poop
oh that's fine I don't know this palette
because this ballot is male I only know
the female one
so if I engage I can do the dance huh
[Music]
wait if I dance like this and everybody
who's next to me can do it again
so I would want someone to stand next to
her too maybe
is that how it works
oh
[Music]
okay
interesting of course
uh hope I'm not doing this wrong
unfortunately I can't oh wait
no it's okay the others are doubles so
this positioning is fine
and four months is combined dancer and
Twilight
as though it is dance for me Hortensia
[Music]
arigato
oh that's good let's go
what a greater good mentorship
okay
let's go
let's punch them in their stupid faces
sadly not a kill though
unless I get a crib with the killer ax
baby
[Music]
I didn't
unbelievable
I want to see what we can do with that
somebody said I should engage
thank you
[Music]
one HP
should I do the full breath Maybe
yeah
only if I go a step back maybe
yeah she become dragon
[Music]
I'll just
oh maybe there's a chance you can create
there's 47 chance it's pretty high
[Music]
yeah I had to stop you
data
hey hey
I'm engaging everyone from the get-go
are you seeing this
aren't you like really confused
Chihuahua is that you
atrocity
you have my respect
[Music]
okay took as many down as I could even
though they were really far away
shall we
don't know
this map is super easy so whether you
engage or not doesn't really matter hey
I'm feeling good about myself right now
don't you ruin it
maybe if it's so easy I can tension
about something what should I tangent
about guys is there something that I
mentioned before
um
you got your merch by the way yes I did
I got the blanket I got the oven mittens
on the other side oh you know
[Music]
um
until she ordered it on herself by
herself paid for it
that's why she had it earlier
uh yeah
we have to save them
goodbye
and anyways you gave me my stuff
and I I realized oh you don't have the
the
stickers right because you don't
you didn't get the full set but I saw
her on her laptop you know and she has
some stickers on her laptop
so I wanted to give him one
so I cut out
I was like China which one do you want
from my stickers that I only have one
too but which one do you want him
and then she chose of course she chose
the biggest one the one right in the
middle the one with Chihuahua not the
cats not the cafe chicken or whatever no
she wanted the Chihuahua so I was like
hmm
yeah okay
so I cut through the middle of the
sticker sheet
cut her out the Chihuahua sticker so she
can put it on her laptop
yeah I thought you know
I probably don't really need it
by myself
uh I have a lot of merch of myself so
no
it doesn't hurt
I wonder if I can hit from here oh I
can't but it wouldn't kill them
[Music]
first
can I get a thunder going no
wait what do you mean destroy
oh she means the side walls
do I have to
this kind of sucks I can get so close
engine oh well
what's my first
it was a bit difficult because they
speak so fast or they want you to speak
so fast in those
and kind of have to time it so that it
fits with the video and so on I was
recording it alone
but it was fun and you guys have been
praising me said that my voice acting
it was better than usual well thank you
appreciate that
[\h__\h] she would get a lot of
hmm
325 yeah whatever
let me help
oh it's great yeah true I haven't played
it in a while
oh by the way I got a credit
yeah yeah
the best acting so far thank you no no
directing I just um tried to
make it sound natural yeah oh but you
guys are all surprising me for my voice
acting for the Valentine's video too
right so yeah and that was also just me
directing myself
no I think in general I'm not so bad at
it
getting better
[Music]
me first did you guys order it around
Wednesday March by the way or are you
waiting because I think you can combine
it right
Dream well you can probably combine it
with the 3D merch that would be smart
because the shipping is expensive right
waiting to combine I've ordered only got
the voice back oh thank you
I guess that one doesn't need shipping
thank God
waiting for free diva waiting until free
okay okay thank you thank you that's
smart
I suppose it's fine wait a second
can I dance again
who's the dancer
were you the dancer
yeah but you can't dance again can she
ah
um
one per engage
didn't wait but I bought you and a few
other girls thank you
hey
well I hope he survives another turnout
there because I can't really
no I can't do anything I'm sorry dude
I'm sorry
I'm trying to get there
hmm
but what happens after I get there are
we really gonna go for those doors like
I suppose so
should I do the rest thing
once I have some more
peeps
I can reach with her but it also doesn't
kill
that's it
well
the Killer Bow doesn't
but founder and L fired can
well our dancer will live let me help
almost fall
because you keep on dancing Non-Stop
uh
possibly I think so possibly
[Music]
what I do with all these doubles here
now
they can attack back right so chances
are that they'll just take care of this
dude
that way they're not useless
I wish I could move them
I will not lose
[Music]
it
they still I guess so
[Music]
um
wait if I take a step back
and then attack with the hand ax
[Music]
my goodness how awful wait so dancing
dancing class you can't change any
others into a dancing class oh you can
only have the one dancer that the game
offers you
only one yeah
is that only like that in this fire
emblem
when all five
that's how it usually is
and the bottle of ring hmm I see
well the good thing would be to uh
what was that skill that makes them move
after they attack
if I could get that
uh for everybody
that would be ideal
absolute you'll have to destroy those
doors
yes I'm gonna start doing that I don't
know what for but
when you got that ring back
when will I get it back give me back
[Music]
I want it back
radiant Dawn is a bit of an outline of
advantage
what about these walls why can't I break
those just for fun
yo what's so good
oh
let's take this boy down
Unforgivable
what does iirc stand for again I I
really
care
[Music]
okay I choose you that's it I Choose You
Wawa
wait where's koala
did I already use
if I recall Court
it but Chihuahua so far
[Music]
can I like talk from with you from a
distance can we just talk a little bit
louder I'm sure you can hear me
hmm
I love you all
right
I might do that because you guys said
the map is easy anyway
good level up though
should I rewind
try to break the wall and then let her
go through
it was a good level up though
I still got to keep
honestly it's fine
okay
why would you talk to anyone else huh
lame
I'll open the door
I hope it's not bad if I open it too
early
oh
I guess he'll join my team and we'll run
together
right
oh should I move
these front units already through
the door
what's this oh
there's a lot of that here hmm
be careful of the floor here okay
you gotta talk with him okay I wait then
I guess I'll wait them
[Music]
we'll see you soon
no
elephants
why does he not come to talk to me in
his ally face you're wasting my face
[Music]
what you got to say are you there are
you hurt
who are you okay I'm not your enemy I'm
the Divine dragon
he clears the fog
my card spoke true unexpected Source
indeed
thank you
I am Cedar a traveling dancer his voice
sounds like uh from Tales of arise
um the the the prince guy
yes
same voice actor fell victim to some
sort of curse
then
tell me who is this mysterious ring
woman command me and we'll find out
together
it's almost like we're playing Tales of
her eyes
oh
[Music]
I am emblem Corin I'll fight with all I
have thank you the polls the sad the
aura
thank you emblem Corin I'm sorry I kept
you waiting for so long horn time
I like her
big ears of Legends see doll would you
fight by core inside
you could use your help getting out of
here it would be my pleasure
it's world
wanders upon wonders
[Music]
but for now see that will be using her
oh
did those doors just
huh
be able to escape the way we came in
let's try that path over there and I
knew that I anticipated that
so
I can't do anything
as a dancer I can please call upon my
abilities as you see fit
alrighty what about you getting rid of
that weird purple stuff
the gym from current summoning cutscene
was a few heavily arranged strings from
the first Zone in the performance what
in her pretty Deadpool
what
[Music]
um
okay I know that thank you hmm
[Music]
yeah but like it
thank you for telling me about the nose
it's such a rush earlier I notice the
miasma all over the place
the creatures must have brought it with
them certainly wasn't here before
use my power to dispel the miasma and
open a path for your allies
emblem Quorum can restrict both movement
and create the terrain to control the
flow of the battle the same skill drag
in the main adds terrain effects based
on the user's unit type while clearing
the same area of any Flames or miasma
[Music]
the engage weapon dual Katana unlike
most swords is strong against lances and
weak against axes
[Music]
huh uh-huh I will not remember that the
engaged skilled Dreadful Aura prevents a
Target and Falls adjacent to it from
moving for one turn after the user
initiates combat
Gage attack torrential Roar blasts froze
in front of the unit for three spaces
flooding the terrain and clearing it of
flames in miasma
[Music]
but I can only do it like once for
engaging so I can only like clear
this area that's like close to it no
well that we see right now unless I
charge again sometimes soon
should I do that now
while standing here
Dragon Vine is infinite
oh okay but
I have to do it step by step
but now I have to break that [\h__\h]
I don't care that much about this one I
would have just went on with it
so
that's stupid I didn't
disappears next turn
yeah but I don't like it though because
I cannot pass through
that's stupid
I can't do [\h__\h] I would just walk
through and then I would stand here
stupid
yeah I have to I can only break it one
more one that's also stupid
it's so stupid
[Music]
and turn
the stage is mine
[Music]
oh I did it
Grumble Grumble grumble
oh
look at them shooting around the corner
with a curved shot
[Applause]
[Music]
seems handy I guess yeah okay in this
case
yeah it blocks this one from attacking
me for now
hmm
I really wish there was a two where I
could move everybody together
yeah but not the one I'm sitting on
right now okay
busy hatching that one
pick one of those that have no chance
in life but no sorry I'm not like
laughing I'm
so
it's all about options yeah but as a
streamer
wouldn't that be so lame as I used that
of course
maybe privately yeah but I tried it once
and I didn't feel think uh it really
helped me much
it was with that one um
what do you call those training maps
again I was doing that you know the one
where I was really struggling and
redoing it a million times because no
matter what I ended up dying
verily
reposition
oh
why not
and they enjoyed that
huh
foreign
[Music]
honestly
yeah I mean it was very very painful
learning process
also that was really that that warping
was really unnecessary I just wanted to
do something
[Music]
yeah skirmishes
can I oh
I like it let's go
immunography
speaking of Mr marnell you reminded me
yesterday the day for the next and last
season of Mrs marvelous Mrs maisel
was it now I think it was uh April one
of the shows I'm waiting for is next
season April I think and one is May or
so I don't know ooh nice level up
so marvelous Mrs maisel and what was the
other one what was the other one what
was the other one
ah
the emperor
the great the Great
[Music]
that's why all my life that's one of my
favorite shows ever because it's so high
quality
but the humor is so stupid like oh my
God the amount of curse words they use
in that show that the show begins it's
nothing no I'm nothing compared to what
how much day
curse
yeah
it's so freaking funny though
so funny
have you guys watched it before the
Great
have you seen that show
me first
I can really really really recommend
that one no no please watch it
silly it is so silly it was so good and
you learned some history although I mean
of course A lot of it is like you know
not made up but like
kind of made up
is that the one with the Russian royalty
yeah exaggerated yeah
definitely one of my top
five favorite shows
ever
um
you know what I don't think we should
let him really
I will
um
and I want it
no
but four is okay then I'll I'll let her
dance or he will dance for you that's
high praise it really is
yeah and for marvelous amazing I'm
really excited too because it's so so so
so so so good too and really funny don't
forget your loss but also you know it's
not only funny it has like emotional
sides to it too but
this is the last season and knowing that
makes me sad
[Music]
I love the characters and I love like
the the costumes they wear both in The
Marvelous Mrs Basil and the great
good things about it it's like so good
and I think it's a lot of it
uh the reason why it's so good is
because it was being produced by the
same person who made the Gilmore Girls
it really explains a lot in terms of
like quality they're two different
completely different shows but when you
watch it you will see even though
there's so many many years between this
show and um Gilmore Girls you will see
it like you will understand like oh it
makes sense
there's something about it
and I find really interesting that you
can like see
you can feel
that the same person produced the show
and the writing yeah
the witty writing I think that's it both
killer girls and The Marvelous Mrs
maisel have really witty
dialogues and fast
dialogues that keep you on your toes
then the humor is very similar
it all comes back to kill the kills you
get it you
can
you get it you just get it don't you
should I do that okay just wait four
times I think I'll wait
hey
oh
Gotta Wait for kisara too
[Music]
okay
I haven't even looked at the rest of the
map
there's two up here chilling
[Music]
they also be chilling oh and then
there's doors again and I have to open
up so I still don't see the rest
okay well we take it step by step it's
still a small map for sure
[Music]
thank you
oh I can attack
alrighty
yeah they are married couple yeah yeah
I've noticed because of the last name
you're so genius
yeah she deserves some action doesn't
she
you know what that might be what I'll do
can't let her always lag behind like
that man
thank you
I feel refreshed
how do you remember what I have in the
Convoy yo
front line
strong people to the front there
um where is
[Music]
it uh if Jade walks over to kiwawa she
can just choose to use the Convoy right
that's how it works
does it make sense to do that now
I guess
because she has nothing else to do right
now anyway
where are those booties I don't I don't
think I have them
they would be here wouldn't they
have death of strength
yeah I used them
the ones I had a [\h__\h] meant I had
more
somebody did say to use something else
on her I think that would strength
even though she already has plenty I
would say
[Music]
um
nine minutes
oh well
you guys are so quiet speed is King
I had no speed
hmm
oh well
at least she got a bit closer
[Music]
oh she can just fly over that
and be absolutely unbothered by it
me first foreign
are you saying that he will prove you
wrong
he will prove his strength to you
see I don't need that like
icy stuff I can just walk over all this
stuff
I don't need it right now
oh hey
we just brought her to the front line
don't be so mean wow
who said book I don't might die
oh yeah yeah the the corrupt that are
going to step into the miasma
dismiss yes nice nice
however I need to heal it's nothing
Christmas
does she have a wall I think she does
okay
[Music]
oh there's a charging field over there
hmm
relax
unforgiveness
Maxwell
makes it very difficult to kill them
no
no I'm having no troubles at all
look look at me killing them like flies
to never turn
[Music]
again thank you for coming
you're not killing those emails oh I
mean these ones will be hard to kill
nah
[Music]
nah I'll prove you wrong
thank you
okay maybe not with her
oh someone
or they just follow me they'll just
follow me
Grandma they wanted why not
no it'll be fine
[Music]
yeah whatever
no no no this is no problem
maybe I should stand and what what is
the
hey we got minus
wow wow wow well well well
Ken if he does that now does it hit
those no
only that one tile
only he could make himself dance
What if I
join me for
it
because it's they're still too far
well maybe maybe maybe
well one of them is
one of them is long distance magic user
you know it's all right
the other one will have to step forward
in order to attack someone but if he
goes to kisawa or to Tamara he'll just
um give me asthma again
tomorrow
[Music]
or for Celine
you have to go to model there will be
fine
[Music]
will they freeze if they're selling in
it that's also something I was wondering
just now
[Music]
okay challenge accepted
I wonder if I could do a funny thing
with
oh
I was thinking of engaging doing the
thing
but this actually does plenty damage
[Music]
I'll do the thing
emblem see how that goes I'm very
curious
hey
oh you know you're still here
oh oh is that the one in the miasma
[\h__\h]
[Music]
foreign
and this one just stepped one to the
side okay okay okay
oh
okay okay
and I didn't
even though I had one percent less
chance
thanks dude here we go
look at this look at this look at my
Flex
oh
make the Earth shake
okay that one is still alive but it also
got rid of the miasma
[Music]
all this power I have
I know
I stress I didn't know I could do that
either
ETO
before I move you the choice is yours
I'm gonna move you first it's like
playing
Tetris
oh they're awesome
I want to get you out of the way I'm
just gonna have her uh take care of the
door
wait there's two doors
are we gonna split
I hate how even a door triggers me with
having like one or two HP left
two doors I love the tutors
history
baby
so if I put Dragon Vein from here
only gets rid of that one listen
um
[Laughter]
enemy might be behind the door
yeah probably
but
I might want to open two doors
okay we'll use him for dancing only then
[Music]
who could do
the most damage
[Music]
all kind of
um lame
two doors and
[Music]
ah
that's me
emblem engage let's see what he can do
for one
the awful one
hmm
maybe no kneeling until Christmas
I will however take care of this one for
now
[Music]
totally possible though
all right
it's so far we can't do [\h__\h] right now
because I'm going so far with everyone
else
hmm
automata
oh mending
to stand there scoozy pork bubble
[Music]
yeah
I think I'll get more
three wood if I take a stab at the door
[Music]
I'll just have to
have to
come out of the no way he's a mage he
won't he doesn't give a [\h__\h]
[Music]
and
really annoying miasma that's why they
made the map so small because it's
annoying anyway already plenty
English
plenty annoying already anyway there we
go that's the right order of words
[Music]
look at them being understood
whatever
now
I can't
find Gage let's end this
Storm's eye at upstairs and always
follows up foes cannot follow up
hopefully
wait so he can't attack back
that's
exactly what we would want in that case
because otherwise he would kill me
I see Freud I see through it all
down
[Music]
eh well she's she has Hector
that's why she has the wolf fail
he was still
um
we'll see what happens I thought that
was a smart move
[Music]
haha
I didn't take the deals into account wow
I do think I will eventually use the ice
though because this is annoying
I just need to get him to the front
though
[Music]
a little [\h__\h]
is that worth it
[Music]
we'll designed this map one of my haters
pretty sure
thanks girls
no damage
from the one who's got the noble weapon
really
[Music]
secret rooms no way like really secret
can I are they Hearts too
fine
okay
who we got what who we got left
what are we gonna do with you
[Music]
hmm
me first
sleep now
oh great
yay six Christmas I think this is okay
and that's okay
could be better but also could be worse
why is it why can I just keep on
bringing me back
the enemies
[Music]
okay oh he went out of it yo
I knew that he would
yes
oh this one is kind of cornered so he
had no choice oh [\h__\h] no
oh he only attacks once thank God
okay
uh
[Music]
that should work unless we missed
okay I'm sorry you had to see that
huh
[Music]
smash Plus
finally finally
now I will endure is there someone who
wants to charge okay Waba could charge
I don't know if she's close enough
though
um
door open
[Music]
I'm surprised there's more me as my
there who would have thought and of
course I can't read let's go
what about you you can read thank God
okay
now you my friend
you must make yourself useful
please
I can't believe
I look like her don't I orange hair edgy
makeup cute ball
just like me for real for real
um
what's down there
oh a chest
with two enemies
[Music]
should I try to bring him to the right
side first you know what we'll all wait
until that chest is cleared
right now one of them is standing
on the miasma and one isn't
[Music]
what about here how's it looking here
oh One charging plate
a couple more
okay
[Music]
you're gonna come for me
no I said I will wait so I will wait
[Music]
a minute rough here we need some healing
huh
did you bring some you didn't
[Music]
I already moved everybody else
like Chihuahua
holy please
[Music]
anti-toxic nails too
you know what
oh
I have questions nice
and we got him to move out of the
meat I still don't have to use the
stupid eyes let's go
Unbreakable
[Music]
reinforcements to find one we can't keep
this up time to make our Escape
I'm trying
I'm on my way I'm running
[Music]
you're okay
she's fighting just like in her game
oh
I will hope for that 15 crit come on
come on come on
papaya
[Music]
okay
the other one I know oh but it's okay
looking for my Note but all these
tangents are from before I told those
already
those are all old tangents
villain name it I wrote some on my other
phone I have too many phones
no no there's definitely like still
tangents that I just can't think of
right now because there was just too
much happening at some point I just
stopped writing down Facebook when I
remember I will remember
I will remember
no nothing on here
[Music]
well then you guys have to remind me
yeah I met you a little bit but
nothing happened because we only talked
like for
five to ten minutes maybe
how many has you
free
if you have free phones but one of them
I don't really use and the other one I
also don't really use
ha
when I was too right oh well briefly
two times very briefly
because one time was in the previous
trip
uh
uh it was when I was a lit me Ahmed
and
who
we were going to the arcades right that
arcade day
yeah yeah I was just trying to remember
who sat next to me in the Izakaya we
were going to the arcade
and then
before I met up with Ahmed did I tell
you this
I was I was trying to coordinate it so
that the other group
which was Bill's Iris and fauna
uh would be able to meet Ahmed because
they've never seen I mean I've also
never seen Iris at that point
so no I mean
I guess but Iris wanted to see other
list for a second I guess
oh no it was weird but there were two
groups now let's try to coordinate it
but Ahmed was like only looking at her
phone
every now and then and she was kind of
lost and you know
uh and wasn't replying and so I tried to
um
I went to the station I went back to the
station
but the the Bales Iris fauna group
didn't want to come out of the station
so I had to go in
uh and then I said hi to them I had to
stop you and they told me they were
gonna go to some vegan restaurant
and then
I told them that ama is somewhere
and I I wrote to her but she stopped uh
you know looking at her phone I guess so
now I don't know where exactly she is
and I'm trying to get him here you know
and then they were like oh but we gotta
go we gotta go to the restaurant
I'm like oh you can go to Vegas I'm sure
they have some vegan stuff too
and I'm like no we're going to this
vegan restaurant so yeah in the end they
didn't
uh
uh we didn't like manage to get everyone
together so then the groups separated
again so basically I spoke two words
with Iris
and then the other time was only
when I was already sick they came over
for Mario Party
and when they gave me back the
controllers I opened the door and Iris
bales
no Ina we're standing there am I was
still in her room
and they gave me my controllers and they
said
goodbye
and I said yo Bales sick kicks what a
dose holy [\h__\h] damn girl
didn't even really have a conversation
besides that
so
you can count up the words that I have
exchanged with Iris
uh you could count those on on one hand
I think
I live in the desert
sorry Amazon
sorry
hi and bye pretty much
hmm
what was I doing
what is my goal here is there any is one
enemy left down here
[Music]
I wanna get to that trash god
okay
no so far there's no plans no
uh
like if she wants to meet up I'll make
some time for her
of course even though schedule for the
next
week is packed but if she wants to
[Music]
hmm
I mean I might as well
is he in the miyaz bundle right
[Music]
and I [\h__\h] yeah right enemy will beat me
as well whatever I'm like work I'm
working on the ice okay I'm working on
it
[Music]
yeah she got Lynn maybe I can take a
shot
I could shoot wait I don't even need oh
so [\h__\h] overpowered it's overpowered
like I know they can go through a
distance okay but going for walls
that is kind of broken I feel like they
shouldn't even make that possible
she doesn't ask for that
I mean it was more like a
oh well never seen each other before uh
everybody like I'm it was on a very
short trip that time
it was like I think she was like what
if if there's a chance
it'd be nice to see amen
It's Magic don't question but she
doesn't even see it where she's uh using
her magic towards to
someone said Iris doesn't ask for those
things what did she say that on the
stream or
how do you know that
there's a window okay that's actually
true I see the window
destroyed
thank you
hasn't take the initiative to meet up no
how do you know that I mean like it
seems to be true from my experience
[Music]
I guess so I guess that's true
my goodness how awful
[Music]
is it does
but it's just like
a passive towards everybody or only you
know
does she get on on passive
when she really wants to meet someone
[Music]
it is known oh
foreign
well I don't know
[Music]
I don't know what to say
she doesn't really stop collapse across
anything no no no no humu humu well well
can I open it from here yes okay nice
energy trap
I got a couple of them I should really
like give them to people
ah let's see uh yeah they're all setting
the mask but let's see if that works if
I can do the eyes
let's see
can I
no I can't
well that's really [\h__\h] annoying
isn't it
I couldn't do them all at once anyway
because I couldn't reach that far
Santa Claus engaged the other one I used
before right uh
but who had Korean
oh wait hit what am I doing hey was that
the thing I did before no uh no no no
that I was thinking of the other thing
that I did with the the hammer the April
that you know got rid of the miasma too
emblem engage we can try this one if
this one applies now attack and flood an
area torrential Roar
oh it's straight a straight line
[Music]
oh that would work if I would exchange
spots with uh
forget about it okay
yeah you know what you can take this
spot actually
Korean in action let's go
[Music]
it doesn't do much damage though because
it gets rid of the miasma right
foreign
flooded
yeah it worked
freezes them also
for their comma coming up turn or only
like now so that they can't attack back
what finally oh
nice
I showed
um
use this to my advantage
let me see
Kiana sweep
sweep sweep
sweep sweepstakes with Dreadful Aura
okay I don't know really what that means
nice move
you can put corn on a different unit
after this for a better effect on ice
possibly
he can't kill anybody she she can't kill
anybody lame I hear you
okay you're gonna take care of
this one
foreign
flowers eventually wilt
just a harvest now yep is this does it
have like some effect now avoid minus
30. even for me
um
ah
guys did you realize it's March
did you realize it's March yet
and you know what that actually means
the four fast is like what two less less
than two weeks away
bye
yeah
[Music]
so excited and I just can't hide it
so it's time for you guys to get your
tickets Your Spawn
streaming watch tickets
getting closer and closer
[Music]
I do want to do that if you guys are
still interested I do want to do that
watch along afterwards maybe of
day one
bought it last year you quick
at least not one of those people who buy
their tickets uh one hour before the
concert starts
yes three months along
should we do it members only or should
we do it public
I don't mind doing it public too I guess
you could do it public and then do
something normal for
um
members because I've been doing all
these watch alongs these past three
years but I I guess free member streams
in one week
is
you know even if it's watch alongs I
would say that's pretty
that pretty how to say satisfying for
members and
you're eating well I would say
also can I make myself some more tea
because I actually I really need to
drink tea like 24 7 at the moment if I
want to talk
uh
before Holo I was really not that much
of a tea person Look At Me Now
Look At Me Now
I have to boil water I'm also running
out of water again
good
um
[Music]
delicious
lean levels of tea power yeah
I don't want to be like that
[Music]
the water is cooking what do you usually
drink
I I oh sorry that's the honey
I usually would drink my drink of choice
would be iced tea like sweet iced tea
like nasty or Lipton
cooking or boiling both
and juices I love juices and smoothies I
used to drink a lot of smoothies
nowadays not so much
I guess
Japanese green tea yes I like green tea
and Japanese green tea
oh before the massage they served us
like a Japanese
um
snack sweet thingy with some really
thick green tea that was served not in a
teacup but in a bowl
was really thick really green very green
green tea
couple years ago I once just for the
sake of having done something touristy
I once participated in a tea ceremony
thingy
alone
I booked like a tea ceremony thing at a
at a hotel fancy hotel
quite nice
yeah right in front of my eyes some
relatively old lady that looked really
serious and professional
made tea for me in like a small
Japanese looking room with tatami mats
and all that
it's been years though
[Music]
I think that's one of the typical things
a tourist will do
in Japan oh that's not enough water oh
wow
[Music]
magical
foreign
[Music]
was hoping was a cute lady I mean it was
a cute old lady old ladies can be cute
too
As We Know
running out
running out of teeth
will this even be enough for
the Stream
I I do have some more fluids in my
fridge
liquids
it's not the most desirable ones
[Music]
yeah look at you excuse me
is a very different direction from here
do you I saw the the
[Music]
um
Whatchamacallit as Ina likes to say
every time she says that recently I've
been paying so much attention to it I'm
like oh she said it again
you know when sometimes you hyper focus
on one thing that someone does
[Music]
the the pre-choice pre-selection
for German contestants I saw them
somewhere decent
well actually they were all decent but
all very different directions
and then
when I was with Cali the other day she
said it and I thought she got it from
from Ina
she said no she's always been using it
but no no no now I pay so much attention
to it
okay
I missed the first few hours of the
stream but how are you feeling you sound
like 98 better
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
if you plan on watching the VOD maybe
skip the first 30 minutes
okay they chose a a metal band
the day
what am I doing
sorry is lagging behind again
[Music]
foreign
I'm now curious what happened I was just
not feeling like myself
but as
uh as every once in a while
when I don't feel so good when I start
streaming then you guys make me
eventually forget about it
jugado
relax
[Music]
you had to see that
sweep
[Music]
sweeping
19.
I wanna give her the kill wait was there
Christians
12 7 22.
okay I'll go for the 22 for a chance
come on come on come on first
you're dead oh yes
thanks for not letting me down
I don't think it's what I want you to
stream and you always make me make
everything better really
[Music]
thank you you guys are so sweet
oh this room is pretty much done just
one more enemy
um
thank you
I can't do any damage to him
so
um
I'll just wait
we can't do anything either
well we'll leave it to someone else
foreign
yesterday I had another one of those
moments
where I felt like
so happy to be doing this job
because
I don't know I'm so lucky
but I have so many people who
are there for me and enjoy what I do and
like me for who I am
[Music]
and then I finally got lucky in life
after such a long time where
I was always only struggling
no matter what I did
it's always just a failure
I think some people can maybe relate
with those kind of stuff
him
oh
even though things are tough sometimes
I really appreciate the
opportunity and the chance
and I want to make the most out of it
[Music]
no I'm still I'm sure you're not a
failure or
if you think you're a failure then look
at me how long it took me to get
out of that and I already gave up but
then it still happened so maybe you're
just on the path something big
a yo wait bilaf is participating in that
too
motion
because she was standing there
cool
never give up
foreign
[Music]
why can you move
didn't I just
do you have
what
huh
they made me move again
ah wait I get 12 damage oh well
bye bye now
you have my respect
might give up on staying awake 6 a.m you
should go to sleep
[Music]
please go sweep
you can use it with braiding Stone and
get it
Where'd I did at service this is another
turn what's going on
sheesh
and here we go again one more room
[Music]
oh yeah the exit is here okay and one
more chest okay
let's do this let's get out of here
that's amazing storms ability
okay that's a lot of minutes
gotta get the dancer here
come on over
um
that's an old K-Pop song
okay
and meanwhile we got some time to catch
up here
trickiest manipulate them really
watch and learn
I say but there's not really much to
learn
from me
have a fun stream see ya thank you yeah
why do you know you know
wait Which group was it
which which idle group
[Music]
ah
an arrangement I thought so
it I I didn't really like uh I wouldn't
say I was a big fan
but you know I do know their songs some
of them from some of their old ones
let's see if my astral storm can reach
someone
foreign
[Music]
they cracked the formula they they
cracked it
and they know how to do it what can I
destroy
or the ice cold no no no
you know what they're doing
that um
K-pop produced a Japanese idol group
niji you
they released a new song Yesterday
Paradise
it's kind of a cute calm song but I'm
very happy because my Oshi in a group
gets a lot of good lines because she's
main vocal
like a really main main vocal there's
like two main vocals or so but she's the
main main vocal
for her because during the
um
what they call it again Survival show
she was like
I was so mad with how much jyp
criticized her
because I really think she wasn't that
bad during the Survival show at all
what
do you mean promo getting a new outfit
did she announce something like that
but she didn't reveal that just a
silhouette or what
you didn't know what I saw finana got
one
nanny
update about Twitter
where where is that announcement my
Twitter is full of ninja posts
it's currently full of energy retweeds
all right I gotta go straight to Pomo
Twitter
foreign
wait what the [\h__\h] like the
usually I think
for outfit reveal Graphics like this
the background Vibe kind of matches the
outfit right
now her silhouette doesn't make me think
that so much
but the background makes me figure
something MGS related or like style wise
in that direction right
right
oh my God is she is she going for like
an NGS video mgs fairy
wait when the 10th
that's in six days
[Music]
hey I'm so curious yeah she has a beret
or something like that cute
[Music]
hmm without the background
it wouldn't have given me that
impression but oh wait it's a side
ponytail huh
that will be her third outfit Ryan
oh
my problem oh that means that probably
since banana got one recently
now let's put them so after that and
Lira will be getting one two
let me drink my tea should be drinkable
you do collection get some secret
information
I can do that within Hollow but maybe
not
um for knitting
I wouldn't want to even ask and put her
in that position or she has to say no
sorry no
no no no no no
but I'm so excited for my own new outfit
too but it's gonna take so much time
guys
you guys will love it
I wish I could spoiler you
but you know it's a different artist
this time so I'm really curious to how
it will look
um
on my body
because they're still gonna use the
hookah drawn base model basically
the artist that I chose
draws bodies
quite a bit
um
how to say
longer taller
usually
so hmm
but it shouldn't be an issue shouldn't
get in the way
oh
how do I get the most out of this
probably if I stand here
and then Dragon Wayne downwards Wayne no
it doesn't hit the right one what the
[\h__\h]
hmm
[Music]
I can get the left one on the that one
or
okay maybe that's the best one
[Music]
95 legs man like four days yeah kind of
I mean I do have long legs too but
I'm a bit worried put the outfit itself
that's wrapped over they look so [\h__\h]
so excited
I'm so excited
[Music]
um
I know you'll do best to make sure it's
adapted well well yes
it
oh wait this dude has two lhp bars
I didn't even look at that I guess every
map needs
some kind of like boss
[Music]
hmm quickly
after this time
um well in the past I've already like
showed drafts that were induced so in
theory yes
[Music]
I might do that again like show you
drafts when the outfit gets revealed
well right now I can't yes
should I go here to charge
[Music]
not behind scenes yeah me too I like
seeing that kind of stuff
it's a very interesting Insight I would
say
dude
but it doesn't do anything
hmm
hoping for ponytail koala
oh well I always try to go for
hairstyles that I haven't done yet with
my new outfits
and bye now
especially with the upcoming new
hairstyle
for like last year's anniversary
there's not that much choice left
me first I'm not getting an afro
[Music]
stop I'm stopped
foreign
Simpson hairstyle no no no
it's okay it has to get out
the more leaves my body the merrier
[Music]
let's do this
they got items
[Music]
when you say guys are they Whiteford
they're welcome to continue following me
until we reach
the team squad oh my God what
what
[Music]
dude
boys Griffin I forgot what her hair
looks like I didn't look pretty normal
put chihuahuas in the back so we could
tackle them
together well let's keep on moving
let's keep on moving
[Music]
not many enemies left here
so generally
I think nothing to worry about
[Music]
is an escape map
so you don't think I should um
how many are there just four
[Music]
there's no problemo
I will not forget your loss
[Music]
have to open the chest anyway
I think I'll use her to heal for now
just you missed it by quite a few hours
it was really good we look cute and did
you notice in her thumbnails she didn't
have the cape
but
thankfully she had it in the actual
stream I think it's so cute
I think uh
in the call-in with the Apex Squad
they mentioned it but when she puts her
arms up in the air straight up they
become like one full circle though the
cape becomes one full circle is cute
[Music]
in case
they come down here I do want to prepare
the area
[Music]
foreign
I'm closer it's okay I already moved
them I already moved them
I'm sorry not not leaving you there to
die I think
hmm
oh wait maybe maybe he doesn't have that
bow that can attack
that
things are located not only the physics
of the cape
I love her K physics yes but one thing
I've noticed
booby physics
[Music]
um
they seem very very
special to me
I don't think I've seen this kind of
booby physics on any other whole life
member before
I could be wrong but
[Music]
I don't think Cali or so
have the same kind of booby physics
you know what I mean like when she was
like
like putting her arms
closer to her boobies
the boots would like lie on top they
would like liquidize and be like form
themselves
according to their positioning and
Collide yeah I'm collagen yeah yeah
you did not notice
it happened quite a few times
yeah
yes
why were you not paying attention to
that it was so beautiful to see that
because normally I think like ninity
would really
um
what's the word
appreciate
um
then she would
[Music]
benefit yes benefit from that
because I see her arms often
clipping into her boobies
instead if they would do the thing that
they do with major senpies
boobies
oh that would be that would be pretty
dope
[Music]
ah
damn it who do I go for
all right I'm rematching it
like watch when she for example throws
the ball for the first or the second
time
very specific it just
you know those kind of things I noticed
because you know
it's important to improve the quality of
our 3D stuff you know you know you know
and um yeah
[Music]
I know
that one is a tricky one
[Music]
oh
he's standing in the miasma and I still
can't do this much damage
oh
[Music]
let me help
yeah she's so sweet
now Amanda was in on my stream but also
wasn't she in a stream too
popular
en guest choice huh
right
can't take that one down
hmm
you know what I'll use him to open the
chest
oh wait oh wait
that's not bad 19 damage oh wow
me first
I think it's one of the samples who
um even when we were still very new but
even also now
uh would be one of the first Senpai to
ask all of us for like one-on-one
collabs
[Music]
I feel like she asked all of us oh no oh
no
um
how triggering that must be for them
yes it's very proactive
very friendly and you know she also has
awful hands with
it
[Music]
also there
hmm
I feel like she meets a lot of em
members even IRL
ie Kelly
there you go
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah
she definitely gives off that Bentley
sweet vibe
really appreciated
nice to have a senpai like that
[Music]
and gentle
hello Birds also friendly yeah I agree
but why are you still here didn't you
say it's 6 a.m you give up staying uh
away
are you okay
was that too much
can't say goodbye yet huh
you don't want to leave me they gave up
on giving up
[Music]
he is diesel fighting oh my God
about to wake up with a collab
at least it's weekend
oh it's half plus 8 P.M so after this is
over I really have to stop and read some
super chats unfortunately
[Music]
we don't want to have this
um
backlog for
more than a month or so right
[Music]
because I don't think I have time for
Super Chat reading next three next week
unless I want to sacrifice a normal
stream but I don't really wanna since I
have been
uh losing so many opportunities for
normal fans already
I'll just try my best while streaming
normally
you can consider doing the DLC maps up
soon I considered that before and then
you guys said you want to watch it
uh which I understand too
maybe I'll do one Upstream just one
you can choose which one you don't want
to see
yo I did it
all right okay a little faster
come at me
[Music]
and then we'll leave we just have to
step on with one unit right with one
unit only we have to step on the green
stuff
as far as I know
[Music]
we want to see you reckon to Camilla
okay okay
Camila is long filled with reinforest is
kind of a chore so maybe that one uh
oh
has to be sea though oh oh okay okay
I'll put them in position
or
[Music]
no
does he got exp from this I forgot
what did they kick in kicking
oh
I don't think he gets anything right
bonding
we need to be together all the time but
stream will be safe haven spots to be
having fun together
[Music]
okay
I'll have you be healed
don't worry I know you're dying
and sipping your last breaths of air
thank you
hey
on the 8th the new DLC comes out
I already have my hands full with this
one
the minimum standard of royalty
of course like the little coward rats
they choose to stand by the miasma
you little shits
I swear to God
Howards
[Music]
no you must come to me if you want to
fight
you must come to me
yeah that's how it is
that's how it will be
foreign
[Music]
wait what was that
press plus two you know what I'll use it
to get that out of my freaking inventory
hmm
around him because he had it
basically for the people who don't have
much rest then it would be nice to have
more rest right and for the ones who
have plenty rest for them it was also
nice to give them more so it doesn't
matter in the end that's how I feel now
for the ones who already have much rest
that means that they generally need it
I'll pull back for now but next time
different
[Music]
revenge is coming
of course I thought it was gonna be easy
are they like extra strong
oh
yeah and that's why you don't Frontline
with your majors
but I want to
here's a good example
a front lining with my mage
[Music]
I'm not supposed to fight them
but I want to again
look how easy it is
ah it's fine it's fine
[Music]
so what's this about what this new ring
and me using wind Magic
is it worth it
[Music]
or not
it's already been such a long
stream today
long long long battles
why not make it even longer hmm
hmm
[Music]
thank you
you guys tell me what time it is at your
places
tell me tell me tell me tell me
what time it is
why are you suffering 5 p.m 10 AM 5 30
A.M
48 A.M
2 30 pm
[Music]
yeah I'll see a lot of you people must
have just woken up or you made it
through the whole night
thank you guys
remember when you said well I couldn't
start earlier today because you know the
Showcase yesterday too I would have
started earlier if it wasn't for the
showcases
but then I would have had to like you
know stop early
and Bloom engage
[Music]
really
with two engaged attacks I still cannot
kill this dude
[Music]
this makeup is starting to look like
clown makeup to me
because I feel like a clown right now
[Music]
that's what I was hoping for okay
Dream well
should have used win really
I want to see the effect of that
[Music]
okay come at me bro
oh
ouch [\h__\h]
don't kill her don't kill ivy
oh I couldn't what the ax the Xbox
I have to withdraw they are stronger
right than the others that were on this
map
thank you
okay I want to see this window tag what
should I use it on
huh
but hmm
no no no no no no
[Music]
they're
you mean they're not they're not meant
to be fat well well well
I do not follow those rules
to the death I do what I want
Unforgettable
me
everything must be cleaned up
just in case I'm gonna bring some
reinforcements
fine by me
I'm on casual so I don't care okay free
leaves replace clean yay
oh
who said they aren't supposed to be fat
make your own rules
engage Jade so she made the love no it's
okay it's okay we'll we'll deal with
this
I'll be fine
[Music]
all right throws it here
that's pretty close
22. whatever
I took the world and I threw him on the
ground
oh [\h__\h]
so close
hmm I do breaking though
I will not forget your loss
oh wait we got a crib
Celine might be loving yeah
we did it whoa
what were those um exclamation marks on
some of them for
[Music]
cleared it
our paths diverge for a moment
emblem well sometimes I want to shoot
them
but then I'm more aware of what actually
happened
I've been late in the MVP
higher Christian's weapons
oh
they signify the dangerous due to having
special weapons to collect equipped
foreign
don't tell me more of the corrupted
is everyone okay oh I saw those monsters
coming in and got worried Veil oh my we
meet again oh now I think she's the evil
one but she's actually currently in nice
mode yes light mode versus dark every
last one I'm glad how have you been I'm
surprised to see you out in that
blizzard I hope you found the cathedral
whatever game you're playing stop it huh
are you mad about something don't act
like you forgot don't you understand she
has different eyes now lies
what do you mean I
know
Step Closer
[Music]
why is it you're so mean to me now
thanks for the membership how did you
know
father
you took my country from me
my father
what more do you want
people you killed
they had families but you don't care do
you
all that pain
you don't even give it a second
moment I
I held people
who drop the actor
you know what you did
dare you show your face
you murdered my mother and stole the
raids
believe me
leave me believe you
like I believed we were friends
I won't make that mistake again
[Music]
we've got to do something
Let Her Go
it's probably a trap ah you're right
Divine One are you all right I'm fine
but the next time I see fail I swear
what what
hmm
somehow I don't know I couldn't take
this very seriously this scene just now
I understand what's happening but I just
hmm
I know
yeah
um
it needs no no
it needs more punch to it
it's not as engaging as it should be
ironically
dialogue
I liked it when she turned evil though
that was good but her switching back now
and being like
that the way that scene was made
with that bgm
all right doggo you're coming with me to
the sky
don't worry you will not die here okay
insomnia just because you're in heaven
doesn't mean that you you died
[Music]
oh
oh now she switches back
it's still Rings why would I do that I
don't understand
lady Vale
I finally caught up with you oh
you know who
you're a hard girl to find why'd you
disappear had me all freaked out Papa
told you to drag me back home right
told me to huh oh I see what's going on
here
you're the other one the other one I'm
going back what do you mean no matter
what you say
papa will just make me do something cool
and he awoke
I thought we could finally spend time
together
but no always telling me to kill the
Divine dragon or attack so-and-so's
Castle oh well I don't want to what so
she's been told even in life mode
remember is that she's been told but she
doesn't remember the things that she did
those things she did when she was in
dark mode
even the Divine Dragon was angry with me
and I thought we were friends the Divine
Dragon said you were friends
wait you met the Divine Dragon I really
like his design wait he's got no nipples
look whatever those people told me
ruined it for me it's not true they were
imagining things
think so of course how could you have
done something bad and then forgotten it
right
I couldn't have you only accept that
before maybe there wouldn't be this
awful misunderstanding you want to try
and speak with him again
straight I do
but
weren't you going to bring me back if
this is what you want I'll help out
nothing if not loyal that's me all right
thank you Chris
seems I misjudged you it's settled then
why there cause that's where the Divine
dragon is going
how do you know that
come on we're on a schedule here gotta
head for the port and set sail
you want to patch things up or don't you
I do you're right no time to waste
this ought to be real interesting
[Music]
again very very very soon
um but I don't think I can squeeze in
Fire Emblem next week to be honest
only shorter streams there's a lot of
like recording stuff and rehearsing
stuff going on next week
rehearsing because right before
Fest
so
yeah have some
full days
very full days during the day
and also me and Callie are trying to get
the girls all five of us to do some
stuff together because we don't have
much time left together and trying to
squeeze some things in also because Cali
we'll be traveling
um
again soon so that kind of like gets rid
of a lot of opportunities where it could
be all five of us
yeah so we're trying to make some more
memories next week
um
[Music]
tomorrow too after the collab stream I
think we're gonna like spend the rest of
the day together that's good that's a
good thing about the stream being so
early for us early in the day
I think we're gonna try to enjoy the
rest of the day together
how much longer are you gonna be in
Japan I can't say
safety reasons but you will see when I'm
when I'm back um I'll be back
[Music]
oh yeah
that's more important
um
yes but you know I I know that you guys
also want to see some of this kind of
stuff on stream you know that's five
together
so that's why I'm planning the Tuesday
of collabo
yeah that is most likely going to be the
last one the last full five member of
collab for
a long long long long long long long
long long long long long long long long
long long time
[Music]
really really long long long long long
long time
yeah
yeah so look forward to that
and we're gonna read some super chats
I saved right
after that conversation shows now I'll
save again hey
[Music]
okay where where should we go
here
oh shh
the kfb workers just busy in the kitchen
wondering why does my boss look like
that I've been busy
in my shift I couldn't watch the stream
that she was doing
now she comes back here I have no idea
why she looks like this
and don't mind me
I hope I'm not occupying
on the space too much
trying to change the size
oh
that's also not quite it
how about that
hmm
I don't think they have the time to
wonder yeah yeah he's gotta flip the
burgers
okay okay okay okay so last time I think
I know where we stopped I think there
were like three more streams before the
Showcase
that I needed to read
possibly
um and we need some BTM
I'll see
you worked hard for seven hours
there was something I wanted to ask you
oh yeah is your cat really called uh
come on is it like in Korean either one
or is it or is it in
uh
in English
tell me tell me tell me tell me
don't smile at me like that tell me
tell me
what does that mean
I need explanation
tell me
I cannot sleep unless you tell me
ban him no
I haven't watched the stream for a month
but I watched it diligently today
you bought it
thank you but
uh
starting a question does he understand
is your cat really called
come on
wait did you hear that
awesome
[Music]
and where he smiles again
that's not an answer
thank you
foreign
yeah but
laughs
[Music]
I said that is a stupid name to give to
your cat
eh
goes soon
[Music]
foreign
no that's not okay
[Music]
a poor cat
well now I demand a picture of your cat
s yo
[Music]
photo please oh
picture
I will only forgive if you trade me a
picture of your cat
on Twitter reply please
don't worry the cat doesn't know Korean
or any language
how do you know huh maybe it understands
it just can't reply properly
and it's suffering because all you do is
call it by come on here come on come on
well if you want your cat to come on to
come to you
how do you say
come on come on
it will get confused it will not
understand what you want from it we'll
just think you said it's name twice
hmm
yeah maybe you should have tried and say
Stout and Bud and have embarked instead
anyway we're gonna read superchat from
the Vata Mako lab I think
oopsie
tell me tell me
[Music]
you know my Korean Clippers they make
Clips out of pretty much every occasion
when I speak some Korean
so assuming this will get uh clipped
why does the chat look like that
the viewers will be questioning why
why do I look like this today
what does this mean
why does she have this weird edgy makeup
on why is she wearing all that all those
Rings just to flex or bling bling
um
hmm
I'm not gonna get the Ellen ring nope
um I wait I need a big Jam I didn't put
in any bgmate
what should we use
tell me tell me
this one
oh it's nice this one's nice make it
louder
so you hear this
oh wait no you don't
boom boom how about
that's weird
I really low
there it is
how about now is it okay now
there we go okay
Mas
working and having fun meeting wonderful
people and making coffee hella proud
thank you I'm glad you think so
I had to do this potato chips collab
because I promised
hmm now that one's off the list yeah
thank you thank you soon for the rest of
the chat enjoy the snacks YouTube thank
you they were so good I mean there were
some unusual ones
well a fun collab idea snack Exchange
I should find another snack box
subscription service because I really I
want to do those again
when I'm back in Austria
but I have yet to find one
that's that ships to Austria and has
like a different box every month maybe I
maybe I need to crawl back to that snack
box service like I crawled back to the
taxi in Indonesia
not looking forward to it
thank you for the recipe
thank you
thank you for the pinky kiwi
what is that supposed to mean Kiara
the kiwi I'm a kiwi now
I like I like kiwis
kiwi takanashi kiwiwi
kiwiwi
yes
why
yeah I would feel like there's more than
just that but maybe in Europe there's
not so many choices New Zealand
hmm
did you ever cancel no because I didn't
feel the need to because I
no use it
it's hard to post pictures because I
don't use Twitter oh I registered a cat
picture but I don't know if it was
registered normally registered where
like on as your profile picture on
YouTube because it still looks the the
usual
I mean you could change it to your uh
you could change your profile
profile picture on YouTube
unless if you post it on Twitter let me
check my replies now
[Music]
boom
boom boom boom I don't think I see
anything
[Music]
oh wait I see
how cute
she's cute
oh she looks so small is she a baby cat
she's so cute
thank you
for showing me she's cute
come on come on
she looks so sweet
wow
wow wow I hope she grows big and strong
and healthy
you're welcome to always show me more of
those pictures whenever you have some
just randomly at Chihuahua
show me anytime
I'm waiting
foreign
RBC thank you for two red Super Chat
it's been a year since I was blessed
with your positive energy during a year
my life has changed much better for
example I've determined to love myself
and been studying languages to enhance
my value it's all that thanks to you
today February 21st is my birthday and
by Your Enthusiasm I've already been
congratulated May the blessing be with
you alive forever this is a Korean bro
your English is so good
RBC
you're probably not here now
but I hope you get to catch the archive
to here
when I want to say
um
thank you
thank you RBC
my dear chicken
[Music]
wow
beautiful Reverb
20 February 21st okay that's already a
while ago I'm really late I'm so sorry
um I hope this will reach you
and it says it's been a year since you
were blessed with my positive energy I
wonder if that means you haven't watched
my stream in a year or you just haven't
sent a super chat in a year
but I hope you get to catch my streams
more often than once a year hopefully
but thank you for coming bye and
updating me on your status I hope
everything is going well and you're
welcome to show up in the chat more
often I'm always waiting for you okay
[Music]
Super Snake Mario thank you for the
Pinky
and a yellow one hi Kya looking forward
to see what fun we have today with
vatime I'm also here on a mission to
finish what I started in your last
stream I started the rainbow last time I
couldn't finish before the streamlined I
was wondering if you're gonna do that so
I'd like to finish that today when I see
a sweet smile or hear your cute voice I
feel all warm inside as though I had a
fever night or day I'll always support
you I love all that you do keep it up
you do you girl thank you
I want to tell you that I always liked
you ever since your debut because of
your orange cream my favorite color oh
and you being a phoenix which I love but
the thing that won me over was your big
heart
oh thank you yeah orange your favorite
color there's not many people who have
orange as their favorite color but I
would say that it's very cultured
very very positively cultured
thank you so much now your Super Chat
has been finished from before and we
don't have to live with this Cliffhanger
anymore Hallelujah
um
thank you you saved us all from falling
off the cliff because you cannot
hold on to the Cliffhanger for too long
eventually someone
will step on your fingers that are
holding onto the cliff and you will fall
down
and you will die
thank you I was so close to that
I was so close to falling
I've been saved
Yuki Kansas
[Music]
um
I'll leave this one behind
hmm
[Music]
that was fast right
oh
next is this one with the absolute
marvelous
thumbnail
I love that thumbnail me too me too
it was perfect the fan art came just in
time
speed running I'll try
and thank you
Tracy I think I should thank you
Captain meow dungeon for the pinky fund
for sokiara to afford YouTube premium
oh yeah right
uh
um
yeah on it on which account
because I I was logged into my account
in order to stream to
YouTube
why did I not have YouTube premium in
that situation I definitely don't have
it on my personal account yeah
yeah sometimes when I'm really annoyed
fed up with the ads I just switched to
my other phone because on my other phone
on my old phone I'm logged in on the
phone
uh onto the Chihuahua YouTube account
but on my new phone I'm not
cause I don't know
uh sometimes oh no it's nice to have a
different account that gets different
kind of recommendations and so on I
guess
and then I'm subbed to some other people
on that
not really many people but
y'all
and some ads I mean that's okay I can
handle
um
but then my own phone doesn't have
Netflix on so mostly I watch Netflix on
my new phone and if I want to watch
YouTube more often I watch it on the old
phone but when I'm home I watch YouTube
on my TV anyway
where I'm also however not locked into
my chihuahua account
so when I want to watch YouTube on my
big TV what I do is I take out my old
phone and I use that feature where you
can
you know show what you're watching on
your phone on the TV
it's getting complicated yeah
because I'm too lazy to log into my
kiwama account on the big TV and the
other day when my brother was staying
over at my place you know he logged into
his premium account on my iPad and then
I was watching with that for a while
and then he was like
you're still logged into my account and
I'm getting all kinds of weird
recommendations because of that
and I'm like hey sorry it was an
accident even though it really was not
an accident
and then I logged out I got kicked out
no it wasn't me too with recommendations
I think it was um like you know those
videos those uh real crime true crime
videos at that time I was like
constantly watching that
[Laughter]
no not a crime no no no I did nothing
wrong it was an accident but he should
have walked out of his account when he
left
ah
Derek twin
Dell C1 Danke Schoen but
I can't believe we got to see what the
upcoming 3D showcase and forefs are like
this is a great stream
yeah
it was hard to live up to the
expectations after the sock puppet
stream
with our actual showcases and I feel
like we didn't quite do it justice
because the sock puppets were just so
marvelous hmm
oh well can't always be perfect right
Maxwell the first time
thank you for the rest of it up the
stream so funny thank you
[Music]
it was a bit difficult because
we were not really in sync Cali was
always doing different movements than me
so in some way doing a sock puppet
stream was not uh with someone else was
not as easy as I thought it would be
but it was funny yeah yeah I went to the
wind of the Bales that was funny
[Music]
uh she really wanted to drag her away
so cute
but we also had fun like
um usually when I did the sock puppet
streams on my own I would just stay
quiet but also because I was trying to
save my throat
from
that evaporating
um
but with her
we had fun using our voice too
um
singing along a little bit
and chanting
hmm
thank you Father
glad you enjoyed it
Skye Duncan Shadow pencil Duncan
foreign I hope my sock puppets will
um be showcased properly
at the
Expo I have yet to give it to them I
wanted to fix them a little bit but
I left some hot glue at janma's place
and now she can't find it anymore
and I don't want to buy another like
soccer another hot glue gun
uh so I'm just gonna try to make it work
they don't have to be moved after all
they just have to be showcased on in
like a case or whatever
so
it'll probably be fine just depends on
how how they handle them I hope they
handle them nicely
my babies
yeah one which one was it one got really
badly damaged
like the head is completely detached
from the mouth
but when I tried to put her back in
place I think it was the the Cali one
yeah
uh when I tried to put her back in place
for a photo
yeah the one I uploaded afterwards
it definitely works as long as you don't
move her around anymore after that
so we'll see we'll see
um
that's that was that
[Music]
late Christmas Carol got some super
chats again as well
nail
[Music]
foreign
shouldn't it be like here yes
okay
gonna read those two
um
[Music]
yeah that image is really pretty I felt
so bad about having to cover up a part
of the image with that logo thingy that
I did which I have to say I did a good
job at I wanted to make it look like a
logo
um
yeah because what's behind that part
looks really good too felt bad for
covering up
a Holly Jolly kickory Christmas again
hey
okay
[Music]
thanks for the pinky take care and rest
well kiwawa I hope you feel will feel
better very soon we love you thank you
love you guys too
thank you thank you
oh yeah that's when I was sick
um
so [\h__\h] unlucky man I hope that the
rest of this year I will stay
healthy
how do you stay healthy just I guess I
guess I just should stop going outside
I used to have a really good immune
system I used to never get sick
really changed recently
yeah I hope I used it up
all those
become sick
Jokers
like for my previous job before Hollow
or for school
I would actually always be hoping to get
sick
I would be happy when I got sick kind of
Happy
as long as it wasn't too bad
and then I never would get sick I never
got sick
and now when I don't want to be sick and
I want to always be there for work
that's when I got sick
and the past the previous one with the
bronchitis laryngitis and sinus
infection was
one of the sickest I've ever been in my
whole life
top top two
sicknesses I've had in my life
hmm
it was pretty [\h__\h] bad
and it dragged out so long to
yeah I'm glad that's over
and this one's almost over to pretty
much over
I wonder how Cali's doing
because when I
got sick it started with my throat
itching
I want to ask her
are you feeling any signs of sickness
by the way
just checking up is she okay
she did write that she's not streaming
today right
hmm
hope she good
that's incredible because even though I
was
um
I was determined to
stay away from her and
not give my germs a chance to jump over
to her I think there were probably
plenty of
chances for them to jump over in the end
if she still dodged it
then that's pretty
impressive
[Music]
foreign
oh yeah the sock puppet stream
no not that one I mean the
the
Rubik's Cube stream we were more or less
relatively close to one another but also
during the whole Spa experience
we were talking so much
um
and had to especially in the pool area
had to speak pretty loudly because we
were having our 50s in the bubbling uh
hot warm water the jacuzzi area
and it was pretty loud the water was so
loud
so kind of had to almost scream
and we talked so much passionately about
all kinds of like
things
hmm
so I wouldn't be surprised if she got it
from me
Albedo again here oh
[Music]
okay
yes okay
a ceiling fan I'm sorry boss I don't
think I can come to the stream or the
next my dog just passed away after
getting hit by a motorcycle what the
[\h__\h] so I'll be taking some legal
actions
yeah [\h__\h] yes you have to I'll be there
for the 3D though oh my God
that's terrible
that's absolutely terrible
I mean what that is like the really
worst outcome
[Music]
um
I wonder how old your dog was I hope he
got to live a long long happy life with
you until that point
it would be really sad if he just lost
his life way too early
um
so I'm assuming you're not here
but
you know I wish you the best
that's so [\h__\h] sad
take your time if you want to
you know
pay respect to your dogu
and get revenge
for that [\h__\h] on the motorcycle
[Music]
I'm going to hug my dog now yes hug your
moon dog
[Music]
um
Revenge
that's not fair
it's not fair it's just not fair
uh profile is that a rainbow that I see
you did it kiwawa you buried me for 20
years thank you two years of laughter
and Unforgettable wonderful moments with
you that I'll always treasure in these
two years not only did I learn a lot but
I also had the best time ever and I
can't tell you often enough how much I
appreciate your hard work how you
interact with the community and how you
stalk us of course you introduced me to
the vegetable world you were the first
one I watched and I actually followed
and sticked to you caught me at me
caught my attention so fast after
watching my first stream the unarchived
karaoke of Cali that was your first one
Leaving on a Jet Plane cry kfb it was so
relatable that I got more interested
that was your first one
then the whole like sadness of like
leaving each other for a long time
could not possibly have really gotten
through to you at that point
interesting
damn
but you still get it now that leaving on
the Jet Plane meme
that's true sometimes I watch like
I don't know something
like YouTube videos from people I don't
know I've never watched before
and suddenly jump into whatever story
they have to tell
yeah even when you don't know people
some things can still like immediately
catch you
and you immediately feel
emotionally moved by it yeah
yeah just seeing two people being really
sad about something even if you're not
involved in that at all you can quickly
feel with them yeah yeah that's true
I'll take it back for real fro actually
I can remember many such cases where
that
happened
um
but it's still a funny stream to join
kfp at
uh Mario can't stream after that and you
cursing in German that's when I decided
to become a member but I already told
that even if it wasn't if I wasn't here
from your debut stream I watched all the
vods
and we could all see how much you've
grown
and how you got to reach your goals I'm
so happy and proud that I had the chance
to experience that
together with kfb nice one second
let me take fruit candy
every day with you is special because
you make them exciting I love to watch
you play because of the laughter I
always end up with stomach pain love to
listen to your tangents and because you
make them fun and interesting at the
same time Love You karaoke
because your singing always impresses me
and love your songs because they're
always a banger
thank you again for giving me the chance
to support you for two amazing years and
I hope you can bear me for many more to
come love you my Kami Oshi
two years two years two years
wow that's such a long time if you think
about it it's a miracle you didn't get
sick of me yet especially now that you
have someone else who you also really
like as opposed to for a long time where
it was just me
um but that's okay thank you I didn't
really want to bring it up but it just
kind of I just I have all the flow the
flow of the sentence just kind of went
there
I'm so sorry I didn't I didn't want to
go there I didn't really want to go
there
I can't help it
some I guess a part of me is just really
jealous
I was scared I think what really is
happening is I'm worried that you leave
me
[Music]
don't leave me
don't leave me Kotori emote threatening
your mood
don't don't leave me
especially not on a Jet Plane
foreign
don't leave pressure pressure that's
that's
thank you guys
usual room treatment
that makes me think I have a good
um picture
to share with you guys
I took this during a rehearsal
very proud
[Laughter]
yeah I'll upload it on Twitter after
this
anyway thank you so much bro for
supporting me yourself for such a long
time you know even at places like tokomi
and so on
it was really great to have you there
and I hope that there will be more
chances like that for us
um
you are a wonderful chicken
so supportive so sweet so kind
yeah nothing I could ask more of from
you
so thank you so so so so much
for everything
[Music]
until the third year let's go
hope I can continue to make you laugh
and happy and Entertain You and make
this a place for you where you feel
comfortable
nail to the queen of cats sure
[Music]
and talk attack
I'm so glad to have Christmas with my
own see yes isn't it great
cause some actual Christmas you may have
had other things to do but this one
definitely not
we also get a present soon from Kiana
and Santa Yago
we miss Kiara on the day due to free
plagues
oh yeah those three plays yes but those
could not stop the Phoenix even a hot
wings can attack you forever glory to
kill me
as heck
oh what was the gift though from
Santiago
what were you hinting to
um
maybe the freaky showcase
I don't know
maybe you didn't mean anything in
particular but oh well thank you so much
to YouTube
thank you for being here again and
celebrating Christmas with me
[Music]
soon
oh
[Music]
foreign
so oh that leaves us with the 3D
showcase we can get started a little bit
we can dig into oh Kelly is saying not
at all let's let's
go
nice
she's not sick at all
let's hope it stays that way
um
that's why
takamori is just meant to be
I can't even get her sick
she's immune
against that
other people may not be immune
she is though perfect match perfect
match
hmm
yeah recently I think you guys noticed
I feel like what's been
getting
all along so well
that's really nice
I appreciate her she appreciates me
that's how it should be all is good all
is well
um
everyone has a crush on you what did you
do
I wouldn't say everybody
I won't say so
[Music]
well
I don't know I didn't do anything in
particular
I think
but it's good
it's I I would gladly have it continued
to be that way
I've not heard a single non-positive
thing well of course not
even if they were thinking something
non-positive
of course they wouldn't say it
[Music]
we're drowning in pretty ladies this
trip
hmm
but all I care about is these pretty
chickens
[Music]
all right
do I have the thumbnail downloaded
perhaps by any chance yes
[Music]
um
all right uh
how many super chips are these in
numbers
how many are these
hmm that doesn't sound like that much
uh but I guess it also has a lot of Reds
and pinks again
oh yeah I see I see a lot of red colors
oh
they oh holy [\h__\h] yeah that's a lot yep
yep yep yep yep
85 braids
[Music]
but
thank you guys so [\h__\h] much like you
guys are so freaking crazy supportive
ah
I I don't know like man I
I don't understand why
but kfp [\h__\h] strong
um
it's insane
thank you really makes the hard work
worth it thank you thank you thank you
thank you
um
I will share it with YouTube
and my company
and my country but the rest I will
happily accept
and
invest into the future of
takanashikiwawa
thank you for
making everything possible for me
yay
as an Austrian I say thank you to krp
for all them tax money weekend
you're welcome
it doesn't hurt at all it doesn't hurt
at all
finding the Austin roads in school let's
go
yeah that's a good thing good thing
keep Austrian as the Austrian Austria is
the beautiful country it currently is
which never really helped me when I had
no money where I went to
the whatever place I was like I have no
money I can literally not survive give
me something some support please and
they were like no
and I was like okay I guess I'll try to
survive otherwise
how'd their name right right
guess I'll die
[Laughter]
really makes you wonder where does it go
then back it up too real too real okay
okay
all right all right
so we are gonna tackle these super chats
now
it will take a long time
check it monkey thank you for the pinky
I hope your throat is doing better Kiara
and congrats on finally getting you a 3D
showcase I can already feel it in my
chicken bones that this is gonna be
amazing with all the work you've put
into it feel the hype kfp and cheer on
our amazing girl thank you
I hope that your expectations were met
for me personally
um if I wasn't sick it would have been
even better but I even think that the
sickness didn't get in the way that much
my chicken bones were correct nice yeah
I'm very satisfied it's what I wanted it
to be
um the tracking could have been a little
bit more better but besides then I'm
very happy with it
um
I'm happy I got to Showcase kfp properly
with the props and a cute fun game
and then have still a lot of singing
uh but also friends over
was able to perform my all my English
songs
I purposefully chose the English songs
only this time because I thought well
English
might as well throw in all my English
songs
yeah Kiana snail 2.0
[Laughter]
I felt like I had trouble keeping up
with Sparks I also to be honest I also
really had trouble keeping up for Sparks
been a while
it's been a long time and uh in
rehearsal I was making a million
mistakes and I was just not happy with
it
um
yeah I had to relearn it man
people nights 2 a little bit
um but mostly it was still in my blood
and do you overall
definitely also a huge struggle
[Laughter]
next week
[Applause]
as well the tires can hold for long
black children by Mia
recently I've been listening to do you a
lot thank you very much
oh yeah you know what one thing this
Super Chat money will go towards too I
really think I will buy that
um that VR thingy the VR goggles that I
found
you know I was talking with Amy about
uh if only if only we are
um you know
the Dancing movie are
in theory isn't so bad if only the
goggles were not so heavy and big
and then I wrote I wonder what the
smallest BR goggles are and I looked it
up immediately and I found those
tiny ones
hmm they're not available yet but
they're available for pre-order and
austrians would get it within the year
it seems like an A and A is first Europe
is like second
Japan is last
they're releasing them in waves for
continents
but those really seem
really really good for if I want to use
more VR
and like I've watched a review
of an early
model of it
somebody who got sent to goggles early
and was able to test it out and he said
that
he was wearing them for two hours and
not a single time did he feel like he
had to readjust him
they're always
on point and he said there they don't
feel uncomfortable at all
they're super light they're just really
really comfortable
and the fact that you don't feel like
having to re-adjust them is a big
difference for me I think because with
the big ones
I I've constantly felt like they didn't
they were not quite a position and that
kind of gives me a headache because I
I see it
that the view is kind of messed up I
don't know how to explain it but they're
just not sitting correctly and I keep on
adjusting them and Blue by Blue it sucks
the one thing that would be better is if
they were Wireless
so maybe I'll look at an option if
there's some relatively small ones that
are Wireless
because there are Wireless ones right
or if there's some kind of solution
where I can put a head tracker on my
head
uh without the need of wearing the
goggles
HTC XR Elite is Wireless
HTC XR Elite
uh they also look pretty small
oh hey it's Vive don't I have Vive I do
have Vive don't I
convertible all-in-one XR headset
I'll also found oh they are at the same
price range thousand bucks
wait are they available now
pre-order
both of them are pre-ordered
wait they come with wait no they come
with some controllers that look like the
ones that the other girls have
A vibe right not a valve the other girls
have a valve I have a Vibe right
I keep on like mixing it up but
they have the one that you order over
Steam
I have the one that's not ordered
through Steam no okay wait never mind
maybe I have the valve
I don't know I have a boyfriend okay I
couldn't get that one that's why I got
the Vive
but the Vive controllers are very
different from the valve ones that's one
thing I've struggled with is that the
hands because the only way I can do
different hands
and we are streams is when I change them
with some buttons and but there's no way
for me to remember
where to push to get like peace or
pointy finger and so on but this one
from live XR Elite when I look it up
they look the controllers look like the
ones you know that valve has I think in
in terms of like how
it will
find out what hands you you currently
are showing because there's like a
circle around so I'm guessing it works
similarly Maybe
Maybe
no wait maybe not
hmm oh well forget the fingers I don't
care about the fingers
yeah those really don't look that bulky
either but I guess those are not
um
[Music]
those are not
custom made
so who knows how well they will actually
fit
hmm
yes I'm still streaming welcome look for
some hat-tracking device without VR
goggle sets from affect your dancing
streams
hmm
well I don't know
the lab controls are called knuckles
it can be used for any PlayStation one
maybe I should just get the valve
controllers
uh
and
the other
the not wireless headset
I think about it I'll think about it
both of them are still pre-ordered so I
can still think about it
um okay your boy Stephen Adams thank you
for the rainbow
here's my first rainbow super to you I
just want to say congrats on your 3D
showcase and I'll be looking forward for
other hello myth members for the
Showcase
and I will always support you all thank
you
I'm proud to be your kfb employee love
forever thank you
your boy Stephen Adams
thank you do you happen to know a
Wednesday Adams if yes can you give me
her phone number
or are you not related to her hmm
thank you so much for the support first
rainbow looking beautiful I appreciate
it thank you thank you thank you I hope
you enjoyed the 3D showcase that I
worked so freaking hard on thank you
[Music]
mama
okay Wednesday cute
[Music]
ah damn dance dance with my hands hands
hands
[Music]
okay
soon
skyduction for the Rainbow Oh another
rainbow man must have been really good
weather
finally you're pretty I knew my gorgeous
talented amazing tent stop we'll Rock
the stage you may heard this so many
times already but still would like to
say I'm glad you are my osiko Kiana
thank you oh
thank you thank you thank you I hope you
liked it Skye
thank you for the sweet words and the
big big support I really really really
thank you from the bottom of my heart
Skye thank you
hope you've been doing well
I will try my best to push
so that I get uh the chance to do
another 3D stream for my birthday
I'm gonna push push push I already like
uh
three weeks ago or so
because I still didn't have a clear
answer even though I already requested
I didn't have a clear answer if I could
do it they said maybe but in order to
maybe give myself higher chances
I
I like immediately jumped onto my PC to
make um
a PowerPoint presentation
I made a PowerPoint presentation
with a clear outline
of want setlist which songs so I chose
the songs already I chose the guests I
want to have already I chose the outfits
and possible locations everything
already
and the order all of it
and
yeah he
so that maybe they would
see that oh oh she's already a step
ahead of us I guess okay this we can't
turn her down if she did all of this
and then even though I don't know who
would produce my birthday concert if it
were to happen
um
to the one who produced my birthday and
my Freddy showcase I was like
um um so maybe uh you know I I really
want to do a birthday or concerts oh if
you if you happen to you know or end up
producing it yeah yeah it would be great
if you could
[Laughter]
inside
yeah let's hope let's hope for the best
I really want to
because I've barely gotten chances so
far you know
this was the first time I did something
properly
with the
production
with the cover production
in their Studio
this was the first time and I've been in
Hawaii for two and a half years
there needs to be more to make up for
all the years where I couldn't do it
hmm
power
[Music]
guess example
foreign
that's honestly fine to me
if they delay it I guess I mean better
than nothing
but I asked early enough and I'm open to
Flying to Japan for it so
um
So yeah
thank you
freaky glasses imagine imagine our 3D
streams oh baby that's like next level
imagine you need to wear 3D glasses for
our 3D showcases
or maybe in the future for
um fifth Fest or so
maybe they can stream a version
maybe a normal version and and a version
that you can watch for enhanced
experience with 3D glasses wouldn't that
be so cool
that would be actually like why hasn't
that been done before I wonder if that's
possible
that's too difficult but that would be
so cool that that would be a thing I
don't think anyone has done before yet
they did that yeah
when
polar I've did that with Cali
was there a normal version of it too
could you like choose
it's pretty easy
was a test run oh so they're looking
into it
um
raining
uh five fifth Festival
um
it was almost impossible to get in even
agent had big problems with it oh yeah
right because they did it in in the
whole earth right
did they do it for Cinderella switch
no no that's like you put on a VR goggle
or so right you put on VR
and you're like part of it inside right
I want to do that too I want to partake
in Cinderella switch
I do want to do that that would be so
much fun
please
my if I had to choose someone in whole
life English
to do it with me
it would be Cali
I want her to cheer me on and I want me
to cheer her on
please
let me write it now I want to ask if
that's possible or if that's too if that
could be considered
I want to ask
if Paulo Ian has ever been considered
before for
Cinderella switch
I would love to do it with
okay
I just want to know just wondering just
wondering
I mean we both have a lot of songs
plenty to do uh
Cinderella switch I think
foreign
we both have the most
original songs in myth so
and possibly in all of whole life
English no except Iris
the amount of plans and ideas tend to
sense General Instagram I have to
otherwise I forget
neighbors
the best thank you did you enjoy it come
Sunny down I hope you enjoyed it
I hope many Korean Bros were able to
watch the 3D showcase too yeah
maybe one day Korean convention can call
kiwawa again and uh we can do it in 3D
hopefully but that really depends like
in terms of when it comes to conventions
it's really on the convention side
whether or not they want to do it and if
they can offer
um the like venue and everything
that would make it possible because not
all of them can do it we wanted to do it
at dukumi and it wasn't possible
um really is up to them
if they can accommodate it yeah
it would be really cool though
because especially with Korean
conventions like previously when we did
a Korean Convention as far as I remember
um it was way easier to sing Korean
songs
uh that's why I chose to sing a Korean
song
in terms of Rights you know it was
easier
and so what I would love to do is
perform
well possibly also my original songs but
I want to perform
and
Korean songs and dance along in 3D
I just hope my TV doesn't melt from the
3D and the Phoenix Warrior textual
cuteness Overlord
well did it
is your TV okay did you have to buy a
new one yet
shouldn't it be used to it already by
now or do you normally not watch me on
the TV TV hey was I not hot enough
[Applause]
or was there some kind of like fire
protection that your TV came with and
you didn't even know about it
hmm let's say it's that let's say that
that's what it was yeah
I want to I really would love to but I
feel like
um I'm too small which is weird because
it's a dance studio but
I would love to do something with them
like a collaboration
um
one million dance studios
would be so cool
I think Bales would totally be up for it
too
she surely knows about 1 million Studios
there's no way she doesn't
it's a really famous Korean dance studio
that got really popular after posting a
couple of videos of their choreographies
and dance classes on YouTube
they really were blessed by the
algorithm and then
got more popular and popular
and they were releasing videos like
every day
and now they're like you know Top Class
everybody wants in
everybody wants to get a class there
and they choreograph like for famous uh
Korean Idol groups too
um
yeah
thank you jsw
well thank you so much as always for
supporting me you're always there I can
always rely on you thank you
showcase will be a total blast always
proud of Yuki Wawa thank you I hope I
didn't disappoint you
thank you you can sign up for a class
next time in Korea it would have to be a
beginner beginner beginner class
yeah but I don't know
[Music]
huh
I would probably be so nervous that even
with beginner class
the choreo wouldn't enter my brain
but I wonder how far in advance you have
to reserve I can imagine that it's just
so packed
so so so packed
can you see the schedule
on their website or so
how many spots they have opened
hmm
went to bed said I couldn't watch more
than the start yeah now you're watching
the end yay
okay
yeah you can see it oh
maybe for the next time I'm I'm already
like thinking
of going to Korea again this year in the
second half maybe
so I'll plan ahead
they do private teaching session too
that's probably way too expensive
and I think it would be kind of cool to
be in the group you know
that's the experience
could get to know some people there too
make friends
um
anyway thank you blue blah blah blah
blah Jenna thank you for one two three
four five six seven eight nine ten pink
orange super chats
I feel like
I feel like I
feel like I saw this when this was
happening
because when I was in the studio
preparing everything
and not pink I mean orange did I say
pink
yeah when uh I was there I I saw the the
chat saying something about orange
carpet orange carpet orange carpet
um
yeah
did I write on Twitter soon after that
then yeah I probably saw it
it was so sweet like seeing you guys
there in the chat
[Music]
are we so happy that kfp showed up
good
to show you the fruits of my labor
anyway those may be
um orange super chats but I will read
them because together they they look
like they make at least one red one if
not two 20 40s 60 80 100 20 40 60 1800
that's what I thought
I hope you get well so intentional
you've gone for harder obstacles than
this before combat in there I think this
is another appropriate time to take out
the orange carpet once again at last
moment that have been waiting for a very
long long time has arrived congrats on
your 3D showcase finally I'm sure
everyone is excited and I bet you're
excited as well I can't wait who will be
cast for The Stream and we know this is
going to be good real good
wasn't everybody's
um
expectations
if there were guests and it would be
at least one of them if not two if not
free
but definitely those two
yeah very important to me and I wanted
to get someone
for this special occasion who I had
history with who I had a connection with
who I just wanted to thank by having
them on my showcase
and just make memories together
in that showcase yeah
hey Mama I can't wait and of course hope
that you're usually upgrading the door
adjustments came out as good as you
wished for I don't know what more you
will have in store for us but regardless
what that might be I'm looking forward
to the 3D showcase
show me what pretty cat is capable of it
is time to show that spicy moves and
skills that you have been practicing I
think that
um hip movement and fever nights came
across quite well but I'm telling you I
was I was moving those hips
so crazy
like a bouncy house
I was moving those hips like twice as
strong as it actually was captured okay
tried really hard thanks for the
membership gifts again thank you the
hatching was quite spicy
uh
proud
what was I gonna say oh yeah the butt um
upgrade I feel so bad because I feel
like I got everybody's hopes up because
that's but that's because they got my
hopes up because the screenshots and so
on that they sent me as I told you they
just looked so much bigger now it
actually was but at least the shape is
somewhat improved
um
well
sorry I'm sorry
I think pudding made a video right where
it seemed like he was definitely not
satisfied with it
oh
this is like McDonald's burger ads
um
[Music]
we're still miles better than it was
before I guess so thank you thank you
normally I would write a few more stuff
but I'm sure you have a lot of other
super chats to read so I will just leave
it at that comments again on the
Showcase
uh
wait there's some Korean text
[\h__\h]
[Music]
well okay should I read this out loud
too
um congratulations to the manager who's
worked so hard so far finally the
manager's efforts are paying off I look
forward to a good stream and don't
forget we'll always be there for you
thank you thank you for the beautiful
orange carpet can I take that one home
and bring it into my apartment thanks
for the memberships
can I take it home
I need another carpet
what do you mean it's already gone what
do you mean you already put it away into
the storage eh
bring it back bring it back
bring it back
I need that orange carpet
man
oh my God thanks for the gifts
ah
yo yo yo yo
thank you thank you thank you thank you
orange carpet retrieval quest yeah I'll
get it back one day
yeah
thank you all Kindle L5 Guardian thank
you wait you know you got a kiss
L5 Guardian thank you for the rate of
chat oh my God that's a big one too
pretty party time whoa so excited for
the stream you work insanely hard and
it's always such a pleasure to see that
hard work pay off you're amazing and
you're going to do great congratulations
on the Showcase much love to you Viva La
Canada yeah thank you
hahaha
yeah yes payoff finally I hope you
enjoyed it I wonder what's your favorite
part of the Showcase
well much much love back to you
and Viva La Chiara indeed Viva La kfp
even more
thank you for coming to this special
special occasion L5 Guardian
I appreciate it here's a kiss for you
triple kiss
oh baby a triple
you are my favorite part of the Showcase
oh stop
stop
Jeff stop thank you for the pinky I need
to see my ocean glorious ready I don't
need to sleep
oh yeah you were one of the European
Bros on that day
thank you
I appreciate it
um what time was that 12 minus eight
four
A.M
that is a really shitty time I'm so
sorry
um was worth it thank you
set my alarm and slept again right after
sorry guys
someone had to suffer hmm
but it was a very important stream so
yeah thank you for waking up for it
you didn't have to but you did it anyway
thank you Shadow pencil Danka sure and
that code thank you for the rainbow
another rainbow
congratulations on your foreign
sorry I've been a no-show
don't worry about it you came to the
showcase my job became suckle I couldn't
miss my oh she's 3DW though especially
after your nose flow
went uh-oh
what are you ready to go go we love you
you know so since you're amazing Divine
and the best you get another rainbow and
I hope a good rest you were like rhyming
there hahaha
hey are you okay
your job not treating you well that
sucks
that really sucks
well I hope you can do something about
it maybe it changed job eventually but I
know that might be difficult
hmm
or maybe enjoy the job it's just really
busy in that case oof
what a um conundrum
but you're not forgetting about me and
you still come to the important days
that's okay yes stay strong stay strong
they'll call it you can do it
thank you I hope you'll be able to watch
again soon
Jacob 47 out thank you for the red-up
attack the moment of truth is here the
long-awaited 3DW I can't even imagine
everything that had to come together to
make the stand possible but I'm sure the
result is going to be worth it the
Phoenix is really going to show her
stuff tonight
I would have shot more and we were too
embarrassed
thank you Jacob for the very very
generous superchata well
it was a long time we waited for it a
long long time
finally it's behind us thanks for the
gifted memberships again
yeah hopefully there will be more like
this in the future right Jacob because
I'm sure you enjoyed it
right
so I will try my best to deliver more
um
thank you for the words of a tattoo
Conrad Scandal new 3D showcase I know
you have been waiting for this moment
for a very long time and have been
working very hard rehearsing I want to
let you know that I'm super proud of you
time to celebrate this big milestone
love you thank you love you too
yo thank you for being proud of me ah
thanks for the memberships oh my God
thank you holy [\h__\h] I guess in exchange
for not being able to Super Chat today
you guys are sending a lot of
memberships
thank you
well moon dog thank you for the support
I don't know what to say I keep on
repeating myself but thank you thank you
thank you thank you means a lot to me
that you're still here after this long
time and we're getting this nice nice
reward for it
um
[Music]
it's 10 p.m I should stop after this
thanks for the pinky so incredibly happy
to see you get here to your 3D showcase
your endless creativity passion and
determination is why I'm proud to call
you my cat me or she
finally we'll get to see you fully
Unleash Your 3D self and dance like
crazy you got this
thank you
thank you Miss best
I tried my best
was fun
it was fun and I'm so relieved it's over
I was so [\h__\h] nervous
um
I think one reason why I was extra
nervous is um
possibly like all like a [\h__\h] amount
of uh tea and that other magical
medicine that I was drinking
um combined with nervousness and a lot
of like throats uh
candy thingies
I think messed up my stomach
um
and the like I when I arrived at the
studio and prepared
um
in the one hour before the stream
actually started
I had to go to
a big Idol meeting twice
and that was quite a problem because
um
you know everything was like calibrated
and set and you know I had to take the
finger thingies off several times
[Music]
and I I was like [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] why
why why why why why why
literally cannot hold it back I really
hope
that this doesn't happen during the
streams
I was really worried
I was really really concerned
thankfully
during the stream it was okay
but it made me really really
worried
hahaha
yeah it might have been really the
extreme stress I had on me you know the
stress of really needing to get healthy
immediately when I was in the middle of
getting sick
um
damn damn damn damn
I just felt a lot of pressure insane
amounts of pressure
to deliver
um
well yeah it went okay
it was okay
so I will leave it at that uh remember
Miss fist number 86.
I think that was already a decent amount
of super chats that I read today
considering I also played so much today
eight and a half hours in total
kick on it
oh my God tomorrow's such a [\h__\h]
special day what the [\h__\h]
yeah right now
I have to emcee [\h__\h]
oh
I don't wanna [\h__\h] what did I think
about it
I just realized again
panic panic panic panic panic panic
panic panic
oh
it's okay it's okay it'll be fine it'll
be fine it'll be fine I can probably
look at a script while I'm doing it
probably
um
okay okay
I can do it I can do it
[Laughter]
we'll have fun that's the most important
thing
we'll have fun tomorrow so I have to
prepare for that
and do some other stuff so thank you
guys for watching and enjoyment if you
say goodbye I'll see you guys tomorrow
uh on the whole life English Channel
panic
[Music]
foreign