where where's Peach
at got to get out of here come
on great okay calm down this looks
familiar little too familiar why is
everything so tall here all right
there's got to be something around here
that can help wait what is
this personal research notes Wii v15
three nothing here no there has to be
something I don't understand
what day 47 first attempt at human
form these opposable thumbs are
impossible how do they maintain such
precise knife control kept trying to
grip like it normally would and bur
blade designs cumbersome unweld the
standard 55 HRC showing High signs of
wear absolutely unacceptable performance
day 889 breakthrough watching Michelin
star chefs I've been using hammer grip
like an amateur the way they've mastered
these strange appendages they use what
they call a pinch grip and that gives
them precise control and Perfect Balance
kfp deserve the same I started materials
research today needed something
revolutionary standard still won't be
sufficient for cross form adaptation day
152 a fiery orange revealed itself in
the Damascus vg10 during the crafting
process to today like Flames trapped in
steel tests show that we've achieved 61
Rockwell hardness far beyond standard
kitchen knives made it lighter Nimble
easier for us to use a beautiful
Kashi a beautiful flavor of the cut it
stays sharper longer and the pattern
reminds us of who we're serving day 173
sh'll design prototype testing premium
Maple and Walnut hardwood another team
member dropped everything today I saw
the fear in their eyes not from changing
but from being likeing soone stable the
integrated handle we put in it's an
anchor point for them something to hold
on to when everything's changing
transformation machine targeting system
requires stable classification
parameters manual override implemented
after
c727 H7 h727
incident wait day 208 implemented
protocol 8873 today I had to watch
another team member break down during
testing they caught the reflection mid
shift
and third one this
week they kept targeting people with the
same name and you could tell they were
really rustled those jimmies we thought
so long as we attach a number to their
name then the system would work even
when there's multiple team members with
the same name but the device keeps
choosing the wrong form they trust me to
fix this help them no no names the class
ification system will help Class C Class
H clear definitions clear
rules and what's happening to me what
happened to them I hope it it was me I
created protocol 87.3 to protect them
from the pain of transformation but I
all I did was make them forget who they
were made them forget who I was
c727 that's why everything felt so
familiar access codes the prot calls the
exact placement of your document I wrote
them what have I done to us not just
paperwork it's hardcoded into the
targeting system every team member
buried in numbered bureaucracy because I
was terrified of anyone else
experiencing this I remember now just
one slip of the finger a wrong number
that's all it took the machine couldn't
resolve the situation didn't know what
form I was in every transformation
became unstable
I was losing myself if I kept changing
if I couldn't keep my attachments then
why should anyone else that protocol
that was the mistake I still have time
the the new training video no more
hiding behind the Protocol no more rigid
classifications everyone free deserve
Teno in the form that we were meant to
be error cation parameters corrupted
applying randomized transformation
protocols what oh
[Music]