[Music]
do
you
[Music]
me
do
[Music]
you
uh can i have like three more minutes
i'm i'm doing stretches
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
foreign
you
[Music]
push
which
[Music]
it's not minecraft don't worry
we should
i
could just
accidentally delete the pokemon logo
[Music]
don't look at my hands
where the [\h__\h] is that minecraft logo
well which logo this one okay
ah
don't look at my hands
gosh it's so embarrassing to have four
hands
i feel so weird hello
hello
sorry brain slow need to warm up
although i'm feeling very
very hot right now
uh
oh i was cleaning my room and my
apartment i was cleaning my apartment
and then i was doing quick stretches
trying to squeeze everything in i have
to still clean so much
um after the stream i still have to
clean
um
[Music]
yeah
wow
[Music]
four hands
yeah oh i'm not i'm not human confirmed
oh sure
and where's the logo
yeah
ah
there it is
almost almost put a png or fauna on the
screen we don't we all need that
pokemon
excuse me with the german logo
i mean we learned we learned german
yesterday and my members only so you
probably know what legendary means
probably even without the lesson
okay
um
video capture device there we go
look at that
oh let me flex on you
uh
wait
is there anything yeah bye
maybe yeah uh look
meet that
look at all that space available
me tahoe
oh my god
oh
gb
isn't that beautiful a beautiful sight
to see
i bought also i bought a new jug for
water
one that supposedly
filters
tap water oh sure our tap water is
beautiful
in in austria but i actually bought it
for my other new object which is another
humidifier
so i don't i don't have to keep on
moving the humidifiers in between rooms
oh wait that smells weird now
i haven't tried drinking this filtered
water yet
did i use it correctly i think i did
maybe it smells clean
[Laughter]
huh
it tastes fine
you want to use it a few times before
you drink
use it a few times
i
i filled it once and filled all of that
into into the humidifier
now this is the second feeling
they smell like dirt for is it safe
it's safe right it's fine
you scare me
but it does smell a bit weird
i mean it doesn't i don't know it
doesn't smell dangerous
i think i have a cat hair in my mouth
again
[Music]
whatever have some
even worse case if they're if this means
that i am
have been getting some chemistry in
inside my mouth well that's um
that's just wonderful i'm a phoenix uh
if there's if a phoenix gets mixed with
uh
chemistry i will be turned into a
powerpuff girl so it's all good
your show
it goes up pokemon
oh
i missed this i played quite a bit off
screen and
high sing guy the cake
night
main story system tonight i did not
continue the main story
so
we good on that behalf
why is the screen size just not accurate
um
that's what that reminds me of uh i
changed my clothes i'm looking gorgeous
um i got orange glasses because why the
[\h__\h] not
um
found a shiny end
i i have yet to find the shiny
but
i will try to um
i'll
actually
i'll try to show you what i did because
i i took some screenshots don't look
so
oh yeah so i caught
off screen i called a big flying snake
that's it
it took me quite a while i had to
restart because i ran out of balls
but i thought it was i found it randomly
i was like yo this is this is cool what
i didn't know that they could be flying
around like that well now the more you
know
uh yes got it i'm using it in the team
right now and i couldn't hold back guys
i'm sorry i evolved my eevee into this
beautiful gorgeous thing then i called a
mime junior i actually called a lot of
mime juniors afterwards because i did
find later on and uh actually already
since the beginning accessible spot
where there's a lot of them
um
and their evolutions then i kind of uh
ran into this and for the first time
experienced this kind of [\h__\h] uh uh was
pretty about uh i did survive and i
caught a lot of pokemon but fighting
against these three
um at the same time was pretty tough
because
having a pokemon out that is maybe
strong against sneasel doesn't mean that
it's strong against that [\h__\h] ghost
or whatever
uh that was [\h__\h] tough man
yeah but i did catch i think all of them
eventually i killed some as well but
then i did some more
then i evolved this balloon
and i did some more fighting
i caught those as well
uh
i collect those a lot of items in there
uh then i um
holy [\h__\h] man
uh i think from these ones i had to run
away i think
i think i'm not sure
ah no
no i managed to kill
the two pokemon on the right and then i
was against stelix apparently nope i did
not i don't think i managed to um look
at those fainted pokemon
yeah i was alpha it was alpha i ran away
from this one i think pretty sure
and then yeah i reported i don't know
why uh i took a screenshot of that but
just you see uh i caught some new stuff
and i did the shiny ponita side quest
it's a side quest anyone can get the
shiny bonita
ponita it uh kind of i guess introduces
you to how shinies look like in the game
a good night good night why are you
sleeping at the beginning of my stream
well when you wake up i might still be
streaming so that's that
yeah i got it just because of the side
quests i did a lot of side quests a lot
of the the ones that were like long
overdue like the breezelle the bowie
zeller one and why you need to get a big
one
i did that uh oh why did i take a
screenshot
i don't know why i took a screenshot
of that
might have been an accident oh then i
got a new rank um
and that's it
yay
and
i think let me look
next rank is not that far off
oh oh yeah i caught shallows i caught
gastron
abracadabra mr mime
because
you kind of have to look around but
there is
um
there's uh there's an area where there's
like a ton of those in the first in the
first map
[Music]
oh yeah i was looking for cheddar beans
they're pretty hard to find but i you
need them for a side quest as well
and then i found these as well there's a
lot of new ones here ah i caught
chimchar
i have a did you guys know i have a
pikachu now i evolved my pichu
um
yeah i think that's uh
i got a lot of or uh two two
i i
got two lime juniors
yes yes so i was i was very active but i
was holding back still
because i didn't want to do too much
and i did not continue the main quest
that's what we're gonna do today so that
i can do a lot of side stuff again uh on
my free time
on my vacation
uh also teach me some more it's [\h__\h]
expensive but hell yeah never found a
terribly they're so hard to get man
[Music]
because um they uh they spawn out of
trees but apparently only in two
specific areas and i think only one was
accessible for me
um
is this loud enough by the way
wow
maybe one more god he's taking all my
money
didn't get a to be until the fourth area
they are yeah they're probably maybe
more um
more easy to find in later
maps okay no no no more
well how much space do i have now
oh i also made one of those dolls for
side quests um
okay okay not a little oh this is some
stuff that i have to put
uh somewhere else
did you find any ah yes and i have
another eevee now i didn't show you
maybe uh this is my team right
now
um
[Music]
why is everyone female in my team almost
everyone
and
i forgot how to play this game i haven't
played in like two days
um
oh yeah let me run over
here i wanted to train a second eevee
because i want another at least one more
evolution
does it feel laggy only to me
i want another evolution in my team
uh look at all that pink man
i'm thinking
well we don't need to plant evie we
don't
i said i want the fire evie
right so
we're gonna
put her back
ah but okay what do i need what stone do
i need to evolve
do i need to get for the fire evie
what's it called does someone know
and who should i get rid of
the thing is though inflation does have
a fire skill that could cover us with
fire a firestone okay
do you think anything else maybe umbreon
but yeah that would be dark what can
umbreon do besides dark
could also kick out the pikachu
and do an electro
eevee
i did see
that in time space events you can you
can get eevee evolutions too yeah i did
see i'm broken tank oh
[Music]
tanky pokemon
that's pretty good
good i think no we're not going full
evie just maybe like two
um
jolteon sounds good as well
ombre has some psychic attacks
sidekick see i i think i want to keep my
balloon so
i guess nothing that
um
overlaps too much with
him
maybe
[Music]
uh
the water evie might be worth it too
because then i can get rid of
gyarados
oh no gyarados doesn't even have a water
scale right now that's the funny thing
all right can i give
[Music]
wait a second
i can't decide there's so many choices
but paul ryan which one is that again
the water one
dossier
might should i keep should i keep
this big snake
should i keep him does you have a water
skill now water pools
splash
the users just flop some splashes ha ha
that one uh
maybe water pools at least for a set of
[Music]
this one
big snake is good
okay
um
better offensive a poorer and better
defensive dossier
well at least now he has a water attack
because we don't need bite and crunch
yeah
water snake oh yeah we need to rename
him
[Music]
why snake is too simple too easy
we call him sliver.io
this stream is not sponsored
yeah i think that's pretty good because
he can do he can do dark moves and
dragon moves and water moves that's
pretty impressive
um
i think eventually
we will kick out either trunk or
sparks
which means someone has to if we kick
expired sparks and it might be good to
get jolt on jolteon i suppose if we kick
out
chunk
then it doesn't really matter because
junk is such an all-arounder
and dark is being covered by someone
there's no rock
evie
i guess so
hmm
party management is a pain talking very
fast
no i didn't see it yet
wait it's where what is is she still
doing cuddle again
or is she
what's
let me see
where is it where is it
man she's singing right now she started
at the same time as me
i missed it i got to go back to it maybe
we can ask for a
uh
maybe we can ask for it
[Music]
she just sang it [\h__\h]
damn it
wait can i can i go back in time no it's
not possible
okay well guys we will we shall watch
her um archive
please let's let's watch her archive
later
um
i didn't know i didn't know that she was
doing it like i thought she already sang
it to be like yesterday or so
[Laughter]
she sounds good of course she does she's
an amazing singer
okay let's not think about it too much
right now uh let's just
[Music]
let's just go with this team for now
and uh i might evolve my eevee
on my own time
and uh
yeah you'll see what it becomes
eventually or or we find a
an evolution luckily in a space-time
distortion thingy
okay
sparks encore what is she doing the
sparks anchor i don't think she's doing
this is she doing if she does but don't
ask her for it because that's annoying
uh why is it so low that's what i'm
thinking is it lo no i feel like it's
lower fps on my screen than it is on obs
no it isn't it is did you see that that
was little fps what the [\h__\h] is going on
why is it what's happening
it is little fbs do you see that
what's happening
it's kind of like a laggy no
switch are you good
what is happening
anyway
that's the main quest
[Music]
it's still fine i suppose
there's an outbreak apparently right now
should we see if we can find the fine of
a shiny there just by by accident i
don't really care about getting that
shiny but
i've never checked a mass um outbreak
before
here ah and i should go
here
how long do those last normally oh also
this is this is where you can get a [\h__\h]
ton of abracadabra and mime junior and
the evolution of mime jr
um yeah lots of stuff going on here
lots of
creepy freaky pokemon
yeah
okay
let's check it out oh yeah i should also
after checking that out i'll i'll see if
i
oh [\h__\h] i should have cleaned my
inventory i'll see if i can um
put the bgm back on
that we had before
uh this
ghost is this for that
who's who can evolve with the ice stone
oh shutter pressure
wonder what those are for
who is those that for evie it's a
glacier oh so there was an ice
ice eevee oh
we have an ice stone
i don't know if i want an ice evie
i feel like the water evie could learn
ice skills probably anyway
[Music]
you could get ice nine tails what
oh you're right wait stop uh i just
remembered i wanted uh
nine tails for
um
to cover fire
i forgot that but what
yeah hello there's an alolan vulpix in
this game what the [\h__\h] but apparently
only in late games so probably not
really worth it um
kingsley
combining this herb with other materials
needed to maintain
[Music]
don't really care for them so if it's if
there's no shiny then i don't care
there's no shiny if you like if you
catch like all four of them are they
gonna like continue respawning or is
that it then
i could catch a few i guess
who's yelling at me
or the big bullet
they respond for a bit
higher probably
ah way higher
i feel like there's a maximum of
they respond when you return to the area
oh they keep on following me
are you good
are you insane
hi cute pup you're not gonna attack me i
know you're you're cute burp you
wouldn't hurt another boob
i'm going to try to catch them like this
now they're in a good area
oh ghost incoming sheet
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
i am hoping that today we will however
find a shiny randomly
just like out of pure luck
out of pure streamer luck
so oh wait there's a andy's lost satchel
here hmm
i'll go grab it for you
[Music]
shawn and uh
uh
what's over there
yes i give you my energy thank you
yummy
can you jump good good horse
i see it i think no is that it
oh yes i hate it
[Music]
uh [\h__\h] um
stop looking at me
are we good
come on we good
there's an alpha pikachu
oh pikachu
[\h__\h] scary look at that pikachu
[Music]
that was the wrong pokemon to go with
apparently
what you got done pokemon choices
a rare spawn
maybe i should try to get it
we could go stealth oh level nine oh
okay yes then it didn't really matter
okay
um
[Music]
threatening intimidating
do you want the berry
do alpha pokemon eat berries i forgot
they do
oh cute and scary
oh big
[Music]
should i switch out my current pikachu
uh with this one
the level difference is not that
not that big
even if i do i will have to do it later
i suppose
oh lesson found
thank you you're welcome
bye-bye
okay uh
you'll definitely be stronger
to intimidate
huge
fat mouse
[Music]
yes okay we're fast traveling but uh
actually oh
that's where i wanted to go
we're going to the other
uh
we need that we need a professor hello
hello i'm done here yes i only caught
one pokemon but it's a special one
it is a special one
oh i could switch pokemon at the camp
that's true uh but i wanna switch area
um
return to the village
can you can you switch area while you're
in another map like switch to the other
one
or do you always have to come back here
i'm not sure but um
let's switch out pikachu
we'll call it we'll give it the same
name
is it this one it's this one it's alpha
and female beautiful
oh
[Music]
sad spanx he's not sad sparks if
anything he's fat sparks
[Music]
fat
white sparks
sparks
very confusing
if you didn't watch this part of the
episode then you will not understand
where that came from
i'm very proud of the slippery dog iodo
sparks redshift aha
i thought i don't really see um
i guess yeah you know what i would love
to hear a redshift uh remix of sparks
okay kuza
from that so we can see him ah okay uh i
rarely do that
oh where are you
it looks so small though
you should have been bigger
wait but the sounds
the sounds
of his feet listen
they sound very
big
very heavy
[Laughter]
i don't have a normal one anymore well
apparently this is pink
[Music]
okay
let's go to the main quest i'm curious
[Music]
to yeah once it turns into a it will
become so pink so big
um
oh yeah i'll also need um
i also need to eat a banana sometime
sometime during this
stream
wow a lot of people died here
don't worry guys i'll get your satchels
eventually
uh
where's the main quest ah
i did that did you go hmm
is the main quest
uh hello
side quest
rosalia uh-huh i have yet to find the
resilient here this is
probably going to take a while
banana thank you
it's right next to me i just gotta
wait a little bit when they start
talking i might eat it um
[Music]
why don't you learn to follow the blue
signal so sniff
oh oh yeah by the way i still normally i
still don't write on ursa luna because
it's kind of annoying to ride on or luna
so generally
i choose to uh write on
what what's his name again
i forgot
wait what's that other mount's name
wasn't ourselves right
i need to sniff out wait what
blue signals to sniff out arizo in the
crimson marlins crimson ireland
where exactly though where dear oh yeah
oh okay i can't cross there i think i
remember that uh blah blah blah
i see he's like
he keeps on trying to
lead you somewhere else
oh
he's running
towards where i don't know where do you
want to go it's like so unclear
where where he wants to go
what's
it's probably above
uh
oh hi there huge [\h__\h] time gala oh
god ow
um
run
[Laughter]
how does it open that i'm gonna run with
you first
he points to the location but he doesn't
know how to go around yeah it's a
i don't know they shouldn't prove that
it doesn't work so well
oh man so many ghost pokemon
scary
coyotes
i did that quest with the hippo
hippo pokemon
i did that already the fashion one
i did so many side quests guys
are you proud of me
okay here we switch to the bear
and i guess from here on we follow him
with like do you have any idea
another treasure twenty tumbles don't do
wow
thank you chad thank you
i want that
go up there come on
follow the blue
ah
blue
right now it's green
why didn't we have blue scents before
wasn't the blue like in when i was here
and i feel like it should be more
further
deeper in the map
just logically thinking
he had but he went too far
i passed it
so should i go back is it is it always
like is it a random location or is it
always the same location
she's more north oh
oh
well then let me speed back
um
can i go for that water
okay
switching i guess up this blue that's
that's blue
there's
blue blue blue oh oh stop you can't go
there apparently
okay on the other side of the river
[Music]
where where exactly oh my god oh my god
oh my god that's not blue oh that's blue
that's blue oh
what
another real life human being oh fine
goodness i was on my way back to the
base camp when i got attacked by some
wild pokemon i managed to get away from
them but i got completely lost when i
was running and um please can you tell
me how to get back home
that way
that's it
i mean this way right of course i knew
you meant this direction
i should
oh was i looking for this lady for
another side quest
[\h__\h] can i um
i noticed that bigger rocks i can't
destroy but like what about
what about this size of rock
oh this size of rock i can't destroy
okay anyway
um
wait is it that way maybe
i don't see a blue
[Music]
oh
it's no blue it's just green
i love fat city so but we can't go there
now
oh
oh this chunky monster is so dangerous
and
or at least uh wait no not what the [\h__\h]
was that pokemon's name
it's the evolution of anton
psyduck
gold duck oh
blue blue blue blue
[Music]
in this water okay okay okay blue blue
blue this is like so vague
this is way too very vague
now it's not blue anymore
oh no
oh [\h__\h] aggressive junker
maybe it's uh over there
it's a game of hot and cold i hate it
because you're hot then you're cold
you're yes then you know you're in and
you're out you're up and you're down
[Music]
sometimes i feel like he's low-key
leading me but then again
it doesn't feel like it
i don't know
any shiny i really want
um
an eevee shiny would be [\h__\h] amazing
i want an eevee outbreak okay it's not
here
thank you for the membership comes on
nida
no blue at all
nothing
here's blue again oh my god but it just
came from that way
wait it has to be like here i don't know
oh
are there ever has anyone ever seen an
eevee outbreak
for the shiny evie witch evolution i
would have to think deeply about that
um gotta go up the mountain
no mountain you have to go from the side
not
sure
where from wait there's no there's a
someone's stuff over there
is it up there on the edge
gosh what the [\h__\h] is this
maybe i can go up here
yo
what is that stone wall there for when
you can go up with your mount
it's a good sign
oh it's gone it's gone
should i go down again is this
this
i was there before
ah
i can break it oh this big one
i can
i feel like i can't break
can any pokemon do that
only this strong looking one
it's a sign
oh wait a second
i thought i was looking for a pokemon oh
you're addison i forgot
[Laughter]
ah kiawah how did it all go ever saluna
uh i called the dub
wow you're really strong but how do you
find me all the way out here
russell luna found you
you tracked me all the way here by the
scent of those potato mochi i ate also
banana opening now
a banana unpacking asmr
i don't know if you heard anything
banana unpacking
unboxing
potassium
[Music]
oh
good banana
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
banana
wait this music
some of the some of the sounds in this
music is kind of like
late night um
tv advertisement uh
music if you know what i mean with late
night
[Music]
wait i'm just gonna finish eating a
banana just give me a moment
remind you of donkey kong
yeah
if you're lonely call now
six six
six six sixty nine
sexy
sexy mommy's waiting for you
that's the kind of stuff that was uh on
tv after like i don't know one o'clock
uh probably not anymore though
[Music]
um
hey did you guys not have that on your
tv
okay i finished eating banana
[Music]
sorry
that was still part of my breakfast
yeah yeah yeah
[Laughter]
that explains the strange powder i found
on earth luna it must have been powder
from little again but what happened to
your leg dear
i was gathering ingredients to make
bombs but i i fell and sprayed my ankle
see the reason i went to jubilee life
was to get help for luna and also learn
about crafting but while i was there i
bumped into professor lovington and he
told me about the bombs you used to
quell cleaver
so i thought i'd make some for liligant
using her favorite foods
she already prepared them nicer your
galaxy people know all sorts of things
i'd like to learn even more from you
really
well then we'd better take care of your
hour where the [\h__\h] did he come from
our lady and get all these mess results
first okay
what were you thinking
doing all this yourself did you think i
couldn't help you
though no one would blame for you for
thinking so not much of a leader am i
i've never even seen almighty sinner
with my own eyes
and i failed to imagine that lilligan
might have become frenzy too
listen up kiawah i'll take the bombs
that arizumate and meet you at bravo
arena
don't you worry arizukian will come
liligant and that will be that things
should settle down
head to bravo arena
that's where lilligant's seat lies
audience will be taken care of my dear
bibarel and i will make sure she reaches
her lady
all righty
ah
she's helping her with her leg now
sweet
oh what what is that
what is that
oh it's skunk tank
graphics are a little bit weird on my
game capture
card
brava arena
which is where again
ah there i couldn't go there before i
think but okay
ah do i have to go around from the side
because like i think from here i wasn't
able to reach it
i suppose i have to go all the way from
the side
yeah it looks like pools of blood
huh
not a hotel so i will try to go
north
but through this path
i don't need oh dear i don't need the
the bear anymore do i
[Music]
and i'm gonna catch you or i guess i'm
gonna fight you
there's a bridge
okay
um
twister let's flick with that
ah that's not the twister that i imagine
holy [\h__\h] that's weak
oh that's weak i'm burning
right 37 wait second holy [\h__\h] why is it
[Music]
am i really supposed to pass through
here
no need to go around
um
all right i think i'm not supposed to be
here but i found the last satchel
hello
so there must be another way
um
[Music]
there's a bridge here
but i remember not being able to go like
very far there but i'll try
[Music]
hey
i wanted to turn on some btml for you
guys
[Music]
which ones were the ones
what was this one
no that's not it but that's so cute
[Music]
those two
okay yeah
you hear that
tell me if it's too loud
let me know
[Music]
all right adventure time
well that makes no sense how do i get
there
huh
i mean it can't be like
they can't be asking me to like glitch
over the mountains
there was no path through here
there's the world behind blood
[Music]
i mean i feel like it's a bit too loud
a road from the diamond settlement
so i have to have to go through there at
least for a little bit
even though they're so high level what
the [\h__\h]
i did so many side quests how come i'm
like too low level for this area is this
normal
were you guys also so low level
[Music]
i have to go through here
what is
yo this looks like this i don't know
orange juice in these
ponds
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] wait my my game capture
screen
uh stopped moving
ah okay okay i fixed it
what what
oh wait but no whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
what's going on
there we go
i did some weird stuff i didn't see what
i was doing
oh
is this the road
quick
everybody's so strong here
why is everybody so strong
[Music]
oh little village
hello is this where i was supposed to
come
[Music]
i was little 50 60 here
hello
nice to meet you i'm kiwawa
yes i'm from galaxy team
do you know the medicine that can cure
headaches i need it for my psyduck
i live together with these little ones
and i can tell they're uh they've been
suffering terribly i wish i could do
something to help but none of the
medicines i've tried have worked at all
there are so many people in the galaxy
team
wait don't worry psyducks always have a
headache
that's just their default state of mind
what kind of medicine you want kevin
mentioned that might use the headaches
of suffering psyduck
yeah
anything else here quest quest wise no
okay uh
so
i go like around there
follow this road i suppose
yeah they're just born with it oh hello
i wonder what level those are
i hear a sound
[Music]
um
oh dear um let me just uh i want to
catch some
for some exp please some free exp
[Music]
um
are they aggressive
oh wait this one is 27.
you need to explain to me
why this one is
normal level decent level
[Music]
levels of various hmm
it's very confusing though
[Music]
all right i'll catch the other one
catch them all
ah
another one who wants to fight
fine
yeah the alpha one don't worry i won't
run into that one i suppose it's pretty
high level
[Music]
65 apparently
that is crazy
let me get some levels here
what is that
[Music]
you get a leaf stone that easily isn't
that also for evolving uh evie
[Music]
oh
what are you who am i fighting
[Music]
i didn't know you could get them from
these kind of random
places as well wow move mastered nice um
i guess i i guess i can save
oops no sorry i'm so confused sometimes
but i do have to go here too
annie's lost satchel
it just feels nice to help someone
doesn't it
maybe this motivates people in real life
to instead of stealing stuff they find
randomly
in places uh
to uh bring them to the police or
wherever instead to the lost and found
instead of just taking it
oops okay let's fight
in japan
um i've never had something been stolen
before they really live by that
by that
find something and give back
definitely always try to give something
back um
lifestyle
but in europe holy [\h__\h] i still remember
when my [\h__\h] super new phone
that i was so excited to have
and wasn't even a week old when i had
that stolen in berlin
[Music]
yeah
that was stupid i was [\h__\h] up
well if that over there was if those
pokemon were normal
um leveled and i want to go back a
little bit
i'm not gonna go past the alpha uh into
through the alphabet here now let's just
try to
yeah pickpocket
very common in some european countries
some more some less
but yeah be careful
if you travel
to a country that where pickpocketing is
more common
uh
i feel like the alpha is looking at me
but that's just
that's just my
me being really nervous i suppose
[Music]
oh
in korea folks just leave phones on a
cab coffee table when going to the
toilet well i in japan
yeah i would just leave all my stuff
on the table on the restaurant table as
well
oh did you just did you just
they never want to go into the ball well
then you're gonna die
whatever you prefer honestly
should i feed them first
oh and it runs away [\h__\h] you
i don't i don't need so many of you
anyway i think oh wait didn't do i need
a full pokedex of the of that rosalia
or was it just like a couple
for the side quest right yeah
all right i'll do that probably on my
own time
was it that parasect maybe
eyes running away
okay
i'll catch you
or you know what i want to fight you
um let me see though
research level is seven i need an alpha
and a large specimen defeated or if i
defeat another one i get the three
hmm
you know what we'll we'll defeat it
i don't remember i'm guessing it's plant
ghost or something okay plant flying
maybe
[Music]
shiny charm all pokemon research level
10. oh oh this is pure grass
sodera
[Music]
that is
grass in the end
it makes you think that it's more than
that
[Music]
is there another alpha near it sounds so
threatening i gotta try to get that one
let's see
oh
heavy specimen feeder grass grass tab
that's kind of a hint that uh grass is
effective
i'll take that hint um
you know what i'm gonna fight you oops
ah
never mind i'll i'll catch you
i'll fight the other one because this is
a good position
[Applause]
[Music]
ah
okay rehorn or right horn
we don't even need to be too strong
style echoes
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
i guess i suppose uh seeing your
reaction i suppose it's ra ry horn
[Laughter]
in in german it's called rehorn that's
probably why i'm saying it like that
[Music]
it's pretty much the same name
but instead of a y it's written with an
eye
oh it didn't it's still not noticing me
though
maybe i want to find it i don't know
what's more important
i'll defeat it
youtube is saying four people are
watching
wow i'm so unpopular man
thanks for the membership welcome
i do have stuff sprays i think i have
all kinds of items with me but i don't
know most of the time i just
don't use them
i tried using a couple of them
on my private time when i was in an in
an area where there were just too many
pokemon close to one another and they
kept on seeing me and running away
i'm one of those four y'all are
definitely one of those four
maybe i should attack let you attack
first because i want to see stealth
stone from you
okay let's do false swatch
you have four phones watching you
watching me right now
so it's all you
oh what person
celebrate there we go
thank you
huh
[Music]
yo today i i had a little bit of a
conversation with amelia watson
um about where
she she's pretty serious about
this thing me guys i'm so excited
[Music]
probably before summer
probably before someone's just gonna
visit me and and your dad amelia watson
the emily watts the famous announcer
from uh paladins mm-hmm
we we don't uh we still gotta talk like
detail and stuff but
yeah and i told her yo if you're coming
uh if you're coming over you wanna fight
you wanna fight fine with me
are you're coming over
then might as well um
might as well go like
like to quick trip somewhere else in
europe as well how about that
yeah of course we can do off courage
i'm so excited i didn't know she was
like so so up for it oh there's a
satchel i think
um but yeah uh she needs to come she
doesn't necessarily need to but
i i
i have something that
um
currently only she can help me with
and i talked to her about it and she was
like yo i can come over
and i'm like okay what really
really
let's go
i if that really happens i'm gonna
i'm gonna um look up games that you can
only play locally with someone
so that i get those um
sorted out
because you gotta make use of those
opportunities maybe we can do 3d um
together
if that happens after the 3dw or so
wouldn't that be fun
i see a ghost thingy over there
is that reachable
ring fit off
ring fit collab now you know what i
could teach her i could teach her
dancing like some of my choreographies
hmm
teacher there's another one over there
uh teach her to dance
we're together with you know what you
know what would be funny
i'm as uh farmer
and then kiwawa in a special new noodle
version
like the opposite of buff
which is probably you guys would say my
default state but that's not true
that's not true
can i get one of you
i think i caught one of those before
though it's not so important
oh
okay
uh
i don't know how about sparks
alpha sparks
extra cursed extra skinny
literally like a skeleton of kiwawa
paralyzed what come on
attack
it caused me to fully snap awake noise
and spaghetti
yeah ah a cute lava but with like
spaghetti arms you know those uh isn't
there like a superhero what am i
thinking of
a superhero with like spaghetti arms
what am i thinking of
shh
suck oh damn it hi
mr fantastic mystery elastic fantastic
maybe
what is that where did i see that
spat face
why are you keep on surviving
[Music]
sparks spark caused it to fully snap
awake i love that sentence
yes fat spikes is female cute
cute tail buh
hi
rainy stream is over ah okay
okay
okay shook him up
i i won't play the video but let's
listen to the audio
um
pokemon shut up for a while
she sang it so well of course she did
where is it
it's kind of i think it's and did you
tell me well singing
where it's snow
ow that's it
[Music]
don't know what to do
don't forget what i
said get out of your head life is only
what you make and you're gonna be okay
so go ahead and do it do it if you want
it let's get to it everybody's gonna
know your
[Music]
don't stop don't stop just go your own
way so don't be afraid trust your heart
in the game
don't stop just go your own way
we're looking back take the fast lane
now and the driver seems trapped they
just gasped
going so fast
[Music]
so take a step don't move it move it
unless you try you won't get through it
everybody's gonna know your name
cause sparks like the flame turn the joy
called the night and today don't stop
don't stop just go your own way so don't
be afraid trust your heart keep your
head
[Music]
that one is really tough because you ran
out of breath
by that time and then having such a high
note is really tough
get down get down the floor everybody
don't stop don't
[Music]
strike a match
oh yeah yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
oh guys watch watch her archive uh later
or on the side to
to to give her like a like i'm gonna
thumb it up hell yeah
so good i love her singing voice i wanna
i wanna do a song covering
that was sparks not fire the song titled
sparks
oh
oh i'm so happy she uh wanted to learn
and sing my song
hmm
always very exciting to
have someone
sing your own song
um
also
there was something here i think ah yeah
that's what i meant
standing fire today
she's starting a [\h__\h] foil let's go
arson let's go no not good
only only
only in the song let's only start a fire
in the song
please share what you're eating oh i was
eating um european version of pocky
poketab
oh that's so okay i heard there's um
fall damage so i've been careful
but that was still apparently
fine
mikado yes yes exactly
the difference um
the cookie texture is different
the chocolate taste is different
and it's a bit thinner than pocky
yeah
what
[\h__\h]
fight
me find me
valentine's day yes
i am planning on
doing um
a baking stream
again for valentine's day
it will be the one year anniversary
of
one year anniversary
a part challenger
so valentine's
day
i know
[Music]
why do i need to keep on killing them
why i keep on killing them what did you
say oh [\h__\h]
because they must all die
i shall be the only pokemon left
in this world because that automatically
means there are no pokemon to catch
which then means
i have caught them all
this is my way of playing pokemon just
kidding
wait um how about
how about using a flying ball a feather
ball
not flying
but i don't know it's faster
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] not not him not him
come on
get wrecked
[Music]
oh damn that does do damage
turn the additional bgm on again sure
when the fight is over
sure sure glad you like it
okay i feel like i've done
some stuff let's go um main quest again
i think it was it over there yeah
we've done some fighting we've done some
catching
now
i probably got to turn it off again
though because there's probably going
gonna be some proper music here
hello other man
so you've come i take it that means
you're ready
i no wait don't wait don't wait no wait
don't wait
ah [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
ah [\h__\h] ah [\h__\h] uh can i still go back i
need to kill my pokemon
yeah
uh what i i hope i don't need um
a grass pokemon for
this one
oh hello
yeah
he'll still ask if i'm ready okay all it
took was one of my pull what pulled his
portis to get arizo's leg all patched up
ma'am i'm the only sorry we've had to
lean on your help so much especially as
we're from different clans
aniso tried to solve the whole situation
herself i dare say she bit off more than
she could chew and caused some trouble
but her heart was in the right place
[Music]
listen hey listen blink listen
the lady of the ridge lilligant is like
a dancer always in motion always darting
about flying is my best bet
[Music]
fire flying ice on a hotel ice i have on
chunky
you'll want to watch her real close and
learn how to dodge her moves
[Music]
fire i have on my ghost team but that
one only has two pp left
that's right if you keep on dodging she
might get tired out then that will be
opening that's when you can bring out
your own pokemon improve your mic don't
let me down
okay
makassarots
[Music]
yeah true i don't have to flag
um they did not ask again
um
[Music]
hmm
i know then i have to dodge my wife
i know
the game already told me before
um wait a second
nice
they got revived
[Music]
uh
what the [\h__\h] is that automatic um
god it doesn't work ugh
[Laughter]
[Music]
one hit nice
okay uh uh
[\h__\h] hell
come at me [\h__\h]
[Music]
what's she doing
oh
let me find you
[Applause]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
ah
[Music]
when i wanna eat pocky
give me a chill chill moment
[Music]
[Applause]
if
[\h__\h]
[Music]
really
[\h__\h] you
so much for being invulnerable while
dodging
only for like a tiny moment but if she
keeps on jumping when i like still i'm
taking time to
get back up admits defeat oh hell no
ah
okay
wow
okay now it's like a lot better
zero damage run let's go
[Music]
let's go i'll show you the real me
is this pokemon or dark soul
[Laughter]
he got
[Music]
come on
i changed direction
uh in a weird timing
[Music]
nope
oh oh oh you want to fight you want to
fight
no
[Applause]
doesn't work
and jump and shoot
okay i got too close
yes
okay
[Music]
energy ball
not very effective moment you good are
you fine are you dying too full
mummy is very digital
aerial ace strong style
[Music]
okay my chance is my chance stay safe
it's now or never
i am gonna live forever
[Music]
it's my life
what is the
is this uh is this a
uh history version of uh the rosalina
pokemon or
because like the other one also was
originally a different one right
one that already existed
as far as i know
what does it look like originally
i need to i need to see
dexter
elegance
pokemon
oh
the one with the boots
[Music]
um it doesn't look like so different so
dramatically different
um compared to
uh the other one that we had the other
one that we fought
that one looked more like dramatically
different like color wise and so on
um
mm-hmm
nicer
[Music]
thank you
it was far more difficult i mean the
shape yeah but like the colors and
everything is the same
um
cleaver is an evolutionary gun is not ah
uh-huh
yeah because i thought cleaver looks
very different
because he was suddenly so brown while
he was originally so
green
we didn't just save lilligan you saved
arizo as well i appreciate it
first is luna and now lilligant you're
amazing did you know that
being all uh frenzied didn't suit logan
one bit i'm so happy she's back to her
graceful self
the ballerina
yeah
honestly you still owe someone an
apology
hmm
oh don't worry about it
a young one like her is bound to get
caught up in some trouble from time to
time remember what's written in the
selassian ruins all lives touch other
lives to create something on you and
alive
there is wisdom in those words i imagine
they're the teaching of almighty sinnoh
itself
[Music]
of course i'd completely forgotten about
them until a certain somebody helped me
remember
me
that was me right
i was helpful
we owe you one ma'am
me
am i ma'am
don't try to solve everything by
yourself honestly
you're a warden of all people we should
know how to stand in solidarity with
others i think he was actually talking
to her
know how to stand in solidarity with
others it's our job to stand side by
side with pokemon after all
yes i know i'm sorry
well i can hardly start yelling at you
now after calaba wrapped all that up so
nicely
yeah ma'am you're ma'am i'm mad
just one more thing honestly i know you
were trying to do what you thought was
right and i approve of that but from now
on do it without keeping things from me
agreed
other than that no need to change your
thing you're pretty cute i kind of want
to go out with you sometime
huh
fine i guess blue and red are
opposite colors but
that could be a good thing
let's work together from now on to keep
the meyer land safe on a zoo i'll be
sure to inform erida that both the
diamond clan and galaxy team helped save
orza luna
you did well kiawah
all our different groups finally joined
hands to work together today
i admit it was a fun day for me but now
it's about time i be on my way
listen
you know me i'm out i'm on leader of the
diamond clan and i worship almighty
sinnoh the ruler of time
time is all about change and we can't
live in fear of that we can only try to
help the time we live and change for the
better
something tells me helping you folks out
will help me do that i'm looking forward
to it
thank you for everything kiawah i think
i'll stay and talk to lilligan for a
while
oh
what happened elegant how the
current-hearted pokemon like you end up
all frenzy huh
though it's not like i'm perfect i hit
things and light and couldn't even keep
you safe
i'm real sorry about everything
hey
she's huge
[Music]
all right we have to go back to
commander kamado apparently to report
uh what we have done here
[Music]
much better than the first time
i didn't quite get the timing yet the
first time
but all in all
all is good
could there who could this be
ah
stop it burmese
burn it burn the burmese
i'm ready for dark souls now
really
am i
what
why why is there uh
why is there an exclamation mark
did you see that why was there an
exclamation mark
anyway i think i'll just teleport i
guess or
oh sure
i need to claim the low loss and phone
items huh wait what
wait my own
did
i lose no i didn't lose that one time i
died okay uh uh-huh
uh-huh
95 marathons that's pretty good good
stuff
okay
um
then i shall
return to the mylance camp
this is the first time you got an item
ah i see not a hotel
hello yo real wonder uh does he want to
fight me again
i saw a light disappearing into the
space-time rift quelled another frenzied
pokemon have you
we still don't know what's causing the
enlightening what that frenzies these
pokemon but you you just go on rescuing
them without even a hint of trepidation
you might even change the entire course
of history here in history and i
definitely want to see it being the good
books of someone like that let's stay in
touch friend
report
did you get the clothing mr gift
no no
how do you get that
i didn't pre-order so i didn't get all
those pokeballs either
[Music]
oh we completed paris did i not complete
that before
not sure
[Music]
okay
it's for all players it should be in the
mystery gift section
oh
smashing
smashing he says
what i have done is smashing
a cute kimono
growl grow leaf color
whoa
i shall check it out later
you're a potato match here mm-hmm
[Music]
what do you mean
you mean be thankful with money
um
i know i have to tell kamadou
i'm very well aware of that
same meal every day yeah i don't know
that would not keep me motivated but
okay
um
[Music]
girl gotta get more nutrients
how does potato mochi taste
good question i actually haven't had it
before
it seems to be a specialty in hokkaido
[Music]
now i don't eat lasagna pizza almost
every day
yesterday i had
orange
fried
chicken
fried orange chicken with rice
you successfully calmed lily good
yes i did
excellent
[Laughter]
[Music]
of course vegan
or maybe times when the galaxy team will
be forced to fight against pokemon but
it is all for the sake of creating a new
home for ourselves free from war and
strife
a stranger falls into a world from a
rift in space time 10 frenzies are
induced by strange lightning which
likewise falls from that very same rift
but you have no connection to the
lightning isn't that right
we may need to investigate the rift
itself to prove your motives are beyond
impugning
yeah orange chicken is yummy
[Music]
not sure if it tastes like a potato dish
in germany
there you go piping hot potato mochi
fresh from the stove
yum yum yum
now this is life and enjoying tasty
potato watching with friends sharing the
latest findings from our pokemon
research and topping it all off with a
good night's sleep truly who could ask
for any for more
sure it's nice yet i keep doing the same
thing day after day is it really getting
us anywhere
oh
it's depresso espresso
[Music]
what
um
okay
uh
with our research on we're carving out a
life here thank you for renewing your
membership chiang huang
all right
have this flesh in your recipe kiawah it
ought to scatter these gloomy thoughts
scatter banks i already don't i already
know how to make those
come on now don't worry yourself so my
boy
as a wise man once said trust in
yourself and you will find your lane
these words are worth taking to heart
as long as we truly believe in ourselves
i'm sure we'll even complete that
pokedex of virus someday
17 months wow
that's over a year
i could buy them i couldn't make them
yet oh
i definitely used to use gem before
well good morning kiwawa
morning sleepyhead
ah it's you
you'll never guess what i'm gonna start
working at the hairdresser's shop let's
go
can you do more hairstyles now
now you'll be able to try out my oh no
that is exciting
oh let's go let's go let me try them
we're trying to try kamikaze
[Music]
if you want to work here in jail villas
you are family to us no matter where
thank you
more hairstyles
the new killer you will come with me no
no i need i'm pretty little [\h__\h] but i
need to i need to change my hairstyle
i'll come later
you probably won't even recognize me but
hey hey am i being taken i'm being taken
are priorities
these people have just arrived here in
new zealand they will live together with
us in jupiter live village
okay what do i care
not many yeah probably just like two or
three or four
when we of the galaxy team first arrived
in this land we came ashore on prelude
beach it is where everything began this
is where a new life for all of you will
begin as well
we've heard that the history region is
inhabited by many powerful and
frightening pokemon
but we've also heard the galaxy team
knows a great deal about pokemon and
uses their mysterious powers to help
jibber live village grow
and you have both heard correctly
and the reason such tales have reached
your ears is largely thanks to kiawah
here one of our survey corps recruits
through the combined efforts of all our
team members let us continue to develop
our village and thrive here in the
history region
we look forward to doing our part
commander
can we trust them
the advancement of our understanding of
pokemon and let me turn on bgm this is
quiet
thanks to survey corps has expanded the
areas where we can operate safely that
is what allows us to welcome in
newcomers like them
our village is growing bingo
i really love
i pokemon so
pokemon have done grave injury to many
of our fellows in the galaxy team and
yet you still find love for these
creatures in your heart i suppose that
is a necessary quality for one in the
survey corpse
remember this though pokemon are
terrifying creatures
i mean just look at
look at pichu
gives me lightness a grown-ass man like
me
i know
[Music]
um
arena
you guys here even though the cutie
[Music]
all right let's go
huh he brought me all the way here but
he doesn't he doesn't bring me back
really
wait i'll just teleport
[Music]
ditto
you know i guess i kind of can see
how that would be maybe a little bit
scary
okay let me try um
someone said there's nothing should show
but i'm just gonna hide it just in case
took them
um do i say check mystery gifts
no i know get via internet okay
give me something
i'm connected to the internet
i'm connected to the internet i know
searching for gifts
oh
merry christmas
ho ho ho
is it cute
fancy kimono fancy bottoms painful fox
mask oh
duncan
thank you
all right
uh oh my god can you cut my hair please
yes 500 is cheap
let's see what can we do
[Music]
no more old lady hairstyles man
is that new no that's not new that's not
new
twin thousands news
they're so short
uh
wait that's really not much new
ah i guess i have twin tails
we both go wait hair color though oh
that is new cute
blue
crimson
crimson blue and peach pink are new
where is the orange
should we do a red
i don't know
maybe go with peach pink
it's it's not even that pink but
all right and then do we have new we
have new eye colors we have new eye
colors
huh
doesn't look like
oh no wait it's uh eyebrows oopsie okay
you know
mama
all right
thank you for the new hairstyle girl
wow
i look like a
six-year-old
thanks for coming now thank you
i guess hope you think up some more
hairstyles because that's not much
um
okay you'll keep on polishing your
skills okay i mean it looks pretty cute
hello
side quest
there's a pokemon i think would be
perfect inspiration for some new designs
shallows oh i have shadows
[Music]
uh
easy showers in the west seashells i
don't know if i have both of them
let me see
the pink one the pink one i have
i only have a pink one i think
oh
and i probably don't have the other one
do i
doesn't look like it
the blue ones i catch in the next area
ah okay now
all right
what is that is that you
[Music]
a sweet treat are they the xp candy
what you can buy xp can hear they're
pretty expensive though
how cut
hot guy doesn't it
i actually have one let's give it to
all right
yeah not not quite worth it
i'm gonna look at those clothes later
i'm quite happy with the ones i have
right now
we haven't seen them for so long either
let's go up talk to our boss
we answer only to the highest
peeps in here
[Music]
i'll commend you on your successful
research of the pokemon living in the
crimson milans
your next orders are to begin the survey
of the cobalt coastlands whole next area
already i i feel like i still
i feel like i barely
investigated the current one but okay
um
i guess i can do that in my free time
let me use my blanket
i call it a blanket
hmm
my show
i will let you know in advance there are
no pokemon nobles and oh in the cobalt
coast
allow me to explain
we didn't have a lord in the coastlines
until a few years ago a strategy tragedy
took him from us here
you can revive him with an item
[Music]
now we've had reports of people saying
strange shadowy figures on the island of
the lord used to call his home
we have also received word from both the
security corps and supply corps it seems
some of their members were attacked by a
ghost while out gathering materials
around fire spit island
a
these are serious concerns and moreover
my clown just can't tolerate this this
sister desecration of our late lord's
seat
normally i'd entrust this to our warden
in the coastlines but her situation is
complicated
okay
a lordless island i'll meet you in the
cold with coastlands i do love it there
it's a beautiful area
oh and i know this must be bewildering
situation to be dropped into i'm sorry
king
think nothing of it
don't worry
don't worry about it
[Music]
indeed kiwawa quote the lord of the
woods i've seen both her strength and
her kindness first hand
[Music]
the next area for you to investigate
will be the cobalt coastlands it is
further afield than the crimson milans
much farther and the path is long and
trying
with your current rank you should be
capable of braving the cold coastlands
you know your mission investigate fire
spit island
[Music]
next area pretty good ooh
interesting
gonna be a ghostbuster
um
i don't i don't believe in ghosts
but if they're if i come across one i
don't know how i will react
y'all be
yummy
okay should we go straight there
vulpix is in that area
if it isn't kiwawa who's talking are you
though i suppose it is to be expected
that i'd run into you in this village
why are you going to study pokemon next
um paulina certainly in a bit of a
situation over there she's awarded him
yet she has no noble proceed to there
are even some people in the pearl clan
that speak ill of her though not to her
face
oh but do forgive me perhaps i shouldn't
be hearing dirty laundry a piece of
advice then as an apology for wasting
your your time
some pokemon are strongly affected by
certain stones which hold mysterious
power with the right stone you can
i know i know no no thank you
what i'm trying to say is basically this
if you and the survey clubs want to
learn all there is to know about the
pokemon of this region then the stones
you find throughout history will be very
important there is even a tale of a
stone that contains the power of
creation the very same power almighty
all naughty say no used to create the
universe
my voice
needs to be rested i can't voice too
many characters today
great pebble
[Music]
yeah i skipped hard to evolve sky for
into cleaver i kind of saw it a split
second doesn't matter
because i'm not planning on it
i may be at the end to complete my
pokemon pokedex the ginkgo guild
has them from time to time
yeah but i also know where else to get
them don't worry
okay so we can go there directly oh
there's a lot of water and the volcano
and that looks like a hand and that
looks like horns
interesting
oh
are we high level enough i hope so
oh yeah yeah
your face again
oh
is this where we're gonna get a swimming
mountain
finally
probably
ah the colbert coastlines assembly
lovely corner of history sand sky as far
as the eye can see what kinds of pokemon
wait let's hear here wonder water types
flying types hmm i simply can't wait to
start anymore
oh yeah yeah i have a mission uh
about the warden
wardens in fact here in the colbert
coastlines you'll find paulina of the
pearl clan and the center of the diamond
clan perhaps they'll be of some help to
you as you dig into this blah blah blah
okay thank you i already see my waifu
over there
waifu for life food
waffle
[Music]
she looks so cute from behind from every
side
she's gonna call the water mount
or
[Music]
huh
do i always have to play a whole concert
to call him over
hmm
i do love the flute it feels as if it
tone its tones carry to the very ends of
space
but i am here and so are you so now i'm
going to focus everything i haven't
battling me
why you don't like me
i need to understand my weaknesses
please do this for me
why can't i only do the same man since i
can ask why again
and she says the same thing okay
okay
very good you have you who have seen the
vast space beyond the rift here i come
rikuya
oh she's a glassy one
wait i knew that didn't i i knew that i
knew that
enough for evie wait she's battling me
with two why don't i have two out
i don't understand the logic
but okay
why is it two versus one
i mean i've seen it in in
random battles outside but in a trainer
battle
question
[Music]
wait it's just level 15.
yeah i know i've been fighting three
versus one before um
in in non-trainer battles but this this
is uh
interesting
wait that's a wild one it's not it's not
a wild one she's probably trying to make
a full eevee team
she seems like a type of person to do
that
they don't have pokeballs so they're
pokemon always outside
oh
they're just i mean even if you don't
have pokeballs you could tell
your pokemon to stay behind at first
to make it fair
don't you
think if you're gonna battle someone
just for the sake of battling
then you could tell one of your pokemon
to stay the [\h__\h] behind what the hell
nanda neeta
[Music]
the world is vast and i'm small within
it
well it makes it a bit more fair because
uh npcs are weak anyway most of the time
thank you for healing me
you should be healing your own pokemon
though
all right with you i think with you i
can't be frank
frank i thought your name was in rita
well you're secretly frank
i'm a bit shocked to be honest
i mean
you still look cute so
i can probably
accept it after a while it will take me
some time though
i can't afford to look wink in front of
the diamond clan's leader or your
commander but in truth i am frank
i sometimes wonder how i've ended up
with the bird inside bearer hmm
you see we have a warden in the
coastlands a lovely woman named paulina
but she tends no lord or lady and she
will not raise the successor to fill the
late lord's empty seat evil
some people have started to question her
worthiness to be a warden at all
but lina that is to say paulina
she's very dear to me no matter what
anyone might say
we were both in the running to become
leader of the pearl clan we strove to
surpass one another but she taught me a
great deal too
having said all of this i have a favor
to ask of you
please help her raise the pokemon she
looks after and her true heir to his
father the late lord
with the help of your strength i think
our late lord lord's heir would grow
into a wifey successor and if he
succeeds it should silence lena's
naysayers
i don't know if anyone might trust more
to help with this than the person who
helped the pearl clan by quelling
cleveland's frenzy
you'll be able to find lena up on the
headland huh
head down this hill and turn left you
should find a slope leading up onto the
ridge
thank you
cutie pie i wonder so far the npc's all
had ooh hello really great designs
yeah
so i'm excited to see another cute girl
design
cat
cat cat cat cat
i have a cat
there's another cat there's so many cute
oh so fast oh
it sits so elegantly
boop your nose
i got it i got your nose
[Music]
cute alina is unfortunately in a
relationship
well that doesn't mean that we can't
break her up
from her relationship don't you think
why am i running back i had a reason why
i'm running back i forgot ah i wanted to
craft some balls
although i could do that anytime i
forgot
oh you sure
i'll make a few more
a few of those
oh wait we have a leading ball now
ball is a ball that is too heavy to fly
higher for but is highly effective if we
manage
uh-huh so it's
just a better version of the heavy ball
okay i guess we can make a few
mm-hmm
alrighty
let's see
oh
i wonder if there's a new pokemon not a
burme behind this
and i feel like yeah we've been
disappointed but this is a new form
i haven't seen this one before i think
should i catch it does it uh oops
is that important to catch it i wonder
the different forms
catch him okay
oh please come on
yay
[Music]
leap out of trees they only leap out of
trees
oh berries
oh i can't [\h__\h] i don't have space
anymore
sasuka
what is that what is that
what the [\h__\h] oh
whoa
oh whoa
new pokemon is always so exciting to
see the new pokemon in an area isn't it
yeah funny now
well you know what i'll try
i'll just i'll just although this is
probably really high level ride this one
so
i probably won't stay in my pokeball
um
oh this one is 27 though
this one level 50 oh then i should be
able to catch it in
theory i've caught someone's attention
it seems
let me try to catch it oh
oh oh
oh
uh i don't know what what element you
are let's just buy
scuttlebee
oh i guess your
grass is or beetle
poison oh
poison only bug poison ah
so
fire is
indeed affected
try
he did not like that
sometimes it works sometimes it just
works
without fighting you can just catch an
alpha like that
it's kind of ridiculous but oh no
don't i want to catch you not fight you
oh what is that
all right
does that turn into y lord the big boy
it's so cute
um let's sneak up on it
i never use heavy balls
why it rolls like a ball
i'm not here
it's so heavy oh there it goes
oh
oh [\h__\h] oops i was boxing holy [\h__\h] it's
really heavy
uh
it's not so easy to sneak up on them
here there's not much to hide
it turns into nana with a beard
don't need to sneak
i don't want it to see me though
let's try this one
don't turn around sanity
sorry that must have hurt he died this
year
oh you stupid [\h__\h]
no wait
oh there it goes
is that
[Music]
pop pod no i don't want space right now
let me see can i uh
get rid of something maybe craft
something
um
i need those for subquest oh
then i'm taking them with me that's for
sure
each episode let's go
yay how far can i go
i don't want to go too far it's scary
you're sleeping it's sleeping isn't it
okay this one we can get come on
[Music]
oh it's so cute
oh cute
oh that was a heavy specimen
oh it was just lazing around on the
beach
let's fight one
don't run away gosh you're so cute
kawaii wanted it
kill it one hit come on
oh alpha strong style
the power
ah
kawaii i kind of feel sorry for killing
it though
it's just too cute
replace gyarados with it
should i i don't know but this one can't
use dragon skills
so
i know canada is
more useful i think
[Music]
water ice it has eyes
trunk also has eyes right now
i don't need dragon tap moves
um
uh hello
uh i haven't defeated them yet fire time
all right i've got it got it got it
let's go
what i left an island somewhere
i don't really have space
damn it
[\h__\h] hell man that inventory yo
you want to fight really you sure
what is that what is that
morphine
is that what uh
the evolution of the
burmese
cute i like moms mobs are cute cause
they're so fuzzy
mushy
with my flying ball
there oh
no [\h__\h]
god damn it
that was by accident
but okay maybe that will help me a bit
there's nothing else to catch around
here these go away pretty fast though
there's no small bombs
[Music]
craft that
let's craft all these
craft oh
oh
scatterbrain can be made with popcorns
i guess i'm crafting
all of those two
what is that
remedy
okay now i should be able to pick it up
there we go
[Music]
all right i'm gonna turn around now
oh
i wanna catch it
hey respawn so quickly
oh i'm not here
oh it goes so far
i got i guess it's i don't have to aim
so high with this one
oh what
there we go that one worked
i didn't i didn't uh quite know yet how
to
deal with the flying ball
how to aim with that one the federal
ball i used normal balls for get
outdoors by the way
sheesh sheesh
thank you for the pink for the orange
super chat thank you
uh
i'm getting used to throw them without
locking on but sometimes i tried locking
on but then it just does
aims
really badly
so
i kind of
kind of don't trust the locking
mechanism that much
oh [\h__\h]
damn it
what is it with you
you know what you're gonna get a berry
eat that [\h__\h]
tommy don't
[\h__\h] help
[Music]
okay you know what um
i'm gonna catch
you for a battle
if it must be then it must be
level 13 not bad oh it's getting night
time
faster
one more
no no no no no no
[Music]
what
you what mate
that's just
not nice
[Music]
magical leaf because we didn't have
anything else at least when we first put
that in there
i don't know maybe by nowadays
something's better
actually let me let me see
mummy is dead
[Applause]
that's what you get for trying to kill
a girl
poor archangel
this is karma
this is just karma
um you need to understand
okay
uh we have a leaf edge is that that's
that's not better is it leaf blade oh
that sounds good that must be pretty new
yes
that sounds good
um's changed she has leaf blade now
um yeah so aggressive
[Music]
kiana may run a corrupt restaurant
uh mods ban this person
[Music]
i don't want to do too much damage i
think i want to catch this one let's see
if it survives
it did survive nice
slander yeah that is simply
simply just slander let's
[Music]
is took the melatonin um
last night i feel like it worked pretty
well
i didn't take it too early because i did
want to watch some some netflix but i i
fell asleep definitely a bit earlier
than like an hour or two
more than usual
and today i'm going to take it even
earlier
oh there's something flying up there
that must be
the final evolution of that boob yeah
i think it helped
[Music]
it also happened i was cuddling with
smoothie while falling asleep
probably
alright now i got the tumble stones
oh big drifloon
oh
let's get that
[Music]
no thank you i don't want to go on the
other side
do i need to get a flying mount for this
one
it's the moody point
good daddy get out of here
never mind
i'm gonna continue exploring
[Music]
don't yell at me like that
i'm just
i'm i'm a big big girl
in a big big world
oh
not a hotel
uh
i don't know
what to fight you with your dark flying
i suppose you have a really cool hat
crowny
sheesh
roll out nice
yup buddy
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
since when
oh water
nice
[Music]
good job pat sparks this is such a bad
name man i feel like i'm bullying fat
bugs
final evolution
[Music]
yeah let's take a look
at the final evolution i have not seen
it yet i have uh not spoiled myself
i have not seen the final history
evolution of this pokemon yet
this is my first time
mata
i hope it's cool
oh
fancy glasses is that a pee pee
um
wait let me compare that to your actual
evolution wait is the the pokemon name
is still the same is it or or does the
name change as well
um is that fighting
is it flying fighting now
what fighting and grass no flying
anymore same name
this
pokemon this door
oh
[Music]
oh it looks pretty similar the uh
original also i never have i actually
have never seen the final evolution of
the og either
i
think this might be a first
i don't know so they both have glasses
the cape is just shorter
and he has a
a little attachment
on his crotch
and the hair is funny now
um
i would say the og looks better
but this is okay
i suppose
do you even see what's in front of you
you should cut your bangs this is like
me when i was a teenager my bangs were
always too long my mom always told me to
cut it my teachers were always also like
kiara can you even see [\h__\h]
so it's grass fighting now
no more flying huh
not much better than grass fighting
oh the og is grass ghost in the final
evolution
triple arrows oh
but this is uh now our first fighting
skill so that actually is good too
um
what should we what should we put in
aura sphere do you usually lose a blast
of our power from deep it never misses
that sounds better than triple arrows
they're both good
triple hours is a signature move
[Music]
i guess should i take both and get rid
of false swipe and roost
[Music]
hmm
wait what about air slash no you guys
say physical
this attack never misses
replace ariel ace
roost is useful for healing i've never
used it
um
rock smash
yeah should i not keep ariel ice i
realize i will keep it
i need i want at least one flying attack
um
okay
tortillas well we'll do it like this for
now
just triple arrows
and then we switch the order of some
other attacks oh well okay
wow
wow what
uh
am i going the right way
no i need to go
i need to go
you need to go up the mountain
i think
if that is so then i have gone too far i
feel like on it
can i go up here
oh oh ah here it is
here's the path
alrighty
we're going the high road
pokemon
that was close because it was flying
away
come on
oh come on uh
oh [\h__\h]
did you guys see on twitter uh oh my god
[Music]
um that little preview of cow carrots
video
oh my god
it made me also like watching that made
me feel so nostalgic about ocarina of
time
i want to play it
it's so old but i want to play it
not yet well kyle parrott is working on
uh on a clip
about um
about the whole story with uh circles
and he made a really funny intro video
where you know it's the ocarina of time
like
loading screen opening screen
uh when you ride in the horse and it's
me riding on circles
with the same music and all that and
then the logo uh remade into the legend
of cute kiwawa i think
uh
it looked so good
um
if i hit minus it will organize oh okay
it didn't feel that unorganized but okay
let me heal
um
[Music]
okay
oh i see that i see that
oh
hello
ah
wow it's threatening
it's looking pretty good from here
oh you want to talk to me
nice to meet you i just wanted to be
helpful what did you do
now oh aren't you the cervical spindle
who called the lady of the ridge well
listen to this a couple of eye pumps
stole my backpack full full of goods
ah where did they come from
they've been darting around leading me
on the chase almost like they're teasing
me i haven't gotten a whole hope of
catching them
monkey
monkey business it is
we must be used to dealing with pokemon
can you get my pack back from those ipob
they're uh they have a very different
name
in german i only know them by griffling
reject pokemon return to monkey yo you
got a
butt as if you were stung by a bee i
wanted to say oopsie i i wanted to catch
you to be honest but
[\h__\h] um
damn it
[Music]
i have nothing ah
finding oh
well that's helpful
fighting is the only super effective
thing i have
[Music]
mermaid can deal with those iphone as
well oh oh the stack will disappear okay
that's so i don't mind that at all but
okay
do i need to catch them or fight them
um
stealth catch
i don't know what i'm doing well hello
guys looking at you
you look like a person in a bird costume
well look at that
[Music]
[Laughter]
why
okay you can go away now
you can go away now
he's dancing
let me
try can i not actually uh
fight them and catch them without
fighting
hello
they disappeared
you're not gonna talk
oh bye bye
thank you for wasting my time well i
guess i just have to
run after them
what is that behind me
ah
chase him down what is that what is that
what what what no no no no
oh
i'm gonna catch you
cute they have such a beautiful smile
they look so happy
they look so cheeky
monkey
suddenly
threatening sounds
i don't wanna fight them they're too
cute
two versus one
so our new skill is apparently pretty
good
uh-huh
wow wow oh that looks cool
yeah mermaid's getting pumped
[Music]
wait should i try to catch it
oh wait i can't
i can't
[Music]
oh can i
no i can't
i'm gone
there is no choice but to destroy them
return to death not to monkey
to ashes
home sorry monkey
[Music]
at least you're together in heaven oh i
guess not
well well i see you chased down the eye
palm
and my goods are all safe thank goodness
how could i repay you let me think where
is the other other why is that
what
why is there only one left where did the
other one go
i oh it's gotten into you looking so
weak all of a sudden
one died off screen did he put it in the
backpack
what
maybe he did
that's the only thing that really makes
sense but how could he suddenly catch it
so easily
all right all right no hard feelings
just stop it with the sad look i wants
to be together with its friend so he's
gonna catch him both
oh
no more pranks
yes pranks
they took your what only your guard down
complete
bamboozle
got some exp candy
hold up
i hope we see some cute monkeys
on our honor what do you want on our own
time
sometime soon
maybe on this map
is the train the way no
good
good stuff and never paris dead
one day there will be no more paris what
do you want what do you want i don't
want to fight you
where's the volcano
what
look
that way
we have been led astray
but we're back
back to business guys
just gonna swoosh past those
uh
no space again
going back because i want to stealth
guys
this means
we're switching someone out of our team
because we need to make space for vulpix
[Music]
hello my baby
hello my beautiful beautiful baby
look at it looking so cute and tiny and
fluffy
come on come on
i'll put her into the team once we're
back in the camp
it's so cute
i've never had a nine tails before in
any pokemon game
i think
i think i always just wanted one
but i never had one before i think
although i think um trophy
i think i might have had an alola
uh nine tails
previously
in the
in the ds game
[Music]
[\h__\h]
headshot
yeah alolan ninetales is so cool
[Music]
um that is uh
oh [\h__\h] you feel the earthquake guys
oh um at that hand
oh god
it comes closer and closer a lot he's
coming
[Music]
i wonder what level he is
45 i could try to catch him oh yeah you
saw me
no no he if he fought he saw me
oh what am i doing sometimes i get so
nervous
[Music]
big chunky butt
can we catch it with this bowl
[Laughter]
okay never mind i'll catch a or i could
fight it as well i guess because i
didn't fight it yet
um
now catch another one
hello pigs
[\h__\h]
no it's gonna run away
don't panic
calm
barry i'm sure it likes the berry
uh do i have anything that looks tasty
how about a peanut berry
it's gonna be our prenup
ah i have to give it food anyway [\h__\h]
god
damn it
don't look at me don't look at me
yo
come on
[Music]
oh finally some bgm it's daytime guys
it's shitty winter though really shitty
weather sky tumble stone hell to the air
i'm going to try again to catch that big
chunky bastard
oh my god
don't tell the chunky boy that i'm here
just don't don't don't don't tell him
don't tell him
is it endurance stream no it's not i
actually i can't stream uh too long
today anyway
um
but definitely for another
uh at least at least three more hours
um
is that breakable yeah
okay let's go through
fluffy
messed up again
oh
lord he coming
he can't come up here right he's too
heavy for that
what can you
yeah maybe i'll throw a berry
um what berry would this boy like
what
stupid butterfly is gonna get in the way
again
is it gonna come back to his normal spot
looks like it
okay here go eat the berry
he's coming
you know what [\h__\h] that ball i'm just
going to use a great ball what
i didn't even see the eating animation
did you just gulp swallow it in a hole
wow
i'll wait a bit maybe he comes even
closer
yeah
i didn't save though
oh whoa whoa whoa
wow
yes
whoa
right in his butt
we got the junkie
[Music]
we got
a it alpha specimen
oh my god i kind of want to use it
oh
the big boy
remember in the last pokemon play for i
really wanted a pur ugly but i never got
one did i
i really wanted one though cause i felt
like they look so majestic
no one can tell me otherwise
with squishy nickel though
yeah they do appear very late in pearl
that's right i always saw the pearl
uglies in battles
um
but i never saw one or at least not
until very very late
on the field
what if i do a team with only chunky
boys
chunky pikachu
chunky chunk
chunky cat
[Laughter]
wouldn't that be beautiful
yeah only the fluffy chunky ones
no but then we have to kick out um my
what's i don't know what it's called uh
my kusogaki
is kusogaki is not chunky you know
i don't like that
i don't want to kick it out
you know what let me i need i probably
need some more
of those light specimen
uh defeated not any of them okay
hi
a cat team
um
dollar run away yeah
me too
oh i see that
chick that they were talking about up
there
let's uh throw a berry
here
[Applause]
i don't know what to fight it with
though
it's my cat adventure yeah
boy fight me
ugh
[Music]
looking so arrogant
come on please
give me a chance
finally
should be a one hit
okay that's one for the pokedex
hallelujah and now we shall proceed
and see
damn it
one second
um
and see what
this new lady has to say to us
i'm gonna craft those and
craft all of those
craft all five of those
that should have made some space
thunders
did i just get a [\h__\h] thunderstone
out of
that so i can get jolteon
or that too
what
how do i do that i how do how do i just
how
i thought that was for jolteon is it
raichu what what do you use for jolteon
then the same item
fat sparks can get fatter or does it
have to be a click on item on use
oh my god
same item
okay for now i'll use it on
on this boy compatible oh
cool
right
out of nowhere
the fat is
wow
oh my god i have a fattest sparks
i guess i'll change the name
um
or oh we call it obese sparks
[Music]
what's better
[Laughter]
sporks
fat is
sparks
the chunkier the better
the the more huggable
[\h__\h]
i run out of space it has it might have
to be f a t t e s t
o p e s e it has to be obese
fake sparks
do not like these sparks
is that too too real
ob sparks
oh ob spikes
oh b sparks
ball
oh b
oh b oh big spikes
it could mean many things ob spark skin
oh thank you oh they didn't even want
you to do that but look at him being big
whoa
you're huge
take it
oh
compare that to
you
oh you're not you're not losing to the
gala that's impressive no compare that
to you
it's very tiny very small
compare that to you
oh he's sleeping we woke him up well we
didn't actually wake him up from his
slunker but we can get him all out here
balloon oh that's dead [\h__\h] dead
killed by my balloon
wake up
oh he's so cute the whole gang is here
yeah oops i want to take a screenshot uh
yeah
cute he had a heart attack he was like
oh [\h__\h] a ghost bug
so
what does she look like she looks cute
from behind she has a
uh
volcano's voice
oh
hello nice to meet you
[Music]
settle down
who do you remind me of
she's pretty
[\h__\h]
hmm
wife out of 10 uh
yes
i'm not sure
i like her
uh but not quite my to be honest not
quite my marriage type
more like my
[Music]
my i look up to you type
i'm paulina of the pearl clan and who
might you be
ah so you're that child from the galaxy
team
i heard how you aided cleaver and
liligant when none other could quell
their frenzy
your strength must be amazing and yet
you have such a gentle face
so what brings you to the cobalt
coastlands
we have no lord here much less a
frenzied one for you to quell
our previous lord was swallowed by the
waves
he was rescuing his young pup that had
been swept out to the sea and ended up
giving his life to ensure the pub safe
return
if you were to guess which of these
growlithe
would you say is the previous lord's
child hmm
since you're asking like dad i'm gonna
say the small one
[Music]
oh you have quite a good eye
this quite skittish a quiet skittish
gorilla is the child of the previous
lord
it's cute fluffy too
i have no doubt this little one has the
potential to be a fine lord but
witnessing his father's demise has left
deep scars in his heart he seems fine
there are those who expect me to train
him more strictly and force lordship
upon him before he is ready but i could
never bring myself to do that
no matter what the rest of the program
says my mind is quite made up i'll stay
by this little one side and let him live
his life as he wishes
so why don't we use the other one the
big one you have
um
so now that you know our situation might
i ask your purpose and come into the
coastlands
i'm i'm i am
for this five-speed island i guess
a serbian fire spit island i see
there are rumors the place is haunted by
strange shadows these days you'll need
the aid of a pokemon known as basco
legion if you wish to cross the sea
you should speak to ish iska in origin a
word of the diamond clan he should be
able to help you
there is definitely something strange
happening out on firespit island those
shadowy figures are concerning of course
but then there's also the odd lightning
that came from that rift in the sky
lightning is a sign that the heavens are
angry i worry that we may have offended
almighty sinners somehow yeah cause you
didn't stream sparks enough
in this in the past the pure clan and
diamond clan were locked in conflict
over which side revered the true
almighty sinner
even if we've reached an uneasy peace
the true almighty sinnoh must be angered
because there are still those who
worship a false image of it
[Music]
ah but i digress i do apologize
isin lives on ipam hill just past the
ginkgo landing i imagine you'll find him
there
wow
those are pretty fluffy too i wouldn't
mind having the
one of those in my team either but now
we have
our vulpix
with the goal of turning it into a nine
tails
so
um
[Music]
yeah not yet i suppose
oh
dangerous
all right so you're saying i should
leave uh here and go
to all the way
[Music]
there
okay
what a waste of my time
all the way around the
island you can catch ninetales i suppose
i can
i don't see one here
you miss an unknown what
that's what was that white thing that i
saw
on the stone and i was like what is that
but it just looked like
nothing
hmm
but i thought maybe it's just like some
kind of
decoration
how do i
do i just catch it with a ball didn't
they say you can't catch them or you
can't fight them
oh okay
seems like you can catch them
i'm
our first
basically
oh that's an r ah me yes you
thank you thank you for letting me catch
you
you look funny
[Music]
hi kitty cats how's it going here
how's it going don't mind me passing
through my glamour is beautiful
horse which is not a horse it's a deer i
think
an elk is it an elk
[Music]
mustache
a reindeer ah
makes sense
[Music]
[Applause]
ah the cute
the cute energies
oh that's the evolution what the hell
looks funky
it looks like you know how in the
medieval times they were wearing like
white wigs on top of their heads it
looks like it's wearing a wig like that
it looks very funky final form nana
thing
it does look a little bit like ninji
but i'm not getting it no no i'm scared
i'm scared
evolution of voice out
[\h__\h] who's who's who is it
yeah following you
who
huh
ah you
holy [\h__\h]
stupid murkrow oh no no no
at least it's not very effective
um
i don't know what i have that's
effective though
i'll use ariel ace
pick up vulpix
should i
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
yeah baby
[Music]
one
hp clutch health
[Music]
yeah for everyone who is watching right
now keep in mind that this is the last
stream before uh my vacation
so
yeah
you might want to get as much
chihuahua as possible
right now
um thinking of going backwards
[Music]
uh
i'm gonna go back pick up the vulpix
you guys know at what level it evolves
[Music]
oh a firestone oh i don't have one yet
it needs a firestone only
um
interesting what are these dolls for
anyway
just for selling them
[Music]
when do you get those pokemon here maybe
i want to see my pokemon
so what is that beautiful beautiful
vulpix here which one should we take we
have two
where's the difference uh 99 55 54
66 56
61 1990
64 80 80. yo this one is much better
66 56
55 54 is that the level weight 229
ah 32 okay it is a few levels above
what about the
wait one one one
three
oh this one is all on hp
i don't know how that really works to be
honest but whatever
we're gonna take
the nature
where do you see the nature
search
or summary
nature
hardy
and
you you can judge that because i can't
hearty and adamant
attack up special attack down
party better
take the hardy one
this one is just hp up i guess
or nothing up actually
you can improve those things uh i've
seen with the powder stuff this one is
way better okay okay
um
[Music]
chunk is such an all-arounder i'm kind
of like
ah now this is the difficult part i
think i need to
get rid of chong because water we do
have when we have dark and black and
what do we have here and then
rock we don't have but
um
chunk
get rid of the balloon the balloon has
been pretty helpful so far but ah only
because he had fire to be honest
no my balloon i love my balloon
i love my balloon though
maybe at least for a while we can still
rethink it also
how about putting pearl ugly in here
psychic normal fairy dark nah if that's
the case we have fairy we have dark red
psychic actually the move set is pretty
useless
okay
does vulpix have any
other
skills or only those four
it does have more
ember
600 which one is better um
because this is a physical
it does have a ghost scale so that's
actually
actually amazing
you can use ghost it has the same ones
as
our balloon
flame wheel oh i don't oh i have
flamewheel already okay okay
wait until we get a good one okay
hello my pretty cutie pie your face
looks like smoovie's face
so pretty
can i like
bug up here i feel like i can
feel like i can go sana style
come on come on come on
come on
yeah
i
i believe
i can fly
almost fell down
maybe there was an easy way to get up
here from the other side anyway
but i
believed yo
let's walk this way i don't know what
exactly it leads me
i'm only if i can touch the sky
hey what is that oh
[Music]
there's more of you here let's see
shall we send our vulpix into the battle
oh we didn't uh have a oh you don't want
to fight anyway don't you
we didn't have a name yet
um
you're not gonna run away really oh [\h__\h]
i'm doing quite some damage
you're five levels above me so
[\h__\h] uh
i don't wanna die
what wait did i just drop the waterstone
i got three stones in this platform in
this episode today
the leaf stone the electric stone
at the waterstone is this normal
it i didn't even notice
[\h__\h]
what's up
oh god there's a obese cat
oh my god
why do i keep on getting all these
stones
water stone do you want to use that for
an eevee no not really
we have the water snake
after all
[Music]
definitely not that lucky in my runs
nice dodge
[Music]
well i wish i could give that waterstone
to you guys because i don't uh need it
i thought that was a mushroom
[Music]
get some at least some exp by doing uh
by collecting these things
i don't even care if i don't get them
you want to fight you want to fight
i know i have no space i know i know
i think i shouldn't be up here
[Music]
i'm not supposed to be up here
but i gotta go down there
fine can i jump here will i get some
damage
maybe a little bit
yeah we're good
okay we have taken a special route but
we have arrived
why hello there miss kiawa fancy running
into you out here me ho i'm on the hunt
for some plates
plates oh i have a couple
no need to be humble i see you've
already got your hands on four plates
yeah so you don't steal them you gain
plates when you quell friends at nobles
and when a great pokemon recognizes you
as worthy of bearing isn't that right
the way you've been collecting those
plates it reminds me of the ancient hero
um
the one that's said to have battled
against almighty sinnoh
wait who would that be what the [\h__\h] is
that me again from the past like time
traveling even further
behind
what the hell who would that be
you know i've been wondering the 10
pokemon that are said to have followed
the ancient hero their pals are supposed
to ten
you can only have six in your pokemon
team no
their powers are supposed to have come
from almighty sin or itself
why would they seek to challenge
almighty sinnoh along with the hero ew
perhaps we'll get some answers once we
gather all the plates
well let's both do our best to find more
but please don't over exert yourself i'd
hate for something to happen for to one
of our guild's loyal customers
not so loyal have barely bought anything
from your shop if anything at all
ash
i don't think ash was alive at this time
hmm
hello
knock knock
do i have a visitor i'll be right out
give me a moment
oh
[Laughter]
you look funny
oh i'm a mission of the diamond clan
stop looking at my eyebrows please
i'm a galaxy team member with a
celestial flute oh
and now his eyebrows have a funny shape
when he looks sad
oh you might speak one more
how have i um
he talks he also talks like he's kind of
like nervous maybe
maybe he's really like
like maybe he gets bullied a lot because
of his
head maybe his last remaining hair not
his eyebrows
well yeah i think it's his eyebrows but
yeah funny how those are so bushy but
the rest of his head is not
yes
well sudden visits give me quite a shock
i don't hope you'll give me advanced
notice in the future how would i do you
guys have phones
so why are you here
i need that water
mount i think
your bag looks like corn
mmm like a corn cob
yes i want to go to five spirit island
yes snack hmm
you have it
difficult
big hurdle
it's impossible
what the [\h__\h]
how
i'll tell you well i have the right
materials but i like them myself so much
i like to eat them well you see this
next part is something i could never
manage but you need to catch this one
pokemon that appears tonight which one
leave it to me
[Music]
its name fills me with durand
so the materials for the food have to be
imbued with the flavor by the dust
club's dark pulse that's the only way
you can make special legion's favorite
food
got it
[Music]
titanium
well the pokemon i need has only one eye
and can be found wandering around that
wood hold
ah that wood haunt is the area that
looks like that a hat ah
oh homer a lot of wrecked boats oh [\h__\h]
i tried very hard to avoid those
one-eyed pokemon so now i know a lot
about them you see
would you would you like to wait here
until night
yes
i think so who should i know
[Music]
he has a cute oval mouth though did you
guys see
he has like a cat mouth
what a funny weird character
all right i'm on it boy leave it to me
did you bring it no no i'll i'll i'll go
now
i thought you still wanted to wish me
luck or something oh monkey
monkey wait can i uh
not rest here
[Music]
oh man it would be nice if i could rest
here
let me and you let me in your tent oh i
can
can i rest
hi little hearted
oh he has a double bed but he won't let
me sleep in it
but the inside looks nice
nice tent
oh
and this looks nice does these tents
look nice
okay then i have to heal by myself i
suppose
sorry rubix i just wanted you to get
somewhere experience
my dear dear
cutie pie grab something
um
[Music]
i guess i'll just heal you again
yeah i wouldn't mind uh sleeping in that
tent actually um
one of my friends
recently
uh went on a vacation
where she um also
uh stayed in a tent for at least like
one night i suppose at least but it was
it was glamping it was glamorous camping
did i tell you that guys i want to try
that too
it sounds
sounds fun ah you speak handy
[Music]
nice
glamping yeah have you guys ever done
that
probably a lot of you have done camping
before but glamping
that's a different story
[Music]
glamorous camping
never have i want to do it but i don't
know where i need to look it up someday
ew maybe for a vacation maybe with ahmed
amy seems like the type of person who
would like to do some camping
or maybe a glamping glamping
glamping maybe
i'm i think i think she wouldn't would
like to do that
[Music]
maybe one day
i mean is the dirty camp but yeah she
brought she probably doesn't need the
glamorous part
[Music]
it's probably unnecessary but
i need the glamorous part
it's for me for me
i can i'll i can take up all the
glamorousity
and and she is she can do the normal
camping
[Music]
camping with a glamia
i would love to do that then you have
something sleeping
something cozy to cuddle with
i will i actually already caught a lot
of them
um
like i'll catch
i'll catch one more i guess i also have
to give it food
[\h__\h]
that was my trigger
my trigger
it went dove
i'll take the glam ammo can do the
ending
don't run away now
[Music]
it's
wow the rain is so strong is it always
raining here or is it just right now
[\h__\h]
i don't know i don't know i don't know
[Music]
just right now oh
i don't know why i only do sparks i
think because i want to promote sparks
yes i have a giant uh alpha rager yes
but i caught it when it was uh a pikachu
i think
yeah
was it
you know i i think i caught that one in
my free time right then i think it was
the alpha picacho
it's almost too easy to catch alphas
without
even fighting them
i mean taskaroo but
isn't it too easy
vulpix was up here uh up here somewhere
on the way to the edge of the mountain
thingy
good luck
do i still need you
banana for monkey
[Music]
yes it wanted food anyway
um
what is it it's weakness though
oh
wait [\h__\h] i'm gonna mess up oh i don't
know
it's not gonna it's not gonna be enough
fighting [\h__\h]
oh it's gonna run
anyway maven you are welcome
wonder if maven is watching the stream
probably not but you're welcome
all righty
honey
sorry for stealing your honey
uh
am i going the right way
yeah
at the end of the hand i think they said
water is way too electricity
the knife djm is pretty nice yeah
no just use this
are you looking for dust clubs yes i am
i know he will show up during the night
time oh i shouldn't waste too much time
then i guess because otherwise the
nights will be
over by the time i arrive
oh
something's going to attack me
i saw that i i i i
felt something i felt a disturbance
i didn't see it but i i i
i
was able to smell the scent
mina
[Music]
nice dodge ride
perfect timing
no
[Music]
um
maybe we'll find something while we're
doing this
oh
but i don't have space
wait a second
uh
no space this one
wait how about i use some of these uh
grit dust
use it on
who i'm gonna keep we're gonna keep
obese spikes
what should i improve chat it's already
speedy
maybe improve defense
um
more speed even more speed
okay let's just do it all let's just do
it all
[Music]
attack i don't know if it's a special
attacker so i have no idea what i'm
doing
sorry some of you must have face palmed
just now
um
grit gravel
[Music]
use this tool i guess
uh-huh
more speed
we gotta weigh out the
the weight literally
nothing uncompatible
defense maybe
for this one
i don't know
i just want to use up these
oh this is this is even higher
incompatible all of them are
incompatible okay no problem
and then i mean crafts oh my god it's
always the struggle with having no space
in this inventory for [\h__\h] sake
didn't breath of the wild have an an
endless inventory there was like you can
put like
endless amounts of items in it why
didn't if you if you had to make this
game so much like breath of the wild why
did you not copy that as well huh
you could have copied that too
while you're at it
[Music]
for who
can i go here
hey lilligant petty little ah
yeah i probably won't be needing that
then but yum so lucky
so lucky
lucky
oh those are the shippies
see the shippies
the wrecked ships
get rekt
oh there's some more interesting items
here
hello dribloon balloon balloon
whoa these ghosts
cute
they look cute they're so small
oh he's speeding that's the speed limit
my friend where did you find it
wait wait wait that was not it that was
not it
found it
[Music]
anyone know what to do with black orga
right
wow wow
for scifi turns into
what
for cleaver
it's really easy to get those items yo
you you want to fight me
now you don't and you want to oh [\h__\h]
uh i don't know i don't know what to
fight you with
no it's no more day [\h__\h] wasting too
much time okay then we'll spend some
time exploring
ah
run
i could not show them who's the better
bird i had mercy with them okay what is
that
what what bird are you you look cute
it's a music bird
shut up
you're gonna run away of course you're
gonna run away
[Music]
i don't think i've ever seen this build
before
yet
and there it goes of course
one more
i'm getting pretty lucky hell yeah
what the [\h__\h] is it with this bird
we are oil
that bird looks drunk over there
let me get you
pokemon
ghetto
[Music]
what about this
you like that doesn't it look yummy
why she saw this show
i have to feed it nice
come
on never catch one of those it seems
well then fly away
fly away then very stubborn yeah
why would you not want to be
owned by someone like me
oh oh
[Music]
forgot about that holy [\h__\h] there's so
many dead people
um here no i wanted to craft something
if i can
i can craft this one
what is this
aux power an item that sharply pulls the
fences under hook and during battle
these effects disappear
i don't think i'll ever use it but i'll
at least make it so that i get rid of
the
uh
[\h__\h] i should have made this one damn it
[Music]
14.
and attack buff i never used the adults
and pokemon games so
[Music]
i shall
i shall catch you
[\h__\h] that boat how
how's that possible that makes no sense
i was more than far enough
finally
[Music]
during daylight hours that's right
[Applause]
angry bird coming right at me um
i don't know what to do with you
but oh but you're already done fighting
me can i destroy this
[Music]
yes pokeball
oh
some trashes to be
stolen here
don't get this [\h__\h] stupid bird
right here
i remember that
but i have no time to
fight a stupid starling evolution
enough with your pranks now
why is this one so reluctant to get into
my ball
let's not get into my ball
it's a wonderful vacation thank you
i am
i
i'm i guess i'm excited to have a little
break again
but i am
a bit worried whether or not i'll do a
good job skiing this time
i want to
um do better this time to you know prove
that i am a real austrian
because it's kind of a scandal for an
austrian to not
hey i've been using federal goals
was that not affectable insuffedible
it's a scandal to not be able to
um
ski or snowboard one of them at least
believe in yourself
it's not so much
about that
but that was in hokkaido with cali that
was my second time screening in my whole
life anyway
uh i just
going
to ski
it's actually
in austria too
quite the expensive um
hobby
because the skiing pass
is pretty expensive
and if you don't have your own skis
which i didn't have until very recently
because they're very expensive to own
yourself then you have to rent
everything
that cost sex or too so i just could
never really afford it to go on ski
vacation
[Music]
it was out of the question
yeah i think skiing is pretty pretty um
expensive no matter where you are
i know
[Music]
so
so i hope i'll be fine i'll tell my i
mean my friend she will know
she will see that
i can't
immediately go for like a very difficult
um
how do you call it
how do you call it in english the
slopes i suppose
yeah i hope she'll go easy on me
and
uh
hang out with me on the easy slopes a
little bit
until i'm ready for more
another one
you're welcome
[Music]
one's in there
not a little
good stuff in here
[Music]
there's a fish
it's packing mine thank you i will miss
my cats too
you want to fight
it's so bright i can't see [\h__\h]
is pokemon games in water fights
the pokemon will always just stand on
the water which was never really
realistic i guess that's their way of
improving that
oh not bad something's bubbling there
and never no fish i want to try catching
you but i'll probably get like some kind
of water balls later anyway
and then i'll have more than enough from
you stupid fish
[Music]
where does the raft come from well
naichu has bought and installed
installed raft
i suppose by the way
just see how some
is it music playing game
no
did you see how
uh
japanese members have been playing a lot
of rafts these days i don't know there's
every now and then there's some kind of
game
hype
first arc then a little bit of raft
they've been rafting yeah i wanted to
raft with someone too
and at the same time when
when i was thinking about inviting
some girls to to raft with me
uh
fauna was asking
yo who wants to play raft
and everyone was like me me me me me
what did i actually drop here
sticky glob
green kink
actually so many people wanted to play
raft that i said how about we make two
groups
uh
and then
yeah split up
rather than having like an eight-person
raft collab i feel like
eight people in a collab is like
usually
not desirable
but i don't know depends maybe on the
person
[Music]
eight would be madness right
i figured as much
[Music]
oh
now i think four is a good number but if
you like start a raft game with four
people
um i've read up a little bit about on
how it works but can you only um
play it again if the person who first
hosted it
is available
[Music]
or can i go back to the same raft at any
time even if they're like offline
[Music]
what
i have uh two waterstones now
okay
[Music]
and this is black all right
lucky phoenix
very lucky it's not getting nighttime
anytime soon huh
can i
i can't teleport there
i have to speed
let's go
[Music]
if i find an npc i can make a camp oh
that's what you meant with uh i can camp
i wasn't i thought you meant like i need
some kind of item
to camp
anywhere okay where is that dude
will the quest show me if i mark it
um
[Music]
which one is that
this one
oh
well that one
[Music]
he's on the head how did i not see him
is he hiding on the boat maybe
am i blind
ah
there you are
i suppose i'm blind
hello
[Music]
oh you're here i've been waiting
sorry
oh no well you're not the person i was
looking for
you're right should
you're still somewhere
[Music]
somewhere here
maybe under the boat
i feel like that's
where he could be hiding
hello
there's a chest
[Music]
cool stuff
no no no no no no no no no is he on the
boat
no
[Music]
am i blind on one of the fingers oh
okay well i've checked out pretty much
everything except like this one
[Music]
that pokemon is bothering you
those always run away from me
so stay away
wasted
why
oh it's repeating you
ah a parrot
talk talk
having fun
no the opposite help me
[Music]
oh now you're gonna fight me really
you're not gonna fly away
[\h__\h] i have vulpix out
but 31 maybe 31 by now is uh strong
enough to handle a battle
[Music]
wait music oh my god
no
uh i'll try
[Music]
i'll try
it's to mimic me
oh
the flame wheel is not going to help you
against me
[Music]
come on kill it
yes we're getting yakitori tonight
yakitori
[Music]
pokemon isis looks so fun yeah i've been
having a lot of fun with it
um you're welcome
back when we're accurate folks often
said that if you hear someone talk when
nobody's around it's not a ghost playing
tricks it's just a chateau
anyway thank you kindly for finding your
rich i'll have him set up the camp now
you're done you can
we desperately needed one
there we go
thank you
for that
it's uh but if that's scary one night
pokemon is here i don't know if anyone
wants to stay here
yeah yeah it's gonna be useful though
that's for sure
um
[Music]
let me sell something
um
[Music]
i'm going to sell oh i can also sell
stuff from my box
let me sell this
actually i don't need to sell i could
just move it there i have even if you
even have a sunstone
crazy
i
need to
speak to my box
this can go
there's this
this
oh beans
um
[Music]
don't need this
and just work with this for a while
and this one
this one
okay
these
no i will not say it guys you can't make
me
you can't make me
oh now we got a lot of spots open but i
feel like they're gonna be filled up
again immediately oops
[\h__\h]
so confused
can i craft something
no
okay let me rest until night time
[Music]
ah the cyber revolution item oopsy true
i can put that away as
let well do that
oh this one
don't don't i never use that either i'm
gonna move that on that one too
okay i feel much lighter now
[Music]
all right then see you guys some
animation
where was it supposed to be what is it
huh
which can be found around deadwood haunt
during the night and take it with you to
isian's home
okay
i see it
uh so i suppose it's a ghost pokemon
what do i fight it with
um
is it like berries
i try to catch it normally
oh wait there's more than one wait does
he just want one i thought there was
only gonna be one that like appears
specially
[Music]
oops
obtain dust clubs which can be fun that
was dust clips right he just wants one
i'll catch another one or i'll fight one
well i don't know
the try with me
good morning guys club
not a hodor
[\h__\h]
yeah
it's gonna be a
bit difficult
no um wrong pokemon
super effective dark
uh ghost super effective oh yeah vulpix
i will
go with
big snake maybe or junk
i haven't used big snack that often
[Music]
slimmer down are you let's go
show us what you got
a strong crunch please
just like that fried chicken always
tastes like
it feels like
crunch
[Music]
pokemon
is that the
uh what it looks like before the
evolution oh [\h__\h]
oh
you're
trying to escape
yeah oh it's so cute
they grow up so fast
okay i see
i see how it is
it does look like that sunset
[Music]
oh wait i'm fighting both
i don't know
[Music]
okay
i don't mind the exp
oh
not so much
[Music]
out well by the way guys yesterday i had
a what i told you guys i had a recording
ride [\h__\h] where am i
uh very early
at like i think it was like 10
am
yeah yeah that was uh
again
i'm i'm
not gonna say all the participating
members but it was again with eov
i do stuff with easy so often these days
but like
i have yet to collab with her normally
but we were like in the discord getting
together
and i was like oh hey your feet and
she's like you again
yeah what's up
again yuffie and kiwawa it's like we're
like the choice the perfect choice
for
official stuff
yotori
the only place we ever made this for
these kind of
recordings
i don't know what it is
it's like we're bound together by fate
or or by the management
russell
hello sir i did the thing
it's not that scary man
not that scary
yeah she's a nice girl here yeah
don't bring it out okay
you're gonna give me the mouth now
uh
i need you to be accepted by it but
julian give the signal you have and you
have that dust bop stuff yours
use its dark pulse huh
oh you want me to use that pokemon
oh
do i have to oh okay the game does it
for me
oh
three
two
[Music]
sleep with me
and go
what's gonna happen a delicious aroma
laughs for the air but surely g on his
favorite snack is not ready
looks uh poisonous
okay ginkgo landing
okay
we're gonna get the mount to be honest
um
i could have probably assumed it but
uh
i
i didn't really
i wasn't sure yet if we're gonna get
like a
water mound
until
i was spoilered against my will
yesterday yesterday by the german
nintendo account
they showed like a clip of the water
mount and i was like oh good to know
that there is a water mound but i kind
of didn't want to know
they spoiled me
damn it
wow i was waiting for you oh
god that line the way it's written there
it's so
sweet let me pour some water
some of my fresh filtered water
damn corporate okay
i feel like
it's it's not it's not been that long
since the game release you're already
spoilering me man
he's a sweet guy yeah
hello eshen
ah they look so cute together those
three
oh ballina i thought you said we
shouldn't be seen
that's what you meant guys
i'm sure kiawa can keep her secret you
two are together
besides both i and the growlithe pups
were eager to meet with the great batshu
legion again
i i see you well in that case let me
summon my solution
yeah
you loosen it
wait what secret they didn't even
explain to me what secret
it's not so unclear maybe we still have
a chance
oh
splash
what
hmm
you look for funny
[Music]
funny buddy
question mark
um
you're i like your tail
very pink very cute very cloudy thank
you for the membership welcome
funky fish
ghost ghost water fish here
you can give food to blast religion okay
it has the same color as the pokemon
funny
that's it
oh
a great passion legend
thank goodness i was a little worried
about where the best legion would accept
this favor
so
thank you
hmm
isn't it a bit small i would have
expected a bigger amount but okay
let me write you
my pony
squash plate
it's my water pony
[Laughter]
okay okay stop talking
stop talking now i can't speak anymore
my voice my voice needs to be
chilled
but so you it yeah tell me
i mentioned to you before how the
previous lord rescued his grow lift pup
well
during that incident ishin and patron
legion saved my life as well
since then
i felt a great deal of affection i don't
care shut up not i didn't want to know i
don't need to know
i truly adore him
but i know there are those who speak ill
of me behind my back
so i try to meet with issan where there
are no prying eyes to preserve his
reputation
[Music]
you'll always just do it what any decent
person would do when i saved you
perhaps but nonetheless after that day i
found the strength to accept crowley as
he is and not force him to become the
next lord and it was all thanks to the
courage you showed me is in
oh perhaps we should save the discussion
for another time after all later in my
tent you coming
you already have a tent
right here
sorry
oh the girls are back
i'm the eldest and i'll be your unlucky
charm
but you spotted a full leaf clover well
i'll soon have you seeing double i'm the
middle sister than one clover you can't
pick
heads i win and tails you lose you've
got no chance in this game of fortunes
i'm the youngest coin but i'm definitely
not your good luck piece
we're the misfortune this is not across
the front line the pixel and you look
stressful
now get ready to hand over close
no
you want to take my partner if your aim
is to pester us with bad jokes those
ridiculous introductions of yours were
more than enough haha roast them
yes exactly what you said
leave it to me guys leave it to me
gengar she's a king car now
oh no
wait did they take the big one because
they thought the big one
would be the one
did did they take the big one
[Laughter]
they don't have the intuition that i
have
okay
[Music]
we can't live the kind of lives we want
because of narrow-minded groups like the
diamond clan of the poor clan if we want
to live freely in the great land of
history we need to have powerful pokemon
on our side
uh
don't worry we'll make sure this pup
grows up nice and strong we'll even make
him alert for you
let's take the mother to our camp and
get to work no one will bother us no
place so miserably hot but like can any
pokemon be a lord or is it like only
like with
something that's a pokemon that's
in the same bloodline
what no prolife
special ones
i could have definitely done something
there but okay
what should we do okay why it's an
emergency
[Music]
oh i've never actually had my partner
battle before you have a partner
may you help us that growlithe is a very
very dear pokemon to me please save him
they're sad they weren't going to a
place where nobody would bother them the
only place around the cobalt coastlands
that seems suitable is firespin island
oh now that you have the best legion to
help you cross the water you can rinse
an island too
yes
of course
[Music]
yes
you're gonna come too okay
[Music]
you're not gonna come okay
yeah yeah i'm on my way go go go go
jump once again in the air to go even
higher
and throw items from best relations back
to in your case i guess that would mean
throwing pokeballs to catch pokemon
okay
it's watertime traversing a lot of the
bastard legion press the plus button or
the aim button when you're in the water
to summon bastion legion and crush the
water on his back while riding
bachelorette on you'll still be able to
throw items what's more when bastard
legion jumps into the air you'll have
more time to adjust your aim before you
throw
yeah
how does that look
i thought it was a
i guess
not am i not deep enough right
huh
it i just don't want to drown
oh do i have to have to ah okay
okay okay
what do you mean i have enough time to
adjust my aim i would like to aim when
i'm still but okay
[Music]
a double jump
wow
magical jump
now we have such a big world ahead of us
you want to land on there can i
oh
thank y'all enjoy my vacation thank you
soon
i'll see you after the vacation i
suppose
uh so how do i
just jump back in
okay but i suppose that
if i don't activate it for too long
i'm eventually gonna drown
i'm guessing
[Music]
okay what is that stone
oh oh what is that what is that
oh
cute what's it called
i've seen it before
uh okay let's try the catch i suppose
i wonder if a flying ball would work
well
because these are pretty fast
zooming hmm
it's gone actually no
man take
cool oh here is that other color
um boy
gotta catch it
we have to catch it
the blue one because we already have the
pink one but we need both colors for
that fashion quest again
easy
[Music]
and thank you for the membership
let's catch another one
oh it's daytime
nice i prefer to be on the big white
ocean when it's daytime so
better for me
i think i
don't really need any more of those two
lines
six out of six now
where are we going
where am i going
fire spit island
but i think i just saw uh
see that purple light over there
go go go go go
i've seen it from very far but it
disappeared
but what's there i swear
what's wrong here
oh there it is
so why did it disappear
i got it i got it
thank you for the membership oh hi small
thing
yes indeed
you didn't see it
you have to look better
get some glasses
i'm gonna miss my cat
oh
let me find you
bye my smoothie
uh oh you ought to switch to bastard
legion not a whole dog
raichu is rafting again
well
it looks really funny
i mean it's probably better than him
just swimming or
uh floating
in the water
okay so jump
swing
wow
[Music]
no it's gone again
come back
wait there's a wall
whoa
oh come back
did i get it i got it
this is is this the evolution
i don't even notice me i'm not
close
oh
come on come on come on
damn it
let me try again come on please come
back this is not gonna come back
okay i'm gonna
uh swoosh over to the main quest this is
this is the right path it should be
this ocean is huge man
jump when you throw makes it easier
how does it make it easier
[Applause]
parkour
alola writes your form
apparently you can get it but not until
the end of the game so i don't have it
what was that oh
uh the
uh the tentacle
pokemon
and some more fish oh
i want to catch you
one of you please
would one of you like to join me in a
pokeball
[\h__\h]
oh oh what what what what it's right
there
yeah
okay that's gotta be it that's gonna be
it
yeah those are really cute
fish pokemon
damn it they don't seem to be bothered
much by noise though
and also not by having balls thrown at
them
[Music]
i like making circles
i'm gonna try i'm gonna try to catch one
while jumping i guess i don't see how
what what was that
maybe one more time
[Applause]
why
why would i do it like that when i can
just catch it like this okay now i kind
of threw it into the water but
damn it
jump first before aiming
slow motion
oh
[Applause]
that was a slow motion moment there oh
is that what you mean
oh let me try again
jump jump
oh oh [\h__\h]
how long is this gonna where did it go
dunking it like in basketball
oh this is it didn't want to stay in but
that's okay
all right good to know
oopsie
birdie 60 uh that's pretty fine i always
say 360. 360 no scope
is that 360 no scope
it's the evolution
look at that
[Music]
oh it's mad is that an alpha
looks like an awful
yeah the music now says it all
hello
can i know
[Music]
what if i go from here what is this
what are those
stickers ancient stickers
they look like pokemon
oh there's the the ball pokemon
wait aren't these from the future
they shouldn't even exist yet somehow
are these all the legendaries
looks like it yeah
dan said no pokemon go
where am i
want to go here
shouldn't have gone through there okay
we're there we've arrived
grow some form
[Applause]
finally land under my feet again
yeah
oh
that's cool though it kind of uh makes
it feel
makes the world feel very very big with
that big ocean now
oh yeah
we get interrupted by ishin certainly
hot enough to feel like a sweat bath
isn't it
oh i like the music here
oh
turn that up
you hear that
[Music]
oh that's that's good stuff
i hope they have that running all the
time though because like
most of the time the bgm disappears
after a while
no we've got a ghost about it to deal
with on top of the heat
i'm very sorry but do you think you
could lead of course i knew i was gonna
lead anyway
[Music]
oh
oh oh
[Music]
that looks like a slushie
[Laughter]
oh guys oh she uh by the way um
my russian snack box
arrived
uh
but yes yeah buddy um looking inside i
have to say it it doesn't look
i mean i can't really judge because i've
never been to russia but it doesn't look
that russian
so i actually looked up
um on amazon if i can buy any russian
snacks on amazon
i didn't think i would find anything but
actually you can buy a [\h__\h] ton of
um russian snack boxes
on amazon either even
and the snack boxes
on on amazon
look
pretty
convincing they look more like older
snacks so i feel like if i could do a
mix of the
the ones ooh that i uh got from
the one service that i ordered the one
the first one and then combined it with
the one from amazon
that one is really big though
but yeah i think i'll just combine it
[Music]
so because i don't want another
i never you know
korean snack bugs moment where all the
snacks don't really represent uh korea
much
same with russia i don't want that to
happen
[Music]
i want to catch you not kill you oh wow
i got a firestone
what
[Music]
if we if we didn't get the nine tails i
would have used it to get a flareon
clarion
what's going on
nice
don't look at me
don't don't don't don't
[\h__\h]
oh
are you pretty far away ah
no
[\h__\h]
wasted
do you want berries
respawn right in front of me
who gets it who gets it
grab it
[Music]
you want to fly okay if i get the other
one can we wait a moment
yeah
uh i'll kill one and i'll fight one oh
no you only you're participating okay
cool with me
a baby one and a big one yeah those uh
they actually have a size difference on
on the map
surprisingly
let's see if i
can keep him alive and then
catch him
yeah looks good
i'm burning though
not
not feeling very good right now
[Music]
yeah the other one is bringing the
bananas
to the to the camp
yummy
sliver don't die
oh he switched from burn to poison very
nice of you
please
oh finally
so
russian snack box reviews [\h__\h] for
[\h__\h] sake
is gonna happen after my
after my trip
um
yay
where are
there
i hope they're tasty
the thing is it just looks says to me
because there are like two
two um chocolate bars in there with
a german brand name one of them milka
and one of them alpengold um so
i mean they might be
they might be a version of it that they
only mostly sell in russia
and that's why it's special
but it's just
i'm just like yo
i eat milk up all the time here in
austria
and elephant gold couldn't sound any
more austrian to me
even
it
it's named after the alps so
i mean okay there's alps in other places
too but i feel like
we have some pretty dope alps and it's
german the name is german the name of
the chocolate
isn't milk a swiss yeah but still like
it's one of those
the most popular chocolate somehow here
in austria feels very german to me or
like yeah swiss german austria
switzerland german austrian we like to
eat milka chocolate
how do you all notice me there's nothing
to hide here man
[Music]
well maybe russians eat milk a lot too
are there any russians in the chat right
now
have you ever heard of
the chocolate alpine gold
is that so common in your country
i am
where are the russians where the russian
i've been called is a russian what
right i've been going all the time okay
okay okay
it's really popular oh
oh good
that's good to know at least even though
it sounds so german if if it's something
that you guys recognize then we good
and while i was looking on amazon i was
like okay if you have russian snack
boxes what other snack boxes do you have
i wonder so i was looking up i'm not
gonna fight you
i was looking up um
some other countries i tried like mexico
snack books they didn't have any mexico
snack boxes
unfortunately
um they did have more america snack
boxes a lot of american snacks
um and a lot of them looked pretty legit
they had like nerds and hershey's and
[\h__\h] so
it could be
a good choice to
go for if
we want to do um a public american snack
box review because we did we did that
members only one but that one was not
only american it was a mix of all
countries if you remember it had
pop-tarts but it was not only american
so we have yet to do a
american snack box review oh that one it
looked like it had it had blueberry
pop-tarts
the one that i
saw but to be honest
if it's an american snack box i might as
well just ask one of my gen mates or no
uh not germans but like anyone from
um
whole life english
to send me
their most recommended snacks themselves
and then they could get me one of those
one of the good pop tights
one of the good pup that you guys were
like swooning over
what was it again was it something with
cinnamon apple cinnamon or something
like that
we can get our original and then even
get like a little bit of the preference
of whoever's sending me the box
we will see what they like probably
i can't do that with every country
obviously but with america it's very
much in the reach
um
cinnamon
i need to go to an idol meeting i'll be
right back guys
i
i'll try to remember that
okay in a moment
[Music]
do
get that controller
i brought no one with me this time my
cats were a bit slow i think they were
in deep slumber
trunkers came by but she was like a
zombie
yo
okay i think we're gonna do some
fighting
um
gengar probably is gonna be my opponent
i don't know what's strong against ghost
besides ghost because now i don't have
my ghost anymore
[Music]
any recommendations
yes sleepy drunk guys
i can evolve no i cannot
wait
okay
oh because i have the firestone
right oh [\h__\h] i didn't realize
i forgot
ah it has hicks true oh
so early
oh my god
[Music]
majestic
nine tails
whoa
the floof look at all the loose tails oh
i wanna brush you all day
gorgeous nine tails
wait it doesn't have we didn't give it a
name yet we need to give it a name
[Music]
i have a name
wait for it wait for it
so fetch so fetch
so fat oh my god
it does look a little bit like cubie all
right
she is so fetched
i'm so proud
oh my god nine tails
[Music]
honestly you look like smoothies still
meow
to you too my beautiful darling you're
so fetched it's not gonna happen it is
gonna happen fetch became a thing
all righty i hope i hope you're not too
weak to fight these
stupid idiots i think i have one more
exp candy though don't i have one
oh no i don't
apparently i don't
but i could raise your comp
your your thingy you
know something what do you want to have
raised
what do we want guys
[Music]
special attack
speed
[Music]
okay
oops no not that one
this one
[Music]
wow the music is pretty cool here as
well
i should check for moves [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh come on involve already
it won't
we've done our homework any pokemon
gutsy enough to come to this lava trap
is supposed to evolve so get all of it
already it's not fitting that we evolved
nine tails here then
you will become stronger like it or not
help me
[Music]
oh look the pest again snapback sisters
i'll take care of her girl apple my snow
smash is full to pieces oh
ice
should still be fine
and of abdomination of snow fire and ice
i i read that as extra sorry
okay well uh
i don't want him to attack twice
four times a week to fire oh well then
yo
i am not extra sorry for defeating you i
don't care how that looks well um
bring on ice pokemon here in the lava
area to begin with is kind of weird it's
just gonna melt by
standing here
you know mama snow can't fight at full
power and crazy heat like this it wasn't
a fair battle exactly but you should
have thought about that beforehand
in fact how dare you make for obama's
snow battle in such a street yeah that
was you that was not me that was you
no no that's
any sandy stator
yeah thank you for saying it you're the
one who sent out a bomb of snow sister
go on then toxic rock pour out some
poison oh
no
another battle
right away okay
oh
oh perfect that we're we're in with so
fetch again we have something effective
oh but it didn't kill
whoa
[Music]
that might miss snail right because i
got mudded
[\h__\h]
[Music]
hold
on [\h__\h] mud
flying or
flying
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] if we had a flying skill on sliver
because now it's not even stab anymore
on mermaid
ah
but okay no problem though i mean he's
pretty much dead so
well that was unnecessary
[Music]
you killed my beautiful nine tails
that is so not fetch
unbelievable
um
ah i guess i lose the coin toss
sometimes
i did warn you then i that item i didn't
want you didn't i that i had a score to
settle with the galaxy team
all the pain and suffering i experienced
after coming up here from the county
region
to work i'm going to make you pay for
every last
sign right
what you what are you gonna use genga
and ryden
right on time
[\h__\h]
[Music]
sliver boy
can we one hit it without that i'll try
go go go
wow good job
yeah
and now gengar
oh i'm feeling drowsy
do i have crunch
please let me use it
please please please to trust
[Music]
is so powerful
okay chunky boy
need you to survive
don't sleep
crunching real good
with your teeth show him who's got the
better teeth
[Applause]
i mean gengar has quite the bright
smile but
um
trunk has the sex appeal
yes although gengar looks also very
chunky gengar would also be a good
member for a chunky team
how how could all of us have been
hey tom i healed off the bomber stone
coins toxic you wanna fight again
now i can keep battling until we run out
of potions and revives just like kiara
when she was fighting that [\h__\h] and in
pokemon pearl
but no
ah
they're gonna
maybe she changed her mind now in order
to help she's gonna let him become the
lord after all
hey no one invited you tiny
you're really going to insist on getting
in the way you little runt
take him down toxic croak no
i know it's hot but hang in there obama
snow smash that runs is that the only
pokemon you have
well if please stop you cannot beat such
foes
paulina what are you doing here i
thought you were waiting with growlithe
little roller
i was but then he jumped into the ocean
without running a swamp all the way oh
imagine that little girl name just doing
his best
to swim and paddle paddle battle battle
battle
battle battle imagine imagine paulina
picking him up and he keeps on paddling
paddling
into the ocean when he was terrified of
the ocean after it swallowed up the
former lord his own father
face
yes but master ben's father wow
gown
he's a fire type must have been pretty
rough for him
who's talking
oh it's happening he's becoming the lord
everyone get on your knees
[Music]
wow
is that a
a new
form like a
cinna form it's true bravery lay not in
crossing the sea but in finding the
strength to face hardship head on
you gotta be joking why the puny one
involved
uh sisters something's not
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
he's three for him oh yeah buddy
oh
oh whoa whoa
did he just now literally now that turn
turned into a frenzy isn't that the same
dude
it shouldn't be glowing
like that
oh the timing
what
[Music]
oh
well then we can take him down right
here right now what's happened with him
oh strange lightning hit him he's become
friends he looks just like the other
nobles oh that's exactly why i didn't
want to come to this island
oh he looks cool though
[Music]
everything was going just as we wanted
before it awful ruined everything enough
of the sisters will leave this place we
won't be making any living without life
without our lives
now get out of here i need some space
right now
this will be uh tough to dodge because
i'll probably fall into the lava a
couple times
hey wait this is all your fault
we should get out of here too molina
yeah leave it to me just leave it to me
and i guess that other arcanine
let me do it
ah erita
what are you going to do about quarter
lift i mean arcanine
night
that dear little pokemon is my
responsibility as his warden it is my
duty to protect him with everything i
have
hmm
what must we do to quell his frenzy
please tell us what we need i don't know
i don't know
what we'll need to make some bones
bombs erita what are you talking about
i'm the leader of our clan is it so
surprising that i know a little more of
these things than you lina oh [\h__\h]
didn't have to say like that
i held my tongue the first time but now
i must insist stop calling me leader
[\h__\h] fight snickers yeah for both of
them
what
what calm down you two
and yes i'm well aware you're our leader
rita how could i forget that you were
the one oh she sounds a bit salty
you who can use your celestia flute to
summon pokemon and have them carry you
to even the farthest reaches of vast
history
i've learned a little about these
frenzies as well there's a special
method for dealing with them we can make
bombs pouches containing a mix of the
lord's favorite foods and throw them
from a safe distance isn't that right
kiawah
yeah can you do that for me i kind of
want to just stay here for now
um i do always carry some of cruelers
yes you have it with you
[Music]
why isn't once again your thoughtfulness
saves the day
now we can make those bombs right away
okay
dig down that's good
[Music]
they're ready
okay wow we're dealing with another lord
today then it seems
um time to save
okay i hope this time i make it first
try my last time was a bit embarrassing
but this time the
battle arena
looks a bit tough
to be honest
um
i fear
failure
is uh coming upon us but
uh oh yeah are you girls gonna heal are
they gonna heal
are you
can you
can you heal me do i have to do it
myself
i feel like they might heal me but
um this one is hard
you don't need to heal
i want a revive sliver
[Music]
they probably i feel like they will
because then i ran into the last lord
the battle thingy
and was like [\h__\h] i didn't heal and then
i got healed
you'll die many times it
teleport away and back oh
can i uh teleport back here
oh i can
oh
let's make it daytime then
oh [\h__\h] it's raining
i hate rain
now i'm here guys don't worry about it
i did save beforehand i think
before healing
okay
[Music]
green god the late lord act arcanine
would launch devastating attacks after
standing still and gathering light
around himself
uh-huh
remember that while you're doing dodging
while you're dodging moves will slip
right by him i know
okay
when he's like
surrounded by light that's when i have
to be more careful
cute
[Music]
when i play i have some uh cat toys with
me
no
it looks very frightening now this this
this one looks the most threatening
but if you guys say i will fail then i
probably will fail
and pounce
oh he's doing it where was i can i
actually not accidentally fall into the
whoa
into the lava anyway
i wanted to go to the side
come on do it do it then do it then
how is this gonna look like
it's taking quite some time next time i
could throw some stuff at him when he
does that
[Music]
okay
if i were to attack uh
i just want to prepare the right pokemon
uh uh
oh [\h__\h] was that the moment oh [\h__\h]
was that the moment though
[\h__\h]
what are you gonna do
oh i should i should focus on him
oh okay we have some time with some time
but i'm probably gonna die
i don't know
i'm not dead yet
[Music]
rock slime
well um
so much for that
okay
[Music]
good attack twice
no i'm not gonna make it
i'm not gonna make it i'm not gonna make
it i'm not gonna make it
what are you doing
i tried to dodge but i don't know maybe
the timing was off or where i was too
close but okay cool cool cool
cool cool cool
restart
what they mean with continue battle
did it say continue battle
[Music]
it's interesting though that he doesn't
necessarily go for me but he goes for a
specific route
like if i'm standing here he could just
literally go
come at me but he doesn't wanna
oh
okay i never mind i'll go somewhere else
then
where where is swiss is that always at
the same place
a bit
how the [\h__\h] do i dodge that
i have to stop it how do i stop that
i have to hit him
huh
i can't dodge it oh
oh well
is he gonna do it again
no okay
very repetitive right now ah probably
if i'm always here it's gonna keep on
running up and down but if i'm like more
in the middle he's gonna do the left and
right left and right that's actually
pretty good okay oh
okay uh
[Music]
i was
a little bit too close
[Music]
what does it mean to continue the battle
will i just continue at the same hp uh
that he has but i will be healed
checkpoint i guess it's probably better
to do that
you're just gonna you can carry over
some of the problems you've made
baby mud
[Music]
it's oh hot here
i cannot go i'll go there anymore i
suppose
he's too close to me
[\h__\h]
okay try coming here then
[Music]
oh
how do i stop that i have to
eh
how do i stop it then
what do you want him
now i could go
[Laughter]
[Music]
i tried
i kind of want to do it from the start
it's kind of too lame to start restart
there but
um
[Laughter]
gamerovian okay straightener because you
said that i'm gonna restart the battle
because you're making fun of me
i know you're making fun of me so i'm
restarting
no not here not here not here
okay
i will give myself one checkpoint if
need be
ah
okay uh wait um
that's how you do it well now that i
know that
[Music]
now we don't need to i think it was a
one hit
it was a one hit actually
let's go
[Music]
spam those bombs faster you [\h__\h]
what are you doing what are you doing
i need some private space social [\h__\h]
distance yo
[Music]
[Applause]
okay i can take some damage this is
oh [\h__\h]
how do i how do i stop it
[Music]
stay alive stay up
now now you can call me the gamer but
you can mean
it you may mean it
down
stuff good stuff good stuff gamer chill
hell yeah i'm the gamer lvn
[Laughter]
that didn't
take that many tries as i thought it
would but it was very very exciting the
the
battle arenas are getting more and more
difficult because the first time it was
so easy because you could just run
around the tree and
he would always bonk against the tree
and then in the in the uh in the one
that we had uh at the beginning of
today's stream
it was like there was no place to hide
but it was at least a pretty big and
round simple flat
arena
and then for this one
there's uh
barely any space to move around and it's
very uneven um
because there's so much lava in between
so i i suppose it's gonna get more and
more difficult
what do you mean excuses
i'm not excusing i'm just talking about
how more difficult it gets with every
time
oh look the strange light has left
arcanine and is vanishing into the
space-time rift
oh
now we see it properly
wow
looks so cool
wait so you're saying
you're telling me that
if i get um
this pokemon instead of
my nine tails
that this one would at least have a
super cool new evolution
now i'm thinking about replacing nine
tails it's unbelievable but i can't have
two
fire pokemon but this one would at least
be like a a new type man a new not a
type but new new look i mean
but nine tails is so cool too it's so
pretty
i need a firestone for this one too
oh maybe if i get another firestone i'll
see it as a sign from the gods above to
tell me to get this one
because i know this is nor arcanine it's
[\h__\h] strong as hell
oh i could get alone nine tails later on
yeah
is it easy to get the this one i suppose
you just catch a normal one and then and
then give it a fire stone
anyone didn't i didn't want to play
pokemon i never said that no
plan to the point i am at now time to
mute the street so super chat oh but
you're still staying thank you yeah i
don't know how much more i should play
though today because i still gotta like
do stuff like clean and reception i
suppose and
preparing to pack and stuff
there's an alpha nine tails somewhere in
the island oh
you mean what happened to my mouth my
mouth is normal
if you do decide go get an argonine you
better name it go fetch
why oh oh because i can't go fetch
because it's a dog why that's so funny
why are that so funny from sofas to go
french so fat you guys replaced my
girlfriend it actually makes so much
sense are they in-game mouth i see it
it's just too bright for you guys
probably i see it actually
go fat
that is
a genius move that is literally
fate is asking me to do that
because i called nine tails so fetch
this is fate speaking to me i need to
call it go fetch
oh my god
look he looks so big and fluffy and cool
oh my god i always wanted a dog
what could possibly lie on the other
side of the rift i wonder
come
this is the ghost
there can't be two
ah
[Music]
oh oh what you make me cry
now i understand
oh that was that was sweet
my little girl live ah no i misspoke
lord of the isles
arcanine
you and i must now live apart so that we
may attend our separate duties
[Music]
oh sorry wow
from now on let us each strive to
fulfill our duties as lord and warden
oh now she's a proper warden
now go lord arcanine your realm awaits
[Music]
wow
lord of the aisles go fetch
no i always will not be the lord so i
think it's okay
hey
oh was the only one was i the only one
who felt like they heard the cry of the
previous lord arcanine earlier no
how long i certainly do you liar you
heard it why would you say you didn't
boys i hope you're joking i'm usually
scared as it is why why what am i to do
if i start hearing the cries of ghosts
all the time
no need to worry ishan i only kid i also
heard the voice of the previous lord
calling out to us it seems i wasn't the
only one watching over his young pup
this whole time no
yeah you have my heart felt i think
they're having a heat stroke that's why
they're hearing these voices
yeah but my heartfelt thanks for helping
my dear little one the new lord arcanine
wow
ah
i'm sorry to ask even more of you but
please look after erida as well of
course she's not taken yet after all
unlike you
now then listen i believe we'd best be
off
titty
kayala
i wasn't much use just watching from the
side was i
you know when lina wouldn't raise
squirrel live to be the new lord and
people in our clan were doubting her
fitness as a warden i urge her to put
roller for the proper training but she
snapped at me this poor pokemon saw his
own father died she told me is it a
one's duty to force a child in such pain
through that training
those words left me with much to
consider
and even when arcanine became lord of
the isles and girlfriends did all i
could do was watch
that's not true
please all i did was arrive late and
help explain about the bombs something
you could have done without me is that
so praiseworthy let's give her a hug kfb
she needs a hug
i will volunteer
i know i'm so
i'm such a hero
do i deserve to be recognized for such a
slight contribution
i took on leadership of the pearl clan
so young with no grand vision for what
it should be still i tried to respect
our lord custom old customs insights
even as some called me old-fashioned for
it
but watching you i finally see i know
what i want to do i want to protect this
vast land of hissey
grant me another battle someday kiawah i
want to battle alongside my partner so
we can grow strong enough to be there be
of help to you and to broaden the
horizons of the world i see
yo how about next time you battle me you
send them out one by one and then not
all at once otherwise i think i'm gonna
have to decline
looks like i've got lena to thank for
yet another lesson that i've learned i
should let her know and hear more about
her relationship with arden easton while
i'm at it
oh she's cute
look at her be cute
okay
here's where we parked for now kiawah i
need to get off this oven of an island
[\h__\h] sick
i'm in love
is this what love feels like i think it
is
this must be love
doki doki doki doki doki doki doki
well that one wasn't there before was
that
she oh wait what no it wasn't that's a
baby version isn't it
something i got on it
[Music]
nice
it's so cute how he's singing over there
mac b
whistle
[\h__\h] oh uh hello
you wanna fight maybe cuz i don't mind
fighting either
my baby
oh so cute let me take a look
wait
from here
look close i don't know can you guys
look close it looks like it's out of um
super mario 64.
and then
now it looks proper but you see that
difference now it looks like literally
super mario 64.
and then
[Music]
i think you need to look closer but oh
my god
[Music]
it's cute nondeleto
gondolas very cute
finder [\h__\h] stone
unbelievable
i just i just cannot be stopped guys
i just can't be stopped
um where do they report the commander
kamado oh all right all right let's do
that
that might be the end of the
gaming portion
yeah we already have a thunderstone so
we can have two joltons now
[Music]
hmm
oh we can make this one with candy
truffle
i make some stuff
[Music]
okay
let's go back then yo i've been for a
lot of [\h__\h] today man you have no idea
11 10 26 wow that's pretty pretty good
[Music]
oh
look at those
look at those what are those
14 000 poke dollars for all of that
trouble
[Music]
oh
it seems you've made some new
observations let's have a look
illuminating
indeed come on
yes
splendiferous is that really a word
results i dare say you've earned
yourself a promotion to the next rank
yes i have yes
i think so
let's go back
poke stocks yay
with this much uh
uh
advancement we i think i have a lot to
catch up on in side quests
uh look at all those new cyclists look
at them
i'll have some stuff to do
before going to sleep and so on on my
vacation
i have like so much stuff
uh to bring to this ski trip
i can't i'm not even gonna bring my
laptop so
yeah
i think i only bring my phone
bring as
few things as possible but the switch
the switch has to
has to come with me
i need my switch
wait let me uh get my rank finished wait
that was uh downstairs oops
[Music]
switch is essential yeah
oh y'all what do you think impressive
huh
oh
four stars
wait fifth the fifth star
oh
it looked like four to be
[Laughter]
wing balls sixty-five
[Music]
five
okay fine
five stars
even better
fetch oh my god
[Music]
okay next stop is uh commander
we will tell him that
that area has a new lord now thanks to
me
[Music]
stop trying to make it happen no
you stop stop trying to stop it my cat
baggage what
thank you sir every sarah
not only the galaxy team but the pro
clown as well
i do hope your efforts will also have an
impact on the space time rip somehow if
we're able to get rid of that rift it
should clear any lingering depths about
your origins
okay so how we might actually close the
rift i haven't the slightest idea
don't worry about it we'll just kind of
throw some stupid bombs at it if we if
need be
remain true to the mission
gotcha
that's it
oh
potato mochi time
[Music]
tastes a bit different than us because i
use the pokemon's flames to roast them
oh
[Music]
that must have been if only i had
journeyed to the fire spit all in to
witness the event myself
would you even ride on basilis for sure
legion in the first place professor
what are you trying to say are you
saying he's fat
rude
god now you know my coordination is so
poor i couldn't even hit my own pokeball
and i can't dodge pokemon attacks to
quite literally save my own skin
of course i can't possibly alright i
talked to fear some beasts like foster
legion
well that being said
hey i'm gonna touch snow not grass
we all do well to remember these wise
words
the every strawberry soul is rewarded in
the end
do i sound scary
and strive for sure for the sake of my
research i will surely ride a pokemon
one day and record the experience in our
pokedex for all posterity
[Music]
oh yeah yeah just you will watch
i don't know what you sound like
i'm having fun with the english language
the next day
he has a
a food child in his belly
hmm
he ate too much potato martini
who are you
you look [\h__\h] up you do remind me of
someone though
[Music]
good morning good lady who came from the
sky commander kamado told me to let you
know he awaits your arrival in his
office
[Music]
you know that guy he's from all the
games oh well really guy from black and
white what
what
diablo i have your next orders you must
go to the coronet highlands to quell
another friends and noble electrode lord
of the hollow
electrode has a propensity to store up
electricity in its body and then unleash
it
but since electrode became frenzy those
electrical outbursts have become giant
blasts
we'll be enlisting the pearl clans aid
and securing your safe passage
to electro's seat a set word to the head
we're dead do you read asking
no no you don't have permission to go
out there
or say but i'll be stopped by the likes
of you now out of my way huh another new
character
another new character there's so many
characters
[Music]
uh dear
um
hey ho bassman kamado i thought it might
have slipped your mind to send me an
invite so i took the liberty of stopping
by anyway
mary what are your manners we're having
an important conversation
well there's your issue right there
adamant how exactly did you attend to
discuss electric without me it's mighty
warden here too you're the warden oh
[\h__\h] you're the white in
dub
there's no more to discuss we've already
asked kiwawa to quell the lord of the
rings
oh come on it's not one of the rings
it's a lot of the holo is it me you're
trying to humiliate you or our entire
clan besides do you really think it's uh
this flimsy little noodle
[Music]
that is quite the insult
commander i'm sincerely sorry for this
headless interruption
look at his face or her face i'm not
sure but look at the face he looks so
disgusted
i love the hair though i do love the
hair
[Music]
paint no mind it seems even security
corpse personnel i trained myself cannot
stop once so
[Laughter]
that being said
it's very tall
or it's just that the hat that makes him
tall
it is clear that the security corps
needed even further rounds of training
from me later oh he's very mad
hear that melody the security clubs will
stop themselves to sleep tonight thanks
to you the commander sumo moves concern
even bold is flying
[Music]
if there's anything you might assist
with
please assist please uh
now go
uh yeah i would love to have that hair
color
looks so fetch like oh my god
listen melanie the galaxy team well at
least kiawah is amazed at least at least
oh that's very nice saying like that all
the others are like
useless but me
[Music]
will prove it follow me outside
you have a baby
i have a baby too
look
oh my god is this what happens when you
when you make pokemon meet one another
or is it just because they're like the
same species
that's so cute i can't take it i can't
take it
what
um
are you the main quest
go around with me you bit
i suppose
huh
oh you mean i thought we were walking
around you mean you were battling around
oh
oh [\h__\h] uh
interesting
battle
[Music]
[\h__\h]
i should have seen that coming though
oh
we're gonna
send out fetch wanna see some action
hey don't follow the rules yeah
okay these these eevees must be
intimidated intimidated by my beautiful
beautiful
nine
[Music]
evie tails looks around okay
i could literally like hide underneath
the tails
so
beautiful
what do we do with you
[Music]
kill it
make it feel our wrath yeah
for them not following basic
common sense pokemon rules
we see how good kiawah is now yes no
more sneering at her
now i think our helper from the borough
clan was going to meet you at the
training grounds once you're ready
till later kiawah glad to have your help
as always
the training grounds
shift yourself
shift yourself is that a way of saying
[\h__\h] off
[Music]
i know it's not a normal land but it's
common sense to
you know fight one somebody one-on-one
like even human versus human you
wouldn't do that
it would just like not be unless you're
there with the
goal to kill
whoever your opponent is
but if it's a battle like this
then you know i feel like it would make
sense to
have common sense
[Music]
ah
yes
uh yes
um
yes
okay
oh
i suppose we're gonna do that next time
[Music]
yes so
i'm supposed to go over there
but
i will read super chats now because
i would love to spend more time with you
guys but i have to get some stuff done
so
thank you everybody you may still stay
if you want to have some more time with
me because i'll be gone for a couple
days um
yeah i can't even tell you when i'm
coming back
um but yeah
it uh it
it will be after a few days
[Music]
i'm not leaving on a jet plane no
i'm not
leaving on a jet plane
don't worry it won't be a dumpling
so i won't be singing the song
it doesn't apply
right now i said i'm not leaving on a
jet plane
i'm not leaving on a jet plane
yeah it's maybe if you have some
archives to
catch up on then maybe it's a good time
to do that um or enjoy your time
watching something or someone else
if you wanna um
yeah maybe like a good time to
um detox from kiwawa always good to
and do that so that you don't
um
don't get sick of me
oh
15 days i see
fifteen days hmm
[Music]
okay like yeah that was a little bit
critical you know yeah
man i'll miss you guys too i miss my
cats too
you guys and my cats man
sad
but
oh thank you for sad thank you mary
i i i'm
a bit worried about the trip but i i
will try my best to um enjoy it
and make the best out of it and
hopefully not get hurt
yeah now let's uh go read the super
chats from today
so that we don't have anything
to um
you know
no more work piled up clear it all up
before i leave
[Music]
i'll miss you boss i'll miss you too
excited to hear about the trip yeah i
mean i don't know how much i will tell
because it's literally just me going
skiing
i don't know how many exciting things
will happen but i will write everything
down and document it
okay let's move charlie masada
oh wow
[Music]
hmm
okay
fixing the chat just one moment
that chicken always is here to welcome
me always the first one
where are the guards
to protect the door while they're
intruders coming in here all the time i
mean not that i mind
it's cute to have a chicken always say
hello like that
yeah i need some tangents uh you may
have noticed today but
yeah there are some days where
even i the mother of tangents can't
think of any
it happens
it happens sometimes
[Music]
so i hope that this vacation will give
me some
oh so
um
music wise you know what this one is so
repetitive um
did you try the melatonin yes i did last
night
i did i did it was fine
i slept pretty well
there was one time where i woke up in
the middle of the night because jonker
is usually there very quiet
uh during the night
but this night i don't know chunkers
decided to zoom
and uh
not really filming but she was very i
don't know suddenly she was very
interested with the dry flowers that i
have
on the side of my bed
and she kind of looked like she wanted
to munch on them and i was like stop and
i just kept on pushing her off of the
nightstand and she kept on coming back
and i'm like jonker stop and i kept on
repeating that
several times
and she wouldn't stop so i had to move
the flowers into the living room on the
shelf where she couldn't reach stupid
chunks
but besides that i slept pretty well
usually usually my cats don't do that so
i'm not even that mad um
but it was disturbing
can we hide in your suitcase
you're you're coming with me in spirit
um
i will i will still be active on twitter
um at least once a day so
yeah it's not like
i'll suddenly be completely muted
i'll be around
i'll be around guys
uh
huh
[Music]
now
let me close the game
[Music]
animal crossing ish music thank you sean
i'm really scared of like oh going down
those slopes i i have ptsd from that
hokkaido trip [\h__\h]
[Music]
i hope there's like a baby slope man
i hope so i didn't really look it up
i don't know what kind of slopes there
are
leaving on a ski trip
the problem is like
i
i can like move around in the ski if
there's good snow but i i remember when
i first learned skiing that was the
one out of the two times in my life that
i went skiing i was but i was a child
it was a school trip
um
thank you
yeah
don't run no stay
uh i remember
i told this before but i learned skiing
on a school trip
and i was in the beginners in the
amateurs class
in the beginning for like one day and
then the teacher was like okay you're
getting it so i'll put you into the
um
normal group
which i was really excited about and
yeah it's a bit loud isn't it
i was really excited about it and and
and then um
that slope was
pretty exciting uh it had some pretty
uh adrenaline inducing
curves and [\h__\h] it got really really
fast um
my problem is that i
i'm kind of too scared to move my skiers
in a way that
uh you should in order to stop
to uh pull the brake basically i'm too
scared for that
uh because i feel like i'm gonna do like
a front flip if i do that
that's my my imagination at least yeah
the pizza i can't really do that so what
i do when and when i need to stop i
always just like
like i i i slide it out you know
that was uh also
basically the problem in hokkaido
that and the fact that i just had too
much speed because the snow was terrible
and on that uh slope where we were at
[Music]
so i just normally i choose to just
slide it out and it worked a few times
it worked
a couple times in hokkaido as well
i was just like zooming down that slope
straight pretty [\h__\h] straight
but then the last time i zoomed right
into a fence
and injured myself and thought i was
gonna die out oh my god time for a
re-debut
but i don't remember
me being that [\h__\h] when i was a child
i i also didn't really know how to stop
besides just sliding it out until until
i have no more speed
but
the snow was nice so i was at least able
to do some curves you know and be
somewhat in control
[Music]
so i hope that
uh this time
the snow will be kind to me
that i at least have some chance of
survival
[Laughter]
yeah and hey i bought like a whole
[\h__\h] set of equipment i have my own
skiers now and my own helmet and my own
shoes skiing shoes
and my own skiing underwear and my own
skiing suit and all that i bought a full
[\h__\h] set of everything ski socks i
even have skiing socks
yeah i have my own stuff so
uh i hope it's worth it because up until
now it was also just um borrowed uh like
rented stuff and i can imagine my my
friend also said so my friend said um
if it's like rented then it could be
that it's either like pretty low quality
or it's like so
so overused that
um
you know it might not
work so well anymore apparently that
happens with skis as well
yeah
[Music]
so hopefully everything will go well i'm
so scared i will tell you i will update
you on twitter if i break something
i'll update you as soon as i can if i
die
yay
[Music]
sure my friends can like
help me because the thing was with
callie
um while she was very eager to just go
into it she was very much a beginner as
well
more than me in some ways
so she was definitely not in the
position to teach me anything but my
friend that i'm going with this time
uh she is very skilled
in skiing she goes like several times
every year
uh so she knows what she's doing um
she has your own equipment as well
i don't want to never respond i would be
the same person but yeah i don't want
another respawn either
uh the hockey stop not the not pizzas
hockey stuff
not quite sure what that would look like
ah you mean like go like a curve like a
cool curve
to the side
i think i know what you mean
like swoosh
[Music]
that kind of stuff turn 90 degrees ah
gosh that's scary i can't i think i
remember me trying to do that when i was
a child
but i could only do like pretty big
hockey stops
pretty big curves
pretty rounded huge curves but it kind
of worked like that combining with
trying to lose speed by
the distance
is what i was doing
[Music]
but it was it was uh always very um fun
even though the slopes were
pretty terrifying to me even the
beginner slopes very terrifying but it
was fun the adrenaline was insane
[Music]
who here who here has uh
skate before and who hasn't
and say
say
have if you have or haven't if you
haven't
[Music]
uh
have
you know what i want to do a poll
this this
doesn't help me
or snow have you
you skied or snow
boarded before
yes
no
[Music]
not allowed for medical reasons oh man
well that you know what that keeps you
on the safe side
sledding does not count
never seen snow what
that's so crazy
[Music]
miami wow
or you can water ski
right you can water ski in miami
[Music]
what
62 percent no
[Music]
that's quite a lot
yeah
i guess a lot of you maybe live in
places where where snow is not really a
thing
i want to do another poll
[Music]
i just know where you live
yes
no
[Music]
no no no
no
[Music]
yeah that's a problem too it's expensive
a heavily optional
[Music]
going skiing in austria in april oh
in april
that's still that should still be skiing
season
but i think it's like around the end of
skiing season
[Music]
oh this one is pretty
almost 50 50.
[Music]
you know what i'm gonna bring some
pineapples over here i have some cut
pineapples that i gotta eat before
the day ends
[Music]
i love food oh my god
food
i want to marry food
oh my god
[Music]
you
pineapples
[Music]
supposedly good for my fruit as well
no it's not that korean pineapple drink
just pineapples cut
they only sent one drink
and i i finished that like on the same
day
[Music]
okay
super chat reading should not take too
long i know you guys want to be with me
for long for as long as possible and
since i'm nervous about my trip i almost
don't want to leave either
yeah but
but i gotta do what i gotta do and i'm
probably gonna enjoy it so
let's just let's just do it
do it just do it
don't wanna say goodbye i don't wanna
let's just not say goodbye
we won't say goodbye anyway because we
say auf wiedersehen and first of all
that's not goodbye and second of all
it's it means to see you again
[Music]
don't worry we won't say goodbye in
german yourself with using
[Music]
thank you
alrighty
are you guys okay with this btm or do
you guys want something more exciting
um
oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h] i still need to record
something quickly today i think
i mean it probably might kitty be fine
after my vacation
i need to record today though i just
need to record some harmonies from
uh for the song cover
it should be pretty fast i'm pretty
quick with harmonies as long as there's
a guide
i'm still [\h__\h] to record i'm so too
i don't even know what what animal i
should go for this time
[Music]
what can i imitate
a monkey
[Music]
tiger i did tiger just a little bit ago
i'm a good monkey i know
i don't know if i'm proud of it but
i i just need to record myself laughing
and then it will sound like a monkey
[Music]
a spider
oh for that i think
i might do that another time but what
[\h__\h] sound does a spider make no no
sound at all just say hi
i'm spider hi
[Music]
a cricket dog
anyway mr cat's big stan kitchen
top five cutest pokemon okay okay okay
tangent there you go um
let me let me see
um
one of them
[Music]
i think we must all agree
because it's in the name
and it's you guys
[Music]
execute
eggs egg cute just kidding no it's not
on my list but it's a funny name
[Music]
no
i think um
well if we do a top five we could fill
it all up with uh eevee evolutions but
no we're not gonna do that
um
let's say let's say
we're not gonna include any evolutions
because that's not fair
i think
i'm looking at a
chart right now
um
i think
this one
this one's pretty cute
dragon there
maybe we might kick it out later if i
see something cuter
[Music]
vulpix
it's [\h__\h] cute
especially the alolan vulpix
go with the alolan specifically because
that's just
beautifully cute
and then
[Music]
damn
there's so many
it's once it's one color pokemon
topo five youtubers
oh that was cute that one's so cute [\h__\h]
oh
it's not fair i can't do a top five can
i do a top ten
i want to do a top 10.
um ferret
cute
top notch cute
[Music]
honestly centred is also up there but
looks so similar to ferret
wait does ferret turn into central
or the other way around or not at all
[Music]
center does turn they're both cute their
count is one they'll count this one
okay looking for gentry
[Music]
i have to i have to put this one in here
uh plus landminam i'm just gonna put in
this one though
too cute
i mean all the [\h__\h] pikachu pokemon
in this game
they all
they all are [\h__\h] cute
[Music]
paulie and palin
i live
this one
chime chill
[Music]
does nosepass get a pass because of his
nose
what is that name
okay let me look for gen4
[Music]
we've seen a lot of gen 4
uh
[Music]
in
pearl and in the game that we're
currently playing a lot of a lot of
gen 4
[Music]
pacifist
has to be
in my top 10.
and again one of those pikachu pokemon
i i can't not put it in here
[Music]
besides that
her
purgley whoo
perfectly am i gonna put you in my top
ten let me look at you again
nah
nah maybe not
[Music]
cheddary is cute but not so special
well it's called gen five
in five to five to five
gen five
five
wow they're starting to look crazy in
gen 5.
starting to look pretty
weird
where are the cute ones
oh that one is
weird never mind looking at it closer i
changed my mind vanilla
i think the idea of it is cute an ice
cream
cute
what's cute
this one is [\h__\h] cute
oh
so fluffy what do you think it is what
do you think it is
whimsicott
it's so fluffy
[Music]
wait a molga
what does that look like again where is
it
oh wait this one also so cute
oh [\h__\h] mintino
[Music]
damn it
one two three four five six seven eight
nine
[Music]
looking at gen 6 right now
six
[Music]
doesn't look that
mind-blowing to me
oh they have to then cute like it looks
exactly like pikachu
wait a moca
i found it now [\h__\h] mug is so cute
why are there so many cute pokemon in
that gin
how is that possible
oh my god this sprite is so cute
[Music]
upset
kawaii
[Music]
look at it
oh
[\h__\h] no i only have one more and
[\h__\h]
how can i choose
oh
it's not fair
[Music]
rowlet is so cute
i want to put rowlet in here
rowland is one of the cutest pokemon
ever
[Music]
okay wait i don't actually have that
many pokemon left anyway
yeah gen 8 doesn't look so cute
jenny looks fun but not so cute
i think i can
with good conscience
put
[Music]
rabbit
as the number ten
okay
[Music]
these are my
top ten without evolutions
cutest pokemon
in existence
what do you think pretty cute right
[Music]
not considering what they look like
after evolving just in that state that
they're in now although for some of them
even the evolution is a banger
cute
questionable
hmm
peter is cute too mimikyu is cute too
[Music]
wait
only one more that i would put in here
[Music]
from the uh gen eight would be more
pickle
pickle pickle more pickle pickle
more bacon
i love that one i actually have a
plushie of this one in my bedroom one of
the few plushies that survived the big
cleaning
the big throw out
that i did where i threw out everything
it's not really being used though it's
in the box
[Music]
wait i'm trying to clean my pineapple
huh
[Music]
you know most of the things i um
most of my things i had to kind of
throw away because uh
yeah
um
i don't know
when moving yeah skinny i know skinny is
[\h__\h] cute too i saw i was thinking
about it i was looking at it like
it's difficult
anyway
this was the first super chat and it led
to me going for pokemons for a long time
you can't do this to me thank you for
the membership
yeah big girls don't have plushies i'm a
big girl now
[Laughter]
also i needed space on my bed for my
cats
all righty
[Music]
recommendations ever watch uh show it
crowd no it's like big bang theory but
way better plus british
um
you know i wanted to because you guys
recommended it again um
like yesterday or so i wanted to watch
uh what's it called again though
something's happening it's always sunny
in philadelphia but i looked it up and
it's i can't i can only buy dvds on
amazon of it no no digital version and
most of the dvds are not even available
right now apparently but
the only streaming the only way of
streaming it is getting another extra
streaming service that i don't have
i already have
netflix
disney plus
amazon everything that comes with amazon
prime then an extra extra one that's
called stars play
um
and i feel like i have another one that
i'm i can't think of right now
i don't want to get another [\h__\h]
streaming service
what i'm thinking of maybe um
getting rid of stars playing again and
then switching to sky
plus at least for a mo
a month because that's where uh always
sunny in philadelphia is on
for me
the one that's available
in my country at least
yeah i'm watching arrested development
on netflix right now not my first time
but holy [\h__\h] is so funny after all
ah
what a show
what show arrested development is oh my
god it's a trip
[Music]
okay
can't mix that's already the second
tangent and i've been reading free super
chats
show recommendations for
[Music]
a tales of bears area by the skips out
of steam
and pizzas
[Music]
um
game recommendation for while i'm gone
[Music]
wait what was that
what was that again oh this one oh [\h__\h]
i don't know
[Music]
why is that window so big
atelier isa
hmm
i suppose so but that really is like
something that if you don't like that
genre you're not gonna enjoy it at all
and
[Music]
yeah i mean if you want to play
something really good tales of brazilian
play it play it play it on steam
um and if your pc can't take it then
that was the wrong question to ask me
thank you
and have fun i guess you know
oh i feel like i played ninokuni and
watched the movie
um
long time ago though
i think
uh is that on pc i played it somewhere
else i think
[Music]
but definitely very good as well yeah
but bezaria is one of the best tales of
games it's also the one that came out
before
tales of uh arise
uh
the other big one that came out before
that and so i think you should enjoy it
has a great story and great characters
it got a pc port aha
i see
okay continuing
thank you
[Music]
ah
welcome back hi to you thank you for the
red super chat
thank you
thank you thai tea
are you gonna miss me tai chi
i hope you'll still be there when i'm
coming back all of you
mike weber
shut up
steven gardner thank you soon
[Music]
both times you play legends i have found
random shinies this time was a shallows
one man
i want one too i wanted to get one today
maybe i'll find one off stream
she kind of fears
[Music]
you know the old lady
resembles a kodokura or little people
that live under butter bird plant leaves
from ainu folklore that i know being a
tribe in hokkaido that even has their
own language very few speak speakers now
though
[Music]
you got some deep lore there damn
you found the shiny logs right and
that's why luxia what the [\h__\h] that's so
unnecessary
[Laughter]
to get both of them
oh
[Music]
it's your alarm but that makes sense
know i i i said laura because just
because not saying that it's not real
but
[Music]
theme sickle thank you
that's the cheat
codes the hacks
of uh north american kiwawa watchers
[Music]
hits with ease
is
have a wonderful vacation chimpkins will
definitely miss you but please enjoy the
time with rmd hope you can chill and
recharge your phoenix power at least a
bit and have a lot of fun pass off the
alpha i already can't wait for the
tangents we love you thank you
thank you
it's also nice to be able to spend some
time with rnt again because both of us
have been very busy
and um
yeah we kind of haven't really met since
our last vacation
uh i mean we met like once when she when
she when i got when i locked myself out
and
i picked up my keys at rmt's
um
but yeah it's been a while
knew
she's a a very
comfortable
fellow
she's
um i think a good travel partner for me
because she's the she likes to take it
uh when it comes to like beach beach
vacations and stuff she also likes to
just chill
and take it easy
and um
she's not really like a party person so
she
she wouldn't
go
she doesn't feel the need to go to
parties and disco and party party she's
very chill
[Music]
very sweet
yeah
and she enjoys
uh
a good wine and [\h__\h] but she doesn't get
like crazy drunk which i absolutely hate
[Music]
so i thank her for that mm-hmm
yeah she's so
very nice to be with and she
she's so easy to talk to
and uh
i don't i don't get annoyed by her just
being there some sometimes some people
you know they have an annoying existence
was she sweet
yeah
[Music]
uh she is into pokemon so we gotta talk
with her about pokemon gonna show her
the new pokemon game yeah
where was i did i read the whole thing
hope you can chill and recharge your
phoenix power at least a bit and have a
lot of fun pass off the elf i already
can't wait for the tangents we love your
tension thank you
as i said there probably won't be too
many tangents but i'm thinking of doing
like a i am back stream again where i
show you guys photos and stuff
um of where i was and what i did
uh probably if i don't get too much
content together i might not
maybe my fingers are always freezing so
that i can't even take photos who knows
but i'm planning on doing a stream like
that so the first stream after coming
back should be like a report like a
zatsu hmm
[Music]
ah don't talk about it don't mention it
i'm gonna miss them too
i don't want to think about it
i'll have to annoy the person who's
taking care of my cats
a lot asking her to take photos from me
of my kitty cats
[Music]
i miss them already
gonna cuddle a lot with them
before i go
nah they won't be coming with me i
already have to
carry a lot of [\h__\h]
already
um
yeah i need videos helicopter parent
no i have cats not a helicopter
[Music]
enjoy your skiing location with rmt take
care and looking forward for your
amazing pics and tangents yay gonna try
to make you guys a little bit jealous
with some cool
photos of snow
wow so exciting everything's white
but no i try to take some cool pictures
i will try
[Music]
see on the blue burp app yeah the blue
blue twitter
[Music]
marzipan
is that just a mexican word for marzipan
because we have that too it's very uh
popular for some
sweets
to be used in sweets and some cakes here
that's the same thing i wonder
ah
i'm not a big fan though to be honest um
[Music]
oh oh don't worry
i don't i don't remember
there's always too many messages in the
chat so don't worry about it
well thank you for uh coming back and
apologizing i guess wow that uh deserves
respect
[Music]
for maximum
thank you
very nice i think tencho need a
dissonant counter at the battle
that was my that was my method of coping
with the stress and the situation
[Laughter]
[Music]
those fights are pretty intense
uh but it's a good thing
i think
yeah
very intense
very exciting
[Music]
thank you soon
was going to have a baby form that was
cut from the game
interesting but i understand because
like it's already looking so babyish
yeah
but it was gonna have a baby form in
this new one
[Music]
how can you make vulpix any more babyish
than it is now
how would that even be possible
in gen 1 until
oh i mean i would have liked to see is
there like a like a
like a draft or so
we're supposed to have three tails
it's already so small
it was gonna have three tails we'll pick
six nine tails nine
oh
smaller vulpix it's already so small
[Music]
if i go back to japan i really want to
eat those potatoes and watch it they're
like pushing them into my face
so often
i think i think every foreigner that's
playing this game right now
will if they ever go to japan they'll be
like yo you know what i gotta eat emo
mochi i'm gonna eat those uh
potato mochis now
um
it's probably going on everyone's bucket
list now
misters thank you tracy duncan alvaro
duncan iron iro ivron d
thank you for tank thank you for the red
super chat
[Music]
you live in russia don't you because you
play you're paying an rub so i'm
wondering
is that russian snack box review gonna
be something that you're gonna be very
excited about
yes you do
for zach bring me some good snacks for
zach
i want you to
send me some samples on twitter pictures
of
uh
of snacks that you think are popular
well known in russia
i'm gonna check if they are
in that
snack box amazon snack box
[Music]
let me know
the one on the amazon snack box look
generally like
like things that you can only get in uh
in russia
like i've never seen
those anywhere else
i will try okay
well take your time take it down i won't
be streaming for a while
thank you though thank you i'll do my
best to have fun
uh don't don't miss me too much just
kidding actually you know what you guys
need to miss me
please miss me
[Music]
mary pippins thank you for the pinky
enjoy your time off have some pocket
money and try to avoid another crash
well thank you it is actually
probably
one of or the most expensive vacation
i have been on yet because the equipment
and the hotel and the skiing pass and
everything the travel
i think it might be the most expensive
or maybe
i mean at least like compared like in a
uh
considering that i'm not
uh going outside of
austria compared to my grease
[Music]
trip
i think it's pretty crazy skiing is so
expensive i mean i could have rented
everything
that
was a thought i had for a moment but i
was like yo why not just get my own
stuff and then i don't ever have to
rent somebody's somebody else's
uh skis
ever again
it might be a pain in the ass to carry
them
but then i have my own things hmm
yeah i can reuse them so um because i
bought them i told
i told rnt yo now that i i bought them i
gotta at least go
skiing one more time this year just for
like a day trip
because you can totally go skiing just
for one day as well
uh in austria there's so many so many
skiing places in uh austria like
hundreds
so the plan is to go
one more time this year before the
season is over
just for another day or one or two i
don't know
that is unless
if i have another accident i'm gonna be
extra traumatized and probably never ski
ever again and regret that i bought all
that equipment
wish me luck
[Music]
thank you for the pinky
enjoy your trip dancing do be careful in
other news i just got your birthday
coats yesterday just in time to grill
some fajitas would you say
oh you're gonna grill them with the
apron on is that what you're saying
exciting thank you have fun and i think
i might have what's so fajita again i
might have never eaten one before
[Music]
fajita
hitachi
oh it's like a it's like a burrito
[Music]
it's like a burrito
is that not just a burrito
they all look so similar the enchilada
burrito
you really like wrapping stuff don't you
these people really like wrapping things
up
[Music]
they probably sleep in burrito blankets
you finished playing yes i did and
you're welcome to watch the arcade
we did a lot of progress today as well
tom what's that
extension jackets monkey and jackson
thank you for the pinky
[Music]
buy yourself something nice on this trip
you deserve the rest
the rest thank you thank you
i
i i um already booked massages
yeah so i'll invest it into that
i need a massage
[Music]
i'm excited for that too
thank you
i'll report on my massage afterwards
i love massages let's go
i bulk
massages
[Music]
love it
happy birthday it's a birthday today
during my birthday today
[Music]
happy birthday
yay
you're older now
congratulations
thank you for spending your time with me
on your birthday
hope you had a great beautiful lovely
day i mean there's still probably
yeah quite some time today maybe you can
have some nice dinner treat yourself
tonight
um
sean are the ancestors for the pinky be
safe and have fun danger then i will try
i will try i'll try i'm so scared i'm so
scared i'm so scared i'll be happy
can i stay at home
um afternoon eight thousand have a nice
vacation hope you can de-stress
yeah it won't be like a typical beach
vacation it will be like a sporty
vacation
so i'm not sure
uh i will definitely i guess get my mind
off of
uh
work a little bit and like be very
sporty move my body touch some snow
[Music]
i want
i want like floaties but for skiing
scared
[Music]
i'm scared
there's some snow here the [\h__\h] ptsd
that makes it so so bad because like uh
in hokkaido the whole skiing thing it
wasn't even planned ahead it was like
super
super spontaneous like we woke up and we
were like yo what are we gonna do today
we had like no plan i was like you know
what we could get go go skiing like
close by
look for something that's fairly close
and we're like okay let's go let's go
like i was not worried i was like i mean
it has been a long time but
i learned it so quickly back then it's
gonna be fine right and now i'm just
like freaking out about it
but i'm gonna be careful gonna be
careful gonna be careful and it's it was
the fault of the snow it was the fault
of the snow it was not my fault the snow
is she was [\h__\h] and now it's gonna be
good snow probably hopefully i don't
know
[Music]
if only you could hold hands with
someone while skiing but it goes so fast
it's like impossible
bubble wrap
i think my skiing um
outfit will serve as bubble wrap
basically
uh
[Music]
and i also don't like the
go go cold it i'll enjoy it i'll enjoy
it i'll enjoy it i'll enjoy it i have to
enjoy it
waiting for your video
i'm also scared thank you and i'm you
know i'm appreciative curbs
i love them curbs yeah
nada ai inna bangaroni dancing for the
rexella chad tends to have lots of fun
but please be safe at the same time a
red packet for best health luck and
prosperity if not too troublesome can
grant me a nice kfp position
oh normally it's like you choose your
desired position thing
don't you have anything you want to do
anything in mind
i don't know what your bangarooni
name means but you could be our uh
banker
kfb banker how about that
yes i want the powder snow too
and clear weather no no snow please like
no snow in the air just on the ground
[Music]
bankers make a lot of money too so yo
take the job take the job
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat and
yeah happy new year to you
[Music]
you think thank you for the pinky have a
good time tanjun take care i will do my
best
i will try to come back
in full pieces
no no pieces actually full fully
assembled
thank you
the shirt is giant thank you
[Music]
yeah they make bank they do it's in the
name
jackson fb don kishan
i used to not be able to turn it on the
snowboard because i was scared to face
up the mountain
now i can do double black diamond runs
whatever that means here
sugoi i don't know what it means but
tsugui
thank you for the rest of the chat let's
go thank you taji this will be a
vacation for you too because i won't be
streaming
are you gonna enjoy your vacation from
takana kiwawa
are you gonna be sad
thank you thai tea
[Music]
lord
phoenix foreign
[Music]
cute
oh
you can't come to the speaker when i
stream
please take a video and upload it on
twitter you have to you must i have to
see that you can't just tell me that and
not show me i want to see all the cats
[Music]
do it please
do it do it do it do it do it do it do
it do it do it do it do it do it are you
here are you still here
i need a cat tax yeah you have a cat
then you need to pay the taxes
it's simple just take a photo or video
[Music]
thank you
you also enjoy your kiwawa vacation as
much as you can okay well come back when
i'm back please
thank you soon
you need to sat down thank you yeah i
feel like i remember skiing um feeling
like so
free
and i hope i'll i'll be able to feel
that feeling again
it's a very
free feeling like almost like you're
flying
very uh dynamic um
but also scary
trevor g duncan slow poke danke
[Music]
you know what if you make a snowman in
the shape of a slowpoke then you could
call it snow poke
[Music]
this music doesn't help me get my point
across
[Music]
solid fun mom thank you
maybe it's an alola version
[Music]
do you have any movie recommendations
that we could watch when you were on
your trip yes the great gatsby
[Music]
lord of the rings all of it
including the hobbit
[Music]
other than that i mostly have only
watched like
[Music]
tv shows and not movies in the past few
years besides you know
our watch lungs
[Music]
i have a cat hair in my mouth again
yeah well that sounds exciting
that you're going skiing too nice
everyone doing those winter sports let's
go
unknown darkest for the pinky enjoy your
vacation so i hope that everything will
go well for you and hope that you will
have an amazing time i'll definitely
miss you a lot we'll
we'll be re-watching your vlogs while
waiting here for your return no you need
some detox don't watch me too much
love you forever my aussie no go read a
book
read a book or something
so that you'll miss me even more and
then it will feel so nice to have me
back
you need to detox i'm scared you're
gonna get sick of me one day and you're
just gonna be gone
yeah avoid the burnout now that you have
a chance
[Music]
no
that's the omo cat booklet count that's
a book
that's not even enough content to get
through
that time without me
[Music]
it's fascinating how some of you just
don't get burnt out
[Music]
my lore video
you can watch that if you want
[Music]
did you get burnt out with pickled up
the thing is a piccolo that i
i joined the whole life and then i was
just too busy to watch her
so i don't really know if i would have
gotten burnt out eventually
[Music]
lasted a week or two
don't get burnt out
usually i can't watch you all the time
the other stuff when you're i'm
streaming
it takes a lot of time out of my other
hobby but i always enjoy being here
thank you
since the beginning experience vernon
around the first anniversary i still
kept watching you and now i'm fine again
thank you that's scary that's that makes
me think of the fact i could have lost
you no
[Music]
oh yeah i did watch all the archives
i feel like
you're always the part where you start
laughing
oh
i watched the witcher oh i haven't
watched that yet by the way
have anti-freezer never burn out
huh
that that doesn't make sense does it
so to avoid burnout is not to turn this
into an obligation and try not to worry
in case you missed something yeah
that might be one of the things that you
might be
needing to take care of i think a lot of
you two kids
are
so in love with me which i'm happy about
but so in love with me that you feel
like you have to come to every stream
um
and have to be there from beginning to
the end
and like for some of you watching an
archive is not even an option you feel
like you have to be there during the
live stream which i really appreciate
obviously but don't feel like it's an
obligation
right
it's always okay to watch the archive if
you feel like you need to take care of
something else
[Music]
say okay mama
okay mommy
say okay mommy
[Music]
thinking mommy
okay okay
good
good good thinking good champion you
deserve a hug for that a pet pet
[Music]
four heads again
many cases so that you can
use them when i'm gone i don't know i
mean you know just because you know
that sounds weird but i don't mean it
like that
uh patricia gutierrez
salazar thank you for the pinky
we're almost done by the way
hi kenneth do you often feel sad
whenever you're separated from someone
you love i haven't seen my bff for some
time and it's been making me sad lately
just wondering if you felt some similar
towards anyone close to you i hope you
have a fun trip potential
not really only towards my cats to be
honest um
i genuinely like to be alone
even even when it comes to people
that are very close to me
i generally
don't mind seeing them as little as
possible
[Laughter]
i also don't mind seeing them a few
every once in a while but you know
the the
less often the
better i'm busy right now i have stuff
to do
my friends
uh yeah when i was living in japan i
i might have missed my friends in
in austria a little bit but
uh
i mean at least i knew that like
my my trip my stay in japan had an end
so when you know when you know
when you will be able to see them again
i think it's more bearable than when you
don't know when you'll be able to see
them again
[Music]
but indeed like i don't know
um
i think one issue might have been that
once
when i was in japan you know
um i was kind of isolated because of the
sea thing starting out
sorry
and um
before
before during her life i
i didn't have anyone really to hang out
with i was just doing my thing but that
was not much
and then even after joining whole life
there was like
obviously most collabs are through
online
um
so
meeting
all these girls it's not like it's not
like it's so normal to
just because you live in the same area
to
meet up randomly with all of them it's
not really normal
especially when most of them are
somewhat shy
there's there always needs to be like a
reason like an
off collab uh
for the first meeting i think
which i did get with some of the girls
but still besides that i didn't have
many opportunities to socialize which i
i will say that i generally don't care
about but
maybe it affected me a little bit in
feeling
isolated to be honest i don't really
remember how i felt back then anymore
[Laughter]
maybe i don't know maybe you guys
remember better how i was doing
emotionally
maybe you guys remember it better than i
do you probably do
[Music]
but i think
when i if if i if i back then said that
i was lonely then it was probably mostly
because i wanted to see my cats and i
was worried about them
and worried about them being without me
for a whole year and you know seeing
them and them forgetting me i was so
i was so worried about that
that was
my biggest
worry
[Music]
huh
yeah and that's com combined with the
stress i had in the first
weeks months of her life
whoo
yeah i didn't i didn't do well i
remember like
like after after streams or so
um
crying in my bed
yeah i mean
i i
[Music]
had a tough time
yeah
thankfully that's
not the case anymore yeah
i'm mostly
mostly pretty happy after streams
[Music]
always feel like
yeah that was that was a good stream
good job kiwawa now it's time to eat and
cuddle
yeah i am stronger now and i have
everything that i need
to be
maybe not everything i mean there could
be things that would make me even more
happy but i have everything i need to be
happy
which is
a comfy place to live in
comfy cats to cuddle with
the the means to eat
good food
[Music]
and
an amazing
amazingly loving fan community
[Music]
yeah
and friends to see whenever i want to
see them
an infinite lasagna generator would be
amazing why does that not exist why are
there like
water
thingies where you can get water out of
like a tab
i wasn't even thinking about a tablet
now that i think about it yeah i
couldn't just say why are there taps but
why why are there no lasagna taps huh
huh
[Music]
damn
well you know like you know you know
like
um cotton candy machines why are there
no lasagna machines
[Music]
or you know ice cube generators they go
like
well i don't know lasagna generators man
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
yeah
it would be helpful if at least there
was like a bolognese sauce generator
where i could just turn on tap and it
would like come out of it and then i
just put it on the sheets
that would be already good enough okay
but
[Music]
i'm sure you're not garfield
no
key i feel chiara rarfield
[Music]
garfield
lasagna
i mean my my freezer is kind of a
lasagna generator because i can
buy
um
frozen lasagna i guess but
i need to make some myself again because
that was really really good
indeed
[Music]
hope you'll have a great time with your
vacation attention we'll be waiting for
you patiently also my birthday's on the
7th
but instead of the 7th day of tomorrow
instead of a happy birthday can i get a
little [\h__\h] in advance
and now
[Music]
your little [\h__\h] aren't you blue
you're a little [\h__\h] aren't you blue
you're a little [\h__\h] my dear blue
[Music]
happy birthday
you little [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
did that make you happy
i don't mean it i love you
i wish you all the best
you didn't do anything bad you don't
deserve it right now
or maybe you're gonna do something bad
on your birthday don't
don't
brandon would dance in for the pinky brb
do i need to wait for you
[Laughter]
thank you for the pink super chat that's
it i'm gonna skip the sneeze chats
i suppose
[Music]
another pinky come in
thank you
you guys should go on vacations too take
the chance i hope you can
especially the people who do like office
jobs and [\h__\h] man you need a vacation
that [\h__\h] eats you ups look
makes you older fi you age five days uh
each day when you do an office job
um
get a vacation please
you can still watch my stream starting
vacation so it's not a vacation from kfp
just from your other job
[Music]
please read in full first before
what
what does that mean
ah read before i say it out loud or what
[Music]
let me just uh
um i gotta say
the shoto generally
yeah
[Music]
and theory generally yes
um
for indies
i think it's maybe a case by case
i don't know i haven't really asked
uh much
i think
um
at the moment
there's not really
there isn't really an indeed there's
just one girl that i really want to pull
up with
who's not an indian
with indies uh
yeah forgot the moment there's not
really anyone anyone in particular that
i want to collab with right now
oh but i'm generally open to it and i
think generally it's possible but of
course it's a case by case so if there's
like um you know
something some
someone with like a maybe a
controversial past or something
obviously that's a uh kind of fun g but
it depends you know it's case by case um
anyway
um oh
i was thinking about lumi
uh
lumine collab would be probably
cool
sometime
yeah
would be fun because she's also
in europe oh
[Music]
two retreat got so many replies i went
through some of them but not all of them
if i i was thinking you know if i uh
uh do some if i want to do something
then with eu
youtubers i can always go back to that
tweet and look through it
stratified
[Music]
i know as i i think i mentioned before
i'm not like planning anything
specifically right now but
i was just wondering you know kind of
maybe hoping also to find some friends
in in europe
um
some cool people in europe
that do the same thing
um
maybe i could like you know
contact them and be like yo
let's let's be friends
um
yeah but but there was so much holy [\h__\h]
i felt a bit overwhelmed by the amount
of
tweets that were thrown at me
i didn't expect that much holy [\h__\h] but
yo
yeah
[Music]
um
i was thinking or something like that
could be fun too yeah patrick chen
um
but
it's not not that i like tweeted it
because
of that i just kind of treated it
randomly
you're popular girl now kiara i wonder i
wonder
anyway we're done
i hope someone will feed the baby while
i'm gone
yo
[Music]
it's kind of
feels very lonely to go but
girls got to go when the girls got to go
and um
some i have stuff to do as well yeah i'm
nervous
okay i better just go and without making
too much of a drama out of it because
it's gonna break all of our hearts uh
uh
so
without further ado
um i'll see you guys on twitter
and uh some some some maybe two i think
actually this time there there's not
much content i can upload there's like
two videos
um
so there might be some days without
anything
um but yeah um in german we say
[Music]
bye
why not go this way
i can say bye bye to you bye bye
bye
[Music]
i said i didn't want to say bye bye i'll
see you later
[Music]
bye bye
i'll see you later
johnny
um
[Music]
my neck crack
pink
[Music]
okay just be there when i'm back promise
me
be there when i come back
um
[Music]
bye
you