foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
oh my God
uh seems fine no one's complaining on my
side audio good I think everything's
good oh
Mario
um
is everyone around the holiday move
jingle jangle yeah
[Music]
wait
hey
hang on I'm turning up everyone full
volume 200 everyone wow oh boy oh boy
oh my God the voice is definitely
peeking okay that's fine that's fine
[Music]
I'm loud
uh let me turn down my mic okay maybe
this is okay
God ah
why does everyone have 200
oh
one second
I'm going back and forth in the portal I
keep hearing you know is that 200 volume
[Music]
I gotta go drop my cat off at the house
oh yeah I have like 12. I think
but then again there's never a such
thing as too many people okay your house
is looking good now
thank you Amelia added a nice place on
top I don't really I think it looks
better
um what it looks better what is that
yeah I think I definitely made a big
contribution
oh yeah I ate them oh wow
what is that supposed to be play the
game
it's a
finger a long finger hold the finger is
it a middle finger
you will be stood outside now you can
say middle and you can say that
I think the answer is clear if you have
to uh ask
Ed this is my sword here we go
oh I got a cat
yeah I have a cat is in your house
salmon huh I trapped him okay he came
out of the wall he came flying out of
the wall uh I don't really know how he
did it um someone else's cat maybe uh it
didn't have a collar yeah there's a
Wildcats your entrance to your house
why is it that when gura walks all this
dirt comes up
because she smells
too
I didn't come here to be bullied man
you didn't come here too but that
doesn't mean you're not going to be did
you guys see the Christmas tree is this
your Christmas tree oh yeah let's go see
the Christmas tree over here who is
doing that
yes Christmas tree
yeah I built this I built this earlier
I'm hungry
so if you look inside this chest yeah if
you look in the box there's like a bunch
of different decorations and shears so
you guys can make your Snowman and
they'll be alive
these pillars here that have snow and
they have the pumpkin if you grab a
sheer from the chest and you uh use the
sheer on a pumpkin then now you have a
snowman you can take off the pumpkin
wait what that's cool how do I get in
here and you can jump oh there's no game
so up here
[Music]
and then you can take the pumpkin off if
you want to or you can leave it cool oh
my God they always try escaping I have
to put a fence here
that's so cute is that a mod or is it
actually in-game a feature
so much better than sentient why
and what else they're trying to escape
one snowman that you made
I uh walked I walked into the uh build a
fence
oh no it escapes
oh that escaped I trapped him hold on
I'll just make it I killed my snowman
and all he left me was these snowballs
what do I do with them
uh you can throw them at people
can I build another snowman I miss them
yes
how do you build a snowman how do you do
it again
right click with the chair on the on the
pumpkin pop oh yeah oh yeah you just
need like a few snowballs and you can
make a snow block you don't need like a
a crafting table to do it and then you
can uh
put two down and put a pumpkin on top
[Music]
I know you already prepared a lot of uh
decorations on it but I also prepared a
bunch of pumpkins so that I can also
contribute I want to put some pumpkins
on this tree yeah pick whatever you want
I just picked some extra stuff that goes
and if I do
oh but it's gonna be hard to decorate on
the other side when there is literally a
cliff there
um that's why we have a scaffolding yeah
I've never used that before
yeah scaffolding go forward because you
can just click on the ground and it just
builds itself
it can build really hot yeah
let me break with like one one hit like
like and then breaks all down it's
really good oh they hit spacebar and it
goes up look at that when I use the
snowball it just uh it just makes me
throw it yeah um you gotta make it in
the in the blocks oh yeah when you press
uh
to the side
I did not build up okay yeah
I'll get out of here if you have a
shovel you can also uh you can dig these
the snow on the ground
what happens if I put a torch as a light
on on the tree does the tree burn
in it
glowy I can't put it I can't put it on
there anyway but yeah we need to lighten
the tree up as well no don't set it on
fire
that's that's not no don't worry I'm not
gonna set it on fire is there a color
scheme we're going for or is it just red
uh oh whatever you want whatever color I
think yes
the lights
bring some clothes I've colored all over
you put them wherever you want
climb up this elevator thingy
Daisy
should we build a star on top yeah yeah
nice idea apparently there's like a
redstone lamps or I have these shroom
lights either work
it's so pretty
damn
can you not put the scaffolding on a
bush
oh
[Music]
um
is anyone here already have a tree in
their home did you put them on the side
of the wall Callie
here
anymore what's going on yeah
fight for the top music
I didn't bring my put them on the vines
night one day uh uh
yeah on the grass it's not oh you gotta
put it on Sideways stuff like uh on the
wall like this oh
quick
good this is not over yet
oh sorry
all right you've done it
what are you guys doing
today
how about how about this the Crimson
Roots
at that what a shame oh these are
zombies
can we have a snowball fight oh yeah
[Laughter]
that's what I before
stairs are right at my arrow
[Music]
again yeah
the words come in handy the ones I
taught you oh yes delicious
where'd you go where'd you go
oh boy
where'd you come from where'd you go
where'd you come from Cotton Eye Joe huh
huh
I see I need to bring some stronger
weapons
hahaha
she's going to get more weapons
Christmas is all about right of course
fighting fighting we're fighting around
the Christmas tree
who did that
oh no I need to eat something oh no oh
no
they need some steak
oh that might be nice actually maybe I
can at least put some bones oh wait no
oh no now all these weird rocks are in
front of our tree because I tried to
make a big a big hour so I could I could
put the star on the top
I've ruined it
should just be able to like jump around
like if you come this way Cali
yeah follow me I think we can get to the
top like this we just jump on the blocks
yes oh okay maneuver around the tree it
should be like a little stairway
okay did you call a uh
yeah yeah
how does it work thank you for the
steaks I got them now okay all right my
inventory is a little low so hold on let
me get rid of something
snowballs I don't need them I wasted it
I said it got it
what is that
what is you plotting now
hang something on fire but don't worry
it won't fit a Christmas tree
I just want to put this bone somewhere I
can't all the things that I want to put
down I can't put down and you press e
and you you click on your inventory you
can drag it out and then just drop it
just drop it somewhere okay cool I'll do
that yes make the star with Glowstone so
I close
oh yeah yeah but there's also the
there's also Redstone light but I'm not
sure how to make it
that sounds pretty
oh
wait so I'm just going to bring more
scaffolding from home
pencil balls
paper stuff like here
oh yeah my contribution
were around our town until now I put
some bones there they're just kind of
floating well they disappear I wonder
yeah she's got the chicken legs
no
[Music]
uh-oh oh
yeah
where is she
[Music]
let us have a snowball fight those are
snowballs you goober
oh
my God
they look like them
I mean
oh no the Snowman
that's okay we can make more
yeah
all right all right we're safe
here's zombie
oh there's so many chickens
I don't know why you tell me why ma'am
[Laughter]
foreign
they do eat a lot of KFC in Japan for
Christmas yeah they do I don't know what
so why on Christmas but
I eat fried chicken every day hello
girl is the star girl is the star on top
of the tree
thank you for the information
do not make it weird
you get close don't hold on let me get
it I am like
I have some glowstone I have 28 to take
a bit of it ah if anybody has Redstone
Dust I can try making the redstone lamp
okay I gotta think
you know I'm writing your house for
Redstone Dust
okay I forgot where I put it but it's in
there somewhere
oh I fell down
he was shooting at us
bringing out the battle accident
Now ladies let's all play fair yeah
that's right impromptu star ready okay
um Enderman is here I heard Enderman no
oh there you go he wants to party with
us is it the Enderman from the uh the
railway
okay
Amore yeah could you take a back step
just not
oh where's the click
dude I need a little bit of room for
this stuff okay guys are you have I ever
thought have you ever thought of the
theory that Enderman might just be enma
song
our manager
and impossible oh
I'm gonna go put some fun surprise that
would be quite a twist
what's your building I don't know oh oh
oops
and I'm just showing off the lights
all the different types of Lights yeah
this looks so nice in my head
stop breaking here it's gonna be a
scuffed scar I want to see how it looks
from a fire
hey we need a little bit more yellow
here
wow
looks good looking good
let me see how that star is looking
probably nice might not be very starish
but let's get you there because I just
can't put them anywhere else I wonder if
we could have like a few more color
variations in the decoration although it
looks kind of cluttered now so I mean
should we add more
um I think a few more colors would be
nice though
yeah I think that would be good we can
add I'll put mushrooms on it pink and
green
let's see what colors I have
ah all right and see how this looks
until
excited I'm gonna put some of my fancy
white glazed terracotta on it but can I
have it back when the tree is gone maybe
maybe not because I got them from far
away lands okay I don't want to lose
them I'll sing you next Weeknd
they're they're really fancy that's a
nice idea we can make lots of TNT we can
make fireworks so we can send them yeah
but before we blow it up back there you
go oh it's pretty easy nice okay this is
easy I can do blocks the Ritz I can't
understand I can't make them work I
tried very hard it's not working they
don't want to go
the style looks good
how's that little scuff but we can
improve it later
it's nice
I can't get up the scaffolding ow who
pushed me
wasn't me
I was gonna say it's a chicken no no no
no I'll eat you don't blame it on my
employees
they're innocent
of course it is innocent legs
wait does it it's the tree lopsided or
is it just me I don't remember it being
like that but it's possible that
I may have forgotten one side
laughs
I can't make progress how do we get up
there oh God oh man I can fix this
what did you guys want for Christmas
um
[Music]
well you had to ask but what about
everyone else
I want
to sleep
that sounds good I want just a free day
oh wait do you need leaves I have like
like a day of three oh yeah leaves you
have you have leaves yeah I do hold on I
need them
we can't make the tree even bigger
you won't believe how many leaves I have
um
[Music]
I have Birch and uh Oak and I have a lot
are you on the train like
oh I want to drink and Spruce no I'm at
my house oh I'll come to you
our house
we're gonna have a
very mixed tree oh yeah okay this is
slime
do you guys like uh when trees have like
themed ornaments or do you like when
it's uh like a bunch of handmade
different colors
I like colors lots of colors and that's
like a more personal
layer to the trees I think
are you are you guys even gonna get a
tree this year I'm probably not getting
one because uh I I don't want to get rid
of it's kind of annoying in here and you
know in Japan you have to vacuum after
the trees a lot so it's easier to get a
fake one especially if you have the
answers
sometimes your pets like to hide in the
tree in the chest
thank you okay I'll hide in the tree
yeah
when you have cats and a Christmas tree
that's fun yeah I had some kittens that
were hiding in the tree on Christmas it
was very cute
it was adorable
okay
the door oh
thank you thank you
hmm
[Music]
if I make the star a little better it's
going to be like bigger than the tree
[Music]
beaker look at it from afar
I can't wait to see wait it's glowstone
that means it's gonna glow I'm so
excited to see this guy you guys
yeah
this could be so much fun
I wish we could make like different
colored lights
and stuff can you we can make a we can
make stained glass
idea I'll bring some
ah my trees
I'm trying to make it a bit more space
here
we can put even more in decoration looks
so good from afar it's so cute
they're not always perfect okay yes
exactly facts but them being
individually beautiful that's what makes
them special
I literally have no idea what I was just
saying but okay I'm glad that's a lie
you do you know it sounded good
um
[Music]
no I mean I brought some stained glass
I'll put in the chest thank you
I only brought like two of each because
that's all I had left over but if you
need more I have more at home
[Music]
[Laughter]
how do we light up the stained glass
still can you light it up or I guess you
can put it like in front the glowstone
so if you look from the front it looks
like a different color maybe
what if we put torches on the tree
will it catch a fire that sounds like a
flower
they don't even place on the on the
leaves oh I guess you'd have to have a
block
what if you use something like um what
if you put it on an ornament is it
getting too much now
you can put the swatches on like the
pumpkins or the Terracotta yeah
[Music]
it's missing a bit of clothes and over
there okay it doesn't burn the tree
I'll be fine
if it burns and the Sun is setting yeah
[Music]
should we put something under the tree
like a carpeting or something like um
all right
the tree looks so yummy
what candy forbidden snack
what color should it go under the tree
guys red all right yeah red okay
oh I'm sorry I'm trying to move yeah
oh
I hurt myself
are you okay are you okay are you okay
she's she's dead herself she can't she
can't die right yeah true facts
that she looks so cute
oh I want to see hang on oh that is so
cute
oh my heart oh
wait wow looks so cool
there's like a perfect spot for a
photograph
in the photo
oh you want me to be there naked okay
okay
[Music]
that's what I like to see as well I see
our tastes are very similar
that's why we are both business owners
Taco Bell and kfp hell yeah exactly oh I
think I could use some more Stone
way up there okay
let's see let's see we can make a
Christmas card and then we can sign it
and then we can post it yeah it looks
really pretty that's a great idea I like
that let's do it again
happy holidays
thank you yeah
while I eat these potato chips I will
provide a view of the Christmas tree for
everything do you eat anything besides
potato chips
is there a reason too
and bread that's that's your favorite
food I'm gonna order some vegetables
later for lunch I wonder wow
I mean potatoes a vegetable right
yes yes or a potato chip is vegetable
healthy yes agree
[Music]
Minecraft collab
I'll shoot them down guys don't worry
guys when there's in there and I have
one buddy yeah buddy
I bet you I
wait oh come back down and just bite me
like a real fandom
wait hello nice nice nice shots
is there only one
that's only one wow the skies are safe
another day yes I feel bad I wish I was
there to help I tried to go to sleep you
guys remember the first Minecraft collab
where we all just started to start
how times have changed
how they have there's a party going on
in my chat right now
Tony just reached 1 million
[Applause]
seconds
[Music]
I'm ready for battle maybe we should
sleep and what if they destroy our tree
[Music]
we can take them thank you thank you I
love you guys
oh sweet
where is it I see it enemy spotted I'm
just gonna slip is oh this is me at the
cat I don't think he likes the cat oh
wow
yeah you know I think I'll go ahead and
go to sleep are you sleeping or not I'm
gonna go to sleep I'll go to sleep
Sometimes the best option in a battle is
just to sleep
does anyone need extra I will I will I
will also sleep I'm sleeping on your
cat's bedina okay
okay because the Phantom's around
I think so I'm gonna sleep to the the
calming sounds of their hissing
around just pretend they're um cats are
something funny no it's like it's like a
dolphin or whale sounds you know very
relaxing from the ocean
I'll find the bed all done
so peaceful
thank you
thank you everyone oh my God they're
still partying party party party no
they're gonna burn to death
just go Inferno
they look like phoenixes
except they're dying instead of coming
back alive
what
[Music]
so how many pets do you have uh yes
understood
[Music]
[Laughter]
I see there was actually a cat that
looked just like the first edition I
think it was gross girl skin
no
yeah it's like yeah three different
colored ones
oh yeah yeah
I have a lot of kids now I can't really
remember what they all look like I think
we're gonna have more and more cats
because of the uh
I mean I'm fine with that it's so cute
right sure I only have one but I want I
want millions of cats in my home
yes wait what is this can I ask what
this is is this like
the uh the photo zone for this is the
viewing platform yeah
the photo Zone
apparently I'll just take these off oh
it's so cute
trees looking good
really good
I'm really happy with it
um
he's a little more red oh
it's just a little more red in my
opinion more red or just a little more
red like bright red like this kind of
red
oh
baby baby
[Music]
I can't
right
yeah lucky yes
we should make like a red carpet that
goes to like the entrance oh good idea I
have some red if you would like to do it
do you want to do it yes please
thank you
[Music]
so our elevators are gone huh
oh it's okay
no worries oh
oh good in the hood I think I'll just
climb it the old-fashioned way oh here
there's some scaffolding here
shoot me while I was partying with my
employees
we're trying to shoot me it might be
zombies You Are by the end oh really oh
really oh really oh really good huh
you really think I would shoot you while
you're having an intimate moment
I'll watch the archive I'll see what
happens there
okay guys this is an archived
get rid of the evidence
it's okay it's okay
um it's okay
I like being shot because it feels good
yeah she's used to dying no I like pain
I'm a masochist yep okay Merry Christmas
kids look beautiful I wish we could add
one of those how do you stop it I just
called those hanging things the the
hanging ones I tried so hard because the
vines
yeah
I thought what
uh get fun separately
a low power no that's not good what I
have vines that I can bring I'll bring
him I'll go get him
oh they're not Red Vines
the game has stuff like that what no no
it's not a tinsel are you talking about
like tinsel that you wrap around the
tree
nothing like yeah it just hangs down but
we can we can do it oh but that's cool
yeah why do I hear a zombie mama is
there anything you don't have
um I'm telling you guys there's zombies
everywhere
careful they got arrows too they'll
shoot you you sure do
they'll get you
Millions what's for Christmas dinner by
the way oh bam yummy chicken and
Christmas cake
yeah
I'm gonna steal your snowballs no you're
not
oh my God
the sound of the sound of snow when you
walk on it isn't it amazing
crunch
cornstarch exactly you can only have 16
at a time it seems
I have to tell you something
from a distance
[Music]
you look beautiful
thank you
I break the Snowballs we'll do some
damage so we can have like an actual
snowball fight that would be fun if we
could throw
we can throw some arrows at each other
oh yeah almost
until we die
maybe we should build that we should
build a Coliseum
ring
my house
do we want to have a battle Christmas
battle I'd like a Christmas battle
forget the Christmas dinner it's time
for the Christmas battle yes the
Christmas battle that's what I'm
concerned about yourself
KFC and yeah exactly I'll just bring you
well actually that's not really my job
it's kind of my job to keep you from
coming back but uh you could ask
what's yesterday
12 deaths of Christmas no I'm really
lagging oh
Martin is suspiciously quiet has anybody
seen monster I'm in the tunnel what
Neptune
I'm not going to get vines and I'll be
I'll be back in like
we take success six seconds
okay oh my goodness there she go
[Music]
okay that was good I'll give that to you
that was a good one that was really good
I know
I am a comedian
oh my God a communion
Kiara you are on fire tonight
always on fire
uh
look to the left side
why
I'm not impressed I know my potato chip
bag pushed into adoption
do you like my crossbow yeah I like it
I can't do it it hurts my heart okay
mint on my life no no you were going to
make an attempt on my life because you
don't have a life if you're you're deaf
exactly that's the point which is why it
wouldn't work I don't know why I feel
like battling could happen
[Music]
both of you
it doesn't hurt both it doesn't hurt at
all though
I can pretend it is
this looks so good I really like it
adding a little snow
ah a frosted Christmas tree frosted good
idea like Guy Fieri yeah you're like
right like that guy facing Around the
Christmas Tree
all right coming back with vines
yay
that must have been a lot of vines
you killed it oh man do your thing oh he
only you gave him a life yes I saved him
from
I don't know
the snow
how do you put it down
uh oh do you mean yes no man or snow the
snow on the ground on the it's like uh
what is it anytime
right now if you take the Snowballs and
you go in your inventory and you line
them up in a straight line I think
that's how you make them
and then you get snow blocks
or you can get you can get like the
little little snow thingies
like the flat one
yeah
cool snow thingies oh yes yeah there's
nothing easy
what would you call them they're like
platforms I don't know
I don't know the snow sheets yeah yeah
yeah
oh
okay like this
I don't think it'll melt them
uh
I think all the snowmen just fell down
anyways
can you put the Snowman on a lead
that was a good question
can we put a saddle on him
let me ride the snow can we make a snow
horse
he's so cute though
cute very merry
well at least there's still more and
more snowmen just jumping up and down
they're cute
[Music]
for our Christmas dinner
I wonder oh
and we should get the uh those red
bushes
they're like Holly we can put a Holly
hanging oh yeah can we make a mistletoe
yeah yeah
that's good yeah
you're right here maybe right here
[Music]
are you making an igloo
strawberries
I brought some red yes
um
should we make lanterns for the uh
because I thought the Torches look like
candles but like I was wondering if we
could make like bigger candles with like
oh yeah yeah yeah
with us
this idea
here
[Music]
's sniping skills
do your worst Phantom oh my gosh
are you fighting them
all right nice nice nice
foreign
cute box in here
hello friend
Nice Shot nice shock yeah saracism
looks so good from the distance too
doesn't it it's so colorful so pretty
Christmas cake
oh that's gonna be a cake
yes what
that's cool I have a lot of wool as well
as you need for
I have uh too much wool
but but you know
doesn't the ground layer be
I mean okay it's all gonna be out of
cream okay again
not we could have it layered a layered
cake good
cream on top with strawberry yeah and
then you can have the side showing so
you can see my strawberry
yeah I can build on top of it okay you
have yellow for cake oh this is the I
mean I have pumpkins
while I'm sleeping does that look like
from the side like it could be what we
want it to be
lemonade
oh a layer of what
image just the visuals yeah just a
visual
[Music]
all right well sarcasm
um
you do it
do I just where do I put them you see
this Vine here
this little blend in I don't know it
would hang you can hang it off of stuff
[Music]
okay let's see what happens
go get em tiger
cool it makes an interesting It looks
interesting oh that's I see they're only
in green
uh yeah except for the ones from the
nether but I guess you can't put those
on the tree for some reason or maybe I
grabbed the wrong ones
you know
the energy please
see I'll put some on the glowstone
that'll look neat
I heard them
[Music]
what is it spotted
oh three o'clock by the trees
I
[Music]
oh yeah
I got one shot left that's not good guys
oh no
oh
don't ruin her I have my battle ax
one two three
hi
far
yamate could you stop yeah
they could just stop doesn't even care
about us it's just it's just chilling
[Music]
you don't want to attack afraid of the
cats oh my God oh my God oh is that
thing
they don't like cows they're afraid of
cats and like dogs and Etc
all the more reason to have lots more
cats
thank you
uh yeah that's good enough
okay uh should we get a buddy
I buy yellow does this look okay oh or
is that too yellow
okay yeah
very good I'm gonna drop something for
you
huh what is that
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
Cali had like four that she got for free
what if she wanted to swim in the lava
oh hey I didn't want to
listen
they're trying to destroy our tree a
tree
oh no get away from the tree everyone we
lead them away it was fine we will not
do such a thing
go away
I'll try and drag them away okay can we
can we kill them with snowballs or
something it's fine it's almost morning
we need to keep them distracted
snowman's fighting laughs oh I know like
what's the flying like right like about
me yeah
thank you Snowman
that's this guy doing he's going the
wrong way man the battle's this way what
are you doing thank you
[Music]
thanks guys for helping you nice snowy
dudes
big snowballs
Jeff
uh
right here
like where I'm standing
let's do it sold out there's like one
one
um yeah
I could have sworn I had one white block
on the very edge thing that I'll do
you got it
no that doesn't hurt
do you want to come up here for a second
for what just to see it look at the
thing I'm good though anymore
yeah you know
what is this I will wait for you
oh big egg
I'm so lone
you didn't come to kiss me I think we
need one more here
[Music]
one here
okay like this
beautiful
oh yeah I see okay beautiful
I have I have these red these red things
here that we can put we can use them as
as uh as strawberries
yeah it sure does so so let's use those
as strawberries I'm healthy very good
thing are we done with the tree itself
it looks done
are we only imagine
no I will not burn everything Dude
where's the pizza sama
with your daddy
no Danny DeVito I will not burn our
Christmas tree excuse you they're asking
that one person
right exactly
oh I think it's scaffolding closer I
have a little addiction when it comes to
fire I enjoy fire a little bit much my
whole techniques
yeah
they do another cake layer
up in that and that glass building over
there
I'm curious if you guys sure do a lot of
things in this game huh
will you burn it for 10 no no amount of
money dude
you're just gonna be wasting your money
dead people so you're wasting your money
I need more cake
[Music]
leg that I was hitting you with
Jack are you guys hurting each other
come on no no we're people you're people
uh and having fun it looks like they're
high-fiving each other yeah
we're being good buddies and good bodies
like to touch each other every once in a
while
what
oh what's better what's hatching what's
better about touching come on
I mean yeah I can't focus somebody's
making the cake baking station hostile I
can't focus
now we need we need more cream
well hello it looks really good
I got the I got the I got the uh the
whipped cream
[Music]
what's going on
what's up
family friendly
of course we are what the hell
a little bit of body touching is there's
nothing wrong about that
okay
[Laughter]
you burn it down for a Scooby Snack no
would you do it for two Scooby Snacks
well gosh
we're good for the strawberry now
and oh you gotta do it like a like yeah
like a clock right like blink and then
yeah
I didn't take screenshots again it's
tasty
kill you
ah yeah oh yeah oh yeah gotta get some
making our photos here what I'm leaving
this area I even I don't even have to
hurt myself
like that
what I'm just taking a photo of the
progress what the hell wait do we only
have two stuff
you said don't you do that to me what
maybe there's more I'll check the things
[Music]
you said making out photos no making off
photos
that wasn't how I wanted to hear it no
it wasn't up okay
[Music]
until they're done
[Laughter]
wait this isn't gonna work
uh we got a implies I got some more
strawberries ready more strawberries
right right here it really look like
strawberry yummy
like huge
one for each member a big one so we
don't have to find straws
should we I know this is not a birthday
cake but should we put candles on top of
the strawberries
the strawberry looks a little weird
do you think it's expired T is not
exactly a strawberry
she burned down the tree for unprotected
hand holding with Kiara what the is
wrong with that
I didn't cut down this tree any
objections
[Music]
no Christmas kisses no Christmas kisses
I put those trees down because I was
gonna hide anvils at the top so when you
guys cut them down they would fall on
you but it didn't work out so yeah
that would have been funny though come
on think of the contest
for the content yes I'm using again
wait I got an idea
hmm
a Christmas steak
like a very special block I can light on
fire
I forgot where I put it though oh there
you go
second if I made a second Christmas tree
and burned that one down make for a cozy
fire like
just make a bonfire uh
um
[Music]
this is cute very cute
can I hide inside of the cake
it jumped out
like what what
like a chicken dinner
uh-huh
wait bye-bye
I am
oh I put a bonfire at the top very very
special fire yay ah it's a soul fire huh
yes Soul fire that sounds interesting I
want to see
hold on it's nice in here
I was chilling it's like the uh you know
when you make like a marriage proposal
and then
marry me
Kelly
and this is how you eat a cake normally
in my country from inside out
don't ask me question kiss my quote
unquote wife yeah
I don't um
who ate cake I didn't even cut it do it
what are you talking about
um
I spit it back out and I put it back on
the cake it's fine
why are you guys scared of some shark
cooties is that what it is
that sounds so weird
what else can we build as Christmasy
um
I messed up
can we put some cats in the tree what
are you doing to my camera later that's
in the tree yeah that could be fun if we
put one of the kids to put some cats on
the tree
like his little decorations
yeah you know you have a ton of cats
right you can go grab some put them on
the tree I know we can do it we can get
eyes
I have a bunch of ice I can't bring it
hold on I'll go get the ice
skating green we can transform the
fighting ring into a skating rink
something a little bit maybe yeah that'd
be pretty big tiny bits yeah I bring a
lot of vitamins
foreign
[Music]
will you give me permission to build a
giant chicken on top of your uh
I mean we can fill it together because
that's what I wanted to do anyway
[Music]
um there's a blueprint for it before oh
yeah oh yeah please yes yes I got a lot
of will uh wool as well so let's do it
together
yeah Majestic chicken I'm gonna make the
ice glue
we gotta make it look like a little bit
like a phoenix so that my my employees
don't misunderstand what it actually
what we actually sell but it's laser
chicken if you
maybe I just realized the Christmas tree
was right above my home oh
it's right on top of my cave nice you'll
never use your way this time you still
don't have a proper home let me check it
out I mean I worked you can come see
some of it I worked on it yeah
you can come take a look I still don't
have a proper door but you know don't
hear zombies
hold on
I got super lucky I picked it up as I
gotcha
oh my goodness
and then there's and kitchen up
here I'm still working on it but
is this your pet or Kevin
a zombie a zombie oh the zombie oh yeah
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
thank you I have your salmon buddy hold
on
your cave has potential
oh
she was told that before but she didn't
believe it I didn't want I listen I just
didn't want to do it because they told
me to do it
listen she doesn't want to be told what
to do she's a rebellious teenager
[Music]
I'll get you a door
oh I'm getting ice but I already have a
bunch of ice so I'm just picking it up
and then I'll be back in like four
minutes
okay okay baby
[Music]
uh door
Hello Kitty I think it's another door
actually hold on
tip
Kelly I got the perfect door for you
punching bag really love that salmon oh
shut up
punching bag
listen I don't know how buttons work in
this game so on occasion when I try to
feed my cat the Sam and I end up hitting
the cat with a salmon instead of getting
it
I just don't play the game often
there's only two times
I do you know you leave me a door okay
get him fast it's a nice color too thank
you nice nice a real door hooray thank
you so much it's uh adorable how's
everyone doing okay
[Music]
it's raining sharks and Squids
laughs
oh cool can I fight can I go kill some
more fish I need more food for my kitty
I need more employees here
not enough people working at kfp why did
everyone quit their jobs what the hell
no I think you need to look at yourself
not in that respect
why did they leave I wonder I don't know
I've heard some stories
every now and then they love me they
will never leave me
not have a face
that would never leave me I think it was
just you
have a face for me
it was in the back of their head I
couldn't tell
he was looking at me maybe I think
you're going into the side of it yeah
foreign
I have some ink sacks
oh
I have some anvils
your house has a nice raw salmon on this
tree and maybe the cats will come to it
you like it I've been told it's a finger
apparently
it's a very interesting hat yeah
maybe maybe that's how they say hello to
each other uh we're on my phone where
are you from
[Music]
the UK is not how they say hello in the
UK
yeah let me try hello I'm okay hello
hello
is that how it sounds
I will not let them be hurt by a stupid
zombie
dead
zombies
[Music]
it's not hello
[Applause]
hello
hello governor
come on kill me I hate it
I gotta stop though they're gonna kill
me they're gonna kill me people from the
UK
I'm sorry I don't mean any disrespect
they like me did I do that the Aussie
twang
yeah I can't do that
there you go you've got it
I got the cowboy covered though oh with
myself wow I love that
British people be like subscribe to my
YouTube channel
oh my God
I love vtubers
you guys sound legit
amazing
all right anyway how's that ice coming
along I'm almost back I'm in the tunnel
on the way back I have 52 ice okay
maybe we can make a long slide or
something instead
he's got an egg
yeah maybe he's gonna make us breakfast
oh wow I don't want that that would
probably taste really bad zombie
breakfast
inside of brains
Mmm delicious no I need let's see if I
can uh
wow
[Music]
raw flesh I like collecting that
Kiara
I I I'm just uh admiring your beauty
when the sun is coming up you shine even
more beautiful me than every
oh oh my
God
we know nothing's as beautiful
it looks beautiful
[Music]
the cake is almost bigger than the tree
though yeah
it's enough for everybody
no
yum yum yum yum oh yeah
he's good thank you thank you new
audience
do you see our delicious cake and our
beautiful tree
[Music]
and what do you guys think we should
build I have all the ice but where
should we put like an ice maybe an ice
slide because if you go really fast on
the boats but then we can't oh
52 won't make that big of a square but
we can definitely wait who is building
something on the mountain
that's good at yeah
what is building up there nothing
nothing actually nothing
actually nothing
from the mountain down down there yeah
you go down ice like that is it still
slippery oh
cutting board just for you thank you
thank you
[Music]
but we need one she is the cutting board
all right I'll put stairs
let's go up there
okay
you guys want some stuff
I think man
oh man no oh what's happening
why are you coming after me really what
is the actor using you ate like a freak
what's wrong with you Spiderman pickaxe
oh what is that oh there's a pig
we'll just use this
oh wait
let me get something there you go
spiders have eight legs right
[Music]
yes okay
why you know what else has eight legs
because I called him and it like a week
and I'd like to be correct when I insult
them
all right that's good I was never
answered that question before I like the
view from here nice the tree looks also
nice from here because hi
that's a weird oh yes
oh the tree on top of your house
looks very weird
it's weird
in a snapped
what looks weird huh
I gotta get one of those
[Music]
I have the same thing we all have the
same thing everybody
no I'm getting one I'm getting one and
I'm getting one I'm getting the same mic
as several of you
Griffin
same microphone same go XLR hell yeah
all right oh my face
[Music]
we'll put somebody do like this side
with blocks like either dirt or concrete
on the other side and then
um we won't fall off when we when we go
really fast
oh I mean like uh
fence to make sure people
that's the way that might be the fun
part
those bodies
we'll do it over this uh this ditch here
you know so you guys uh it's more fun
that way the chance to die make up the
little pool of water at the bottom so we
can like wee into it ah
[Music]
well maybe I should maybe I should it's
a it's an icy diving board of death
block the plank
I'm gonna put a sharp turn here
oh
it's like Rainbow Road
[Music]
uh that's all the eyes I have
aha sorry
the leap of faith I am dropping I'm
dropping a bunch of boats if anybody
wants to pick up a boat
[Music]
you don't want to like put us put a put
some stuff on the side so we don't fall
off is the link nah I bring some dirt
now though but that's the fun part
no wait I can make it safe
thank you
I'm a land boat wait I'm gonna put away
my diamonds somewhere
oh I wish you could bumper you off the
people
I will make this place safe I will make
it safe so help me
and I brought that I brought extra dirt
so help me Poseidon oh my God
oh
[Music]
I guess we'll fall off I'll get some
water yeah
I'll make some buckets what
oh god I like blue yeah your color is
better
blue is very nice do you want to make
this longer or will it end there
I don't have anymore
[Music]
there's no fall damage
apparently there's no fault that is from
both oh so we can we can do it without
the Walnut whoever falls off first is a
loser
whoever falls off first is a stinky
stinker stinkerton
now
[Music]
you don't take fall damage oh
really I just found out
how do I get out of it
oh hello
[Music]
my boat can you give it back to me
I'll just take this one
uh what about my boat
I see I see yeah let's make another
scaffolding going up
my mind
it's actually kind of fun it is
unfortunately your boy actually has to
dip out
I have a meeting I thought it would only
be an hour 30 minutes for this okay okay
that's fine
like uh like straight so we can go zoom
in and just fly
[Applause]
don't worry about it okay let's go take
a picture yeah screenshot
we go down to the tree
and we have the tree Edge the cake on
the picture
we can do that
I'm coming I'll go to well then
picture time yay
um to take selfie oh it looks kind of
prettier during the night should we wait
until this night
flower
and salmon yeah let's go on top of here
it won't get both on it but let's at
least cut the tree and then we can get
two hours three
F5
F5 there you go
F5 is the change thing yep yeah you can
probably once again
you want to take off your end your uh my
equipment good idea
pretty oopsie my button
[Music]
should I what should I do go get it no
if you want sure it's fine
no worries hello oh it's all about four
oh how could I have forgotten
maybe we can all uh Crouch
yeah how do you crouch
shift oh shift yes
yeah cool crouching in front of the
Christmas tree it's perfect
okay and maybe one more should maybe one
more person should be uh downstairs
Shorty's in the front
is so confusing
all right down you go girl okay
okay okay one second it's perfect right
now it's like not too dark okay
how can I get rid of the UI F1 F1 oh you
know what you want to crouch again all
right let's screenshot again F3 F2
okay other signs take signs
okay
cake size oh you guys
have room for both of you up here
do we want to be on the cake
[Music]
it's so easy let's just yeah sounds good
ready are you able to get up oh hey
motion that's broken sorry
here we go
okay
okay yay we did it yay now I gotta say
goodbye
you guys have fun okay enjoy the rest of
your time together although I mean I
think we're all on the end here yeah oh
okay yeah
I I I would suggest that we leave the
Christmas tree forever okay yeah I
always I want it forever
it will not go bad yeah
[Music]
thank you for watching
happy holidays
[Applause]
oh no they're killing me they're killing
me hello
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
Minecraft Christmas
good night teammates
thank you for all your support