[Music]
do
hello hello it's time
the time is here hello everyone and
welcome
can you hear anyone lucky number four
collaboration stream hololive myth we
will show you how we do
i'm calliope mori welcome to my channel
it's collab time lucky number four my
favorite
can you guess why kawink poe ink cowink
how ink how about you ladies do you know
why
do you know why forest it means death
yeah
i also feel very relatable to that
number
oh yeah i'm sure you do it's not
surprising
well anyway today we have all gathered
here to try some tasty delicious
japanese snacks all of us had
similar similar ones delivered to our
places of residence
and so we will be trying the many
different
varieties i anticipated very exciting
stuff
and we also chose some unique ones as
well
which you can see on our desks oh
exciting
exciting stuff i hope that you all have
brightness
[Music]
before we dive into this next i wanted
to ask you a question
how has everyone's first month been
doing
this stuff stressful it's been a month
only a month
what a wild ride so far wow oh
i literally placed all of my
equipment i got a new microphone i got
new internet i moved i got a new
mic arm like i got a new audio interface
i got everything new
right oh sorry about that by the way
i wanted to help you and then it ended
up being
really bad and uh no and and hurts you
in the end so i'm sorry i wanted to
apologize
you helped me in so many ways but
generally besides that
those rollercoaster things like
technical problems
besides that everything was very
exciting and
went fine really quickly but it already
feels like
we all are like a family us five but
also
us in the audience i would say it feels
like
like really grown together a lot already
so so no sad face happy face
yes he's got it huh yeah
my voice is low
how is the volume um is it is it journey
turn up kiana we cycle through everyone
and test
volume and chat yes that's a good idea
just by telling us about your week let's
start off with gouda
okay ah my week was
busy wow last time i checked it was last
week
it felt like yesterday we did the the
last collab
and now here we are again and i'm wiping
jewel from my mouth because there's all
these delicious snacks in front of me
and also the food on it
yes busy week wow wow on to the next one
yay
chat was that all right how was the
volume let us know
good good good girl
well let's move on to uh miss hold on i
got this i got this leave it to me
amelia watson
amelia that was pretty good yeah it was
pretty good
uh my week uh i played a lot of games
playing mario odyssey
i had a lot oh
i froze no
oh no i'm fine for me
for me um yeah it's just me i'll i'll uh
i'll fix it don't worry all right you
guys
continue to test your levels oh yeah
pretend we're all still here we're just
invisible yes we're just invisible for
now but anyway
um yeah i'll guess i guess i'll go ahead
go ahead and go on
uh from here so for me um i enjoyed
um i enjoyed things like getting
destroyed um in doom
eternal which i've really wow i've been
slogging through that game because
fps is really not not something that
your boy is good at i much prefer the
scythe
i much prefer the blade um though but
the ballistic weapons are really just
not for me uh but we are getting through
we are getting through it
uh i came in clutch so to speak at the
end
at the end there with the help of my
chat um giving me many wonderful tips
and also being very patient with me so
that's been fun um
and by way of music uh i finally am
finished with my break and we are
starting music production again this
coming week
it's scheduled that did not seem like a
break
aren't you always romantic like for me i
mean it's still technically a break
right just for music you know i needed a
little one
no kelly it's okay to take a little bit
of a longer break too when it comes to
making music
and i have stuff to do i got news to
produce like every something every week
please take care of your health
kelly yes but i do okay maybe not every
week but i did promise every month
every month okay
i'm looking forward to your future works
thank you i hope that you'll i hope that
you will anticipate them anticipate them
who's up next kiara tell us a little bit
about
about uh about your week
didn't i already tell you about my week
i said it's a roller coaster
but yeah it already feels like a big big
family and uh i also started like a
bunch of different games i started fire
emblem i started super mario 64.
so yeah i also did my first members only
stream yesterday which turned into a
podcast
because i didn't move but it was so fun
i feel really connected
to my my my kiada
fan club kfc members oh that's so sweet
nice oh yeah minecraft manga oh we gotta
get like everyone like i started
minecraft
like a couple of days ago a week ago or
so
and but i hope we can all like
in the near future i'll just play
minecraft together
it does sound funny you anticipated
i wanna build underwater city of
atlantis and minecraft thank you
that's what i'm gonna do i'm an entire
underwater city made of glass
nice yes it sounds fun i want to go
wow could be slightly louder
bum chiara volume uh you're already at
so it might be something on your end
yeah i'm like
i'm like almost eating the microphone
though maybe
is there a way you can turn up the mic
settings for your microphone
specifically
it found maximum okay just shut out then
let's just shout out
try to get at the peak
yeah maybe we can just lower the bgm a
bit and just have that be that
huh okey dokes well let's go ahead and
move on to uh yeah
oh yeah you go ahead go ahead i'm sorry
go ahead
you're good i'm still working on it i'm
still working on it okay okay okay
it's okay um well
i played a couple of different games
today or not today this week
started off with passport tour we do i
do
um everyone's mascot and ottawa senpai
and
marines and phi i continued on with
kolokatsu playthrough i think i'll be
able to finish it
next stream and then
i played a 51 clubhouse games
ahmed and then that by daylight with
girl that was really fun
i haven't played those games before that
was really fun
i hope we could all play that by
daylight together as a whole group
i kind of want to see kiara become the
killer chasing after everyone
i don't know i feel getting us back
getting us back for every time we call
their chicken
yeah um the past week
oh for more fun stuff next week
i still haven't planned it yet though
gotta get more [\h__\h] and kitchen in
there too
me and amelia are chefs now in case you
haven't heard
yes let's get some okay uh we have to go
into
a loading screen for one second just so
we can fix
some problems then we'll be back to
taste some snacks
yeah we're gonna taste these next all
right we'll be right back
[Music]
again then i suppose we will just have
to be cardboard
fine you can listen to the the wonderful
sounds of us munching and
crunching um upon the snacks that we
have gathered here with
today shall we get right into it yes
ladies
grab your pretz
[Music]
so we have at least i know that kiara
and i have
uh we got the same uh about the same a
similar package
so we have the crispy pizza
i have bacon potato i do too
crispy pizza batter crispy pizza
i have a pizza fan give it a taste
baking potato it i'm too loud now
apparently what happens
i'm fixing it i don't know something
with your microwave don't worry about it
i already ate many times i can't open
mine
you can do it well it smells very cheesy
very very soothing
it looks like little bread it's like
tomato
chiata is perfect nowadays oh wait you
were always perfect
thank you
[Laughter]
i was expecting such a reply thank you
thank you
oh is everyone eating it already uh yeah
i'll try it
[Music]
um oh it's like ketchup
you
it tastes very cheesy the pizza the
crispy pizza one
tastes very cheesy i would like to taste
more of the tomato that is on the
package
yeah same very crispy indeed
[Music]
inside i'd give it like um i'd give it
like a
three out of four
oh my god it was so good it's it killed
her
what happened together yeah because i'm
alone
i'm alone by myself
and um i just give you a cardboard image
of myself
[Laughter]
all right i'll send it to you go on
without me go on without me
well as we've seen before a cardboard
image can have a very strong aura
it's true it's true you're absolutely
correct
happens to the best of us am i right
last time it was gotta burn and now it's
my turn
yay i just remember chiara's face just
like staring into the floor
it's it even though i always had the
same expression
this one expression it just said so much
about everything
all right well here i am my cardboard
self
are we gonna rate the preps i mean i
gave it a
i gave it a three out of four but that's
because i was using the fourth scale
because of course why would i not
ah that's a really small scale but okay
i'm gonna use it too
i'm gonna give it three out of four two
i give it give it a two out of four i
give it a
one point eight so we have two out of
four one point eight
um i say two out of four because it's
tasty but i don't taste the flavor
exactly you don't taste the flavor you
don't taste the bacon and what was it
bacon what
bacon potato you don't taste either the
bacon or the potato
no this is just the breadstick
well i guess that's slightly the potato
but not the
not the bacon part oh maybe you have to
wrap real bacon around it
all right ignore that ignore them i'm
really big right now hello look at how
big i am
the bigger the better everyone stands to
my beautiful eyes
only sky is this big home
sorry about that inserting dominance
it was it was starting to hurt my back
the way i was holding it before so
hopefully this is okay we cannot
fix it we're still pretty early in if
you want
i don't want to keep the audience
waiting we must soldier on we can't
go out for it and i finished it yeah
we have time do you want me do you want
me to move i'm
i'm concerned there's a reason i think
that they want me to move and i won't
say it out loud
but like when they choose chat you may
choose what you would prefer
can you guys a minute or two to fix
it and then hopefully that'll be the
last problem we'll have today i think
it'll be fine once we fix it
we'll just extend every minute that we
uh had technical issues we'll just
extend it afterwards
next yeah
yeah we have time all right we'll fix it
i swear we'll be fast very fast
we always are yeah all right we'll be
back goodbye
for now
[Music]
okay
we back
oh my mic is muted hello
hello
i'm sorry about that yeah the pizza one
also mostly tasted like cheese
but not so much apparently fixed i fixed
it
okay okay we're good
okay we were just telling what we
thought about the preps again
oh yeah it would need a bit more taste
right so
my mine tastes a lot like cheese but not
so much like pizza even though it's
supposed to be
crispy pizza but the crispy part is 100
on point
very crispy super quick yum
[Music]
let's go 10 out of 10 breadsticks
kind of buttery almost yeah this is
really buttery
i like it i don't really
i'm moving on to the next one let's go
to the next okay
is one of my favorite japanese chocolate
cookies
oh ma'am it was mama
i think i think me and callie have the
same country mom taste but the others
have different ones is that right
yeah i think we got the same package and
um
japanese me and cali have vanilla but
what do the other
girls have i have vanilla too oh
i have a lot of cookies but i can't find
that one
it says country mom
i guess it's country man
tell
[Applause]
we are all here and we are all hungry
oh my gosh taste right
i like it it tastes like a cookie yeah
it's very it's very soft inside
and the chocolate there's like um the
the the ratio of chocolate versus cookie
is indeed very good balanced
so you get a good amount of chocolate in
your mouth when you eat
the cookie yes tasty but the vanilla
taste is also very prominent i must
sing in my originality
maybe losing some originality points but
it does taste like a good cookie and i
prefer it
it's soft inside yeah it's crunchy on
the outside soft on the inside the best
type of cookie
really yes i agree
it almost tastes like a like how coffee
smells
did you get a different kind of taste
it just has vanilla how does
this taste like coffee smells i don't
know
how many smells like fruit don't like
taste like another food smells actually
interestingly enough
like vanilla flavored coffee
that smells like milk and sugar yeah
[Music]
for sure that was tasty mm-hmm i like
this
[Music]
pasta mm-hmm
we should say don't you start
out four out of four yes
i give it a three out of four it's too
sweet for me
one i can see that i may have to agree
with ame on that just because uh
losing points for lack of originality
like
classics are classics yes that's why
they're good
they are the original because they're
the classic
uh you know okay that's a good point
well maybe i'll go ahead and upgrade it
to a four out of four
not just because the number four but
because i can see where you're coming
now two out of four
what did the madam country do to you
what did you do yeah it's too sweet
too sweet how is that possible i like my
cookies
[Music]
you like salty cookies yeah you know
you're supposed to put salt in chocolate
chip cookies
i know but that doesn't make it salty
it's supposed to emphasize it's more
savory savory
yeah only time i had salty cookies is
when i mistook
sugar for
or salt for sugar no i just look at the
packaging and there is indeed
a salt in there you just don't taste it
my salt powder is very high
you never had this callie no i've never
had a
my bow before i'm gonna try the tail
big cheeto oh whoa
i bought um nine different
flavors of my bowl and i the one i'm
england i think the others maybe don't
have but the one i'm eating is
yakitori taste
um grilled bird grilled chicken
taste so i'm gonna eat this
but it has nothing to do with
cannibalism okay
i mean thinking that until you said it
oh wait it smells really good
it smells so good
mental flavor i don't know what mine
says it's in catholic honey i can't read
it
yes maybe uh
it's orange okay i do not know that i
think it's cheese flavored tea
i'm gonna eat the salad one oh it smells
like yeah i never made
macaroni cheese from the box it smells
like the powder you put in the macaroni
did you hear the crunch oh you crunch so
crunchy
i like it it tastes good i like it a lot
my bowl is so crunchy
it's like somebody made a cheeto a giant
cheeto
no i never ate a cheeto before i never
ate a single before
we should do another snack tasting where
we have uh stuff like that
yeah can we do a snack tasting with
american snacks because i
think i only maybe in my whole life i
make one
american snack before i'm home
i really don't know what i'm working
snacks
i like with the crunchiness because like
you know how
the the the texture of the food can
really change the experience
of your dining experience
the crispiness makes it but much better
even
i give it a full mark i want to eat the
whole thing
i am eating the whole thing open it it's
not it's good
all the flavor
i have to say there are there are some
tastes and some some flavors
from umaibo because there's like tons of
flavors okay and there's
many flavors that i don't like but this
yakitori
flavor is so good i give it a 4 out of
4.
with mine what this is my bowl that i
actually like
who has the corn one hmm
is like pollock roe okay
yummy it's so good
i'm not a fan
it's fish eggs
but it needs much more mentaiko flavor
you need that fishiness to smack me
upside the head when i eat it
why is there is there no salmon in my
bowl you need a small mouth in my bowl
oh i feel like there could be like
grilled salmon
it was so good is there takoyaki in my
food there probably is yeah there is i
think
and i think i have i haven't actually
yeah i have it too you don't have it
i don't
if anything you should be the one having
the takoyaki taste yeah
i don't have a choice
[Music]
big crunch i want to try the chocolate
one you guys have a chocolate one
actually cali how many how many flavors
did you get
i only had two the cheese and the real
flavored one
then i think i have the most flavors i
have like
mine can i tell you all the flavors that
i got so people know what
crazy flavors they have yes okay so i
have
a yakitori the one i ate then i have
teddy teriyaki burger
then i have the corn potage that you
guys have too
nice then i have the
mentaiko that gouda ate then i have the
cheese
one then i have the
oh i bought another mentaiko i'll give i
send them over to yogura i'll ship them
over
yeah and then i have a nori shio adi
which
[Music]
i'm really interested in that one i have
salami
taste salami
oh i love salami so maybe this is also
good let me try
can i try quickly are you i'm opening it
the chocolate one is so weird it's like
not like powder you know how the other
ones are like coated in like a powder
like the chocolate one is coated in like
a weird fudge like a donut
yeah oh well i have to
confess the salami one is not good
the cheese you can't lose with the
cheese because it really tastes like a
cheeto
i raised the salami one zero out of four
what a shame i mean the corn one the
corn one is ten out of ten i already
ate the whole thing that's the classroom
the corn one has been around since
centuries since hundreds of years really
no but it is one of the
the most classic ones but it hasn't been
around
why don't we go into the next like yay
there's like five million five million
on my balls on my keyboard
and next we have papa kameda
[Music]
meaning no peanuts which is fine i don't
think mine has peanuts either they're
like long
they look like some sort of nut
one is just the mini pack yeah oh you
got the skinny one
oh they're hard
a certain japanese airline and they hand
out
this as a snack from a different brand
but it's basically this thing they hand
it out to you when you
i remember the hairline and they're
spicy but it's
not not too tightly wait what are these
i can't tell
it's kind of like they're rice cake rice
rice crackers
i'm actually like really uh sensitive
when it comes to
spicy things but this is still
manageable
yeah manageable right oh so i wasn't
imagining things i feel
seeing it's just a little bit spicy
my tongue is
realized that since i said in the
previous collaboration that in my
previous life it was a flight attendant
and that's why i brought out that
[Music]
how much do we rate these uh rice
crackers two points
four hmm
[Music]
i'll give it a two 2.5 out of four
it's still a bit spicy for me and i
can't see myself finishing the package
this is too spicy for you oh my god
kelly we're meant to be together
it's a little bit too spicy for me so i
give it the same points as kelly
what makes sense though is that you
enjoyed it and i hated it and then i
could say here you have it instead my
love but guess what it doesn't work that
way because we're not together
[Laughter]
all right next is
wait does everyone have the same taste
because i think me and callie have a
normal taste like strawberry yeah
we have some milky taste but the others
have strawberry
oh let's give it a regular
oh it's red yeah
can you open it for me no do it yourself
can you open it with your mouth awkward
ball
can you no please callie please
okay wait almost like you're taking it
yourself oh there's so many
there's some lemon taste in there i like
that
strawberry it tastes like strawberry gum
mine has like a lemony flavor i don't
know how i feel yeah me mind you
no there's like a lemon but i think like
actually um it doesn't taste so
artificial it tastes quite not
like um not okay not maybe not natural
but it tastes
it's not too strong it's like kind of
refreshing it gives the cooking
a bit special flavor so i really like
the lemon taste
i don't know what yes
it smells really artificial
this smells artificial to you yeah
it's like what what my
[Laughter]
i like how you compare the taste of
things with the smell
of things um
i get it
but you guys
our conception our different conception
of how this tastes really
like shows that we're like from all over
the world
we're worldwide because like i'm used to
to
very european tasting things
true i'm used to things that taste like
they're from the underworld
does that taste good that sounds kind of
disgusting
i mean yeah it's true
but i've recently got gotten into human
foods so everything tastes pretty decent
to me
these days since i have a human body
right
i like most everything that isn't super
spicy and
fishy
she's so good i know gouda think of it
this way
me eating less fish means more for you
and the sea so don't worry about it
true true true
i will also offer all my fishies to
yogura
i don't know i kind of i like i'm like
grilled fish
and i like eel but generally you can
have
all the fish i don't need them i'll just
eat chicken okay
i'll take it
[Music]
i used to i really like shrimp
sure help yeah nobody likes fish what
can
i like fish
in my whole life i have never eaten a
shrimp before
huh why not really you know there's a
there's a saying in german that really
applies very well to me it's um
and it means um what the villager
or the farmer doesn't know he won't eat
so i kind of have the problem that i
i i i don't eat a lot of things that i'm
like kind of scared of eating
oh that makes sense that makes sense you
should try it is an adventure
i should try yeah could i can you send
me a good good quality shrimp
oh yeah i got you covered but you got a
lot of shrimp
quite a few quite a few
well ladies shall we move on to the next
snack the next night again
[Music]
kelly kelly huh next snack
is me what but only for you oh what
is it chicken flavor
you can you can have me as the last
snack when the stream is done kelly
i didn't get it but now i understand
um
[Music]
does everyone did everyone ever drink
laminate before
um
anyone who didn't drink lemonade before
no um
all right lemonade is so good i love
ramen
and this this candy like it looks like a
tootsie roll on the picture but like
they're like um
these little uh circle candies they're
hard candies and then they like dissolve
in your mouth yeah
and they're like they have different
yeah i guess they're different flavors
they're like different colors
it's kind of like the texture is kind of
similar to like those chalk heart
candies
oh no yeah i give them i
already give a rating because i don't
like it i give it zero out of four
it's done yeah no no more
good i see you're describing we don't
like these
no no no but like real ramen is so good
but this
no it's like it's like medicine yeah
it is it is a bit like medicine
it doesn't have any vitamins but not
healthy taste
wow like i would think this would be
better um
the only medicine i like is from amen
i like it when she injects it into me
oh
[Laughter]
i need to drink a bit more i'm a bit
thirsty
yeah i get that drink
while
that's not what i see on your desk
purple
salmon milk
like when salmons get babies they also
have milk and that's the same yeah
wait what what
when cows have babies they have cow milk
it's the same thing
oh yeah i don't think that's real
you milk it from salmon they have unders
i just don't think that's real oh well
i'm drinking lemon ice cream because i
love lemon ice cream
okay we're gonna take a small break we
froze but we'll fix it it'll be
very fast
[Music]
do
hello okay
sorry for all the issues i'm surprised
that we actually went on that long
without freezing
i cannot i actually cannot believe we
have
extra extra snack time yeah i think we
all agreed that this one was a piece of
s word so i guess we can move on to the
next
ducks last we have the baby star
rabbit do we have it all in the same
flavor because my flavor
is chicken off the chicken
chicken chicken oh no
well i like i like chicken taste i like
it
feels very familiar to me do you know
what
chicken of the sea is speaking of
chicken
uh yeah tuna yeah
this is also baby star ramen is such a
classic
oh my god so i have a little story about
this oh really
yeah i went to i went to uh the asian
food market
so that i could get uh this this baby
star ramen
and when i went they had it um in a long
what is it
a long connected uh all the packages the
little packages were connected and uh
there are sticks
yeah yeah one on top of the other and
whatnot so i thought
because it was so cheap because it was
so cheap
um only about a dollar fifty
um i thought that i was supposed to tear
one off and go
so i throw one off and i went to the
cash register and i said sir i'd like to
buy this
he said what and i said i want to buy
this and he said
where are the others and i said what are
you talking about this is the one that i
want to buy the poor
the poor freaking the poor friggin
inconvenience store clerk
asian food inconvenience store clerk
looks at me and says no
get all of them and i say what and and
we couldn't i didn't me
i didn't know what he meant and so he
said come with me
and let me let me back to where i was we
searched and i said oh there it is
and he said yeah you're supposed to take
you're supposed to take all six of them
and i said really
yeah and i'm like this is a dollar fifty
so yeah i'm like all right
so now i have way too many of them i'm
like this cannot be real
that is also the reason why i have ten
with my balls
i tried to buy only two i went to the
register just like you
and then they're like eh you gotta buy
10 of them and i'm like
i don't even like most of the tastes i
don't want to buy
10 but i had to
this is so cheap they give you like they
they throw them after you they're like
bye
all of them does it taste like ramen
you guys do you taste like mcdonald's
oh
thank you for saying that i like these
little noodles they're like little
noodle chips but they're like actually
noodles but they're like fried or
something i don't know
mm-hmm something supposed
really thin pretzels well some people
actually do eat raw
uh ramen out of the package i'm not one
of them i know that they're ready
what not what yeah you take
all the sauce and then you like shake it
up and then you eat it
what kind it's good um
what that i mean that's that's cool like
you can do
that it's just pretty weird
you either drop you eat it raw but you
put the sauce over it
yeah that is so weird people that you're
all roman are completely normal
those of you that rocks uh pasta like
that pasta you guys are the weird ones
that is true
i guess but there's a difference there
indeed
but i don't i've never heard of anyone
eating raw pasta
yeah that's a little exactly too much
i feel like that's something that i did
it's eternity eternity ago
uh when i was a little reaper many many
millennials
but that's not how you made me curious
now now i want to try
raw ramen yo i really want to know now
that's what you do with the pieces at
the bottom you shake them on your
mama
i mean i i mean i guess because if you
cook them they become like really really
short noodles and they're hard to pick
up so you just eat them while they're
raw
that's a weird reason but okay
it's a different kind of snack for you
it's it's for normal
people it's a like a dinner or something
for you to snack
by the way i give the baby star ramen a
four out of four
yeah it's pretty good you know four out
of four
two point but one why
i give it a two out of four it doesn't
taste like anything
yeah what do you mean there's like ramen
more chicken
flavor yeah more chicken
i mean you could live off of it if you
were really having a hard time
i really like it it's like a really
classic
snack that i could snack on anytime but
it's too small
it's too small yeah i want bigger to
pick up that's why you get six packages
and then you just like hold the package
as if you're like drinking out of it and
then ah
throw it all into your mouth i think
that's how you're supposed to eat it
i think it would be good on pizza or
like if you could do it
oh yeah the topping or salad
yeah it's like croutons that's a good
idea
the pizza idea idea sounded weird to me
but the salad crouton idea sounds really
good to me
oh an ice cream that might be good
actually because somehow
then again there are humans that
apparently dip their french fries into
milkshake
yeah that's pretty good
since this tastes like mcdonald's it's
basically the same thing i guess
wow mcdonald's
wait does anyone in ella eat
french fries with ice cream does anyone
do that yeah
awful yes what this sounds wow
never heard of that you know yeah like a
milkshake and you dip fries in it
oh my god terrific it's delicious
absolutely i'll try it next time it's
getting
surprised does my flurry work
yeah you know okay i'll try next time
i'll let you know
[Music]
all right our next section
it says individual snacks that's right
oh
boy we have individual snacks and i
can't i can zoom in if you guys like
need help describing what you're eating
because like uh no i think it's fine how
does that mind yeah it's good
yeah it should be okay well let's see if
there's individual snacks behind my head
i am cali's individual snack
shut up all right i want to kick this
off who wants to kick this off
yeah what you got over there huh fishy
ones
yeah welcome to the sea shanty
all right we got
sorry about that well okay we're okay
okay we're good
we've got oh boy
uh mysterious fish sticks
mysterious dried small fish
we've got mysterious
thing uh in bag
full brown thing in bag and then we've
got it
[Music]
are we trying these are we just
describing these yeah eat all of them at
the same time
how about we go through and then
everybody describes theirs and then we
can try
we can start snacking okay yeah yeah
uh my friend and i have it's like a
it's a soda lollipop so it's like fizzy
and it's got a lot of powder in it i
don't know it's kind of like
[Music]
a lollipop i think you'd like it and dip
it
it's panicking what's that
it's called panicu that's the name
yeah and then i have like these things
they kind of they're like pop rocks
and um i don't know what flavor it is
they're purple
purple flavor and then
i have this giant rope and it's like uh
covered in sugar and it's like gummy
it's like the airtight thingy it's like
a giant lawn
like a nerd's robe yeah yeah sort of
yeah like just the thing inside not with
the nerds on it
and then i have a small melon candy
which i'm looking forward to this little
tiny green
candy
nice sounds tasty here's i've got i've
got the classic
koala march which is um they're little
they're little koala koala dudes and
they have um
chocolate inside of them um it's
apparently a very popular snack
for children in japan so i'm excited to
eat the koala marches
and let's see i've got uh this says
donatsu
and it's got so many donuts yeah many
donuts inside a box
i think you're supposed to make them
yourself oh
wait a minute wait a minute yeah you're
supposed to make them yourself
good job kelly good job
now wait a minute i can come up with
something else hold on i have
i have uh i got the you here there's
some gummies i got some gummies
um and they remind me of um who is this
there's like a superhero dude on them
and uh
i i picked them out because the sword
and the shield reminded me of the
weapons that that hook
papa designed for kiara that took it
are you followed because it reminded you
of me
no i just i like the design of the
weapons so that's why i chose them
i haven't said it completely let's move
on i also got uh there's an interesting
one that i chose because it was kind of
weird
this looks like um it looks like a pig a
pig body and it has it's labeled
all the different parts of the pig um
it's like a chocolate
a chocolate with the different pig parts
so you can learn the pig anatomy
um so yeah i'm gonna look at the pig
anatomy while i eat this pig
it's chocolate cool you can educate us
it's right
yes sensei yeah
all right what about you
[Music]
okay so actually one thing in my lunch
box
seems to have been mixed up because the
breads we all ate together in the
beginning oh yeah yeah
um so instead of the pretz i have
another classic
it's called black thunder black sanda
it's like a chocolate uh cookie that is
covered in chocolate and inside it's
like a crispy
um thing that i cannot describe but it's
really good
and i have eaten this before so it's a
it's a safe one
then i got a pocky that
is uh in the taste of lemon
and peach so that's really yummy
that sounds like very um
good to me it sounds very refreshing and
summerish
on my in my lunch box it's on the left
side
what is this it says if there's like it
says it has like a sweet
honey taste and it looks like popcorn
but i think it's probably something like
yeah it's a rice snack
in honey yeah those are good
and the last one i
i heard kelly also bought this so this
is fate
i i did find the curb the last one
is on the right side of my lunchbox it's
a curvy gummy it's really cute
it's really small and really pink and
it's uh it's peach flavored there were
other flavors actually but i chose the
peach flavor because
i like peaches mine are peach and apples
so not totally matching
just so you know okay okay for reference
for the people
those are my snacks yay
actually i got something similar to cali
i got the hamburger version where you
have to make your own
snack and i decided to make it
beforehand
nice this is the smart one the smart one
is right here
hey um i should say that i already ate
it
of course but um i
i was surprised because i thought it was
gonna be one of those like you know like
food-shaped gummies
i thought it's gonna be like that but it
actually tastes like a hamburger
and fries and coca-cola
but the texture was like the gummy gummy
oh
no no the texture was like bread meat
and cheese
with eww yeah it was weird
that's so way weird what is it made out
of good
everything wasn't like like powder form
and then you add a bit of water to it
microwave it and then put it together
what you're like a scientist
i felt very smart so you couldn't pour
all the powders in your mouth because
that's warm and wet like a microwave
[Laughter]
i don't think you're supposed to just
put the powder straight into your mouth
i don't think that's how it works
you gotta actually have to cook it
because who knows what's in
those powders but it was good it was
uh i'd rather order an actual hamburger
it's like it took like 30 minutes to
make it i was like you know what i could
have just ordered ubereats
30 minutes for like a really tiny thing
right how big was it like your thumb
it was like it was like yeah it was
around my thumb
and it was definitely not worth it
anyways um what else do i have
it's a anpanman soft sundae
so it's just some babe i don't know what
flavor it is
a coconut sauce
[Music]
it looks like some kind of cracker
coconut cracker looking thing
[Music]
and then i have uh
kokuma gumi which is just really small
uh i forget the name
like gummy bears yeah scallions
really tiny gummy bears is that like a
haribo
fake
they don't talk about that because when
you say
gummy bears the only thing that i can
think of is that
i wonder how they'll taste okay i think
we can dig in
we're back in bus let's dig in yes
because i have the same ones i'm going
to try oh corn
actually i'm gonna
eating the curvy gummies already haha
beat you to the place i want to try it
i probably should koala marches real
good i'll eat the quad marks
are these fish sticks are they fish
strips
it looks like the jerky the the red
packet right
yeah those are really good i like them
[Music]
smells very fishy
i do not envy you i do not envy you me
neither
am i supposed to suck on it or just eat
it
do it rubbery
just do it don't let your dreams be
dreams oh my goodness
i don't like it i don't like it
[Music]
give it to gouda she's right in front of
you don't give it to us
i think i bought that one too that you
got and i didn't really want to buy it
because i knew i wouldn't like it
[Music]
they're really good with um a certain
carbonated uh
maybe alcoholic drink
him i like um
i like sucking on the koala marsh until
it melts in my mouth
and really i like to eat the cracker and
then like leave the chocolate
and then chocolate
did you eat that fish yet there's like
there's like i was just about to ask you
it's like a tiny little fish that is
sliced open in half and then like
spread open and it's like it looks like
it's candied or something
don't try it oh i hate it
you eat the whole thing should we go all
in yeah yeah i'm gonna eat the whole
thing i'll take a bite
come on you just put the whole thing in
my mouth now
i'm moving on
oh it smells so nice to peach kirby
gummy smells so nice
yeah um
you could save it for a batsu game like
how i sometimes drink spirits when i uh
start speaking english during an english
band stream
what does travis need wow that's really
good it tastes like real fish
i mean it is a real fish
[Laughter]
it's like a candy fish yeah
i'm moving on to my first snack to the
to the
corts tell me who that is
what that is how that is that's the yeah
that's the one on the left side online
tell me i'll tell how how it tastes
or should i feed you the cashier also
also gave me sticks i'm just ignoring
you the cashier also gave me six of
those
is it sweet they're salty they gave you
six of those
uh it was the same situation as the baby
star ramen
oh i think probably you got like a small
version of it and i got like the big
version
yeah i think so i better be good um
what so crunchy mmm oh
oh this is like i really like it you
should eat it it's like
you know the the rice crackers that were
really spicy that we had
uh-huh it's like that but not spicy it's
more like sweet
i'm curious i'll try some i have a
question actually
for everyone no i'm curious no
if you had to spend all of eternity
eating either
sweet desserts or salty snacks sweet
what would you choose
sweet sweets
salty healthy salty
you have to pick one yes you must choose
either
and you can't have the other ever what
no it's the challenge just to balance
each other out
oh no right but you must choose uh salty
steam probably me is choosing sweets
yup looks like
i get sugar overload and so you guys
would
would go for never eating chocolate ever
again
that's not a snack that's a dinner snack
there's a hamburger in front of me it's
a hamburger oh well done that is a snack
that is indeed a snack because that's
not a real real hamburger
humber hamburger oh my gosh
there he goes um it's interesting
because actually yeah there he goes
um what's up ghost rider
yeah give them some big ups and shout
outs you guys um
interestingly enough i put um that my
one of my favorite things are sweet
treats
but the bad news about that lads is that
um i actually can't eat sweets very much
because
i get overloaded and i get really sick
very quickly which is why i wanted to
mention
eating all these snacks i i've gotten
very sick
if i eat too many snacks yeah like
really really quickly
go found some more of that wine then no
maybe not there he goes thanks ghost
writer for the super chat i always
appreciate it
[Laughter]
um
oh i want to hear your reaction eating
that
have you ever eaten umeboshi ah yeah
i've had
my mercy before oh okay okay then you
know what's coming
hey this looks not like what um i've had
before
oh now it's like a flattened dried one
[Music]
um oh yeah that's fine it tastes like
you know it smells like a raisin
it's like oh
it's a big salty raisin
it's sour yeah it's sour it's a little
sour but it's not bad
it's very very sweet for um
me yummy
[Music]
well there's the sour there it
there it is you guys can continue
but i think it's i think it's the end of
the line for me i just need to drink my
zoo
too many snacks take it easy
[Music]
that's all right that's all right
i also gotta drink my lemon iced tea
nope nope nope nope
take this corn you got a lollipop i'm
gonna try to bite it in half
oh right yeah
[Music]
so i'm pretty much done eating too
i mean i'm not gonna eat everything now
so not completely
just a snacky snack yeah i guess we
don't have to go grocery shopping
we have i have snacks now for the next
five months
because i i not only bought the things
that are in my lunchbox i bought like
five million other things too
the texas is called vinegar
oh yeah it looks like tater tots
are we gonna rank the individual ones
too
yeah i was gonna ask what your favorites
were out of everything that you tried
yeah
if you guys are finished kind of judging
i suppose we could start with gouda if
you want
oh boy that's me okay
okay
okay adam all right we all love them
we're good
[Music]
so i would say my favorite was the the
small fish
in the package
[Music]
and then i would say the fish strips the
yay
fish strips were number three and last
would be the corn
including the ones that we ate together
oh my favorite yeah
uh um
you know go ahead i'm still trying mine
this is like little pills with little
rocks
hmm what
what pop rocks
okay out of my out of the oh i haven't
tried the milk i'm not ready can i go at
the end
i hope you feel bad i'm okay guys don't
worry
don't worry about me i'll be okay i just
need to keep drinking some water
don't worry about me i'm good i'm good
ah let's see what did i like um
let's see probably a bit boring but i
really like
the countryman cooking
yeah it's a good choice for the saltiest
um i really like
uh the baby star ramen
[Music]
um and also the umaibo cheese flavor was
quite good but i would have to put it at
second behind this yeah
my evaluation nice gummies didn't
look anything really just the sugar just
a whole bunch of sugar lumped together
that's for the usual that's how it
always ends up for me
i can eat one gummy and then i'm already
tired of them
curse all righty how about you kusatori
[Music]
thank you mama and
mama oh wife
i guess it should be why thank you wife
okay my favorite i think
was huh i think the
i have two two at the same place
i would say the black thunder and the
the kochu butsuko i like them
about the same so they were my favorites
from my uh even in total with all the
other ones together but i also
enjoyed the country mom it was a classic
and yeah my um was really good
too though the specific uh
flavor that i had yakitori i like that
one
but with my bowl generally i don't
really like them
the other tastes but this one was good
so i would say a
black thunder boots
yakitori taste yes
thank you gucci sauce
[Music]
my favorite sweet one was definitely the
the cookie
the country ma'am cookie
oh it's very popular we all like it
right
yeah it's like the perfect cookie
crunchy on the outside soft on the
inside not too sweet
well at least for me um and for the
savory i'm gonna have to go with the
corn potage in my book
is anime ready now
hold on wait i'mma are you not done with
your investigation yet
i like pretty good time all right
i want to do this until microphone if
you guys don't mind
[Laughter]
it feels nice
um out of all of them i'd say the corn
oh it's still happening whoa the corn oh
my god
i like that one the best it's like nice
and sweet and savory and creamy
and corn i like corn and
um but personal snacks i got this little
tiny ah
[Music]
what's happening okay can we get some
more popping i asked tomorrow we want
hold on
do a whole stream of that
um yeah my personal favorite from the
personal individual snacks is little
melon candy
it tastes good um
that's it
[Music]
yes and
five years later ahmed was still popping
in her mouth
[Laughter]
nice i think yeah we all set our
favorites yeah
good snack we did it we did it guys
pat's pot
daddy did it
let's take a deep breath after that yeah
food coma i didn't
i take food comas so i i don't i don't
take food coming up so easily i just
i slip into them so easily after i eat a
ton of snacks or food
as soon as i as if i lay down for just a
moment i'm out this human body is so
strange i don't know lies
i don't know well before
i guess i guess before we close all of
this off does anyone have
any announcements they want to make
anything big happen no
no nothing ah but guys oh my god
i okay i have two things to to mention
first of all we did all this snack
eating and and all have like five
million snacks in front of us
what are we gonna do with the leftovers
you know what which month it is
it is spooky spooky's booktober we
all prepared halloween snacks to give
out to the cute lovely children
already we don't even have to buy
anything more
we are prepared no one comes to trick or
treating at my house
and one more thing and one more thing i
wanted to mention
so that we all have it in our
head and realize what's happening in one
month
our collab band is lifted oh in a few
days
a month or nine or how many days
wait what did i say one month yeah
i mean i meant one one week in one week
hour one month
ben has lived up yeah yes
yeah yep i can't wait oh my god
i'm invited then we're going out in the
big big
world to our senpais it'll be scary
and exciting
[Music]
collaboration time
but i still like um this this week
this week you since i was kind of busy
with moving
i couldn't collab so much with you girls
but i really want to collab more with
you
you i missed out on a lot of fun this
week so maybe
you girls want to collab with me next
week before we go
out in the big big collabing world with
japan
and indonesia and china talents
so yeah i was gonna ask you i have i
actually
have a minecraft thumbnail ready for the
two of us to go play minecraft together
is it the one that was fan made
yeah so let's go minecraft maybe we can
all before the collab ban
ends uh we can all just have another fun
maybe a fun minecraft uh collaboration
or something together you have to do
that first it's nice
or something yeah
the only one who is left to not host it
is good
so i guess it's going to be good
by then also we did um we did cali's
[\h__\h] in kitchen
like we had the idea that we'll continue
playing overcooked but since it's only
four players we thought we might like
swap out
um some people so like maybe two collabs
this week or something we can schedule
it yeah we have inna and kiara
and we swap them out we can all play
yeah yeah that's a good idea i like that
let's do it let's make it happen yeah
yeah i
said this in one of my streams before
but um
i really i really want to like have more
time with us five to cover because uh
things are going so fast and i just i
really really love this
small family that we have so i wish we
can have some more wholesome
time together yeah i want to play more
games with everyone
yeah sounds fun i got some permission
for some other fun party games cat wink
that i'll have to tell you guys
about later some of them only have four
player which is a shame but yeah
it's fine more collab opportunity yeah
yeah rotating
yeah that's all i had to say
i don't have any announcements yeah i
have a schedule going up tomorrow or
monday
that's it yeah go ahead um
yay
my schedule will be up for members
shortly after this
collab um and then we'll come out for
everyone a little bit later
uh so yeah it's like that and also i
have a i'm doing a music i'm doing a
live show a concert it's free
i gotta go which is it again
it's october the 16th 17th it depends on
where
you are in the world but i will be
posting the yay
thanks i'm posting the poster on my
social media
and youtube very soon and i will also
schedule uh
the live stream at that time so that you
can set a reminder so yeah keep your
eyes
peeled oh i can't wait i wanna open your
kelly live
yeah yeah will you sing
i'll be doing my own and then i'll be
doing approved songs
that will allow me to archive the stream
i think
it's exciting yep
you know you have anything uh nope
schedule soon
that's it
okay nice well thank you everyone
who became members and everyone who
super chatted and came to watch and hang
out with us and try snacks it was fun
thanks for bearing with our technical
difficulties we are we are getting
better at this
i promise
thanks to the technical difficulties we
extended the stream a lot
yeah yeah yeah i think it was fine in
the end i do want to say
also um i thank you um
to everybody that helped um with the
collaboration like planning and stuff
yeah uh ina helped um she made the boxes
and then gura made the doodles and then
kelly uh
organized the outline and also did like
the chalk
the chalkboard um aside from the girls
doodles
and then um kiara was uh
emotional i was moving i was moving so i
didn't do anything she was busy but
she yeah she's a good sport too yeah
thank you to everyone
just because um it is on my it's on my
channel but everyone really contributed
uh for for this collab because your boy
was real busy
so i wanted to give a big thanks to all
my homies
my crew um we we really we really kind
of
we work well together when it comes to
like putting putting stuff together and
like getting s word
i'm surprised i'm really excited for
crunch time
and i'll get into work mode it's so
funny
it's so funny when we gather and we're
like okay we have 30 minutes left
it's like five minutes it was
literally 30 minutes not even kidding
but it was fun and it worked out it's
because we're a great team
so i guess with that being said go to
sosa everyone
we're going to end here you should say
something at the same time like timed
okay cool okay uh what should we say
that
yeah yeah let's do that at the same time
because we have a delay anyway
okay i'll say three two one go
okay ready hey all right here we go
three
two one go
[Music]
hey everybody's
thank you for channel
[Music]
please dessert i am
you