[Music]
hey
ah
ah k
k
K chat chat hello hello I know it looks
like I have no arms that's like the
standard
pose St my my standard state of
body in this form I look like a like a
salt or pepper
shaker shake me shake me let me spread
salt over your
eggs shake me shake me wait I want to
shake
myself let's you guys are the eggs right
you guys are next let me cut
[Music]
here you guys are so
salty nice salty
[Music]
eggs I think it would be great merch
yeah yeah yeah small hat the
[Music]
Hat
okay what am I doing I'm a salt
shaker salt shaker
shakeer salt shakeer
shakeer Sal shakeer shakeer
shake
shake yeah they are my arms they just go
back into my body by default but I have
[Music]
hands
hi
I please await announcements about such
things I will not answer maybe I should
H I should have a press release
yeah I'll have a I'll have a press
release let's do press
[Music]
release
okay
no more information for
you announcement announcement the flock
has arrived locking your heart in a cage
for good
[Music]
time spotlights on us make some room on
the floor give us a sweet salit we want
to
Anor
not
acceptable no it's not related but just
somebody was like announcement
announcement
song
okay uh so in order for you guys to not
see my non-existent hands and make fun
of me I am hiding them like
yesterday you didn't say anything
yesterday guys because you didn't see
it can't complain about what you don't
see right what you don't think should be
existing do the H
dance dance at over 4 million views oh
well it definitely did incredibly well
and it will definitely lead to more
eventually I made some
tea so that maybe today I can get
through the toad voice a bit better I I
still shouldn't do it too much obviously
cuz yesterday it was really painful at
the
end even though I was taking fruit
candies to barely shows up from now on
that's good that's good okay let
me oh you can see my hands I'm pouring
I'm pouring honey into
the cup oh I forgot I forgot got a
spoon damn it I have an
unwashed uh
merchandise the cocktail s
stick
but yeah can I get a
spoon can I get a a
spoon a little
spoon
[Music]
okay I I am big
spoon you are small
spoon okay I got the
spoon I uh t t still has to
wet some
water we're in for a comfee
stream did I bring my phone yeah I
brought my phone I brought my phone I
got the phone okay ah before we
start before we start
let me start with a
[Music]
tangent let me start with Tangent
because this tangent has pictures two
only short
one my I met my my brother
today and uh last time when I went to
Japan like he asked me to bring him some
random
gcha uh
winnings item and I didn't do it because
I didn't get to go to gacha
place
but this time I did because I went for
you know the small literally what I am
right now this I've went for myself
small Wawa uh gacha
machine M didn't get myself though
but while I was there I thought oh wait
wait my bro my bro he wanted um
something anything he said something
silly and boy did I get him something
[Music]
silly
um I was looking through the Gata P
machines and just looking for something
interesting and I found an interesting
type of ear
plugs and I remembered my brother like
talking about using
earplugs uh a lot uh I
think maybe while he was staying at my
place or also elsewhere I don't know
maybe maybe while he was on the
pilgrimage um so I thought oh perfect
just has an instant connection and it
looks really silly it looks so silly
[Music]
so let me show
you the special ear plugs but the thing
is one GTA ball had only one earplug
inside you so you were kind of forced to
get at least two and then the chance of
them being matching is really
low
T
tentacle H get
tentacle earplugs tentacle and and and
fish
worm earplugs now why did it go back
like this but you can see what it is
[Music]
right it's it was silly and
cute
[Music]
t
to and I got the first one I got is the
the the the tentacle one on the left
side which I was quite happy about and
then I I I thought okay I need a second
one because if you use an earplug you
probably want both ears to be plugged
right not just one like what's the
purpose so I did a Second Spin and I
thought I got the same but I was
Bamboozled all I was seeing was this
like paper inside the ball and I thought
I had another tentacle but I was
wrong uh but now when opening it it was
a nice surprise actually cuz the the
other one is pretty cute and it's
basically a
Taki and a orange yellow takoi look at
this these are the things I
[Music]
got
yeah it's an orange Taco like it has
ears like the taco dais I was like what
the do a
takoi yeah Taco MIM Taco MIM
taco and I think I didn't realize this
right away but I think it's a it's a d
it's a word play cuz in Japanese when
you say Mimi T you have a taco in your
ear I think it's supposed to mean like
you you you you're hard of
hearing like you can make fun of someone
like do you have a taco in your ear it's
like saying like why don't you why do
you keep on asking me to repeat what I'm
saying like dude are you like uh
incapable of
[Music]
hearing
so you put a taco in your ear and you're
literally becoming harder of
hearing my brother you I I made him we
were in a restaurant I made him I forced
him to put them in his ears he was
really embarrassed but he found them to
be really cute and funny so mission
accomplished but he was embarrassed to
put them in
[Music]
so so so
so yeah but he said I mean they don't
really block the noise much it's it's
pretty like ineffective in that purpose
and so like
what is he ever going to use it after
this probably not but it's a funny item
he wanted something from magacha machine
and he got
it
yeah utub ah see the thing is like all
of these are like single ones except for
the utub the yellow
one apparently the yellow one you would
have gotten two plugs in one but the all
the others are like single so they're
forcing you to get more but that one's
like on one ear you get the head and on
the other ear you get the tail sticking
out you see that the yellow
one yeah the
eel damn it it's 400
[Music]
Yen now I have two like
totally
unrelated
tacos
M yeah but the taco D is so cute I
almost wanted to keep
it okay but they are related not really
they look so
different GAA will want that no Ena
would want
that let te
time
haven't used my Fus in a long
[Music]
time oh I dripped some hot tea on my
pajama pants thank God they're fuzzy
enough to protect me oh my God you can
see me saring my
tea you can see and
here it's too hot now I can't drink it
now
waiting for the
tea okay okay now we can play the
game Mario let's play the
game where do we go next ah here a yeah
yeah yeah we stopped at the city last
time the new
city did you get k no of course I didn't
because they sent it
back cuz they're little
shits stupid little
[Music]
shits I don't know when I will ever
receive all these things the H talk
things as well what am I supposed to do
here a talk let's talk with them ah
probably have to go inside here please
Mom you're going to help us okay oh oh
oh you hear the audio yeah you probably
what's happening up there is she still
working up a
sweat yeah it's all at the man
everyone's digging and digging I can't
keep up with
them
what
what what what are they
doing I'm guessing I have to go in here
oh oh dear I sure hope the kids are
okay the way they try their best in this
game to express emotions with jumps all
the
time it's so
cute I know how you feeling but Ming
around here ain't going to help a
[Music]
thing why is the movement so funny man
what the way she leaves too like take a
few steps backwards take a few steps
backwards take a few steps backwards and
then turn around and then leave who what
was
that no what I said but I don't think
I'd be feeling any different if I was
her we're getting knowwhere fast we'll
never reach the kids at this rate
finging that out there that's the old
entrance to the
mines ah but we can't reach it
anymore yeah it's it's very
Charming it's trying to be a faithful
adaptation is it's just so goofy so
silly if only that fellow uh Mario were
here he could reached that in a
heartbeat W oh was speak of the devil
yeah leave it to me nice nails you got
there oh oh oh they're running on the
same
spot oh oh they're so excited to see me
well I'll be Goomba's Uncle if it ain't
him in the flesh Mari you're a lifesaver
Mari have you heard the news yeah uh I
mean I think someone's stuck in there
right of course of course I'll help
you thanks Mario well there's the
entrance up
there oh yeah I'll I'll hop on you I was
thinking it might not be high uh low
enough for
me if you giving me support that's
another story oh dear oh oh oh he's
speing so
scary yeah okay we got to
fight who am I fighting now okay lava
bubble and Bob B all right uh I don't
know we don't have so many points PL
points so let's start
normally ah oh yeah right timing
timing is the thing
right
oh
nice last time PE many people have made
fun of
me for
missing the timings I don't know am I am
I missing the attacks right now too I'm
not sure if it's like uh if the the
attack
number is in that like yellow Kaboom
shape does it mean I I got the
[Music]
timing uh this one was
not correct right but but this no I
don't know was that I don't know
I I don't I can't
tell you can tell from if you hear Chim
you did it oh what the are those
clusters what scary
[Music]
looking that was ah ah that was it that
was actually uh correct huh a this one
too is that the
sound is that the sound I'm looking
for uh that was not the right
timing but it still
did a lot of damage what the
what what what how much how much HP did
Gino have that he
died double your coins yeah y see see
okay I got him on the right side so I've
never missed this one
before it it was hey that was certain
what the
[Music]
for know what do we want to go for
uh this one has a bonus 53 to 59 the
others are just one
up should we go for the one with the
bonus we have more dancers now they
dancing
together okay okay
okay that's why I told you to go for the
Clusters first not hold on uh oh yeah
wait uh let's do ah oopsie ah oh did I
just use a flower box and a
FP eh I only used one item did I cuz if
you raise your FP it uh recharges them
too
right
okay I didn't accidentally use two items
did
[Music]
I I wonder if gentle beam is effective
against the lava
[Music]
bubbles
nice this one doesn't make the sound but
it said perfect so I guess it shows you
in a different
way m
[Music]
m
n oh that
one self-destruction that one also
didn't um was I didn't time it correctly
man I'm so bad at
this there's enough to Mr
bonuses well I'm playing I'm not playing
for OBS but I I do have some
apparently there is some lag even even
if you like uh play through the game
capture card right so I will just blame
it on that thank you Ravel you're drunk
hopefully just a little don't drink
anymore okay let's drink some
water let's drink some water and lay
down and watch my
stream and relax thank you though eight
damage that's it that's it okay never
let's never use that again oh wow that
was
good against the Leva bubble nice that's
a lot of damage guys
shees oh nice a triple triple
timing triple times correct timing
nice
[Music]
okay understood n good you seem to
be ready open to listening to
me I I the other day I was watching a
really
incredible
[Music]
um police body cam footage of like a
drunk
driver um it's so funny my my God and I
was wondering cuz I never have been like
let me turn off my hands I've never been
drunk before right
so it makes me wonder
like is it
like when you
like when you're
[Music]
drunk like
how how
much I I don't know I I don't even know
I don't even know what I want to ask
anymore but it's just fascinating to me
drunk people fascinating to
me how
oh how
ridiculously different people might be
when they're
drunk it's like when you're super tired
and your brain doesn't work
right do m
M no I don't even I don't I wanted to
ask you guys something about being drunk
but I forgot what it was I guess I have
to watch another
video I was like oh I'm going to ask my
viewers something about being drunk at
some point later cuz I don't I don't
know how it
is let's ask them instead but I don't
remember what I was going to
ask how is strong Calli the friend
Callie
[Music]
cie
I I don't think I've really I feel like
she has quite a high tolerance
because like even after two glasses I
feel like she's still pretty
normal
um and I'm I'm used to different
things
so I feel like either she has a high
tolerance or she's just the same for
like a while while until she gets really
really a y I made a
mistake oh it broke anyway until she
gets really really really really really
drunk maybe then she gets
[Music]
different two glasses is nothing I I I I
know people where they drink one glass
and they can already tell a difference a
big difference in their
behavior B p
p everyone has a limit yeah everyone has
different tolerance I suppose I don't
even know what my tolerance would
be let's just attack normally at
one wait it has
babies now I don't want to kill it
anymore how can I kill his whole
[Music]
family oh they don't have that much
uh HP do
that yeah he wait low damage sh what
still only
[Music]
one family
dead stone family
dead oh yes double double them again Yos
see in the
middle okay again righted side Yi Yoshi
I know where my Yoshis are you can't
fool me I have a six cents for my
Yoshi's oh
hi hey have you heard there's RS hidden
in the mines if I find any I'm going to
sell them to someone in town I'm in it
for the
money he's honest oh wait I
wonder is there something here I think I
still have the pin on don't I on
Gino
it's literally asking for me
[Music]
to jump on it who who what's happening
why why why why did I B bunk my head at
the
top Croco is
back coins beautiful coins grab the
coins no no no no no no hey no you can't
do that no
way
rted wait how many coins did you
take Mario Coco got us
again she took our coins too let's chase
him down and get them back okay
definitely scripted how many did I I am
really down to zero like if I wanted to
leave now and go to a shop and buy stuff
I literally wouldn't be able
to
n
there they
are looks like dead end here but not to
worry I've got a bom never leave home
without
them oh thank you you're opening up this
path for me
too so let's
go uhoh the coins are Minish you now you
got items to use in the B
[Music]
uh yeah but what if I run out of them
like now let's say I don't have full
inventory of items and he steals my
money y y oh wait a triple move I don't
know I I I just want to can I
not can I not do the toad thing or is
that only for Mario cuz now I'm on
[Music]
Gino oh oh nice that was really
good toad is gone I can't get the toad
move
anymore
[Music]
oh now I don't want to use up the Triple
move just for such shitty
[Music]
enemies see normal attacks are
fine oh
nice nice hey I'm getting better I'm
better than
yesterday you telling me there's nothing
here
really then why is it possible to get up
[Music]
here
what about you oh oh they're spinning
boys fast wait should I just go this way
first where I actually know they're
going wait hold
it what this looks like
hoton this looks like
a hatas fence fused together
what the hell okay I shall use one star
RAR attack against one
Enigma wow 250
damage oh
I'll try a super
jump yeah it oh it's it is their
weakness I wonder if if a super jump is
your weakness is a normal jump also
their
[Music]
weakness
uh another
one SP let's try a normal
jump probably should be
in yeah okay
[Music]
[Applause]
wasn't super jump the
com no you're mixing up some things it's
totally not
o you little where did you leave
your boss your crocodile boss
[Music]
huh
okay K get oh no they're all leaving all
of
[Music]
them
cowards you just wait we'll get that for
this maybe not today maybe not tomorrow
but someday he didn't have the coins on
him but he dropped a flower tab
okay can I get up
there
no I don't think
[Music]
so I caught him
off I think he was going to leave the
room down there but I caught him off
[Music]
early hey I'm not healed though
uh
well
[Music]
whatever got to
try
[Music]
um I guess I'll keep points for a heal
or yeah let me use the honey syrup and
then bow will
[Music]
heal got a
freey
y on Gino and let's hope mow won't die
in a week you become a phoenix P come oh
I forgot to I forgot you have to
push something there too bomb nice cuz
the bomb does a lot of damage it would
have killed mow for
sure
[Music]
um here we
go 58 I mean could be
better do you like a
fireball it says weakness but it only
does
[Music]
15 you the
Y that's that's like ridiculous
ridiculously low
[Music]
what I was try my best to mash I even I
even used my other hand
finger nice he keeps on going from mow
ah cuz of his magic being low ah yeah
maybe I should put some points into
magic for
[Music]
him I
see wonder if a thunderbolt would be
worth
it okay not wor it we learn and we lose
but we win in the
end and we're getting more timing rides
very
good I
miss
oh ah this time I didn't get it
um need some
[Music]
FP and Mario will just attack normally
again I guess
it's pretty
decent what's that no what was that you
want them back what are you stealing
again and
leaving oh no he's not
[Music]
leaving okay this time did more
damage
yes um let's try the super jump
again oh I got three hits this time okay
I'll get
better I understand the timing now I
thought that you really have to press it
like last last last last last
millisecond but no it's quite early
while he's still out of screen almost
[Music]
yeah only 28 damage and maybe I should
just attack normally for the rest of
this fight it's kind of ridiculous
but
oh nice
[Music]
block
19 yeah it's like I'm playing
volleyball why is the damage so
different oh that was a
Miss why is it why is it not like stable
damage enough already did I get
[Music]
you the hell was that anyway what about
the rest of my
[Music]
money no stop does he still have my
things no I guess we're done I picked up
a micro bump ooh where shall we use that
oh we're back
here oh I
originally went that way right this
[Music]
way yeah
po there was one room move two paths
no like another one ah this
one oh to the left to the left
[Music]
getting the timing right but like I
barely get the AOE
thing
today
ouch the stoner
family what a happy family
man you know I found out some
something
today that I was
shocked about that I never never heard
about this ever
before I might my brother told me this I
might from my mother's side of the
family have some American
jeans from like my grand great
grandmother
uh uh no the the father no great
[Music]
grandfather so I but that
person
Amer
Lees well that but that person if that's
is really true on
something uh I mean is dead obviously
but like the American
descendants would be in America because
that was you know war
time and you I don't I don't know if
this is really true my mom isn't sure
either apparently my my brother heard it
from my mom who heard it vaguely from
her mom which is my grandma it's really
confusing I don't know if any of this is
true
but
that great
grandfather if this is true true went
back to America and now I may have
cousins in America and I'm really
curious about
it are you guys my
family can you guys ask everybody you
know in America if they had uh like a
like a great great relative who in in
Austria in during the war
um made Austrian lady
[Music]
pante yeah I I want to do a DNA test but
the DNA test will not really like tell
me much I guess I don't know won't it
just tell me that I'm white will it
actually tell me I'm I'm partly American
won't it just tell me I'm
white but I really want to do a DNA test
now it does it tell you like
countries like how how could it tell you
countries doesn't not just like how does
it work there's not an American Jean
right they ancestry website that
supposed to like yeah maybe I'll me and
my brother we were talking about you
know we should find out this we should
do some detective work we should do some
digging this is kind of interesting I
want to know more so so
mysterious so mysterious especially
because I wonder if my mom is
listening I never heard about this
before
but
um my uh grandma she has passed I think
last year
and I I never heard the story until
today but my brother told me that on her
dying bed she changed her story a little
bit and said her grand father may not
have been American maybe he was French
and now I'm like what why why do you
change your story what what do you
hiding so I don't know either French or
American but like the
if if she only changed the story at the
very end then
I it's kind of kind of sus maybe was
maybe she was confused because of
medication I don't
know we
we oh we we
bucket I could be French you guys don't
know it you guys don't
know my true potential
[Music]
I'm I'm going to get a DNA
test will it tell me that like if I'm
like a little bit French will it tell me
that I'm so
confused left
hand K French Fenix
sort of perhaps it
should french I think so it would tell
the
percentages
interesting yeah cuz ethnicity but not
nationality right that's what I
thought and that's that's nationality
how can it know anybody's nationality
what if they live in a
country that they're not like uh
descended
from what I'm so
confused
[Music]
H you love me whatever my ancestry may
be really would you still love me if I
was
5% North americ
can would you still love me if my
grandfather was
baking crunchy
buett we we we
we we
we would you still love me if I wasn't
[Music]
AA
oh he missed
oh a special enemy what a waste of a
special enemy who's just going to
self-destruct what what but I got the
EXP for that
right just self-destruction just
collateral
[Music]
damage
maybe maybe maybe maybe I am American
and cover you this in the audition
process maybe they did a DNA test on me
when I auditioned oh and die by oh nice
that's why they took me because I was
American enough to be part of whole life
English yeah they have decided that that
for me
oh and all this time I thought you know
I wasn't good enough for whole life
English branch cuz I am the not quite
not really the English speaker of
myth but I wish I was but in reality I'm
actually American all this time I
thought I was Australian if anything but
turns out I'm America just
kidding just kidding
but
yeah I'll go investigate sometime in the
[Music]
future you know even my mom understands
the quas me but cie still doesn't the
other I really I don't get it why does
Kelly not understand the quas me how
does she miss it the other day she she
um had like quasa with her and like gave
it to me and I was like quasa and she's
just she just says yeah and I'm like
kind of hoping for her to come back with
another but she just always says c c
normally like she doesn't go into my
joke with me she's probably just
thinking I'm saying it
cutely no it's more than that
she doesn't get
it even my mom gets it even my mom says
back to
me seems like you found something Mighty
useful my kids Dina and might are
trapped back
there Dina and might let's blast through
and find
them W thanks
Mario
I don't know if I wouldn't have found
the crocodile what my plan was to get in
here but
lucky guess you're right I'd just be a
burden on your fallace well then I'm
counting on you to find the kids here
mixing all kinds of accents
again
Brazilian uh uh no I I don't know I'm I
I I would think no but who knows at this
point who knows could could be
anything always thought I was
[Music]
Austrian now I might be
American for
5% no how much percent would that even
be I don't know if my let's say my great
grandfather was something
else how much percent and everybody else
was Austrian how much percent would I be
something
else
12.5 oh that's quite a lot
[Music]
actually 12.5 depends oh I guess depends
on how much key was of that or
[Music]
what ah the
mystery so
mysterious no SS
sus oh down or
up maybe down
first oh up leads to that path I guess
[Music]
okay
not a
hold the moment that came out I was
looking at the chat so I didn't even
clearly see what was going on oh thank
you for the Frog
coin thank
you I should look at the screen when I'm
changing
[Music]
screens was this effective for B bombs I
don't remember I feel like I used it on
the on the flames
and it
wasn't but for the Bop arms yeah okay
pretty
good nice finally AOE
[Music]
yby the American might have been some
German Heritage from all that we know of
yeah you know who knows
really I wish I knew this kind of stuff
like there's some families who keep like
these family
trees from way way past and like no
everything about their great
grandparents and their great great and
their great great great and their great
great great grandparents and I know
nothing absolutely nothing I'm so in the
dark about like my family anything past
grandparents and even
grandparents I met my both my
grandparents from my father's side but
from my mother's side I
only I only met my
grandmother I think yeah I think
[Music]
so no mysterious lots of M
mystery oh nice
[Music]
ah everybody does a DNA test DNA test
how much does it even cost I think it's
not that cheap right oh what there's no
enemies left what about
here
ah yes ah there it
goes now I zoom through already level 9
let's go okay I wanted to do magic
but this one's free up this one's free
this
one's two that's pretty shitty so let's
go for
physical
maybe next time if there's a bonus melow
also level
9ine uh two
four uh three oh four oh HP or phys then
I would say
uh a HP or give him some physical like
I've never gave I never gave mow
physical points
before h H so if I would then his Bonk
would get a Bit
Stronger Yeah okay maybe it's good to
balance it out a little bit also oh I
want to I want to go back a little
bit cuz I zoomed for all of this
[Music]
now
uh y but I know this area already don't
I I'm just at the top now of that path
so what about
[Music]
here no not
interesting how do I get that when I get
like ah wait oh death perception I
thought it was more like in the middle
of the
room so
confusing oh we're already at the like
whatever boss
fight what about your father's ancestors
any no no no no not my father's my my
mother's side great
grandfather my great-grandfather from my
mother's
side may not have been
Austrian may not have even been from
this continent
so I find the idea of that very
interesting and amusing cuz I never
expected that and like my my brother
told me some interesting
stories of why what might have possibly
went down
and I'm I'm just like why have I why why
don't I know any about this I want to
hear more of these kind of stories Story
Time mommy sit down with me and tell me
everything
[Music]
thing oh nice I thought it was too early
no okay that one was too
[Music]
late how does he know I think I just
heard from Mommy at some point don't
know what brought them to this kind of
[Music]
conversation
M nice good one
[Music]
oh did you hear about new updates for
Mario Kart game wasn't that a while
ago or did they just get all the last
courses
we got to play Mario Kart I wanted to
I've been wanting to play Mario Kart
with you guys
again uh ooh
five HP it
is oh
nice boss fight
upcoming
[Music]
yay nice
jump oh wait I should have ah
wait uh no we're healed we can go what
the hell we can fight the minions first
okay not really what I wanted uh can I
[Music]
leave I I'm just I want to go straight
to the boss if possible oh
I
what
do I have to fight the
[Music]
minions ah maybe I make him blow up can
I make him blow up this thing no he's
not looking there hey you oh wait I can
to attack him from behind
Okay good day the name's
punchinello oh punchinello never heard
of
you they say I'm a hot head but I'll
show them you you will make me
famous so long I don't know what kind of
voice to give to him
whatever let's start off with the triple
[Music]
move let's look at the beautiful
animation for one want 238 all
right uh let's try a super jump come
on ah it cut me off and he resists
it
ah
[Music]
useless oh oh oh oh oh micro
bomb should I focus on
them I want to try this oh wait what
attack up oh it's a
buff I'll give Mario a buff how about
that a
okay random Clos thank you so
much super jump was resisted so let's
try to fire
is still pretty damn
weak but funa wasn't efficient either
maybe I have to do G
[Music]
beam
oh oh I can block them okay okay
okay let's try General
beam normal attack better oh
that wasn't so feel
bad ooh
oh is it it must be because of my attack
up oh now the real Bob ums wonderful let
me do some Thunder bolting hopefully get
them
all
nice
[Music]
just get rid of one of them defend up
yay 100 is my buff still working I
wonder oh nice nice timing and we also
get
[Music]
defense
mhm
[Music]
definitely doing better
today nice so many
Buffs buff is active until you get koed
oh I wish they had like little signs
somewhere like icon signs at the bottom
at the
pictures to tell me if I have a buff or
a debuff and how long it's
active h
[Music]
I want to attack the back one thank
you oh they just blew up like ah cuz I
killed him
okay oh right you asked for
it a big
bombs the kind of bomb you just want to
throw off a
Mountaintop m
the kind of bomb you just want to pick
up with your hands carry to the cliff
and then ye
[Music]
him don't you know what I'm talking
about I'm talking about Super Mario 64
guys why are you acting as if you don't
know what I'm talking
about
[Music]
never play it damn that's the first boss
fight pretty much it's leg
[Music]
legendary nice pretty far uh so far
pretty weak
boss where I'm just getting
stronger by the way guys we just
yesterday just yesterday talked about
how maybe two days ago people were
getting notices oh that my CD my album
was being sent out and just today
Japanese Bros are already posting
pictures of them receiving
it and I'm just like
what that's so nice but I I never got to
see a photo of a sample or whatever of
the actual product I thought it was
still in production I would have liked
to see it before I see it from
fans but at least now it's finally
getting out there and they can already
listen to the Sparks dark
remix also that was so close to me
leaving Japan that I wonder if there was
already a physical sample if I could
have just taken it home now I have
nothing
so it's kind of
[Music]
lame can I please thank you why is it so
hard to select the back
enemy you haven't gotten notification
yeah that's I Think Geek Jack right but
maybe maybe maybe they're actually on it
you know maybe they just don't want to
notify you but they're on
[Music]
it last one still standing H you got
some
guts didn't get one from Whole Life shop
either or maybe it's a location thing
cuz like some overseas people did get
their
notification maybe
some for some countries they can't ship
it out right now I don't know I must be
dreaming I'm
ruined I didn't want to do this but now
I have no
choice I think he's
bling
simmer down fluffy I'm not going to
waste this on you who knows what might
happen Take Your Best
Shot enough I've got my pride now you're
in for
it what's you going to do huh H what the
heck why is it not
[Music]
working it killed him he poofed into the
void if this if this thing explodes
where
[Music]
history this is a fine mess let's scam
now we can't just leave leave it to blow
up on its own down there like what's
that going to do to its surroundings
everyone everything's going to fall
apart
he's he's like leaving his pants when he
jumps like so his shoes are are not his
feet are not connected to his body
they're like
fake did you see I'm talking about
malow one on Earth for
that well we won the battle now I hope
we don't lose the war where are din
might and the star the star is
there
nice you just noticed
yeah I didn't notice
yesterday I I guess that part of it is
is has been
answered come on Mario
hurry our third star or fourth third go
meet the way they're
[Music]
turning number
three let me make some more
[Music]
oh it's so heavy I can't hold it
with one
[Music]
arm come on we still have to find Dina
and
M together their Dynamite
wow making some
[Music]
te no I turned off my hands for when I
was drinking the tea cuz they were
like spazzing
out but okay now it has to cool down
again anyway so is
waiting if it's spicy sip some tea says
Lena to
me okay Dina and might
doco
oh
cute
oh the one is really
small ah this won't B oh I hate this
stupid thing help me here give the M car
a puss okay you jump in yeah yeah Car
Care to read the warning yeah mine car
guidelines press a to break B to jump
get mushrooms and press X to accelerate
a a b b to jump let's remember B let's
forget everything
else cuz I'm not going to remember b b
jump a to stop
ex to acceler oh
[Music]
god oh oh wait there's a
timer ah
ah
[Music]
ah not I was wondering if that could
happen ah no
way uh
jump Slow Down slow slow down and up
jump and up jump uh oh yeah
okay a
slow okay no
problem and slow
down ah no way that was F too fast still
come
on I want to go again that was almost a
minute oh there's still
more oh no way I was jumping I didn't
register my
jump
no ah no
no
no no I want The High
Ground no please let me do it
again oh more
[Music]
how long is
this a come on no
way
[Music]
Ash this is really
difficult
uh wait jump coming soon
yeah no I was going to break before that
[Music]
oh I missed all those coins no
no
ridiculous
no what what they this these shitty mine
carts man who built
them no
what I'm already slow as far
[Music]
I no a now it jumped out of
it can I jump like can I jump over this
curve I
wonder no please let me do it
again is there still
more there's still
more m I don't
know okay okay I'll try my
[Music]
best oh it's a roller coaster oh got to
accelerate it does one acceleration take
one
[Music]
mushroom
W I want to try it
[Music]
again am I what where am I going to land
I wonder how those kids are doing sure
wish they'd hurry home hold your horses
M I asked Mario to help us out so I
reckon he'll bring him back when he's
good and ready are we going to fall into
the house I just have this off feeling
that they'll be dropping in minut
now H yeah yeah that could happen that
could
yeah
okay ah knock knock there still got to
use the door like everyone else M now
settle
down we did
[Music]
not we're
home gracious they really did drop in on
us oh my poor babies are you okay little
might are you
hurt no we're okay Ma isn't that right M
we had
fun he's been knocked senseless you poor
baby you're safe
now Dina haven't I told you often enough
to never go into the minds by yourself
that's enough Ma just be happy to have
him back we haven't thanked Mario proper
either I'm so embarrassed Mario we can't
thank you enough for
everything what's that the roof you say
n that don't matter none right P it
ain't nothing at all you just leave any
repairs to me give me a holler if you
need a hand with your place thanks again
for bringing your babies back to us our
babies you're
welcome I'm such a
hero I even came flying through the roof
that's quite the entrance
[Music]
yeah you found dynamite and the star
piece but where's Peach
yeah we're finding a lot of things but
not the one thing that is most important
to
us can I leave for the hole I made in
the roof now
please
no
no h come back Mr Beetle don't you want
to come to booster and play who's
talking yeah don't run away we just want
to play we'll take good care of you I
like what they said okay Mr
Beetle oh
oh shy
guys not quite shy guys not the typical
ones Mr Beetle Mr Beetle come to
me uh-oh uh-oh you're not getting them
I'm giving it to n these are not
yours don't you dare touch that Beetle
it's a present for booster that's right
just hand it over and
easy yeah like they said or we won't be
your
friend Boer really really really likes
his beetles we but he can't catch his
own that's right he's busy keeping the
princess from the sky
entertained so we're catching Beetles
for him shut up I'm not giving it to you
this Beetle likes me this Beetle has
chosen me as his mommy okay I shall be
that for
him no no
no oh no it's getting away I C it clch
it clch
[Music]
it well they don't seem evil so maybe we
should let them have the beetle evil
Beetle oh cute what are you doing in
there that was empty before I'm so
hungry she wish I had a carbo cookie oh
can I get a carbo cookie
somewhere you guys sell carbo
cookies no they have mid oh oh oh wait
these heal more than the mushrooms that
I have but 80 HP might still be a lot oh
but this one I want think we have like
30 I yeah almost 40 almost 40 oh that's
a lot FP and healing it with 10 each is
kind of
lame this one we already have this stuff
we also
have
m m
M ah it's the one I saved from the mine
or like not really saved but wait wait
what did I just buy I I I did register
that I'm buying like that something's
costing 100 coins but oh what did I
buy what did I
[Music]
buy what did I what did I buy the jewel
right CUA is lucky it
will is that that's what I bought right
what in battle I I'll use it in
battle 100
[Music]
coins
uh I don't have that much money but
okay let Trigg the coin XP mini game
[Music]
a let's see
um anything in here
changed I guess I'll save oopsie I want
to play the the the mini game again that
we just played and I want to do better
can you play it again if you maybe maybe
if you go into the
mines toad toad stayed
here I don't I don't want to stay here
if Toad's left in one of these beds I do
not want to
true she sells the carbo cookies no she
doesn't but somebody
[Music]
does is there shortcut to the mine
cart me a name I call myself tea a drink
of gam and bread oops that's not really
how it goes I'm just bored but if you go
to the mountain they'll sing you the
real for real
they're going to sing Sound of Music for
me this whole my wife dog is a shortcut
try let's go let's go let's go 10 coins
okay yeah my high score is 3 minutes
we'll surely beat that will
we or you can wager what why would I
[Music]
wager in case I make more and pay it
back and then what I don't know let's
just pay 10
coins no my house are
alive with the sound of
music let's go can't promise I'll really
do better
but oh here it
is
[Music]
okay
wee I don't know how much I really have
to slow down but last time it was really
[Music]
sensitive
okay ah hey I was slowing
down damn no
way stupid ass game no what the
[Music]
no no no no no no no no no
no this
[Music]
this you got to be no
no
so yo this makes me so angry I want to
scream so loud but I'm going to destroy
my
[Music]
Bo okay I'm I'm relaxed I'm chill and
relaxed and slow
[Music]
down
oh
my
[Music]
God
just go there no you actually go back
okay I hate you so
[Music]
much
I'm already over 3
minutes why am I doing worse how is this
[Music]
possible
no
way I am in absolute
disbelief how did I do worse even though
I knew everything
better I like fell out of the track so
many times the first try shut
up shut up you game
sucks yeah I I didn't want you stupid
trolling my
God it's
[Music]
unbelievable I'm looking for the people
who are going to sing Sound of Music for
me where are they Al I want the
cookie where is this
[Music]
cookie that's an insane that was an
insane mini
game it it like it gives you this hope
in the first try making you think oh
it's so much
fun but you didn't do so well the first
time which is only because it was the
first time and the second time surely it
will be pure fun and more
success and so you give it a try and
it's only disturbingly frustrating and
painful and all the fun is gone
[Music]
do you have any items to get rid of if
you have any extra items I'll take them
for
you oh you give me points and I'll get a
gift look at the sign to see the items
we
offer wait let me
see we exchange items like mushrooms and
syrups for points oh like old mushrooms
in case I want the newer ones for every
point to get an item we can choose one
of the following items to take a fright
bomb which allows you to make one enemy
quiver and fright a firebomb an ice bomb
for an ice attack against all enemies
H that's pretty
cool if you still have like a lot of
leftover uh items that you think you're
not going to be using then yes but I
think I'm going to keep
them yeah I see AA hi please please
please help me to hurt Mario's Family
please I need to see him be in
[Music]
pain I need him to be in
pain significant
[Music]
pain
[Laughter]
I hate
Mario booster pass okay there's a hidden
treasure nearby oh wow it's been a while
wait actually what look look I saw
something Sparkle was a frog coin let's
go
oh oh this is a cool
area oh oh what is that
enemy It's a Spooky Halloween
carrot oh my
[Music]
God
it's it's one of peas hair carrots that
she threw away after they didn't look so
fresh anymore this is what happened
happens with p's used carrots
mhm this is where they end up
at do you like a g
[Music]
beam oh it killed him with one attack
nice M spikes
seies
okay I was unable to block any of
[Music]
that
nice by the way did you notice that I
had my hands on for sipping my
teeth you saw it once I'm not going to
do it
again
oh
[Music]
it's like the mimic but it's an it's
it's it's this cabbage looking thing AR
to
shocks I am
shocked
what please do it again you didn't
notice how much did it
recover the whole damage I just did to
it or what let let's burn
it that's its weakness okay wa who I saw
his
face but how much does it
[Music]
recover not as much 77 HP ah there it is
okay I'm
[Music]
blind oh my
God
uh it will heal more than that will it
oh but actually I get another attack
okay let's let's use the
fireball 100
two heal 77
[Music]
man static
electricity uh another Fireball and then
it should go down I hope
what a weird enemy it's like bamboozling
me cuz I can't fight all of
[Music]
these I didn't find the treasure guys
let's find the treasure
first where is this
treasure feel like it's something ah
yeah I was going to say I feel like it's
somewhere here
I was right but is there another one cuz
it's still saying there's a hidden
treasure
nearby uh what else could it be like
here
no here oh oh it's another fake one
impostor pasta with
[Music]
a
mhm really annoying of youer but I guess
that's just your
style amazing chest ahead really
look okay there he
goes where's this chest
[Music]
that you are talking
about what about
here no really
[Music]
really what about is it does it have
something to do with
him look
down
[Music]
where
for
[Music]
I'm vibing ah what a
bob the I can't stop please change
the bgm I can't
stop
I need Mar
racas where is this treasure guys tell
me
[Music]
[Laughter]
for highest point of there near the oh
okay I thought I thought there must be
something
[Music]
there it's the highest point
though
[Music]
in the
corner
[Music]
I was jumping
here rage inducing
game
[Music]
monist agent these frog coins per ride
up free what free frog coins per ride up
hold
[Music]
door stop I literally can't stop I can't
stop oh thank God please tell me the
bjam is
changing it's over it's over are we
happy or are we sad
Bowser
[Laughter]
[Music]
get it out of my
head get it out of my
head get it out of my mind out of my
side booster at such a nice place I miss
my
Fortress I miss a good old days PE
screaming in Terror about rushing in to
save her
cry B listen to the
[Music]
song you like
it do we do Bowser
version Oh Jus
Mario okay okay calm down don't let him
see you like this
how have you been no not like that dummy
wrong toe it needs to be more confidence
I have
confidence you what are you doing here
if pet were at my castle waiting to be
rescued she'd be crying like a
baby she is crying like a
baby stupid sussy Baby
Peach they're even babier than the
actual character Baby
Peach H someone talking about me did I
just hear
something what is this melody I have in
my head oh I feels like something like
[Music]
this why do I have this in in my head I
wonder it's coming from down there wow
it's such a beautiful
[Music]
sound I hear an echo of my own Chate
song from
above wa who's singing
this who does this lovely voice belong
to that I hear in the
[Music]
[Laughter]
distance oh that was Peach she's joining
in we should make a
band okay go back go back
Bowser
[Music]
St
[Applause]
[Music]
please
no different
bgm what's the matter the door's not
opening or
something well thank you for the
pinky hey he's
back for our band no he wants to open a
door for us how nice of him
[Music]
huh
why I'm a piece of Arcane die can't
figure out what I'm all about huh well
now we can go inside let's
go oh this power looks too I know I know
you're thinking a big strong guy like
him would be great to have along long
right is he inviting himself to my
[Music]
group N
but he's doing it
like he's trying to make it look like
I'm joining
him H I'll let you join my
minions it's not like I want to keep on
hearing the chat song and sing it
together with you while we're walking
happily around
these beautiful trees that's not it at
all I hate the song but I'm joining you
to make him shut
[Music]
up no
way on the dude from inside was sticking
out his face and like
peeking can't with this game I can't I
hate it and I love it
did you like an explanation no I think I
know probably should I switch someone
out what's your guys' goto
[Music]
team
oh new
music an incredible Vibe the
music Mario Gino Bowser oh seems like
all of you no everybody's kicking out
mow everybody Bowser doesn't even fit on
the
picture doesn't even have anything I can
give
[Music]
him
h
B was a pretty tanky do I not need to
get items for him maybe they sell some
stuff here maybe this is not okay no
never mind we do fight here okay wow
what a Jester sheesh what a
design oh I can switch in the middle of
the battle
too no
[Music]
way
for
I
can't you're going to set on fire like
the jester are you the jester Jester
chicken is that
you okay I
[Music]
will why have I started this why have I
started
this I can't stop adding CH to
everything emergency tangent oh what are
these pictures
funny
booster oh wait booster booster was the
one who liked uh
the the bug that they were trying to
catch
[Music]
right what the is that on the left
side
[Music]
I can't help
me what what the hell is that these
enemies like some of them you see like
these like Snippets you see in other
Mario games like that but then there's
enemies that as far as my knowledge goes
you don't see anywhere
[Music]
else oh triple move okay maybe on wait
is it an AOE cuz I don't think I chose
the enemy
oh it's an alien or is it oh yeah it is
yeah oh it didn't it feels like it
didn't hit the back
[Music]
row thank you guys for the super
chats
maybe I need to end the stream I think I
need to end the
stream stop I I don't want you guys to
suffer the same
fate I think it's
inevitable oh oh I P atten okay let's
let's tangent yeah uh okay yeah so uh
this not really a tangent though I'm
trying to remind myself to think about
it if I want to do it because uh the
coming
[Music]
Sunday but the OG music has the same
Melody doesn't it it's like pretty much
the same just more
[Music]
updated wait but there's
a for real no no I want to go back
there's a treasure that I didn't
get no no don't force me
what the
I'm booster this is my famous tower
of amusement normally I welcome visitors
to play with me and my
sniffers
you're I didn't I I didn't laugh or
react at all upon seeing your face no no
don't get the wrong idea it's not like I
I'm I'm I'm not laughing at your face I
I I just I I sneezed that's all I I
don't find your face funny M no your
face is really
cool Doesn't Remind me of
Wario at
either not like a up Wario no no
that's M no don't worry I'm not I don't
want to insult you your face is
beautiful yeah
totally now the voice doesn't
fit however girl fell out no
MM however a girl fell out of the sky
and into my lip recently since stand
enough been busy keeping her happy and
entertained and I no longer have the
time to play so please enjoy yourself at
your own risk that
is do I follow him stop let me let me
join you he's running that way never
mind I wanted to go back to this room
anyway no before these come back no no
oh I found it oh oh okay I don't want to
fight the shy guys
please
oh okay don't even think about it K
don't even think about how the lyrics
could fit to this melody don't think
about
it don't ruin
it thank you
[Music]
H don't don't don't don't consider
it the don't to
my I'm okay I'm fine I don't have a
problem I can stop if I want to I don't
have a problem I don't need an
intervention yeah yeah about the
Christmas
Reef I don't know if I should do it
because it needs quite a lot of um
things to buy I I would have to buy
quite a couple of
things I still should have the base of
the r from last year honestly I think it
was a really nice thing to craft because
I literally used it for all of the
Advent I lit the candles
nicely I'll be busy managing the Adam
calendar that is true but like making
the wrap reef is just a one time thing
so and then I have something nice to
look at that's also Christmas decoration
so I kind of want to do it
m I kind of want to do it oh sure cuz it
would be one Christmas them
oh cute one Christmas F I'm not even
going there uh crafting no oh can you
help me I thought I just messed up the
jump how we going to do
this
how I'm not ah I have to land on it
maybe when I ah from the very
top oh we have to fight too I thought
you were just going to give me
a a
speech Advent sock puppets yeah I think
there's an expectation of me to make
Advent sock
puppets I guess I'll be doing that
too um last year I was making them on my
own outside of a
stream but this year I could show you my
skills and and make it on stream maybe
in the member
stream too bad I'm not sick this
time F sock
puppets can you
imagine wait can I do something here on
this table
no can you imagine all the lipsyncing
potential with the fule
I can't
run with the
fle
uh sock puppets
huh you be so
silly please no sick this year I hope so
too last year was really crazy recover
what
did wait that
enemy I was thinking like I always kill
it one hit cuz it doesn't seem to have
much HP but I just understood the the
catch now it heals itself up if you
don't kill it in the first round and
raises its HP
[Music]
maybe terrorized that's your only skill
that's so
five only oh my
God please be
effective okay
good okay okay okay
it does it he ah it heals others
too you think it's good
terrorize
maybe every time I got bear as a debuff
I didn't feel like I was much influenced
by
it oh it reduces attack and
defense
why can't you run away from these
[Music]
fights I didn't say anything I didn't
say
[Music]
anything
oh oh ah he got
scarecrow I can still do the
beam
[Music]
but the first one was perfect the first
one was actually like Pleasant to listen
to the first Melody I added it to
agreed I I would almost say it's still
enjoyable
but who knows I just really want to no
where am I ah I just really want to jump
down on that thing again that's where
I'm trying to get
to oh this time I can run away C of
course I
[Music]
can thank
you chicken
chicken chicken chicken
chicken chicken
chicken I can do with your names too
guys
yeah
[Music]
are you at acceptance stage yet or what
okay how to get this jump R I guess if
you get
[Music]
Nah if I mess it up the path is like so
long to get back
here do I just let myself drop or should
I jump I wonder that maybe with just
like dropping yourself just running off
maybe that's good
enough
maybe
[Music]
not oh no
[Applause]
way you kidding me I need a
[Music]
shortcut is it worth
it
is it worth it I
[Music]
don't not the
bubs it's totally what it's
what Mama
[Music]
Mia I I went too
far no
no I was like I moved while I was flying
cuz I was
[Music]
unsure
no a very good weapon for Mario oh I
can't run no way why
not why
not
I I'm trying to hug uh the
corners Bowser needs a weapon and
[Music]
armor now that I think about it I feel
like I did see uh game footage of Bowser
being in the
um and I completely forgot about
it but if he's in my
team that means I'm not I'm not going to
like fight him
anymore oh middle I
think yeah yeah no I just today I was
thinking about it like I was looking at
the box art the game artwork that I have
for the thumnail I was thinking oh wait
so now I already have these three
characters Mario Gino and mow and then
there's Peach and Bowser but I'm
guessing Bowser is on there because he's
a villain the main villain and Peach is
on there
because she I have to rescue her you
know she's just like they're just
important characters but especially now
did I see Bowser on this screen I'm
guessing Peach will also join my team
eventually and will be on the right side
of this dancing
parade
[Music]
interesting very interesting no way
please let me run
[Music]
a but at least this one is
fast
that's quite unusual that you get B
Bowser on your side and Peach even
though she's on your side but like
having her fight with you that's that's
quite interesting
[Music]
choice oh my
God if I can't do this jump this
time no
it's taking me
years to get
[Music]
back don't have the
patience I'm going to it up no
no I'm on it
though
please po have
mercy why won't you have Merc have mercy
on
me have mercy on me I'm begging you for
Mercy why won't you believe
me begging you
for why want to believe
me
[Music]
ah I mean the first room I I still some
how can dodge but this
one's uh oopsy only for skilled
people but at least you can run from
those
[Music]
fights is a kind of tradition and RPG
Paper Mario Paper Mario
too oh God I'm so scared
[Music]
Yellow
Block Yellow
[Music]
Block
I'm silly I'm blind what do you mean
what do you
mean no I can't do this
anymore I'm going
insane
[Music]
no I'm sorry
guys so no
[Music]
I'm not ignoring chat I look at chat
every 5
[Music]
seconds I did it did
it
a yeah I did read that right
now
[Music]
ooh yeah that's nice but why why was it
not a Bowser weapon feel like a Bowser
weapon would have made more sense here
but okay
[Music]
okay okay
now can we actually go through here oh
oh okay no we can't but there's an
[Music]
item oh my eyes are getting tired
again getting the annoying sea to work
well worth the
pain thank you I mean I guess it's worth
it but I don't know at what cost cost
man at what cost
oh check out booster pass booster pass
you
mean that Choate
[Music]
place what do I get all kinds of
different versions no it's just stay
like
[Music]
this is this how it looked in the
original nah no way this just like a
different the first Mario game or
[Music]
so
[Laughter]
sorry that turning small running back
and then dying here was uh scripted
right what a c cute little Easter
[Music]
egg so in the actual Mario game that
Easter egg existed too and you also
turned into the classic
[Music]
Mario
oh bye-bye feel like I'm high level
enough I don't need to pick every fight
but these ones h
yeah exactly the same
[Music]
unchanged
nice yeah Advent
calendar maybe happening yeah it's
happening I already
SED um
but yeah I'm kind of nervous about it
because I'm helping planning
it
um but yeah I don't
know like icons are like being drawn way
earlier this time but like videos don't
exist yet so this time the order is
different last year it was like the
girls would make a video and then based
on the video within like 24
hours the icon would be drawn based on
the video now they we had them like
submit their ideas first and then the
icon would be drawn based on the
idea and then they're making their video
later just so that the artist has more
time even though he's still drawing it
within 24 hours though even though he
has more time he's still blasting them
out
immediately
M need a key
okay uh but I feel
like maybe it would have been better to
have the original order I know I did did
it they wanted to make it easier like
time wise
for um the artist but I feel
like it it it would be
better with with
um the V like doing
it while watching the videos but oh well
they still like look really really cute
so
okay oh you got to do some smart jumps
here across the corner oh o there's
another
seesaw no wait
no wait let me go back
thank you cuz I didn't get this one yet
now you can please get me up there again
thank
you the portraits they're a
puzzle
oh a
[Music]
puzzle oh
um more like a bum
Boozle bum bum
puzzle that's a puzzle you didn't know
either are you playing a game and you
missed this one
too no I read the note but I just
thought like it's like please look at
this they're so beautiful you know just
to make sure in case you didn't pay
attention to these beautiful
boosters just give them show them off
again you know I didn't
think that it would mean there's more
than that behind it but they also had
them in the first room I wonder if the
first room
connects with
this cuz I didn't particularly look at
those
either yeah I just thought it was like
look look how great these people look
because this is the house of booster and
you just want to flex your boosters or
whatever
[Music]
ah okay so the first room does have them
in the correct order um well I don't
know I'm just like forcing my way
through the portraits I
guess how do I put them in order
[Music]
though like this one looks the
youngest is it
[Music]
not
I have to check them in the correct
order if I fail once and starts from the
beginning or
what a oldest to youngest okay see I I'm
stupid but uh
oldest I don't know who looks old this
one was wrong this one was wrong this
one was wrong maybe maybe this one yeah
okay
M maybe this one
no
[Music]
great I'm not going to go back to the
first floor that's so
far no I'm not going
back how
about maybe maybe the hint maybe the too
far a hint I don't know how many this
one had but this one has two this one
has three this
one okay after that I don't know let me
try my Fury no it was wrong it was
wrong damn
it ah yellow hat
okay
ah yeah no harm getting exp I
guess
M okay what this one is second oldest he
looks really young with the
[Music]
hat and then I guess they don't really
look their age but now I really wouldn't
know this one still looks somewhat young
this one looks pretty
old the pirate
oh this is like a
biker who
[Music]
next or this one
maybe yes then this
one oh thank you thank you
tasu I got
the really loud noise
uh that's a weird
Dogo
ow am I being raided by
fuu they gazed into each other's eyes oh
is it going to be helpful to have Bowser
now cuz they like each
other Mario she's a bit shy look the
other way will
you I really can't
see oh she said she's been lock stopped
ever since she took a bite out of
booster so now oh is it a weapon for him
maybe
[Music]
or oh could be could
be yes it is
nice
marvelous I just saw something there was
it
just reflection oh yeah it was
reflection
okay so we got two weapons are there any
more I wonder maybe there's weapons for
everybody in this
world
[Music]
oopsy would you guys like to see the The
Reef stream again just asking to make
sure I mean you're obviously not going
to say no right I feel like certain
ideas are nice to repeat other ideas
maybe no need to repeat but something
like this why not have it annually
right different design yeah I can do a
different
design last year I made it just
orange I don't know what I would do this
time maybe just like Personal Taste
instead of make forcing it to be
[Music]
orange le
le and this year last year I I made it
with the webcam right this year I can
show it on like a more higher quality
camera
so chicken CH no they're they're just
round
usually oh
[Music]
can't make them in another
shape I mean actually yeah they are
actually uh some people make them in
like a straight shape just have like
four candles lined up straight with some
of those like
Evergreen
things
H pink and white yeah definitely that's
that's very girly
and one
four okay I guess we're going for HP
again I feel like we've been going for
HP a lot but you should go for the one
that has the most right
ideally Gino level
five
oh
one
three last time we went physical I
think
Bowser at least should I shouldn't go
with the weakest one
[Music]
so I'll give him some more
physical I love another colored beat
stream that one there oh that
one takes quite a while to make one like
a
character takes quite a lot of
concentration it's like making a pixel
art oh come on pixel art in
[Music]
Minecraft turns out really cute though
and is a nice
present could make it like Christmas
themed too could make a Christmas
version of somebody
maybe I should make one of the Rissa to
give to her for the when I see her in
the
moldes oh you
see oh left
side nice exp
double a blue and orange I don't know
about mixing blue and orange m
I don't know I I'll if I will do it I'll
just get
whatever looks good to me new attack for
mow but we're probably not going to use
him anymore are we so
sad oh well mow I'll just give you m now
wait we wanted to give him physical but
we're probably not using him anymore
so that's
that there's a hidden
treasure where could it
be
[Music]
oh got to jump
everywhere maybe up here no or maybe
here no
really I feel like it would be here
h
no wow okay
[Music]
no mow magic I know but like we said we
wanted to give him some um physical
attacks so his normal attacks aren't as
useless left side first
walkway treasure do
[Music]
do I'm not uh I think my con contion is
like not there right now that's why I'm
not getting the timings
right but it's fine we're strong enough
to get through it
[Music]
mostly I know we still got to give him
some points
[Music]
somewhere okay let's
see here maybe oh there it is thank you
you a frog coin Let's Go
Frogs frog appreciation in this game is
strong we could go this way too huh oh
oh frog coin oh two frog coins in one
room oh even more FR
gunsby
ybyby lava blbl it's blue
now they look like they would resist a g
beam cuz they look like my
beam 130
shes oh I
missed oh it missed
too what the actual
wait why didn't I get super
Fireball oh my God m
right I don't remember I don't remember
what
they are weak
to feel like fire makes no sense jump
also not much
though oh that's fine it was
jump Yoshi
uh okay there it is righted side H my
eyes my eyes are so
tired I feel I feel like I think I know
what it is no
no can't why is there so many fights you
can't run
from anyway I feel like I know what why
I've been so
tired when I'm streaming yesterday and
today when I came back it got so cold
right so my mom turned on the the
heating in my apartment and I I kept it
on I turned it down but I still have it
on maybe it's a heating is making my
eyes feel so
tired that that makes sense to
me it's not that warm though like really
it's just
like M it's not cold it's just like
really normal room
[Music]
temperature yeah Warmness definitely
makes you sleepy but it's not that warm
it's just like I feel
like the what what heat or heating does
to a room like to the air and all
that I think it's also adding to me is
this a is this a
maze I think it is I think it is I see I
think it's adding to me uh having like
Thro torch as well speaking of fro TCH
let me pour some hot tea into this cold
te T the
season of FR
T I have to bring out my
um air humidifier
[Music]
again I don't really feel like it ever
properly helped
but who
[Music]
knows again damn Yoshi shows up so
much my eyes are too tired for
[Music]
this I never got it
wrong okay is
there a hint to this I
wonder I mean partially the coins I
suppose
maybe from here
up maybe one more and then that
[Music]
way I maybe always the
shortest way oh but like now in this
case do I go diagonal probably not right
maybe this
way
oh and then straight to the next ah okay
no that doesn't necessarily
the logic I just had in my
head you just jumped
oh
H
H oh man I was thinking oh I don't
necessarily need to always jump on them
right surely I can get one hit in and no
I was
wrong oh this Bowser didn't
miss okay now sure surely we got to go
this way but I'm going to jump
too okay get done surely now it's normal
no it's not hey I felt so free for a
moment because I was able to run around
freely huh is there a system to this or
not
un how does
[Music]
she
again oh my God I can't look at these
Yoshis anymore
ah middle
y
ah please I don't want any more
Yoshis should I go this way what about
the left
door
no okay these enemy encounters are
getting really annoying to me oh
oh
key first go lock first oh okay no Yoshi
go away why do I keep on getting
Yoshi I mean I'm happy but oh this is
the first one where I'm not
sure
okay why do I keep on getting
[Music]
Yosi Baby Yoshi no baby Yoshi I love
baby Yoshi I'm sorry I'm sorry Zoom
shoes ooh I'm guessing they're making me
faster but I I don't know let me
see I don't think I want them if they
only make me oh wait there's there's a
ooh wait speed oh wait not just faster
on the field but faster in the battle
too
okay how then I think I'll put them
[Music]
on I want to keep on the signal ring
though
[Music]
oh I'm forced to fight them
sh oh I can run
away let's run away if I can spawn
[Music]
okay couldn't run couldn't run don't lie
to
me of course I can
run
[Music]
oh what is
[Laughter]
this this is my personal
really my it's you again I'm amazed made
it this far yes quite amazing you are
since you're here maybe you could clear
up something for me my right to be is
[Music]
chanting
to what does that mean I don't speak
nongo wait a
second oh you're singing the same song
she got it from you you guys together or
what huh that's not fair She's mine now
okay so get the out of
here that's a slow descent what do you
want what
what what is this picture
frame
oh I'm booster now but what
[Music]
now that didn't do it ah I ran out of
bumbs that's it that's all I had to do
wait it out
[Music]
that's
it oh
my okay kind of empty room oh we have
reached the
end makes sense cuz I feel like this has
been quite a lot no I want
to no I want to I want to go there oh
wait from
here 1 2
3 that's not the hidden treasure
though yeah that's what I thought mhm M
mhm wait there's
[Music]
more no that would have been funny
though a chest on the treasure chest
that you you can't jump up there from
here you can you could only reach it
because there's another platform there
that would have been
[Music]
funny oh maybe here though
uh
no I guessed it but I guess it on the
other
one this jump is harder to make
actually holy
[Music]
cusa oh my God absolute genius
wow
wow my brain is
expanding oh uh do we have some
something special recovers recovers
okay let's go I
guess oh Peach toy oh and some other
toys and the
beetle
[Music]
H okay funny can I get in
there
no what's this
room Mario mar Mario Mario
[Music]
Mario nothing I
guess a pitch Mario is it you I have a
song I want you to
hear but maybe now is not the time I'll
sing it for you when we can
hug what you want to hear
it okay maybe maybe if I Hey sing it now
the door will open on its
[Music]
own what should we do booster is
returning isn't he I know hide somewhere
and wait until he opens the door oh
where could I hide in this room oh good
good question it's opening for
me good luck hiding from booster and the
S oh
okay I see uh-oh oh are they going to
like choose different curtains each time
and I have to be lucky to not be behind
it why shouldn't we be concentrating on
the
girl right now about a girl in my life
who thinks I should marry her well speak
up
the wedding ceremony would make a great
party ah party we haven't had one of
those it could be fun so what is a
party well you drink punch and eat cake
I think that's a Christmas
party drink punch eat cake sounds
complicated I don't know if I can must
the energy to do it let's walk through
it once it's wedding rehearsal
time a
we will now begin the ceremony walk down
the aisle with the hey someone make her
smile beautiful bride to
[Music]
be wait Mario Mario your shows up about
now to ruin the fun we've got to take
that into consideration you know someone
go and get the mar you
[Music]
though I'm not here it's up there guys
just don't open the curtains it it isn't
here ah of course it's here you lazy
little
shits it's behind those curtains number
one no no no no
[Music]
where no no
no okay oh they're really
[Music]
slow okay
okay hide here now it's not going to
open one twice
right is he getting faster he's getting
he's getting faster how
you oh okay no but not not fast enough
to really make me
sweat I wouldn't go and lose my Mario
doll you idiots number two you your turn
is he oh they both look oh they B
look no
problem interesting
uh interesting boss F oh oh okay no you
little you little he changed
his mind there
ah okay you done no
no you're done now right oh God no
they're not now you're done right okay
okay okay oh they're going to add a
third one oh
y this is so cute though this is such a
cute fight if you could even consider it
a fight uh-oh yeah bye yeah
bye there's only going to be one
way here okay okay okay okay okay here
unless he changes his mind no he's fine
now
here
oh okay okay okay okay
okay no no no no you can't do this to me
okay
okay okay this is so cute this is
actually fun and really cute really
adorable is this like the boss
fight this so cute okay I need to calm
down from
this okay honey go
into my teacup a cup of tea a cup of tea
a cup would you like a cup of
tea a cup of a cup of tea a cup of tea a
cup of
tea oh what I could
fail up to three times and then I have
to fight
him what what how do how do they excuse
any failures up to the third one
like how how does that not immediately
turn into a boss fight wait so if I
failed then I would have had a proper
fight and now I don't have
one just better than a party look God
come come
on
Mama me I worked so hard on not getting
revealed I didn't want to leave the
closet I get something better I get a
rare item oh the peach
doll wait a second it's right up there I
found the Mario doll what what about me
what about this
me you're not going to react to
me but will never be able to reach up
there all the sor oh what am I going to
do they're going to make a
[Music]
ladder I'm going to help him get
him how nice of
me I feel like they could have just made
a ladder of the shy guys and you know
pick it up
was did I did I have to do it like and
yeah how did they not notice me no they
they're are they are aware of me but
they don't
mind goodness you're so kind thank you
for getting my
doll he wants to reward me booster's
charm hey
yo
H my happiness follow you wherever you
go all right enough is enough cancel
every so going on with the
show no I I'm I'm here to stop that
right here's the
[Music]
password they take the name from
the
switch cuz I never entered a
name gosh holy you guys you
guys oh like from the account thank God
it's ke
oh my
God holy they're keeping me on my
tippy toes
[Music]
man that's
that's my
brain they're already gone oh what is
this enemy interesting oh two more
Jesters stick
around okay Knife Guy and great
[Music]
guy
uh let's
see dock by Mario wait how much damage
did that do I didn't
look uh wait
I have the tri the triple attack let's
use it on both I guess yeah right cuz
it's an alien let's
go can I also have a no Mario team can I
take out
Mario can I can I take out Mario
literally uh no I I of course I mean
nothing of
harm no you can't ah okay well too bad
you mean wait in both ways in both
feelings I can't take him out
go oh oh wait I should have rotated oh I
didn't know
that oh wait I can
still did I do it
right thank you
certainly oh oh ah you're the medal guy
I'm sorry I'm so
[Music]
sorry
we have oh 246 holy we have so much
um FP now it's pretty great when it's
all the way
[Music]
up yeah cuz it's a debuff huh all
right yeah I I'm never getting the
timing right on that one IO find
stop
it
[Music]
yum 156
okay ooh wow even without my special
attacks I'm doing big damage we like to
see
it oh I got it right for once
have
confidence you put me to sleep
[Music]
Wow Let's try a normal attack might be
not so bad either oh yeah he died okay
it was that it that's the boss
fight I guess you got to consider the
fun right before
[Music]
that because this alone was too easy but
let's let's consider what was before
that also to be part of the boss
fight
oh that cloud that cloud had a cute and
very simplistic face maybe it's uh
related to
mow mini game no way please let me go
want you please PR
please and why my bir really booster
really
really I want to play hide and seek too
I don't want to play anything with
you yummy cake is waiting for us after
we climb this hill let's go no I don't
want to marry you please let me
go happy Mario I'm like literally right
there right in front of them all it's
Mario we done playing
this why is he not moving he keeps on
walking but he's not
moving you're on the ride the wedding
besides we still have the rehearsal I'll
be happy to raise you to the wedding
hall but You' better not get in my way
ready
go child is back I'm not going to do his
voice this is the booster hail track
need some advice
yeah you can only move left or right and
jump you can't go forward or backward
okay okay easy
easy touch the snifter sniffers or any
of the barrels and you'll fall back
okay okay uh-huh uh-huh I
see
okay ah jump on them not over them Reach
Out And Touch Princess Peach and you'll
win flowers okay I'll try my best
ooh but I can't boost
[Music]
right should I actually try
no ah I'm so
bad
no well I'm trying to stay on the safe
side but oh it's hard to time to
actually jump on the barrels
they're so
far
ah I jumping on them is good oh I got a
little
[Music]
booster no no no way there we
go yeah got her got
her mind in the gutter when thinking of
peach it's getting a lot oh oh
oh oh wait for me
oh double
jump
oh
no
[Applause]
y
[Music]
no y I got one
more
[Music]
H
oh
ah ah Y is
over seems over SM I I got two I feel
like you could do so many more but I'm a
loser I
suck or or is just like pretty
normal
I mean I didn't get hit that much either
I just barely was able to land the
jumps you got zero okay okay okay okay
yeah I played it very
safe not too bad you you I mean that's
two extra FP I mean it would be crazy if
you could get like 20 FP out of
this K is why I started watching whole
life thank you wow what a compliment I
am
honored marry Moore they're going to
marry and
marrymore wow if that isn't on the nose
then I don't know no treasure here
really
you
sure welcome to marrymore we have lovely
wedding hall in fourstar hotel
facilities please enjoy your stay here
what you're seeking a man with scraggly
beard and weird
helmet how could I forget him he's up at
the wedding hall why did you not stop
him my God that was obviously not a
voluntary
wedding what the is wrong with you
toads why do you support this kind of
sham marriage huh we were about to begin
the ceremony and some kids and dark
clothes kicked us out
help Raz and rainy were they going to
get married I'm barricading the door so
don't even bother to try and sneak
in not letting you here and you can
forget about the back entrance it's
locked at least I think it is we'll say
about that but this box looks
suspicious H actually so no never mind
the Box doesn't or can I push it
no
[Music]
oh you made me want to stay I love
you I love
[Music]
you w that looks so good it
so oh so
what are you
doing Ah that's nice you just stepped on
the your
F why as a German why why I said
[Music]
German how who goes there not me you
look like Mar but the door's shut tight
listen mustach you and your overgrown
Turtle friends can take a hike go
scat I'm a scat
[Music]
man oh we got a problem I better go tell
booster ah the door is too heavy
could you maybe help me open it Mario so
that I can report
[Music]
you why am I actually helping help
him oh I'm not helping him oh should
I wait do I jump at
[Music]
it oh there why did I help
him Mario's here are we actually going
to fight booster now wow shut it oh my
turn move by is it you I'm in here hurry
get me out of here oh that was
Peach i f suddenly suddenly booster
opened his heart up to me and became a
[Music]
fan but atas he said I'm not a fan I'm
not a
fan it let me in yeah help
me strong strong Bowser I'm lightning in
a bottle I'm earthquak in I can I'll
bust this open in no time let's go do I
also have to oh okay same thing okay
shut up I don't want to read that
again no sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
[Music]
sorry hey come back Bowser help
me why did I send him
[Music]
away
ah no running right just just uh no
jumping running is fine
I think
ch ch P okay snap snap
run there we are
[Music]
oh this is why I have stereophobia yeah
you see she almost died falling off the
stairs more or
less her Tiana that's her Tiana looks
like a
[Music]
ring what are you doing it little it a I
don't even that's not her wait that's
her that's her chest piece
no great I look like some
peasant now without my tiara and my
chest piece H
disgusting ew I hate myself I'm so
ugly I don't want to be myself
[Music]
anymore I'm so naked
the bride is growing impatient let the
wedding begin I'm not going to
marry you right now look at me
ew why don't you understand tastes salty
I
Dr he drank
it he did open his mouth and looked up
he
[Music]
did
funny
[Music]
so funny
man I believe the Brad may be uh crying
um cry crying what the what the
what's what's making her cry uh
she's saying she's like ugly as
right now uh and that she's
naked ah I don't see her being naked
what what
women
uh Mario is already here so we're kind
of effed right
now okay they want to find her stuff I
will find it
first um Bo you're supposed to be on the
right the BR would be on your left it
really just testing he's drinking the
tears again like this
right no no hey hey hey that's mine no
why do they get to find everything I
need to fight them I
guess even the shoes
wow he wasn't there one more thing right
the crown I have a
crown oh no I don't have the crown hurry
and get back the accessories from the
sisters and save Princess Peach okay no
problem Oh
what
they think I'm helping
them they they're just giving it to
me thinking I'll give it to no
way that is too easy oh wait
what is this like a
timer where's the where's where's the
last item they're turning on the candles
I don't
[Music]
understand
what what they're training them on jump
on him oh he has it I didn't see okay
what now we talk
now you Mario so you've come to crush my
wedding up
soon Mario and Bower you guys are a team
now what the I thought we were
forever
[Music]
enemies oh free people who want to marry
me I'm so popular let's
go
[Music]
okay ah what the yeah now she's
having the Bowser reaction that I was
hoping for what a waste of time I've got
bigger fish too fry so like I like you
at all peaches peaches peaches peaches
peaches not I never sang that no wasn't
me I know I'm good times when you're
around Mario here's a kiss for my
hero
Baku hat don't do this in front of my
eyes you going to kiss him it's
disgusting he didn't he didn't wash his
face or mouth or body for past two weeks
okay also I saved you me I want a re too
I'll take a kiss give me a kiss stop it
you guys are disgusting ew so
Mario you're the only one for me
oh
oh what
[Music]
what that could have been such a nice
cut scene and there she is chuckling in
the back that be
she's laughing for real now that's one
for the
Scrapbook you'll never get me Mario I
friend zoned you 5 years
[Music]
ago that's fine I prefer Daisy sorry to
have still waiting uh We've made some
most amazing cake you won't believe
it here is cake
but where are bride and the
[Music]
groom where is
everyone sister big
tble that's an amazing cake but it is a
Christmas cake again like what is this
with this Christmas party VI the bride
is leaving is leaving Chef
water you're taking the bride away but
there won't be anyone to eat this
cake what this can't be re worked all
day on all t on
it you fo no it's okay I'm going to eat
it don't you worry about that I will eat
this
cake oh why why are you so mad why not
talk with
me just talk with me B what the cake is
called Bo is it actually going to do
something
I stepped on their cake that's do roll
that's because I really wanted to eat
it can I attack the cake there it
[Music]
is I'm going to eat you up resistance I
wasted my points on that kidding
me what why is what am I supposed to do
stop it what the am I supposed to
[Music]
do I did I did attack the cake
but oh more more oh this time it
actually did damage okay I was really
confused cuz nothing I did did anything
okay no no you stop
it
ooh
[Music]
good
D can you stop bullying
Gino he's a real boy
okay wait did it always look like it had
faces on each layer ouch what are you
doing Chef to the cake is
moving the cake B is not moving back to
work yeah actually yeah it didn't what
it's been rotating right so the faces
were probably like on the
back do I continue with normal
[Music]
attacks don't fight we can all just eat
it together it's more than enough for
all of
us the Cake's moving talk no more of
this no really really truly why would I
lie because you are sassy baka
[Music]
idiot say is not moving I
see is the cake alive oh my god let's
run choose hope he does
in oh the oh the candles are turning on
attack with a to blow the candles out
[Music]
okay
ah
o why the hell is it able to use a sand
strong and a
blizzard
huh it's a lot of damage
man terrifying
storms ah I'm not nailing my timings
man is it going to die already when I
turn off all the lights oh Gino's
dead
what's going to
happen o I can switch him out why not if
we are allowed to do that hell yeah and
I immediately get to use him too okay
mow welcome back wow shotgun enemy hit a
just as the bat lands but doesn't even
work now because they said attack of
a don't
know oh maybe now special attacks work
with the all the candles are off
[Music]
maybe I jump on
it m no
special oh still really
okay then let's not waste it oh it's
turning oh we got rid of the top
layers
Rasberry it's only raspberry now M looks
good oh she
so please let me eat you jump jump jump
jump jump please let me eat
you I'm going to eat you
up I'm going to Chomp you down I'm going
[Music]
to I'm going to inhale
you you beautiful beautiful gorgeous
Majestic piece of
cake let's revive
[Music]
him haven't had deaths in a
while but the storms are you can't block
them and they're pretty strong
so sing you're hungry I actually had uh
Ramen for lunch normally I don't eat
that much oh for lunch so that's a lot
of food I took in before the stream so
I'm not hungry
actually what you want to eat it
too a hey number one where's my cake
this is your
cake 70% chance the object you're
standing on is the cake
yeah this thing's a cake what the
everyone needs a stumper how do we eat
this what do you mean how do you eat it
you boil no you don't boil
it please do not boiled cake you eat it
the way it is it's
finished I you just swallow it one in
one gulp yeah I guess in the boss fight
is over go ahead I guess but I wanted I
wanted some bites
too why can I not just swallow it
hey I guess he has the bigger mouth
I feel like I forgotten to tie my cord
before a bungee jump
what oh he's scared of it now it's going
to crush him did the cake just
move this doesn't feel right yumy y it's
going to kill me yeah
[Music]
no delicious oh you like that hang on
I'm feeling I'm feeling yes yes it's so
good it makes me want to cry
TR I'm jealous I want
to e happy ending what the I
thought it would crush
[Music]
him what kind of ending is
this what kind of ending is
this making me do all the work and
getting rid of the cake and then just
like eating
it and one
[Music]
bite true ending better than the ending
of Final Fantasy 16 for
sure
h
that was wonderful B my night and
shining
armor finally let's get back woohoo what
a day can you believe it I almost got
married to that
thing I hope someone marries me someday
but not
you that's for
[Music]
sure I am salty about that yeah Baba
still play it's only been 3 hours but
yeah it feels
longer Peach joined the
party of course she
[Music]
[Applause]
did so you guys when I asked you you
guys said your team always consisted of
Bowser Gino and
Mario so are you telling me Peach is not
worth
[Music]
it sorry I'm leaned really far
back in case you can't
tell the same girl girl who liked cilia
and V yeah I mean cilia too had Bad
Endings but it also had a good ending so
the real ending was pretty
good actually was it cilia too that kind
of ends with a certain person a certain
character kind of becoming God and I
didn't feel that that one didn't make me
feel unhappy
though at all it was really happy
[Music]
ending it wasn't
negative peach is broken heals Peach's
healing powers are beyond amazing oh but
I don't even need that much healing
maybe later in the
game
H was that silia one with the turning
into God of a certain character no
[Music]
spoiler you died twice yeah but like I
didn't really feel like it was
[Music]
stressful um
let me eat say
[Music]
chol
I just why is this why
is first I thought the kid was shaking
outside because it was a scary situation
but the the kid is still shaking like
insane what's wrong with
[Music]
him idle meeting he looks like he
wearing diap first
though just
go I feel
like I I don't know this doesn't seem
normal I feel like they they gave him
something that mean we can go on without
weding yeah go
go let's get to this wedding let's get
this wedding over so we can strain the
suit and go to our
honeymoon you're honeymoon's going to
suck compared to mine you've never saw
the
males yeah yeah yeah he drank
coffee oh I feel like wasn't there in
Malcolm in the Middle wasn't there an
episode where
Dewey was like
this or am I imagining
[Music]
things
a on Candy mhm he was high on Candy
probably
yeah oh well wait the shaking sound
didn't come from the child it was the
fire Sugar
[Music]
High save the game no what's going on
here
M
yeah
cheese
smile nice show
me not going to show
[Music]
me I'm surprised nobody's saying
anything about me being totally
unrelated to them and joining their
picture
time they don't mind they're happy
people they don't mind a complete
stranger joining their wedding photo how
nice of
[Music]
them oh it's in my
scrapbook let's see
[Music]
a you little
why did you not look straight to
the camera wish my ski
season don't we all don't we all why why
does he want to ski I guess this
place these mountains could be nice to
ski
down so
unrelated
M was it his chocolate side maybe in
German we say chocolate side to the side
of our face that looks the best
Mario the chancellor is waiting we're
going back now right
okay
yooo where where where is that the
chancellor is it in in the like the toad
town in the
beginning uh wait I leave through the
for
[Music]
here
check out the item shop first oh okay
wait did they have an item shop
here
[Music]
uh oh wait uh
ah
here don't worry don't worry I can
control
myself
n it's always
[Music]
Su
stop I'm in the funny mood very funny
mood this is like this game is
putting me in the funny F mood and it's
exhausting me
mentally like honestly yesterday too I
felt like a I can't play this so
long it's not like I don't know it's
just it's so funny maybe if I wasn't
streaming it I
could play it while not
um you know
going uh totally
BL jelly becoming jelly making my brain
go
jelly it's okay no we're continuing I
think because this stream is too short
otherwise can't have that
happen let's get like a couple of these
just in case I still have a couple of
normal ones but just just in case and
then this would be
good
and this is not good oh we have do we
have like a real chump and this is the
fake
chump so it's one uh attack less
effective just
one but at least we don't have to pay
for it we got it for
free oh happy shell yeah why
[Music]
not happy shirt hell yeah
don't know I guess I guess I'll still
give him new stuff in case we switch him
in for
emergencies why not we have the money
Virgil Fox thank
[Music]
you nurturing overflowing with the
power it's a wedding ring is there like
does something happen when I buy it and
I put it on
Peach
it's expensive I don't want to try it if
that's there's nothing
happening I feel like they would do it
they would put something
[Music]
there there's a very convoluted secret
what what does that mean
convoluted it's half damage taken
wouldn't it say that wasn't specific
item for her to use during battle oh
okay okay
okay for an item you get much later it's
complicated
oh yeah it it does seem
complicated can I not go up there faster
I have to go for the whole
map we're going
here you use the suit a bunch of times
and the the suit you try to use it again
with no coins the hotel makes you work
for
it okay and then how does the ring come
[Music]
in use an item you buy in Moville called
lucky egg piz must use it 10 times while
wearing the
ring and then what do we get a baby
does the egg pop the lucky egg do we get
lucky one of her one of her eggs get
lucky is is that
like what the point
[Music]
is is that how babies are made use lucky
egg 10 times get
baby I mean with this game I wouldn't be
surprised if that was what they were
thinking look like you're still one
piece yeah I guess I found the one piece
princess
princess I'm finally home with Mario and
some eggs that won't be
hatched let's go find the chancellor Le
on come on Mario must keep the Chanel
waiting oh he'll be so
[Music]
happy that that you should be nurturing
a clue ah
the egg gives a hint to the connection
to the ring a even then it feels like a
difficult thing to figure out when
you're first playing the game with no
hints just on the's
back thank goodness this has been a true
nightmare I'm a nervous
rck heck heck oh I'm fine though don't
worry about me
with a little help for Mario I was fine
a little only a little most of the
things I did yeah come on everyone let's
get out of this drafty doorway okay yeah
why did
we Mario I hope you know how thankful we
are it it do have kind of FAL Vibes mar
mar Mario o oh
[Music]
you tell me one thing how on Earth can
you trust
Bowser trust Bowser what are you talking
about I I love how we're actually uh not
ignoring
this happening this
[Music]
situation
AR what are you doing with this piece of
h i don't get
it oh they're
scared
no Bower Bowser has become more more
friend of of the years yeah yeah yeah
yeah
yeah and he is now this is all a plan
he's now closer than ever to Peach guys
closer than
ever and she's not running away from him
at this moment
either Bowser finally figured out that
the way to Peach's heart might not be
kidnapping
her although I don't think the way to
her
heart um like I I don't think it will
work this way either like forcing
yourself into her friend group her
closest friend
group to get her heart that's that's not
going to work
either
but it's a game so let's try it
out wow what a concept generally being
friendly surely should work better than
kidnapping her and forcing it on to her
ah but still this is also kind of
wrong and why has he kept doing that
because he's stupid he's a turtle
Dragon
dinosaur I don't
know no brain only gain in his muscles
that are
[Music]
pain Turtle brain
tle tle small small tle small small T
House
s
small house ah cor I saw that coron s
stream that's going around as Clips too
hilarious hilarious
man I laughed my ass off
too M be being so scuffed that
it's hilarious
it's
art yeah where they go to the
toilet and then at the end when when cor
I wonder what what in what position she
was in real life because at the end she
was just like making break dance
[Music]
poses
M the gift that keeps on
giving I should do a Muki collab stream
too H I also found it really funny how
she walks like but like obviously she
doesn't walk like that IRL but Muki just
makes you look like you're walking
really weirdly it it has to do with like
lifting your leg any any movement where
you lift your leg will be like pretty
inaccurate
Chancellor listen everyone relax Mar's
got things under control he's got him on
a leash very tight one he kind of likes
it Bower perhaps it's time you told us
your story what exactly do you mean when
you said you have bigger fish to
fry can't tell them the truth if this
gets out I'm finished can't tell them
that I want to start an acapella group
with them has to happen naturally
excuse me sir perhaps I can set their
stage and the others can add their
comments along the
way what where where did Mario go the
princess Bowser and Mario were thrown in
different directions after terrible
explosion something huge crashed oh oh
star time through the star rad high
above Bowser's place and
went
cou
[Music]
r two Bowers
C
SC all of these producers developers
think they're so
funny was a gigantic sword if I
pronounce said correctly now bouser keep
has been taken over by monsters who work
for some creep named
sney they they thrown me out of my own I
mean I decided to take a
[Music]
vacation they can't do this to me anyway
I was working on a plan to get my house
back
when Mario walked up to me and begged
not egged he begged me to let him join
my
minions I had no choice but to let him
it was
pathetic you sure Bowser that's what
happened he's telling him the real story
it's okay Mario we know bows are
stretching the troop a
little and Mar how about you why are you
traveling with
Mario well Mario was helping me find my
real home and my parents and we're
trying to find out if I'm
American H wait no never mind trying to
find out if I'm a um uh what was it uh
frog that's why we're on the road
together what this is Dreadful news
awful
horrible oh I hope you're not American
for your own
sake yeah I hope so
too
that peach said that that was Peach's
reaction I don't know what her problem
is I don't
[Music]
know me and this game we're a great
team and um Tino I was it why are you
and
Mario oh wait I feel like I haven't
heard or or made Gino talk in like a
long
time the sty has been destroyed I'm here
to fix it Mario is helping search for
the star pieces I need them to rebuild
the room star pieces
huh the Star Road Grand our wishes
unless we find all the star pieces and
fix the Star Road we can kiss our dreams
goodbye what this is Dreadful news awful
horrible
just
like the
American it's okay it's okay it's okay
different different let me separate my
head from this totally different
things
um oh why' you w up like that what the
hell trying to kiss my
feet do you have a feet Kink huh should
be ashamed of
yourself I I I definitely don't
uh I I just admire anything that's made
out of Flesh rather than wood anyway
indeed for example I say Bowser
kidnapped you without the aid of the
Star Road you'll probably never be
rescued actually that sounds pretty good
to me let's just forget about these star
things great Bowser then you can just
kiss you precious keep
goodbye uh I thought she was going to
say something
else
what let's see if Mario can find the
Stars Peach will be mine but I won't get
my keep back unless Mario finds a star
so if I want my keep back we need those
star things and but why that pass me
yeah yeah please I don't understand it
either I don't get
it just ignore that Baka I don't think I
could take a word without wishes a
world we need to go and find those star
pieces now
princess you can't be serious you're not
thinking of joining them are
you is a sheare Madness you're princess
what will people say I don't care things
seem so hopeless right
now I'm tired I think I need to lie down
in my room for a
while that
room Mario Meo Gino and Bowser you too
good
luck she already give up on joining us
that was fast one word from the
chancellor she gives up on it oh wait
maybe she's faking it maybe she says
she's going to her room but then she'll
just like when we leave this
Palace she'll join us she's actually
just like waiting for us outside that's
probably
it now
then thanks Mario the princess is back
and now declare the state to be known
Forever The Return of the princess
h no never mind
uh could haveen is smiffy who attacked
our
kingdom I fear we have no cause to
rejoice in fact Mario we must ask you
for yet another
favor please on behalf of all of us must
defeat Smithy it is the only way we
shall ever live and peace ever
again that's the plan Prince p is home
safe but she has decided to stay at the
Kingdom or so you
fought
[Music]
she's not even going to beat in her room
right
sh she is
here good luck
[Music]
Mario all
right I think she will still join
us
I already found that secret don't
worry is there something new
[Music]
here anything
here you didn't do the side quest she's
gone for
good what
please tell me guys that this person is
full of
[Music]
Mario a cute are you saying goodbye or
you jumping out she is jumping out
umbrella umbrella
umbrella
okay surprise
I'm joining Super Smash uh
no wait uh different game uh what's your
group
called I thought this was an invitation
to Super Smash
Brothers well then I don't know if I
really want to leave but I guess I
already committed to it so uh I guess
I'll be
okay sorry for the
[Music]
confusion let's
go where's the
star Mario at times like
this what should we do we should ask
Grandpa my grandpa should know oh yeah
frog let's go to the
Frog the gang is complete
she really just
escaped just like
rapel
[Music]
hello show yourselves
tadp I need to see your great frog
Overlord your froger
lord hello let's talk what voice did I
drew I don't remember so it might be
very
different and Grandpa have you heard
anything about the star
pieces well if it isn't Meo I do have
the latest news about falling stars in
fact a large star SP head on Star hell
[Music]
rabbit it does seem likely that a star
piece would fall there we should go
explore Star Hill right
away what I wasn't listening even though
I was reading it out do you know you
know when you read something out loud
and it's just
not FOC I'm focusing a lot on like
creating the voices I
think no idea what was just
sad yeah yeah you know how it
feels Auto Reading yeah I'm on auto mode
where's the
flag where is this
flag oh there ah getting quite far
tentacle oh it's gone now it was a white
tentacle there oh there it
is is it an ALB no
Taco what
pretty but like is this supposed to
be is it supposed to
be
like I can't even form a
sentence to Star Hill talk to the flower
and the star gate will open
to marry more
all oh thank
you oh this is Star Hill this this is
Star Hill wishes which were transformed
at the Star Road Fall to
here but some wishes that haven't been
granted yet are falling because Smithy
destroyed the star the Frog Sage
mentioned star piece on this hill let's
see if we can find
it what wait these stars are wishes is
that what you're saying oh
look wish I had some cricet
gem that could be a frog
wish no what is
this what is this
doing I activated it but like what what
what what maybe I have to activate them
all oh yeah
[Music]
probably
oh like there was a prompt there it is
can't wait to start a family
a maybe that's is from
Bowser surprisingly sweet I hope my
baby's cute that's from Peach because I
have made her
pran
successfully oh wait are they they're
lit up right
okay I wish I weren't such a crybaby
that is
mellow it really
was this one's private why don't you
think you off come on Quest for the
star pie are important everyone's
counting on us we got to hurry I was
just like randomly like putting the
wishes to some random
members
but sorry
mow I I feel kind of bad about that
one I want to fight
these wow that's a lot of
enemies
six o
no I wish I wish Mario had some kind of
AOE wait why is mow in the team o
I don't know let's try I feel like a
jump would work well on this kind of
[Music]
enemy oh oh they're leaving
okay mem you do me a mem maybe it's good
that mow is in the team cuz he has the
AOE that I
[Music]
need he
um okay mow you can leave
now oh wait that would be switching with
Bowser would it I I don't get it
yeah
fail absolute
[Music]
resistance
lucky oh
cute I don't even want to block that CH
Coline
Skittle oh nice perfect
[Music]
hit ew
ew
disgusting e e e e e only did one damage
on Bowser
do punch
punch
the geckos look kind of cute too oh he
did one of those enemy throws not didn't
know you could do that
too oh HP Max
nice ouch it's so cute fck can't take it
this game is a lot on me
man
you going to die
cute aggression that m talked about is
real Yoshi let's go
Yoshi
Middle look at our full
gang a
cute Peach's head is huge my
God
ooh
six that's that's a huge boost holy
I have to take it I feel like I
keep on giving them HP but
like they have such a huge boost I got
to that didn't I already activate them
all which one's is missing oh maybe it
doesn't matter maybe it didn't matter
oh this one this
one is that not what you're supposed to
do actually it's not turning it's not ah
there there okay I thought cuz I
couldn't click it that it was turned on
but no I was just like
standing wrongly in front of it now I
can go through all
right
mhm
any more
wishes I hope I become famous who could
be that one
[Music]
H I want to be the best treasure hunter
in the
world oh we have to watch
uh the movie please let melow find this
way oh that's
for what this wishes mow is again being
called out but this time in the most T
way
ever of
punchinello cute he's happy he for my
mom and
dad they're wishing for me to come home
oh I don't even know who they
are this isn't the time to be quiet
they're waiting for me to come home come
on M we going to busy schedule to keep
I'm making eat if you don't hurry I'm
trying I'm trying my best it's but don't
you think it's kind of nice to at least
have found the wish even if we don't
really
know who it belongs to where it came
from so nice to know someone's thinking
of you and they want you to come
back you never know with like you know
adopted stories adoption
stories feel like that would make you
feel very an anxious about reuniting I
want to be a world class be I want I
want to be wild class
Bea yes I know who that came from the
German
Bakers I did I read this one the hunger
oh for some food someone
[Music]
hungry uh wait is the is that the
same door that I'm I have to go
for the one I came from
again don't see any other
one
bom it's cute that all these wishes you
can kind of tell where they come from
yeah okay I I did it right
right I didn't go back I think if I
could just get that
Melody do you mean the Choate Melody
oh the star piece it's just randomly
over
there but why if I'm already seeing the
star piece why can't I still activate
the
flowers want to help out my older
brother Mario
louisi well then come over where are you
if you exist in this world why are you
not helping me
l
[Music]
Luigi where is
you okay so what about the
star
oh why did I is this for going back why
did I activate the
flowers this one's really easy to get
it's kind of like
freebie
can
hi for real for
real really can we really have it that's
already the the fourth one
[Music]
nice
T cuz you just thought bues yeah yeah I
was wondering like in the beginning also
somewhere yesterday I F boss and I
didn't get a star piece I was like H
okay I guess just not like for every
boss you get a star piece and now we
got you know kind of two in a
row not
[Music]
hold it's fair to earn it while it
remains unguarded yeah I I was hoping
that maybe one or two would be kind of
like easy like this I was hoping for
[Music]
that
the booster Quest is quite long yeah
that's true makes up for that okay
okay where to go
next I think there's a place called
Seaside Town up ahead I hear that it's a
busy Resort town so the people there
might know something let's go and
see you've come a long way but your
journey is not over yet there are fre
more star
pieces
Yahoo he
through this door I guess so it probably
was for going
back wait where
here another
city damn there's so many cities in this
game
wow they're blue are you guys
okay there's nothing of Interest here
don't bother looking inside
sus can't
enter sus are these even real
toads
H can I trust
them also it didn't say that they're
secrets so maybe I don't need to look
for
[Music]
them what are you doing up there how can
I
[Music]
buy momy what's wrong with this
place hello go find the village ell in
his house he's the most respected person
in
here if you want if you want to enter
the ocean jump into the wh
pools are these
people something had like did they get
like poison or
like magically
touched they keep spinning and spinning
yeah they seem um what's the
word they
[Music]
seem
uh hypnotized yeah that's what I
mean I'm just a
customer don't tell me you want supplies
I know oh you actually going to sell me
something
oh trop for cookie that says muku muku
muku
M poison
mushroom what the is this just like
food doesn't say how much it
heals
[Music]
should I get one oh
no this is the
[Music]
in you may stay for free all right if
you stay for free I'll take it might not
be free anymore after I unhypnotize you
guys oh he's watching so Somebody's
Watching
Me
Yahoo that probably only happens when
they're
[Music]
hypnotized that's not creepy of course
it is if you say that's not creepy that
kind of sounds like that's what you do
normally watch people
sleep okay let's look in here
if I can hey someone's in there oh did I
say that someone's in
there wait it did say something about
someone being in their house the mayor
or
something oh didn't I I checked every
place ah maybe this
house
[Music]
yeah finally it took you long enough I'm
the Elder of this Village I got to my
exalted station in life by pleasing my
wait he's blue but he's not hypnotized
so maybe they're blue by default for
real for real which is something I do
well a star is falling into the ocean I
need for a certain purpose you must find
it for me you need to
Star I needed more
though
M
frog pom is that you Bert frog
BT hello there you Mario right do you
remember me we met the too Pond when I
was to too he you already grew up I
graduated from froy school I now I'm
searching for the maning of life it's
been so quiet around here it's almost
Eerie something going
it probably doesn't concern me but if
you have any4 coins I've got some need o
see you earlier times what run from
Battle season nah start a battle over no
nah ooh exp
booster coin
booster
FP Manti
booster oh these are more
[Music]
interesting good for mow but we're not
using
[Music]
mow oh it is hecking expensive I could
afford one of the other
two I feel like XP booster is
nice to be
honest
but if you say I should really save the
for the
flowering I guess I
could about everything there is we to
lighting oh really H well I can't get
the flowering though no money but I will
remember this
frog cuz he do be a special
boy okay so I talked to him and he he
said
the star is in the water so can I go
there
now to the
tentacle yeah kind
[Music]
of uh my dead then oh yeah mow is in the
team right now I guess we'll keep him
done for
now
oh oh wait that's why that's why nothing
was ringing because malow was in the
team I guess
it does it count when none of the free
main members have the ring but someone
in
the like backup members
signs Idol is C okay okay okay then uh
great Item B
smell
oh what Malo doesn't really need the
speed so we could give this to him um
it's quite a good item
she should I give that to
him why not goodbye goodbye thank you
for watching thank
you thank you
oh
hello we can talk
been a while since people came around
here oh I can
buy party refreshed refresh the
status pick me up I maybe
[Music]
one oh the hurly glove would be better a
classic Mario toss I I toss Mario with
this as
Bowser oh oh H
[Music]
ho what what sounded like Ena when I was
doing the sell's voice nah no
way ooh wait again new clothes I just
bought some new ones recently but this
this one's only improving
defense I guess wait don't they are they
always only
defense oh we I think Peach is not
wearing anything right so she gets the
Sailor dress for
sure I guess I could sell yeah I I've
never sold
anything let's take this let's sell some
[Music]
stuff
mhm
mhm it's only things that I'm not
wearing
anyway they're not that uh much money
anymore should probably keep the
accessories oh can get rid of
this
[Music]
yeah oh wait did we not equip the early
glove what the
hell oh some people went into survey it
but they never came back there's
something about a ship sinking
I skipped too fast
oh already getting rid of the chain
chump so sad but this one sounds funny
so
whatever oh I guess we're getting the
new cloes as well that's expensive
[Music]
though
okay okay
chain jump is good yeah but the Mario
toss is even
better so always got to get the best
stuff Min
maxing hairing gloves are the funniest
for real the weapon Sho
and Miss missable after you get the next
star it's weak though get enough you
want it's 123 if it's weak then I don't
want it no no no oh
[Music]
no ah they look so pretty so shiny and
glossy and yeah I think those I remember
those were uh weak
against
thunder so that makes sense but we don't
even need to use thunder right
now because we are strong as f
[Music]
46 okay that was that that happened so
fast I need to see it again okay I'm
using the Thunder
whatever 100 and you're still
alive are you
gladus yeah bye 23 oh my
God
twice
[Music]
oo yeah yeah I know I know I saw as a
special enemy still
though
[Music]
oops get them all get them all no
no a okay that's fine just missed
one level 11
free ooh uh 7 8 9 that's
four okay maybe some Magic for his fire
balls I mean we did say before that we
might want that
eventually level
four
three three h nah this time I'm giving
him magic again too much
[Music]
HP too
much imagine if you decide to grind all
of those before yeah I feel like that
might have happened to some
players oh how could I run into him
ooh what is that new enemy cute
jellyfish
Fish Fire probably not really good but
we can try jumping
maybe yeah pretty
good ow holy
okay these enemies are getting
stronger
[Music]
again oh how does this work again I like
this ah okay okay okay
no
[Music]
no I I think the game expects me to have
Peach in the
[Music]
team holy
I'm just hoping that this kills
them all nope it doesn't okay I'm
okay byebye bye
bye-bye actually oh it's his magic
defense that's really
strong
yeah uh hold this
now
Peach grou and
therapy can you you can't revive them
though
huh I see let's do a solo heal
then
nice and was was Thunderbolt good
against the jellyfish too I didn't
really see much going on but I'll try it
[Music]
again yeah they resisted okay I thought
so I thought something was happening
there oh yeah y b no please no
no mow is really taking this like a boss
so holy
ah could
revive what are they what are they weak
[Music]
to um what was I going to do
yeah yeah M
sheesh wait to fire oh okay okay okay oh
oh I'll just attack normally
then oh
[Music]
nice I might do a mellow Peach Mario
team then for this area
oh oh
I make a mistake oh but
it's it's not bad
[Music]
you're still alive I hate
you still
alive there we
[Music]
go
o Peach
congratulations and ooh
[Music]
nine wow wow wow wow
wow I didn't know the bonus could be
that
high
[Music]
she yeah okay
um uh how about group F yeah yeah heal
HP how much does it heal oh wait that's
not the this is the one four flower
points should be worth it yeah oh it
heals them like fully oh my god
wow then my
team how do I there we
go we'll be this for a
while and also um I feeling like I'm
behind on exp a little bit right now so
let's fight a bit more again and blooper
is a new enemy that we haven't seen so
far I mean in other games yes
[Music]
but even without the action command it
tends to full heal characters yeah
that's just that's
crazy but I wonder if her normal attack
is also useful at all
um I wonder can we jump on the
blooper yes we
[Music]
can
slap let's go Peach let's
[Music]
go a very sophisticated slap we
like to see
it wouldn't you love to be slapped by
Peach where's Yoshi where's
Yoshi ooh I think right side
Yosi peach peach
love oh okay um actually I might take
a oh yeah didn't know I had that
lying
around
you want to be slapped by me yo but with
my noodle arms I might break my arm if I
slap you guys so I'm going to choose to
[Music]
survive
nice
nice mhm yeah yeah that's fine going to
finish the rest with
wow oh my God please
stop oh my God please
stop yeah you really need Peach here
holy
[Music]
A how sweet how
Tey
p is so broken
yeah they know what they did her there
with making her so such a strong healer
it's really
[Music]
necessary
SL bring back the Super Chat slaps nah
those I mean
that was so
stupid not doing that no no no more are
you guys not happy with your kisses huh
kisses from your
misses are you bored of them now are
they not special to you
anymore
[Music]
wow that was a long time ago yeah so are
we going this way way or the other way
cuz there's another
star I came from here right so I I'll go
this
way
ooh o they said something about entering
the
Whirlwind
but probably will hypnotize me
[Music]
no that before I joined
really haven't you been like around for
ages why can I not reach that one wait
that's where no wait that's where I came
from ah ah I already activated it that's
the
[Music]
thing nice
a slap shock
wave I do remember them I don't remember
them I know it might have been like even
two years
ago uh middle
yes why is it so hard to get why was
stream to Lo for me E YouTube weird
today no way no
[Music]
way why is there a safe Point here
already
not but there was still like this whole
other path that I wonder where it was
[Music]
leading I never
mind now I can't go
back I can't go back can
I what's that for there's no boss fight
there
was a
[Music]
loop oh cuz I entered for the bottom
side so I didn't see the safe point at
first but I guess you could have entered
that room
first H
oh
oh can I swim out to the oh it's the
tentacle
place maybe if I get taken by one of the
whirlwinds I'll be sucked to the
tentacle
[Music]
or wa I wonder if we can drain the water
cuz there's a pipe
here but like how do you drain ocean
water I guess leave it to global warming
I don't
know fight me no
okay I'll I'll give the well winds a
try
oh oh for a while I get to be down
here oh how
longa MAA you take a very big straw I
feel like I saw that in like a SpongeBob
episode or something like
that
there's a page from the travel log let's
take a look at it we're done for a giant
squid just got a hold of us the ship's
going down fast uh yeah that didn't end
well oh
spooky there's a page travel yeah let
look at that let's look at that the door
to the cellar is locked with a sixlet
password to get inside you'll have to I
think I know like the boxes have letters
on
[Music]
them so it was J and J already
JJ j
j j again
J maybe it's not just JJJ uncover the
secret of the six hints since they are
provided by different people they' be
tough to solve maybe
impossible
a stop the
blizzard Reacher another new
enemy and Reaper the Grim
Reaper interesting
interesting I wonder if jump works on
you but let's try normal jump
first it does it very much
does
how about thunder you don't you guys
don't really seem like you care about it
but it was their weakness for real oh
okay they don't look very watery
but I you right the pure water
oh but funer worked really well too I
didn't need the pure
water
[Music]
magic I don't
know these are all pretty
bad Nathan thank you board games you
bought a lot of board games for
presents
oh they do seem really easy to rap
anything you want for
Christmas H I mean not that I'm getting
any Christmas presents IRL haven't
received Christmas presents in many
years
but like I
mean like an actual proper present like
I've been given like how do you call
like things that are just uh handed
down like within the family like like
used
clothes that someone doesn't fit into
anymore hand me down yeah I thought so
so I don't know normally when I want
something I just give it to myself
um I
[Music]
wonder I how about
uh uh
uh how
about a voucher
for of any amount to go
to a spa or a
[Music]
massage or
H what do I want what what have I seen
recently that I want what the are
you guys
doing
ah I want that new VR goggle thing but
that one you can't get that
easily I guess need my my my face
measurements for an iPhone
too cuz those are
like very very individually
made fited to each individual purchase
[Music]
yeah the Beyond talking about the
Beyond VR Beyond VR that thing is so
cool hey Peach is
dead uh oh mow is melow sad that there's
a dead body right right next to him a
corpse corpse princess how dead are
these he misses
[Music]
oo 15 okay not
good
what diamond saw oh he
missed oh
[Music]
nice nice
nice destroy
them destroy the green
hot
[Music]
I mean Fireball when I use those weaker
attacks I'm kind of like testing the
waters you know don't want to use up all
my FP basically where did I come from
from
[Music]
here oh
no
nice one
coin or does it just show it as one coin
and you get more
actually what are they
doing ooh wait it's like that
Meme it's like that Meme but there's no
way because that Meme surely didn't
exist back in the day when this game was
first
created oh there were more oh
sorry I I haven't played many Mario
games so this doesn't come natural to me
oh you don't get it anymore
after wait j j j one two what is this
meme but yeah uh you guys know which
meme I'm talking about the one with the
like the reaper I
[Music]
think
grp hog I
guess
mhm hey that doesn't count as you
attacking first excuse
me
[Music]
so just waiting for the funderbolt don't
worry sorry
guys hello
Mom hi
son that
[Music]
reach still thinking about
presents any honestly like games would
be great too like
either digitally or physical versions
but like any kind of game that I might
play in the
future steam cards
yeah Gino
well
five oh this one's not bad either magic
Gino and Magic G uses magic too
right why
not
[Music]
button is floating wait are these things
supposed to mean something to me all the
J's
like go away please what the
hell why you chilling
[Music]
there can I make that
jump he's following me oh maybe I got to
make
him push the ball over
yeah I was wondering is he like
following me the adventurers IND
adventur indigo's memo there is an s in
the
word okay Indiana Jones Is by the way
the thing I the thing I was saying of
what movie we should
watch s Indigo
s special
[Music]
enemy which one I don't know first one
how about we start with the first
one usually I like to start from the
very
beginning a very nice place to
[Music]
start oh
yeah I don't think I've ever watched
one
[Music]
oh
aha I'm guessing you can't just make a
bounce on
one wait does it always fall off at the
same spot fall down on the same spot
can't English Okay so it has to jump
from the left one to the middle to the
right and then to that
button and I'm guessing they kind of
have to all stop in the middle
position
that's difficult as
[Music]
someone can I reset
it
yeah uh
that's maybe the
middle
no that's the middle I
think no no no no no I
wasn't yeah when all three are stopped
it
automatically drops the
[Music]
ball
uh we were a little bit too much on the
right side last time right so
maybe
here
no
[Music]
maybe to the Box position well I mean
more or less that's what I thought would
be the way to go in the beginning
but I don't know doesn't seem to work
the last time I
tried no no okay now I'm too much on the
left
ah how about when it's
like in the middle again let's try it
the very middle maybe I was just a
little bit
off M that's too
far the problem with this one is
immediately it will drop the ball like
ah even when I made a mistake and I want
to redo
it ah let's see that could be n no no
yeah last one has to be way more on the
left m
[Music]
M this riddle which isn't much of a
riddle I would appreciate it if it
wasn't that much time
consuming they could have made it a
little bit
easier maybe give it a bit more of a
wider
hitbox
I don't know going to give it a
try that could be good Ang
[Music]
y
y uh the adventure Indigo Junior's
member memo it is found on the bed of
the
ocean I have to go
outside and check something in the
ocean Indigo junor bed of the ocean in
the other one Indigo was it just Indigo
was
s ocean Mansion I don't have to go
outside bed of the ocean what does that
mean what does that
mean
maybe we'll still figure it
[Music]
out oh I didn't need to do
that an s on the ocean
floor Shell Shell Shell
Shell sh
[Music]
sh Shell
Shell
[Music]
Shell Sherlock Holmes I
am no no I fell
down where the am I
[Music]
maybe that's not the way to
go no I think it
[Music]
is Callie gave up on this one what do
you mean she gave up like how do do I
not need oh wait there is a give up
button do I not need to do this why why
does this game have a give up
[Music]
option like it's it's going up
right what what is this section oh
[Music]
oh down
again oh up
again eh down
again what the oh I found
it what
nice Callie get up on this one
huh
oh wait can I not just oh no I
can't did she get this far
huh
uh oh is that bad did I reset myself or
is this where I should be at this point
oh I can go
[Music]
back do you have to go down and up again
oh where am I
oh oh oh piece of
cake ha
Kelly
haa
ha this is also where you stop playing
what come on wasn't so
hard has two vowels
shellfish what two no not two syllables
two vowels what then shell vow vowels
vow
vows vowels vowel a vowel a vowel is an
e well then can't no can't be shell then
fish no starts with s
right on the ground on the SE ground C
see see
see it's the
same if it's free letters then it's the
sea it seems like it's free
letters wow wait but the sea is not on
the ground of the
sea wait wait about the sea is not on
sea the sea is just the SE wait never
mind
uh never mind then
salmon somebody said
salmon could it be
salmon is salmon on the ground of the
sea nah not
[Music]
really H it has an S but it doesn't have
to be the first letter really I felt
like it's sad it has to be the first
letter maybe
not I get it I get it this time I get it
now yeah no I don't want to fight you
again what the
[Music]
an
s on the
ground and two
[Music]
vowels
scallop scallop
I can't get
[Music]
past let me run you little
tuna but there's no s I can't
I can't get no I have to fight
[Music]
him
corals
oh
[Music]
maybe are you going to ask me the
password
or good hey it's good to see you oh
no
anything new no no then I'm good thank
you a hint it's God to do to see thank
you so much even if you don't get for
all six of the obstacles you can try to
deduce your way through good luck
six oh there's three
[Music]
more I skipped the
enemy wait what what's going on
[Music]
here
parkour so don't wait for
me
ah do I have to catch up with them and
collect
them welcome
back already
failed can I do it
again
yes I I
won I
won was that not the the thing you were
supposed to
do too fast this time
what don't catch up before the
end can't catch a last one until the
end just the last one I want to keep
until the
end
[Music]
oh oh I think I get it now he drops them
and I want to pick up everyone he grabs
and get all the coins I could possibly
get
no
no or do I not need all of them
maybe just the last one before it
disappears and on the way any coin I get
extra is just just me being lucky
cutting
[Music]
cutting now I missed one that was
unfortunate otherwise this would be a
perfect
front I just missed
one
[Music]
okay
no that jump is
[Music]
difficult too early I get to jump
right but I mess it up by being too
quick
quite the
[Music]
challenge no no no no
no no
way can't believe it I can't believe it
I'm pretty good at it though I'm pretty
good at
[Music]
it
no no that jump that jump one more
time this is the one this is the
run my eyes are getting really tired
[Music]
though
my eyes oh I'm like oh I'm losing
my
eyesight I'm getting
[Music]
blind I know I don't need all of them
but I now this like makes you want to
get all of them like I mean all the
Riddles
Answers
[Music]
that was dangerous man that was really
dangerous cuz I fell down once the
search party onyx's memo it is very
valuable so maybe like something like a
jewel
h a jewel with s two vowels on the
ground of the sea no maybe not I don't
know what's the next no I don't want to
fight you
Crystal
Crystal wait is he the
hint
[Music]
Crystal a pearls oh wait what is he the
hint
I mean
yeah pearls I mean they may be in a clam
in on the bottom of the
[Music]
ocean yeah Pearl would fit oh why did I
not do the usual
[Music]
thing seven letters oh what was it
supposed to be
six
pearls so where's the
hint not that I need it anymore what the
is
this
huh
oh hold then let me read let me redo I
think I
understand hey oh
[Music]
wait ah
oh well only one
[Music]
try
sh
woo it's is actually okay that's where
it tells me it's a plural world word
word okay I mean with Crystal I was
really close and then you guys told me
it's a pearl so it's okay I don't take
it as you spoiled me I feel like you
guys innocently just also guessed it
it's fine it's fine and that was pretty
close cuz I was like oh maybe it's a
jewel right so I was kind of
[Music]
there therapy for myself self
therapy selfcare treat
[Music]
yourself oh we' reach the
end the end of the sunken
ship why are the two buts n
[Music]
can somebody of my party come out and
help me with this or do I just go
through
[Music]
oh once I've come up with that key
letter speaking
[Music]
here
oh ah uh even those letters choices are
giving you a hint though
number
two p e ah no oh a was fine p e a just
need to know how to spell was that four
yeah pearls are a girl's best friend
yep e
take I thought I gave you to my
brother context only if you watch the
beginning of the
stream good job I'll let you feel if you
can get past me first that
is it's very slow oh like how here we
fight you here maybe maybe I should have
no we're all healed we're good only FP
could have been better uh are they
always going to be free
tentacles should use my triple move now
oh this one just heals us no then let's
not use it ah let's just
[Music]
attack ouch ouch spank no why do you all
spanking mow this game is bullying mow
so
[Music]
hard
Peach I know I know I already had the
the AOE or was that with Gino and Bowser
I think so I did see the AOE
attack oh I wonder how about how about a
super jump do you like
[Music]
that why why can I never get more than
this h
[Music]
H you're
welcome hey what hey leave me
alone M May okay one tentacle is
down uh status would also be healed
right so I could use it but I
think yeah okay let's do it is cheapap
[Music]
anyway
yes what now it's Mario's turn oh
these tentacles are
[Music]
kinky I don't have much more points
let's just continue with
[Music]
Thunderbolt weak oh but it worked it was
enough surely there's more after we kill
these threee
[Music]
tentacles yeah we move on and there's
just more
tentacles but wait there's more let's
heal
Mario
but the last hole in the very back you
see it's pretty big maybe we'll see who
is the owner of these
[Music]
tentacles where the jumps
decent yeah I'm pretty
good nice AOE damage
bye-bye Mario
ye they learned that from
Bowser no thund the
[Music]
B Zippity
zap that you like the
game what what why did you make
it no not Peach
too she can't heal right if she is
feared like that
well well it'll go
away no she can wait what H fear just
makes you makes your attack and uh
defense go
down okay never mind then
then that's a different
[Music]
story
you know today or yesterday in Germany
and
Austria there's something a topic
trending that I talked about a while
ago where I said I want to make a stream
with that idea from that television show
and I thought at the time that that
television show was dead turns out they
were still doing it and today or like
yesterday was the last day
of that yeah TV show vet andas the last
day after 36 years running with the same
host
even and if I understood this
information correctly the host also
started oh dear it's a Big Blooper or
Kari uh the whole started
with 36 years and did it for 36 years so
he was pretty old at the
[Music]
end
lots of ear plugs
yeah so 36 + 36 is like 72 quick MTH
good
oh let
go that's just 10 but I'm going to use
it cuz I want to use up those items
man barely does anything but that's
fine and just for the the people who
missed that story just to explain that
TV show is so special I really really
liked it so basically it was uh one TV
show
host and some celebrities as guests and
then a lot of like
commoners with some bets they were like
betting that they could do something
really special really stupid really
original really
weird um like blindfold at testing a cat
for example yeah there was like uh
blindfolded testing cat food and
figuring out or like knowing which brand
it is or just sniffing it or
whatever or
blindfolded rubbing toilet paper paper
20 different sorts of toilet pepper
pepper paper against your cheek and
knowing which one uh which brand it is
again stuff like that you know those
were the kind of bets they would do and
they would would like do it live on
stage in front of the big ass live
audience and the celebrities before they
start they would say whether or not they
think you can do it or
not if they think you're going to
succeed or if you're going to
fail and uh I think no matter what the
celebrities say the
person the commoner would still be
rewarded if they succeed but if um if
the celebrity believes in you and then
you also succeed then the celebrity I
think also gets something out of it I
think if I remember
correctly oh yeah yeah there's a famous
incident where one bet
actually had one guy break his spine and
I think he's been since in a wheelchair
cuz he did like a crazy flip in on a on
a little bike I think like there's some
crazy stunt bets sometimes but I think
ever since that happened they probably
became a lot more careful on that show
to not have that happen again probably
yeah no that was that I completely
forgot about that but I remember now
that you say it that that was something
that happened
yeah
[Music]
one time someone threw up after drinking
for a
bit
oh I don't know that one I don't know
that incident but I remember like since
this show has been running for like 36
years I remember as a child with my
brother and my family we would like
watch whenever this was happening was it
like every Saturday or every second or
every every month one Saturday or
something like that I feel like it was
definitely Saturdays though we would all
get together and watch it like I feel
like the so many families would watch
this TV show
[Music]
together it's like a
ritual oh once a month oh yeah yeah
can't be weekly because it was quite a
big event each time we were always
looking forward to it so much I never
wanted to miss a
show so yeah good
times very good
times heard about this from my German
teacher oh
really it's really famous in the German
speaking area oh sometimes I remember
they even had some Swiss participants
sometimes Switzerland beds sometimes
they wouldn't have the bets happen right
at the studio sometimes they were like
longdistance beds like where they had
like a a camera crew somewhere
outside wherever the bed was happening
sometimes it was necessary for the bets
because they were just such big bets or
whatever or just had to do with doing
something
outside yeah yeah remote
B
[Music]
for Mario
Mario Mario
Mario you
good oh yeah yeah yeah the the
celebrities they brought in were also
always quite special sometimes even
English speaking celebrities yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah and they had interpreters
didn't they yeah and I legit as a child
I was wondering like hm I want to be on
this show what bet could I do what weird
ass skill do I have that would be
interesting enough for a show like this
cuz it really had to be really weird B
something unique something that hasn't
been done before
ideally even Hollywood ones I think so
they had some crazy celebrities yeah
even from
America my frog that's not of B that's
not a proper B no it's not riveting
[Music]
content those are going to I guess I'll
just do
this riting I didn't even I didn't even
get that you did it
[Music]
again this fight feels endless and it's
my fault
it's completely my
[Music]
fault
oh now that's all that's left is uh
he himself okay maybe I might want to
use the shock
[Music]
instead can't believe that show has been
running for 36 years and I thought it
was over but that's what happens when
like nowadays so many people just don't
have normal television anymore I think
I'm not the only one by far who just
goes with Netflix Disney plus all that
kind of stuff instead of instead of real
TV and we got YouTube
too and Amazon Prime and all
that now it was
over what do you mean it was over that
was the last show they
[Music]
did
oh welcome to the
membership TV's fault for being bad yeah
the amount of uh advertisements first of
[Music]
all and I mean yeah what like when
Netflix first came
out I mean it was
still like people mostly still were
watching TV and then maybe
simultaneously Netflix
but then after Netflix so many other
like services like Netflix showed up ah
and that
basically resulted in us consumers more
and
more um getting more and more of these
Services because you kind of feel forced
to do it at some point when there's a TV
show you really want to watch but it's
like split all over these services and
you get more of these services and at
some point you have so much to choose
from so much to watch that you don't
need actual TV anymore and you're
already spending so much money on these
Services anyway that you might as well
stop paying for cable
TV yeah please use me I don't want
to I want to use honey syrup I want to
use all my honey syrups before I use
anything better than
that I don't
care I don't care I want to um do
something good for the en environment uh
you
know I want to be
[Music]
epical I know it's slow but we're
getting there it's probably going to die
soon oh I have to hit it when it lands
what
[Music]
what more streaming now than actual live
broadcasting cable is dying stream rep
yeah but like H I guess maybe streaming
services will just do live TV at some
point for certain things that you know
like certain shows you you can't really
they got to be live they got to be like
you know in that kind of
format why are you healing one because
it also heals the the debuffs and
no I need to heal the debuffs because it
makes us
weak um but
now now we might add because nobody has
the debuff we might add another honey
syrup use it all
up I think it's the only one doing well
really I read Disney plus is struggling
really well Disney plus
honestly unless you're like a huge
Disney plus nerd Disney nerd I have
Disney plus but I still I barely watch
it because they barely have anything I
like they're lucky because recently I
discovered that they have um uh Home
Improvement so I've been using Disney
plus like daily these past days to watch
Home Improvement but besides that I
haven't there definitely have been many
times where I was like barely using
it oh yeah I guess I have Star Wars too
yeah if you're Star Wars fan or Disney
fan then you might be happy with Disney
plus but if that kind of stuff doesn't
interest you or you've seen it all then
[Music]
well of course I can do the do the Tim
Allen everyone's
scared okay let's focus on finishing the
stupid
[Music]
fight taso that's all that's all Apple
TV has Tad
lasso that's all they have like I think
Apple TV I'm sorry but it might be one
of the worst of those streaming services
in terms of what they have to
offer
just as the bolt L okay okay too
early
oh a new attack wow
[Music]
so my Coco hurts because that was bad
for the
environment they have some decent dramas
what what SNS what what s never heard of
that never heard of that also I don't
have Apple product so you know I mean I
guess I have an iPhone but it's a work
phone
so you need an Apple product for Apple
TV
right what can't slap the calamari I
guess oh what I feel like I got the
timing ride but I guess that was still
not quite
[Music]
it four hits or five I feel like it was
five more than ever
[Music]
before
I when I Google I just watch I thought
actually only on iTunes
iTunes H there's TV shows on iTunes I
feel like maybe I saw that before but
that's
[Music]
crazy oh still only 75 oh he's dead
sorry that took so
long I was like so to
[Music]
talking wait wait what that what iTunes
it definitely hasn't succeeded in
um getting the point across that they do
movies and stuff what the
hell yeah I too like iTunes is one of
those things that like at this point it
should be like
icq
or
win or lime wire like just things that
are
gone like that's that's how I think of
iTunes for me iTunes doesn't exist
anymore what iTunes exists still
that's a thing of the past that's
ancient iTunes is ancient it's actually
kind of like maybe worth respecting that
iTunes has survived so
far
but surely in some way it's just like a
zombie at this point it exists but like
does it
exist
successfully you bought my album iTunes
yeah okay that's the only thing that
iTunes is good for buying my
album and my
songs hell
yeah I guess
so well well
well
oh sure why not
mow
yeah why why is Apple music different
from iTunes why is that not the same
thing I don't get it I don't understand
Apple at all sleepy
time uh
[Music]
by I did it where's my
star
where am I and what's going on what
what
[Music]
here is this
normal
[Music]
enemy
that of course that was the boss they
recently added HP what for real yeah HP
is like hell project is like wait they
edited to iTunes what about Spotify uh
cuz that's what they really need or
apple music yeah if they edited to Apple
music what they really need is like
Spotify and like all the music services
are you saying they edit their music to
all the music Services they're so late
on that that was a mini boss
oh I was taking my time cuz I thought oh
it's the last
[Music]
one I this for buying a down ah Apple
music for screaming
[Music]
okay once again let's go
peachy is it on Spotify
okay then all is
[Music]
well but yeah back in the day I remember
it was difficult to listen to hello
Project Music cuz they didn't use any
streaming services for the longest
amount of time just relied on CD
releases like physical releases and
perhaps uploading their music videos on
YouTube but they were also late on that
one
mhm pushing physical CD cells no yeah
but you got to you got to catch up with
the current
wave of how things are being
[Music]
done
talk oh interesting thing well of course
something was going to
[Music]
happen
happy wait it's Thanksgiving now wait
wasn't Thanksgiving
already no we can't do our Thunder
attack
no
uhoh screaming it over right oh is it
like uh a specific day each month not
specific date each
month but he not anniversary
wow congratulations to Hino we time to
stream those uh uh remixes
today you you all are invited to stream
the hoton remixes on my channel in honor
of hoton
day oh S sonk one or more F fotes what
does that even
mean no no I know he not only was
released at Thanksgiving but you see how
it doesn't overlap now I guess it's
[Music]
uh why why why is it what yeah it's the
the four first okay okay that's what I
thought that make sense a specific day
not a specific
[Music]
date
I'm kind of like uh bored and
tired what what where is all the
entertainment I had of this game until
an hour
[Music]
ago like not tired asn't actually tired
and want to
sleep where is this
treasure
[Music]
Oh e for Real where is
it should be one in this
room
oh what am I supposed to find more of
these boxes and then jump on them
because I don't think I can reach
that are they like lower ones that jump
from one to
another I needed the fake
Mario can I do it
again I need to stand on him but Mario
is gone okay whatever I hope the item
wasn't too uh
[Music]
important not without exiting the level
damn what's what's here besides the
Enemy No
Bully Peach almost dead y
[Music]
b 222
sheesh
M the full heal special no so far I
don't really feel like
[Music]
it it's kind of lame I wish you didn't
have a full heal special here cuz like
if it was something like an attack I
would use it all the time or even a
buff but we're doing quite fine about it
thanks for the uh membership
renewal uh God I'm like kind of done
with this for today again why is this
why is this so
tiring let me get out of this dungeon
and then we are done
but I wonder how much longer it takes if
you guys are saying that was not the
boss I feel like I deserve two stars for
[Music]
this no way that there's nothing
there uh
I don't want to fight him
[Music]
again oh
oh
okay oh oh that's looking
good this looks
like we are the real
boss thank you for the membership
gift I saved
right
if I jump over there uh I can't go back
so that's the way
[Music]
right woh this one actually has a
different
name you little oh I know jumping
was effective unless this one's
[Music]
different it's still effective let's go
let's try this one zon whatever that
means let's find
[Music]
out okay first of all it resisted it
second of all I still don't know what
that was supposed to
[Music]
do it landed on it
correctly I should have rotated it Oh I
thought I supposed to find
the the place to land it on oh well what
about thunder attacks I I'm guessing
it's not going to work so
well no actually that's also pretty weak
50 for
[Music]
real for for
real
how do I I feel like it's capped at Five
Guys I always jump at the same timing
and I never get over
five there's something very sussy there
I'm telling you to thought
[Music]
you okay okay at least I block a
plus
n he does resist it but it's good for
the Goombas oh my God can you
[Music]
not nah does it get
faster if it would go faster than up to
100 would be
[Music]
insane mini Goomba is more deadly than
the normal ones it feels a little bit
like it yeah becomes frame perfect as
you get more
[Music]
gems it gets slowly tighter
oh I did just feel like maybe it is
getting faster
yeah
[Music]
um
nice another funer ball to get those
shitty Goombas
gone but the treasure chest is also
almost dying oh they even more okay
let's just kill the treasure
chest perhaps one normal jump will be
sufficient
yes still got to kill the goomas I
see
H
hey
no no
[Music]
hey nice wow 240 sh the difference is so
big sometimes between doing a normal hit
and then a a timed
one I got a safety
badge what this prevents smood scarecrow
fear mushroom slip
poison so basically an
upgraded uh True Form pin mushroom
scarecrow
yeah
currently I'm carrying the T oh I'll
I'll wear the safety badge cuz it feels
like in this world they're like
constantly putting one of those debuffs
on
you remember to save one more
time
okay
[Music]
okay I only have super jump for the
reward you get for doing 100
oh regular jump gets stronger than the
more you use it what what do you mean I
get stronger the more I use it
what can you level your skills
somehow why they why what is this
area where's the boss
fight I'm losing my
patience do I go down
here which way this way
what do you mean I'm
blind Lord elok you
are kind of Moody today aren't
you U what am I doing what was I going
to do
ah
blind blind
CH
what what was I supposed to
see now I can't go back up can
I oh was oh frog coins and that look
like the original
no go away
fish
[Music]
oh oh they're not saying I'm blind for
not seeing something you guys are
answering to someone telling them that
I'm playing blind AKA I'm playing it
okay wow big misunderstanding time time
mhm what we're starting with peach now
she's the fastest in the group
now okay let's try
this okay we only affected one but it's
the big
one sleepy
time m
[Music]
where the is the boss honestly look
like the longest dungeon they have in
this
game so far at least even I I may have
taken my time with the one mid boss but
even besides that this is hella
long
ah this region I passed
[Music]
okay so probably this way after
all a please leave me
[Music]
alone
the Stars be
like don't go away let me fight you
don't go away let me fight
[Music]
you
let me
go uh
interesting there's like a door there
but doesn't look like we can go there
don't we go here oh my hi can you lead
me to your
boss what's going on here who are
you H what you're looking for a star
let's a sea
star anyway you're luck you see whatever
falls into the sea becomes Johnny's
property got that
matey and one last thing read my lips we
ain't letting you through God what
lips what
lips bandana
Red O do you guys have other colors
too matching so
[Music]
cute
ouch
ouch ouch ouch I don't know the
timing for
this
uh
please kill them all please
please
[Music]
yes poison gas for Bowser poison foes
interesting
you're stronger than you look better
warn the upper dick come on
[Music]
mate please tell me there's the boss on
the upper
deck all right where's the I don't see
him you guys you guys look the same as
the ones who just
left no
no
e i I'll just jump over it right and
it'll catch the other ones behind me
jump jump jump oh no didn't even have to
jump ouch what the how dare you dodge
the battle
Barrel I do not want to dodge the
battle okay
okay okay
okay my marshmallow will'll take care of
you don't worry about
it he's got to get to
him and not have him die with your poke
sticks they're doing the Hokey Pokey and
I don't know when to dodge
[Music]
it they do shake it all
around ah they still standing
no
oh once
again
[Music]
lucky mow zimu yeah honestly it would
have been perhaps helpful in this
[Music]
area please let me fight your boss
please let me fight your
boss
[Music]
oh that's exactly what I wanted I chose
that
willingly should have healed maybe my
FP Johnny Johnny I don't think you're a
real
shark could it be that you're just
wearing a hoodie like
GAA is this this where GAA got her idea
from from this game the old one so
you're the
Mario not much to look at well this is
this star fell into my sea so it's fine
if you want it you'll have to fight for
it this is not a shark it's a I think
it's a cat a cat shark Wait cat
shark H I blocked it once
Wow Let's try some sleeping
time
nice oh count how many sheep is that eh
wow the main boss resisted but his
minions did sleep okay I guess that's
fine fair fair
enough oh
here
[Music]
comes if I kill us minions does he just
immediately bring them
[Music]
back yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I mean
yeah it would be kind of lame I guess or
too easy if I could make the boss fall
asleep
[Music]
oh that wakes him up oh I
mean you do it's quite common to wake up
someone with a slap isn't
it please do not wake me up like that
please do
[Music]
not magic doesn't wake them up well but
Peach really only can use her slap to
make damage
[Music]
sadly I can't for some reason these Pok
sticks I can't figure out the
[Music]
timing all right that only did 21 damage
on the boss I think
o o
[Music]
oh oh even though it hit them that
didn't wake them
[Music]
up
no and maybe I should switch um Peach
out I might do that
[Music]
for now like I can always switch her
back
in let's bring in
Gino and now the special attack won't be
a heal attack anymore right start Riders
let's
go combiner
Power
Attack yeah finally some damage ooh oh
he turned oh my God it's it's
[Music]
G does it change his resistances I
wonder I hope
[Music]
not
n
did
it ha not
Fu how about it Mario Mario me want to
mix it up
no no no he's no Mario no that's to do
solo cre look alive and tear me
[Music]
on it what for real what they're just
looking at the sidelines come
on I didn't change I didn't switch in
Gino for nothing let me use
[Music]
him God damn it diamond saw
no
no and now I'm out of uh FP oh let's do
one normal
hit ah come
on I'm out of the cheap
syrup I have no
[Music]
choice this
sucks 30 should I just recover 30 for
[Music]
now would be great if I was good at the
jump at this point but I am not at all
I'll try one more time
[Music]
um why am I so
bad w why why want try the fire and my
experience so far has told me
that there they're resistance I don't
know water versus fire normally water
wins but okay let's give it a
[Music]
try it's not much
better m
you think I'm pressing it too
[Music]
early nah damn
it how long are we going to do this
until he
[Music]
dies
uh-oh back and forth
a that's also a tough cookie to
[Music]
dodge oh I got two two times attack and
now he's down what really that's your
big ass boss honestly the the tentacle
boss was like more threatening
more of a challenge
too look more like a big boss
too I feel like they should have
switched but I guess I don't know at
least this one can talk to me I'm
oppressed matey you've earned the
star think of it as a souvenir of our
fight
Jack reveal yourself I'm want to pull
off the
hood we got to get a reveal of the
[Music]
Sharky the squid was weak to fire ma but
it was also weak to thunder wasn't
[Music]
it two
more we got two two or free today free
did we get free today o o o
o what that's that's it that's
like so casual now just looking out the
window what are you what are you
contemplating
about you must have really wanted that
star now go and get out of here before I
Chang my
mind oh perfect timing on the low
battery
perfect
let's get out of here that took way too
much
time
H awesome progress
today yeah I I have to say though that
last area this shipwreck
area anything before that was a lot of
fun today but the Shipwreck area
M they had some fun riddles in there but
it just dragged out so long that it
really bored me I'm sorry to say
everything else was a lot of fun are
they not hypnotized anymore like what
was going on
here you found a star well done put your
journey ends here you're so go ah of
course I know I I I kind of thought so
like they can't be normal toades they
blue I'm Spirit ofit a member of
smithy's gang shocked it's no wonder my
impersonation of an ordinary person was
Flawless it was so flaw I thought you
guys were you guys were hypnotized or
like
imposters search for the Stars has wor
smiy so if I take the star back to him
I'll earn brownie points this is the way
to get ahead it's fut to try and fight
me turn it over uh
no he wait is it
okay wait wait hey hey hey Gino why
[Music]
you I thought Gino would stop me why did
Gino come out to help
[Music]
me what what just
happened was I going to give it to them
anyway was it like scripted if I was if
I would put up a fight I was going to
give it to them anyway cuz I would lose
or
[Music]
what I really I face spawned really
loudly yeah cuz
I I I would think the first option would
be
fighting and okay to me felt like okay
let's
fight they just they just torture the
Elder if you
refuse so I have to give it to them
okay they would have tortured the real
oh so actually this is kind of better
maybe I'm such a genius it scares me
some sometimes no wonder I'm so
important all right everyone listen up
we're returning to the castle all right
should be here about
now I left out of reflex I guess but
what what which is what has just
transpired why did we just give it away
that
easily the reward increases if you let
them keep torturing him
[Music]
oh best reward for giving it up right oh
oh really uh well all according to Kaku
I knew that and
I was hoping for that wait so over there
are they keeping the
prisoners wait we have to open
it that's where the real villagers
[Music]
are
Callie got the worst priz s
Callie she wanted to torture the old
[Music]
people okay okay okay I think we'll
leave it at
this I'll read super jet
though uh
[Music]
oh
o oi Aura you in my chat Aura you little
aura
or or are you in my
chat not anymore huh
1 hour ago she
uh she sent
me steam gift
card probably cuz I was talking about
presents at the
time you shouldn't be gifting me
things
no no that's too nice I don't deserve
from
you
no
no no
[Music]
a I don't know how to react to
this
no
no no no
no no
around
no no no
no I don't
[Music]
like I don't
deserve
no what the no I really what I mean
no I'm fighting with her
now
no
y damn
it give her tunic
so I'll make her play tunic
[Music]
yeah
okay uh let's go to my small
office
[Music]
where's do you guys think I can finish
it in the next stream would it have to
be perhaps a bit of a longer
one I mean these ones haven't been so
long
so far I've been giving up pretty
early think so you could yeah cuz it's
like only two stars left unless there's
like some big plot
twist then hopefully that should be the
[Music]
end
two seems no I want to finish it in one
more I don't want to you
know this is like streamer a YouTuber
brain especially streamer brain I think
streamer on YouTuber
brain um I want to keep it compact I
don't want to like especially if it's
already manageable and doable I don't
want to split it into like too many
parts
[Music]
especially cuz like with RPGs it's
always
like with
every stream of an RPG streaming series
every stream is going to have less and
less and less
viewers you
know so you want
to aim for doing less
streams so as many people as possible
will see
it
[Music]
yeah
bye yeah so I want to finish it next
week but I'm thinking of not doing it
early next week but just on the weekend
again so that you guys in case it
becomes a longer stream can all watch it
M do we keep this music running what do
you think maybe for a
while I'll turn it down a little bit
actually
[Music]
wait
this will it be the first Mario yeah it
will be my first Mario game that I'm
beating I think unless I'm forgetting
[Music]
something it gives the Super Chat
reading villainous yeah a little a
little bit
villainous that's fine I like that mood
let's go on Hyer last time I finished
the final fantasy ones right or did I
not finish the the last one I did I did
right I'm pretty sure I did so after
that comes the retrospective super
chats and the Holo Shar tank which was a
genius stream of
mine definitely like ways to improve it
again but uh first time making that idea
a reality so yeah me Anda were saying I
was saying to her I want to do Japanese
version of this perhaps maybe on her
Channel then and have Japanese members
pitch things to us in Japanese so the
other way around h
[Music]
did I not finish Super Mario did
I that seems like a game I would want to
finish but I guess it got too difficult
I get I I think I don't remember
finishing
it I didn't it got so difficult but I
really love Super Mario
Sunshine I think it was a skill
issue
oh was a skill issue for
real Anya could enter again
yeah if she Anya had some funny ideas if
she wants to enter again she's very
welcome you way better you think I could
do it now you raged hard in a part yeah
what was it what was
[Music]
it it must have been one of the sand uh
block levels in the void you know what I
[Music]
mean must have been one of those
man yeah the bonus stages
ah those are made to be rage
inducing I don't even want to think back
at
[Music]
it that just made me go
insane okay uh so super chats from
retrospective
[Music]
why is
retrospective I asked music department a
couple days ago but I didn't get a
reply um I asked him like do you know
why is retrospective cuz like one of you
guys pointed it out to me I think in a
tweet or on YouTube um that it's not
replacing the video me
in the releases of point of
view yeah let me check
something YouTube
studio
video is it maybe something really
really
simple like is it set to be a gaming
video cuz I feel like you guys pointed
that out to me too but the conclusion
was it doesn't make a difference but
maybe that's the
difference no it is set to music H then
then I don't know can I like do I have
the possibility to replace it
manually tell YouTube that this is the
video for
it it's so weird like all the other ones
happened
automatically
[Music]
I don't I
don't I don't
know no
idea Auto generated by YouTube
[Music]
music sorry for the jump
scare
[Music]
feel like I'm being
murdered ah thank you okay whatever I
don't know I'm still waiting for an
answer if they have an
answer also I'm waiting for pictures and
videos of my album but now I already saw
that them from some Japanese Bros
Japanese Bros fans are faster than
getting me pictures and videos wow
T py danin py danin Jacob 47 D Jim Tracy
D it's really short so I'm not going to
put up the thumbnail Jacob 47 Jim Tracy
D Val
EV I'm so happy to get along with
l
should add the I saw that today I think
it's the kfb
hashtag I forgot to put the label
probably cuz I did it um while I was in
Japan or was I no I prepared it before I
went to
Japan thanks for the pinky birthday was
on the 11th start at Final Fantasy 16
from demo checked your second stream to
see where I was and support myself on
something let's go oh no and let's see
how long it takes you to get to the
super chat with all the collabs love you
buzz thank you I mean well the collabs
wen't so much
isue but I was in Japan
so thank you for being for me I am
changing the bgm thing there we go I
think it was
crackling uh oh yeah no need to remind
me I think I let me put it in my
calendar actually the the Christmas reap
Christmas
R um I know it's Sunday so I should put
out the schedule but uh please wait for
tomorrow I'll do tomorrow tomorrow I'll
be signing the cards that I have to send
out
tomorrow I have to otherwise I get
bunked um I still I'm still missing
several hundred card hundreds of cards
so that will be my activity until the
post Office
closes and my heart H hand breaks I
can't speak English brain
H and then in the evening I'll I'll
record some stuff that I have to record
and make the schedule for you guys but
currently the only things I have uh for
sure planned are finishing Mario RPG on
Saturday and then if I do the Christmas
reefing it will be on Sunday because
that is the first Advent
mhm that will be a hand stream also I
got to do a member stream
members maybe
[Music]
here sure okay but yeah hi
Aura you little
December so soon yeah it's so
cold it's so
cold I don't want to go outside anymore
until the end of
winter
[Music]
uh check
Discord uh have the Christmas Market
started in yes apparently they have
apparently they have and what was I
going to say oh yeah I don't want to I
don't want to go outside anymore until
winter ends but at least I'm going to
the males in
January besides that
I don't want to go outside I feel like
in any season besides winter I always
say that I like
winter but then when it's actually
winter it's also
insufferable it's not so bad I was
actually really happy to see snow the
other day got me really
excited so winter it's okay you can come
I'm receiving you with open arms but I
need to get my scarves and everything
out it's my fault that I went out
without scarves like the wind was really
strong around my uh neck not good not
good oh yeah I will be migrating to a
nice beautiful private Beach
Island with the clearest waters you have
ever
[Music]
seen speaking of how's your neck doing
it's still pretty but it's
definitely getting better yeah
yeah I wish I wish it didn't happen but
it happened I'm getting through it
though I'm
surviving I'm a
Survivor where was I uh oh yeah
uh wait so happy beled birthday oh my
God it's been oh wow that's that's a
while ago I'm so sorry happy beled
birthday
I hope you celebrated yourself cuz you
deserve
[Music]
it crusty D donate blood and
watch Mar say thank
you Valentino d py d and IEP D that was
from
retrospective now let's do the no wait
that was not from retrospective that was
from the lytica
collab I mixed it
up now is retrospective
p7
d d Cruz D Andre d Dominic d tempor d
pet i
a r
SW G thank you for the red super chat
can't say enough how great the song is
definitely one of my oldtime faves cres
to you and the team thank
you n
retrospective was like one I was worried
about the most I think in the
album cuz like it's a genre I I
[Music]
haven't really explored much yet and
singing it was a bit tough but
also the beginnings of the song made me
feel really doubtful until we changed
like The Melody of the singing uh
Melody uh then then I was getting more
and more hopeful but still like I wasn't
sure
like are people going to like it and
like is my voice going to fit this and
that yeah I'm really happy you guys
liked it so much thank you
m Tracy with the pinky thank you what I
you to me my oi
forever incredible MV for my favorite of
the new songs Mone went all out on the
art and the video is fantastic thank you
and they so nice it's really not that
like you
know the those free songs are obviously
like made to be low effort MV is more
just like for me it's really just like
something to visualize
it
yeah I I didn't want nothing I thought
something was better than
nothing and the art also served at the
same time as being art for the booklet
the P booklet pamphlet booklet so yeah
I'm glad some of you guys still enjoyed
it enjoyed it but I I heard I heard you
know some criticism here and there of
course it would be nice to have like
high quality mvs for each and every
single one and of course if one if is
like more of your liking than a
different song like pineapple or sleep
talking we're getting the better mvs
then you're not going to be happy with
how I split things up but for me
personally I saw the most potential in
those and also like sleep talking for
example was finished the earliest and uh
pineapple too pretty early I think so it
was like easier in my mind to like
have a plan and a vision for it you
know yeah so was easier to plan for
something that was already existing and
you know something I could grasp and
make something out of
it and even though plans have changed I
did want sleep talking to be a Fredy MB
because it's such a dancable
[Music]
song but sleep talking is now getting uh
like
a not 3D MV but also not like the same
kind of one illustration
mvy it's going to have more than one
illustration and they quite sensual I
really like them MV I'm aiming to get
out there at uh before the month ends
which I don't know how we're going to do
it um
might cut it close cuz I have to send it
to Legal
[Music]
check we'll see how it goes whatever at
this point even if I'm
late yeah it's not ready like I haven't
seen anything of the video
eh
yeah but the the video cre creator
doesn't currently doesn't have much time
like like we didn't give him enough time
there was also some delay in between
that I feel like was a bit unnecessary
because of lack of
communication uh could have been faster
but also the art took a while too but
like artists also worked really as fast
as they possibly could so not on the
artist either it's just like the
decision that uh I had to make as well
was kind of late I think it was like one
month one
month until I wanted to release the
video from when I made the decision that
it's going to be not a 3 MV after all so
one month to get illustrations so I gave
like half a month to the artist and half
a month to the video creator a little
bit tiny bit less than half a month
and that is not quite enough uh if it's
got to be like bit better
quality yeah kind of tight but let's see
if we'll make it if not then then not
that's okay
[Music]
too it is what it
isep
[Music]
oh sorry I'm checking
Discord then just don't rush it no like
generally there is a reason I told you
guys there's a
reason why I am trying to get it all
done before this month
[Music]
ends trust me it all makes sense in my
head behind the scenes it all makes
sense I can't tell you the reason it's
kind of I think uh crossing the line if
I say
it it's like
a
yeah let's say emosion breaking
business business
reasons anyway um TR C spe space water
and ANP D thank you guys for watching
the premere of
retrospective one more to go sleep
talking the Coro for sleep talking by
the way also turned out really great
even though it's not a fre DMV I really
hope I can showcase the
choreography some
sometimes
dramatic all righty
next
uh
is
oopsie the nail
[Music]
collab I'll put up the thumnail TA
cute ah chy really helped me out so much
with the thumbnails while I was in Japan
and usually he didn't have much time
either like he would make it in like one
evening for
me like the the the poses I did the rest
but like Chucky made the poses and I
think they all turned out so cute and
really well representative of what the
stream was supposed to be
yeah I'm so happy it also helped me cuz
I was like really stressed and and
busy so so so big
tus I feel like I want to do 3D mvs more
often now like I I may not like to use
my default outfit
much but I thank you
takey but for these um thumbnails it's
really great to have chy I know you're
waiting for an answer from me but I
don't know yet I have to ask the girls
first please
[Music]
wait no outfit is the best one thank you
I mean I'm I'm happy you think
[Music]
so all right so let's read Jacob 47 d
assas assas d py d Studio RO with the
pinky and nailed
it what did I nail this was like the
stream wasn't even starting was
it thank
you I want a 20 wat lightning cable
dection what a random ass
username Ted hat 325 thank you for the
pinky isn't this
the the Kiwa race
fan en jooy join join for
thank you T so happy that I could bring
joy to
you but I thought you were sorry I
thought you were Japanese cuz of your
name and all that but you're donating in
uh Korean
one question
mark
come kiar after so long they just hear
switch says it's about oh I didn't hear
it maybe it
is I don't know I just moved the
controller so maybe it's going to be
fine um but yeah uh that was the first
time we like IRL talked properly like
for longer than a few seconds too I
think
so yeah I'm happy about it too it
supposed to be originally originally
when I first thought okay who am I going
to do this nail collab thing with uh I I
realized I could do this because
cie uh showed her fingers on stream
without gloves before so I I knew okay
she might be okay with it most
likely so I don't have to you know worry
about that being an
issue and also you know I know Call's
always down for this kind of
stuff so great opportunity for off
collab for Iris I wasn't sure if she was
going to be open for it but there was um
some recording we had that you will soon
see I think where we were uh together
and uh we were like chitchatting during
the waiting time and then she was asking
me oh when are you coming to Japan again
and I'm like oh and oh oh no I think she
asked me how until when are you in Japan
I'm like I'm not in Japan no I'm going
soon and then she was like oh we should
meet we should hang out I'm like okay
how about you join my off club with
kowi so that's
how this group got
together but I said you can join the off
CL but you have to show your hands so I
hope you're okay with
that
she had quite nice
fingers quite nice
fingers big potential for
[Music]
nails yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah actually
I was just really sad in hindsight that
you know me and cie were having dinner
before and Iris was supposed to be there
too but I guess traffic was really bad
so she showed up when we were like done
with the pizza and we even waited we
waited really long until we ordered um
but like it it seemed really like she
wouldn't be there anytime soon so we
ended up just eating and
then you know she came really really at
the very end and so since I didn't
finish my pizza anyway I said I'll give
this to
IIs
I just had Margarita Pizza I gave her
the
rest she did eat it she did seem to need
it hope you had a nice time chatting
with call though yeah yeah like oh I get
plenty of opportunities to talk with her
about stuff but it's like we we never
we're never done
talking yeah yeah yeah it was good it
was good good times and then I I those
two went to kawi's place first and I ran
to get some more supplies for the nail
uh
stream yeah yeah yeah yeah you're both
big talkers yeah we
are big talkers big
ventor girls talk with Iris soon no we
can do that I mean I haven't done Ghost
Dog in a while and it's not really on my
radar right right now if anything I
should put Hol talk on my radar
again at least one more episode before
the year ends come
on remind me guys remind me to set up
another H talk session come on keep on
reminding me you're welcome to remind me
let's do one in
[Music]
December really have to really got to
Moon Nissa girls talk is a must oh
English speaking honi uh Girls Talk w m
yeah we can do that yeah hell
yeah that would be cute I generally
always want to only have maximum three I
don't want to do four cuz like four
always four already gets kind of chaotic
three members is I think perfect for
like this kind of chatting type of
stream cuz because the balance is pretty
good and like how how much people get to
talk and how much people get like hyped
up like with two people it's usually
like more calm I feel like on the calm
side but then the third person if
there's a third person really adds to
the excitement but it's not so exciting
and Loud that it's like overlapping and
like too much going on too much
talking people talking over one another
yet for for the fourth person and there
chance it gets a little bit too much so
trios are like yeah the best perfect
Dynamic for streams for
me for at least for these kind of
streams you triangle
Illuminati there will be confusion about
n and hor I mean honestly I don't see it
uh that like seriously or like M have to
say what's the word what's the right
word I I think we all have an
understanding like me and Nissa and hot
toi
director we all have this understanding
that the current lineup is the current
lineup and that's how it's going to be
at least for a
while and she's the ins and you know I
don't think uh I think we made it really
clear and people are not really
expecting her to be part of the musical
group H see this is like recently I
learned about this Disney program that I
never knew before but apparently was
really famous in America The
Cheetah Girls so it's like the Cheetah
Girls was a really popular movie based
on a book that was based on Destiny's
Child I never heard about this ever
before but I watch this like documentary
on
YouTube of PE of someone talking about
them and like what went down how they
fell apart and all that but yeah so the
Cheetah Girls that were like touring
musically the lineup was different from
the movie movies cuz the fourth cheetah
girl she was too busy to take part in
the musical activities you know she was
cuz she was also playing in this Disney
show called raven where she was the main
character right which I also didn't
[Music]
watch
mhm obviously she was super popular from
that so no time and no need to be like
touring musically I'm I was really
surprised I never heard of that and and
that they like actually did so well
without that one super popular member I
would think that they wouldn't do so
well but it seems like they did really
well without her
too but anyway this is like how this is
how you could see
somehow the relationship between horor
and
Nissa like nerissa can be seen as a
horor um but not she's she's she's not
in musical
activities yeah yeah yeah
yeah and that's fine like no
one no one has an issue with that
everybody gets
it
it's not something to be like super
super uptight about like don't even call
her h no no I
mean I I think since people understood
it so well and are not like forcing her
into the musical group I think I'm I'm
I'm like more chill about it
too no I don't think it's only the
people in the Super Chat raing from the
from what I see on like Twitter and
clips Etc I don't see anyone being like
uh release put her in the music group
release a song Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah
Blah
no I think we were really clear in the
beginning and there were Clips made of
it too and people got the
[Music]
point
H what do you mean it's the opposite
kle I still see people asking for
Kayla honestly I really don't think any
anyone is really that serious about it
for
[Music]
KY cuz she also really clearly
sets uh draws a line and says I am not a
bird not just like jokingly
yeah so I think we're fine on that front
[Music]
and so I will I will gladly call
narissa a or hor intern you
know it's it's it's all the
same candy stamp s should be faction
thank you for the WR chat thank you
thank you thank you thank you why why
why what are you are you soy happy about
the naked hands or what you're welcome
you're welcome you're welcome you're
welcome are you happy about my naked
hands or about I's naked heads
[Music]
huhh all of people refuse to take the
hint yeah I also like accidentally a
while ago kind of made a penguin joke
about her I don't know if she was there
or not I don't even remember
anymore um
but I immedately felt like really bad
about it but it it just kind of happened
like
naturally cuz I kind of wanted to friend
in a friendly way include her in some
banter oh yeah she was there yeah yeah
yeah I wanted to include her in the
banter just as a friendly joke but I
immediately felt bad about it in my
mind mhm ah yeah doing the hold up
practice
Yeah
I hope she didn't
like take it
negatively at the
moment yeah yeah
yeah she can take a joke right yeah
yeah yeah cuz mum was there too me mum
and Kyla yeah so I was just just kind of
like trying to say oh the BBS are
together or something like
[Music]
that but she's not the burp she's not
the
[Music]
burp prin Rock
Catherine Le
75 I'm a little as someone who's trying
to get into painting her own Nails I
really appreciate the stream for
educational value honestly I also
learned so much WoW was a big learning
stream for me for me I didn't think it
was like I didn't imagine it was
actually that easy to do it
yourself gel
nails M especially like making them look
cute and getting some decent design
designs going and we even just did it
like no plan
freestyle if you plant it ahead it's
going to turn out even
better learn about different hair
extensions oh I guess there was a lot of
learning to be made in that stream no
morally
imoral donate blood
and Chad cast right yeah it was uh chat
cast but swapping out Bales although
Bales last time I saw her she had like
really really nice
nails and so yeah she's she's really
stylish always feel like she would have
perfectly fit in as well at least like I
don't know if how how she is on like
being creative cuz it was definitely a
stylish and cutesy but also very
creative stream you got to be creative
yourself I don't know if she would have
enjoyed that as much
[Music]
but she hit them with eyes yeah yeah
yeah I think so I think so mhm she told
me about the place and was like you got
to go there it's so good there yeah yeah
yeah just like advertising it to me but
I mean even after this experience I'm
not planning to get my nails
done unless it's like a special occasion
like getting it done with like together
with myth for example cuz we're in Japan
together Let's do let's do our nails
together you know unless there's
something like that I'm I'm not planning
to do my nails like I'll keep them um
free
empty blank
canvas yeah cuz I just I don't know
[Music]
the moment I put those Nails on my
fingers I immediately felt like I
couldn't touch
anything and I went I only had it on one
hand right but I went to idle meeting
once I had those Nails
on stuff like that all every single
thing in life that was so
easy suddenly becomes really difficult
unless you're used to it I guess
[Music]
but
yeah everything's
[Music]
difficult yeah
so if I if I put them on for a long time
I would probably get used to it but I
don't know I don't really want to go
through that face it's the same with me
maybe
not drinking alcohol if I would force
myself to drink alcohol I would probably
eventually end up liking it by getting
used to it but what why why why go
through the trouble when it's just going
to be Troublesome and take up money both
the nails and
drinking yeah controller died it's fine
I'm I'm letting the music run as long as
I
[Music]
can
yeah well this the first thing that
comes to mind when you see the
word if somebody clips that what I did
today I'll send it to GAA I I'll tell
her she has inserted brain warms in
[Music]
me
H where was I oh yeah V faction
action um glitter I think you mean x no
no no eggs eggs eggs eggs Michael menes
D Jim Tracy D thank you CL you liked it
sing
D what's your worst beautification
experience oh my God I I didn't read
that at the time thank you for for the
question though I would have definitely
mentioned my hair
removal
Arc that was before whole alive where I
cried because I hated the lady and she
was like kind of
mean not not very
[Music]
um how to say sensitive for someone's
feelings
or yeah I don't
know and it ended up being like kind of
traumatizing some for me like going to
another appointment would always make me
feel so stressed out and and
like I got really really really nervous
even though I already had like I don't
know 15 appointments
before but just the thought of having
that lady do my hair
removal like where I'm like in a really
vulnerable situation ation being like
you know kind of NY
and uh having her look at mean like I
don't like being niky that's why I don't
like to go to
onen and then it being like super super
painful
too and her not going down on the level
of
strength because otherwise it wouldn't
be as efficient itive which I understand
but when I first started the those
treatments the hair removal treatments
um I started it in a different city and
the staff that was treating me there
they were like really really sweet and
caring and understood that it was really
really painful for me and they would
turn it down for
me and I mean I was I was understanding
too that it might not get as many hairs
this way and I may need more sessions
maybe but I don't know just kind of made
me feel really really bad about wanting
to go down on on the on the
level and just generally had this like
weird attitude I don't even remember it
anymore like what exactly was going
on I have erased it out of my memory I
guess but I just remember I was like on
the brink of Tears the whole time and
before I would go in and and after I was
walking out I would be
crying and I would be like always
terrified before going in cuz I know
that I had this lady be in charge of me
again and it was going to be like an
extremely
uncomfortable uh like one to two hours
cuz those sessions were really long
too like it's just
m
not
good
yeah being in pain and feeling like kind
of
judged and being in the
vulnerable
nakedness yeah for such a long amount of
time
yeah we have tried to get another person
yeah yeah sometimes I did um but
sometimes they were just not available
because they only had like two
[Music]
people and like usually like after one
session is over we would sit down to
like make the appointment for the next
session which would still be with the
lady the evil lady that just treated me
and normally she would like
like suggest dates that work for her
where she was available I guess and I I
I I couldn't outright ask like uh for
this date uh yeah like I don't know are
you in charge
like oh you are uh then please let's
let's a different date you know you know
I can't like aim for that like asking
are you actually in charge cuz like then
I
would kind of let her know that I don't
want to be treated by her
oh it was kind of hard to get around
[Music]
that can I can I have the other lady for
no particular reason just just that you
suck you have
no what's the word
[Music]
compassion not nice lady not
nice why not it's okay to have a
preference but then like if I if I if I
have to get her because there's no other
person available because H empathy yeah
empathy cuz I think I remember I
remember one more problem was like that
the other one last more one more
available staff who actually like I
think she went like on a vacation or
something and then she wasn't available
for like two weeks or longer or
so
so yeah didn't have much Choice
sometimes so I still had to
be
like have her like be neutral with her
as much as I could didn't want to have
her know how much I hate
her cuz that would make it even more
awkward and
painful yeah empathy empathy that's it
yeah she had no
empathy yeah
yeah uh where was I uh Jim Tracy dun oh
no I was here just a dank Raven dun I'm
a little D Kon
dang study found cor oh yeah this one I
read and I was really confused about it
angry ghost thank you for the rested
chat H question what is your favorite
winter food in Japan like eating Ramen
at a stall in the cold was mine when I
was stationed there in Germany I learned
to I loved gline at the Christmas
festivals ah yes yes yes yes I don't
know uh you may have been a viewer of
the other girls and asked it in the
hopes that it will be answer then and
you're not hearing the answer now I
don't know
but winter food in
Japan I mean for most people I would say
people going to mention stuff like Oden
Oden which um you can get in like
convenience stores but also in like more
specialized Oden places too but
basically it's like a a warm soup with
some stuff like egg and like Kaku but
thing is I hate Kaku and there's like so
many kyaku ingredients and there's
barely any ingredients you put into Odin
that I like so I don't go for Odin
ever even though it would be like the
perfect winter
food what's what's kyaku
again let me tell
you
Kaku uh appears in or a type of Japanese
St blah blah blah blah no that's not
it no no no no no what is Japanese
kyaku where is the where is the real
answer it's kind of like a weird jelly
ah is a rubbery rubbery flavorless it's
not really flavorless I don't like it
zero calorie high fiber food made of
yams
H yeah they come in all kinds of shapes
either in like doodle form or block
form yes Devil's tongue is that great
gelatin with the dots yeah that's
it
[Music]
ah you know it from Stein
gate and not the drink not the drink
conac
[Music]
M I need to go to Idol meeting let me
finish
this where was I oh yeah so that's like
favorite winter food in Japan for a lot
of people I would say but for me it's
like maybe Ramen and like K udon like
any kind of uh noodle soups like
udon or or
Ramen yeah hot hot noodle soups in
Japan that would be my
goto Japanese wither comfort
food M
and you know one thing is great uh one
thing that is great in Austria or like
Germany or generally I guess in other
places too yeah other places too but
they like this is one common thing they
will sell in Christmas
markets uh to
eat hot foil oven potatoes with sour
cream and maybe other stuff like
toppings like uh bacon and cheese
Etc yeah that M I love eating that at
Christmas Market and of course roasted
almonds roasted sugared candied
almonds always love
[Music]
those I got to go to Christmas Market
soonish but they're they're like so
expensive so my friends don't want to go
like yesterday I was like hey who wants
to go to Christmas Market with Wawa and
they're like I don't want to go the the
glue Vine the punch so expensive
these days everybody's like I don't want
to go too expensive let's make punch at
home yeah I mean that's fine too making
your own punch
[Music]
but it's like about the atmosphere you
know of a Christmas Market all the
lights and all the Stalls the
people being cold as
and drinking punch out of the the
each of the Christmas markets special
cup that they
have that you can keep if you want or
you give back and get some money back
it's experience you know I guess you can
I was thinking so too of was suggesting
okay let's make our own punch at home
put it in a ferace and then go to the
Christmas Market don't buy anything just
drink our own
punch I don't even care about the punch
cuz I I don't you know if anything I I
don't order the normal punch I just I
just get the the children punch with no
alcohol alcohol in it but I'm also fine
with just like nothing
I'm I'm more there for the food than the
drinks most people go there to get drunk
on the
punch I go there if anything for the
food and and just chilling
there it's like like at least once in
Winter you got to go it's an a must
activity at least
once my throat is
dying it's t the season T the season of
fro
hord guys it has
begun you're going to hear fro hord from
me throughout the whole winter
it was nice until now was nice not
being fro
h no I drink so much it doesn't
[Music]
help I need to pee okay let's finish
this
Ving T the g t need more daa s fancy
tacos burritos
iceo
Dy TV table Marcus V mat P sender
downburst d sanot d Kevin p d EV d stand
d i Am
thank you for the
pinky I I I I want to
say generally I don't think my fingers
look so much like sausage fingers but
somehow with those angles on those
cameras they look a little bit
sausy they're not that crazy sausy
IRL no I know that too also just having
Nails immediately I said that already
but immediately makes your hands look so
much prettier and longer and
elegant I'm falling
asleep the Great
Ghost Sky
theh z d Mar D and I
am thank you
guys so happy you guys liked this idea
like way more than I thought especially
like you know when I when we were like
in the middle of it and I noticed oh my
God this is taking so much time oh my
God it's been like I don't know 2 hours
oh my God it's been 3 hours holy
taking so long I was really like worried
that it wasn't entertaining it was
boring but
but I'm I'm really
stunned you guys even though it was a
girly stream and we were also a lot of
the time super focused on the nails
rather than
conversation I still enjoyed it so much
what the
hell yeah I was trying my best to like
bring up conversation topics but was
also struggling cuz I had to focus on
the nails if I don't focus on the nails
it's going to take even longer and it
was already like at some point like like
past 11: and then it was past midnight
y so trying to balance
that really
difficult yeah it was kind of like a
drawing stream yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah maybe Ena would have been
really great in this kind of
stream she already is pretty um well
trained in talking while drawing isn't
she
okay guys I'm going to I'm going to go
scattle thank you for spending time with
me winter is killing me
I have no energy I'm tired my
throat H let's let's get through this I
just hear
[Music]
meow tomorrow no
stream and but schedule will be up
later
[Music]
and see you soon maybe I'll upload a
YouTube short tomorrow actually um
remind me feel free to remind me on
Twitter W you wanted to upload a YouTube
sh thank
you okay byebye J we say in
byebye
[Music]
down oh yeah the thousandth video too