[Music]
n a
n
[Music]
hello
hello hello K what does that
mean
k is that how you guys say hello who are
you I don't know who I am am I just died
a moment
ago and I revived here in this empty
white
box there's a couple of other people
here there's a a sign that says
enigmatic e
n uh enigmatic is that how you say it
recollection would be nice if I
recollect my memories huh
yeah must revive my memory can you help
me please please I don't know who I
am my my head feels
so light
today as if like there's something
missing there but it feels quite nice to
not be wearing anything on my
head what do you mean I have a German
Channel I don't speak German do
i h
well well
well in any case it seems like we're
here to do something
interesting um you know uh let me
introduce myself to you I think I know
my own name right
yeah I am
Tak uh from nothing in particular as far
as I know I'm just my own
person um and yeah I'm a phoenix and so
I di sometimes and then this happens I
usually gradually regenerate my memories
after a while so I'll probably be
fine uh yeah I like this white box it's
like a box for insane people right
usually you put insane people into a
white
box with no way to get out that seems
like a thing you would do with insane
people does that mean I'm insane
perhaps or or am I the one taking care
of all of these insane
people
H who
[Music]
knows I if I got is well I mean I don't
know yet what this world is like because
it's just a white box maybe this is the
whole world maybe there's nothing else
to
it yeah here let me PL but let's get rid
of the bgm for now because I have a
feeling that something's about to happen
in a moment or two it's just a box just
just huh that rings a bell somewhere in
my mind just a
box somewhat familiar but it feels like
someone else's memory to be
honest just a box in what kind of
situation would you say that this is
just a box just a box just a box just a
box just a
box H brain came out oh is my brain
leaking oh sorry let me get rid of it
thanks for letting me
know oh sorry that happens sometimes I
guess when I
revive let me put it back in okay yeah
yeah yeah that felt weird like it did
feel like kind of
Airy Airy and
Eerie okay thanks that's better I feel
more closed
off who is our crony
wait no do I know I don't know if I know
I'm not
sure our crony like if there's our crony
is there my
crony the ah ah is it a typo should it
be h o u r crony is that her
name the hour of
crony makes sense surely that's her
name or is it
macaroni m
mro
macaroni you don't remember massaging
her who who did I
massage I'd prefer to get
massaged if she can do that then we'll
be
friends so yeah are you guys uh excited
to help me recollect my memories I don't
know if that's really what this is about
probably not that's just my own side
quest my own little personal character
side quest uh what do you call that kind
of stuff you know character Arc my own
arc what about Kelly H who's
Cali
H let's see is there a cie
here she
cie no she seems kind of shook head at
the like it's seeing
me let's
see oh she's orange I like her
G
ninoa cute she has some orange in
her oh Mor
copin Mory kopin is that her this woman
you speak of so
fondly Mor
copine is that how you pronounce that or
is it Mor cantal opian can't
elope can't elope can't elope with me
huh Can you she doesn't seem to be
hearing
me I
wonder what the
hell wait I thought we can't but I can't
be in inside of you huh that's weird oh
the hour crony
girl the hour of
[Music]
crony you think she'll give me a massage
if I turn around massage please massage
please massage please massage
please massage
please here massage
please does she understand
hey my back kind of hurts from being
revived come on come
on come
on I know I'm muted she doesn't
understand also she's wearing the wrong
Cape no that's because she wasn't in the
in the meeting where we told people how
to do the cape
thing she'll have to learn eventually
there was no meeting on new oh people oh
people oh
oh I don't have a BL button you guys are
talking to each
other give me a
second you're supposed to
be
uh
what that didn't work out
server closed that's not how was
supposed to
go think they're restarting the server
or
something okay now that we're out of
this I can stop role playing for a
moment
right as long as we're not in the game
we can I I I I'll stop role playing oh
we can rejoin okay
ah
hello hell
oh my God it's so
red am I dead Mo your mouth now a cron I
was trying to you I I have this feeling
that you might want to massage me so I
was turning around and like
telling yeah
of I don't know why but I have the
sudden urge I than so you're so good at
that what about you you the voices are
I'm
aat very quiet so L ear it is really
loud here so you will have to figure out
the cap thing later as the gods are
telling
me we were like muted
originally I don't know but I'm hearing
voes
like this is the last 24 hours I can I
can see their names a I think a lot of
adjusting
cop people have been telling me about
you good things bad things I don't know
they're asking me if I remember
you do you remember me will it make the
people watching you feel bad if I say
that I do not no because I also don't
remember you oh okay well then we're
Square I I guess it's probably no
problem I like you because your voice
isn't Jonathan G too loud right it's
nice in this corner that's not really
what it you can stay in the corner and
maybe that's not really what I'm right
now what are you think I get nervous
around people that I don't know are you
insane by the way
maybe let me turn you up cuz your voice
isn't too loud
is jonath I wouldn't be surprised this
room seems like a room where you put
insane people into it spelled Jonathan
like an asylum yeah that's yes yes
Jonathan why are we in this box wait a
minute can we get out doesn't seem like
it we're stuck my initials leading to G
stuck yes Jonathan G me out oh I
see good luck to you as well on getting
out of this box
hello hello hi
[Music]
some of the others are hiding
in of the of of the okay
andyy okay sorry oh is this Z
okay I
guess I
guess Exchange
[Music]
oh Echoes of Forgotten memories press
sneak
key I'm pressing it I think oh ah okay
Who I Am the world I live
in and more than
anything who the [\h__\h] are
you the people I hold most
dear faced with Oblivion I feel
empty oh is this where
we
relieved yeah I guess kind of relieved I
mean this is normal to me I show up here
every once in a while perhaps
distraught I do not know they don't want
me to look
around
mysterious so much I don't know and yet
I know it all so much don't know I hear
voices again so much I don't know so
much I don't know
hello don't
know let's go towards the light let's
go have I
fall which light actually yeah which
light a lot of
lights the
bright I must yeah don't fall there's uh
it's kind of oh wait that's it looks so
cool what if I want to fall does
somebody want to never mind
oh this looks dangerous oh
I this place must be
like oh I guess careful me
lady oh thank you than you the light
follow the light is this
it
B they have him
Beam Me Up
Scot take me take me alens is this feels
to be Dad wait what is an
alien familiar too somehow go towards
the is this
the what that that looks like an egg
this is
much
that big egg like a broken what is is
this a hole but oh my God it looks like
a hole oh it's not a hole okay not a
hole which
light is that the
moon should we go towards the
moon sit on the
EG byebye
[Music]
oh can't move liestal Castle in two FPS
no we're good we
good you there what are you doing
here you have to look off Outsiders
about
you oh wait could it be send to his
majesty is it always a God one talking
the heroes have arrived at the sanctuary
yippee right
away heroes are we the
heroes Royal audience chamber let's go
cute who are you are you the
king welcome Heroes this is the kingdom
of Lio and I am its king oopsie oh ah
the guards who brought you here have
informed me that you remember not but
your own names am I not alone
here a side effect of travel between
worlds no doubt no side effect of
Reviving but
sure it's a little bit different for me
sir you going to say
something this must come as a surprise
to you but her can well uh it was I who
summoned you here
you see an unprecedented Calamity now
threatens our world it has shown the
Earth with corruption and driven us from
our
homes this blighted land now gives rise
to creatures of Shadow known as
stains this Kingdom of liestal and its
surroundings are now the only safe place
left to us leeston but should the colam
be left unchecked it's only a matter of
time before it consumes the entire world
world oh
no that sounds terrible faced with this
Prospect I scor the ancient Texas uh
text for a way to combat the Calamity
and therein I found one
me the ritual of her
summoning you who hail from another
world have been summoned here by my to
by me to become the sav saviors of the
lesbi uh
Lio
yes only you have the power to save our
world and so I ask Will
you oh green person hello you you
Majesty what is it a great host of state
of broken for our defensive line
no we're rushing to m defense but the
situation is dire Your Majesty we must
get you somewhere
safe what about me I don't deserve to be
in a safe place
huh who who are these
strangers maybe the real Intruders was
me along the way what say you Heroes
will you accept this Destiny there is
great power within you will you use it
to save us to save this world yeah sure
okay I have nothing better to
do are you guys fast your name
Ruby Cel swords oh we have
swords
I my name is who are these interesting
beings you look like a
bunny you met the cake
so many
voices I guess I'm somewhat of a hero
myself who
you you
am nice to meet you a you look so nice
you look nicer I like
cats you like cats can I adopt you
yes cat
adopted well I'm going to follow you
everywhere now oh nice okay that's more
like dog behavior but
sure I am going to leave now okay do we
talk to these
people you yes I do sense a mysterious
power well my name is Rubi
okay the r hero the room Heroes named
Ain braing Ain my specialty shut the
normally but he fortune favors the ball
don't it let's show him strange what for
E strange what stains what for
eh the ancestors blessings uh upon you
uh my name is celest do not hesitate to
call upon me should you a need for my
let your art be your compass uh compass
and I have faith we will
prevail we
will pra
uh uh there the guy from my
side I thank you for learing right Brave
Heroes you may call me
VES V you may call me VES you may call
me VES oh thank you for Lending you
eight heroes you may call me
V okay okay good good good good I just
thought that was your name cuz that's
what is written above your head well are
you more coll why is this big ass Castle
oh my God I guess so
wow
wow all right I'm out of here I guess
I'm going to go look for Adventures ha
no this is quite a nice land I don't see
any any
evil here at
all this world probably is fine yeah I'm
going to solo the world Dam in Solo
run I regret that he must face such
things
so you
mad someone was killing me someone some
some some was it
you a dog no no I I adopted her she's a
cat I'm not killing her tell me wait
there's they're talking to us was like a
dog
like what the hell
uh I I regret that you must face such
danger so soon after you arrival uh
wait all right should is high voice
better I don't know as his majesty no
doubt explain to you our kingdom faces
an unprecedented crisis the Calamity
beils the land leaving it bft of life
and infested with the monsters known as
stains not even the mighty Li
[Music]
best fight fight fight fight fight for
the King fight for the king
I beat you my take them down I take the
I'm
DPS is it taking
damage maybe
maybe what I accient
pressed are we all supposed to die babbe
is that scripted oh it might be a thing
maybe we're not ready for
this and I don't have to read
it don't give don't give
up we must kill the K the stay
King was slain by
stain May believe in
believe in me who believes in you he's
not taking any
damage ground
pound St me ground pound are we doing
damage to
him is Immortal
no
got he is so strong we cannot hard them
we're too low level we're too low level
yeah
where is he we got to look out for each
other kill
kill kill kill kill but there is no
meaning in all any of this there's no
point again ready to
play I turn it off shout
Revelation
re
Revelation hold your weapon and left
R let let me eat
[Music]
first
revelation
mhhi
ravioli left the
game well I can't I can't I can't walk
to it I can't
re
Revelation
um there seems to
be
something being typed connection lost
you were kicked from main server
closed use mouse cursor connection lost
shut up you were kicked from Main shut
server closed use mouse cursor or tab
button to
selected
online four milliseconds short role
playing message of the day of Minecraft
server zero out of 50 players
online screen element one out of eight
selected L back button screen element 8
out of eight left click to
activate I think I turned them off I
think it's CV
right I think I think so okay okay okay
even though it was quite nice to have um
you know a more like deeper voice
Somewhere In the Mix of all the High
voices okay okay there's a little bit of
um waiting time um the the the the the
the Revelation has to wait a little
moment it seems as
if it takes time for Revelation just
like for revolution you
know it takes a moment or two and I
think that is very realistic it can't
all just like be so easy as like lifting
your sword and screaming Revelation at
somebody what does it even mean
Revelation what does that even
mean vivola
Revelation are you guys fine by the way
so so far with no bgm I have this like
cute bgm but like I I don't think it fit
the vibe quite much right
now um also I'm figuring maybe some of
you are watching more than one stream so
maybe it's already very much to take in
right you're good okay then well I'll
get rid of it then
okay oh
Revelation in German means often B
wasn't it nice that we met someone
German speaking along the
way and that cat seemed the name of the
cat seemed rather Italian to me maybe I
can speak Italian to
her yeah I can use my
languages maybe maybe one of my strong
suits mhm I don't know she just had this
like German Aura like German people just
have German auras around them that's
just normal you wouldn't get it you
wouldn't understand
yeah why is it so hot in this uh room I
am in this room that I am residing
in let me do something about that well
since we're not role playing right now
let me tell you I had weird dreams I
haven't been sleeping well the past two
nights I don't know man also in my dream
it was like
whole life and hello project merged into
one company
somehow and I was I was realizing like
oh I'm quite the Senpai and then there
was there was
takari
uh which doesn't say anything to you
guys I guess
but and and ah who were the others there
were others
too also I could fly again I was again
escaping from
something and then somebody
yeah what happened I don't remember
anymore I should have told you right
away in the beginning when I woke up but
alas
alas was an interesting dream for
sure I didn't said anybody on fire this
time I don't think
so even though that sounds like a fun
thing to
do prophetic dream I am the
prophet I am the prophet
I am for telling you and foreshadowing
you the
future I I shall let you know that on
the third and the fourth I won't even be
able to participate in this which is so
sad because there seems to be like
something cool and new every day and
I'll be missing out on a lot and then on
the fifth well jst so PST is like 345 is
like 2
three4 the days where I won't really be
around the on the fourth SL fth fifth
jsd um I can stream but I can't really
stream probably when everybody else is
streaming so I don't know um I already
asked someone to accompany
me um at that like at at an earlier or
later
stream so somebody will accompany me
then but still I'm like missing out on a
lot it's I'm so sad and then I probably
most likely won't even be there for the
finale which I'm so mad
about I'm so mad about it but I'll do my
best to participate on the days where I
can
participate yeah yeah I'm most mad about
the
finale which it seems that the finale
will be pretty exciting from what I've
been told they prepared a lot of cool
stuff for
[Music]
this a lot of
interesting missions and dungeons you
saw you saw in the in that trailer uh in
the 3D program right you all watch the
3D program right that I was in where I
Mis mistook M for
fuaa
um yeah yeah they showed the dungeons so
like they will open dungeons each day
and so like I think today the first
dungeon will open but for the third
fourth and fifth I won't be there for
the dungeon
openings so that's
like really
mutai I hope I'll be there for the
dungeon opening of my dungeon I think my
dungeon is
probably
the lava one but I I'm also confed like
I feel like the Atlantis one and the ENA
dungeon is pretty
obvious but I don't know uh which one is
which one's mine actually I don't really
I think it must be the one with
lava uh yours is effectively than never
is it really like nevering is it
nevering is it doing the never
thing I don't know I don't think I'm a
boss no but I have a like a karap
[Music]
dungeon oh only only the lava there's no
never like bricks and stuff I don't I
don't think I saw anything neish nothing
that looks like never in the
trailer yours is the second level one c
yeah that's confusing like I thought
like is this Callie's or mine you know
we'll find out we'll find out eventually
Kim could also be
mountainous I guess yeah cuz Flying
Phoenix and this and that but nah it has
to be with maybe maybe a flaming
mountains fire mountains lava Mountain
volcano or something like that I don't
know but anyway it's already built so
we'll see the Austrian Alps no those are
not very fiery
I think they'll let us know when the
server is ready like I I have Discord
open on the side seems like they will
let us
know so we can just yap
yap
um e and Reco a Minecraft server how you
guys doing by the way how you guys doing
I learned my last Coral yesterday but
the next today and tomorrow I have to
like
like like try to put it stronger into my
brain I have to like really learn it
like I say I learned it but I didn't
really learn it like I picked it up but
I'm I already forgot a lot and I need to
like you know you need to practice it
several times so that it's like really
in in the in the brain oh
wait Can We join now
[Music]
H
oh oh okay we can go back joining to
play he's still
there the
game men use mouse cursor or men use
mouse cursor or tab button to
select have too use mouse cursor or t
accessibility settings narator narrator
narrator
no
longer free from the darkness and back
into this large white room oh truly care
shark there's a shark nothing but
torture there's a
shark
where there's a shark there's a
[Music]
shark going to eat
us a gluten tarian a
gluten oh you don't eat people
I like bread you like bread oh okay me
too I keep my eyes on the yellow one the
yellow one seems to Havey
appetite she's also just eating
bread
hry we could be the bread
Club y bread Club I only have four left
wait can we touch
tips oh my tip please don't eat
my what you do you sto my
sword starting
again was
the do I need to revive again C
all
power they won't let us out of these
wall hello beautiful hot woman to the
voice is in
my I will never
know if she survived that oh okay we I
guess we're restarting everything
skiper
skiper skiper
Skip it's okay this was pretty cool so
why
not oh mum is sick of
it just kidding toward line oh oh my
Japanese
keyboard who was the fastest to Skipper
Skipper I wasn't skipping I was reading
I was thinking that
oh I was skipping I was yeah I was all
in our head going be first let's go
let's go to the light slow let's
go oh
wait oh you can walk on this hole that's
crazy who give me a heart
attack does that
mean that oh they really like made a CH
children
save accent
thank let me test
this
oh
oh I she it's
safe cat my cat come here my cat meow
meow I have I have some tles no don't
get aggressive over the treos I am I am
a wild pamper I'm telling you I can I
canot tell you at any moment if you were
a wild Panther then why did you let me
adopt you because you I like cute
girls come on I got I got some more cute
girls over
there
yippe
okay I'm not ready I don't know who she
is myces know we didn't finish our
conversation some I'm looking for
some my wife oh might be uh because I
find you very attractive can I have F
you do I you're very attractive too hot
women let's go look at that
[Music]
behind you know they say we have to save
Lee best but I think what they really
mean is we have to save the lesbians
[Music]
I think they might be right let's save
them together let's do it okay for the
[Laughter]
[Applause]
lesbians we'll save you
guys we'll save
you careful K careful K too much
lesbi this is really cool over there
want to go there looks like a boss fight
Arena do you believe
for the
lesbians careful
K too much lesbian let's be in Castle
okay oh my God uh hi nice to see you
again heres have arriv to the sanctuary
yippe it's keep keep oh hi King
hiking is a subunit of the idle company
hello project made up of several members
of all of the hello project idle groups
uh such as morning musim smile Ed uh bet
scobo and
cute and it was a very successful
subunit and still has only released very
few songs but I highly recommend it as
they were really really good at what
they were doing and big recommend uh
there was T in there and she absolutely
slayed
[Music]
so no that just came to me like the word
High King it literally rang a bell in my
brain you need to
go uh uh uh
okay wait I know what happens there's
going to be enemies Happ yeah how do you
know
how do you
know I remember you guys don't remember
there was a battle right here am I crazy
yeah I crazy are we in an endless
loop probably how do we break it I don't
know maybe we need to kill
someone one of just someone oh yeah
let's kill someone anyone will do oh you
I won die without a yes shall do who are
you you purle like the St
why do you smell like chicken please
don't why are you purple like the
stains purp am I a bad
guy maybe you're the evil one oh my
God that makes all of you my enemies
then oh you be how
exciting maybe we can top that and have
an you can top come on no one will ever
oh hello didn't we have this before
sounds familiar
yeah you want a massage yeah can you
massage please please go ahead guys
massaging outside of the castle Yeah
yeah I don't know how she knew that I
needed that endless
loop do it right that that's sword
that's a nice technique you got there
need your help thank you I thought maybe
someone her oh oh special
massage okay all right thank you I'll
massage you back uh eventually a big hat
you
have massaging each
other you one oh yes I would love a
massage please
please please please I will give you
some bread I will give you some bread
you must prove
yourself in other ways oh what what ways
what ways must I prove myself you must
break this endless loop
okay I promise I will break this Loop
and I'll get a massage what is your name
my name is tanakak karia of the oranges
you have hair
Tak wait you autocorrected
me
takiar no
tanakia
tanar of the oranges tanak kakar of the
oranges oh I see I see I see it is nice
to meet you t t just call me Shakira
just call me
Shakira oh Shakira yes yes Shak Shak
Shak oh I know that
song my song something I remember my
song us
out I am smells like it's you are I was
about to say it smells pretty to them
maybe that will trigger something
right you are I will up the sword and
protect her royal what is sheing I want
to hear to I'm a little curious what
what is going on the big guys are
talking oh okay
oh it's happening
again oh you're right it is
nice fall
the wait I'm ready right here I remember
from my past life yeah it's going to
happen here I see the blood that's still
in the
soil what do you
remember I remember you Perhaps it is
too late to save this world from
destruction
nevertheless my name is
Jonathan it is our duty to defend our
King and our countrymen to the very end
Brave Heroes From Another World let us
go forth with
yes let's go
long live the king wait that's I think
we're still not doing
[Music]
damage are
okay maybe he has like a like a weak
point him from the
we got a jum after
really I want to
Rive not the same without
narration yeah it's not as
dramatic nice
nice don't lose your
motivation what happens if I die
what if he's just really hungry oh God
I'll save you from this evil
dog no don't don't hurt my wife of them
don't hurt my
wife we're on a mission to save the
[Music]
ladies like a pig
a ground pound maybe we have to on head
I'm not sure chop chop chop
chop oh
no
R what happens if you die fuzzy one or
did we make the fuzzy one I don't
remember well
let's see if this time we can
shout
Revelation
oh
Revelation the stain host has been
routed
routed okay
cool oh
hello hello
again
Celesta you thought bra can't evse I
pray you are not
injured yeah I'm good I'm fine just a
bit confused generally fine I got my
popsicle sword happy about that for sure
oh don't want to
one must be their leader the stain King
fascinating Most
Fascinating Orin Orin was the the the
the orange one
right wait uh
[\h__\h] uh we St more D thanks to your
Val our kingdom is in your de thank you
yeah the orange one was supposed to be
like
British I
forgot uh I must hasten to inform this
Majesty of our Victory will you
accompany me
yes oh oh we're back inside it's
gorgeous royal
chamber I heard the news though we
called upon you suddenly you Rose to the
occasion you have my deepest gratitude
what interests me most however is the
strange power you manifested during the
battle with with which you were able to
defeat the
stains that power May well be the key to
saving our world from Annihilation that
how you say that according to the heroes
the power came to them like a forgotten
memory when they spoke the word
re spaghetti but once thing used it to R
the stain host it seems to power
vanished Without a Trace oh well that's
blood uh or oh wow that's BL bloody
blood bloody brilliant ain't
it so what are we supposed to do the
next time the stain's
attack revelation we must un cover the
secrets of this phenomenon if we are to
Prevail against the
Calamity many questions remain but one
thing is certain the kingdom of liestal
still stands St thanks to you
here here so the heroes I ask of you
once more will you lend us your strength
to save leel and the lesians from
ruin hell yeah
Revolution
Revelation marvelous on behalf of all
the bans I thank
you we are blessed to have your eight
King
EOS allow me to introduce the for great
Gil
G guilds which are responsible for
ensuring the Kingdom's peace and
prosperity uh the heaven of the Curious
curios where knowledge and creativity
are valued above all the scalet
wound the home of for glor gloryus with
Ambit and vision their closest closest
or Allies become fiercest ah rather
the Amber
coin uh the sanum of heing where the
spirit of empath and
Devan the beon of the Rous and the loyal
uh loyal their great threats
ah
ah threats are faced with even greater
courage s
SW one of these guils will become your
home during your time
here Beyond this door lies room
of will of shall decide your guild
oh okay ah I'm just
ahead Revelation burning Phoenix
Revelation burning Phoenix cool wait I'm
supposed to walk right ah ah uh fear not
introspection is a vital step on the
road to Enlightenment excelsia or as I
always say even higher or ever
higher time to roll the dice eye by
saying some of you some of you down at
the Amber 's going to have fun reading
this one
huh she's not going to be changing her
accent at all for that one let us s vot
together so the room of the TR go for
for
Valor I don't know who her is no idea
didn't talk to
her ah room of
Truth step on the platform and receive
the will yeah of the ancestor okay the
will of the an why am I so dead oh my
can I eat
first amidst the countless sparkling
lights seek Enlightenment with Scarlet
F sure let me eat though I'm hungry what
does that mean amidst the countless
sparkling lights seek Enlightenment with
Scarlet
fervor my swe
scet oh oopsy that's fun
sneak
appicon
orange gang what's up
oh Dawn the
cloak yippe I'm with an unwavering whe
seek wait to
defend I am wearing Z clo unfortunately
it doesn't work with my weapon
weapons in here wow it is ey with a
beautiful new cloak it really looks
fancy doesn't it seek to defend the soul
of Jade H soul of Jade I thought I was
Amber what sure what
what oh admatic
recollection roll the credits oh on the
table
T hello there
yipp oh wait oh it's our Guild sorry to
keep you waiting oh that's I got a
walkie-talkie oh what was yeah you also
got a recycling
why recycle be got a map oh yeah we got
to recycle for sure oh my goodness how
do we talk we got to speak to the Gil
Master how do we talk to the master uh
we have the British
one wait we totally do oh I I can talk
to him how how do we you speak British
yeah right click he says Watcher this
air is the Amber Corn's little den of
operations uh name's aurin and I'm the
closest thing in charge around
here aurin we have the British
one straight away after you were
summoned but we appreciate it now you
one of us me We Fight Together against
some stains maybe do a little we saving
while we're ated eh
perfect wait he's Canadian
too
Canadian Town we're in learn how to
accept and
perform quests see there's a quest board
out in town where missions get posted
might want to take a bches out and see
what the quest master has to say are you
perhaps are you British true because you
do it this so well I don't understand
either I'm trying to catch up here oh
that was
that was me that was that was the M
was skill Master next go to the quest
board we have strangers wait where is
the quest Master honestly that
conversation took so this is the quest
Master but don't worry you need bother
him okay the quest oh go to the quest
board okay let's go to the quest board
we're up on to the next Quest slow down
what was your name again for the I'll
follow you B okay what's your what's
your name ah me you yes what what's
what's your name I am uh nice to meet
you I'm takan nikara of the
oranges what is your
name or all of your names what is your
my name is
panta I already adopted you yes ra cute
cat nice to meet you nice to meet you
both my name is the B and this over here
is three very nice nice to meet you
that's not that's the lazy version of my
name free no it's Cleopatra Eisenhower
divin she the great the third for short
three just call just call her three
three the number
three she not very nice try not to get
on the bad side no I I just treat people
the way that they should be treated
that's
all these are very nice I don't think
we're going to get along y
I what I think that I think that
there'll be a Twist in this story line
and we'll be the bestest of friends
that's the twist I don't I also wait is
this guy is bookie the quest guy perhaps
this one we need to find the quest
board sorry I think the first thing you
need to understand Isa where I'm going
we're going we're going the wrong way
everybody do you think that's the quest
board everybody I going to find the
quest board where oh you're right we're
not supposed to be here well we're not
supposed to be here oh we're not
supposed to be there oh no going in
trouble we're going to get expelled oh
no we just got here expelled like guess
this a school or what I I I honestly
would like please leave me alone wait I
have an egg do you guys also have an egg
I have an egg I have an egg can we eat
it cuz I'm running out of
bread would you like a piece of bread no
I still got two but like just wondering
for for you know the future if I can eat
the egg well I have five so five eggs or
five breads you have five eggs wait we
lost our
cat we lost our
cat cat
cat cat where's the
meow ah meow she so
oh the sun is already coming back cat I
I I lost you for a moment yeah I noticed
I lost you so I came back for you come
with me cat thank
you I I knew there was something
missing the purring was missing thank
you there she is I got last cat needs to
be on a leash it seems no I'm free one
God can we please have a leash yes need
the leash for all cat please no I'm free
kitty harness guil cat I am
fine free cat where are we going today
uh according to this map I think the
quest Master should right over here nice
look like a board that sure looks like
one oh
yeah that's a good
board nice
board let's see looks pretty empty to me
you must be one of the heroes then
Master told me about you I here is the
quest and requests people here
hello oh did you guys come from like a
different
Castle the green
Guild green
people what kind of people are the green
people
they're nice this at this oh my God your
sword is way bigger than mine I know I
meks imagine I don't think I was
supposed to
find about how you use it of excuse
me but it has a really long going on
reloading
thingy think
don't why your SW so big
I have a shield too we need to
go hour we I don't remember
[Music]
what
Jonathan eradicating the stains but I
hope you'll take the time to help some
citizens in need so side quest you must
be tired of my P by now and how about we
get you started with a quest right away
ooh this year looks like the perfect job
for you well best of luck uh off you go
okay where the heck did you get a horse
speak to the GU I don't know I just to
ride
one you stole it you must have stolen it
wa where do you check the where do you
check the quest give the horse
back my
horse hor me horse me hen
yeah I'm on my last piece of bread It's
a Wonderful Pure Heart stallion it was
a to the how did she get
Horan maybe she already completed the
horse side
quest speak to
the a GU Master is our side
quest right click
I hope you have the time for some
ciens
wait get off how do I get
off circles who
circles my friend
all the
same
thees
thees yes me lady we are going on a
quest do you care to join us I shall
join you of course as we are Guild we're
on the same Quest join us except now I'm
lost I don't know where they they left
us we'll catch up with them yeah by the
way may may I actually uh receive one of
your remaining breads you may because I
have more than you thank you I have zero
at this point wait I can't give it to
you oh we may trade oh how do I
accept like this yes like so okay one
one bread for you did you did you get it
you are so kind uh I guess I oh wait no
just here go wait I can't what just type
accept I can't I can't put it in your
box oh yeah May
[Music]
I must
exchange oh wait I lock in to trade we
got to uh click the red uh thing in the
B at the bottom
I one more time one more time stand
still do not when you put the bread in
can you click lock to trade on the red
box
thing huh uh uh below the golden icon
there's a red
thank you yeah but the the bread you're
missing the
bread oh I got it thank
you I shall not
starve are we going let's go we can go
with the horse
too you ride are you a wait what the
heck how did you get the horsey you
right click the egg horses come from
eggs and this
world that's so
fast W so
fast Apprentice of blacksmith is that
The Apprentice oh we got it's up there
oh I see oh my gosh wait hold up what sh
you can get off with
shift okay shift whoa you're killing
your horse you're killing your horse oh
my God
horse oh cuz I right clicked egg hello
hello over here we're in the wrong house
ladies oh I don't think we can get in
there all right how do you shift shift
shift you shift you shift okay I shift
all right it's this way stressful hor
how did you disappear this V is so into
the house I was just it's just the power
and S I love the houses look at how big
me endless speed is it in air in air in
air that's a sh
I think he's there he doesn't have thece
problem I think it's up there what's the
oh yeah it's over here mhm so this is
the smithing but I don't know what
materials we're supposed to
have we need 10 logs bunch of trees we
can
oh okay
what we have axes girls oh let's just
go how far do you think is is this I
know how far is that can we take
this can we take these trees I I don't
think so I don't I don't I don't think
so we better not maybe we can go a
little be like further out yeah yeah
yeah yeah further what the
horse outside outside what did you say
your name was CLE
Cleopatra Eisenhower Da Vinci Eisenhower
d the great the third
okay oh I shall remember it this time I
Believe In You Cleopatra thein TR you
I'm TR a I'm
sinking okay I'm
fine be careful
cat you don't like water let's go
where'd they go we lost them
again hard to
well they're probably around the the the
trees
right oh there they are here they are
okay let's grab some yeah not considered
outside it respawns right away but oh we
don't get the wood from it Farm here who
even wants
these well
then wow what's this
Arena even there this is such a big
arena one might call it Ariana
Grande what I did not accept the quest
but it says complete the side quest and
then speak to the quest Master at the
top of the
screen I
follow outside maybe
maybe I
never Cleopatra
I was told that I did not accept the
quest
actually you didn't accept the
quest oh no oh no oh no oh no help
someone help me help help help you need
help help what's wrong what's wrong I am
in a dangerous
situation here how did you do that I
might die good goodbye no don't die I
I'll try to go step by step
yeah well well well that was a shortcut
for me to uh go back and accept the
quest properly how come you guys know
the game better than I
do those girls shall not be concerned
about my well-being I shall find um my
way one way or
another um
ah right I have a map so I go I'll just
go to the quest Master
again
correct what is this oh yeah this
way it's because we're not distracted
yeah I am confused uh overwhelmed
um this is a quest
boardy you must be tired I died once
maybe you have seen
s
there um well you shouldn't try to like
get stuck in high places let me just say
that I see I see so how did you has WiFi
how do you accept the quest
properly I think you talk to him and
then click on this and click on the
thing oh click to order thank you so
much you have my gratitude Forever Green
lady and black and white oreo lady thank
you so much I appreciate it remember
that for the when come to col anytime
anytime I shall honor my my
promises
okay uh well then I shall try to go
where they
were by this is a radio but like I'm not
sure private call party call I am not in
a party it's okay um they
are uh
probably where the arena is and the
arena is
not there I don't remember going
there
maybe we just need 10 little to the tree
that has there's the
arena okay and I mean are they looking
for me I want or did they just move
on hey go to Smith again what oh okay
sorry oops uh is that shown on my
oh this
sh it seems as if I am on my own very
own side quest here yay
okay oh oh
oh I'm not the only one who's
late with all of this uh I talk to him
or what how how does this
work oh oh it says completed completed
already
okay
what coins 100 collect 10 J pick up the
phone oh
hello oh her Guild is trying to contact
her my guild does probably think I'm
dead
forever who what how did I how did I do
that is that is that my cat
my cat my cat my cat I I found you oh my
God where you looking for me haste I was
the where are you I'm
here how do you go outside what I'm I'm
call I'm calling to be at the phone oh
wait a sec wait Bae where are you
there's phones in this Medieval
World oh H how how did you one
outside wait I still need to go
what yeah no I don't I don't need the
phone right now I was muted I'm sorry
G I know how to go outside we have to go
to the blue spots come here okay but
wait I'm not sure if I really accepted
the the quest so okay let's go double
check um cuz it says what does it say
for you it says I have 100 coins and
side quest materials needed at the
Smithy is it yeah it says the same for
me as well okay but they say I need to
still talk to the blacksmith I'm ready
to cut down it
says needed no you hang up let's just
double
check what do I want do we need 10 oak
logs may we need we need 10 o Oak CL
yeah okay I mean that seems like I'm I'm
through with that okay we can go go
okay want to make a party together yeah
yeah I invited you I invited you oh how
do how do we accept the party though I
don't know but we're in now we are in
the party okay okay good let's go let's
go Horse Adventure okay we have to go
here probably you want to go on your
horse cat it's it should be like right
here so it shouldn't be that far
there should be teleports here blue spot
we should find some crystals crystals
[Music]
H maybe the child can tell us child
seems to be
local on the gate on the gate probably
doesn't talk to strangers is it is this
the gate I'm I'm checking
when blue stuff on the gate I'm going to
call B maybe again then to us okay wait
I'm going to call Ba no no no I'm
calling you wait
sorry me uh
pral where's me please pick up to leave
town just approach a crystal by the gate
I did see a a crystal by a gate but not
this tiny gate like a bigger
gate was like here
here here I see it l acka i see it
does she hear me when she's
calling this one
right
yes I don't want to go without
her come
here over here I'm sorry over here never
mind we found it I I'll be right
back she just caught me for no reason
she made me terrify for no reason she
made me lose 10 years of my life that I
just started for no reason
I found it yeah let's go you found it
you made 10 years of my nonexistent life
that I just hello everybody hello I am
back from the dead living
again we have enough wood we we have a
lot of wood we can leave now oh I don't
have enough wood it's okay I have
wood I have 30 you want to trade once
again I can do this
yippe yipp
yipp
wonderful would you
like so generous I don't know how to how
do we trade yeah accept how do I
accept press T then then click on
accept oh okay done Mom let's go back
and get that
corn we finished the quest yeah
there you go take it we
have how do I get it think you click
the thank
you wait actually I haven't got
it I'm going to
grind yeah eventually all right let's
get out of here let's get out
[Music]
here let's go wait ladies should we
create should we create a party uh L's a
party leader right now she would have to
invite
you okay I invite the party pleas I
invite tree as
well I invite hey hey hey hey hey hey a
hey all right let's go
back that why we can't hear anybody else
what noises are
those hello oh wait she can hear me
man what are you looking at get out of
here let's get out of here I I don't
want
to yes okay oh it's getting dark we got
to get out of here
oh
oh let's ride boy I mean
girls where are all the hor just like
that now does it change each
time made
it yeah you guys got e too know
here um I don't I'm not comfortable
should we just are there people I feel
very unsafe right now I I don't feel
comfortable do not know they are there's
danger should should we come back
another time we should come back another
maybe we should introduce ourself may we
should make more aliens and more friends
where we the Amber coin may not we must
not be uh scared by
others EMP corn
incoming
Cobblestone oh oopsie how do I make a
pickaxe you can't make one
youing
mat M was made do you have the required
materials wait what my master where
where's the Master it's completed we can
go to the quest Master yeah where's the
master especially if you need coin wait
do I have to do something with them ah
everybody have their pickax
yeah she gave you uh oak logs right yeah
I think they're in a box still right
yeah I open it
and ah we got a fail to purchase you do
not have the require we got to make
planks and sticks all right I okay we
need PL I have planks and we need sticks
all right I how many I was I was trying
to skip the process I understand I'm
sorry so we need to make planks d i got
this one CH perhaps got it don't worry
how many though I can do that how many
of
eacha oh o okay I got all of it then
what what do we have to do now
complete okay I made the pickaxe it cost
money
CRA the wooden pickax and then talk
to the thank you so much over there if
you bring the raw
materials Cobblestone next
cobone too many people are speaking to
him at
once we shall go and get cobblestone
girls I'll wait for you outside all of
our money am I am I using all of our 10
Cobblestone okay we got to go go
Cobblestone right yeah yeah so let's
wait for the other girls out here
yeah Cobblestone with the pickaxe I see
I see there's an order to this after
that we'll probably make a a spoon and
with the spoon we shall get
sand talk about being old through it's
not really no that's not what that means
we got the next
Quest order younger they don't live
that's shallow the
B keep hearing hearing something in my
ear but you know it's just three
Cobblestone is
here I want the
[Music]
EXP oh no careful it is it is a nightly
time where many danger awaits Us in the
outside Fields yeah what is the what is
our current Quest here Cobblestone
cobblestone
tan Cobblestone AEP 10
Cobblestone rep I still don't understand
do we all need to get cobblestone all
right you got Cobblestone each one of us
needs like I don't know how many 10 10
Cobblestone cobone okay okay oh that
makes oh I'm sorry that makes sense
because then we can upgrade our tools
I'm the next the next going to happen
okay I got so every time if we get if
they ask for turn we collect 20 you know
that's let's
go did that wake you up
huh that's
sick extra extra it goes in one line huh
I really don't think we're going to get
long three if we
don't stop fighting you two I think I
think we got a slowburn going
on it's more morning let me
morning
right I've got enough I'm ready to go
back are you ready to go back also ready
[Music]
yeah just need 10
right
yeah okay okay and we go back to the
back
[Music]
me blue protocol maybe didn't work out
but this is kind of an MMR Pino huh wait
watch out out
out was already
broken where are you my friends
Elizabeth blood flame Cleopatra please
don't get us in trouble with other
guilds oh hello there you are you're my
friend yay where you going is no
mattering
your she isop D Vinci something
something deferred you must respect her
those legendary horse girls oh wait they
don't hear us do
they they not hear us I don't have
enough coins oh oh oh I don't have
enough coins either we need to go far
maybe how many coins you want what did I
want I'm no longer rich I no longer Rich
all right I have 21 Co what what what do
they want us to buy
thank you what do they want us to buy
now
iies I don't know your losing her oh
what we supposed to do now I think we
have to go back to the uh maybe the the
quest
board okay maybe me of armor would suit
you best Quest Master oh yeah Quest
Master Quest
Master you should just
I think they're busy this way oh here oh
a new face is here hello can you guys
hear me yes very well oh thank God hello
there's who the heck are you I have no
idea who are you why there's so many
cute girls all around me all of a sudden
what are you in me lady oh I I don't
know what I'm doing I'm going I sound
like someone I want to get my nails done
with what your name what's your name God
my nails done in ages my name is Iris
and I don't know anything else besides
that name oh Iris s so helpless and
[Laughter]
weak a cup what do you mean cup I got a
new Quest what what quest what do you
mean cup what group are you bu
Something Blue Team oops The Blue Team
cup that's what I was asking oh goodness
all right another one some gold I don't
remember the names of the other
te only ours matters he number three I
haven't said it do we have what have I
done to these people I don't understand
talk to the shopkeeper what
shoper perhap have on it might be hey
did you not get a quest that says so
build something you're asking the right
questions what have you done what have
you done I don't think I've done I I
don't want empty lot we all heroes but
I'm the
big interested in conru and it says to
shopkeeper were talking to
you
shopkeeper yeah well okay if it says
that let's do
that I have the same
Quest I mean the B
where no I got the same Quest though um
okay that's pass the garden and you'll
find an empty lot right oh yeah there
are many
quests TI oh there are more than
one we can actually switch the pages oh
these are all the the side quests is
there no main quest okay let's get all
of them this here looks like the perfect
job for you okay
okay complete the side quest and then
speak to
the where did the other two go suddenly
okay oh over there Iris yeah if you're
with the blue
people you do you want to like join the
blue people or you you can join us too
oh yeah I don't know who the blue people
are and I I honestly trust you guys
more you can join
us our our party leader shall invite you
to our group for now yeah yeah yeah I'll
invite you we shall babysit you babysit
me please yay y y are you still on your
first Quest yeah I am well we can help
you with that thank you how do I how do
I accept this invite um um you click key
and then you click on accept with your
cursor nice
nice excuse me excuse me I you you you
seem to have a blue aura around
you no we we have decided to Babys her
because you guys are too late I found
her I found her help teammates teammates
to the quest they're they're trying to
kid her who are trying to take her away
no she's ours now she's ours they're
trying to take her away she's
ours don't we can take turn oh my God I
have will protect her with my life
this is
our our team you were not there when she
needed you quick come with me no no
jo are you win think too late now
so okay you can have her I
mean what what you're Bing me no no
honestly if you want to be with us you
can be with us
help you complete your quest gu come
here come here come here let's go Iris
super you leave us you let's go leave
them behind byebye no come to the dark
side come to the dark side I know you
have two halves one dark and a and a
lighter one you
must listen to the darker one us give
her back oh my gosh she's suddenly
hitting me she's suddenly hitting me
Who hat You Who hat you I will hit them
back with you evil one massage lady I
see that's why you were massaging me
with a sword re Revelation to you
reation
[Music]
Revelation Revelation no she's grounding
oh you're fisting
oh nice
fist oh thank
you cute they look like from a retro
game what is a retro
game yes I know not of what you speak
hello who are you you beautiful
beautiful violin lady oh at least you
know I am to be the next Queen of the
kingdom of lesto what I did not know of
your intentions so that's how you say it
this is not an intention this is meant
to be your destiny it was meant to be it
was meant to be are you are you related
to them are you their
air be blood blood related are you blood
related to that tiny King what no we
have bued eyes and we knew that we
were you married the king are you under
with the
King it's
complicated was to close to
me but you don't have to you didn't have
to
accept wait I wanted
to talking to
me all right all right this is the
future Queen of the
liest yes
yes I'm glad you know fellow peasants
peasants my my queen I'm sorry for
speaking to you withrespect we will not
protect you if you don't respect
that's why you're in a different
Guild you need the you need the support
of all the guilds in order to be
successful wait wait a second where are
all my guil kitty cat that's okay kitty
cat que yeah yeah I'm talking to ba the
phone oh what is she saying she says hi
she says
hi where did they go okay she hang out
okay so are we are we going to help Iris
or she left uh is I think she'll just
like probably end up leaving her group
and go to uh the blue people she doesn't
seem to want to commit to us that's okay
let's let's go to shopkeeper then right
you know where it
is yeah all right awesome let's go she's
still in my party well she'll have to
figure out how to leave one way or
another childrena
nice trid children that have that tend
to the
gardens H what
shopkeeper ah there's a
chef
oh kitty
cat kitty
cat kitty cat
meow I was muted I'm sorry
why you keep on muting yourself I don't
know why it mutes itself I'm not sure
why which one's the
shopkeeper okay this is the shop but I
don't see any shopkeeper do you see any
I I I think we're actually aren't we
doing the a different Quest from each
other wait uh do you know how to how to
see your quest but mine says who's
interested in
construction yeah
exactly
okay and what he says what you got to do
oh oh right now I have to speak to the
shopkeeper okay good okay good let's
let's let's find
shopkeeper this is the shop but there is
no shopkeeper
H
um
Chef I don't see any Quest book did the
other girls also take the same Quest
I'm not sure like B wait let me do a do
you want me to call her I suppose so you
could you like calling her
okay Outdoors maybe Outdoors you going
to hang out
oh I found I found the shopkeeper oh you
found it he's right here cute little hat
there you go oh that's so
cute so are you the
one I know he doesn't do anything for my
quest okay we completed yeah
completed yeah what did you do did you
press like alone
off conspiracy
theories you sker sker oh all these
people talking about this one
come here have to go to the Garden okay
the best child in the
gardens where are the
gardens I see the I see the
child oh I see it it's out this way
hope she's following
me this way oh oh she's following me
over
here in here a we talked to this child
before is it here yeah over here this
one scared to hurt the
child car you're one of the heroes boom
this must be my lucky day right well
this here is the gardens free to come
and use them whenever you like pretty
Acy in it my job is to keep an eye on
them scare any away birds and stuff if
you don't like gardening you can also
try building and there's an empty lot
just past here where you can where where
your Heroes can build whatever you like
and you and your guil mes can work
together to make a right spy place to
stay stop by anytime if you want to do
some building or gardening oh say can I
tell you a secret did you know there's a
place in town called the pit fighting
pit mom say as kids aren elogical but I
heard you can play a really fun game
there oh you're her so I bet that let
you in maybe you can go check it out and
tell me what it's like anyway I hope to
see you again okay complete speak to the
pit
doorman oh okay so I guess they just
generally wanted to tell us that we can
we should or could build something but
first they I guess it was just
inspiration and now they want us to talk
to the Dorman okay yeah let's go do you
you know what it is I yes this map
always tells me where to
go up here so now now I'm good at
navigating am I
not this is how you do
it but it's like a little bit slow to
update I got to stop sometimes and
sometimes this is like too far over here
over
[Music]
here we're back at the am coin place or
is it oh there we go hit him hit him
excuse me wait
we're I need to talk to him it's a
misunderstanding
you don't tell me you're one of the to
AR rich I know you could make a
fortune to run with the before no
they're in the Amber coin just like me
okay you guys can go ahead without me
they also taught us how to work as a
team
sword yay I got it okay point at your
mate right click on from there oh we did
[Music]
that okay we need to talk to the Jade
sword Guild Master so we have to go to
the other way you skiper skiper
again yeah you can read for me please I
no it's
okay you can I love it it's okay it's
okay okay so what guil Jade guil Jade
sword Guild Master yeah this is the
messenger so M we probably have to go to
their
yes let's go
over somewhere over the
rainbow this is Orin wait did I go the
wrong
way ah oh too early turn too early
sorry and this
way and this
way a g I know
but oh this
way she still following good good good
good my cat I'm following
good oh must be in here
oh yeah
on know
about see returned break hero they're
pretty fighty they're feisty you don't
want to get in between them learned
about
adventuring has born have
turned I have not familiarized myself in
town at all
[Music]
same oh you were calling me the
Calamity I was like what is this
sound hey you just got to you know you
got just got to follow like the on the
map the the the name that says that says
VES oh okay yeah it's a red name
v m oh I think I there you are no I saw
you over here
over here oh oh oh I see it thank you oh
my God just so you know where I am yeah
yeah yeah I got to talk to the guy in
the
middle I thought it was somebody's
sticky keys okay stinky Keys who has
this how do we leave this
call it really is please socialize with
me gu
Master regain your powers of Revelation
to that end I have just received word
from one of our Scouts regarding a
possible
lead to the pl to speak to
hustes on the Jade sword oh interesting
can you read an Italian
accent uh where have you skipped
everything again no then read wherever
what you're seeing right
now
okay uh go for with Valor
I'm here today to thank the Guild Master
bravery and
Leadership they nothing much and you got
to talk to the middle guy oh I already
talked to him oh you Skipper
Skipper are you actually reading well a
little bit Yeah they put some work into
the floor you know you know you know
what from now on I'm never going to skip
erever again okay
wonderful so oh see Iris was abandoned
once again should have gone with
the
oranges
IR yeah we would not have abandoned her
she abandoned
herself she abandoned herself for real
say exit the Town Gate head to the
Plains and speak to hastus of the Jade
sword okay okay okay
map MAA MAA ah I see okay follow me how
do you find the the the the gates uh
when you open your map it's a bit hard
to see even for me because at the very
bottom left she left her
body uh but yeah on the bottom left like
the whatever um you know there's always
something written and read when you have
a quest the oh really yeah the writing
and red is always the goal where you got
to go oh oh and I just follow that
direction yeah I see I am an experienced
uh traveler and Warrior so I know these
things please feel free to rely on me
little cat so nice I'm so lucky not my
first Adventure I must say and certainly
not my last she's experienced indeed
allora okay uh I from here
oh yeah he's pretty far maybe get on
yeah we can go for a little Adventure
that's cool yippe you yeah let's go with
the
horse wow wow it's nice wow wow what are
these mountains look at that it's such
such a big map that's amazing what this
just the
beginning
bad oh I think yeah we reached
it oh yeah is this one oh okay so hello
I'm going to read for you now okay read
hello you arrived we have been expecting
you our initial for for for a have
determined that the portal into the
ruins is yet sealed with no way to enter
the ruins we are at L at a loss for how
to proceed same some have reported
hearing a strange voice
but we know not what to make of it the
voice seem to be saying the souls on of
stains open the
way what might what they attacking us
while we're eaing it's not
safe don't worry keep on reading keep on
reading okay okay
oh I cannot read anymore yeah why it's
skipped oh water a coincident skiper
skiper again I'm duing I'm not Jing I'm
serious wait was the last sentence what
might have mean by that that was the end
no worries yeah okay slay 10 stains
let's do this let's do this let's go I
wonder when we're in the party it should
normally count each stain like for both
of us
right okay let's see well let's say one
out of 10 go oh here you cannot proceed
yet oh ow they're so aggressive I need
my
sword you have a sword yeah what's your
weapon actually oh um real weap weap
this one yeah use that one it's stronger
the Perfection
executor no the perfect exe
execution
executor yeah the perfect
executor nice
I kill pork because we need food as well
oh yeah careful I I don't even know how
to use my some cuz like usually don't
you have to uh press right click in
Minecraft when you want to use your
Shield it doesn't seem to work I'm going
to provide food
now oh provide food huh yeah make food
because make food I actually we have 63
bread so I don't 63 bread don't you have
have so
much 60 yeah wait when did we get that
must be a reward a quest
reward is it auto blocking I
wonder not
sure also is there like a I didn't see
like anything that says how many we have
so
far I guess one two free yeah it doesn't
says but I think we can just go check M
yeah let's see it will say once we have
all 10 of them I think oh yeah probably
says that it's complete is this a is
this what they call a
mess that's a messa
[Music]
biomi where are the STS really we're
done oh cuz I is that why they stopped
spawning nah there's another one
there thank you guys we can't wait to
play again or I mean to fight together
again are you leaving my
wife we miss we must
away yes we have be safe who got the
fireball man it is me the Phoenix of the
fires and the oranges hello lady of
water Lady of water I can put out your
flame in an instant try it then put out
my flame you're on cool down yes I am I
know it because will not stop me good
luck have fun at least I can swim unlike
you you wouldn't know a thing you w know
anything about that about
me all right okay I don't know but I
have a feeling I will know well how
about you prove to me whether or not you
can swim there's water right over there
in this wonderful wonderful world me
around you're gorgeous over here
Shar get in there yum there's a diamond
how about you go get that
diamond would you like a diamond have
you have you done with the quest and if
I sink what will come of it oh I shall
save you by then because I am a
hero go on go on do not be scared she's
walking the I'm in the L scar we're both
sing I'm
sing Oh this is nice so try
swimming what did you do to her I I
guess I accidentally kind of uh killed
her in indirectly um but
like why um
well what guil do you belong to traveler
I that is none of your business um cat
what Guild are you part of no don't
don't tell her don't tell her I am
everyone was she just like role playing
really hard why did she
[Laughter]
drown where's my sorry uh sorry kitty
cat uh da yeah um we're done with the
quest right yeah we're done with the
quest now it says investigate the underw
dungeon don't wait it still says slay 10
stains for me honestly okay let's let's
do more
then okay okay okay okay okay cuz I
maybe you got 10 but I didn't and so it
really counts for usually I can help
Okay I was meant to save her how would I
have saved
[Applause]
her it's okay she died at my hands it is
my
fault the
diamonds we're just looking too nice
go this really feels like an MPG right
now feel like we're beginning area yeah
with all the weak
mobs so many
strangers stranger
danger can we get
ore I guess we already could if did do
you have a stone
pickaxe uh yeah yes I do ooh well
try go for
it what I got it it didn't give me ore
maybe I need the iron
one wait maybe I did get 10 wait okay
let me finish this
one are you done we got to investigate
the underw D I guess I'm probably done
why is Iris still listenting a party oh
true didn't she leave the party she's
still written on the party list she
should leave the
party well pastas has nothing to say to
me it
seems will you just like talk to this
guy again and he said Quest complete or
what there he is has
toy cat what the heck what the heck we
found you why didn't you answer your
phone I was so worried we on the
phone why you on the phone you guys have
been on the phone enre because sometimes
we're not next to each
other I Tri call you I love how we we
thought like all righty we got to talk
to you our for determin that the portal
has been yet to be sealed this I you
muted
again no I was muted again
I don't know
why anyway I was saying um when I was
done with the quest it appeared on the
bottom left the the text saying oh
complete this Quest yeah okay it still
doesn't say it for me so maybe I have
like nine out of 10 let's let's try
again then kill people we're going to
kill people
now well they're not people B I'm sorry
I was muted by a mistake it's okay have
you completed the quest
yeah we we're doing the one with K now
and then we go to the dungeon are we
going to go together yeah we got to kill
stuff too wait we can we can leave the
private call and then maybe have a party
call oh maybe how do we do that I don't
know oh oh I I left now
okay how do I saw that
before uh how to make
how to make group I don't
know from ah from the
phone
ah wait wait I'll get to it I'll get to
it I'm in to call of myself
now it still says that is no do you hear
me wait how do I how do I get her
I don't know ah I don't know how to make
a party call with all of us okay we can
I can make a party call one sec okay I
think I think you guys may need to
accept I'm I'm calling you
guys I'm not getting any call M Weird Al
I still maybe it doesn't
work
H we are in a party though yeah oh well
how come I still hav't I'd certainly
have killed 10 by
now try to talk to this dude use regular
sword I don't think it'll make a
difference I know he doesn't really do
anything doesn't says anything no maybe
don't try to don't don't kill my kill
but I've been killing them without the
sword too so with my other sword too
this minimum
10 but yeah maybe somebody did steal my
kills I don't
know but I
don't ah finally okay yeah I think there
is a kill stealing yeah yeah seems like
it for
quests um CP this be what the voice
meant by The Souls of stains open way
obtain under the world key oh that car
Kelly dungeon perhaps this key is What
will open the portal into the ruins you
ought to take it with you hero we shall
secure the surroundings that you may
proceed undisturbed Brave hero the
secrets of the ruins await
yippee I got it I got it did you do it I
got the quest finished yeah
the reason was just because um like I
probably killed way more than 10 but
like you participated in some of the
kills so that made it like your kill and
not my kill a it didn't count together
weird no it doesn't my vision I see okay
good to
know I wonder I need to ask Steph like
if uh if the stats of my sword are
better than a basic sword I would hope
so I'm excited for the dungeon actually
yeah the dungeon we're dungeoning now
yeah next is dungeon
here when when you have the the quest
finished yeah let's go okay hey you you
have you all proceeded in the quest
right yeah yeah you were fast say just
to double check it says investigate the
underworld dungeon right yeah okay okay
good we can go then let's
go this
okay let's go oh it's actually right
there huh okay yeah let's go
woo battle chist
[Music]
Yi wa let's go time to fight time to
fight are we ready yeah let's go we're
ready we're
ready shall we
horse it up oh ah is that another
teleportation
thingy oh woo ready to enter the dungeon
and to jungeon ready yeah ready I'm
ready wait oh wait enter oh ready ready
yeah are we clicking ready I clicked
ready I'm I'm click I clicked ready okay
standing by to enter dungeon okay oh
enter dungeon no player standing by what
do we just click enter now um no player
standby it says no player standing by
though I think could it be uh L can you
like in your party settings cuz you're
the party leader can you kick Iris wait
wait you IR wa click out and then go
back in cuz then it says that I'm
waiting now oh wait wait
wait wait I click
what do you see it
now wait no I said how do I get
back how do you know how do you do that
ready
well well I just walk back and then walk
closer to
it it says no player standing by um wait
do you want to disband the party yeah is
it cuz iris is in it I think it's
because iris is in it so and then we can
remake the party Iris
Iris how do you just B the party now oh
right click
and
then
uh invite fail to invite wait you kicked
B from the party yeah I'm out oh oh I
see I see I see I see I see I'm out I
got kicked okay now I'm out as well all
right let's make a new party
yeah party weite you guys yeah we're I
see your party says l and m think Bae
needs an invite yep I'm in
you in wait hold
on the party or ready to oh I'm in the
party Okay
we okay hello y let's TR wa this is one
out of one is that okay is that
okay oh no now it's working oh now it's
working yeah I'm ready too ready ready M
press ready press ready ready it looks
like you didn't press ready
yet it SS that I did though like what no
uh three hasn't pressed ready
yet three has gone three
oh where is
it where' she go where did she go
mysterious uh three oh oh did she like
fall for the world or something oh maybe
three what happened three talk to
me tree come
back count on the
tree she's entered the dungeon what what
leave it she ented Alone by accident I
guess okay I'm going to going to go now
are we going are we are we entering hold
on hold on hold on can you not exit the
dungeon do you guys even hear her cuz I
don't hear her oh I'm I'm calling her
I'm calling
her
uh maybe do you respawn back at the when
people talk to themselves because they
have those air air buds in their ears
and you don't realize they're on a
[Music]
call we kicked you already Iris are we
going to wait
do I have caps lock on I can't
tell huh I think I do yeah it's probably
glitching the party the party stuff is
glitching all
right confusion has entered the chat
what we doing are we waiting for tree
yes okay
oh yes there she is it is nice to see
you once
again hello hello we have missed you
yeah we missed you very much seems like
it I missed all of you too now how do we
go about this you always in a party you
need to be ready I was ready I was not
right now but hold on hold on don't
click the sword there we go yay yeah
ready we're ready
oh my go I'm not alone this time
[Music]
y let's explore don't ask why but go
here to this door the Underworld the
domain of boundless oppressive Darkness
as feed it is unavoidable it holds the
final resting place for every creature
that walks the Earth yet even in this
realm of the Dead those are who live and
call it home oh my this feels like it
was written by the hands of De oh my
goodness what we going to do um we must
explore orange
juice yummy orange juice I want a sippy
I don't think that's orange juice um
which way supposed to go maybe we go I
know you really like the fire C but
maybe this is not the kind of fire you
like I like any kind of fire you can do
it there's a crystal o hard to reach oh
there's a whole castle over there oh
dang I don't know how do we get to this
m fly have you tried flying before I
have not tried flying can we fly M I
usually can but it seems now I've been
restricted maybe we have to go a
different way
yeah but this all looks like
Islands oh parkour parkour oh oh there's
one over here here ooh over here par
parkour oh I see ah you teleport from
Stone to
Stone probably but we lost the
others that's okay we're too good yeah
new checkpoint oh checkpoint so if we
die we spawn here I think so very nice
very convenient let's go this way okay
parkour parkour wo no don't have parkour
do you sometimes dream about
flying someone's calling me sorry the
voice is what we're here we're over here
over here I really wanted to know the
answer over here over
here over here over here is always a
good way to let people know where you
are exactly over here yeah let's get
ahead of them let's get ahead of them
okay run run run away
where's the next
checkpoint
[Music]
um
okay nice nice okay but from here
honestly I'm not sure I think where are
we going
here are we just exploring if we brought
our own blocks I wonder can we place
them uh we can try
I have no I
can't that would be
cheating this is giving me high blood
pressure
checkpoint
checkpoint yes I I'm not sure where
we're supposed to go from here perhaps
towards that castle was that that would
be that would be a marvelous idea so I'm
going to
find cannot right no hope I don't die
okay
easy jump here
ow Dam
too yeah careful
careful careful oh I messed
up no
no
cleop pH on the checkpoint it's okay
that's true that's true oh okay yeah
it's here it's here it's okay it's okay
oh thank
goodness I was so worried that I have
lost you before I heard the answer to
the dream question the dream what was
the dream question have you ever uh
dream about
flying I don't I wish I did I don't
maybe try flapping your arms when you as
I fall asleep yeah dream flapping in my
dreams I'm dream fling all these nights
it's you sleep flopping dream dream
dream dream dream dream iot song go s
that sounds like a song I should release
maybe I might release some music dream
dream that's not how it goes no someone
from the Lava Girl
shk checkpoint
oopsie has it been checked no not again
not no it was a shortcut
look let's
go okay let's go over
here kitty cat kitty cat come
on okay here we
[Music]
go can you girls be
careful
no
okay no no what why is it impossible to
jump here oh okay you can do it you can
do
it Amber Corin must
Prevail yeah let's
[Music]
go all right how do he go
up side no no they went left side
no help wait for us I see kitty cat come
up here again from the side from
behind and then jump jump and then jump
jump jump
yes
smart Dam
it checkpoint
checkpoint you go first
okay easy easy oh there's a
castle a
nice a huh which Disney Princess does
this Castle belong to
huh evil one
[Music]
coming hello yeah you you figured out
the strap I what it's a group it's a
group checkpoint let's
go la just die just fall down
yourself just die jump I don't think she
can hear us to call her real
quick she can also try proving her
skill just jump into the lava can your
phone jump into the
lava
jump oh jump further
yeah there we
go so the orange juice is safe after all
everybody all right let's go let's
go oh
oh oh
yeah let's go wow wow those are easy oh
my oh my I just realized weren we told
to go and like not just our group
dungeons where we supp to go with like
two
groups no no they only said like uh
there's a maxim how many groups can be
in the dungeon at the same
time yeah we don't need anybody
else yeah yeah of the orange
[Music]
yes you don't like the I wanted
something it was too quiet for
me next time I'll have something more
fitting to each other because we're
going to get lost in this D yeah
wait what is this we found something
what checko oh I got a triangle someone
got I got a triangle oh we can take it
wa why how did you take it oh you filled
it up or I I think we I think the
zombies are going to drop those so we
got a few more so we need to find a star
and a circle he has he he has he
they let's go we got the far I got the
immediately brought it to us
okay I have the circle I have I'm trying
to how do I put the circle in how do I
put the circle in
y's wait only had several
[Music]
circles no yeah make sure to stay
fed remember to eat yes oopsy oopsie you
guys want to try this out don't you
looks pretty sick I'm hungry
wa another life expired leaving behind a
tiny flickering light a soul
representing both a legacy and an ending
I read for us read for us the veiled
figure cradled it in her hands and with
a hint of melancholy she whispered is
this the right thing to do it's if you
need to ask it's never the right thing
to do
okay let's proceed
[Music]
those windows are sick
amber
amber wao there's so many stairs I don't
I don't like there so many why are there
so many stairs I know my
foot what is that this what do this mean
is this a a
puzzle time I'm going to be absolutely
useless all right
um what what change is
it I don't know I just touching it how
what are you are you right clicking it
oh okay okay well uh maybe each each
person takes charge of one side or so
yeah wa are we supposed to put all the
lights onto onto the front face
maybe I think you just want the whole
thing to yeah I think all of them have
to light up I see I I love these kind of
riddles I ha riddles I hate them too is
this okay hey oh oh wait mine was full
for a moment yeah it's a each each side
affects the other side like it's not
just one face ah I
see um wait hold
on that's we should just observe for a
minute I'm not sure if this might not
actually be the one riddle to stop every
Guild from
proceeding we can do it I believe this
might be too difficult for all is a
distraction that would be funny okay I
really have to go to an idle meeting
it's just not this is probably not the
best
time maybe try to figure out one side I
think I can't change anything
anymore huh did I use up my
tries okay
[Music]
oh I can't do
anything difficult it seems like a good
time is it a good time
I do need to I'm going to go to an idle
meeting and let you guys figure this one
okay I can't I can't oh oh I F I thought
I F I F I just got a little bit
frustrated give me the power to press
the lights what I don't understand the
the way they
change I think it's like it's
um okay
it's
two I'm just going to keep pressing
until something works oh my good oh wait
I think I I think I I understand can
someone go to the other side and follow
my instruction yeah no I can't press
anything uh up on the top top top top
left top left click on the top
left okay nothing happens no it's the
adjacent ones it's the ones next to each
other turn on and off okay I think got
it
oh why can't I I was able to click it
before what I'm holding bread now maybe
it's better like if two people just do
that cuz maybe like look can cord better
I'm not sure oh I have also lost the
ability you're on your r
no May if I go kill
myself are we stuck here
wait I think we're stuck
[Music]
no what's the is that counted as a
checkpoint I
[Music]
wonder
bye oh wait cool
ah ah it hurts it hurts so much ah just
another day in the Phoenix
life Which
Way ah that way
right can I get my horse in here no it's
that way though maybe now I can press
the buttons
again I want to click things endlessly
mindlessly without doing anything
helpful hello I'm backe I'm trying to I
I I try to regain oh no it still doesn't
work still can't press it I I am trying
you're doing great I'm
trying okay this
one do you have any kind of strategy Lou
no I'm just like trying to understand
the Potter that's how I would do it
honestly
so if you have any suggestion you're
doing
great no they can't use it anymore
either so it's not just me we have to
make just one
online
or okay one side is light oh
nice okay what I hope it stays like that
I hope it stays like that
yeah looking good though looking good
looking
good I know if it
changes uh left side is still safe and
full okay okay let's what's going we're
still at it and L is the only one able
to press
things what oh yeah you want to probably
keep those the way they are on the left
side we've got one face down we just
need the other two to
go two other three yeah I feel like just
indiscriminately pressing them without
communicating
is what do you mean that sounds
amazing oh did it it's working
okay uh one sec this is just like one of
these I'm so come on Kitty one of
them doing great
[Music]
Kitty I'm trying to
understand oh no we side no wait it's
it's changing on itself is there any
other groups who have solved this so far
maybe this is the end of all of us maybe
this is where this project will
end I don't know I feel like everybody
working on one side maybe it doesn't
work oh Scarlet's group
did how did they do it send
help send
help maybe they deact like the deps
deactivated our powers so that only one
person can work it wonder how the
other's going cuz otherwise it's too
chaotic I wonder yeah one group
apparently solved it so far oh
wow
what we can do it well I wish we could
press it yes not you guys can't press
it I didn't touch it was like a specific
way to make it I'm not sure another
group made it apparent
no oh there should be a a reset button
do you mean there really is one or are
you just saying that I mean
button I don't think there is
one okay try to do the same pattern at
the opposite yeah let's try actually can
you tell me actually okay let me see we
probably need to face the
[Music]
other sorry this is like so on
you you can do it it's okay okay let me
check this poter actually let's try to
understand the logic of a puzzle like
this so I mean there's like I don't know
if there's a simpler way of just like
being like Oh you clicking see oh you're
clicking again okay you can click then
okay let's do together I can click yeah
yeah let's do
together oh I can't cck almost almost
almost interesting you I can't cck
anymore yeah it looks
good yeah looks
good okay
no okay now I I I got an idea
oops she can do
it h adjacent blocks adjacent
blocks keep on
clicking keep on pawing at it oh nice
nice nice you got this one oh wait H you
had this size
oh how that works I really don't get the
logic of this
game it's just if you wait so now this
starts wait wait wait don't
do one side out a time because you can
if you I don't know how to explain this
I don't understand why you're not able
to click it though maybe it's a bag
there's no way that it's a been clicking
it the most yeah yeah probably a bag but
it's probably better than all four of us
doing it at the same time so that is
yeah but the way to do it is like you
just keep track of like what each like
when you the block what it
fills but you just got to be mindful of
the ones that are on the side cuz it'll
affect the ones a different face
yeah so like careful touch like so
here's
good this is probably good but it's like
you can't can't touch these oh oh there
you go there you
go yeah yeah pretty much there we
go all right you're doing great
yeah oh looks good
[Music]
something like
that mental support you're you're very
close you're doing doing so
[Music]
good oh there we goce nice nice
nice
MP
nice let
go let's clear this
dungeon she did it
with those God eyes
MVP the
goat the goat
cat to be useful
again
sington it's so dark on my screen on
screen guys can you
see that was funny
oh
my the bridge G no go should I don't
know if we should have gone this is he
getting rid of the whole
bridge I I I that might be what he's
doing way no no no no no
no what a checkpoint oh this is a new
checkpoint okay scripted supposed to
happen sced death fly you fool okay what
is this don't eat it it's a mushroom um
um um um
they're just staring at the mushroom
meanwhile
decoration oh yeah I know what to do I
know what to do what what you do oh wait
someone someone received bone
meal
yeah Dr
it and then more we need more
the more B meal can we make it
bigger but wa this is hard to ascend can
we come here oh come here gu on this
altar beautiful
skeletons okay okay you supposed to this
becoming stairs clb
mm kill him on the thingy kill him on
the thingy nice nice nice nice nice nice
I don't know
I got
you you nice W it's so big now oh it's
like spawning the the
the what do you call it
again W this is so cool
fire fire fire get them get them to die
like on the tree can we go now if you
can I can we maybe we can yeah maybe
let's try oh I think we might be able to
ascend there's a button here ow how do
you climb there's a button on the
tree just press press space jump into
it then I oh there's several
buttons well I guess they don't do
anything
no I think these might just be stairs oh
there you
go are you going up
yeah but actually we might oh no it's
already reaching the top I can see from
here are you yes it's reaching the top
both sides actually I can't get it oh I
got
here don't know which side we should
go oh this side
okay maybe it's a checkpoint is there a
checkpoint
here close and first
but is that what's over there is that
like a shortcut or like a secret
treasure up
there I kind of want to
know what are they doing where are they
over there go down there
that come kitty kitty oh the kitty is
going to get stuck on top of the tree oh
no we need the
firefighters I am I I am a firefighter
right come up here hello I'm waiting for
you okay I am awaiting then up here up
here oh I jump on the on the yeah that
one first on the side yeah okay I'll
catch
you thank
you now two
more I'm a fire starter mhm oh my
goodness oh okay yeah we got to do it
again I see let's St killing skeletons
first then okay meow meow meow come here
skeleton come
here who's a good skeleton
nice oh
who oh no think do we want them to die
on on here
so you made
it
welcome oh oh more okay follow me hello
over here
here I feel like maybe wouldn't we only
need one of the trees to grow why is
there two
platforms where did my oh my is the
candle C come
here oh I saw her somewhere
there oh
I you have to kill them on the thing
yeah I
see oh oh she's
coming I'm coming oh there you go yeah
jump on that one in front of you and
then to the
side over
there and then here I'll catch you
kitty I thought I had to call the fire
fighters I thought you would get stuck
in the
tree but we have more trees now oh oh my
God not enough though not enough is
there only one skeleton at a time this
is pretty difficult dungeon wait wait I
has to die Thee
[Music]
the this one oh he's following come
here trap him oh wait wait wait wait
wait don't kill a he's going to kill me
wait doesn't drop the bone meal hey he's
going to kill me no no it's a DI tree
he's going to kill me oh okay oh really
good come here come
here
yeah another one and another one here
come here careful where did she spawn I
[Music]
wonder a bit more over here come over
here no yeah that's okay we'll get more
it's okay no you can't collect it it has
to be on the on the tree s the tree yeah
yeah yeah okay okay I'm going to
woohoo come here come here good oh what
is that oh you you dice yeah playing
guys is that
enough I looks almost enough maybe for
safety one more maybe a few more one
more okay okay okay maybe on the on the
left side
I'll kill
you don't kill me don't kill me there
you go okay uh seems like fully grown at
this point then cuz it didn't do the
sparkle
thing I'll give it a
try is mum okay or as they call her
[Music]
free
ah uh this is not the way oh yes this is
the way
parkour tree
parkour I still wonder about the other
one like if I went to the Top If I cuz
why else would it grow that
high is it did they think of something
like that like
Treasures I want to check it
out like you know in RPG said there's
one main way and there's a different way
always where there's like a treasure CH
of items I want to check they can you
know proceed if they want and um mum is
not here yet
anyway ow I should have known that that
would happen oh but oh this is that's
exactly where I wanted to go anyway a
shortcut shortcut what if M wouldn't she
also spawn here why did I not see her
again all right all right all right
let's get to the top
to over there right
yeah let's see if it's possible it looks
like there's a platform there
so they'll call me when they need me
right they'll call me for sure maybe
[Music]
wasn't I there before
no or was
[Music]
I how did
I get
there okay where over here so I could go
there again
oh ah m is up there okay well don't
worry I'll get us some really uh big
treasure for sure
right right
follow the
buttons oh is that what those are
for oh that's a little hint or what okay
[Music]
well
okay you can do dungeons alone actually
and like redo them so maybe I'll do that
uh eventually and see if there was a
treasure there because it will not leave
me in peace
yes I will not be able to forget
that I feel like this just not taking me
down or should I go this way I'm hearing
voices
again I don't know I'm just going down
now maybe there's multiple paths it
seems as if there is one path and that
is marked by the buttons ladies but
there's multiple paths for the
buttons then choose the one that feels
best whichever she speaks to you yes is
only up really the
way this like this way that way that
looks too far though button
before okay now these patterns are
confusing me it's hard to like what I
mean right the tree patterns got it you
have to go down to go up
oh what oh she's being called I'm scared
I'm going to miss this oh checkpoint oh
we can just die now but no that's lame
that feels lame I want to figure it
out oh there we go you guys made me feel
like I was being stupid for thinking you
got to go down a little bit oh no that
wasn't so hard at
all next part okay I'm going to read
this you read bye yeah I
read to the
den den of the
underw the
light emanated by S was vetal vit
vital vital you got this you got this
you're doing so
well okay now I cannot read anymore for
some
reason H I cannot read anymore doesn't
you clicked on next page it doesn't work
no it doesn't
work I don't know can be the other the
other ESL will
continue they needed it to survive in
this ever cold and dark environment yet
among them there was a heretic who
called their Customs into question do we
really need to take others lives to
sustain our own sustain wink no there
has to be another way and so she stepped
into the plane above plane oh plane
airplane which plane This
Plane
surely is the last
[Music]
your power of Revelation has grown
stronger what I didn't fight a boss
fight or anything it's not over right I
want to fight that big
skull you've recovered a portion of your
memories wait is do we is it over
already where's the boss fight do we get
the cut scene there's a cut
scene pick click the oh oh okay okay
okay yeah yeah yeah yeah they actually
they prepared this on uh uh on on a
YouTube link but we said can you just
send us the video so we can put it into
OBS uh and yeah they have done so so let
me put it into OBS so all of these
dungeons they end with a video it
seemed why no boss though why no
boss okay it might be wait I'll put it
in and stop it for a moment ah ah ah
okay T and then let me put myself behind
they're probably going to upload this I
feel like on YouTube too like publicly I
mean okay and then let me change the
audio Source thingy to
monitor
only that should be good okay all right
starting to watch
[Music]
equ okay
that pretty lady job is to lives and
take their
souls that's how it's always been the
spirits of the underworld need their
sustenance but I keep
wondering oh pants those look
familiar from a
game
oh basketball she balling
baby she baby is this the right thing to
do no no no it's not stop Kelly Stop
raping my
soul she in a club she clubbing it
up what's going on
oh Soul energy look at that
they're sweaty turn out we can also use
people's
emotion we don't need their souls at all
H Return To Die Duty Reaper Reapers
should help the
living not take away their future if the
others can't accept that that's their
loss six s swinging oh I want to see her
weapon in
Minecraft oh I'll do things my way
hell yeah
Callie
oh very
cool it seems as if we will all get
something like this
haha isn't that
nice that so cool slay girl let's
go I mean I'm not sure what the
conclusion of that was but that was so
really
cool basically like what so she's a
Reaper and then it's just you know her
story hello M she's a Reaper and she
decided well this is kind of I don't
know depressing so let me get this Soul
energy in a different way because you
don't need to reap their souls to get
Soul energy you can just um be fandy
with people and uh and get their energy
by having them be happy for emotions
yeah emotions right emotions give energy
too and that's all she really so she
says oh [\h__\h] it I'm not going to reap
Souls anymore I'm just going to yeah rap
not reap
genius I've done
it oh have you done it I've watched it
yes oh my goodness have they watched it
too I think they're watching done I'm
done you're done okay M doesn't seem
done then three is watching it probably
at this how we speak
okay it was funny is it first time you
saw it right yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah it
was so cool the memories that they they
told us about that lady didn't we see
her already running around in the
actually I haven't talked to her looks
who was that oh my go was like slaying
oh my goodness I'm her fan now when I
see her again I must talk to her yeah I
want to meet her too we've done the
first dungeon let's go I'm so happy
Yoo good job good job everybody but this
so good
actually how do we return is it is that
light up ahead where the Moon is I'm
going to return by
leaving I
think are what the heck
hello oh pleasure to see are you leaving
or are you
incoming we are
incoming many people death awaits you
this isn't the right way it's not the
right way you have to off this Cliff yes
death awaits you otherwise you have to
pay your taxes yeah down
there
promise as a member of the ceran cup I
trust
easily
the you don't want to
we don't want that death you want this
death there's a move move further move
further follow the light I think it
means you're not ready I can't jump oh
oh okay allowing me to she's not ready
all right then you were
pranked oh oh my weapon is so cool
actually
nothing all right sorry we're pranking
you we don't want guild war I regret to
say that the B may be crashing all right
is everyone so isra
Isen you want to head back's go yeah
let's head back wait whereit is the cat
wait kitty cat and kitty
cat we are uh turning back now okay I
come bye-bye orange child I hope to meet
you again yes
tashii close
enough I shall meet you again uh uh past
the rainbows of Greater uh Beyond
beautifuls uh
yes what is that
hello hello let's go I'm going to put
I'm trying to put music music hold yeah
yeah yeah yeah okay done there you go
y
Yi
hello oh can I get a
signature can I open we saw you in a
vision me alone I just want to go in the
dungeon with my friends please explain
the vision what does it mean talking
about have you seen it
already no I don't talking about I just
want I just want to go into the
some questions I'm sure once you see it
you will understand Big Ups Liz I I have
I I have
questions hey what are you guys doing to
my honor why does why does the The Quon
lady sound like she's in toilet
again
yeah that's right I'm in the toilet so
it's just her state of life now
hello what's your name are you also a
puppy I am not a puppy oh she got she
went in oh I am a big cat very one of
those dangerous one she says uh her
cat's phrase is RA
XD I'm not
inil all right I I'm a I'm a big cat
sorry a big cat yeah bye well then make
a big cat noise then K Kitty we're
leaving of the
dungeon you have lost someone
too what are those
[Music]
sounds
yes was interesting sounds you were
making oh no that's my horse a your
horse excuse Mo for misunderstanding
yeah I don't I don't speak hor have you
given back your quest already I suppose
not what have you back
uh oh oh damn it I
H damn
it I understand
now wasn't
I thought you would do it like cuz you
know I thought you would do it there in
the city but okay makes
sense
can out of this um do you have to talk
to the J yeah I just realized yeah what
is it oh it's in the other
oh oh oh wait no no no no this is not
the right guy no no no wa it's the Guild
Master so okay we have to go into the
city never mind into the city okay I'll
wait till the entrance bye I did have to
write idea yeah okay
bye-bye oh man I wish you would have
done the thing where you like stay on
call Forever you say bye and you just
like
stay oh I caught up I caught up oh I see
I see I yippe
what did you say what that hat what did
you say what you say hello ladies what
is that hat hello
greetings are you a wizard I am the
appointed
point point get it are you now of the
skylet
[Music]
wand I
speak we had a side quest and she took
over leader of our Guild oh cool
it looks like you're
wearing it looks like you're wearing
like a red velvet cake on your head a
big one is your name blue
creature it um
um I don't know the leader she forgot
still don't
know valid hey you aren't you the one
that hit me with your horse oh my
godes and you are the one that drowned
this no no no what oh no I already
forgot that no it seems like she forgot
that too though generally um wait what
it say I can't I can't read that my
heart's on the way that's where the
dungeon is though
no that's I guess the name of the quest
no is that m
she doesn't go by that name here it
seems
but yes oh they're in
here hi
hi oh hi all right which one is it the
middle one
right
yes
awesome oh yeah you
read which one is she
uh it went away I didn't
oh I see you think the ruins held such
Secrets a crystal deep within that when
touched returned a fragment of your
memories to you that's how you are
reading that um character the power of
Revelation Al be it at only a fraction
of its potential mhm that your summoning
and the discovery of these ruins should
coincide so closely there must be some
connection between the ruins and the
power of Revelation oh Brave hero seek
rubius The Guild Master the Scarlet hand
wand
what okay it Guild has also been
searching for strange ruins in the lands
of theol
phaps can't take them seriously when
they say mayhaps they discovered
something I don't know what he said well
I like that word scarlet W gild master
all right sounds good SC well go to Ru
rubius
yes up
there what's up dog what where'd she
go did she find a more direct route
think this is it
though yeah oh R what's up oh where how
where is
she all right I'll talk to this one hey
he's wearing the same hat as that shark
girl that I drowned
there she is oh my gosh you're so fast
yeah it's the red velvet cake
people oh can you can you
yes oh good day to you hero returned
from investigating those ruins are you
I've gotten the gist from V's more or
less H yes I now sense within you a
trace of the power of Revelation
fascinating
most go ahead go ahead go ahead Most
Fascinating one hyp osiz that those
runes are the key to unlocking your
powers we of the skullet W have also
been investigating near the plains Irish
super glue fell from a high place and
wouldn't you know it just off the coast
we
ased a light with a striking resemblance
to Revelation her blood flame was doomed
to fall good hero would you be willing
to travel to the coast and Aid in our
efforts there or is that where like
we'll see at contest I don't
know me members of our Guild are already
there hard at work I'm quite sure they
will appreciate your assistance good
luck and Excel all sounds like a spell
someone would
cast
Okay and speak to the coron of the
Scarlet how long is get tired yeah I
mean I think maybe that's just like the
continuation of the main quest and it
just goes on forever forever until like
very
end dear not sure and did the did the
did the uh I don't know if she has a
different name uh the the red one did
she like leave yeah I think she did oh
okay so it's just uh us and the lost
kitten now where' she go I got to head
off though I'm I still got sick brains
no worries you made it far traveler I
hope our Guild will find much success in
the future
if there's anything I may help you with
or be assistance of uh let me know at
any time we'll do into you
Smooch smooched your horse ah my horse
of course yes my horse only I see you
have an interest in
horses no that's not what that means but
I it's
okay comrad thank you again goodbye
Cleopatra goodbye
goodbye farewell
farewell um the only Point how do I
should I try to
call that's the first time I'm doing
that where's my cat where are you
cat
cat what are you
doing I just saw m yeah no she's leaving
oh there you are there she
is I was talking the phone sorry
okay take her I go yeah goodbye lost k y
I need to talk to the Scarlet one master
yeah this one in uh this Rubio guy I
think here this one talk to him talk to
him talk to
him talk to him do it do it okay go to
the C and speak
to I saw how you ski a skipper through
all of
that all right wait one second now let
me check my
schedule
where okay okay okay
okay I can still like continue with you
for a
while you hearing me K kitty cat be
muted probably no why why you keep on
doing that I hate
myself it's okay I love you I love you
too okay let's go uh go to the coast and
speak to Corin right yes let's go Corin
wait this is so interesting cuz like um
there's oh wait why I getting muted
because I press M because the map ah
that makes
sense I'm thinking of like
House of the Dragons It's like automatic
because every time I think the m is the
map because M and
yeah true okay well I shall lead you I
shall lead the
way wait wait actually cuz this one has
is proximity shall we just be on a
call then then it's not proximity then I
can still hear you yeah let's go okay
let's
go let's go what a great connection this
phone has yeah there's a good internet
connection in this
world the coast I wonder what awaits us
over there
mm this is such a big Lively City it's
so beautiful I really like it it's so
detailed and everything is so cute
crazy okay details you went through
yeah
I'm okay done oh oh there we
go okay should be this way but it's
probably really far yeah let's go Little
Pigs these pigs are so tiny cute he do
they drop meat have you tried killing
the animals yeah yeah they drop meat oh
you can also cook the meat oh cook the
meat ah I understand make it the pasta H
yeah
yeah I sent um okay little little bit
off role play I sent ra oh a video wait
this is a invisible wall I sent l a
video
ah oh I think I guess we teleport
through here oh did you
teleport ah yes you did let's go amazing
yeah I sent her a video uh you know
this's is like really cheap Italian
chain Family Restaurant in Japan called
CIA and uh yeah Japanese people love it
I love it too but like it's obviously
not very authentically
Italian um but like there's this video
of like an Italian relatively young guy
he brings his like father or grandfather
or so to CIA so they're both Italian and
they're testing like all the food there
and he's like really critical at first
but he ends up actually quite enjoying
it especially for the price value
right yeah like I'll be honest I think
the pasta was pretty unedible for me
oh but everything else was okay the
pizza is fine right the pizza I mean for
its price it's obviously not it's not
like the the good Italian pizza of
course
yeah I mean it's cool that a pizza in
the first place well I mean it's still a
pizza I mean I don't know I don't Co
that like pizza it's like I was like n
yeah okay but the Italian dude he kind
of in the end like supported SI so liked
it I me H I've been there just once oh
only once yeah only once I tried like
one type of pasta so maybe I'll try
again we can go together and we eat
together yeah yeah I think that there's
a dessert that I really like it's um I
think what's it
called uh is it panakot no it's like the
the pizza bread um fried kind of and
then top with the cinnamon and with a
vanilla ice cream M oh yeah warm thing
it's so good the cinnamon oh my
God uh I do have a feeling that this
will lead us to the next dungeon
possibly in that case like we wouldn't
be able to proceed anyway um but let's
see where it leads us do you want to
read what he says yeah uh I
already Skipper
Skipper I know I was just reading just
reading by the way we can also have uh
we also have a lot of side quests by the
way yeah if this leads us to the main
like the next dungeon we can we should
do a side quest instead we can do the
Side Glass
oh so
oh should
we yeah let's do the side quest supplies
wanted food but I don't actually
understand how to check the side quest
in this I still have a side quest open
who's interested in
construction but yeah I also don't know
how to is there maybe in
here maybe I'm not sure ah if you open
the book in your inventory on page two
it says check your currently active side
quests click here to
check oh speak to the Mason at the
construction
area
wow okay let's do that then okay uh
Mason to okay Ah that's why on the map
the whole time I have the Mason in green
marked okay let's let's go to the yeah
all right the rest of of our Guild is
offline so we shall start constructing
let's
go but I'm probably not like going to be
here much longer maybe this Quest and
then I might also go I don't know yeah
no worries it's fine before before this
I think I did like 10 hour stream so oh
oh yeah I saw I saw like you were
playing um the clono and then you like
continued with normal Minecraft what the
hell I was like why is she playing
Minecraft now she's literally going to
be playing Minecraft like the next day
like what I was I was locked in I was
trying to play Locked In yeah are you
okay I'm fine honestly what were you
doing in the other Minecraft I was just
building a house for GT GT GT yeah GT GT
morning ah
gy g g
wait sorry little bit
wrong yeah also like um I'm I'm very
very very very jetl oh so I couldn't
sleep all right you're back in the other
side of the world yeah yeah how was it
how was your trip oh it was the worst
trip I've ever
had what what happened yeah everything
that could possibly happen it happened
yeah so wait tell me more about it after
we talk to this guy what why you this
corn of the scalet one I'm talking to
Mason you can build a a house a store
room or whatever else suits your fancy
as long as you don't go out of bounds
what each Guild has an assigned plot and
you can
must it doesn't talk to you oh H it's
like I'm still in a conversation with
the oh okay whatever that's fine now I
can talk to the Mason okay okay okay
yeah it was still like continuing the
conversation from the previous
NPC
oh okay uh so what you can build a house
a
ah oh so does everybody build here then
yeah so every every Guild has their own
space so we can Guild ah nobody buildt
anything yet huh yeah but this seems to
be our space right the yellow one yeah
the yellow one is our space Oh it's
right here perfect and we have a
construction box so we can already play
something
oh just the blocks to receive oh what is
it like a set of like specific stones
that have a look to
them a certain
style we just have uh
I guess I get the same thing right
oh get
whoa what ambern we got to use something
that's
like uh golden and brown and so on
maybe did you choose some blocks already
no what should I use what maybe the
Terra Cotta or or yeah the bricks yeah
the bricks I was looking at them too I
got the bricks okay okay oh we only got
the bricks oh well okay I mean better
than nothing the thing is the other two
can also still get blocks yeah
no bricks I didn't wait I can probably
abandon the quest and then redo it right
no wait no let me do that I think
there's another like we can just get
more in the future maybe okay yeah the
other two can still we can build the
base the bricks we can make something
really big now and then they can add
like Windows and lights and
everything 120 blocks is actually not
much yeah that's why we need more this
is fine let's start to build here you
want to do that can but can we make
them
smaller no you can make like a small
house only we had a stone cutter okay
well now you seem to have a good eye for
Aesthetics so how big should we make it
first if we're only we have this big
plot but we're starting with small
amount of blocks yeah we serve a small
one we start with a small one it's okay
is there a craft table
[Music]
here uh no but actually your crafting
table is on your inventory I think yeah
but only the small one yeah I can make a
big
one oh I made a big one I wonder if we
can place it here how oh yeah I just
with the
planks oh oh right we can just we can
craft normal
stuff yeah
oh how do you
make
uh I don't think I can do anything with
this you know what I'm going to do
actually I'm going to make some a a
chest m one
second and so we can put the stuff on
our chest and uh I can I can I we can
build something together
yeah what's what's
the H how' you make that wait wait wait
wait wait let me let me cut it one
second okay I have a CD I'm going to put
here slime
ball I'm going to put all the blocks
here here you know what I'm going to do
I'm going to go grab more uh food I'll
be right back oh
okay oh oh yeah isn't it right over
there where we can mine oh no it was
somewhere
else was it
there is
SE I want to look inside this
Arena I'm muted I was music again I keep
I keep pressing M Mama
Mia Mama Mia wait this is
not
whoa whoa did you look inside the arena
already no it looks
crazy really what is it it looks
amazing we can like hold some big Guild
Wars in here PVP PVP I wonder if they're
going we going to have PVP no I don't
think
so or maybe at the very end in the
finale everybody will fight each
other oh that' be cool oh that's where
the am uh the amember no the Jade people
are
standing oh wait I cannot find the exit
I'm
stupid any of the like big uh doors on
the edges of the city probably will lead
you out any of
them let me just
try
Gladiators yeah the light is
beautiful no
nice
yeah I still have some work to do after
this guys that's why I can't can't stay
forever oh it's okay but tomorrow I
think I'm going to stream at the same
time tomorrow is
Monday so yeah I mean for me like well
okay in jst uh like now it's already
Sunday for you I guess it's Saturday
right wait which time on are you if you
can ask wait what what right wait you're
in the same time z i okay we are in the
same
time okay I start at the same time so
yeah okay we can uh we can meet here
again but then for my other days uh like
uh Tuesday and Wednesday I'm I'm going
to not be able to stream don't worry you
know what we're going to do I'm going to
help you with the quest yeah but then
you already then you already know
everything I don't mind really I can
actually like I don't mind I don't mind
I really don't mind I wonder though if
there's anybody else I I feel like if
anybody isn't available on Tuesday
they'll probably just do it on Wednesday
and
then it's okay don't wor don't overthink
about it I just want to have fun and
weang out yeah yeah I'll be so behind on
everything no no no we we we go fast
through everything if anything yeah well
this dungeon was pretty fast so yeah
exactly where did where did you are you
did you find the wood no I'm looking for
the exes still
oh L you keep on getting
lost yeah very bad sense of direction
I'd see okay I found
it good good good good good okay I'm
getting food now let's go
didn't realize that this is what that
was
cool oh they did start building
here the what which one is this green oh
yeah green the green
ones they didn't get really far
[Laughter]
either Callie built that oh Callie's in
green
mm oh
oh oh they're
dying I am building I'm preparing
stuff I want to make a nice house
yeah but
like we need a lot of stuff like if we
want to do something nice I wonder wait
with my
Stones can I make a stone
cutor let's see the
stones my God
annoying all I wonder if even all items
are
unlocked
uh if we can't actually build
[Music]
everything
ah they so strong
um I'm not going to
die are we forced to buy them let's just
look
again sorry I need your ah okay
materials like uh or pickaxes and stuff
we can't build them ourselves we have to
buy them I guess other things may also
be like locked behind yeah we need to
buy
them okay where you can Farm money on
killing monsters like the yeah and
making qu doing quests and doing quests
yes where is the maybe in
here ooh ah
armor oh and the blacksmith okay yeah
yeah yeah yeah uh do you have can I
buy 50 coins Cobblestone free oh I can
buy this ypp we have we have Cobblestone
though get it very easily I know I know
I have still my Cobblestone should I get
a better sword I don't know which one's
better huh should I only be using my
Phoenix sword for like the special
attack and then in between I switch to
this one for example yeah yeah yeah CU
yeah this one has actual stats so oh
oh was I not doing any damage so
far I think we're doing a little bit of
damage anyway but how do I get them to
sell me more do I have to continue their
Quest seems so what is
this oh wait they have
furnaces do they have stone
cutter hey and
oh yeah if you can find a stone cutter
would be nice I have a lot of money
right now there's all kinds of things a
smoker where are you in the shop yeah
well they have a lot of things but wait
I don't see a stone cutter come on there
must be
one maybe we need to craft one no I
don't think so I feel like they're not
like letting
us but am I blind I don't see one look
for anothera shop e even though like you
say oh uh the armor wouldn't have a
stone cutter but like the he even has
this like enchanting stuff and the and
the uh map making table so I feel like
he would have everything else too this
seems like they would have anything here
to be
honest this seems like the
place to be but
h h
[Music]
oh
wa he grow so quickly
oh okay I found a shop that sells a
fashion surprise box what what is it I
have to buy this maybe oh my God is this
like more PG is like the cash shop where
you can buy cute outfits like made
outfits and stuff
mom is it got no way I have to buy it I
bought it I bought it I bought the
fashion surprise box I will open it I
want to see it I want to know what it
is two one oh oh I get to choose It's
gotta okay okay okay uh I Choose You mhm
oh what what is it oh oh
uh
uh H do I only get one of these or all
of
these a crypto B I got like it gave me
hats from each like
Guild uh and it gave me a lot of
construction supplies
boxes cool oh it's already in my
inventory wait oh oh that's just the
reveal of what what was where ah
honestly I'm not mad about construction
supply box Chan I appreciate that that's
what I need right now oh no no you just
ran past me oh where are you here there
she is let me bring the supplies box to
our building
field
yeah which was over
there that's the G oh my God it's going
to get me addicted but the hats is if
that's like the main prize I don't
know I don't know I wanted cute outfits
whoa
oh kitty
cat remember when you were able to
choose
the materials that you wanted basically
I got the same kind of box and I can
again only choose like one full block I
guess think you muted by the
way I think you're muted
okay uh okay so should I get
glass for Windows
glass I I don't know I I feel like
having like 64 blocks of glass is such a
waste
no should I get more
bricks
no no more bricks I think we enough
enough bricks oh let me think there's
there's uh cherry tree logs
too no we have we have uh logs it's fine
we can find them but these are pink
maybe some some cute bricks some cute
blocks that we can use for the house but
not bricks you say I mean we already
have bricks so we can make some
variation you know how
[Music]
about white concrete or brown
terracotta or block of Quartz very cute
the concrete it is great okay wait wait
you know what we you know what we should
decide what we want to build in the
first place do we want to build
something big coin
yeah okay so we should consider to get
the same materials yeah then we need
more
bricks do we do you want to make b a
brick brick partially maybe partially
okay okay that's
fine cuz we already have bricks so like
we're kind of starting with that right
yeah yeah yeah you're right I'm I'm
looking I'm looking for some bricks
construction
yeah
bricks I want to build more
Bricks now I spent 300 of my coins for
more
bricks do you sell any
no I want to check out more of the city
of the shopkeepers and
stuff and me like if I can get more oh
actually where did you got the bricks
thingy sorry the the pack um from the
gacha oh on the shop
yeah okay I'm not sure if it's like
really worth
it you know cuz it cost me 300
coins I got it you got it
oh I think it was it was fair to be
honest for 300 for 64 blocks I think it
was worth
yeah especially cuz I guess we can't get
those blocks in any other way if there's
a quest uh where we can like proceed
with like what the blacksmith would sell
us I would like to do that or is it like
dungeon bound I wonder you know that
would be a huge Flex to make like a
little castle or something
yeah wait let me check which materials
do we need though making a castle is
going to be difficult little castle
we need like
[Music]
stones did they have Stones
I'm maybe I don't remember they had a
lot of wood like different types of wood
and some like
turquoise beautiful turquoise
stones but like I feel like the either
the blues or the greens will use a lot
of the turquoise
stuff wait where is this shop again can
you guide me oh um wait mama Mama Mia
there's a quest That's
Italian oh I want to read I want to
read come to the quest
board m
m i want to find the
uh the shop
first where is it let's you use a ter
cooking
pot Master's trying to craft some tools
oh yeah this sounds like it continues
that quest
line I'm going to do that and then maybe
I'll log off after
that yeah if you go to the quest board
you'll find that uh oh you're here
almost turn
around H oh there we go go read the
Italian Quest I go
uh which one is it uh well you should
recognize it let's see it's the first
one for me page one Help Wanted at the
tavern wanted at the Tav okay
Mama I
am more more
Itali more yeah
[Music]
I I don't
have near enough
help do this how it sound like I I don't
know yeah
sometimes okay cuz you say no hey read
the rest of
it but I don't have a near enough help
if you land on me a hand
you
use oh well I wonder why he got caught
off maybe the quest is too
long maybe okay but I actually I I took
the quest that's on the next page
because uh when doing that I think they
will give us um iron tools rather than
stone tools once we complete it so oh
yeah looking for five iron inot so I'm
going to go
outside and this shop can you show me
the shop where is the oh it's a I think
it
was oh where was it it all looks so
similar maybe I found
it oh I found it again it's like close
it's like across diagonally across the
quest
board where are you ah over here over
here turn around turn around turn
around there here if you want to do the
gacha have fun
yeah okay where is outside over
here going to get myself those iron
tools oh wait
who that is is that the
castle
who it's not where I wanted to go but
that's
amazing fashion surprise box yes I want
to buy it too and you don't even the
thing is you don't even want the fashion
you want the the consolation prize don't
you anything is fine yeah like
gotcha gotcha
gotcha I can choose yeah just one and
then it will reveal to you uh maybe
we'll see like it will reveal to you
what what what was in what space there's
a hat too yeah I I like uh I want to get
I can't find the exit
oh hello oh
hi we're both talking to do you hear me
Risa wait I'm I'm going to Pi the yeah
let me pick Turn yeah let
me okay
hello hello how are the fair Maiden uh
uh thank you it's hard to speak in an
RPG way in English for me um a nice Fork
uh me lady is it a pitchfork that you
hunt witches
with yeah oh it has a little fluffy
thing on it yeah flowers yeah have you
uh uh completed some quests perhaps no
but uh these These Girls whom I have met
uh recently koseki beu and fuaa and Moco
are going to go and do the dungeon
together now that we have oh you're
right you were gone Ah that's why makes
sense now we have return so upon our
return We shout destroy whatever lurks
in within the dungeon yay have
fun thank you sorry I can't I wish I
could man I could do it better in German
you know that's okay just speak in
German okay Al does
fa well
men
what nice to see her again where the
hell is the exit what is this ah the
French
lady Al so that's like the the blue
people Palace if I stick to the
walls I will go find the
exit oh that was Russian I thought she
was like speaking some German to
me
oh oh the canal oh it leasts like outs
sign what time is
it I'm running out of time now damn it
I'm so lost why why am I so lost now I
can't find the exent I kept on seeing
the like several
[Music]
times spending 30 minutes running around
here I don't know by the way if they
ever
like will'll give you
guys ah there it is access to the server
I feel like they might oh kopine have
you seen the vision of yourself Jan yeah
I did does it make you think less of me
no it it makes me feel uh like very very
connected to you really I kind of didn't
want everybody to see one of my own
personal memories but like if it doesn't
make you hate me or anything like that I
guess it's fine it's very hashtag
relatable you think so yeah also why is
your si uh sparkling I don't know I
completed the the dungeon and it started
sparkling oh it sparkled after that yeah
a cuz I didn't notice to Sparkle before
interesting
strange what about your weapon is it
sparkling too oh yeah it is yeah I hav
noticed that either maybe it gets more
sparkly as we complete dungeons oh
wonderful that' be cool I wonder if
we'll get to see your memories too I
wonder I'd certainly like to see them
yeah do you know what you did or
anything I don't remember but it's
coming back to me like step by step
surely little by little right yeah well
I hope we can figure it out together
maybe yes if you want we could also um
check out the next uh dungeon tomorrow
yeah I want to do
that depends on the time that you would
be streaming though oh just the usual
day the same time was same as today yeah
are you sure I checked your Google
calendar and it didn't look like that oh
was it wrong oh it looked like you were
starting later yeah they had something
for me to do man why do I know your
schedule better than you I know right I
forgot that thing tomorrow well probably
two hours later then I'll be doing it
but if you want to enter a dungeon with
other people that's fine and we could do
it a different one A different day yeah
a different one for sure yeah let's do
it
yippe Yi bye-bye beautiful
one yeah
yeah I would totally go with her but I
saw in her calendar that she's like
going to be
late uh with her stream start
tomorrow unfortunately that's iron right
ow what are you mad at my pronunciation
or what I hate you I hate you I hate you
I hate you wait I should attack with uh
this
one was it like oh my God what what it
that oh my God they're really mad at me
taking the iron okay okay oh my God
rough rough
alone very rough
alone there we go there we go there we
go I am fighting like a
warrior okay uh I wonder if like it when
I die did I lose my levels and my EXP
you guys have did you have an eye on
it cuz I wonder if we don't lose it oh
do we
perhaps like get stronger with each
level that would be really
cool I kept my
levels do we get
[Music]
stronger imagine if they like went all
the way to like make us like a little
skill tree thingy that would be insane
why am I hearing
voices huh I don't
know even though my window is closed I
feel like I'm slightly hearing something
from
outside not again
die you sha with the power of the
Phoenix does this look like does this
still look like I have that resource
pack on actually it does doesn't
it
oopsie I mean I like it though I do like
it I I want to leave it it's getting
dark I I think I probably have enough
though right always makes me think
there's a creeper wait where's
the where's the
iron ah here blind as
[\h__\h] and then the coal we have to give
him ingots right so it's good that I'm
mining the coal too I was just like
mining it for fun but we needed to make
ingots in uh out of
it yeah yeah yeah yeah I can get the
stone blocks too yeah if I wanted to did
it see me oh it aggroed
me gy KY is so like everywhere and fun
and loud and
exciting I like
her
what
w oh the cow
burn still don't know how to use my
shield by the way
ah but I only have the shield on when
I'm wearing the sword
huh
[Music]
interesting okay it's probably fine or
maybe a bit
[Music]
more can never have
enough maybe it's passive you don't
think the shield does anything generally
it seems like nothing does anything in
general
like there's no stats of
damage can you
not okay I'm out of
here I'm so out of
here why would it make your sword of
range weapon closer e because it's a
cool attack it's not really ranged it's
just like in one line a pretty long
attack
I think it's cool everybody's weapons
were like put into the game they did ask
uh like beforehand like hey this is how
it's going to look do you like it and
hey this is what we're going to name it
do you like it are you okay with this
they even asked me like do you want it
in the left hand or right hand and I
said okay so in I know that in the
trailer and everything they put it in my
left hand and you guys were like w
attention to detail but it's not the
case in here they said they could do it
I said actually no just leave it the the
normal Minecraft way because I don't
want things to confuse me if they're
like on the other side um maybe it would
be confusing for some reason what I was
thinking you
know so it's just the original
way okay uh going back to green oh which
is oh right
there and then I'll use their furnaces
right
oopsie and put in the coal and the
irland I'm making
irland yeah don't didn't want to
complicate anything
mm burning Phoenix if it's official
uh not really also like you know we saw
Callie's video but like when you see my
video is like not really going to be
official lore okay just keep that in
mind don't don't take it's like it's
it's kind of like inspired perhaps by
my my personal like what I see as my
official lore but I don't want you guys
to see it as official official Lord it
gets close to it but I don't know I
could have changed it but I was like
this is fine but
yeah close
enough close enough I got so much iron
H it's going to take a while how much
did I want five okay I got five yipp uh
you
or oh oh they took it from me right yeah
so
now now I get iron
tools let's go but damn did that just
say 100 coins that's
expensive Mama Mia
what happens in enigmatic recollection
says
exactly oh 200 for the sword was
unbreakable oh really oh all the swords
are unbreakable oh that's
good 100 coins
damn damn
that's fine does this one the smoker
does that that only works for food
right ah I could actually I
guess probably make some food right I
wonder is this like cooking zombie
meat oh it comes out oh the snowmo
stakes forget to
more uh if mobs keep attacking you while
you mine the coin cost won't be
bad what do you mean what do you mean
like because I could attack them while
I'm Mining and get more coins from them
what well these monster drops I guess is
just for more food and then yeah the
wait right click to use can be
thrown what would we be throwing it at
and I still have this key
key item cannot be traded can I put it
somewhere where it's not like wait
[Music]
wa oh okay I can't move the key like I
could recycle like this
[Music]
stuff okay I I'm not going to leave this
in here so I want to was new weapon a
charge plate
I mean no I don't think so not what
people see officially as a charge blade
I don't I'm not really even 100% sure
what that is but let's
see
H wait I was going to try if I can
charge it but I don't think
so why is your name blue oh it's white
okay looked interesting to
me ah I really wish there was a stone
stone cutter this is not a stone cutter
either
right yeah
repair
H why
not what is
that no no stone
cutter okay I'm done here with the iron
I got a good amount of
iron I could buy here like a sword
upgrade let's go why not then eventually
we'll need an iron pickaxe anyway so let
me get
that did I get
it what what do you it took that much
iron from
me okay that took a lot of iron from
me
fine eh yeah no I think I was missing
iron like maybe one or two or three
that's okay
okay guys um I'm going to leave it at
that uh wait let me call all we never
called each other back no I wonder what
she's
doing I forgot to call you
back it's okay what were you doing I am
farming to make our Castle oh let's go
yeah I did the like uh iron tool Quest
so now I can buy iron
tools oh my God that's so cool yeah but
it's expensive really expensive how much
is it like an iron sword costs you like
some materials right and 200
coins not that much it's
much 200 coins is not that bad yeah well
the sword at least doesn't
break oh yeah that's cool and then the
the the single tools they cost 100 and
the
materials so okay that is pretty cool
yeah when you find time you should do
the quest too I'm going to go I'm going
to I'm going to make this side quest
soon mhm I'm going to go
too okay so you leaving yeah I'm leaving
okay thank you so much for playing with
me see the same time
okay see you
tomorrow
byebye
byebye yes I think I'll start at same
time tomorrow should probably be fine I
don't think I'm I have like because I'm
right in front of my um in front right
it's right before my my like studio
recording days for my mying life
so
tired so tomorrow I book The Dance
Studio to like kind of re relearn and
like you know practice my dances so that
I get it all into my body so tomorrow a
couple of hours uh at the like end of
the day I'll be spending there but this
is like early in the day um this like
noon time for me in Japanese time so
first half of the day Minecraft second
half of the day dance dance dance and
today I'm actually going to get a
massage later now I have some work and
then I go get a massage sounds good
right yeah the lesbians they shall be
saved but I'm so sad because I probably
won't be here for the finale so I don't
know man I I I probably won't be able to
save them at the end of the day
I hope that someone else will save them
for you guys because it seems like we're
on different quests you
know me and me and narissa are certainly
saving the lesbians others are more
focusing on the lestans depends on the
person
really yeah well I got to run
now I think you already saved them the
tweeting about you right now
lesbians why are you gay
why are who is gay why are you
gay perfect
combination of memes and
[Music]
phrases yay I had a blast we did the
first dungeon and a little bit of side
questing and I want to do more
ideally tomorrow but you know I got like
I got work to do every
day yeah it is what it is
it is what it
is oh yeah maybe I'll
start
I stream I see she wants to start an
hour early so I think I'll join her on
that one probably an hour early or
so thank you for watching and and last
but not least at the end let me here
show you uh a good view of my cloak is
really long
[Music]
wa wow you let me stand
here
woo ain't it
beautiful you know what let me get rid
of this just black
screen wow it's so fancy it's so
pretty and I really like how
the
gem is so like
shiny see how the shininess
moves
gorgeous oh dear or G or oh
gorgeous yeah pretty coold now everybody
has this coat this
cloak finally I got a cool fancy
adventurous cloak
[Music]
okay and with that I say a say for today
thank you for watching I'll see you
tomorrow for more Minecraft we'll be
doing this every day until well not
really every day not me but I think
everybody will be kind of like playing
it a lot and I wish I could be there
every day but sadly schedules don't
align so well riperoni but I'll do my
best to be in it as much as I
can bye-bye we
the adventure
await Revenge Revolution revalation
[Music]
he