[Music]
do
hello
[Music]
oh
oh boy is everything working i think
everything is working
looking good as always
thank you thank you as you are too
anyways ah welcome to the uh
oh what should i say impromptu
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
i was baiting you guys i was beating the
chat
yes there's no chance i'm sorry you're
you're uh safe for today
uh we'll just see what what games we can
play today
as a uh four four pl or three
uh how's the audio for everyone ami
and kiara are their voices levels good
i was just pretending to be muted hello
hi
hello hello all good all good i've been
muted
no she's not muted she's just tricking
you guys
all right all right all good okay we can
get started so
ah there's a few choices we have
we have mahjong
[Music]
that's enough to fill an hour i think
did you look to the very very right
yeah it's all good
yeah okay so
we might try out uh mahjong you guys are
interested in
trying out much yes like i remember um
my mom
playing it when i was younger and it
like fascinated me because it had like
it looked pretty and i i kind of tried
it out myself
but i don't think i ever completely
understood the game so you know you have
to like
explain it a little bit please i'm a
beginner myself
but um yeah i'll do my best
so i think they played a little bit
i know one thing about this game the
pieces go clack when you put them in
yeah i like the clock
sorry i'm guessing you play using these
tiles with the characters and pictures
on them
i actually tried to pay attention now
wow mobile version of the tiles right
that should help also it's called the
global version of the tiles huh
it says here we have to make 14 tiles
that we get
make what are we trying to get four of a
kind
straight uh seems like lots of things
will work
the list here has over 35 hands you can
make
how was anyone supposed to remember all
that
i've been leaning pretty heavily on the
recommended hands in the assist mode
a system cheap stuff is in there
i need isn't changed it has a list of
hands you can refer to
also some tips to help you make them oh
[Music]
number sequence like two three four and
then like five six seven
something like that or are there other
ways they match the colors
uh well you can have like three of the
same tiles too like
three three three four four four and
stuff like that
there's like those like uh symbol ones
like the uh
like there's a blank one and there's
like the red
um box with the light inside
and the uh the green country dragon
kanji i don't know
okay so you can you can match those
together
there's also like direction tiles that
you can do
yeah basically it's like uh try to match
uh the same looking tiles the easiest
i think okay like a matching game okay
yeah
oh you kind of you kind of get a hang of
it so basically you get like
uh it's kind of like card game where you
get the belt one
uh little piece each game and you can
like decide if you want to take it or
not keep it or not
i guess this is not the margin that i
was thinking about what when i think of
my own
the one where there's like a lot of
stones like in the middle and you try to
like get rid of them
you know what i'm talking about
you've been lied to all along
i've been quite bamboozled okay it's my
turn okay so oh i didn't know it's my
turn okay
uh i guess i so
i i want i want a row of numbers right
and it doesn't matter if the color in
between changes
uh no no they have like different sets
of tiles so you know how
um one set of tiles is like red on the
bottom and there's like green on the
bottom and blue on the bottom
yeah so they're like different uh type
of sets and you have to do like the
number like the sequence or the
triple same number yeah
can you go like seven six five
yes because that's the same as
five six seven i don't know
i forget it's a legit question yeah yeah
yeah but one one thing to run out of
numbers to
do i just start a new chain yeah you can
start a new chain so you want to have
like
uh uh i think four
four pairs of the same like uh
sets of three or like uh a number
sequence
like three sets of those and then like a
pair
of the screen tile in order to win can i
also can i do like four
five five six six or should i continue
with only one uh
like four four five five six six one
nine
four five five six six can i skip my
turn
oh you can you can just put down the
same
same tile that you just got yeah yeah
you can do that too
okay and uh four five five six you can
do that depending on what um
what tiles you have too yeah yeah yeah
uh how do i use the sysmod
[Music]
did we even turn it on oh i think i
think it's already on like do you see
the
four two or something to ten five on the
right i think that's the assist like oh
yeah
ten five is basically called a ready
hand so you're like
one tile away from winning or
yeah ah one tile away from being able to
call your win
yeah why did it not change now
i feel like i'm still three to ten bye
it might turn again that's quick well
that's i'm just turning right now
oh oh i feel like cpu is gonna win
yeah i think so too okay you gotta
believe trust in me
oh three against the
okay i found the button versus oh what
was it
what is it left bumper
[Music]
oh
she's reading the ways
twin runs i'm doing ah
[\h__\h] should have done it that way sorry
i cursed i
i apologize i will i will beat myself
afterwards here
sorry show us a little bit
yes okay take this all right
is this one ah
[Music]
oh i see
oh this is just the uh like it just
shows you all the
all the ten flies yeah that's helpful i
should have
now i feel like practicing we should do
like a tournament tournament
oh that'd be fun
i think i messed everything up
it's okay you never know when the
tables are going to turn during during
when the turn stable yeah
um oh my turn what's
what can i do with a blank one oh blank
one is just like
you know like the green green character
tile you see on the
on the on the discarded tiles right now
it's kind of like the same one
there's a bunch of like blank tiles that
you can collect too
is it not something that i can put in
between like if i don't have like number
seven i can put it here
it's just it's just a normal normal tile
what do i do with that i don't get it
and you can keep it if you have a bunch
of blank tiles or you can discard it if
you don't need it
how do you discard wait what do we do
now if the roll of the row is full
uh wait are you do you have ten pi or
what
what's called ten pi no never mind i
don't know what's going on
it's a little hard to get used to or i
get started on
we will learn it daijoubu learning by
doing
i kind of want to see all this on his
hand
oh yeah right i guess i oops i i i
didn't i didn't
make use of it but i guess i did see
inna's hand because i'm i do have the
screen on
oh yeah what's going on i have
i have like it gives me the option to
chi or to cancel
ah a new one she
is a um like a sequence like three four
five or like five five six seven
something like that but you can
uh make it with the discarded tile of
other players so you can call chi and
then you can like take that discard tile
and then like
keep it on your own make it your own
so i may just discard it a two so you
have in your hand something that you can
make a cheat
set with oh i ah i guess i do
i discarded it yeah
one two three right so you have one set
ready get a snowman
goodbye you discarded it did you just
place it and that made it discard
yeah yeah yeah well you know you know
every turn you put down one tile to the
middle that's called
like a discarded tile like you throw it
away
oh you don't want it yeah whatever
it's like wait have you guys
have you guys been throwing in the ones
that you wanted to keep
yes yeah
oh
yeah i was like man of it must be really
bad luck to put those
two green dragons down
i thought i was gonna put them down and
then like make a row of three and i was
gonna
like get a good points or something oh
no no the
the number tile right in front of you
is what you have that's that's like the
final thing you want to have
you want to collect it into your handy
yeah i didn't know that i found it like
normally it was like a card game
yeah in the middle right oh yeah i guess
i guess it depends on what card game are
you yeah
like at the end we show our hand and
then whoever has the most
powerful combo yes yeah whoever gets
like the combo
ready like you have to have basically
it's like
uh it's like you like uh basically
you're preparing to like fire an arrow
and then you know when you're ready you
just be like ha i won
and then you're about to show everyone
but before that you can't be like i win
you have to have like a
you have to draw the bow kind of you
know ah
i can't if i have like a combination now
i just have to wait until the game is
over and then
whoever has okay so attend fi is like
a winning hand where you can be like i
can end
the game right now and then like show
your hand
and be like yeah i win
ah i get it
okay okay i think yeah maybe
maybe i get it too maybe maybe
okay so like when you get a new one you
have to discard one of the ones you
don't have if you want to keep it so you
can have a more
powerful combo
me and julian okay wow wow
wow wow
even though i was playing the game wrong
i'm doing something good
oh seems like someone has a option okay
gonna win now
she knows maybe i'm maybe i'm acting
them
ah i gotta keep a poker face
you
[Music]
man this music is getting to my brain
it's like the jeopardy music
but like macho
kinda reminds me of animal crossing it
sort of does yeah
i recently started animal crossing all
over and
did it on stream i'm so addicted now did
you time travel
yeah cheater you know i'm playing the
game the right way
[Laughter]
[Music]
um in the first stream like i started my
island all over
but it wouldn't even have been an hour
stream if i wouldn't time travel because
like
it just you you have to wait like
certain things you can only do
once a day passes and another day passes
i just did it for the content you know i
really all right
well i'm taking another tea thank you
why does kara have those piles yeah good
questions
those are the the cheese that she called
don't worry she's not cheating
sorry i'm sorry i just went
oh [\h__\h] i shouldn't have i shouldn't
have cheated
made it actually worse but question uh
if i have like
if someone gets a tent by it but i have
two cheese or three cheese or whatever
um does it like like does it even matter
that i have nothing does that give me
points no no
ten pie is the end of the game so if
they call it
then you're done for
and what are cheese even with oh cheese
basically you know how you only get one
tile per
turn like um on your turn
but when someone else's turn they put
down a tile and you can steal it
it's basically like you get an extra
chance to
improve your your deck yeah
hey but it's like separate from my tempe
[Music]
um
can't speak english
[Laughter]
but like like see like i just i just
stole something right
but now um instead of like the the
number to tempi
it raised because i took one away from
myself basically too
no um ten five is basically like a set
of like
different combinations of sets that you
can have in order to have the ready hand
there's like a whole bunch of them and
basically the pc
knows the easiest way to 105
but whatever step you took
was not that so you're further away from
10 fly right now
okay i don't know what's going on
yeah it's it's a little complicated even
i don't i don't even i've been playing
for a while
well on and off but even i don't even
know yeah
[Music]
um
can i skip down i can tell you
can i not skip i can get the g and put
the chi down
if you if you want to well if you don't
want to switch any tiles just
uh put down the one that you just drew
onto the table
it should be to the very right very
right tiles
something else i
see i see how it is
gee oh
that's my pile no that's that's the
cpu's pile
he's cheating he cheated
oh okay
is there like speed my tongue
uh did it go fast usually there's like
a time limit between turns depending on
the game
well i think this one doesn't have like
a time limit per turn
so ah it's like you know you know in
chess they have like the timer
that they do oh you like that yeah
so i got um i got one
key one like thingy now that is like
blue like a few others but
like it has a blue bar but it's colored
yellow
even though the others are colored right
you know what i mean is it is it a five
yes ah that's a that's a special type of
five
um and uh it gives you
more points if you win with that five in
your hand
dora but not the explorer kind
[Laughter]
ana it's of nice to be with you
this is wonderful hearing all these
these
amazing amazing amazing puns
me
oh really good one kiara
never heard that
[Music]
stream one of the questions was like so
what do you do when a pun doesn't land
and i was like ah did they ever land
that one hurt right in the kokuran
is there a maximum of how many i can
describe because i gotta have three
rows already
all right all right here you go
i don't think oh wait a minute pen pie
oh i win
no uh oh there's no title
yeah there's a limited number of tiles
available in the full game
and basically uh oh
i mean i got ten five just in time for
the last bit
but yeah
i kind of want to do it again now that i
know like you know
there's more rounds oh
wait now i have some south and north
thingies yeah
yeah so you can collect those ones you
can collect the
same ones oh you see the direction
on your uh name like besides your your
icon
it says east right
and abe is north ah
i'm south and then cpu is west
so if you collect the three of the same
direction tile oh as you
are sitting at it basically gives you
uh more points oh so how about the other
directions i shouldn't care
uh but the only one you want to care for
is a uh
i think it's called the prominent beast
so like right now we're at a east
east a second round right right in the
center it says 69 tiles
and then uh
e2 so we're at an east table so
anyone sitting in the table they can
collect three east tiles
or if you have the small
letter direction like for example if i
have uh
three soft tiles i can also get points
for that as well
but other uh direction tiles you
uh don't really get okay points
unless you do like a more uh should i
say
complicated um
i sing what about the one that says like
naka in japanese that's also um
uh i think those are called the dragon
tile
so i forget but um you can collect like
three of those
two and then that basically gives you
uh tense like if you have uh
enough uh like uh pairs or not pairs out
like
sequences or like three of the same
tiles and stuff yeah red dragon yeah
the red naka is called the red dragon
i don't know these terms because i just
play with pictures
i just really pretty pictures and match
them
wait no what did i do why did it go why
did it go from 2
to ten by eight from two three to ten
point
oh oh
i've seen
do i want to do that no i don't wanna
you know that google the guy cheating
no i mean when you first start out like
learning macho i think it's good to have
those picture guides
what's uh what's disabled calls
uh that's like saying uh if you have a
chance for
chi or a pun pon is like three three of
the same tiles kind of thing
uh t is like the two e4 kind of thing
uh it just like automatically stops you
from getting those i think
i think i think oh okay
i didn't understand that but okay that's
okay
you're the image like saying i
absolutely get it but you don't get it
that's me
it's okay i believe in you guys
wait what is the blank tile again it's
not it's just a normal tile you can
collect three
of the same uh blank tiles
i love how like you know
literally teaches us everything what
what do we what what we do without this
one brain cell that you know has
wait strong big strong brain cells you
guys they called me smart
my brain so is smart
does um like for example if in my hand i
have like five six seven
eight blah blah uh
like in between is something and then it
continues um is it a problem if in
between my
my row of numbers there's something
random okay so
the number sequences and stuff you want
it to be in pairs of three
uh-huh oh so if there's uh some missing
numbers in the middle of between like
two different sequences then you can you
know do whatever
yeah on google the guide said you need
four sets and each set
consists of three tiles yes so four sets
and then a pair of two
yes to win okay
okay four sets in a pair of now that's
another hotel
okay now that changes everything
it changes everything but how damn it
and i have to throw out like everything
i have in the beginning
like pretty much yeah
believe in the heart of major but wait
wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait like if i
if i chi uh-huh and i take i i i get
like one of those three sets to the side
right uh-huh
if i doesn't mean that if i have four
cheese
and one pair of two does that make a ten
pie yes
if you have more cheese you can make a
sandwich uh-huh
[Laughter]
i have finally understood
[Music]
she's just smiling she's just smiling
i cry every time
what
oh i said she like that
team
my time i said cancel i don't want it
but give it to me anyways
oh thunder maybe i pressed the wrong
button
ah
mistake wait you guys trying to look at
your
your hand no i'm not
wait what
hmm
[Music]
what
[Laughter]
[Music]
hodor
oh in this game you just have to wait
like if you're waiting to make a pair or
set you're just like hoping to get
the one that you're that you want ah
yeah and complete it and if someone
someone puts down the tile that you need
you need you can call iran
what's that you put down
the card that i needed i'm gonna take
all your points kind of thing
and you can win the game what does
what's a pawn again
con is the three of them tiles
what three of the same tiles uh-huh
is it mine's turn uh i think i want to
waiting to call upon or not
[Music]
um
oh
what just happened i don't know what
just happened
[Music]
thinking strongly thinking
hmm
[Music]
wait
how do i not mess this up now how do i
how do i how do i not mess with my song
on it
if i if i go to um
if i scroll over my my my
my what do you even call these uh my
stones tiles yeah
tiles um and like all of them say
nothing
except one says need this number and
this number
would it be the smartest to throw away
that one
because that's the only one i need
something for or
wait on the on the left it says need and
then it has some tiles right
yeah because so you have a template
right now right
yeah so i don't want to mess it up that
means you probably want to throw
away the new tile that you got no but i
think the new one is making me a
template because before it didn't say
ten points ah
okay okay wait i need to see your titles
to make sure
okay okay for for education purpose i
will tell you my tiles
uh it's them it's all blue uh-huh
and it's a two three five
six seven eight five
well the new one is free but i also
already have a three
i guess i could throw it i guess
i guess yeah because um but what if that
screenshot it and send it to me no it's
okay
i'll throw away the new one and hope
that that wasn't the one that gave me a
template
nope i went to damn bite i had it
okay
we tried damn it
damn it damn it i can hear amma's brain
going
she's thinking she's in control
she's playing an fps game
of which which stones she has to shoot
down this one
i'm reading my google guide
i don't need google
i'm not sure about that guide i don't
think the reviews are very nice
look at it
thank you thank you very much
will she put down the towel that i need
i got the tempo again oh
what do i do five six seven eight nine
oh i don't wanna throw it away for nine
eight or nine
wait you tell me to throw away you don't
know yeah because you need you need a
pair
remember so you have what are the
numbers that you have left
five six seven eight nine that's one one
set
so you have eight and nine right so you
need uh
you need to discard an error at night i
think
oh nine probably the nine
chest is nine okay yes yes yes
interesting ah only eight tiles seven
times left
uh do i just i guess i throw away the
new one okay
what chad is saying something like kiara
has no yaku so
she can't win anyway what does that mean
yeah so you need to have a certain
uh certain sets
like certain set of sets in order to win
even 105 is like you're one away from
winning
but like yaku is like okay there's like
a certain
like different different uh
yaku and you you have a yaku or
well i think it's so yeah
yeah well templary if no one wins until
all the tiles run out that means ten
five is the best thing you can have
like one away from winning but ayaku is
like a
set of different combinations
i was one away almost
close enough
okay next round let's do this how come
somebody only had four
tiles can you put away like so many
tiles oh
and that was lara caroline and fourth
because you know when you call a tea or
a pond you put down the
little sets on the side that's basically
your hand
but you're taking from other people so
you have to put it in the pile over
there on to the right
but you're still it's still part of your
hands yeah yeah
okay
i don't i don't think i can like make
any of these like uh
like complicated combinations but like
putting
the right numbers together that's
something i can do so
uh in order to call like call the game
and say i win
uh you need to have the yaku and one of
the simplest one
you can get is called a all symbols
where you don't have any direction tiles
you don't have any of the dragon tiles
and you don't have any one or nine
in your uh in your hand so basically
any number from two to eight in any
any of the symbol tiles and stuff
simplest thing you can go for um
there's like another simple one which is
if you have a lot of east tiles
east tiles like and then uh you can try
to get three of those
i already have two cheese
yeah it's it's a lot to remember that's
why i like having a chart like how
amida's maybe it's nice
if you don't know yeah but then yeah i'm
too lazy to look it up now
well if you if you press the uh
one of the uh the left
trigger button bummer button let me show
you like all the yakuz and stuff
maybe maybe um
oh yeah and if you uh manage to get a
winning hand without taking anyone
else's tile
you can call something called avicii
and then you just wait for
the winning title to be played and you
can get more points
oh
very good explaining things because in
my head it's like all like okay you do
the
the bloop and then you do the swoof and
then you do the
glitch and then you just it doesn't have
it doesn't have
it's okay as long as you don't let the
uh cpu win we're good
yes gina you gotta win go ina
you never know what maybe you're gonna
get a godly hand
and don't let the computers win
i mean we're we we are
i mean we have virtual youtubers we're
pretty close to being something like a
computer
yeah but if we share brain cells it's
basically a 1v1
versus the cpu you know
[Laughter]
i don't put my tiles down like kiara
oh that's when uh you have like a uh uh
you can call like tea or pun and then if
they put that if someone else puts on
that child then you can call it chi or
pon
now if someone puts down something that
you would need to create a chin or a pun
then it gives you the option to do it
so you just uh threw down some some
um some stones that
are were useful for me to make a chain
and that's why i got them
it's just uh depends on what the others
throw down i guess
[Music]
um
interesting
[Music]
bye bye
how's it going nina
um how's it going um
they can do it
i believe [\h__\h] should have kept my blank
goddammit
you gotta reach for the wind
i appreciate the effort
thank you i'll i'll do my best
oh
i think my my technique is just to keep
on
cheating because it seems like the the
most obvious one
like if i put them down it feels like i
did the right thing
oh what's that what's a tan yao
is that just one of the combinations i
[Music]
think
um
guess i'll throw this hit yeah
i'm surprised you guys don't know the ma
john that i i know the one where it's
like all piled up like
like a like a mountain and you you you
collect
yeah and i know too oh
yeah oh that one's like fun i like that
one
i think it's like a one player game is
it oh
yeah oh it's called solitaire
oh
[Music]
is that like not like a like a just
like a fake different game
[Music]
i think it just uses the same tiles but
yeah it's like different
i kinda wanna i kinda wanna see what the
game is like i've never played it
i mean isn't it like one of those like
pc games that's like always like
installed in your pc
back in the day yeah
yeah it wasn't i think it was just on
the pc yeah
yeah yeah it looks super fancy
[Music]
oh
you can you can have my fork it's okay
i'll i'll give it to you
she won a pawn with my sixth
[Music]
um
you can only take the ones that were
most recently
um thrown away
[Music]
am i ah
i'm not sure right now what exactly is
making my template a template and what i
can throw away
yeah still figuring out which one which
tile you should throw away
it's like yeah difficult
do i wait it was uh i need four uh trios
and one do a
duo right yes yes yes so if you have
another
uh trail right now that means you need a
duo if you have
a duo then you means you need a trio no
no i have a
i guess i have a duo but it also it does
some
tell me that i already have a template
but to me it looks like i have a duo
i know i have a i have a trio template
just means you need one
one more tile in order to win and the
title you need to be on the left side it
says need
whatever title yeah yeah yeah
okay okay bye-bye
am is so smart
me
i'm not doing anything
you always smart she's gonna come back
with that
you know how i talked about what's my
run what's it done
yeah that's the hand yeah it's a very
simple hand but
[Music]
nice very clear
now okay
oh one more round okay is that the last
one there's actually four rounds
but there was uh the second one i think
was a repeat because no one no one won
oh yeah ah cut along
oh yeah that's my makeup let's make a
quickie okay
turn under your bead i have a
someone made a a remix uh a eurobeat
remix navino tony
oh i wanna hear it i'll be very fitting
now
i'm taking that thank you
yeah it just happens it just gives you
the option
yeah yeah like you just have to have
them you explain
bad luck yeah yeah maybe
[Music]
yeah so when someone let's say you have
like a three four and then someone puts
down
a five then you can be like
but i think there's a there's like a
rule to like when you can call chi
and pon but yeah mostly bad rng probably
you said my calls are disabled oh
i enabled it okay that's probably why
oh
[Music]
um
oh you know how i told you guys about
the uh what
what's going on
that means i just need to get a uh
i can get extra points my hand is ready
i need the winning tile and then the
game is over
well just this round is over
not sure i understand but okay
what's it
when i draw the one tile that i need
it's called oh my
you're god the master at this game not
i'm just lucky
i'm just lucky that was a nice speed run
yeah that's what we wanted leo says
which means it gives you the points at
the end of the uh
in the round if you win and you want to
make you want to get as many
uh of those as possible
all right one more let's go
oh wait i think it's still the third
round
it's because
wait we've been playing this for one
hour now
we can wrap it up we can wrap them up
this always has been
[Laughter]
this is the three-way chest oh
i got a nice combo
i wanna i wanna i wanna use my combo
do it i believe
not this one but i'm gonna keep it until
the end
so you better not reach or or or sumo or
so
better not reach for it it's me
okay
okay i'll try to play it as fast as
possible so you guys get more time on
your
returns
this one goes bye-bye
hell yeah that's what i like to see
oh wait tell me what would this i
thought that if i
if i do a chin and it's over okay
yes then the cpu is just fast just like
bam bam bam bam
doing the calculations
so as long as you have another triple
and then a duo then you can
call it a win
a duo in a triple uh-huh okay i have a
triple okay
getting very close
hey i am i am in high hopes now
[Music]
another cheat ha
she's making a comeback i can feel it
i can smell it
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
hey
come on please keep making me
what do you need uh
i will not tell you
because then you won't give it to me but
you don't have it anyway
huh
[Music]
well which screen is it
[Laughter]
did you just throw away your dragon i
did
did you lose all hopes for your dragon
oh you freaking kidding me now that's
what i get now
ah
hey everyone is everyone still here
sorry i was i was thinking
i was vibing oh
[Music]
yeah you see on the very upper uh upper
left corner there's like one tile
so usually you know one tile after that
so let's say if that was a two
then the three of the same symbol will
be adora
so uh for now what's what's after north
is the east
i forget but this is the this is the
last last round
okay yeah let's do this
wow oh my god oh that's a weird starting
hand
i don't know it looks so weird to me
i see i see
a story why a quick button
unless they have another way to make
tenpai
[Music]
actually that's pretty good
um thank you
i got those south tiles huh how come i
have three e styles i can't do the same
thing oh no
you keep it keep it because
uh if you don't call a chi or a point
you get something called alichi
if you have like a already yeah so when
you call richie
uh you know at the end when they like
gather up all the uh
all the points you get more points
now the only reason that i put it down
is because i had two selves and then
someone put down the self
so i stole it that's why you have three
on your own
you just have to keep it until the end
yeah
i think i think we should change the the
thumbnail of the stream later on and
just have um
and the title is also mahjong tournament
between amena
and and me
i think that would be fitting
also known as mahjong
[Music]
or how to play majang with ina
ina does not know the rules disclaimer
you've been helping us a lot i think you
know what you're doing ah
yeah it seems
oh
now which one do i choose
are you going to end the game early
we'll see we'll see we'll see
what
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
i'm struggling
having uh four in a row is not really a
thing
right no just okay so i can
okay so i can throw what do you mean not
on hawaii i do have a yaku
look closely
okay oh good
unless hold on let's check ah i can make
this
even bigger
can we wait bless you did you just
sneeze
yeah bless you thank you
not really actually i just realized
i'll bless you thank you
although ah
is there like a german equivalent to
bless you
is a night yeah my viewers like to use
it
we have all the germans isn't it
no one's gonna drop that huh are they
gonna drop it i wonder
ah let's see what happens
no wonder they did that pulling at the
very start they believed
what's uh what's a khan oh khan is when
you have four of the same tiles
and you see when you get a con you see
the um
the tiles uh depends
depends
depends on depends on your hand and what
you have but you see in the very top
left
there's like the north tile and then
like four yellows yeah if you get a kind
you get to flip one more over
so there's a possibility of another
another like a big pointer
uh dora
hmm
ah
i wonder how this is gonna end
hmm
i thought you said something else huh
what what did i say what what nothing
i should have kept that at the beginning
oh it's really fast now everybody i
think everyone's just waiting
oh i mean
i guess i can i guess i can do that okay
now i can't throw out that one
wait kiara can see my tile oh no i
wasn't looking at your eyes
oh someone's gonna pump on
i have to get rid of a tile
sometimes sometimes you just have to
give up on the things that are important
to you you know
do you believe
oh actually if i wish she's gonna win
big
[Laughter]
same
ah
do we have to repeat it again because
you don't no
you won the last round i want this round
so
oh okay we won against the cpu
i think that's it that should be the end
okay
my cpu got second though that's not fair
that's not fair
stupid cpu it's okay you guys were
learning the rules
yeah it was actually like i'm glad that
uh we learned it it was fun finally a
new game
in my repertoire tell you more i learned
it better
play it off
do we maybe to um like uh
end this nicely you want to play one of
those uh that uno game at the end
ah ah is it this one last card yeah
okay but wait how does it i don't know
it just
works but okay let's try let's give it a
try
it's easy
but do you have to like call last card
like before this yeah there's a button
no you have to press it when you have
the last card because sometimes you
gotta throw it all away
okay so this is like for example if
there's a seven then i just
uh even the same color or a follow-up
number right even if it's this different
color hmm
okay and then then the special cards
yeah what's that card on the screen
the the one on the very right uh that's
the
uh tracer whatever
okay maybe she wants to learn more oh no
it's my son
i i know how it goes you know
you know because of
his name hello my name is
when i was younger a lot hmm also i used
to play monopoly a lot when i was
younger
me too monopoly is how you break
friendships is what i heard
i played like a lot of uh different kind
of monopolies like uh lord of the rings
monopoly
oh it's pretty difficult you
walked in order
i'm not sure i don't think i don't think
mordar was really an option
oh unfortunate how the live monopoly
went
oh yeah that'd be really fun isn't there
like switch versions like different
yeah oh is it my turn oh it is my turn
i want i want us to get permission
[Music]
that's okay
last card oh yeah already
oh the cpu got that cpu
give that to the cpu not to me
reverse
oh i forgot to press the button
[Laughter]
too
[Music]
[Laughter]
all right
omelette was like going really drunk
he's like uh he's like
you know uno professional i thought i
had three cards i was trying to mess her
up
so it went on purpose
i guess it's not a joke it's a color
changer huh
and you can choose which color yeah
[Music]
oh
i do
try to put it dry you have to press the
button
i did skip the hell i did
reverse it didn't do anything no not
reverse wait a second
we can work together to take down
inaudible
okay i'm gonna reverse do you have a
plus um
no do it all right we'll just mess up
the cpu
okay
[Laughter]
color change
oh oh oh i choose the color
inna what colors do you have on your
hand
ah the color
of the uh the uh
beautiful hat you're wearing it's uh
it's kind of closer to your your hat
than uh uh i picked the opposite yeah
yeah she's trying to bait you so should
i should i choose that
should i choose that color
i don't know
no ah the
you i don't know what's going on
[Music]
yes yes yes yes yes
gaining more and more guides
which color would you like to have
[Laughter]
okay
why is entertaining it's just a simple
game
oh no cpu is getting close
why did you reverse it you want the cpu
okay it's okay it's okay
you can play the cards right okay trust
me
okay the blue color it's uh
[Music]
oh what's going on what's going on what
is that what is that
what happened they ran out of cards yes
okay
oh there's still a chance there's still
a chance
believe in the heart of cards
draw two nice things right
okay so kids
okay i'll keep it okay
i've been doing my best to spare you
but oh oh god it's the last one in that
color i have i'm so sorry
can someone do a freaking color change
okay okay okay okay
now this is looking better all right all
right all right
all right all right all right changing
up the colors again
color change what color do you guys like
rainbow okay i'm gonna
i'm gonna keep switching you guys tell
me where this stop
okay stop
[Laughter]
okay
all right we're gonna do it again okay
next one
no
did you just forget it or did it i
forgot
okay
life is tough isn't it is
we're going to infinitely like draw cars
oh my god what's going on oh there we go
again this is
this is logo
reverse reverse
draw three wait one oh
color change um
that cpu has no mercy
oh we're running out of that dark blue
again skip
what's going on why hasn't it been my
turn in like ages
there we go don't worry about it
draw two
oh my god i'll give you a chance
i'll leave you how will i ever recover
from that
wait does almond come after me or does
it come after me
tina goes after you what okay so what
color does she have
what color does she have oh god because
i can do two
i can do two different colors right now
it's a smell of
uh i smell the ocean
is it salmon i smell uh
i don't know
are you trying to tell me what color you
have where are you
i'm trying to tell you what color i have
i just said the opposite i don't even
know anymore
[Music]
oh no
gotta get rid of all those cards man we
were so close to
[Music]
skateboarder
reverse thank you
last card all right
[Music]
[Laughter]
first
thank you thank you you're welcome thank
you thank you
beginner's luck yes it really is
[Laughter]
i think overall um this whole stream ena
had the most wins
yeah um i'm just lucky
yeah it's probably ancient ones being
like
yeah she'll get that card or something
like that
[Laughter]
so i guess this is a good place to wrap
it up for today
hopefully we can do the full member
collab sometime soon maybe
maybe something even this week if we can
squeeze it in
maybe i don't know i hope gooda and
kelly feel better soon
yeah i guess we can see them you guys
also be careful not to catch gold
hoods can you
[Laughter]
destroy your health even when you're
only inside so that's you know
i just stopped eating junk food yeah i
ate some
mac mcdonald's yesterday it sounded
so good i could hear her eating it oh
yeah right
yesterday you came to my stream right
when i was eating mcdonald's
it sounded yummy of course
it's just uh i'm i'm a fast food
franchise owner i mean i got i gotta
test out my rivals you know
do you guys have any uh announcements or
anything you will make
not yet but soon me also soon yes
oh yeah you have that mystery collab
coming up this week
oh yeah it's just a mystery because i
wasn't sure if it was going to happen
but
it's all working out well that's your
announcement that you're not going to do
it yet
uh uh i mean i guess that's not really
an announcement
oh okay i guess i can say i guess that
you say now
all right the collab i have later this
week i'll be collabing with
melody senpai
i think we're gonna play keep talking
and nobody explodes again just like oh
i did with kiara she's gonna talk to me
um in english yeah she's gonna try to
help me diffuse in english
oh good luck with that looking forward
to it
thank you oh yes that reminds me um i do
have
uh holo talk this week with mikko senpai
is this week's guest elite [\h__\h]
tribute
sorry i i just said faq i just said
thank you
i just said quote
so yeah that would be fun i hope
everyone can check out holotalk it's um
on friday evening for most american time
zones
and saturday morning for me but yeah i
hope you'll all be there
okay that is it we will wrap it up for
today
thank you so much everyone for coming to
watch it was a lot of fun thank you to
ami and kiara for doing the impromptu
film stream oh no i lost me thank you
thank you thank you thank you that was
fun thank you
it was really fun yeah even though i
lost every single time
it's okay next time you're gonna be like
a master i can feel it i'm gonna study
okay okay
uh we'll just say our bye bye now
and we'll be on our way bye
you