[Music]
yay
you know what's super cute
[Music]
smoothie is chilling
under my dress
like she's
she's vibing chilling sleeping
under my dress
like behind the curtain
switch places no
cats only only cats under my dress
[Music]
oh the mouse moves super slowly
facing
the only inside of the game
[Music]
sensitivity
oh well
i think for this game it doesn't even
matter
[Music]
smoothie
okay
[Music]
okay okay
this music is so intimidating
ah no here
hello kitty
i want i forgot i want to put on
maybe that's why it's delayed i wanted
to put on
like a shower pad wait a second i forgot
i forgot wait
a buddy
it's so intimidating
[Music]
i got it for my birthday
remember it was one of the presents i
received
let me transform
[Music]
these are times when i wanna be
cardboard chiara
don't
[Music]
how
is
give up already you're [\h__\h] useless
when you do accents
[Music]
i could be i could be listening to this
music forever it's so intimidating
wait i didn't tweet i didn't do my
tweets
when i look in this direction it's
perfect
[Music]
oh my god
did you guys see the schedule for this
week
it's exciting i'm so sorry i'm so sorry
the test play is private i'm so sorry
but we're starting with skyward sword
this week
and we still have a tears of varieties
thingy going on this week anyway
yeah and tomorrow we are on cali's
channel for the ttip
but uh
but
yeah so no stream on my channel but i'll
be i'll be finishing up my art
don't worry i'll finish it before the
ttrpg stream
rum so quote tweet
and glory to god free howdy
partner or whatever hearty mighty mouse
[Music]
don't you love this video
it's so good
what is it about it that's so
yo intimidating can we have a
original song like that i want an
original song like that
glory to get b will be the title of it
[Music]
theme song oh yeah this is what plays
in your head when you enter the usual
room
oh how have i ended up here
[Music]
okay okay so we're playing this a little
bit today not so much
not too much okay uh we'll be playing
for
one to two hours quickly read some super
chats and then i
will leaf
[Music]
and so i guess we suck when i when i'm
wait no it's better oh i think it's oh
yeah it's fixed oh
oh oh no
it's obedient too loud
and unintentional fix yeah and
i oh my god i can't it's so good
sorry
[Music]
microphone i'm so
into the intimidatingly loud yes
intimidate me astor
yeah please intimidate me
sorry um uh weird
logo you want me to put the logo on the
bottom left
that's what that space is for huh
peppers peppas please
logo
give me png did you know that if you
look
uh or if you go through google search
uh there's a really useful tool you go
on tools and then you choose
color and then you go for transparent
and then it actually gives you pngs you
it gives you stuff that's actually
transparent isn't that freaking dope
because i got so triggered sometimes
when i look for transparent stuff and i
don't have transparent setting on
because i didn't know about it
and and you know how there's like images
that fake the transparency by
putting that uh that checkered
pattern the gray white checkered pattern
on the background
and you think it's a png so you go on to
there
and you open it up and you then you're
like you [\h__\h] bamboozled me
but yeah if you want actual pngs you go
on google image search and then
you go to the right side you go to tools
and then you go
next to sizes colors and then you choose
a transparent you're welcome
open image in new tab save image as
[Applause]
oh my god stop intimidating me
[\h__\h] oops
oh big can we leave it like that that's
also intimidating
it's my small smart
smart small wonderful
small there we go
josh let's play this game shall we
everyone you gotta help me guys
please help me to play this game
correctly because we played it back in
the day with callie
a while ago a long time ago why does my
head hurt
let's go
congratulations
the october label lettering is complete
your name was pulled
i won a million dollars for a media
placement report to the ministry of
admission
at graston border checkpoint
an apartment will be provided for you
and your family in east graston
expect a class a dwelling class 8 is
that good
oh happy birthday thank you for the red
super chat
midnight it's your birthday
whoa
[Music]
checkpoint opens at last after six long
years can the ministry of admission keep
us safe
walk to work where's my uber november
23rd 1992.
yaha who is that a guard
minister of underneath inspector welcome
to your new position at creston border
checkpoint
stamp passport entry visa and return
documents to entrant
entries restricted to us through scott
citizen only
deny all foreigners glory to us call
okay pay attention to passport
nationality
okay oh okay whatever
german as a sakurambo
uh a cherry cherry
ch so this is a this is
uh what astox okay no problem
wait how do i oh yeah how does this work
again where's the stamp
and there we go ah oh
and wait no a proof wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait
one second let me just copy
[Music]
hey
i just brought i had to copy those
things over here
let's go approved
i got my own stamp here take it bye-bye
[Music]
next door
okay there's a studio moment i know
[Music]
that doesn't look like it doesn't look
like you're from lastoska i don't know
man
denied
never come back i mean come back when we
have like better or better you know
better rules
as those guys only see yeah
bunk next up so i got the basics of the
game but later on it gets like confusing
and difficult
gotta focus a little bit later i haven't
waited in this damn line
no that's not that can't be you don't
you're not from a south carolina
right or am i seeing something
incorrectly
i think that's a no for me bye
see ya next time
i'm gonna go you go to hell if y'all
you should have looked at the freaking
homepage from our website for my
immigration before you travel you idiot
my friends a friend
what was that again say friend and then
enter what was that
again approve that [\h__\h] hell yeah let's
go ina
speak polo and then enter no that was
not it
did i know a lot of the rings but what
was the actual phrase
melon melon it wasn't missed er
he didn't even
oh that was fast i should have done it a
bit quicker oh well they will be
forgiving in the beginning right
imagine spending a little bit so
what ah
okay i get i get savings and seller 25
okay do i already have a family right
now
and on this another i never completely
understood what all of this means so
on the right side it says they are doing
okay is that it
[Music]
who needs heat yeah
yeah okay
[Music]
uh-huh well then we'll save money for
now
what is this stuff oh well let's sleep
safe on food and heat okay but but
eventually won't that
eat my bite my ass
raise the checkpoint a success entry
restrictions to relax
at mid foreigners all right this is
where it gets little
yeah they will get sick man but i don't
have money
from the day foreign hardware is now
installed
check all password information carefully
for this deny anywhere
red button on your desk oh while
inspecting highlight two pieces of this
script
highlight two pieces of description
information from the inspect mode to
enable interrogation
let's go oh
well how much time do i have though
isn't it i thought the weight i don't
know
i don't i can't i mean you don't
aren't they supposed to give me their
passport too now or only the like
is it wait this is the past am i not
supposed to have one more
one more one more thing
hello
basic rules muscles all
i guess then this is fine
expiration date okay in two years
[Laughter]
seems fine probably
right right
no ah yeah
that's double
okay seems good i think
[Music]
wait that one already that one already
expired right
it expired it's expired right
bye-bye i i saw that correctly right
okay good hello
not expired
but um
okay okay
i don't know i mean the graphics are not
that good so like it's hard to tell
honestly
what do you think
i don't know man
no like okay i didn't want to be like
offensive or anything
okay okay okay okay cute twin tails
twinter is always cute let's go
uh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah looks good to me
the picture no the picture was correct
the picture was fine
it looked like her there's no offensive
nostalgia yeah
yeah i know but hey y'all
you look sad you look creepy oh dear
lord
uh yeah i see no problem
[Music]
bye bye i'll also you're from so what
the hell are you gonna do nothing
come on next up
is this changing the color because i'm
lacking time
okay let's do quick
you have longer hair and oh come on no
no no i'm not even gonna take that
probably fine all right those are next
i don't even want to listen to it
[Music]
wait where did you look
what the [\h__\h] is going on no why does
that happen i don't get it
shut shoot
[Music]
oh wait does that always happen the name
was cut short by tara's attack progress
is safe at the start of each day
is that normal it's a scripted event
okay
uh
okay let's sleep okay good good i didn't
do anything wrong
the last one i wouldn't have let in
because the photo was different
alligator is suspected oh my god
alligators
yeah november 25th 1982
andrew for non-non-citizens is now
regulated all furnaces require valid and
for ticket nice nice very good
verify information before stamping
password and passport
entry visa and return all documents to
entrance glory
who is you nice haircut
wait where is oh there it is entry
ticket valid on
today uh-huh that looks good to me
fine thank you for coming have a
although
i mean you did cut your hair
she did cut my hair my hair should they
cut mmm
is that gonna be
gonna be exact here matching matching or
if you say so if you say so
see ya don't think hair matters all
right because that was the second person
that i had like different hair
okay i'm next done next dude
who is you oh you
wait where's your entry ticket how do i
ask him
like that
oh there we go where's your entry ticket
yeah now there we go you should have
[\h__\h] pulled that out earlier what the
hell is wrong with you you think i got
time for this [\h__\h]
man how does she do it you're gonna dust
it
all right thomas have fun in our store
it's a freaking paradise
next door
well you're small did you not eat your
veggies when you were
lung make me no no no no
entry ticket stop talking to me like
that
i'm not interested in that kind of stuff
i got callie at home so that's all i
need
uh honestly it looks
looks fine looks fine to me
[Music]
wait wait where's your freaking ticket
you will make me ask you that
oh you don't have one huh matching it
what did i
matching
what
that makes sense uh all right
sorry sorry for the trouble i'm just i'm
new here
[Music]
how much a [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
uh you guys noticed everything i heard
about it is you're lucky to have a job
so
stop talking to me shingle
[Laughter]
are you single
about it on today okay quick
the face looks all right all right
give you back this thing and that thing
okay
she's shingle ready to mingle
this is this is easy stoke
yeah peppers please thank you that date
is
off uh
it's i mean valid on
a later date does that mean it's still
valid i guess probably none
are you probably wait let's ask him
um date how do i
how do i how do i how do i do that
no correlation the clock
oh there we go
this ticket is for another day it is my
mistake
yeah so
yeah you understand what that means
right
you come back later on that day did you
did you
did you come too early did you book a
wrong flight or did you book a wrong
ticket
yeah hello
you got a long face but that's that's
okay
uh you look fine you're from republia
and the day the ticket is fine you can
have that
and the exploration is fine
yeah yeah no problem here quick
i want to make more money
[Music]
involved what do you mean
hello george
[Music]
please take it please
ah you have nothing
a tape table sorry
[Applause]
come back again
well okay at least we have no terrorists
today yes yes
your son is sick and needs medicine all
right uh
yeah uh
what if i go into the minus what happens
when i go into the minus guys
[Music]
oh god everyone's cold sick hungry
game over well then i can't do [\h__\h] how
do i make more money guys i don't want
them to suffer
okay black market activity explodes
government blames locks
immigration controls checkpoint
expansion postpone all right all right
i have to do it faster get go get good
okay
let's keep good stick the credential
requirements have been instituted
and ourselves sometimes must show their
id card foreigners must secure and
present a valid
entry pyramids enter tickets are no
longer sufficient
a new chapter detailing document
document features has been added to your
rulebook check all information for
ruling
deny any applicants will discriminate
documents right your audio transcript to
correlate any entrance statements
uh-huh okay so
now in the changes instead of tickets we
have like actual like
documents okay let's get good
work ah oh now we're talking okay
duration
remain for 30 days uh-huh seems correct
enter by well that's that's fine because
it says enter by not entering that day
until that day he must enter so
i think this dude is fine you'll call
city
does it say that anyway no alexander
sobolev name is correct okay
uh time for vlan mine's wines
better come and see her vine
okay first one was good
eat good next one a woman peppa's please
what's the purpose of your trip you make
rotting
uh-huh
i have a weird weird uh weird
i'm in a weird mood today
[Music]
oh oh my god i gotta wait passport
number is this the passport number that
is incorrect though
forever duration for what this is
[\h__\h]
do i even have to ask her about it
yo let's go the numbers do not match
it must be a mistake the document is
valid
no no no no no no no
no no
you shall not pass
[Laughter]
enough for you peppas please
oh that's wrong we don't do this anymore
uh
here matching what do you mean what no
that's not what that's not what i mean
i wait you're are you from is this dude
from us
is this no it's not okay
uh your show must require an interview
you have no idea and prepare me i have
ticket here
let me fro no no no no idiot
idiotica
not enough you gotta be up to date you
gotta inform yourself
[Music]
you are [\h__\h]
nice hairstyle i mean honestly it's uh
dasai
that looks fine thanks dude at least one
proper
person as expected from aztoska people
oh yes i turned unity off i was that
smart yeah yeah
but like at what point should i get
naked
hopefully we'll get to that point hello
lenny what is the purpose of your trip
i'm so happy that the bulldog has opened
i will visit my son i have not seen him
in sex yes
the rest never say some of
no you [\h__\h] up you [\h__\h] up
girl i'm so sorry
interrogate you cannot enter your
singing spy diamond oh please
let me pass my son is still waiting oh
no
[Music]
you look scary you don't have a passport
answer me why you don't have a passport
how can you fly a
fly thingy when you have
to be used for the knife
nice cheeks you have really chubby
cheeks that's kind of cute can i pinch
them
i have a job here it will be sexy mom
sir
okay yeah indeed the end
of the body
names do not match uh i have two
different
that is a [\h__\h] but okay here please
what is this
oh actually that seems correct
i mean yeah looks fine actually
what no known alan yes
oh what is oh ah oh that would have been
like the second name
ah
well you have beautiful uh fingers
though so i don't know if you wanna
maybe
um let me take some photos of that
eventually yeah bye bye go now
the fingerprints match
oh that is so cute that looks like
amelia watson made it
still this country for sure what the
[\h__\h] is this
when i'm 100 sure that's [\h__\h] do i
really have to do the interrogation
thingy
[Music]
uh yeah name correct no i don't have to
do it okay
later i have to okay
seems fine expiration fine
thank you
next i doing fine i think i'm doing
quite well now i'm getting used to it to
my new job
no more hell alive only as doska
oh i can finish this one right let's
just stay two days two days yeah transit
uh-huh uh-huh
under the twelfth uh-huh uh-huh
uh-huh actually everything seems fine
do whatever the hell you want
[Music]
i don't get money for this one
the rent has gone up i don't have money
[\h__\h]
okay
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] no food man
republicans track star wonderful
murderer
oh let's remember that vince lestrade
remember that face
he can show up huh he's probably gonna
show up at my
thingy huh
okay thank you
let's go speed run i'm already trying to
be pretty fast though to be honest
you look like a handmaid
did you come from uh the handmaid's tale
oh oh yeah i already see something wrong
here what the hell is that
you're [\h__\h] me the document is about
no oh
no ah do i get money for raising people
hi oshio
pasta out of here get out of here
do you think
i feel like that's she's not gonna be
alive after this
only to visit i say three months correct
uh-huh
this is correct well name is correct
female
yeah huh oh
yeah i think this is fine
okay thank god we have someone correct
next up
to the user room you think they've been
sent to the user room yup
that is very scary all right
quick it's him how do i do this
[Music]
the newspaper newspaper newspaper
where's the newspaper
is this the newspaper
oh scared he's gonna shoot me
i don't even want to talk to him
immediately get him
look i did not kill her i was set up i
did not believe it
no you do not get anywhere close this
place
we did it we did it we detained him
where are my tips huh
okay what about you i am in transit
uh-huh
14 days uh-huh okay
seems fine to me no problem with you
missus
please enjoy your transit you will love
us oscar
expired what [\h__\h]
magic yeah
12 1983
two days nikolai
okay this one is fine this one is fine
wait he doesn't accept
he doesn't exactly look like nah look
pretty close it's just the hair
i'm paying attention i just want to stay
alive
looks good to me
you look funny yeah christians
transit yeah i remain for a couple days
yeah how many you idiot
14 days is not exactly you
kelly can i ask you about that a couple
days is not really
ah smart me
you put a couple weeks okay i guess
the rest is fine i think
we can let him in right
i think now that you corrected yourself
if i think it's fine if he corrects
herself
i mean he's he said it very vaguely a
couple days like what the hell does that
mean
hello nice shiny forehead can i write
something on it
come for visit 12 weeks yeah
[Music]
no
yeah probably ah yeah this one
that looks looks about right hopefully i
didn't [\h__\h] up again
top one no did i do something wrong
no it should be fine you guys are just
about talking about the forehead right
okay
hello another shiny forehead guy
tic-tac-toe let's go
i'll leave it to you guys i'm busy
working uh piotr have we finally when
did he what did you say
forever what the [\h__\h] no i'm not even
gonna ask
there there are no foreign
no no no no no i don't care my wife
she's coming
will you laugh i'll think about it
i [\h__\h] care for it what
you're not you're not you're the wife
you have a beard
i think you do sorry come back come back
come back i'll i'll let you in
oops oops i did it again
two days uh-huh
why'd you ask i mean well
sauce sorry
bye-bye can i get another one
whatever they want uh
i mean okay wait i guess it's uh this
one
[Music]
[\h__\h]
i'm going to live with my husband ah
okay
that is fine probably
audrey carrick oh yeah all right
um is that okay probably
[\h__\h] i lost the game didn't i
how did we do your son is sick and needs
medicine
move upgrading the space key to toggle
inspect mode uh-huh
wait we still have some money left we
can give them
food oh wait oh wait we're already
oh wait this this
ah this means we're giving it but then
we want the medicine
okay okay okay that sounds that sounds
fine
okay okay okay
becoming fewer immigrants taking jazz
from locals
vince lester apprehended apprehended
does that mean he got
taken like arrested or does it mean he's
free
no food
i gave them food food and medicine right
but no heat
you gotta rest it okay 28.
the mainstream member has used a special
under control immigrant label travelers
entering for work can require a valid
work pass
okay work visa no problem
what's it say okay
like we we're we're barely living oh
we're fast
work version of stay i still have a year
correct work correct dentistry correct
okay
uh until 1983
okay this is fine this i guess
i mean does this have to be ma no it
doesn't have to be much what
yeah yeah half a year that seems about
right
doesn't have to match okay i think i
think this one was fine
okay forged we mean forged
food service remain for half a year
six months no shut up
eight free tvs
[Music]
stamps can be forged how would i know
1983 this one is good
oh wait this one
they're unfortunate early in the game ah
okay later on we won't get that far
probably
eh my name name
in the map
do not trust him i am afraid he will
take my passport in front
he's in line today please okay dani
ludum
danny ludum petra
you look like the photo so
burn industry first let's go yeah
take it okay thank
please you the next of honor i want many
people in nastoska
world cup please thank you drafting
duration of stan i stay full yeah
okay
you have you look different on the
picture though
me lady where is the mole where's the
mole
also your nose looks not the same
you picked these different things i've
been cool
i don't think so please show me your
fingertips
oh that is very different do i still
have to do the other thing
uh-huh okay i know nothing about
decades
do it quick do it quick i don't want to
see her face ever again
she stole someone's passport or she
forced it i don't want to know i don't
care
hello oh hello what is this this time
everything's set no no you don't have
the idea
what do you mean what i know he's
he always is missing something what do
you which one do we do
enter entertainment
okay oh man you funny guy
oh you funny guy
i'll see you next time you always come
up with the funniest things my dear
friend
i think this will turn into a long long
long time
long term relationship you want me
man i need a boob mouse pad on my my
hand hurts
i don't know why i'm not using my
pickled boot mouse but i have one
two months work architecture
blah blah blah uh-huh you look you look
does does she look like yeah sure looks
about right
uh rp and hai han
1982 11
[Music]
dad
expired my lady i could not come too now
yeah that is not my problem
that is not my problem
you gotta have uh an up-to-date
permission
it's in the role book i can't do
anything about it my friend
hello hello [\h__\h] this [\h__\h]
i give you good girl on as good as
as you know my girl i don't think so i
have the best girl
also what the hell are you from really
oh they don't blurf correct
name wait oh my god oh my god
of course it says on my passport
well then we have to have a little talk
in the usual room my friend
i saw it i saw it the woman is safe
we saved her life guys we did it glory
to god
to kfp remain for a couple days two days
transit uh-huh
seven uh-huh markowski um 1982-12 uh-huh
right or is there anything else that he
needed
workers must have been trying but it's
not transit foreign
wait andrew no no it's repairment
wait i thought this was the working
permit no this is the enterprise yeah
then it's fine
you're done
looks fine to me
see no nothing coming up okay we saved
we saved we're safe
okay hello you you uh how long
two weeks that is correct okay
[Music]
yeah you guys see a problem
this trailer does not see a problem but
maybe that's because i have my eyes
closed
no correct here this one i think it's
fine
i think expired
no it's not expired this is fun
it's fine i don't see your problem sound
thank you please enjoy
you can go to disneyland or whatever can
you imagine disneyland and there's
must be a lot of fun god you i don't i
don't really like your
your your how do you call it sideburns
i don't like them also your name in here
is incorrect what the
freak i don't even think you can get
through that
name
was it the person i sent in but hey game
not oval
why is that [\h__\h] son always sick he
has the worst immunity system i've ever
seen
he went to disneyland
you know we still have money
all right we shall continue was that
elsa scripted
hmm
save for food oh too late now what did i
give i give i gave food and then
medicine huh
[Music]
and what did i give medicine and
something
that i gave heat oh oh oh
[\h__\h] oh man humans have anyone shut down
oh is that because i did
because i arrested that one dude
to facilitate facilitate facilitate more
for
inspections and search scanner system
has been installed in your booth thank
you
college and extremists are suspected in
yesterday's bombing okay search all
colettians
this seems like it was scripted because
now this co
ends up with this collection
currently pertinent entry in a group of
violating information
to enable wait so wait am i also allowed
to let in any collections
search them
ah currently discovered weapons and
contraband with roblox entry
okay so we search kolentians
that's what's happening okay
so where are you from korea
oh [\h__\h] two weeks sasuke
visit well okay how do i search you
all collections must be searched do i do
this and this
okay you have been selected for around
forever
get naked do it faster
can i have those photos i never i've
never been that far
oh my god oh that's when unity happens
huh
what do you get those pictures naked
nice body hey now
you know what seems fine
[Applause]
your name correct
okay the rest seems fine
oh wow thank you you can have the
picture as uh as a memory
nice nice memory of being in aztoska
right
getting naked right at the first time
you visit us
oh there's something's missing here when
you're from
what the hell you don't have a
entry permit first of all
what is that okay that is the answer to
that
that is all i need to know
peppas please thank you
still scout with buddy wonderful hi it's
lucas
lucas 1951
he got the same birthday as me he got it
was born on national fried chicken day
and and international kissing day i like
you sir
i like you you changed your hairstyle
though i
like the i don't know which one i like
more yo dude
same birthday it's taco kiana
i see no problem here
i see absolutely no oh right right
what's happening
i like him i feel a connection between
us too
invalid possible smuggler
excuse me what the hell
i guess the weight was suss magika
said i mean how how was i supposed to
judge that
78 i mean i don't know how
i guess that's 78 kilos seems fine
oh the way oh i didn't see that no hold
on
[Applause]
no penalty let's go we'll we'll live
properly now
i'll start sky again okay
52 okay f i mean i don't know i can't
really
judge but i guess i'll ask
it's it's a bit difficult matching oh
wait i guess i mean the name is female
yeah i mean
[Music]
oh god oh god i'm stressed out guys
i think it's okay
i'll probably
m
photo looks fine okay name
what do you mean the name was mine
look funny i like your mustache somebody
shady
i'm in transit to stay for 14 days
that is shady mr shady but only 80 to 12
uh huh
are you free uh
wait colettia
uh how do we do this again wait
uh is this the one
okay there we go you're basically like
this
congratulations you're the hunter versus
the customer
get those nudes hell yeah although i
don't really want you oh
wow nice flies damn he got good flies
what the [\h__\h]
shouldn't just deny him i know i know
weapons are
okay on this one
quick you can see of course i can see it
when you
entertain all right all right
10 grams oh i will i would like those
credits but no i can't cannot do
i'm not a dog i'm a phoenix that's the
first time someone calls me a dog
never been called a dog before i mean
sometimes sometimes i wish i was a dog
i'm coming to live for my
husband forever okay apparently that's
fine apparently that's the thing that we
do
boston
nine
is this fine it looks fine to me
i have no time
saint check city where
where city sauce
oh wait i need to um
wait a second now wait a second uh
uh we're probably uh
you shouldn't ah boston
i'm so confused
is there a typo in your passport
i have no idea what you're talking about
oh no
thank you guys you saved me
thank you next door
oh oh no the time is up again oh
[\h__\h] i feel like i barely made money
today
both again we just had this
one second wait i know wait that's
actually correct sorry sorry never mind
never mind
uh vincent my no 1940s
actually this one seems fine
expired it is
can i just deny him
okay
please people don't make me lose the
game
day seven your family needs medicine
blue green available okay
so uh i have no money
for food i have to give them medicine
are they going to die if i don't give
them medicine well then
i will prioritize my wife
[Music]
is this game over it's not
it's not yet yeah we're still continuing
i can't believe it we're still alive
badly sick needs the medicine
oh we can make more kids i can't i don't
know if i can get another oh i guess i
can also have another wife
never mind the colleges have an informal
complaint eh
a diplomat will arrive today for
high-level discussions automatic
searches of collections and stuff no
longer
excuse me diplomats require only a
passport and valid diplomatic
authorization to enter
oh
wait so i i can't i can't look at their
sexy bodies anymore
that's just sad that's just sad
what's the purpose of your trip sir my
presence has requested
ah you're the diplomat wait but uh
you have the other state all the
research authorization
but
oh i guess i guess that's is that enough
didn't it say something like one more
thing
document must have a sale it has a seal
i guess this is the seal that's enough
all right then passport number is
correct wikia name is correct okay
i'll give you this one chance but you
can get out of the city immediately
because i don't like diplomats
you guys think you're special or
something
no special trademark here in nastoska
okay transit uh natanya vinceva
let me check real quick
uh for republia
okay expired got them you guys see this
way too fast why should i ask her about
it
wait no wait i wish i could
switch pages while i'm at it
okay uh
[Music]
ah i wait i i just have to do the clock
okay okay
discrepancy interrogate
what that is my mistake i just renewed
it
well at least she admits her mistake
unless she's
nice i guess
okay you're too slow i don't need to
check if this references yet okay
just deny okay okay oh hello well then
if i just didn't need to deny then
we do this quickly
okay sorry
when i have more time one more money we
can talk more haha no time for laughing
this is not funny you think this is
a decent joke toyo is this a choctaw
twenty antegria where the hell is that
remain for a few weeks i guess one month
is a few weeks
is it uh alexandra
mochina
wait i don't have to do it right
[Applause]
it's invalid next
what is this i've never seen this before
what the hell
presents was requested you too huh oh
briston
uh i guess yeah you have this uh
mm-hmm
those guys there i'm gonna need it for
later oh my god but okay this seems
the name is fine price pass but not
being correct dude
i saw it oh
i know nothing about this impasta
you are a fool
and the
[Music]
for 14 days we said okay jc ledovs
december 1982
expired me lady
what do you have to say
and id wonderful chance
chance um 58 kilo transtessa
1983 little verse correct correct
correct
photo seems alright since i
check the city oh no but i didn't get
anything okay we're fine
oh
66 kilo 1942
directs okay i'll check the city now or
or fake von
is correct mail photo is okay
what the dude what do you mean what do
you mean the dude
what do you mean the dude deny him the
cop wants
how do you know
eh he's that he's the guy how did you
know
oh wait oh
oh my god eh so a coke in us those guys
looking what do you mean matching yeah
i'm matching data but i guess i just
does this count as the night is the
newest stamp the one that matters
it read quickly oh i gave it to him
oh yeah this great country poisoned by
corrupt leaders was
raw has made government greedy and
paranoid you have seen for yourself
help us free us those who are checking
the order of it
so anyway i you have something
what is this oh this one was clear for
entry
oh oh
oh okay oh [\h__\h]
i thought i thought he was so salsa you
wouldn't want
15 okay
do we do we haven't fed them in years
i can't find medicine for everyone
though
whatever i don't care about them upgrade
both
guess i'll die is that really worth it
space key to toggle inspect mode
do i really care about that
i don't really say maybe we save some
money
i can't save everyone okay let's keep
the five dollars
or i need money over medicine
without i will be a waste ah
and someone said it only matters if
they're very sick is that true
people die when they don't eat you
deserve if you're fast enough for
[\h__\h] repel i'm not really fast enough
though
um
[Music]
how about that let's
let's see what happens i mean i don't
mind living on my own
we could have heat though um
now let's save would i die
oh my god december first oh
okay oh my god this is crazy what is
this
an uncomfortable engine of the ministry
of information has been compromised the
minister of admission has offered its
services as liaison
my impossible drop today what on the
cover asian
i don't understand dad but okay you guys
tell me when it's happening
i'm useless hello nice hat
are you just spying are we direct what
no
i am god here my name is kolensk they
told me i get good position
then sent me here this is thanks i get
now they pay me almost nothing
they pay us all as much yes but look
i don't have time to talk that much i
get a small bonus when you detain people
more you detain more they give me for
processing
but this is not fair right you should
get something too so i fix this problem
i give you five credits from for my
bonus for
every two people you did sounds like a
good deal to me i give money to you
after i get paid
let us make the best of this yeah
is he french okay sounds good to me we
got more money
cool hello
what is the purpose of your trip sir
i'm visiting your relatives i remain for
30 days
okay uh well i don't know what to do is
iron
gaiden
25 yeah yeah seems okay
don't you think it's okay i think it's
okay but we can check the city
hi hon i've heard about it before though
uh
what is this what is this import
hi han
so offensive
i feel like he looked
oh come on
shiny head oh
what did you just say i don't i didn't
listen
stay for the days visit okay
oh okay kuduski
great rapid uh
united federation
great rapid uh-huh 1947
um yeah i think
i think this dude is fine
well you're trying to tell me that this
dude is female
i don't think so
okay this is a lady i have not much time
you must hold on to this um
keep that save today i am being followed
by an emphasize
they pretend to be from the ministry of
information but it is a lie if they ask
for documents give these instead
okay if they ask for documents right
side and what about the left side though
you didn't tell me what to do with the
left side
making habits of less circle what what
what
i don't understand where's
[Music]
experience
what did you just say okay
yeah sure we're probably uh true glory
and probably fun i've heard it before
name
okay
yeah yeah
oh god i hope this is okay
ah that's so confusing it gets like
really confusing
transit two days okay kr
that's where it starts to matter to do
uh this interrogation right because i
get credits for detaining and you can
only detain if you don't turn them down
immediately but you're actually
interrogated
hello are you
stupid ah
[Music]
what what does this mean so i give you
one of these but which one
what they are huh which the right one
okay and i get i get to take the money
thank you is this legal
hold it's taking me i'm in transit
every couple weeks i mean that's two
weeks do we ask about that
let's try
matching okay well then never mind keem
neo sandman
[Music]
uh
wait so there's a couple trenton
he said transit ah well transit is not
okay indeed my friends indeed
can we make money again come on give me
that give me that
this is quick that doesn't count you
can't just
okay okay i guess
[Music]
okay okay
you made a mistake i forgive i forget
i guess oh no
yep why does it why do i hear white
noise
no this is normal i thought he was going
to drop a bump
diplomatic envoy
you are an imposter
i see it very clearly it must be a
mistake the document
no no no give me the money give me those
credits
what the hell are your eyebrows that
those look ridiculous
did you shave them is that what that's
supposed to be 30 days visit did you say
visit what did you say transit
visit it okay well i feel like your
eyebrows are a crime
but besides that you look all right
f true gloria and probably probably
yeah i guess actually that looks fine i
want to ask you about your eyebrows but
i guess it's none of my business
gender female yeah yeah look at look at
her
just look at her
[Music]
forever i don't know it sounds
ridiculous to me but okay
oh no they're leaving oh no
it's over twelve a little enterprise
okay it seems okay we can let her in
right
we let her in please come in come in
maybe we got enough money to to give
some food for once
very sick oh [\h__\h] we'll dive about
medicine before no i don't care about
the booth upgrade
how much money do we have
[Music]
huh
i misunderstood
[Music]
wait how much money do i have
wait i have 15 plus 15 plus 10 right
it's marked on huh
oh it's all marked already
ah oh
well then we're good right
oh okay oh i can't believe we actually
made it
oh my god i want to thank my momma
and my cats and my brother and my sister
and i swear i'm so happy that i've come
so far
i wouldn't have come so far if it wasn't
for the chats to be honest my family had
nothing to do with it
but i just want to say thank you anyway
because it means a lot to me
it's a very special day for me and i'm
very emotional today
[Music]
but i will not give up i will continue
growing my path and do my best to make
everyone proud of me
no but that's that's that's all i wanted
to say thank you very much for ever
coming to my cat talk thank you
[Music]
let's go let's detain some people
attack its own roundup disappears
this appearance is blamed on faulty
evidence oh whatever
let's go it's every second
all right who's that who's that who's
that
you guys remember i forgot about that oh
yes we don't have time guys be serious
be serious
the divisional authority of east
christian operations will visit today
maintain your best behavior what
what do i care why do i still have this
one
nice hat what free oh
you are inspector here that makes you my
responsibility
you have received 10 citations perhaps
it was mistake to rely on notary let
this motivate you
claude yo just as i was making my speech
this is beautiful
i'm so proud i'm gonna put the hang on
yes i will hang you know my
cowboy he calls on the wall you know
does he now
visiting only two weeks what wait you
where's where's your [\h__\h] passport
you idiot
oh my god
talk to me what is stupid
denied boy
here you can have that have fun in your
home country
if you can't even afford a flight back
dude hello
you i see your face for the first time
who are you
i'm from asda you look cute
85 kilo okay
i'm so sorry about your passport is
expired
i'm oh wait i should ask you about that
huh
looks like a raccoon i just renewed
wait why can't i not detain those people
anymore i want the money
oh bye boy i don't know how you ever
gonna get back i guess you gotta go to
the embassy i guess that's how it works
see you later
hello milady i got the visit
uh i remained for three months
yeah but you also don't have a freaking
basketball are you guys
[\h__\h] me or what what is bad
are you guys freaking idiotically
oh my god there's oh does no one take
this
you cannot leave it all right i'll
continue i'm excited i get extra money
for that
i will explode like what's that guy your
favorite
kill her immediately
immigrating forever as i thought
okay lyra lay cute name you got both
down
y'all mm-hmm um oh good
oh good da boo that's your boy
hopefully hope
fiction looks different i guess a little
bit
yeah that was close that was close that
was
these ears have been cruel all right i
guess so
it's true it's true the years have been
cruel no known ally
ali is um that looks different to me
nothing just close your eyes and then
we'll all be good say goodbye to your
mommy
hello belka
oh um
do you guys want to ask about this
because i'm not sure
matching oh okay just wondering
you know
oh looks fine
check city
okay uh regional map
uh
bye
next up we got no situations yet guys
but the day has just begun
wait what is this supposed to tell me
something
steve stephanie
[Applause]
okay whatever that means to me i don't
know stephanie just remember stephanie
uh hello some sus things are happening
oh
you are in any way um missing some
things
uh what about this huh
where is entrepreneur beach sorry i have
it here okay oh my god
leilani
but they said they said they're coming
tomorrow or something like that right
enter
no time to waste could not i don't i
don't care
i don't care about your private things
whatever
go home what
in here stephanie and me kyle stephanie
and mikhail
stephanie and me kyle stephanie and
mikhail
burn it into my brain okay work but oh
we didn't have this one for a while
stephanie and mikhail stephanie and
mikayla
stephanie and michael elena romanovska
spaceball dentistry megarus um nsl
nptel when you're uh ah enterprise okay
until oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
probably fine face okay f okay
thank you have fun working name
[Applause]
different
how did i not see that passing through
yeah yeah dude you're missing something
here something very
important can you not think of it by
yourself
oh guys
my god these people are absolutely
useless
did i not unders no one more please
no no i couldn't do so many people
but stephanie and me kyle
[Music]
your family's medicine no they don't
need it right away let's see
oh
wait i don't understand can i undo
this is uh is it automatically selected
i want to give them photo
and i uh can i unselect it
[Music]
i
i still wanna i still understand this
[Music]
oh wait ah wait this one is already
selected
always ah so look out food is already
well then it's fun yeah okay this is
what i want
i want them to have food right or do i
want to
have them i guess we could do
heat and then some medicine
uh what's better what's better
you need enough money to avoid it
they'll sleep it off and honestly like
don't be so sensitive
heat and meds is better
i cannot get everyone uh healthy though
but i don't care about these two
[Music]
but they're not very sick so
they had food yes true okay
but every time i get the medicine
they're just sick again next time
how about we save how about we save all
of the money
smart kiana we save all the money for
next time
and then give them food heat and
medicine
dave how can i save
is there an option to save uh you mean
save the money okay
i think i think that is probably the
smartest decision
[Music]
okay fast at ministry administrative
admission
and 10 grand domestic spying exposed
exposed
december 3rd 1982 let's go
you see normally i don't really like
these simplistic games with these kind
of graphics but this one is just fun and
i don't know it has these vibes
it's just fascinating inspector a
breaking at
mla offices may have compromised our
document ceiling plates
what nothing important was stolen but
intelligence such as counterfeiters have
already begun foraging official ososcon
documents oh
[\h__\h] double check that required
documents contain valid seals
ah correlate missing or wrong seals
you mean dennis against the appropriate
entries
okay okay
i don't trust myself with doing that
but let's go and where was stephanie and
mikhail
this one is not it
one month indeed one month visit
uh passport number correct name
correct and correct glory and in
integria seems about
right but i'll check it 105 kilo that's
what you look like
um and tag rina
glorian all right yeah
i shall let you pass right yeah yeah
no no no the dates are fine too seal
and check how can i undo it
can i undo it which er
what seal like this one or the one on
the passport
this one god damn it okay
i can't undo it okay we can get one
situation that's all right
okay
that one on the work permit okay it has
to be
one of those
hello georgie look at that good papers
was not easy i believe
i believe you uh today's trends
i'm just probably wrong again
oh what did we ask him
he's from
let him in no
i'm not [\h__\h] around today um
what seems to be the issue here
expired passport no it's not expired
his papers are good no way
he's clean [\h__\h] guys you're
bullshitting me let's see
i'll i'll get my my pen my finger again
right
you take this what he was actually good
for once
i got something special i got a b i
gotta be faster yeah
you did it i thought you're like a
character that never gets in
hmm i was suspecting uh
you too much what's your name
rebecca uh-huh i'm gonna try and take
two days
i need to uh
there is a problem here mises you have a
really cute face but i cannot let you
[Music]
win
oh hello i know you good morning good
morning
yeah you retained four people uh-huh i
did
bonuses good baby okay this is not
enough
yes i know so my wife is sick now
neighbor spreads the flow
this is what is left after the medicine
priorities
i'll give you words next time yeah you
better otherwise i'll kill you
maybe to take more people to make it
easier okay
next stop wasting my time
uh visiting your friends how long
couple months oh god 98 to 12.
terrorist jessica um skull upper stone
now the the the thingy though the thing
um
aubriston like this is the wrong seal
right
like are we talking about this seal
this one let's ask
no correlation hmm what's your
yes one more pink one
ah what still is correct
okay i don't understand what i'm
supposed to look
at at the end of the book
ah one of those two oh okay okay okay
okay it has to be one of those two okay
okay that's easy i can remember that
oh i've seen your face before
what do i do what do i do what do i do
what do i do well first of all you're
missing some documents dude
you're missing uh
should i let him in don't let it let it
i don't wanna
are you guys trying to make me lose the
game
my choice
to the ending anyway i'm way too bad at
this game
getting ready forever okay sounds good
don't don't tell me i messed up here
it seems fine to me
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
give me one more give me one more give
me one more give me one more give me one
more
give me one more i need money
okay
okay go away go away
guess i have to ask you about this [\h__\h]
too uh
hi
well
what do you mean i'll give you the thing
back okay uh
it's quiet he's frightening
can i tell my superior about it or am i
the only oh god very sick oh dear
but we saved money we saved money guys
a strange man brought money unchecked to
burn it
a bryce only five dollars ah no wait i
think if
this one i should probably get rid of
that huh
yeah oh i could afford so much money
oh
take it use it this time
is it okay to keep it once but like
if i don't then
wait um
[Music]
my wife is okay
can i let no one die at all
it's my choice again is it like whatever
that i want to be corrupt or not
i don't want to be corrupt
i don't want to be crap but yeah uh
pretty much if one of them dies the game
over okay
forget the uncle yeah i mean why do i
care about the uncle and the
mother-in-law
ah well okay so we still have ten
[Music]
so heat or or
food wait but if i don't give them heat
they're just gonna be sick again no
[Music]
i guess when it says very hungry that's
the last moment when they wanna
have uh can it also say very cold
can they be very cold and very sick and
very hungry like they can be very sick
or or is that already the maximum
yes yes they can
yell again welcome to the membership
thank you
oh
[Music]
take the money no way
i'll just
um
[Music]
i feel like i feel like this is gonna be
over soon
example let's go
oh hello good morning inspector
you are healthy today yes i have just a
few questions for you
yeah we think suspicious group attempts
to serve
trouble i think some member entered this
checkpoint
so we come to talk to you yeah yeah
indeed actually
have you seen anything like this
yes yes yes yes
can you give us here
how do i keep how do i keep
yes very good please return my virgin
paper
okay okay okay you make her really
nervous here sir
this group is very dangerous if you see
any clearance ring report immediately
okay
oh wait i can oh i can actually have it
ah that was a close one
could that have ended the game somehow
hello handmaid's tale lady
that was close
[Laughter]
61 uh-huh 1947 1947 did of course
you know well seems okay to me
is is there a orbit come on there
probably
yeah i think you are
okay
[Music]
you are getting used to this what is
this
stay two days uh-huh 1982-12 of
christmas
okay um lilly
lilly you're just
honestly you look fine what
it's the right seal
the seal is correct i checked
was i was i good was i good
are you proud of me for jackie
my style oh my god
let's go uh name correct
date of birth correct 88 correct
or even correct
face correct gender correct
let's go
do me a favor give my card to any
engineers you meet oh
okay i guess why not so many cards
pay five credit yes let's go let's go
we have a chance to survive guys hello
thank you uh you're missing some things
oh those seals also
you are missing something what is this
by the way oh
oh wait oh sorry i'm stressed out it's
okay
students in foreign
okay how about did you originally said
i say a few months visit visit visit
98 okay the date is okay uh
aza hudson correct face seems about
right yeah
yeah okay you better cause me no trouble
couple two few free is that really so it
seemed fine
still no situations situations
situations
transit two days uh-huh
wait the seal the seal is the seal
correct
documents
yes it is correct that's fine
nothing expired your
mail face okay you're good to go buddy
oh my god oh my god this one what excuse
me
did you just talk about my about my seal
papers please
68 a date of birth
correct name correct
sounds very very awesome australian
um i think a problem here
what do you guys think
1983 yo
district check yeah this drink is fine
i remember that district oh my god we're
going smoothly okay
there we go engineer
should we first should we take some time
here have this card
is this it doesn't matter just look at
it later uh
yeah hiring 1983 online
enter by okay work oh thank you
xp samantha lundberg
the seal
is crap okay good to go you better call
that dude
i mean it's kind of weird that i'm
participating in that
still no fantasy oh my god no petties
let's go
wow full beard how long does it take you
to grow that huh
i guess that's probably pretty an
impressive thing 30 days okay wait let
me check the seal
circle okay correct uh this seal
are you engineer no aviation okay the
sale is okay two
and correct
did you say one month yeah huh
this is all fine your name no naming
great
yo dude you think you can fool me
matching oh i guess it is mushroom
i ride it the other way around oh but
wait what about the city outer grouse in
antegria
where is integria
[Music]
you are missing something very important
no matter if you come for a visit
you see i i hope you have it with you
i do no what happened what just happened
no
what's that scripted
[Music]
again i get money i want
i will not pay the money
2000 no no
no i cannot take very sick oh my god
why are the i just gave them medicine
my family is dying
[Music]
the seal
i don't want to think
don't you
[Music]
uh i'm scared i know
i won't take it
another bumble slips through immigrant
screening falls
i'm doing my best here was doing so well
oh man the symbol theft
okay the new director is unsatisfied
with the level of scrutiny afforded to
foreigners from today and forward all
foreign interns must present a recent
identity supplement
listing wait height and appearance the
rulebook documents chapter have been
updated
foreign entrance okay
well then we shall continue
yeah today's a number of those people
gonna come right
yeah oh identity supplement
i remain for one month okay expiration
date
almost expired almost short light hair
yeah thumb how do i
do i have to check his thumb
how do i
oh i i just okay
[Music]
only prince of something is us okay
tecla
giggly yellow that is correct your
passport number is correct visit one
month what did you say
okay um
you seem fine to me integria the the
permit the thingy it looks fine to me
too i think i've seen it before
tick-tock tick-tock
please don't be terrorized please don't
be a terrorist
good boy i'll call you goodbye give your
head pat's even if you want
glasses uh-huh
a 76 kilo okay three months
visit mhm the name is correct
the thing is correct
yeah glasses is not such a good expired
ah this one is expired oh my god
thank you
wow the hell you're trying to fool me
again you don't want me to get game over
i was busy what kind of excuse is that
name
oh hello good morning
yeah you are not detaining enough yeah i
was
i was trying to detain people yesterday
but
i'm getting more to share part of my
bone detail
don't try but yesterday everyone is
doing so well
is that orangey papers please
visit short hair but you have long hair
currently
oh kind of sucks
also again very disgusting eyebrows
how can you say what
does your hair grow that fast
oh sorry okay
they are actually correct so i guess
i guess that's fine
let me take a look at the this thing
yeah okay
okay okay i guess your hair just really
compare them anyway oh where is it where
is it
okay
matching so
i you have to tell me what shampoo you
are using though
what do you want me to do i'll give you
this
okay i'm so slow i'm so slow
panic
visit friends long hair i i can't really
tell from your bun uh
not expired though but i will ask you
about this
matching if you say so 49
and uh you'll you don't really look like
you're doing the picture okay
orange
[Music]
enter bye oh yeah
tell me about it what's your excuse busy
can i entertain you please
why can't i not detain you
i wanna entertain you how do i entertain
oopsie
how do i detain them at this level
goddammit i felt like it offers me to no
you know the button usually comes up eh
ice kickers do what the hell is this
hang on the wall okay
you're missing some things though yeah i
should have detained him
uh maybe we can detain this dude
and you don't have a entry pyramid
oh wait you're from astorza you don't
have a
citizen card
i know man i told you it was stolen come
on let me throw
nah so
does he not get detained i don't
understand
then we just do this
i'm gonna tell coach
i don't care i don't play that stupid
soccer game
okay engineering what are we looking for
engineering
here take this what is this
it's very special bulb tear what is that
uh i guess bob you know okay again
okay did you not tell me couple days six
months that is
unfortunately very different
will you correct yourself how can you
make that mistake though stay half a
year
okay in that case
expiration date it's fine the door
ah this is this is stressful
let's look at the at the
the these thingies this one is correct
and this one also
you know what i don't really have the
time so whatever
just go away
short hair i guess you can call that
short hair
1982 one okay end of december that's
fine
the thingy is fine this one is fine
uh your name fine helena um
passport number fine okay
i think well you gave me a lot of stuff
here
sealed the seal was fine it looked fine
to me
what oh
who is you i am in transit goatee
wait goatee is that oh is that a is that
a
uh i wanna want a beard why does that
need to get only for you yourself and
just make it harder and harder why him
it already ended oh my god
there's no time expiration not
experience not explore inspired
name is correct uh
okay she seems fine to me wait colettia
though i'm i can't search for
collections anymore
was i supposed to do anything else with
them check the city
uh
outer grouse yo yo
[Music]
oh
but i have a bad feeling anyway when it
comes to money oh my god very sick
everyone very sick
but no money this time eh
okay i can't give food but i can heal
everyone which will just mean that next
time they'll also be sick again
they're not cold yeah
wait what i'm not wait oh
oh god okay
we're really we really have to detain
people wait no don't upgrade bull
why would i upgrade boom i can't really
use that anyways
don't need the booth i'll keep the five
dollars
because i need them urgently
okay upgrade makes this pasta
really really really though
uh criminals safety haven
no no no no no no no you got it wrong
i'll do my best as those guys are very
safe country the safest country on earth
believe me you can leave your phone
uh on your seat in the train and people
will give it to you
don't worry uh
has requested our support daily
bulletins will now contain a listing of
the top three most wanted international
criminals
check faces against entrance oh my god
you're kidding me this is getting so
difficult but this
this place is easy to remember this one
i actually too
yeah i guess you're actually fairly easy
to remember
okay can i put that somewhere
let's go
open up hello
wait you actually look like that
i don't i don't even want to listen to
you
that was fast one down we have some
classes for you
let me throw you will regret it hell now
get out of here get out of here
criminals what are you saying
uh you're one of the most wanted
criminals y'all huh
those twin tails are sus your face is
scary but you're not wanted short curly
hair i guess
yeah it's curly it's curly they stay a
couple days
did you say transit or visit transit
okay
so uh what do we have 1982 12 8 okay
nine into 12 18
okay
x9 uh andrew sucker love mm-hmm
let's look at the
the seal is correct okay
yeah uh i've heard of the city too
so this one is probably fine
that was fast let's go legit
he's a legit dude i want more like you
but also
detain some people united federation
uh short corrupt here okay so remain for
a few weeks
few weeks visiting all right
already kyle his name is
there yeah there is a discrepancy
what is the excuse for that i have two
different names all right we'll see
about that
we never had someone actually say the
truth about that
and as we can see here the fingerprints
are actually correct but there is no
known la
lies what do you mean no correlation
and do i just what do i do
and there we go there's no record of
this game please let me prove now
get out of here get out of here no
[\h__\h] around with takanasu kiana
i'm the best sheriff in town all right
alexander
engineer oh thank god why are these
tickets where does it why the tickets
remain for a year okay okay
take this yeah they're hiring good job
good job good stuff work one year and
then
12.99 enter by
uh alexander reed hi han
the permit seal looks alright 87 looks
alright
nothing is expired good vision what wait
a second
no okay the picture looks kind of
different though
your eyes are so okay i guess it's bad
lighting in here
but good vision what the [\h__\h] does that
mean
sorry just because he's not wearing
glasses
what the hell does that mean
this better be fine
you found about this guy was special
all right
well it's a visit remain for two months
widow's peak what does that mean
what's a widow's peak
hey what does that mean 12 16
two months visit martin flowing
okay 79 okay it's hairstyle
oh okay i see uh
we're having some communication issues
here
and the seal looks light
the seals ice
everything's fine honestly kolechia
makes me feel a bit
uh wait let's let's let's see
we better check because you gotta be
obsessed with colettia vador
okay you seem fine i hope i don't regret
it
let's stop is you you look exactly you
don't we don't even have to talk about
this
visiting are you i think you want to do
some crimey stuff
we welcome only good people only the
good people
not the crime people we have one more to
detain
georgie no i thought you were you made
me happy i made it please give
why are we detaining him though
i don't know why he seems kind of mean
oh he gave me two oh he gave me two
passwords oh
i didn't even realize i felt that wasn't
very
fair a small head okay 99 12 15.
um that's your result
the picture indeed
oh this does not look like you it is an
old picture
[Music]
could be true could be true you never
know
i guess then it should be fine
yeah um
if the fingerprints are fine then
huh got it okay
next time the stage is yours
present yourself to me show me your
talents show me what you got show me
what you got
a glorion angry stephanie if i was
friends but only two weeks name is
correct
possibly number correct expiration date
correct correct
okay let's just look at the city i think
that should be fine i've seen it before
antegria glorion okay face is okay
she's the one what i mean
oh stephanie oh but i don't want to
let her in
because of this
but how do i detain her though need the
supplement
what was that again ah
where's your idea supplement what is the
supplement
all right then uh how do i detain her
i don't think i can
huh yeah i can't
yeah i don't know how you can't detain
food okay that's what i thought all
right next one
oh the bed look
[Music]
no give me one well at least you
couldn't come because i closed right
good timing
good timing i guess they're against the
[\h__\h] sick
well we're still going we're all
suffering but we're still going
i'm moving hi
okay smoky came to support me
did i upgrade oh [\h__\h] but at least it's
okay
wait but that means we might be short on
five dollars next time
we we detained a lot of people we're
gonna get extra money
what does the upgrade do though i gotta
press space right to do something
break for spinal surgery perfected only
possible
are people gonna try to come because we
have the spinal surgery perfected
[Music]
december seventh 1992
did you get it on there gotta nine
wanted criminals all different people
this time okay
that's it that's it no no letter
okay i'll wait
oh no no that's really it that's it
hello sir you are missing a lot of
documents are you kidding me
id card please
i have it here all right all right okay
do we need anything else for citizens by
now no
65 ah i saw that immediately like with
with my eagle's eye phoenix eye
you have been too late for a random
search
let's look at you your body show me
oh i don't need what the hell that's so
useless
huh you got nothing on him though
so well
i guess it's okay i guess he just yeah
ate a bit more
than usually sorry for um i don't know i
guess that was kind of rude for me
sorry um besides that you seem
oh almost same birthday he seems okay
yeah i gotta check safety first that's
right you can have your new
nude picture give it to your girlfriend
or whatever
hello sir you have a big beard they have
to ask
what the [\h__\h] what do i do what if
that's a bomb
probably
help me take this take it
open it dude
but not even at this point it's a purge
one
cut the wise okay uh one
two
three four okay
okay if you i
thank you thank you my family is dying
oh my god they take it very lightly huh
and i i let in one one people one person
with a wrong seal and you
you punch the [\h__\h] out of me okay
uh remain for two months for work okay
uh are you an engineer now surveying
surveillance
but that alone sounds like you're a spy
though
what it you sound like a spy
12 10 12 39
um tara obon kolechia
male
true why do you
ask i mean because of reasons all right
like look
wow wow
[Music]
i'm sorry for intruding your privacy
um i mean what what
what
what you have to say about that please
let me hear the day
honestly i could still be a male but
okay
ah let's see that'll be further
investigation i just can't show you
naked on on
on screen you know uh
i remain for until i die
what do you mean
are you just joking 90 days okay
that's kind of scary man all right let's
look at the seals
gotta be very strict on it
the seal is correct
and um and the seal is correct okay
nikolai
also can engineer
94 the date is correct okay
i think you're fine thank you i hope i
get some extras please please tell the
dude that
uh oh
please tell the dude that you want to
work for him
my family is dying is that not important
to you
okay wait over here i guess so transit
will be a couple days
two days so password i'm a correct the
name
correct f correct
12 25 fine ah expired
passport though i'm so sorry but i can't
let you
in tip typographical era
yeah that is pretty much impossible
that sounds sus
next one please
what if i don't what if i don't
here take this what if i don't
what if i don't i don't wanna okay
we cannot succeed without your help when
aston scott was born the order fulfilled
same role as today
when tyranny ends we will disappear
again
i don't know what that means can you can
you read that to me in german
i don't understand you can't talk in
like griddles with me
i don't understand but in any case you
cannot
make me into a terrorist i will always
be
real okay so what did you just say
sorry i wasn't listening couple days
transit
okay 12 22 12 15
alec do you look like one of those dudes
no oh my god we're running out of time
but you don't have dark hair
quick okay
for sure i don't have time
quick
okay let's take a look uh
there are those are not the same
let me detain you
all right oh
i'm not even you're a diplomatic i do
not believe a word you say
call your attorney or whatever
oh no it's over all right let's see how
much money we made
oh i want my bonus from the detainations
and the engineer thingies where's my
bonus
45.
oh
[Music]
okay grab my bonuses
where are my bonuses
[Music]
okay but we're still we are still alive
guys
[Music]
maybe next time okay okay
the guard is scamming me it feels like
it
ministries fight over staff qualified
guard soldiers in demand
alrighty december 8 1982
you know i honestly thought that i was
gonna go game over
super soon so i didn't think that get in
the stream would be so long already
let's see the ministry of justice has
appropriated the under guard detail you
are now responsible for controlling
twice
what pride can be used to tranquilize a
gun once an alarm has been raised
receive a bonus force i've it like
people can just walk by and
i will then do something
uh a smaller bonus is provided for
firing on but missing your target
i have to shoot people how do i even use
that where do i put that
okay
let's let's go use kit
why do i use it to read the whole thing
wait what oh my god thank you
15 or 5 10 15.
you drop off money at your home instead
every other night oh thank god when
alarm sounds
drop key on tumblr where is that it will
only show up when
it's happening select gun aim fire okay
time is short
act fast one of the criminals okay yummy
next let's go tiana
there's so much information now leonard
blah blah blah
not expired not
expired not expired
70s
a few kilos extra
can you explain that to me sir
please turn towards the scanner get
naked
take off your clothes show me what's
underneath
oil nice body oh nothing
all right then i guess it's good
that's okay then wait lauren does though
i don't know man
can i look good overstan
okay it's correct thank you for your
patience bye bye
i guess a few few kilos are not that's
us huh
purpose of your trip please move here oh
really probably above there
indeed saw your healing immigrate
forever
correct 12 11 very
very close but okay 60 kilo correct
hi hon fine let's look at the seal the
seal is
fine i think
but i'll check i'll be extra exact
ah wait this one
i han female yeah i think
i think but we can ask
matching see
don't be so doubtful
okay you're missing some documents
colettia your papers are missing please
surgery i mean
no no
do i have to do the thingy
uh here this one for example
you also you you you what do you call
that you bribed me
okay i can't i cannot detain her for
bribing me
i take the money oh [\h__\h]
i get one situation i guess that's true
oh wait can i detain her and keep the
money
can i do that let's try
okay let's see does that look like
wait a second 12 weeks you're not
wearing uh
the hat in the picture but i guess
that's okay does that person look like
any of them
no karen azolas
three months
uh-huh 12 19 12 14.
[Music]
uh
matching okay i mean
on that picture that looks such though
looks like the top person yeah
no
[Music]
46 actually he looks fine collecting of
the door
let's just try to let him in strong
cheekbones
indeed yabby i have a feeling that we're
gonna we're about to shoot someone
[Music]
nice glasses i am back how many
engineers did you meet i got you i got
four calls
uh three were civil engineers usually i
need mechanicals
anyway last night is very sharp thanks
to him
oh my god we're thank you
astorska 89
yeah he's fine right he's good oh thank
god
you're a good man
you remind me of a good friend 90 days
fine arts
uh what like
this twelve six oh yeah
yeah oh yeah yeah
no no this one with this one please
i'm not even using the upgrade guys
i could not come until now well that is
not my business
you want an only chance to get into this
beautiful country research okay
oh
[Music]
got him we got so much money
sharpshooter bonus 20. yo 55.
no oh my god
but i gave them medicine
but i got so much money but
at what cost
i'm what did i do
i i even have leftovers
[Music]
can i not revive them
well that's not fair that's not fair
how how how cruel is that
[Music]
uh hi callie yo dude what's up what's up
uh so i have my wife and my son
and my uncle died i don't know can you
maybe do something about that
yeah no i'm a hiatus you know
um nothing really i can do about that
dude uh you know i i really like
i would love to help your dog but yeah
i'm
uh hi just maybe ask my my friend uh
who's still working there i don't have
his phone number but
you can call uh zero zero zero six six
six
uh now you might reach my uh my friend
here
try that but i can't really help you to
be honest
i thought i could count on you kelly
sorry i got no time i'm going to record
some songs
uh what does that mean
no wait
no i worked so hard
the ministry of labor focused on us
those called futures future girl growth
did i saves at some point workers are
expected to support large healthy
families
no your position will be felt by someone
more appropriate
[Music]
hey i didn't buy what the [\h__\h] do you
mean
i found it
[Music]
but i mean there was already some people
dead though
is there like can i not continue
i can't continue stay 16
is that actually um
like the latest point where i left off
[Music]
like right before they died
oh
back one day
okay okay i thought it would bring me
back to the very beginning that's nice
okay
okay you know what we'll not continue
today
but maybe at some point
i wonder how much more there is to the
game though
[Music]
oh
we did much longer than expected i'm
halfway through
then we can do one more one more stream
maybe maybe
maybe we'll get there in the next stream
i i didn't want to stream too long today
anyway so we'll read some super chats
and uh then i'll go to sleep sleep
if that's okay with y'all
because of your help though
yeah thank you we'll allow it
can i uh go to an idol meeting for two
minutes now
is that okay i need to i need to
let something out
i i i need to go to an idol meeting i
need to tell jago
what i really think about all of this
[Laughter]
i need to ask him if he wants to open up
whole life of stotsuka
[Music]
okay then give me two minutes and i'll
be back okay
particularly
okay
that was fun
[Music]
beautiful
boo
i don't know what that is
actually kind of cute don't you think
let me fix the chat
[Music]
again
and my head my my head very shiny
and because i put gravy on it
please don't pet nothing
[Music]
if you try to head pet i bite your hand
nom nom nom nom nom nom
chin scratch i'm not a cat no
but i don't like hugs i like hugs very
much i'm a very huggy person
even in japan i i hug
people very often and they were very
irritated by it
very confused oh
god don't you dare help at me
is it safe to hug the phoenix yeah you
just gotta turn off the
the firewall gotta turn off the firewall
oh wait we're funny today
[Music]
sorry i'm trying to get the cat hairs
out of my face
head butts and hell no what the hell why
would i like that
yo it's all
let's get the super jets fortunately
fortunately indeed we
only have to read the ones
from today
[Music]
you know i was thinking so long today
about what to play today
and unfortunately it was decided very
very giddy idiot otherwise i would have
done a q a or a karaoke or something
uh but i i there was also like a
slight chance that i would have done the
test play today which
ended up being private but anyway i was
so
waiting for the schedule so um i
couldn't make my own schedule
was a good pick yeah i'm glad i always
picked slipper.io though but i think uh
playing papers please
properly for once was a good idea
jealous about the test play yeah it's
kind of unfortunate that
um i can't stream it but there are
reasons for that and uh that
was a little bit of a misunderstanding
from my side that i thought that i would
i would be able to stream that
um but i think we will get some kind of
gaming content sooner or later
just this time i asked if i can at least
like upload a screenshot on twitter
afterwards and and then give you like
my thoughts a little bit i asked about
that so
maybe that will be allowed i think
they're they are generally very very
open
and um very cooperative
so the chances are not too low
sorry i can't breathe
i i think though that i'm probably just
gonna
play the test build thingy that they
played on the
uh tales of a rice stream i wonder if
it's gonna be a different one understand
but i feel like it might just be the
same
thingy you know how um the one that i
showed you that the
the one that the the voice actresses
played
a little bit but we will see i have
i actually don't know
gonna um it on your ps4 oh they didn't
say anything there
in the evening i would i would have time
maybe because for me the tales of the
rice
youtube
[Music]
oh that was fast you guys panicked so
much even though it's just for one
second
so i was i was uh saying that the tales
of horizon's play for me is at 5 00 p.m
uh so we probably i will i would
probably have time
to stream in the evening time for me
which will be unfortunately once again a
really shitty time
for s-e-a people
um but i can't really stream before that
because that will be too early
what should we do what should we play
what should we do
for like uh we could continue papers
please
maybe maybe maybe i'll do that
[Music]
like a little bit after the test play
around
10 p.m my time or 9 9 p.m my time
we could continue paper space
stanley parap i actually asked for
permission
for that game just a few days ago so i'm
still waiting
on that
or or we could play minecraft because
that will be
right after we killed the and the dragon
like like
a few hours later so we could
go and uh try to try to go
to the end and find an elite trail
actually i'm excited for that i want to
do
i want to be the first one to get in the
leads right let's go okay minecraft i'll
put it in my schedule
uh i guess i'll put up a fixed version
of the schedule on the youtube community
then
i'll i'll get rid of the tales of a rice
test play because that's just private
and i'll put it in minecraft
from halloween to fly right
don't die in the end die joe boom i'm
fine don't worry
i'm excited yo is it easy to find guys
is it easy especially in the beginning
because there's
a bunch of them in the end right did you
ever played hazel for zarya yeah i did i
did
i cleared it it was very very intense
not that hard not that hard okay
it's it's difficult not hard not really
okay then let's play minecraft and i
wanna
get the new stuff okay
which tales have you played i i i i
mentioned all of them before in my uh
recent tales of arise
official ambassador uh inauguration
stream so check out that if you want to
know more about
the games i played and which ones i
liked the most and all that
if you watch that stream you'll get all
the information it's
it's kind of recent so if you go into my
past streams you should be able to find
it
i hear a cat meowing in the distance
yeah
now well she's answering me
from very far away
[Music]
now okay she's quiet now
you heard her that was me though
unless you heard the distant one
so cute
hi jokers
[Music]
has entered the room looked at me with a
confused look
and now
it's just snooping around
hi minnie no
oh did you come for cuddles chunky
hmm
she's now just sitting right in front of
me
i don't know what that means
chance hold on he coming
[Music]
i guess i already gave you so much love
today come on
come on be patient it's not going to
take that long
i didn't even stream for that long
a lot he's sitting it's a she okay
jungkook is his girl cute pretty girl
uh
[Music]
oh tonkis wants belly pets
okay bye-bye you can't get belly pets if
you move away the moment i move
okay guys i will be reading super chat
now
on my master super test from this stream
[Music]
it wasn't that almond
both of them i didn't see the
did gura tweet about it oh my god
why did she not tell me
ah she didn't post a picture though huh
did she say it in her stream
she casually said it in the stream
didn't i oh my god that's so awesome
i told her she should get a pet and i
told her she should get a cat but she
was like
i want to get a spider or whatever oh
when you get tarantula and i was like no
you should get a cat
or a dog or whatever something you can
cuddle
i'm glad
count and you're gonna count and you're
gonna count
good choice oh i gotta ask her for
pictures
wait i have to message her
i'll be like good yeah
congratulations caps lock on your
cat send cat
pics please i handle privately
uh
[Music]
okay i sent her a message
okay okay okay yeah what is the junkers
okay
let's go looking for a roast thank you
soon
can i help me with this i got bunked at
work by my boss when i was looking at
your schedule because the image was not
appropriate really for can you roast
that
mf who's picking a fight against your
feet thanks did that really happen
you looked at my schedule at work and
you got roasted but
from from your boss oh my god that's uh
that's kind of embarrassing it did
oh my god i'm so sorry that's like
actually like
i would be i would be freaking out
oh [\h__\h]
is he serious that is like so stuck up
like he got a freaking stick
in his butt
not appropriate the wig i mean come on
that is really it that is really stiff
what the hell give you can give your
employee one second to
to check something on his phone or so
oh give him a moment
can't can't be 150 focused on work 24 7.
yeah that is so strict like when i was
on in my last normal job
i was like constantly watching netflix
and youtube
but that was because we were not really
busy
most of the time i had a lot of free
time in my last job but i was like
yeah i was watching i was watching
piccolo streams
as well at work
oh yeah that was fun that was fun
so honestly um
um i i i think you probably work hard
most of the time but then just one
moment you looked at the schedule
yeah um give give him a
break for god's sake you're looking for
a rose but you should be looking for
a break give a little break in
in the double meaning as in give him a
break to check up
with what what kiara is doing and give
him a break by taking out the stick out
of your [\h__\h] ass
[Music]
it's a chill job okay chill job but not
so chill boss huh
all right
patrick and skye dancing wait maybe i
should put these into the
let me put them into the into the
document just in case so that i don't
miss out on the
red ones
oh wait
[Music]
let me just
i have something stuck in my throat
where's your hat i lost it no it's kind
of hot i don't want to wear the hat now
okay done
now
let's read them petrochem danish and sky
donkey
and kill joey donkey and felix style
thank you for the ransom for chad
wait one more thing
okay el papiya bitte here are my papers
glory to cath we're going to take a
morning
you're six months old but don't have the
i want to get fried certificate to the
other rim of you
intense clucking and flapping body
dragging across the floor just enjoying
what the hell is this role play felix is
that is that what you dreamt or is that
what are you fantasizing about no
no no no don't worry
something like this will not happen at
kfp
don't worry only you're not i saw scott
i thought scott is quite scary
quite quite a scary place but you don't
have to worry about
kfb we are very forgiving and kind
they don't let you struggle
yeah we're not such a bad place we're a
great working place
i i got an award for best employer of
the year
2020 oh
i got an award for that
[Music]
that is true
for real believe me felix thank you
for the red superstar and for the
support thank you
sorry that i'm always streaming at
shitty times for y'all
green wilder thank you and thank you for
the pinky i can't watch live but i'll
leave this here recently i've been
coming up with my own kfb headquarters
oh no another one
i like to imagine the surface service
stuff
uniforms include keanu's red berry and
the kitchen stuff uniform
includes canada shepherd oh you know
what totally i can see that that's why
i'm not wearing them right now because i
gave them to my employees they came to
work and they were like yo i forgot
i forgot to bring my hat and i was like
okay
ah i guess i have to give you one
shikata nasi katakana
wait you followed up with another pinky
so actually that's a red one
oh thank you um
while most of the staff are chickens we
have a small crew of owls working the
drive for overnight oh my god that is
such a cute thought
and canadian cobra chickens serving as
security when this is let me look that
up
copper chickens
[Music]
yo what is this on my timeline
mitra meet with metrosphere what is this
ah
crunchyroll what is this
what is this game kind of cute
all right uh cobra cobra chicken
gotcha oh didn't we look that up before
oh my god that is a very aggressive oh
yeah you guys told me about this before
canadian aggressive chickens right
i see i see icic i understand we might
also outsource people when we need
models for merchandise or commercials
all right my friend you are a genius
you are a genius approved
500 approved i will fund this
i like it those are great ideas
thank you for your valuable input
greenwell
wielder wilder i never know how to say
it
oh maybe stop yelling what's wrong
you want the cuddles don't you want them
ah she's doing uh if i fit sizes
i'm very cute very cute indeed
dashing cats makes thank you soon huddle
rankin i see music foundation kaito aged
dancing
russian
unfortunately it was uh the text was
deleted so
i don't know what it says sorry i cannot
read it
sorry thank you for the support though
i don't know why you were bunked but
yeah next time next time
be more careful it was bad all right
thank you thank you anyway and
even if you get wrong you know then
people get another chance at kfb
and this is just yeah thank you
uma d mohammed
[Laughter]
oh man it's getting a lot
i will probably at some point get rid of
the socks one again
thank you though pudding channel dancing
jackets monkey donkey [\h__\h]
and registering they're doing they're
doing the lyrics thing again
in the super chat singing sparks nice gd
pudding channel youngest and elvis
thomas and thank you for novel pinky
if you don't stream sparks it will be
sent to brazil
that's actually that doesn't sound like
a punishment
what kind of threat is that is it a free
trip to brazil
you don't mention anything about paying
tickets either
no not brazil yo i have no problem with
going to brazil
eh it sounds great sounds like a
vacation let's go
thank you looking forward but i also
want to stream sparks so
can i stream sparks and go to brazil
oh my god anyway that question for the
super chat and
muda you wrote your super chat this time
in uh uh different letters
you want to confuse me huh
what that why the hell would you do that
trying to look smart or something
soul gun of danger in florida
cheers
what the [\h__\h] cheers right day one i
tried cleaning the rhubarb shaking
machine now stuck
knocks and cries going unanswered nobody
drinks rhubarb shakes may starve send
help
i mean what the hell what i don't think
we have a barb
[\h__\h] shake machine that can't be
[Music]
what are you talking about i think
you're the wrong you're the sus kfp
[Music]
probably imposter kfb
thank you
wait what the hell it says sparklers
buckle spank puddings
pudding spaghetti sponge and i read it
in my brain as stream spikes
[Music]
in pudding channel dandruff or duncan
thank you because of your support
and everyone in the chat we got so far
today
i'm honestly impressed this is the first
time i play that game properly i didn't
even know it goes that far
[Music]
i'm excited to see if we can finish it
gotta just turn down turn on our maximum
focus
er antenna
30 days for the whole game what
i believe in your boss thank you you did
really good thank you
happy to be a kfb nice that's what i
like to hear
[Music]
i couldn't believe in eva
hey
[Music]
thank you for visiting this movie
oh so cute so cute
[Music]
cute thank you tai chi and muda dancing
thank you for the red super chat
unfortunately this one got bugs too
but thank you i i think i actually saw
that one
yeah thank you uh
bunk deserved bunk very very much
deserved
thank you for the support though i
appreciate it very much
i don't know bacon 53 hey ken i've been
trying to learn japanese and was
wondering how you started and if you had
any tips for starting out i might
have one of these noises oh scratching
the tree i may have to leave early but
if i do i'll be sure to
watch back on what thank you um
i mean i've mentioned this a couple of
times but i basically only learned
japanese through communication
and using using the words that i just
learned immediately
in conversation and really just talking
every day in japanese
and then actually pretty soon also
visiting japan
soon later on so um i think
if you if you have like someone you can
communicate with like a conversation
partner
that would get you very far i think so
eva
the best choice will always be to just
surround yourself with
the right environment as in going to
japan uh work there
live there or go to school or whatever
but that is
not uh that easy at the moment
and generally it's also not easy so um
you can do like i think there i think
there's probably like
uh a kyla english conver er not ikaiwa
the other way the other way around
i think there's definitely like uh
ways to like find people who want to
teach people japanese and maybe the
other way around
you get taught english stuff like that
and yeah there are apps as well i think
for some of those language learning apps
my brother actually just told me about
it yesterday that if you buy like the
premium version then there's people
actually talking to you
uh and teaching you directly through the
app by talking to you so
yeah try something like that because you
really need to
um communicate in that language every
day and i
don't think that taking
language lessons at school or whatever
will necessarily help you at least not
that alone you would have to combine it
with
more learning methods to have it be
really effective
uh yeah but i
i was very young when i learned japanese
so i picked it up
very quickly i was also very motivated
and very determined
determined the tournament so
i i'm not the best example
but definitely communication maybe try
streaming
on on twitch or whatever in japanese try
try
try streaming into a japanese audience
on twitch i don't know
if you wanna if you have interest and
interest in that that might be the way
to go
[Music]
um
i'm playing skyward sword myself and i'm
excited for you to get it too
hopefully i'll be free that they're able
to cheer you on well now the
schedule is out so you know when i'm
playing it
hopefully you'll join me
i'm learning japanese right now good
luck um
yeah i love you so much queen i love you
too
thank you huh
you don't know your own schedule that
makes more sense
when you're gonna teach us german ah i'm
not your freaking
teacher
i'm not a i'm not a good teacher anyway
especially when it comes to languages
um dwight g dankeshen julian b
dankeshen d mahala's dance
dungeon midnight thank you for the red
super chat
yoshi today is my birthday oh after a
difficult year i was really lucky to
recently fall into the rabbit hole
and find you i love your streams they're
very fun and always make me smile
thank you for making me be able to smile
again tangio
you are so welcome eh i'm so happy to
hear that that sounds like me
when when i fell into the rabbit hole
and got lifted up by piccolo's streams
happy birthday midnight
happy birthday to you
happy birthday dear midnight
i hope you have a great birthday
birthday please enjoy my content please
please have a great time at
kfp and in whole life we are very happy
to
be able to cheer you up
thank you for supporting us
i hope we can support you too mwah
cats ceo
dr zilla 337 nick finland's and duncan
kristoff's
thanks for the pinky why why did you why
did you send so many
like 1000 green ones in one pinky was
there a reason
what were you trying to do this is all i
have left
why did you give me all the money you
had left
well are you trying to
are you giving me your um inheritance
what's going on what's going on
are you here don't give me the money
that
like all you have left what the hell you
gotta keep something for yourself
oh please be careful
okay thank you for the support though
well be careful please
[Music]
yeah always gotta put yourself first
you don't seem to be here but let's let
it be known
put yourself on spot number one
chris nemo thank you and
[Music]
oh there you are
i hope you cheer up soon demo
[Music]
there's a shitty days every now and then
but there's always a sun
at the end of
at the end of wait was there an actual
thing
and the correct way to say this but i
want to say there's always the sun
and after a lot of rain i think i think
that's what
it's supposed to be anyway after a rainy
day there's always a sunny day
[Music]
or rainbow off of the rain i guess so
yeah so um stupid german super chat
and dude good morning again
chloe kfp
[Music]
um
thank you for the pinky quick question
can i get your permission to take
kelly's boy going away and give it to
mama ina
it will also make cali more daddy like
what the [\h__\h]
that is not something for you to decide
and not not for me either and nothing we
can do anyway what the hell
no
[Music]
also that i cannot do bongo bongo
anymore
with her boo boo boo ba did you see that
thing that i retweeted while i was doing
don
i'm talking about talking about the
thing i retweet
yesterday or so i think i retweeted it
get the punching one anyway
big sun um ylc
uh how are things in australia lately
the floods in germany originally are
huge they've got me worried about you
oh are we all good we are totally fine
um
speaking of i always uh agreed on your
views on sand
going to the water makes it even harder
to get it off
looking forward to ttrpg entails thank
you
so you don't get happy birthday
today also happy birthday to your friend
mouse well so many birthdays oh my god
space to jump down flu 1989
the gentle chainsaw
safe wife you can make more kids later
for real
really lexington the la wait no oh no
that was that was a quote from
from me oh wait it says kiana 2021
that was just a quote from what i said
oh
that makes sense lexington the lion
dancing
and my neck is all right it's doing fine
thank you for asking
a round of assumption russian language
class you want me to learn russian oh
wait you're just joking because i was
doing a russian accent
[Music]
it's jackson fb thank you for the pinky
since the country of arstotzka doesn't
pay you enough to keep
being well going to kiana in the cafe
ah you're trying to help me out because
the game was
uh making me go broke and losing my
family
that is very very kind of you thank you
uh unfortunately we died anyway because
i was too stupid to
to put the money in the right places
but there's always money in the banana
stand
i just gotta remember dan kakun dandish
and siren thank you and lulu duncan
spankingham thank you for the rest of
the day i didn't see cat food on the
daily expenses here's some for the
floofy kids
a fan kill actually just today i bought
some new cat food because they didn't
have the one that i always use for my
kitty cat so i bought new one and i'm
curious to see if they'll accept it and
if they
uh will handle it well
so we will see about it
yeah fingers crossed thank you for the
red super chat
my fluffy kids must be fed um
you know when i wake up in the morning
um
before feeding myself the first thing i
do is feeding smoothie because
she gets so
so obnoxious
she will not let me eat before i will
uh give her food it's it's fascinating
the moment she notices that i am awake
in bed the moment i open my eyes she she
notices
by the way i turn my body around to the
other side
she notices and she's like oh mama's
awake and she goes
oh there she comes
and i sound like like a cat alarm to ya
huh it's all good mama is fine
uh yeah so she immediately notices
and she will force me out of bed which
is okay i love her
and she she will not leave me alone
until i give her wet food
specifically wet food even if there's
already uh
uh nip nibbles kipples kibbles
she does not accept that yeah
yeah she's so [\h__\h] yeah
pineapple chicken oh yeah
yeah i love pineapples i i like
uh i like veg vegetarian chicken meat
uh i think that's a great combination
thank you spanky time cocoon
james chen thank you looking for the top
down
you changed your name
he changed you
thank you i'm glad you like my accents
is that fine kitten did you change your
name because i always read your name
really
now my pronunciation is correct yahoo i
always want always has been
[Music]
this seems strange to say because i
enjoy all the streams but this was great
i don't know what's gotten you in such a
good mood but the energy is infectious
and the voices were 10 out of 10.
can't wait to see a continuation thank
you
i don't know either um i don't know
sometimes i'm a weirdo but ah
eh your model fbs is bottom of the
barrel
what that's not true is it
i'm 60 fps
look zoom jump jump
[Music]
he is tripping
all right okay good
man you scare me anyway thank you jacob
and
i'm glad you enjoyed it thank you so
much
for the nice feedback
from
it's time for a refresh meow you're
meowing so much what's up
what she's doing those
yes hello
what is it
yeah that was a joker's the whole time
[Music]
done
okay i gave her some pets
some some belly pets is that good enough
junkies
i'm almost done baby i'm almost
so oh we stopped
and black christian throw through there
we go
the gaming guys sorry sorry
sorry yummy
what is it
[Music]
what you want to come up here oh my god
she tried to jump up my table but she
failed
she fell back down meow
you can do it this movie does it all the
time junkies you can do it come on
you can do it i believe in you
you gotta be confident
[Music]
she's okay
sorry i dropped some things
[Music]
okay probably fine hello okay probably
fine
at the end being an unexpected highlight
easily one of the
one of the streams from you in a while
you you missed the word i think you
wanted to say easily
one of the best thank you i'm glad you
guys enjoyed it
i tried my best to focus on
the documents while also entertaining
you
oh and you continue actually with a
pinky thank you
on an unrelated note some of us are
wondering if you might want to try
singing ichibanka from yakuza 7 next
time you're doing an aircraft karaoke
i know that the song is a little goofy
but it would be fun to give a shot
especially the wrapping wait which one
is that
which one was that
who was wait the song ichiban was
singing when i don't even remember
but i don't wanna i don't wanna
oh the ending song oh that one that one
was dope
i do wanna sing some some kind of yakuza
song
in my next color okay if possible
i don't want a guy to do it one time
well then yeah it will probably have to
be
in an unarchived one oh fly like a
butterfly that's a different one right
that's a different one that one is
ridiculous
thank you for the pinky i'll think about
it
eyes icon
philippe film films
um
[Music]
a lot of people asking me in the super
chats to say some things
um uh
and generally i don't uh
i want to do it that much because then
everyone will ask me to
send messages or say stuff
[Music]
okay okay but thank you for the support
i appreciate it very much
like rich in danger unity chat thank you
thank you for the pinky
[Music]
i'm not on cameo that's right maybe
maybe one day i'll be on cameo you can
make me say whatever you want
just want to say that i for really
enjoyed today's dream you were fun and
radiant
you keep you keep up being amazing and
one day i might admit that you're my
host
didn't you basically just admit it
thank you i love you too it's okay you
can say it
thank you so much i'm so happy about
that
the the feedback what about the pronouns
did i say radiant wrong
yep did i say something wrong or for
really
what did i say
he's 2d hashtag volcano you need to chat
remember that
radiant was right okay for was for
really incorrect
is it for rowley whatever
thank you for the pinky is that how i
say your name are you in the chat
correct me now or uh
be quiet forever
ah carnage okay thank you sorry
carnage thank you for the pinky tantra i
missed your swim stream because i was
helping continue to build on the
gazebo ah at my parents house it's funny
it was the wedding stream because my mom
teased my older brother saying that he
could use it as a wedding venue
ah yeah gazebos are
really pretty for weddings aren't they
i see i see what about you
though what about you carnage and you
gonna use it for the
for a wedding venue huh or did you
already
never mind i don't wanna i don't wanna
inflict any pain
or any burns but you mentioned it you
mentioned it first
yeah 2024 and no no nothing planned
right now okay tell me tell me when it's
planned call me to your wedding i will
officiate
and i'll look at you respectfully
albert school thunder
don't give as much appreciation for your
hard work as i used to so
thank you for the fun stream you always
make every stream entertaining
every song a pop every art piece
adorable every love for treasure praise
keanu
thank you don't worry about it though
you guys don't have to donate anything
at all
thank you for the support just you being
in the chat is enough really
really albert school
thank you for the rest of the chat you
actually sent two one of them
empty what the hell the other one not
oh my heart heart heart heart heart
heart for today
can you at least teach us during pickup
lines all right all right
uh the problem is i never get picked up
so
oh
uh you could you could say
wow do do be so
high is kinda send us to one foot
expense
and i would say yeah yeah yeah
that's stunned
it's uh it means yo wow
you're so hot could it be that you're a
phoenix
yeah i mean honestly that
that it's just truth and
i would be happy because you would admit
that i am hot
and you would admit that uh you were
kind of like instead of saying i'm a
chicken you're saying
you know you you you you're open to the
possibility that i am a phoenix instead
of a chicken and i'm very happy about
them
here come chinese people saying here
don't go me oh no
that's gonna be so cringe don't do it
one person only
no i don't want trying people to say
that to me how the hell don't waste your
time you only got
three minutes only three minutes don't
waste your time with a stupid joke
that i won't be able to react
i'm excited though to speak to everyone
at the
at the meet and greet very nervous too
but
i'm super excited um
oh my god i'm so stupid
i spilled iced tea over my over my
pc gaming whatever matt
i need the one from i need the one for
my birthday marriage
oh let me get some towels
[Music]
okay
yeah i wonder
let me actually yeah
genma is it
possible to send me those
birthday merch samples
or you take it with you
when you come to germany
yeah yeah because my manager is uh
coming to
uh the event as well to protect me
and to help out please bring me the
merch come on
bring me the merch please i need a new
pc
a thingy mad thing what is that thing
called anyway
the thing that i put out as birthday
merch what do you call that
i don't even know what you call that
thing
[Music]
thank you with a pinky a desk mat that's
it that's it
the big one this model is a mouse pad
but what i i'm talking about and when i
release this birthday magic is a desk
matte
that's it yeah okay
little eh
there is no mistakes there's only happy
accidents and this was
definitely an accident i don't know if
it was a happy one
oh well isn't she already bringing you
food
i mean um the birthday merch has
priority
let me tell her that uh if
the food doesn't fit then
retain merch priority
please
okay so albert's good
uh thank you um
good luck with the german pickup ones i
don't know who you want to pick up with
that but i wish you the
is of luck thank you so much for the
support and the love
thank you from the bottom of my hotel
out from the bottom of my big grand tag
mama being great heart
[Music]
foreign
actually japanese just written in korean
[Music]
and picture duncan
yeah but i'm really done with super
chats in one minute so
you can watch the archive it was fun
and so squiggly mustache rats don't let
mama ina know i was here please
last she knows i was in the other world
getting blocked by cali for what i did
last week in her stream
uh huh i see
i think ina is very forgiving but you
must think about your actions please
reflect in the usual room
uh
what happened here again another bunk
what's wrong with you guys today
can you not control yourself everyone
thank you i can't come to dokomi even
though i live in germany money issues i
hope though
i can attend a meet and greet with you
next time i am sure of it i'm sure that
there will be more
uh at least next year for sure
i mean i don't know for sure but i
believe in it very much
you have very high chances if you live
like in europe
i think that those things will hap will
be more likely
than overseas like stuff like meet and
greets but like as we have seen with ax
we are able to do like appearances uh
even by like doing it from home but
i guess like being there in person and
all that and doing meet and greet and
stuff like
exclusive stuff makes it more special so
let's do that more and more um
yeah we're done we're done
[Music]
thank you for the red my first akka so
i'm going to use it to confess my love
to the
most exquisite divine
idol in all of her life
your hard work inspires those in the way
you care for all who
i am makes me want to be a better person
so generally please marry me
i'll i'll let her know i'll ask her i'll
send your message to her
thank you
since you're asking genma i won't give
you a kiss she won't either though
probably yeah yeah
uh thank you for the support i
appreciate it
uh yeah see you all next time i guess
everyone should have done
[Music]
i love your streams do what you do it's
helping me to relax after my work
i'm very glad i can help with that thank
you very much
thank you please watch kiaga every day
hashtag
hashtag yolk and you'll stay healthy
forever thank you so much
and dominic and uh
thank you everyone
thank you guys a thank you sailing fan
[Music]
avenger unknown thank you you know san
antonio
i was told you like hugs i like how sue
thanks for the
if that wear red i could give you a hug
thank you
[Music]
well thank you guys for spending time
with me today i appreciate it you have
been so cute
because that means i'm naked yeah
floor
always cute
[Music]
anyway let's have a fun week i'll update
i'll upload the updated schedule to my
youtube community
board
thank you thank you soon miss fist thank
you gts
oh my god i wait i watched i watched a
clip
of coefficient
trying not to laugh to her whole live
challenge and i am the one who got him
yo and he was suffering
so much before when he was watching the
clip of me and gouda
oh that was so nice to see him suffer
that was really good and then later on
uh
he lost it when he watched the clip when
i read his super chat
that was funny we got him i got him
that was funny i've been watching a lot
of clips these days also like
korean sub ones because like i'm just
curious like what what they are
uh like what the what they find
interesting
[Music]
thank you also i watched i watched the
clip of
nabi and navi mama uh
that was hilarious uh
cause there's i didn't know that there's
a red navi mama
who streams on twitch and he's like
really aggressive and lets out her
inner kremlin
did you guys know that like when she's
when she streams on youtube
she's blue and she's like super sweet
she speaks japanese mostly and she's
like
she's really cute and then she streams
on twitch in korean
and she's like like i kill you i'll kill
you
what the [\h__\h] she is like really mad
it's so funny
um
now that i know her gap
[Applause]
i want to try to get it out of her one
day if i'll collab with her i want to
try to get the red knobby out of here
and see see
if i can get it
she's amazed mama after all you know
yeah i
i always i always wondered you know i've
seen that meme where
they lined up all of nabi's dollars
you know how they're all so sweet and
cute and wholesome
and says all and then there's ame
but hey little did you know
nabi mama has quite some similarities
with ame
she just doesn't show it on youtube she
hides it and then shows it on twitch
[Laughter]
uh yeah
i missed the total sweetheart you're
definitely i love almond
i love she is she's a sweetheart and
she's very creative
very entertaining very funny very
original
thank you for the super chat
[Music]
all right i'll leave you guys now it's
always midnight i'll go have dinner
yesterday by the way i was at my mommy's
place
all day and at her new place
and she gave me a lot of food
she gave me goulash and i have to eat
the goulash today
but i have so much other food too
oh yeah we grilled yes we were doing we
were grilling yesterday
oh my god oh sorry i have to do some or
should i keep should i
let me okay okay chill keep that for
another stream
where you have to talk a lot let me
write it down here
[Music]
okay i'm writing down things for another
time when i ran out of
talking topics
what else happened
not sure what else happened
[Music]
ah oh yeah it was ah yeah yeah yeah
thank you frozen chicken
thank you yeah yeah that's where i i
suddenly interrupted myself right thank
you
completely lost track oh thank you um
yeah uh maybe i was thinking to the side
quite close
to the stream what we do but either we
watch a movie if i want to chill if i
feel exhausted
or we play fall guys or i don't know
play something
i actually don't know i actually don't
know at all
[Music]
my oh we did four lives just last time
so
i don't know this this week is again a
little bit stressful
so i'll just see how i feel um
when we do it dry memory modes yeah i
really i really need to draw members
emails but i feel like i'll be more
productive if i do it off stream
[Music]
um
all right then thank you guys for
watching today i love you all very much
yeah bye bye and in german we say
i'll feed us in
another day ends
bye bye
[Music]
oh yeah by the way if i feel like it i
might do a gorilla
art stream tomorrow um
for the coloring process uh the outlines
i want to do privately because then i'm
faster
but maybe i'll do the coloring process
with you guys
we will see
[Music]