[Music]
male
me deep
good
me
Dabon
me meaaaa hit aaaaa hh
me
[Music]
nh
me
npa
eeeeee hit
me me
me
hh
hit
memedee
Product me
me
n I'm selling me n aa ...
First, let me explain in English. Seaside 1
Willow
hdi Antin Frears by
Sa resident Dixie tomorrow oer
estan
Pad Siemens first in un
r 9 end line 50 os
Chai 2
Usuda ideal 10 people's sound is  I'm not
good at drinking alcohol.
Amane with r 2 under BTS
san gem today how is minutes
dubbing
mastering 0 bobby naka moon
ancher panies along infinity bob
me english 3 years old barter from
thin is it na pi chain fade se super good
today, you know, I
think I only speak Japanese and German, so that  I
think English is a skillful substitute,
but I'd like to ask for a hot water supply,
and tomorrow I
'm in a big whirlwind.
I'm already a lie, Merck and
Spa,
I'm a painter, and I'm going to win right away, so I'll do my best. That's a
late start,
this  It's not a uniform.
Well, I went there today to take some pictures.
Which one do you say?
Well, in that group or in Europe, it's the
same in most places, but in the character's country,
there are no schools where you wear uniforms at all. I
mean, casual clothes, casual clothes, uniforms.  So I was
kind of longing for the cute Japanese uniforms,
but I met a male.  It's
fine in the Japanese charts, but I'm also going to
lower it. I went to Ippudo. It
was a really strange line. No, I'm a
teacher, so
that's not good.
4 Likes, read it as Flair Furya-chan.
It's not a gorgeous flare.
Claire-chan, wait, you're a teacher, so
Flare is fine, right?
That's a smart guy.
Edo suddenly, that's a guy who can block other people. Ah, it
's a daddy doll mark at best.
0 Dari's school has a political party, so why do you call it that?
[Music]
Hmm,
Schaller, I do
n't know, the white heritage, Edamoto and A, you
have to study properly, right?
Ah,
Aaaaa,
today is the 5th issue of the net, right? That attached, Ria-senpai, you're
interested in German, right?
Spear, right?  So I can play in the match, Flare
, Haru Channel,
Hirano, White's Heritage, which one can I play in today?
Yes, I wanted to learn German,
but there was no one who could speak German in the hour.  I'm
really happy this time, please enjoy it.
Tet  It's ak 5, please,
please, I'm
also called by my first name, it's
weird, Kudo, I'll
teach you,
it's been a while since I've done a sticker, but the last one I taught was
Grachan.  That's right, I gave
it to you. I think you've done a little better than the German Grand Champion. It
was a little more basic. It's
great. It's a little bit awkward to see from the basic stand,
but it's okay.
If you're interested, it'll be okay. I
'll start with something a little easier.
Yes, yes, I want to nut, tgn, dimensions,
cha cha
cha,
this is a cha, 8, US Goose, greetings,
peg dependency, baby,
spec stake, that, tab, score,
white,
8 a, as you probably know, that,
in German, it's called a backsound  There
is a character with two dots on top of it, like the "8" or "cherry blossom" typeface.
Overseas, that's a c, and
if you don't type it on the keyboard,
then the zodiac
sign is the voice of the  Two of the stores
Terry's bird Yes, it's
okay to make it a class e, and I won't
touch anything.
You don't have to write it like this,
but for example, if there are two transfers on top of a, then
a
It's okay to use brass, and it's
okay to feel that way. Star said
that fighting curry is something I learned on my own when I met him. It's
actually a bit
nostalgic, and
I'm
glad I bought it.  But then there's that face # ss thing,
yeah, that b
is the letter that looks like a big face b, but it
's pronounced like water, but it's a sound, that pot I
used in Photoshop today, that pot, that pot  I
couldn't write it in the first place, so I'll write it in 10 minutes.
If you don't want to write it, you can just write it in ss.
That's it, so from here on, I'll
teach you a few greetings. It's
Spec V Hayami.  I think you may have heard of this,
but good morning, it
's Guten Goa.
Futenmagen is good, everyone has heard of it.
Yes, this is easy, Guten is also easy after Hara 2,
Guten Chako is Hello,
yes, good center,
good feeling at the clinic, and the empty Amen and Good
evening, Good Day
Abedi Hamburger store is
that,
good good good  It means that it's good from the back, like "
morning Goyo-in" or "
afternoon" or "good morning".
So
there are three, "good morning", "today", and "good evening". If you don't know what to do, you can just say "
woolgutentak".
ec
Or this halo here is possible and problematic. It looks
black.
Um, what do you mean?
Kyoto or some other place, I said it was part 4. Well,
there's a time difference, so I guess that's right. So, it's
okay in English.
But in German, it
's an h sound, but it's possible.
Cao Cao's is fine,
but you don't really need to worry about it.
By the way, if it's
Tsunku, it does
n't have anything to do with the prewar period, but no matter what time of day it is,
Good morning.  I knew you were saying that.  I
said good morning to everyone in the industry
. Ah, it was four games. I
drank those two bottles and got money. The
greetings in the industry are generally "good morning". I
think there are a lot of people who have heard that.  When I was in Japan, I
just said "thank you for your hard work" to everyone.
Kagawa,
he also used his sister, so if you
use "bosou", the word "wardess"
is not used in particular.
Well, that's right
. Unfortunately, there is no such word in the country.
I often
think that it's a shame, but
there isn't one. So in those cases, it becomes "hello then."
[Music]
Well, in those cases, which of these three is it?  That's right.
Ah, even if you paint it like that, how many minutes will the customers be exposed to it
? Well, I
don't know what it is, but the person who is studying German well
will draw Korematsu
tonight.  There are people who say "I'm not feeling well" when it's "Gar",
but this is good
night. Yes, everyone is also saying 4 e  At first glance, it looks
like a good one, come on, um, ah ...  Miya
store Naha city Oh, I'm in
high spirits. I wonder if the ship
is weak. I'm going to show it. There were 5 of us. I'm
going to throw it in the middle of a mess.
But Germans and
Austrians don't usually come.
Gently, the woman 878 is not a hahahaha,
but it's fine, but it's
normal, it's
like this, it's like that, but it's like a sound, it's
perfect,
Nakane
This is blue chip one after another, that's fast, r,
Geyo, headquarters, now love, ping pong, peka pepa sabu,
seal, sugar, as expected
, there was a white one,
ah, waianae
Ah, for that reason I'm telling the country,
well,
after that hard there is cheese extraction,
extraction,
s case,
choo, concentrate, and then it's a number,
press share,
imagine the seashore,
imagine the cheese bass, imagine the
middle
spoon, truth  Re Yes,
I think it's hard to pronounce when you say it in a chain. I think you should be careful with that 2010 book.
Buy more and moisten the uuh universe. Try to imitate just this sound.
Uuuh, let's
do it. It's
difficult.  This is
+, isn't it?
Ah, I
used a lot of Hughes Ah, I
felt it deeply now. Uh, c in c 2
spatula, the shape of a flower and a mouth, right? Uh, it's a burger, but I'd like to add a
little more curry, and I'm
going to mix in the feeling of overlapping with the applicants,
it's difficult.  Pooh
[music]
How can I explain this shape? That
tongue is down, yeah, it's amazing, and now the
character's oooooo
moon
is good. I don't care that much about it,
but
Noguchi  With the mouth of a, f uuuuuuuuuuu,
o 2 r, ahaa, it's too difficult, do
n't worry about it, it's okay, ah, it's okay, that's
right, ah,
tune 4, c,
gyaa gyaa, this is a little bit of a fever, um, um, a
polite way of saying it  And the
final greeting that Kihara uses in the broadcast is Aoni
Leaders Good, it's difficult, it's difficult, it's a
90 difficult person,
delan,
Buyudaji, nao,
winter, dg, an amp, live performance,
ilc, the meaning of the hit lineup  It's a
pretty polite way of saying "I'll see you again."
Yes, that's a really good one. I
remember it
at the end of my stream, so
please remember it until the end. It's
good. I'll
add it to my dictionary.  This is how I got it. I
was given the sound of running, so I'll write it
down. It's a shower from above and below. The sound is this good. It's not over yet.
Bear's basic greeting
seems to be done properly, so I
went to the more difficult one.
Let's go. First of all, I'll put one Adoring on my head. It's well done.
Ahh ...  I'll
get it again, the
words of the goods of Guten Morgen came out, Bouquet
Njegi, the first Buddhist house, well, 2
Ruti, well, normal, good
voice, naoka, big, well, come to the brush,
a key, Abity, swelling, ok, ok,
ok  Tokoko Anne Princess From here, the age of the house
Amen
ore What do you mean by the carrier?
Please tell me the
result of the kennel?
Ah, it's difficult, isn't it? Sell this word.
Aaron, hey, get out, sleep, ramen house, how rare,
ship, can, big, hey, homepage, this  I do
n't have to be a true knight with Ichimakiko, but I
think it looks like that garden now, and I've been holding it for a long time, and I
said it clearly, but
everyone is wearing Kennedy Armenwear.
Menso Soso Soa Let's meet na yo
ne Osaka order is kyura year 8 room
heritage to know more deeply
from here on out my name is
German minor woman I love it
t before I like it
Hey, hey, I just pronounced it like English,
but if you
pronounce it like that, you'll see that it's a licking
drink, and ...
In German, it's a, but the
pronunciation of love in English is good in German.
But when it's next to it, it becomes
love. It's getting
complicated. Well, cyber. Ah,
that's right.
Basically, German is much more Roman than Aid. I
think it's very close to how it's pronounced. For example,
If you try to color this in Japanese,  I
think it's the eyes.
It's the main thing. I tried to read it in English,
but it's not
like German. It's like katakana. I think it's like English.  I do
n't know where the back part goes, so when I read it, I think, "
Oh, it's
nothing special." Why is she like this?
Well, that's true, but
even if you don't pay that much attention to it, it sounds long when Uki tries to read it slowly.
Even if you don't extend it that much, it's a minor eye. Sweet licking
s a It's sad and la Flare walk
Pee
White-san is
10 pieces Such a female know Shira Shiranui Naru Is it?
Ah
No, I say it's a dis Flare Shiranui
Good good
Why is it that you can get Kabe Town?
There is a minor new name and it's a dark compliment. You're the
one who's good at it. You can
easily
say that. Turn and share the total number of units.
Ah, inner ray, flare, Shiranui,
good,
fafa, I want Ino, and that
name, I understand it well,
then, a,
on the other hand, when you ask my name, b, wave chair 2,
this is the tsunami, that honorific, not mug  It
's a casual conversation but it's totally fine. Li Pei Suto 3
Highston
Ui Bridge 2 oo a minor Eyes
Rich seasons Ah only be
highs Douou
a
Front seat Flare Shiranui
Yes
rar
Open bread
Ranran
Asai Let's go
Same habit Hmm Mystery 1  I'm doing various Bach songs, I
think I'm impressed by the 7 songs,
and this one
is perfect. The day of the release is
difficult. It's like a release. Umm, what's the
name of the song?
[Music] Minami-
tsuna, but it fits well.
Urbanis  Such functions I'm sure you ca
n't understand Japanese
English sentences Burn
a
movable action cows are like that It's
because of that range that high sumer
a
yes is
Yes, if you say 8th day, you will be called, you
will be called, it seems that if there is someone called No. 8 Lee, I would
like to see it. Yes, yes, yes, yes,
actually, the word "name" is not included here,
what kind of woman is "name"?
Honda, what do you call you? The
book written here is really
good, isn't it? It's a pretty good love
relationship. If you look at the pattern, it's more like a teacher or something.  I
wonder if it's a good idea to
use it with friends. For example, in the bus area,
there is also a way to listen to "
What is your name?" There is also a way to pick up the phrase "
What is your name?"  I
thought this would be easier, so I
chose this one. Yes, the procedure
is yes, I'm fine.
Increase the amount of praise. Defense. White. I've heard of this.
This is a sunny day.  Ya
Ah
Jude came off and started the bulbs
bais d an
Ah
one layer
get Abue d 4 a
aaaaaaa way
Ikkyuchi
sites
dea
seia  Good
ran Happy can d princess I want it difficult I wonder
b if it
fits, it moves
Geezer well it actually moves
asd you
dear you are you
essbase and how are you doing that
answer is I am Gekiren Miyagi s coupon
is Miya  That alone is enough, but
Nagatomi's 4th turn
yeah If you
put it into a proper phrase, Miyuki
will be saved, so I don't
listen to it Flare management Shiranoe 3 a fee This, please do a big festival and listen to it
Abe Gestia Miyake is
amazingly out of the box
One shot beer ks dear
look up suasuka go to not
bent hugger
ahhhhhh
in the bee field ahhhhh wes
tomorrow eat tree ahhhhh moon
game dew yeahhhh yeahhh at the end there's
no number of earthen flowers but a little
Well, it might sound like that.
Gate Ar
Kyun r Gucci is good. It's
1 pawn ta pull.
Research is reversed and 8 a  The
house is now listening to the sound attached to the ac heritage
bk press machine your
[music]
Myamugesu I
can see the monthly issue ah
that John Sacher girl patch ro
emuge ask tee Evan d
4 gya gya art ok Then next is
Anne and that  Well, excuse me, but how old are you?
[Music]
Birde is a phrase.
For example, you are. Do
also means road. That guy
is a city word.
Lee
Aichi,
US  r
Vezel s d 2
Hey
iis to be a best 2 That's rude to share with Kichan.
Hey, that
's it. Birds can ride it.
Chiara
is especially not old.  I can't decide,
right? Ah, it's more.
If you can answer that, it's fine.
Wiener afe me,
no, ai  Well, I
thought it was completely wrong, but it was like that, right? I
smoked it five times as much,
but in Japanese it was
like, what? I'm 20021 years old, but 221
has it, yeah,
papu.
cani
I'm
in Miyako Fine?
Wow,
fried bread Zoider
, wait a minute, I'm on Discord now, I'm imaginary,
but
Papa Ido, nee, yes, hair,
love nest Banshee,
long, a, I'll
write it in katakana, several times,
minutes  Darutto
i Unundo U
board
Honda Aso stepped on and gave birth to a child
Guu
a example will be set, [ __ ] but 100 y stepped on and
Ah
Aiundaruto i Sore throat Un ran
Hold it and read it Hey hey
wait a minute  4 things to give to a child who is not yet born
by
To is not cute little by little Ah yes
cute Ah Hamabata I was born with delusions
Folder Dofun Nuts Fu
I thought it was a bonder, but it's
better to have a little time to make a profit. It
's the rainy season, so it's earth pressure.  Number 9
Hmm To one cheek q past Ya
Yaso numbers, I'm the only one, I
was studying it a while ago, well, that
Yumeru drawing, I understand a little bit, I
decide, um, and one word  So, the
tricky part is, if it's English, for example,
22 inches, you'd
say "Ah-chan, who will become a pointy one when you order online," and you'd say it in that order, but
if it's German, the last one would be...  I
understand. For example,
if it's 221, it
becomes 201 double. I think it was
a little hard to understand at the beginning because the middle part is mixed up.
Well, the order is wrong.
If it's a
Rain comes first and the temperature is in the production area, and inside is 1
20 OP. It's
complicated, isn't it? I know it's complicated, but when it's
explained, it's all together. Ahh ...  I
can't help it because I'm doing it
tomorrow, but I think it's okay to give
it some Shiller, so I think it's
good to put in my own age properly, and
Pence by now it's a high-priced non-pinch top dressing, but I'd like to dare to
do it
myself.  So please say it. It's a
good American tour in and it's white.
So, it's
not an information person or department. It's a lower class.
Judge, it's a free style.
But a German group is called a
German. It's good.  That's
right, that's
right, it's so real, I
'll do it, I'll walk,
I'll do it, I'll be a
good idol, I'll be a good kid, I'll
go to the bio, Ainon-chan
Pei yabaidozoenzu wife da naaaa
shooting while wine vinegar when in ear
me
roo
2 wife
up a i i
ir is when ing ur ear
wars club stage tae online river he
free
sound papa in his own words  It's really difficult to do, is
n't it? I'm getting old. White Isan is a bit old, but I'm
not going to tell you that I'm young. I'm young,
so I'm a high school student.  Wait, it's
not a Sentai, next time they'll be wearing clothes and it's related, yeah,
yeah, it's here, right? There
's a guy who's not a shabu-sama, sorry, each of us,
sorry, Hirano's legacy, please forgive him,
hurry up, Professor Lugi,
get a grip,
yeah, yeah, baldy, um
, that's right, the white legacy  Um um
um conversation
English let's do it um um I ah me bip
Sudo please listen
big airway
wear and bess do a 1
[music]
brother store green
Minei 8 Akio I don't know that's my  Up to the year
So if you're not sure what to say,
please decide by the next time.
Yes, it's different, but as a version, I'm having trouble with the mouse.
If anything, it's because I'm being scolded. Come on,
angry teacher.
Yes, yes, sorry, as a titanium version,  I
want to know. I
don't know, but I'm in
trouble. My students are in trouble. I do
n't know.
If you mix it up, you'll lose your sight.
So let's leave this aside.
Next is poisonous sushi.  Shall I
ask you?
Where is the Eibou room from
? That means a certain room. No
hair. Now, how is it? Caro, Nuston,
Homu spoon,
Nuko nest zoo. How
should I pronounce this? It's cold.
Community 2. Right,
right.  It's good to feel like a little princess opening up. That's
right, these two words are
ingenious. Now, the
low layer comp toon ridge activity is
finally heat and the end of the day. In fact,
this is the end of the day.
There is, but it wasn't in this font.
If you hear vague situation Shiranui 3,
Ishimei Meet
A
Dokosujumo 22 s under Japan
Yan
Japan or Paso Japan It
's good yeah
Then
aab ta Futami
good comment princess
com foot  Jan yahoo outside Navi
Naa Boda bar
Ah uu uu Jan Japa Nu guard
's Ishibe Aona Capper I also want to go to Japan
Standing
Eh So if you buy it a
a Mr.'s inheritance
a
Please ask me if I'm from 500 or more poison.
Wl Camstar
, I'm blue,
but I'm going to join tomorrow. The
outer skin is good, that's Australia. Uria
and the letters are Australia.
Stone Ediya Soda is very difficult,
but yeah  Therefore, there are two dots on the cherry blossoms of Sakinoa Sky. They
are English letters, but I want to tag them.
Sound quality Mori By the way, winking is also important.
Where is
wig help
air
Well,
after all, it's related, so it's a card, but the head
and the leap, but that Chiara
is often mistaken for an Australian,
so I'm going to use this as a joke and add ashes and
say that she's Larry Anjin  Are you okay? Ah ha ha, I'll
take it later. I
have iFirm Booster in it.
Fear Moon on the iPhone.
OK. Now, turn this to the Play Center.
White-san, let's have a conversation from top to bottom. I
understand.  Takachi
rei house
ua
back, then please refer
to the white heritage and start with those two, please
listen to them.
Yes, my name is hmmm, your name is,
please start with hieh, I'm
already inside me,
remember the source and pronounce it
Opening and closing
year mine 7 h eating
Abi minor ram is Flare Shiranui good
a ueh mi
wii yes battle measuring discharge v discharge
do gya gya gya
let's paste minor eyes killer sad
a
no Mitsuhashi and place ok also on the contrary  Asking the name  I do
n't ask because I do
n't know 3
Prea-v Arthur web
year
Peg Au uun
The answer is 4
Jess
Astrale goods usr Hey, I'll
listen to it
Ice Fu goods yaaaa big
Ets is the opposite  Please ask me Is it
okay
? Ah, no ...
Whey
Guess tomorrow true big taaaaa genealogy
du many car art Miyagi s ah book the
point is they go to sleep now what I just said
ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah by
ks by the way opinion
a
Lee
that bis  I'm
going to cover the
8 y  A little postscript that you can meet in minutes, rare 5
Won ah
waa ...
Heights mirror in So
a
year
Wow A
big boy and bones
Hmm good
a rice flour
wig 6
Ah Aya Pan
That's also one, too bad I can't decide No, it's
okay not to ask that Ah Hanya appearance It
's just to fly  Nongetsu's Ring
Onee-san's
suit is kind and messy, but
I don't think it's all that good, but it's hard for that Japanese person, but it's well done, and it's very kind.
If you have that support, you'll have an
appointment, but it's Germany.  If it's a word, then it's up l
up 1000 up fail 2 minutes That's right,
that's
right. The next one is, let's go swimming.
D village +
various things. I
tried saying something after that one that the senior could use.
Bach Baka Pabu The
same bus can't fly, the first Isaki read,
call, push place teacher, uuuu Lee,
animal, laugh, work, you know, from the beginning, I'm a
half-elf, star-like,
yes, that's right, what will happen with that, I
wish,
bed  ge
Boo Boo
8 Haru Hanyu Haru Bu Elfun, right?
Yes, yes, yes, yes,
I'm a half-elf.
sfa Haru Pero
ani
Boo Boo El Haru If it was English, etc.
But,
yes, it was German. bb
That's right, how will Elf,
yes, yes, I can understand it in German, but by the way,
German Day, if you
count those numbers,
11 is the same, the fifth,
right,
ran, fully concealed, Pim Long Jin,
only 31, something just came up from the middle, that's
it  There are some special ways to read numbers,
like the numbers from 10 to 20.
2nd floor, 2 tongues, tongues, pants,
Edda curry powder, you know, it's piling up, you know,
the numbers, Ash, how to look at it, I
want to give the ring up already, it's
like Mach wow,
goo,
but sumo on my car, it's,
it's, a ...
Yesterday, I was a little worried about the tournament,
but I was talking to a senior about the Seria mahjong tiles,
and I couldn't sleep well,
so I can't sell them.
Kaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa 6 minutes Aso slider Haan
Station Meaty disposal
Haa ...  That
's not the case, it's pretty much the middle of the road in Japan. I
got a call from Flare-senpai in the morning and she
said she was going to sleep two hours ago. I had a flaw.
Oh, you shouldn't say that, it's a promise, right?
Hahaha, you helped me a lot with the tweets too. Yes, I
did. I
had a tweet about nails two hours later, but
Andy also tweeted hours later,
Gray,
when do you often  I'm told I'm sleeping, but it's
really tough. But yesterday, I
wanted to help Flare-senpai, so I gave her a few
tips. I think she'll be able to sleep better
with a lavender pillow.
Try it out.  That's what I said. I
told her, "What is lavender?"
She told me, "Terry, the lavender handbook." I gave her a
lavender glitter mask and
ramen with roux. Lavender is so bad. Sorry, dinner. In my head,  It
got mixed up, but it was too much for two servings.
Lavender
lavender. U-chan is really looking at the back of the snow-covered flowers.
Ahhhhhh, it's
amazing how to read the sugar chains.
Buber-san is also teaching this cute girl
a little bit of German now.
It's really good.  Uuuuuugh.
Rosspati
[Music]
Epchat, ah, in German, papadu, yo,
fur, sa, atata house, but, or,
also, the pattern used in Germany is painted,
yo, I'm
sure, swamp, well, well, 6 t, I know, right?
6 or so far java if you have
Claire's yes
ana
aa ...
At least there
is no in. The
head of the house is not well. Well, the
exercise is
well.
Far turn, isn't it?
Ah, that's
it. What is it? The suit is not well. The dialect is not well. The
finger is old. Fix it. The foot is not c.
Well, it looks a little more like a baby.
Repeat.  It's
simply Aso. The more you talk about the internet, the more you'll understand.
It's a proper word, but after 6,
Vater is a proper German word, but it's more like a
bee colony, or rather, a farmer is like a kachan.
Korma ink and manners and Pato, I feel the sentences
, ahhh, 5 minutes is okay,
but it's Buban, Anfa's, but even when you grow up, it's the same,
or people who say things like Papa, I'm already
used to it,
right, from the tree that was born, right, teach me  If you
teach me, that's what happens. Pub bag Mabuba
Department Babman bag Each part man vaam Vaam I
don't understand German, but
Harvey, how is it? Faye, I
can't sleep, poor thing, but I'll tell you the operation instead.
Let's work on it.  So the ticket,
Shoner,
Yuan family, and the manager, Get-chan, is
4 Nero's outside, shitty player,
Nero year shop slope,
Gerda,
Ah, the recording, Meow Meow, panting, Meow Meow
Meow, and more  I
have to jump, I'm a Susa-
san game, which one is Hara-Hour fan,
hair, yay, yay, not here, trading company  I need to make sure
everyone remembers it, so is it okay,
viewers?
Please make sure everyone is well. From the window of the train on Twitter, everyone is like, "When do you go to sleep?", "When does that guy go to sleep?", "By the way,
Bang Bang"  5 is full of keys, I'm
sorry ...
Okay, okay, so for some reason,
yesterday when I asked what I wanted to know, I was told to
take some medicine.
Hey, it
seems like he wants a sheet for the workplace, so I
think it's good to use it.
Please use this for those who are interested.
Nemunemu
raw
name stand Medicine
Anu6 I'm asleep
Mediteam
Uzen This is also similar to English and it's support.
I chose it, but it's German.  d scene, it's difficult to
say, right, right, neru-ga-ne,
midi tune, numuta
drinking soil,
abandoned, good,
ok, benefit,
cute,
une, there are many people who want to be prescribed that medicine,
doi, what time is it,
well,
I like it too much, I like Kira-chan
When I'm sick, Ah, Flare-san, a
white-addicted
artist of the 1960s,
Hahaha, he's gentle and erotic, and Yabe is also a good
seller, I'm happy to hear that,
but hey, everyone has to take their medicine,
right?
Xenon Tai Metz Iinn removal Metz
Okage Air Shock Fishing Drinking Ha 40
It seems so yeah
line eyes ja
gyaa what's that
gay show mation
Lapu
Curafend s that
sche are all next to each other in this order  And the
situation of becoming a brother Ra
Pension Chapen Creation A little fair
Written by Rapala Era This is something long a eyes
If you do it well, you will go bankrupt  It's
good to pinch it, it's a strange sound game, it's a little
bit ...  It's the
same as the English Ando, but
yeah, well, it means after that or and.
Yes, the
real name will be held in March next year.
Rough
sketch please. Fencer Surfer.
Ah,
Mach One version. The
way Bandai Namco painted this year is really good.
Yes, oval year pattern wool September first pine
Pavillion
[music]
ana searched
This is Caroboom It
might have been better to change it from the other side,
but if you
write katakana, it becomes very
Japanese.  I think it's easy to get used to poikaldon,
so I
think it's better to use katakana or katakana here.
But it's amazing, it's helpful. I'm going to
leave out the slightly unusual reading.  It's
easier for the child to stand up because he's supporting me.
Maybe if you read this all in katakana you wouldn't understand it. Well, I guess this is the first thing you
read. If you read it in katakana, you wouldn't understand "oishii bennu ainu
harubu elfu nakanagara".
Ahhhhhh if it were me, I'd sing this.  It is
understandable, but
if you are a person who is completely foreign to Japan, you will only hear this as a very strange word. I
think that Takanami reading is the same in English. I think
that the tourists who go to the pier are familiar with it.  I
used to work at a company where Japanese people would come and
they would try their best to translate it into English,
but there
weren't any of them at my workplace.
Well, I'm
trying my best to communicate in katakana, but
unfortunately, I'm acting. I
agree with the effort. It's
like, "Yeah, I
understand Japanese, so if a Japanese person
tries to speak English,
I know how to pronounce it, but it's like, "Daikon radish, well, well, there's not three of them.
"
Anyway,
when people are buying and selling, I
want to say it.
Now, Mango Chako,
thin, well, fish, Bontan,
main store,
1 ta, bonta, right, on, er,
1 character, what, where,
how,
ah, name, there's a leftover, there's a rubber band, it's a little
hard to read, there must be other things like that,
unger, there, unter, main cha,
sound  Romance is really good shower
moon calm down Keiko really
Fon well Won Cha
Asian eyes air series
Translated Good evening
Come on Hon-
chan Burn a did it did it
got down got down like Oh
certainly that example bar mom
If you live in a two-story building, you can say, "The
food is ready in one go, so come downstairs."
If that's what you want to say, you
can use this station in that way.
Ah, that's what it means when you translate it literally.
That's why there are various uses for it. Ah,
yes,
please remember this. I have two hands.
Hon-chan, An-chan, when is
it now? Wait, I
didn't have this.  Shi  That
little bit, I dare to say, my hair is good, the
result of the shot is weird, but
everyone's money was good.
Yeah, I was really lucky, I was really lucky, and the
fried rice was delicious, and the last
one was good.  Taunnbo Char
Ah, a
small, amazing senior, a
fighting teacher who praises me a lot,
this is the boss type card Arthur I
'm that kind of teacher,
then I'm the type who grows when I'm praised, so I'll
do the same to my students  Thank you for
making a high evaluation of the flowers of the gentle politics.
Next time, mother and child, well, it's
for the grave of the well-known white heritage.
But I wrote both of them, but I'm
a fool.  There
are many things to come, but the one we chose is
really good. For example,
there are some that say "please come and visit us", and there are also some that say "
Idea" and "English area".  There
are also similar German anomalies.  I
thought this was the best one. It
's often bought.
Sugarko yeah, it
's difficult, but the cup is still goosebumps.
Pete s. No, Shark Kosharu,
Up Mango Pu,
Shuba style cup, cup style only, middle back,
Fern,
Commander in  It's so
difficult to
make, so I think it's really good. Ah,
Ah,
Ushibashi Burn side grass is sticky,
so I'll make it more and more in the shape of a
cafe.  Miya has appeared again Force 2
rear
[music]
Feeling
cool Chinami
Here, one penalty Yes Bell High
Bay Let's make it a Boshi backup Let's
try Pororo Ae Aa In Shimakkoba Wow
I am
Bach is
the best, the best, it's a coincidence,
ahhh, ahhh,
if I could learn German perfectly, I wouldn't
be able to live anymore,
Ash only learned Capella,
even from 5, the bell
Yes, if the Ehime University soccer team had a German person, it
would be called "Kotsu German Horse"
in Minami Ward. It was
called "Narunalgaito" and it was a word like this. It really
hits the spot
in everyday conversation.  I don't
think you'll use the pieces that you don't think you can break in the booklet, so that's
good. It's useful to remember that here.
When you're flying into that chest somewhere, it's
good to have ajr from the day to the water.  I was taught,
hey, hey, hey, this is no good, hey
, let's teach this to the fools, I'm not
doing Papi-hime, Oshiyama Komura, that moon,
boat flare,
white heritage museum, my
mother often said that nail  Gagah, it's a
suggestion, so it's Jello.
Ah, if you
take that and say it in German, it
will probably be the usual one. That
version 6 j is pattern 4 pattern
zoom. Yea, I'll pay. That's right. That's right.  This is also
difficult to pronounce.
Ha ha.
Chayama Butter Mono Mokeko Rattan skips 5th
place.  That
's right, if you attach it to a man, you can
play a lot,
but it's fine if it's
just a pattern, but if it's worth it, I think you
'll add the word ``usual'' to it, and that's natural,
so I guess
this  By adding the "natural" pattern, you can make it look natural. The "nine"
in front of the "nine" pattern means that it's not enough.
So you're not going to be able to do it.
Connecting them together, each one results in a result,
based on the pad's dissatisfaction,
Southern's second place,
yeah, that angry wind,
pattern ground fiber,
ha ha ha ha, the original boy who's still here,
yan,
this beach  It
sounds like it's the oldest in Annaka, but
Gakken means that there's a familiar Nappa.
So, there are six ways to do it. I
wonder if they're doing something bad. Well, that's the most hot thing.  I'm getting stronger.
This is not strong. I'm just saying it. I'm getting stronger. I'm not going to
cut it.  The
healing part is uh, jal,
uh, uh, it's
so wonderful, and
at the end, I don't know, but banana, uh,
look, it's Kanon, Hana, yeah, but still, no, burn, why, what,
what,
give it a ring, give it a ring, 3  The range to raise it is Da-da
Groom. Ah,
what virtual links do you have?
Apple vinegar 4th floor, no rails
tomorrow. From the linker, L-shaped turn, amazing. Autumn is almost here.
Main iHerb f Oh, do you
read it all?
Aira and the cruel Janyamasho-san is
starting, I
'm flying the idols, flying them, f
8 to the exclusive sale, white 3 a, that trouble, but
this one is different, I bought this one, the
waves and the futaa are eeeeeeee  No,
who is it? 21 s Shushuburn
Day measurement period Hmm
[Music]
Good,
good, good, so no one is right-handed
Cloud,
but the aftermath seems to be
ha
chan to run 3
[Music]
Well, it's good to be able to mix various things together. I
don't think I've felt this either.
For example, I'd
like to mix the ash into a liquid. It's a medicine.
Hey, calm down and drink water at Haneda 4 colors,
various joints, pattern, office, bancha,
picture book, still in my eyes, Nogeyama-chan, oh
, no, this is how it goes well, what is the van, what
should I add, everything  Bond
is
probably a [ __ ], but there's no need to worry about the rest of the story. Your
stupidity has made him a loser
. You don't need a new one yet.
Just the next trace is fine.  I
think so, right? I calculated the Meitetsu Sakura
pattern, so that's what Luther is like, this money
channel, bade meli noa game,
and he's like a German
, I guess, I
added Ru because there was no context or word.  I guess that's better.
Well, the Lord is something like Cope,
and well, you see, it's between there, the phenomenon
Fire and something like Turn are words,
or grammar, so you just add them and
connect them, or in Japanese,
for example,
play around.  You idiot,
calm down, take some medicine, and then knead the nails. It's
like that, and then you shift it, and then you nail it. That's how it's connected,
and then you become a garden. I see, I understand.
For example, a, Don't
mess around, and if you say, "You idiot,"  It's
strange,
isn't it? It's true that it can't be used anywhere,
but if
you take one medicine and then go to sleep, if you try to
connect it, it will be
quite loud and barking, and I'm
teaching German.  It's a little bit different,
but I learned a lot from my parents. Mr. Magath
himself asked Shimahana, a
good student and a fan. After his death, it's a
job. I have to ask questions, otherwise I
can't remember.  That's what I like
That language exam passed, so I
need to review it, but I understand the way it is and I
know that it's delicious.
I'm not a real teacher, so I'll keep
teaching you that kind of thing.  I'm not a professional,
but I
hope you understand
. The next one is a
picture you don't need to remember, in the Austrian dialect.
Bach
's bedwetting is, well, if you're
German, the numbers won't work.
Only Austrians can understand this,
probably, but it's not understood by most Germans, so I
wonder how many times I've had to train with this guy.
sess ok a 4 Miller
Yumina Lafitch listen 10
How about the name Spawn Cinder? Ito family operation.
First, greetings
, assassination, Chi-sumi, swarming ugly
blue, yeah, it's
not good, 7 sems, eh,
1 a little strong dialect,
a Gyutou,
se as, yeah, milt
So, there is a
chance to inherit the village, and the succession of the
game voice is extracted. I saw the
chance to
inherit the village, and there is a chance to inherit the game. It's Ichikani Taketaka, so I'm watching it. OK
OK, so the next one is
this.  I haven't used any characters, but it's
beautiful. Anne
Marie is so slow. I
grew up in Germany, but I don't speak
German very often. I want to try speaking German properly. I'm the
only one who speaks German.  I'm really not that familiar with
people who have been using it for a long time. I
can't speak Hanasera,
but in Japan it's something like "Yaruou" or "Ya",
but the usage is completely different.
When should I use it? For some
reason, when I start talking,
Anyway, I'll use Joy Grape in the past.
For
example, when I'm happy
or angry, I'll use this a little more.
For example, I
had a lot of fun today.
I'll tell you,
Oida Fight Bumper Aiai and Ladder are the
first ones I put on for now.
So, if you translate it, today is a different fun day. If you
see someone who bought it, you'll come. Evo 8
is different. Well, I guess Japanese people are
always using it at any time. I'm
like a pig. I'm
like a mother who is positive.
But  Even though I'm 7 years old, I still use it in high school.
Well, he's a really great person. I do
n't know what it means, but when I use it, I
use it like this
.  There are 3, but I ignore the meaning and
just put it anywhere.
Well,
by the way, it's only at the beginning, and I can also put it at the end.
For example,
you can also use it after the "shimasu" that I learned earlier. It's a
loop.  Running seeds or Euler
But that's stupid, stupid, stupid,
stupid, that's what I say, I don't even talk about it, I don't even do it,
you're a very stupid person, I
think it's good after all, in this case,
well,  I
want to try it.
It's close.  I just went
back because I want to see the chat now. Isshiki is
certainly good.
That's not a jack.
Seriously, this might be right. To be honest,
it's a way of using it like that.
To be honest, a. You're an unborder.
Or to be honest, today
was really fun.
Dan is biting everything, isn't he? 10
Oh, that's right, it's a tower. It
's a dialect for putting it in. Bird is so beautiful. He is Aoi
Dai Aoi. It's happening. Next is the best one. It means that.
1 A
little more of that
dialect pack If you pronounce it, you'll
become a king than Ah, after a while, there is
no more book life on
love, it's a preparation bond branch this,
before fashion, etc. Bond ie nursery
school panelist Let's pumps 6 items
Ah, until now, bored years old  The 4th group is pretty good, amazing, it
's like the characters, Eho Gendai episode 9,
speaking of the thunder version, it's a nice phrase, the end is the best,
yes, DNAI one two  I
think the words are pretty cute and cute,
but you
can go with Fiat Ti, you
can say it ...  It
's not a good name, but it's actually the main gate. It's the same. It can be used as a noun. Oh, that's right. I'll be impressed from now on. It can be used as a noun, so it's good. No, it's easy to understand. Pitti. I think it's cute, isn't it? Umm,
well...  Well, he's a good guy for kids,
Pyuti-
Pu, it's
okay to do it, I thought I'd use it, but it doesn't get across,
right? It's always like that,
isn't it? Sakura,
Imazu Minami, please forgive me, that's what it is,
Minnie,
Despair  Well, hey, let's cut it off, let's do it,
DS-san 22, let's do it, n, desu desu,
shinhwa,
Bets-sars-n, three, millime,
summer, so, this,
Umily, a, in proper German
Well, it's a service card,
but in
the dialect, it's completely different. It
sounds like there's more than one, and it's not like it's a year. Ah ha ha, it's
fine, it's fine,
it's not a big deal.
Hey, episode,
what is that? Police whip, right?
Boom boom,
yeah,
ose, that's it on the moon, esperde, way,
delicious food, e na e,
this is
German, in German,
yeah?
[Music]
Hey, Super Anless,
hey  Bar 5 minutes,
market price,
Nezu,
barbell,
rax, orb, s 4 f 4 boo,
yeah, it's
totally different, this one is better,
both are good,
ah
[laughter]
[music] I don't
get it, but
Makushita fall,
copy car 2 cup  Pika-ear copy car pack
Pu-
pan
-pika-kopikatan-
boo-boo-
queen-can't-hear-me-sky-
pou-
dou
[music]
Dou catch like a girl Pika
Chicker
This to our point of view or I don't remember
Blair is passing by & I think I'll put a little salt on it
Joy said that day
Then just yes is fine Aah I
went to the bookstore and there is such a word
So how about  But I think it would be cute if you used the last one. I'm
tired of the universe, and I
'll see you later. It's a little bit of a ...
I was in the state, I was bad
, but I'm going to be a hag,
huh, booth in bar,
but this is cute, isn't it? Some people use it for marriage,
Austria, hmm, yeah,
c, hag,
but this,
rock, you can calm down, powder, English speaking
place, Sarayama  The impatient user is that booth et
German word English is a certain naughty
word brother teru
Aso is painted I noticed it
seems so calm down discussion summary 5 then
call 6 more
on April I don't want e h
Hello, if you think about it, Anubos and English Oyamaishi Baba are terrible in Japanese, so you don't need to use rice, or it's hard or peels off, but it's cute.
[Music]
Ah, I guess it's something called internet slang.
-Well, it's a hard word to say,
isn't it? Golden Enya Granny Fun Biao Lake Ikeya
Aqua's everything is that,
Yukiho Carol, Tasukacha Nishi Karatsu Nuts,
50 Boots, Ah, Anar,
Well, what's wrong with the listing,
Well, but what in the end?  Well, that touching senior a
white person I
'll teach you a little long sentence, but Monya
distribution, I
don't do such a proshiro, the
original decision, Dawn turn,
chain, Wow, Kofu, I'm
trying my best to read it wide, it's finally in front, Hobby,
a ranking  Professional advancement n
Dan catch elegant style
pupupuu
gather people to pressure loser wear
discontinued car this is thank you for watching today
broken winter matching several companies n
Male
lineage, not falling soon, Shasharay faction, A Bonny
Unfair Bunya, d, I wonder,
Chanel registration please,
almost visible,
Abunya, I wonder, isn't it okay, is
n't it, Arty Ayanya, a, keep,
no good with hot water, a,
please give me a high rating  I will check it out.
Gyumeedya Di da
Omememe ada No Daimeiho
Wait for the
husband Kama day Come again tomorrow Money
Safety Beads Game Caught Jump
Leader
Ah Now the volume is also aluminum 3 Sand steaming  It
seems that the main text is long, but let's read it from the beginning. Male
lineage festival 2 cars
Male lineage festival Tsuchon Ebite Abunya Dinka
no
bitte Abu ya Denai Nagi Miyata
downloader Hue
game en Daum de Roar  My
sister Aokko is
also up Bida
H feeling is also Gyan V $ Nyaa
[Music]
anarar
only when I'm doing this I read this
Only when it comes out, the
number of Nausicaa of the Valley of the Wind feels good.
Taayai Pella and Garettou 4 and Ross
Baron Legdale and Peta were
reading that and Leah's tree oops There are a lot of them
If you like this, please distribute it.  I
think it would be difficult to read the font
when I tried it out on the chat, but I saw that it was
written that the font was hard to read,
but this is
super easy to read for people here.
As for the font, what I want to say is that
when I first started studying Japanese with a marker pen, I
couldn't read even the most beautiful handwritten Japanese at all. I could only read that font that looked like it was written on a computer.  Even
though it's a little difficult and I'm still learning Japanese,
Flare-senpai was able to read it well. All of this
was chosen by Kiyama-chan in advance, so
there were some that were just dreams.
That's almost it. I'm really
grateful. Yes, Romer masturbation.
Basically.  I know it's difficult for people who don't use it,
but it's still easy
for that kid, you know?
There is a more difficult one than this, Shurei Push
Cliff, that round, that, that,
Wako, fluffy, fluffy, fluffy, I know how to write it. Then
this writing will be Tanna 2, um,
wait, that really happened,
but  Hey, going to school,
etc. Well,
well, at first, you learn the normal way of
writing 6, but
after that, you have to write it properly,
or you might get in trouble. Then, I had pants on. I was
home.
I'm going crazy too.
Well, I'll leave it at that.
Well
, I'll leave it
at that. I was born in the moonlight.
That voice is German. I'm
sure you'll be able to sell it.  I don't think you'll cry much if you hit it.
Ah,
right? I'm sure animals are also one weapon. I
just looked it up a little bit.
Lives web Ah,
well, I
want to play the service car. I want to hear it. I'm looking forward to it. I want to go. I want to go. Right, right,
right, right here.  Changed to country
But if you live in a country that uses Roman letters, it's
normal to write in cursive for the most part.
For work or in letters, it's usually
written in cursive. But that's
harder to read.  I think that I
want to go to Japan, but I have expectations for English. I
think I remembered that old tab, but the town really hasn't changed, so
when I write the roses or autographs of those who can't write,  I
don't know if
you want to go in and buy it. Oh, that's right. The sign is
not written in cursive. I hate the elementary school students. I
want to go soon. If I
were an adult, I would sign my name.  I
can't call you, it's so messy, there are so
many people who are
really together and writing it,
Kawakami, standing there, we're in physical education, at first, I
thought I'd write it in cursive,
but what if I went home with a hit?  That's
why I want to change my child's clothes.  I
think it's okay to be worried about something, even if you didn't come that day.
If you write that block letter 0, it's already a perfect eating story. It
should be changed today. You're a good student.  Tawaaa
gathered by Arthur Hey hey, the
applause is not Kyaa
... c is because it's wonderful e
No, well, it's not really like that, but I tried my best I can
remember the visits of the chat, the visits of the viewers,  Is that the hard time? Of course, there is a
monster elf in the near area. Everyone,
that Oki Anacha channel registration, Takanashi
player channel registration and high evaluation firmly,
thorough
lift thank you Minwoo's Eyu Rush
Ace Sports with rear spoiler 4 people
Disco Chain Cross Mitre also
floating worm next season future
genetic technique rice tea escort Megupo 5 is still in existence
Eh, after this, um, someday, the
two of us will collaborate again, r,
how about each other  Please register your rating.
Good good 07:00
anoano It's bad ae way boots
Field is bad double property damage talk w Gold grain down Long-
established signboard
This quick recovery fan
Let's and um what is what I learned
in an instant It's a bit of a blur  It's
cold,
but Yellow,
ahhh, ahhh, and loneliness, from where, from where,
all the good things are inside the corridor, something
like that, the legacy of those kids is being distributed, this, the
last thing you say, isn't it, the child, Ah,
Senki 4, team lead,
service, plus, the channel ae
Burst enters it & flares
twitter
addition tomorrow always
says twitter I forgot
Maaaaaaaaaaaa Jajannoncho I'll
write it like that
Nyapurinspetter is tight a Shiranui I don't
know Apis power with two flares
Inflation aaaaaaaaaaaaa Jump Germany
Boy and English I
think I was being too silly
How many accents are there eating the whole road
After the return, Ah, An Nyanpana, if you
eat a unit down corn before an apple, you will
be healthy, that's what it is, that's
right, Nakacchi
only often says the words,
difficult case,
what is the Japanese word for, proverb,
operation  I can't imagine Pudong. It's also in English. A
convenient app called Day Keep Doctor.
Support. An
apple means you don't need a doctor.
But I think that's wrong. Oh, that's right. That's right.
So the code is one employee.  Hey, in the winter, I
sleep, and in Japanese, that's
ahh ...  Register your
favorite words.
For example,
kindness is not for the benefit of others.
That
is a
long and interesting phrase. I like it.  It
's a technique, but there are quite a few people who only remember the part, "Kindness is not for the benefit of others." It's a
proverb that says, "If you show kindness to others, kindness will come back to you." I'm
sorry.  I can't understand the story of the eye examination being
unsatisfactory. It
was difficult.
Hey, hey, that 9r-chan is
a mess. Japanese is too soft. It's
difficult. First of all, I gave birth to her. I
know the truth, but what  I know what you're saying,
but maybe my concentration has already been lost.
I don't know, but I'm going to have to wait a little longer. ...
Rei Mira, the comedian standing up, is that what you
do at the end? Archi Curie, dressed up, Kim Hee-ho, said it like that, ah, Wonder Habo, we had a discussion, Angel 3 voice actor, ah, Bida before the end,
me
Ah, that's it. Yes,
yes.
[Music]
Rae-ryu main Danki Toshitomo good se 2
nao
Well, it's perfect, good Tekki, such as this. I'm
going on a trip to Germany with my senior player.
Bye-bye, Landmon,
so,
Gutenacht