[Music]
foreign
I don't know
[Music]
thank you
all right
[Music]
baby Pizza
[Applause]
Pizza Time
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
baby
all right
I don't know
[Music]
thank you
again
[Music]
baby Pizza
oh wow
[Music]
it's a pizza time
for sure
what's up hello
it's a small one
Auto
[Music]
but thank you for turning on the TV mom
look
yeah
thank you for turning it on because I
only exist in the time that you have the
TV turned on aka the YouTube TV
YouTube TV
thank you thank you finally I can
breathe
it's like the ring
that horror movie
does she also only live when the TV is
turned on oh
I didn't know that maybe I am her
maybe same person
did you get a good controller well I
have a choice of several controls but
I'm going with my
razor pink daiju tournament Edition
controller
oh my God it's been a while since I used
this
[Music]
I
Pizza
[Music]
egg glasses yes or no what do you think
you see even less expressions of the
glasses they're really cool but maybe
maybe no glasses
lots of yeses though hmm
but then you can't see my cute blinks I
feel like the blinks are just the cutest
thing about this
I have the 3D alfiata but I noticed uh I
don't know if it's because of some other
reason but
uh I have no expressions
they put it into the app without us even
asking which is really nice
but I noticed I have no expressions for
it
[Music]
make it a bit smaller and a bit bigger
okay
hi
this is so cute thank you blue for
making little weird TV for me
all my emotions went into the pizza
you know when you make the pizza you
have to put all your emotions into it
it's the passion
passion pizza maybe oh should I make a
passion fruit pizza
[Music]
Italian kfp suffering I love you guys
mwah
it seems like my family is going on a
trip to uh Italia
without me though because I'm busy
kind of unfortunate but yeah I didn't
want to go on a trip and I'm busy and
have some appointments that can't be uh
you know moved or canceled
I don't want to travel anymore anyway
I'm so dead I know I said I wanted to go
the trip this month but I might move it
to next month
um
cause a hell no I wanted to do it before
uh anniversary but yeah
um
so
Korea when
when not in the summer
personally in person not in summer what
does that mean
what does that mean
my throat I don't know I had a little
coughing fit before the stream but
that's just because possibly because I
was laying down uh
look very vertically horizontal
um I don't know
I'm never sure
uh but I again I prepared lots of tea I
ran out of honey though I'm like on my
last
drops of honey
[Music]
need to buy honey
I wanted my first cup can already be
poured
no I don't
know but I spent more than 45 seconds in
the screen and nothing's happening
[Music]
around screen okay cool
it's safe after the light as well that's
so scary
do you think it's a good position for me
to be uh down here or should I put
myself somewhere else I could do that
[Music]
I missed it thank God
but should I make myself a bit smaller
I feel like I'll be covering up a lot
I should
ah
app crashed do we want to share
additional information with the
developer
um yeah why not oh but I have to write
something no thank you
money
don't worry I'm back already back in
Action already I I forgot how to obs
what
[Music]
okay
I don't know just a little bit um TV
will be above you anyway once the game
starts okay
[Music]
I guess I heard this game is difficult
and people are worried about me playing
it
oh let's see I have a window that's
pretty tiny even at its biggest size
because I guess 4k monitor
what I do do I like choose one of these
TVs this is just like a save file kind
of thing
also I have to get used to using PS
controls because the bottom bottom
button is yes
and I've been playing only switch games
these days
where the the right button is yes
oh my God
let's go
what is that the pizza dialer it doesn't
look like a pizza
Tower entrance
oh I'm covering up the money
but uh audio maybe I should turn it up a
little bit
um yeah
okay he seems very scared just like me
should that be scared
[Music]
oh my God is that Mr Pizza who owns this
Tower and is it that is that his pizza
cat
I don't know what happened to you I
guess wait he was a lasagna Kettle
welcome can I jump oh
wow sugoi
is that him
nah maybe his his son and
his daughter-in-law
can I break this
oh what's that what
wow this
okay well
we'll have fun let's try to have fun
it's taunting pairing I have to be fast
in this game right
I don't know if I can
press down to jump you need to put it
down button yeah hold down in the
direction to crawl
okay
thank you for a very nice oh
yeah
[Music]
for a nice tutorial yay
you can break marble and met the blocks
underneath you wait for body slam press
down while in here okay oh
music is exciting
[Music]
some blocks may be hidden keep an eye
out for them press left destroy them
left or right right
[Music]
oh no it's actually always left
okay so Square
[Music]
what is this it's a little is it a pizza
without all the toppings or is it a
mushroom or what what the [\h__\h] is that
a mushroom I don't welcome mushrooms on
pizzas
press left the square to do the grab
Dash it can destroy marble blocks
whoa okay so any kind of destroying with
square
hold our T to start
um
run if you hold RT then jump on a wall
you will start wall running okay RT R2
okay
[Music]
hey
no oh
[Music]
press down well while running to jump
off the wall uh us
press down I wanted to jump off the wall
okay so basically jump again keep our
tea to help to stick on the other walls
but so am I not running them you can
also use the grab Dash to start a wall
run while in the air just keep RT hell
uh wait
no is that bad is that what they wanted
me to do I felt like they didn't want me
to do that necessarily but um
[Music]
that's fine okay
the music is fire even if I don't get
along with the game I will say
um I cannot deny and at any point that
the music is not fire
press square and hold our teeth for a
quick start with the bun
[Music]
what
didn't isn't that one
what's the difference to what I've been
doing so far I don't know what
I don't know it starts faster I guess so
you can also jump after pressing in
order to do a long jump
[Music]
jump after pressing hmm
was that a long jump
I think so otherwise I wouldn't have
wait a normal jump hmm
you can also simply run up a slope next
to a wall to automatically start wall
running
oh wait uh
let's see I thought he implied that I
can just walk against it and it happens
automatically I guess not
what what is the easiest cheese it's the
cheese I think okay I have no problem
with cheese I mean I'm not the one who
would order a Quattro for machi
run against it well that was fine I
think
whatever it's fine while doing a Quran
hold down to destroy blocks in a small
Gap
[Music]
okay rock one is this right okay
release down this is almost to remember
ah what kind do I like what kind of
question is that my favorite is so no
one pineapple pizza
separately
both gladly with some corn
release down and keep holding our teeth
to continue
the macron
oh
okay
well yeah okay
[Music]
look at me
how do I do this wait
there we go
hold down during a math run while on the
air to do a dive okay
[Music]
oh I think I did it he even went into a
diving position very cute
in order to destroy metal blocks you
need to gain speed by doing a math run
you can hold left to go even faster two
left like Korea left even if I'm going
right I know right now it says right ah
I'm switching okay oh
[Music]
like switches depending on the uh
position I'm looking towards okay ah
okay
no problem oh [\h__\h] wait
[Music]
I watched a little bit of Amish stream
playing this
uh and I don't know uh she already seems
pretty far in the game but yeah
I don't know if I'll ever get that but
wait they want me to have momentum from
like all the way here or what
oh okay I did it
[Music]
she's done wow
so good big respect I want to find out
why all of the girls like good at Cali I
mean immediately jumped onto the game
when we got perms like oh my God oh my
God we have to play it immediately
everybody was so eager to play it right
away I need to understand why
let me pour some tea really quickly
so it can cool down by the time I need
it
the [\h__\h] is that heavy
why is that jug so heavy
[Music]
Rico's Pizza and because OST a nice
indie game
understandable I get it running down the
slope will make you go even faster wow
wow
okay so far I'm okay please do not give
me much more instructions otherwise I
will crumble to turn while retaining
masks around press the opposite okay
oh
try turning before falling down a hole
you will retain your speed once on the
ground
[Music]
before falling down
what did you see that book was that not
it
before falling
foreign
[Music]
that [\h__\h]
I first tried it but wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait I didn't think there
would be many more
[Music]
um
do they want me to go back up here
I would say no nice nice okay very good
[Music]
while at high speed hold up then release
it to perform the super jump
I have to already have some big speeds
and then up you can also adjust your
position with Left Right while you are
holding up
ah
wow
and then
I have to let go wait oh
[Music]
uh
whatever I want to go up okay should I
can I jump through that little block
[Music]
this is very very very freaking dorky
this art style and everything oh I
didn't notice I got a tomato on the way
I love tomato
[Music]
it's so silly yeah
I wonder if Japanese members are gonna
pick up on the en hype of this game did
any any Japan member play this yet maybe
they can't play it because language or
coyote did
hi
hey
[Music]
press left and then down immediately to
go through gaps faster uh
I don't know if I will remember this my
brain is like filled up now
it's right she rates Clinton she lost
her mind why why
am I gonna lose my mind too
cloudy said
[Music]
I don't want to end up like that
but hey I don't I don't understand why
my memory card is full
[Music]
[\h__\h] out
ah Mamma Mia
[Music]
did it again oops I Did It Again
she's not my Senpai but she's so
professional
I keep thinking she's the same bye
really I think that's really it
uh Prince left
oh
oh I don't I won't remember that you
guys have to write that down write it
down
First grab them down yeah
this is so Sadie
[Music]
you guys are my cheat sheet
you can grab things with the grab Dash
and throw them by uh left again
the grab Dash
you mean this thing right and then throw
them by pressing the thing again
okay okay okay
learning by doing oh should I have oh
gotten the okay
[\h__\h]
back
hey hey
a strong Pizza okay
easy easy
[Music]
collect these in order to get a bit get
a better rank some can only be acquired
during this game I don't care about
ranks I will not care about rankings
this game is already difficult enough
um
uh
wait wait uh
okay wait how
wait how
can I not break them what
[Music]
um
yes oh I can't okay you need to save
most of the dudes in the cages in order
to advance to the next floor they will
give you money to pay Mr stick if you
miss too many of them you will need to
replay some levels okay
is that
is
what dynamic between us it's almost as
good as the dynamic between fulamoko
[Music]
destroy John the pillar in order to open
the exit gate this will reserve a
reverse the solid pillar blocks
but reverse them
[Music]
I don't understand
[Laughter]
I still can't destroy them right away
I feel like there's a lot of pressure on
me right now I don't know how to play
the game
[Laughter]
I want this warmth
get out now okay uh
my panic panic oh but we did it the
tutorial is finished I'm very proud
[Music]
what what now
ah okay
what the [\h__\h] is those eyes is those
eyes
oh that reminded me of the sand levels
from Super Mario Sunshine
what is it is scary cheese oh it's
scared of me
to come back
wow whoa
how do I get wait uh okay uh wait I know
how to get the pineapple this is like
you know after learning all the
vocabulary to a test then you have to do
the test
and try see if you remember all the
vocabulary and I do not remember the
vocabulary
uh
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
[Music]
am I doing this right wait wait I want
that I don't know what they are there
for six
wow
stupid bastards [\h__\h]
how much did he take from me
he called him quick you think so
did I miss something there
maybe not
the background is so weird
oh oh those are ah those are that's a
ladder
wait I want to do the jump down on him
okay I thought if I was Speedy then
maybe it would be fine
oh
this is my first time catching a Kiara
stream early and hence I'm disturbed by
other YouTubers if you don't mind Kiwa
kiawa as I'll find myself comfy in your
wings
ah you're very welcome please continue
to further going down the the W because
you started with Kiara and then you
ended with kiawa next step is kiwawa
okay
[Music]
maybe you should wake up early more
often from now on
thank you
that was a panic grab
[Music]
a left or up I guess left
we all went through that transition
didn't we
of going from wait
going from Kiara to Kiara to yeah kiwawa
and then Wawa
at the master room what is it with this
uh this Leaf this is basil leaves maybe
I love basil
nice very nice can I like get something
here this kind of stuff
no okay
she called me a chicken
Marissa what is that betrayal what the
[\h__\h] oh wait should I have thrown it
against this that's fine I'm fine
without it
what
these can't be broken right oh yeah oh
okay left left side then
I might not want to jump I want to go um
okay
what is this only
only what only pink people
there is that you're here again you
can't get enough of me huh what's your
defense I need to find Jerome
I don't have [\h__\h] time to find Jerome
do I look like I got time for that I'm
I'm on edge I need to focus 100 on my
own problems
ow
I never said you should play this game
do you like games like this like
normally it's not really my thing
[\h__\h]
[Music]
oh wait wrong
yeah normally this is not really my my
kind of game either as you guys may know
but every once in a while kiwama tries
things
that are not perfect wow that was
so far I'm doing still okay
okay don't scream so much you have
throat problems right now
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] is that it's a Sonic a big
wibbly wobbly sausage
oh
yeah not only kids
I know it's a game that makes me want to
scream but I
well I create like a like a little
earthquake
when I do that
I saw it coming but I didn't think
that's what was gonna happen
I freed someone again yeah I look cool
what's with that monkey he was really
scared of me
okay zooming is kind of fun once you get
like uh the hang of it
oh
my god there was something there can I
break it
thank you
is that a checkpoint
guessing so
um
[Music]
wait
I'm so clumsy oh wait I could go through
that
on the right side I didn't realize
oh wait
I wanna I wanna go there now
I'm trying to not lose my speed and all
that okay okay
and now
up there okay wait one more time without
getting interrupted by the enemy
[Music]
you know when I was talking to an Arissa
yesterday I found out something about my
London trip well it's okay
and I said like there's like musicals
going on everywhere is that Jerome
and and oh God
and literally it felt like every musical
had its own building
and there was one that stood out to me
and rmt
but we we didn't know what to make of it
as I said I think it said six
and me and me and narissa were talking
about the tutors
uh because I told her that's like my
favorite time period
And she said Oh she listens to a Musical
soundtrack that was like about the
tutors
[Music]
the time
and and um uh yeah uh
and apparently it's it's that Musical
that I saw but I was like that doesn't
that doesn't look like related to the
tutors at all because it's like oh God
okay
what's going on
[Music]
press up and [\h__\h] out
whatever I'm not going back obviously
[Music]
Pepino
oh God
I can't I'm gonna I'm not gonna make it
that's me
am I going the right way
[Music]
I can't believe it how did I get B rank
I had like five seconds left
oh
[\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
hey for my first try I would say that's
good I got 50 bucks too
Oh I thought it was failing I was
definitely failing I was on my path to
failure
that time does not affect the score
Oh I thought I thought that was even
without the time I wasn't doing so well
like getting a lot of damage
anyway what I was trying to say is uh
yeah there was this musical that was
like it was like advertised on this
building
uh that we walked by
and it was like six ladies dressed in
outfits that were kind of like looking
to me like like Kiss
the artist singer
uh like really like spiky dark modern
outfits mmm it's the musical that
apparently has been around for a while
yeah and uh
so nerissa mentions it and says it's
like about the tutors about the wives
and I'm like what the [\h__\h] eh what so
those six ladies represent The Six Wives
and they sing about who suffered the
most or so she told me that and I'm like
what the [\h__\h] now I have to go back to
London to watch it hell no
I don't wanna but I'm really interested
in that even though it's kind of weird
that it's like so so modern
what I would love six really
and there is a nerissa told me quite a
bit about the the music aspect
um
interesting
I love how the pineapple is grooving how
can people like dislike pineapple pizza
look at him grooving
he's like
this is like next level moonwalk he's
doing it while like
turning
he's moonwalking while turning
six is good are we in the next level
what is this choir
there's a rat chasing
what what was he a chef
six is also playing in New York City
well but if anything I feel like one
should watch it in London or the UK
because British accent you know they're
supposed to have British accents
oh wait I should I should go up [\h__\h]
wait
thank God the time isn't being counted
uh here wait can I ah can I not go down
from here wait can I
no oh okay then oh wait oh there's a
secret room no
what is this
[Music]
foreign
I guess I'm going down
[Music]
oh but here is friend
um wait how do you do this thing again
and they told me that I told you guys to
write down uh
um
[Music]
sorry guys I really I'm still like
button matching the controls
[Music]
I grabbed them before I could even land
on him
wait
um
uh wait wait wait wait wait how am I
gonna do this
um
but I need more speed
no maybe whatever I don't need to do it
from that side I can do it from the
other side no
[Music]
okay
there you go
[Music]
thank you I hate you what is that
supposed to be anyway cheese and armor
wait I'm sorry
okay
wait this one needs to be broken too oh
this room again okay
wait I want to do that thing again
I did it before I can do it again uh
ah oh do I need like a little bit of
space above me for that but it's working
[Music]
quit screaming is it a princess I need
to save the Pizza Brain says
[Music]
do you hear those screams
that's all right
nice it's a big fat rat
it's good
okay no different red this is Casper
oh
scallops how long do I keep it until I
lose it or like until someone hits me
like in Mario well I'm like really heavy
with this
oh
jeez
until until I find a priest ah he will
pray me oh is this supposed to be a bad
thing or I'll guess so because I can't
roll
uh where do I continue anyway oh my God
what's going on
what is he doing
I can't believe he's eyes for the mouth
for the Casper a High Praise thank you
ah
cool okay
[Music]
never so do you like Lily Allen because
we gotta find even more similarities
I can't believe there's gonna be much
more because we already found so many
and there's no way there's no way
yesterday
at her you know after we found another
similarity I was like girl I I you you
literally you've been watching my
streams
so you must have like noted down
everything
uh you haven't heard of her oh my God
you've been you even wrote it
differently so I will tell you but uh I
told I said yo you definitely wrote down
all the things I like
is that still active
access really what you already liked
beforehand
when you met me
okay
there you go
[Music]
I know I don't want the preset let me go
do some stuff
you're not that dedicated
[Music]
taking notes not for you
don't go down the ladder man wait so do
I what what was that for then if I can't
go down here either
let me jump over the priest
wait how to hit
huh
[Music]
I need a slope what but how when I
hmm oh without stopping
am I supposed to do this without
stopping
[Music]
almost almost okay oh
so jumping over the priest is also like
the obstacle
[Music]
[Applause]
okay wait don't I have more things down
there I could go through the door but
I don't think I'm done yet here
[Music]
ah [\h__\h] yeah
yeah hi friends okay there we go now we
went full circle yay
what is this sign is it telling me that
I should not go down but maybe it's like
reverse psychology and like it's
supposed to tell me to go down
[Music]
but don't deaf below danger it's Doom
okay okay okay left is down there
it's actually uh by accident I was
trying to uh skip it
[Music]
[Laughter]
looks like this
it's so easy but now there were at least
no enemies you know
[Music]
ah come on
ah why every time Mamma Mia
[Music]
oh we got the sword again I see what for
[Applause]
[Music]
me
that was that was fast
I just I just came and I left
y
[Music]
up to Super town
okay
[Music]
the gang's all here is this like all the
all of them will there be more I need
the sword again
double jump my leech
with the sword
[Music]
but I need the speed no
fun
that's fun
[Music]
okay
do I need it again because there was one
more rat
um but it just brings me to some tomato
and cheese I want to try to get it
[Music]
now I don't need to start the whole
momentum from the beginning I assume
[Music]
okay open the door it's funny because I
was just watching The Charmed episode
where
um uh Piper gets the excaliburb
huh
[Music]
I know I know for most of you guys what
I just said makes no sense and you
cannot relate
[Music]
was a fun episode you know it let's go
you said before you watched Charmed it
my mom used to watch that show yeah I'm
like re-watching it uh at the moment I'm
pretty like getting pretty close to the
end like even cold hasn't showed up in
like a whole season I think
Rome
I'm happy that you finally have an em
member in your time zone well she
doesn't stream in my time zone if you
mean Larissa but she watches me while
doing work it seems
[Music]
I want the sausage
sorry I'm getting stuck
trying to do the super jump but it won't
let me there we go
[Music]
let's just go up there normally
I can't lose control anymore
okay another sword
um
what that has a lot of information
okay
I'm guessing we have to go down first
what do you mean it's already Pizza Time
wait no I'm not just am I going back
already
see
wait I'm not
what
I'm not ready for pizza then how do I
even get out of this
[Music]
okay
this is already a disaster
foreign
[Music]
no more [\h__\h] ups now uh
oh is it there but I can't go there
right yeah okay thanks for showing me
[Music]
well
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
hey
oh man
give me the time
[Music]
okay uh uh left or right I left
I don't want it
huh
ah [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] no I'm I'm I'm so done can you redo
from the point where the pizza time
starts
[Music]
I don't know how to get there
I'm not gonna make it
ah
I'm so [\h__\h]
I don't remember how to get fast through
this kind of ah we're redoing it we're
redoing we're 100 redoing it oh my gosh
oh my God
sayonara
what
oh
[Music]
my God
I thought time is over when it's over
put some big pizza showed up
I don't understand and I got rank a
even though I was so bad
by the skin of my teeth
two two people said that I never heard
that before
that was beyond clutch it counts down uh
till Pizza spawns it still needs to
catch you oh but it was right there if
Pizza catches you that's when it's over
oh
no I I don't know if I don't think I've
ever heard that maybe I've heard it
before but it sounds very unfamiliar oh
I have a face
please
Poppins 10 out of 95 secret zero
Treasures I don't give a [\h__\h]
what did it say I should go
you could do a flying uppercut by
pressing up and then left this can work
as a sort of double jump and can also
dispatch enemies in the air okay
for sale oh hello hundred bucks for what
for like a new level
okay so you have to do this I guess boss
door oh can I do another normal level
before doing the boss
you're like that that up there's some
stuff up there but it did say something
about meeting someone who am I meeting
next floor
plastic cook the one and only that's the
only outfit I have
uh okay
I met him oh okay okay wait did I do
this one before
is that where I came from
I
did what I told you and bought the bus
gate from Mississippi
this one's new okay
let's do it ancient cheese
guys you know what I saw today you guys
tweeted it at me gothic the classic RPG
oh it's gonna be on switch
kind of a remaster because it did say
something about Graphics being improved
I am kind of a little bit excited you
know
a bad nowhere no more right I think
that's one of the games that I try to
get permission for
but couldn't nice one Chihuahua but
maybe let's go that way
[Music]
what's up
German Channel game oh should I but I
feel like oh that's gonna barely have
like because like you need to understand
German I don't have so many German
speaking viewers
was that the game that I was thinking
about playing on my German Channel
I think I remember some talk about that
[\h__\h] know what is this
can I break that
huh there's an eye there
do I need more momentum
full speed okay cool okay
[Music]
uh
okay wow your iPhone
6.
20 memberships thank you blank
uh okay
[Music]
do I lose something when I uh fall down
like items or points or stuff oh
[Laughter]
I don't okay
point
yeah
for the secret ah [\h__\h] huh maybe I
should go slowly can I do it slowly
without running
let me try with double double but ah the
cheese thingies they disappears so fast
[Music]
remember eggs get new wallpaper oh yeah
I just uploaded the new wallpaper for
the members on the community board
[Music]
ah try jab tapping jump faster I'm
really tapping it really fast
money
that's always where it gets me
is that checkpoint now
[\h__\h]
was it yes okay I should ah
what
[Music]
just run I [\h__\h]
just run okay oh
thank you okay back to business
oh [\h__\h] I should have picked that up
where where did I come from where am I
going I need to get out of this room
again
whoa
no no kid
foreign
[Music]
but I have no speed
let's have complete what did I do
41 sets of cheese platforms okay cool
but I need to get how maybe from Up
maybe from up going down
right okay
so bad
[\h__\h]
okay
[Music]
okay and now from up we go down maybe
this one also can just be done with
running
okay yes yes yes
[Music]
okay
oh what
it doesn't look like I could destroy it
what
[Music]
Yum Yum Yum
the biting sounds are so
um
yummy
[Music]
my right hand the grip I have on the
controller is starting to hurt me
[Music]
I'm into my singing this summer not
really this this mounting sound I like
but generally
um
this is kind of
[Music]
um
stupid to say because I do it sometimes
too but I don't like uh eating sounds
most maybe some eating sounds are more
like bearable than others
like on stream but then in real life
it's even worse like I I if somebody is
eating next to me
who like munches with their mouth open
or just makes really loud noises ah
I cannot stand it
and it's difficult because sometimes you
know it's a culture thing they just like
in their culture it's normal to eat with
their mouth open
so it's like
but for me
it's so unappetized I'm appetizing for
me I don't do it
um
[Music]
I closed my mouth I try really hard to
eat uh quietly
as much as I can I even like even when
my mouth is closed and for example I eat
something really crispy I hear it in
inside my head and I'm like [\h__\h] it's so
loud I want to eat more quietly but
that's it's in your head it sounds more
it sounds more loud they're gonna is I
hope where am I going
okay
[Music]
don't you hate it when like
yeah you munch so loudly inside your
head you're disturbing yourself
is this why you can't slap Ramen no
that's not it secret on the left
um yeah
[Music]
where is the place where I need to bring
the key to left left left left right
[Music]
gum
like for example ah like when watching a
movie in the theater where do I go
uh and there's like a quiet moment but I
want to eat like my popcorn and in my
head it sounds so loud although nachos
are probably louder than popcorn I feel
like
and then I I I'm like even when I
already put a popcorn in my mouth I will
stop munching
[Music]
when like a a quiet moment happens like
an emotional quiet scene in the middle
of me eating
let's go oh
did I stop stop watching too
people actually hear it but like for me
I hear it in my head so I'm like um I
better stop eating for a moment
[Music]
ah I wanna open that up but wait okay
um
probably not even audible but it's up
anyway yeah stop it unless you're biting
her do that for your streams
at least so let the person next to me
doesn't you know get bothered by it
charged and press down thank you thank
you thank you
sometimes people get the most basic
things you know how it is right
pineapples
[Music]
and pineapple apple pie
what a nice shot
oh okay so now we're using bombs against
the caspers maybe that's what I should
have tried against the rats in my house
in Japan
maybe that would have worked out of all
the things I've tried
I need another bump
oh [\h__\h]
okay it doesn't hurt me
[Music]
and it doesn't seem to have a timer
maybe a little bit from a distance
[Applause]
bye
yeah
foreign
[Music]
but maybe you know like these kind of
games I don't have much experience with
them
so I struggle with them I'm way better
with like 3D Platformers I think than I
am with 2D Platformers right
you guys can
confirm that I think
where was there a bomb
[Music]
I need a bomb here too I hear
okay
easy
[Music]
listen you bring up Mario 64 but
that's like an exception first of all
and you know
you know what camera is
[Music]
so it's not my fault
I want to destroy this bastard
but now he's not moving to the left
anymore
oh
to go right but okay
yeah cause the sunshine I didn't do so
bad with Sunshine didn't I
think wow
[Music]
that was cheesy
what's everybody's favorite pizza guys
tell me
[Music]
uh what the [\h__\h] is this
so what what happens if I hurt him 10
times
wait I'm not ready for that I feel like
I barely did stuff here so there we go
I feel like it's better to look around a
bit more to open up more paths or so
possibly but okay we're done with this
is that it
um
wait maybe
I want to get to a rank before
activating him
wait why do I care about the rag right
now
why do I care about the rank I said I
won't care about the rank because it
will stress me the [\h__\h] out
is that the only area to explore here it
looks like there's more it's confusing
me
God damn it okay
this guy this guy now
[Music]
[\h__\h] you finally
okay how do I I can't break this right
because I need the sausage
what
[Music]
okay I want to go back to the top oh
wait
[Music]
okay okay
uh from the top
okay fine
and we got the the sausage okay
my back paddle even more
that works if it works it works
what else did I miss
[Music]
okay how many points do I get for this
kind of stuff anyway
there we go now I didn't pay attention
I was going to pay attention ah no ah
that's a secret level okay okay we can
do it hundred oh
no secret
what are the question marks
what are they doing here
[Music]
oh I it doesn't like immediately explode
oh
what oh wait was there a timer after all
I was taking my time I thought this bomb
was kind of like Invincible a bit Yeah
but
what is this
uh question marks like the small one's
okay but what is this one
[Music]
looks like some kind of like cartoon
character I mean okay they all look like
cartoon characters but he looks like
legits he could be designed for a
cartoon
okay now I feel like I'm I want to
why do I have to reach a the a rank
because like I see it filling up uh red
and then I guess it turns to a red do I
have to do that before
opening the
the
door to hell or
oh
doesn't matter
maybe can I still get it like after
opening the the pizza time
can it still change to a rank
okay okay okay
[Music]
now let's go there uh where was it
I don't know anymore where is going back
and where is going forward
I think here is forward
[Music]
is this is it is it
yeah right
that must hurt so much poor guy poor
Peppino
um
[Music]
okay
okay Wawa come on you you have clutched
it so many times you can do it this time
too but wait why is there something on
the left side am I going left am I going
to the left
I guess so
I'm already I'm already panicking
foreign
[Laughter]
can I go down or do I have to go up here
because I'm not capable of going up
there right now
no I have to go up
some people say I can but most people
say also I have to go up down this extra
okay
uh
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
ah
government
wow
[Music]
oh no
ah no because I'm a struggle here too
really thank God oh my God
[Music]
hello
no
it's over
yeah
[\h__\h] hell I get stuck in the
stupidest
the thing is I can't do the huge jump
unless I
thank you
[Music]
I can't
oh okay all of this again
[Music]
and I probably would still fail again
let's be real
oh my God huh
I need to try the screamless
[Music]
sure okay no I'm okay it was really
funny it was just like what the [\h__\h]
how am I ever gonna make it
oh [\h__\h]
not so bad I don't really have to do
this right but I guess I'm doing it why
am I doing it
[Music]
my stop button isn't working
why does it keep on telling me I'm lame
you're lame oh
what
what's up button is working
[Music]
ah
no it's on USB cable
let me add it yeah
[Music]
why why
sheets come on
wow amazing
okay
just run just run now we already know to
just run which will now help us here see
without wasting any time oh yes yes yes
yes
okay okay
[Music]
I'm already doing everything smaller
than before don't you think can I break
this one too yeah okay
[Music]
should I have gone left actually I don't
know right I mean because now I went
left but there was a path on the other
side
should I
is it smarter Jerome is on the right
okay
also wait I didn't even go to the very
back where I need to use
the key I'm confused like some some of
this is like too
unlinear for me
[Music]
oh there you aren't your room thank you
for joining the party
yeah that's all this room is okay
I already have the key right
the real game starts when you need to
escape okay the thing is once the thing
spawns you have no chance right like
it's other sticky it seems like you have
absolutely no chance
it's like actually a miracle that has
for me I made it the previous time
oh big door Ah that's the beginning oh
okay I circled back to the beginning
is there actually anything up here
wait
I feel like maybe there's a secret there
no
I don't know
you can outrun it I want to see someone
do that it was so fast it was like
straight in my face
it gave me no chance
[Music]
oh wait I feel like I haven't even
opened this one up before
[Music]
it's going to need lots of speed for
that
I don't know how because I need to make
those blocks disappear first
okay
oh higher not speed oh [\h__\h] it I don't
care what's down there do I care
wait
there we go pineapple I don't care if it
was anything else I would not have cared
I wouldn't have thought that that was
worth the effort but pineapple all of us
love it
foreign
[Music]
who has experience playing this game
because I want to know is it just me my
right hand I'm putting so much
especially into my
um little finger and the ring finger I'm
putting so much power into it so much
strength yeah
not to say okay
oh it's a little finger workout if you
for some particular reason need some
muscles in your fingers are there
muscles in your fingers like maybe
really tiny ones
but you can't really get like Bob right
but this is one of those games if you
play it too long you only get worse at
it right at least that's what I feel
like will happen
foreign
[Music]
it's only been one and a half hours
oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] it really hurts
I've never played with controllers this
is very noticeable right now
oh my God
[\h__\h]
I gotta get up there
walking out
am I wasn't paying to eh wait I left it
what why did I leave it I looked at the
comments
no bombing and reading what
what
[Music]
my butt there's
the Casper too
I'm going to get a little bit angry
sooner or later
I will not be still understanding
anymore
okay can I break this one maybe with
more speed I'll be back later
[Music]
I'm so dumb
remember you can grab this
what what is that what is that I don't
know what that means
does that know what I'm doing all the
time
all right there it goes okay
[Music]
I mean it's what I'm trying to do a lot
of the time but I'm just not
accomplishing it I'm trying it though
[Music]
okay let's get secrets
ah okay this one this one wasn't so bad
I think it's just timing
of the bomb but there you go first try
was it not a different guy last time
guys there will be a hollow talk next
week happy surprise
saying it now but for more info wait for
the schedule
[Music]
I was actually already cooking it when
you guys mentioned it yesterday
[Music]
wait how do I break the Tomato again
a surprise Pikachu face
I love surprise Pikachu face speaking of
like in our like Pokemon unite
tournament uh
uh Discord
people are like saying what Pokemon they
will use as it seems like we have to
announce that what what the [\h__\h] what am
I supposed to use what do I use what do
I use guys tell me
did get back to me yeah we're probably
gonna uh indeed be doing it
uh I think uh
[Music]
uh was Tuesday I'm not 100 sure
what Vaporeon and Gardevoir
blastion
okay seems like there's not like like
one popular option
and is anything
powerful or are there like bad ones
are there any Pokemon that I should stay
away from out
[Music]
oh they did say no
Mewtwo
[Music]
okay
oh this one's the long one okay okay
okay let's run
oh
my God
pretty smooth
it's more than the first time
just check the wiki for tearless okay I
gotta I gotta do some research man I
thought I could go into this without
practice without doing anything without
any knowledge but it seems to be more
serious than I thought it was gonna be
I thought it was going to be low effort
but uh oh dear
ah
come over here
what do I do what do I do
huh
so terrifying
[Music]
I don't want to fail again I'm gonna
Rage Quit like coyote where did coyote
Rage Quit pass does did she get past
this so I would be impressed
I don't think most of the member played
serious herself would maybe fallen and
Kyla
only completed what she's
no gamer
okay wait I almost had it
okay big big time saves
wow
unnecessary I don't know why I'm doing
it but I'm doing it okay
can I do it here
are they okay
[Music]
okay
calm
calm and collected
[Music]
okay okay
I don't know what comes after this
that's the problem
what the [\h__\h]
I'm so stupid to go up
[Music]
where do I go
not down okay
I'm crumbling
no no
no no no no no probably
[Music]
no
I honestly think the times they don't
give me any extra time
[\h__\h] you where do I go I'm here ah
[Music]
it's like a horror game
I did better but still oh my God Mama
Mia why is so red in the car
oh this game is gonna kill my throat
again
oh my God
[Music]
trying to make some Watson concoction
here
I feel like I was so far
you have pizza time is so scary
because I'm so sorry
oh [\h__\h]
why monster
I was close to the exit really it didn't
really feel very cool
uh
okay we're turning off the other thing
it's making me stressed yeah I don't
know
ah [\h__\h] oh God
it wasn't for the pizza time I'm telling
you
[Music]
and they're giving no checkpoints I
can't believe this game
back
wait did I need all the speed for this
oh yeah
well how about we don't do the secret
this time
oh wait
gotta go right yeah yeah
I already did them a million times
don't have patience for this anymore
okay
[Music]
you know we do want to go to the right
side first
you got him
okay
I feel like yeah I'm definitely getting
more like familiar with the levels
the stages
so it's like overall we get there faster
sure but what is that I got new what
club
for what we're getting spiked by the
fork guy
thank you I guess it's worth it getting
hurt
and wait where am I going with this huh
[Music]
I don't remember this part oh no that
did happen okay ah wait let me get the
tomato
[Music]
that's why I should put myself but I
guess the bottom line also is not really
I'm not in the way right
foreign
[Music]
it's got some issues
let me do that again
last [\h__\h]
I hate these ones oh wait I didn't open
it up before I think what is the ding
dong for
what is the ding dong for
points okay but they don't give me time
huh also like I was saying
spilling the clocks barely give me any
time man I'm I'm trying to collect them
but I feel like it's barely healthy
maybe every little small one all of them
together make a a decent difference uh
feels like nothing eh they don't give me
any points so why the [\h__\h] are they
depicted this [\h__\h] clock icons
what's giving me false hope thinking I'm
helping myself by getting them I'm not
doing anything
wow
[Music]
unbelievable
we are gonna cry
the copper it's not animal abuse believe
me
okay
uh wait is it time
oh okay it's okay
[Music]
Pest Control yes I am I'm working with
the pest control exactly
why do I always let them hit me can
somebody tell me
[Music]
you guys are probably asking that
yourself too right you don't have the
answer should we do the secrets I will
I'll do the secret at least once
this one's a bit easier anyway
I still haven't found that other secret
apparently it is free and I only keep on
finding too
but it's okay it's not about the secrets
it's about the trumps
[Music]
should have brought the bomb with me
the last secret is in the Pizza Time
room oh okay
oh
[Music]
wait
and wait how do I uh
break that
tomato thing again I don't need the bomb
right it's too far away
oh there we go
I guess I didn't have enough momentum
after all
[Music]
did I just Parry it for once oh my God
and there we go here we go
wait could I break this
I don't remember if I ever tried
oh yeah yeah okay okay
I think it's Pizza time it's a pizza
time I don't wanna
stay in piece of preparation time
[Music]
God speak but thank you
I can't do it
it's not enough time
this is not enough time
[Music]
no confidence no
no
uh
just follow the fake clocks
yeah and the guy is right the guys would
come point but sometimes I don't see
them and then I don't know where to go
also my chat stopped I only see it on
OBS one second
I did recommend hyperchat to the new
girls by the way I told them for big big
streams
they might want to use it just so that
it never happens to them what happened
to me
during my outfit reveal
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
all right
thank you
[Music]
well
thank you
[Music]
where do we go
what where do I go where do I go
down
[Music]
left or
oh
I'm not gonna make it I'm not gonna make
it
where where
yeah
[\h__\h]
I didn't see you
[Music]
laughs
I
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
laughs
[Music]
[Laughter]
sorry guys
this is it
I'd like to be better at it and play
more but um
I feel like I reached the difficulty
Spike that stops me
there's I can't
it was fun and and I'm not like you know
angry or so I'm just you know it's just
not um I'm not I'm not there I'm I'm not
there
it was fun though while it lasted I wish
it was a bit more easy just a little bit
just a tiny bit
just a little bit
another one
difficulty Spike too big for me I'm
sorry but it's okay it was fun while it
lasted for me
um
honestly I need baby version of game I
would appreciate baby version
uh I don't know if I'll try it again it
was honestly big fun but if I'm
struggling so early on here even after
trying so many times and like being
really calm and doing my best I don't
think I would ever be able to finish
this game
time to play Peppa Pig
Wario Land is the baby version okay okay
maybe I'll play Mario Land sometime
wow that was uh it's like it just makes
me so tense I wish the whole game was
with outfits at time
or if the if the clocks actually gave me
time I feel like I could do it
I don't understand why the clocks give
me points and not time
what the hell
it's okay I'll make my own pizza time
maybe depends on my hello fresh
ingredients if they can wait a few more
days then like until tomorrow because
then I can make my frozen pizza
uh I'm making my own pizza time
we have pizza time at home pizza time at
home
it's okay it's okay like I'm just like I
was laughing uh and and yeah I may have
been a little bit mind broken at the end
there but I'm okay I'm okay
I'm okay uh
uh good try I feel like I generally
didn't do so bad but I mean yes I did
but I I expect it to do worse didn't you
guys expect me to do worse
I expected you guys to expect me to do
worse
all right thank you
let's just let's just play Hotline Miami
next
I feel like I I Vibe more no it's not
about vibing but I don't know I just
had a better time at Hotline Miami for
some reason even though that's also kind
of like a a quick stressful time but I
like to take Hotline Miami quite slowly
a lot of the time anyway
Miami was fun
anyway that was my attempt at Pizza Time
and since it didn't take so long
now we have super chats time
let me just find something that makes
the chat easier to read
in my resources
in a while so you know it's nice to take
it easy although recently I've been
doing so many
um weirdly so many
uh
Chit Chat streams anyone
hope you guys have been enjoying that
because I feel like a lot a lot of
people they're always like hey
why why I know that to dance stream and
I'm like well because I like to keep the
tangents for long boring moments
where there's nothing to talk about in
games
and I know you know I like to always
have something
ready
to talk about and and also because
um I don't know
I feel like
even though
even though that's done is my strength
and I I tell the best stories
not I feel like for if it's only a
definite stream
I don't know
I don't know not so many people show up
compared to gaming streams so
I wish I could tell the chat
a little bit this this I don't like this
no
and and sometimes I'm just scared if I
don't have like very very many specific
topics like after travel
lined up then I'm honestly worried that
I don't have anything to talk about
um
no in OBS you can only like do 90
degrees and so on so it's kind of lame
maybe there's like a plug-in that makes
it possible but I don't know of any I
wish there was like a smooth
tilting thing let's uh let's use let's
use this
that's not quite fit the style
I think it's chat box really
okay
I do still have any happiness I guess
yeah
but not gonna tell them now
gotta spread out the tangents you know
I I'm actually happy that we got to read
Super Chat because because of that I I
get to use this
this office the wealthy office again
not quite not quite
you guys are welcome to stay my Super
Chat readings are always fun
hey
ah okay
let me be cute did you see what changed
did you see
you know I asked to get
um my blush
onto my new outfit
because I had it before on for example
the
casual one but I was told no
no because already used up all the
resources but I thought it's just copy
and paste but no I need to use up like
points
and I already used that but my points
yeah you know when I do the smiling
expression I asked for a blush long time
ago because my smiling expression in my
opinion just looks like my normal
expression mostly so I wanted to make it
more more different by adding the blush
but now I have to ask for like points
every like you know a slot every time
when I wanted in a new outfit
sad I don't have my points left
like some jrpg
skill points imagining like skill points
all the Japan tangents I don't even know
what Japan turns inside are left I guess
there's a karaoke
oh
I mean there's not much to talk about
there anyway
[Music]
well this reminds me when we are playing
something maybe GTA
uh when when when I need something to
talk about hmm
okay
I don't know if I'm supposed to tell any
details about it so I'm not gonna
explain any further don't worry guys
it's just
it's internal things
it's just so that we don't ask for like
a million things you know like five
million accessories like it has to stop
somewhere obviously
[Music]
for sure
which is understandable
should I keep these this bgm running
I think it's actually kind of okay ish
to keep it running
anybody who knows where I stopped
reading super chats
anyone is
[Music]
no idea
uh oh oh
let's jump to Super Chasm oh thank you
you only have to write the first one not
all of them thank you though maybe is it
because I like
read some earlier than others
super
charism wasn't that a Super Chat reading
stream
when was that is it this no
yeah
okay super chats from Super Chat reading
stream
and where are they order
let me type in Chasm
okay here it is
okay okay
uh
okay
um
whoa whoa my throat is kind of fine
right now by the way thank God I'm like
constantly drinking tea
I'm so I'm so British museum changed
please yeah why
you don't like it after all is it too
too weird for you
huh
bloody hell
a bit too tense okay okay
wait if I go somewhere else can I get
like less tense
music within the game
this the menu bgm
if it always stays like this then oh no
okay
this one's nice
hi icky Marshall let's go super tattoo
[Music]
uh
oh my God I feel like I haven't read
super traps in a million years
this feels so nostalgic to me
conduction mixtech Warriors
back of my groove
this is basically Nickelodeon the game
what do you mean
my stream or the game I just played
we all died in the accident remember you
have to let us go with me what are you
saying no oh
thank you
the style is very Nickelodeon you mean
the art style
I guess the art style
it's very freaky
very freaky like it's a scary cartoon
style
um
it's hideous I hate it I do think it's
hideous yes but it's fun funny I guess
it has its charm hideous and Charming
unhinged art style yeah
yeah
funny videos yeah yeah
I agree
I don't watch cartoons so I don't
understand what do you mean I don't
understand the Nickelodeon reference
that's just because I feel like
Nickelodeon in Europe didn't really have
a presence much
like for real for real
we had some cartoons like the the fairy
fairy all the fairy
or the very the fairies the fair
the odd Fair pet what the Fairly Odd
Parents yes
uh
for helping me out
uh and I don't know what else uh
um
the
Angela one creeped me out
uh but at the same time I don't know I
kind of liked it
SpongeBob yeah SpongeBob but I didn't
really watch much sometimes I would
watch it but Angela yeah was that a
thing like overseas too was it a
European thing on Pop I love Powerpuff
Girls Back in the Day yeah
yeah
the weird paper cut out Series so weird
yeah I think I maybe talked about it in
the past but that series it had a
website and on the website it had a game
and I played it when I was really young
and it was just freaky
it's just freaky I don't
can you still play it can I get perms
for it
some members these days right the en
members they they get perms for all
these weird ass old games
wait
Angela Anaconda game
it is creepy somebody I get a YouTube
recommendation from a German person
saying
this adult is saying it's like it messes
you up Gina lash it's a flash game let's
go Gina lash and the Temple of swirls I
think that's it
I think that's it
oh that looks like it's so creepy holy
[\h__\h]
where do you where do you even get perms
for something like this
Nickelodeon
Reinhardt oh my God I think this is it
huh
what why are several people mentioning
the Digimon movie
Digimon sorry
that's how German's saying it
she was edited into it what
why makes no sense
there was a short skit at the beginning
what
laughs
it makes no sense why are they in the
same world
German way is better thank you
I love you
it's like hearing Bae talk about stuff
what do you mean why why are you hurting
it was an ad at the beginning
what that was short of you know I'm
trying to advertise Angelina condo oh my
God why would you even try to advertise
Angela Anaconda nobody wants to see that
okay perms lost before even getting them
good job Mama
yeah don't compare me to Bae she knows
even less [\h__\h] than I do
apparently Bay didn't know what the PSP
is what the [\h__\h] I had a PSP I was so
happy I loved my PSP I had a pink PSP
um
it just eventually stopped working and
then I just stopped using it but
yeah
I think I played uh some tales of the
world games on the PSP
um
tales of the world Ray radiant radiant
Mythology
[\h__\h] amazing goat man I love I I yeah
I really love the PSP so much that I
wished they released more
um tails of games for it but they didn't
um
yeah but the tales of the World Series
was so different from the other Tales of
games but not in a way that you know you
know that phone game for example that I
was sponsored for the phone tales off
game that I showed you guys that one was
so different
but I let's just say I prefer the
difference of the tales of the word a
world uh thing like you know you can
make your own character and all that but
it was still it still felt like a tails
off game it didn't felt it didn't feel
weird
um
the the phone game I don't know
that was like so different but
um
I mean the art style was the same kind
of but
I don't know I don't know I didn't play
much so hard to really judge it anyway
it had a Tales of fighting game what
Tales of attorney on PSP was my first
ass
I think I
oh it got terminated oh dear
I think I was like hoping to play Tales
of attorney on my PSP but I never got to
it oh I would love to
but now my my PSP doesn't work anymore
you played it on the PSP I played Hazel
graces
F on a different console
really loved it
um
but you guys know some Tales of games
makes me happy
oh yeah PS3
see it isn't for PSP oh that was on PS3
um
[Music]
buy a new PSP is it worth it I don't
know just for one game PSP never really
had many games that I was interested in
to begin with
um
no I never played the OG on the SNES
sadly
I would like to
someday
okay let's go let's read oh my God
please mama please just read the super
chats okay it's not so hard
[Music]
she about to blame us yeah your fault
for being interesting
Garden five thank you soon lyrics
[Music]
the day I finally accepted that whole
life is part of my life at last year
so a year ago there was a point where
you were like I accept whole life as
part of my life now
that's so so deep and serious
and also my birthday I hope our
restaurant's Eternal Prosperity I'm so
late and you're probably never gonna
watch this
happy birthday
[Music]
uh this is ages ago I think
oh man is it gonna is it gonna reach him
is it gonna reach him this message
um
Ramen boy 21 dinosaurs
thank you
oh
prevents you from shrimping oh oh I do I
I know what you mean I do shrimp too and
I was wondering you know I should
probably prevent that too there's a neck
pillow that prevents you from shrimping
[Music]
I need to find that what does it look
like what what's the shape
um
like a little belt
like a belt around your head that's
scary
yeah most people were more in the FF
Camp rather than on the
on the Tails Camp secret lab kind of
looks like crony's pillow oh
maybe I can find it if I look it up on
Amazon
um
[Music]
oh thank you I need to I need to
continue that conversation I've been in
contact with them
uh thank you for the support
okay
guess who has a job and can afford to
put that again oh this fangirl haven't
been watching a lot of streams But A
lot's been happening I found my lost
tattoo oh I thought how long was she
lost I hope I can stay around a bit more
now I love you Mama
thank you I wanna what job did you get I
hope you're gonna have fun there I hope
it's gonna treat you well
and keep your cat safe
um
very important speaking of keeping your
cat safe um remember yesterday when I
was saying at the end of the stream like
it's weird my cat is meowing so much
I think I know why
oh
uh after so after the Stream
I stayed seated for quite a while I uh I
went into a phone call with narissa
and we talked for how long was it
does Discord say how long it was
I think it does doesn't it
wait I'm scrolling scrolling I sent her
so many messages
ah yeah okay it took an hour
it took an hour and then and then even
afterwards uh I sent her I was like
listening to new jeans
as the listening to new jeans showing
her all the songs giving her
recommendations because she didn't know
about new jeans really yet so I was
getting her into new jeans and I was
singing this was past midnight I was
singing along a little bit to new jeans
until like
the call ended around midnight right and
then I I was done recommending her new
jeans at like two
2 30.
yeah maybe around 2 30 a.m and then I I
was like stalling so so much I was so I
don't know in a good mood and excited
and I didn't I didn't really feel like
doing
the starting the process of going to bed
um
yeah when I was tweeting ETA that was
around that time
so
that was like three hours of me just
messing around after the Stream
and then I finally get up and I I go
and see
that the door to my apartment was open
um and I'm like what no
no it was not like completely open it
was like a little bit open
I swear smoothie this is the first time
this movie opened the door in my
presence
I didn't think she would do it while I
was there because I thought that was
something she would only do uh when I
wasn't around
but seems like she was really [\h__\h]
bored
but I am I am just wondering
how was this door open and did any other
people pass
like the outside of the door and hear me
talk
what how long was was it already open
during the stream probably because maybe
that's when why she was meowing so long
so now I decided I will always
lock it like from the inside as well
so that uh yeah she won't be able to
open it from the inside
this is so embarrassing
why aren't you lagging it up because
normally
capable of jumping up the dwindle
towards the inside and while hanging on
it it's a relatively heavy door
yeah I was singing for blood at the end
really loudly so I wonder if anybody
heard that
the thing is like I'm just talking to
myself and there's no music they just
they would only hear me singing so
that's also kind of hard to pushy
oh my God
oh my God I hope I hope nobody heard
anything
uh
no my door like locks automatically from
the outside but from the inside it
doesn't so yeah now now I'm locking it
don't worry
that's the first time she did that in my
presence
I sang it well yeah
foreign
when I was like introducing new genes to
narissa the whole time I was listening
to new jeans and like singing along a
little bit you know
what you're eating hey what's your ETA
what's your ETA what's your India
what's your ETA be there right now
there's that boy on my arms
[Music]
of course I know what eta means
estimated time of arrival that's why
they sing what's your estimated time of
arrival what's your estimated time of
arrival
I know what it means
I use it too
so not an uncommon word yeah I showed
her the Powerpuff Girl crossover song as
well yeah yeah I showed her a couple
songs like Dido and OMG and the new Jean
song and
[Music]
um
what's it called
hey
[Music]
I don't like the Lucero film too yeah
yeah
super shy was filmed in my country I'm
so happy yeah and we turned out really
nice and pretty and colorful looks
really nice they used a lot of like uh
overseas like local backup dancers too
let's move to get outside probably she
was probably like just hanging around
outside until she got bored and then she
walked back in because when I was like
doing all this stuff afterwards after
um
after streaming she also was just like
chilling in my room for a little while
so she wasn't like outside the whole
time
yeah I would think um
we did talk about Star Wars and you know
she was very very very understanding and
and nice about it
yeah she understands it's okay to have
like one thing where where we don't
agree but it's not like we disagree she
understands you know that I'm more into
like the fantasy kind of stuff rather
than sci-fi
um
yeah she already knew like she was like
I heard I heard we have one thing that
we don't agree with
okay it's okay
um
is Revenge of the Sith the third one
that I skipped
I don't know if I wanna go back into the
Star Wars thing and watch it again
yeah no no no
I skipped Jetty aha
what's her stance on Han Solo I don't
know ask her go nerissa don't even
answer these are questions you need to
bring to her in in her streams
although she did say she likes bad boys
so bad boys bands boys what you gonna do
what you gonna do when they come for you
bad boys bad boys
foreign
bad boys watch along Oh Yeah tomorrow's
member stream I don't know what we're
gonna do but I don't want to watch a
movie and we kept on we keep on pushing
Belle away
I'm sorry but I might make you guys
watch it with me this time
I I'm we watched the other two movies uh
in the poll that I did
we prioritize the other one I just won I
just I just want to watch Belle maybe
um
is that okay uh-huh
[Music]
yeah it was always losing in the polls I
feel so bad but I was like almost
interested in I I know I heard it's not
like that crazy good
but you know I think it's like a very
aesthetically pleasing anime movie
I have the Blu-ray for that whoa HBO Max
I'm good to go we're talking about the
anime you know that right
mm-hmm
oh yeah Guardians of the Galaxy 2 I
guess was also uh at some point one of
the options
but I don't know where that went
yeah the anime Belle
um
g-o-t-g free came out on Disney just
came out on Disney plus oh really nice
nice nice convenient very convenient
whatever you want to watch is fine with
me thank you
how about Fast and Furious for the
muscle cars ah you guys
all of the freaking movies you guys
recommend to me they're always something
like
masculine like boy movies I don't give
it give a [\h__\h] about them
yeah
think a little bit how about Millennium
Millennium actress I it's an anime movie
right I watched that one before a long
time ago I think I liked it
that's really good it was really good
I had watched literally anything maybe
that's how it should be
how about 500 Days of Summer all that
like uh
Raw rom-com movie I watched it too
million years ago of course
of course of course
what does that mean Arista is that a
movie
perfect blue
uh
I just saw a funny screenshot I think
um
I
got it
um what
[Laughter]
what she wants to watch it with me
perfect blue
perfect blue crony
okay okay okay okay
[Music]
wait this is scary some screenshots are
scaring me
okay okay okay
okay okay
I'll wait for you
and maybe we can do collab watch along
or we just watch it privately
it's about idles yeah I can see that I
can see that it's the thriller not lying
oh [\h__\h]
I almost said that's scary it's about
the Dark Side of being an idol oh oh
okay okay
let me raise up a chance
foreign
I can't remember if I sent you a super
chat for this yet so Congress on the
concert I love that the karate in La was
almost more excited than the crowd in
Japan for the four Fest really you think
so wait you're wearing both wow forever
thank you oh
yes thank you for bringing the concert
up because I wanted to mention this
anyway uh in case you guys haven't heard
or seen
and the en concert
they just released a new cut
and extended the the like one one month
uh period
uh for online watching if you have the
tickets you can watch it uh you have
more time for it and a lot of people are
saying it's already better I didn't
watch the new cut yet
they asked all of us for you know any
changes that we wanted unfortunately it
was during a time where I was busy as
[\h__\h] so I just said I'm Gonna Leave it
to you guys sorry
uh
I couldn't I couldn't make any uh
suggestions but yeah apparently my dance
break in the in the group song is
visible now
um
one week only one week okay thanks for
telling me I didn't know how much they
extended it
um but yeah make sure to watch it within
one week because then the new the new
cut is quite a different experience
apparently
um
yeah
I gotta watch it too
yeah I heard some girls are doing a
watch long I'm not planning on doing a
watch along but
um
you guys could possibly
watch it with those girls I don't I'm
guessing they didn't announce it that
they're doing it
I don't really want to do
watch along for this concert for some
reason I don't I don't I don't know I
just don't I just don't feel like it
maybe it's certain parts that I just
don't want to experience again
and be confronted with
like the MCS yeah
[Music]
this is [\h__\h] awkward I don't want to
see it
alone okay I I will cringe in my own
time but I don't want to be crunching in
front of you guys with you guys
yeah and I don't know
huh
but still watch the best betsukato watch
the different cut version
cool your MC was one of the best
yeah the one I did with Cali yep I agree
I always was not really I mean there was
some like points but we mostly went like
you know whatever like
the there were some points they wanted
us to mention but
me and Cali were just you know being
excited I think um that was fine
yeah
um but I think the MC's we all like kind
of gave feedback that next time
uh we would like to improve
this kind of stuff the MC sections
that's for us I think a really important
part
hug me sister yeah
I mean if there is a next time
but we're hoping for it and then if
there is then we'll try our best to
improve all the things that were
obviously lacking
um
I like that you plugged your upcoming
album
business woman Desu
was that a Drake and Josh reference no
I don't watch Drake and Josh
not one of those girls
[Laughter]
hey oh the hug me sister
yeah it was just what Cali said
I think didn't she like say something
maybe not sister but she said something
like hug me hug me hug me something
she did not say hug me dude this time
she did well there you go okay
quite surprising normally I'm just a
dude this time I was a sister
why was I your sister
like is this a is this an upgrade
oh yeah I used to be dog as well and a
dog dude
I hated to be dog I didn't want to be
dog
um but yeah it's a cool nickname I guess
dark dark
now I guess oh I wonder if she called a
dog she probably won't she probably
and he won't
irony
she'll give them a cuter nickname
than dogs what's up dogs
oh no it makes it's so logical but uh
yeah
somehow I feel like you wouldn't go up
to the dogs and say what's up dogs
ah
what's up dogs
would you prefer her saying again no
thank God that time is over
thank God
where are we yeah thank you Alex Smith
wow
Scarface duncast
[Music]
thank you for the rest of the chat
thanks for the warm welcome I admired
your passion for some time now was even
a tokomi concert 23 or 22. oh but never
had enough courage didn't know if I fit
into kfp after two plus years already
passed this year at dokumi K3 members
gave me the final welcoming push I
needed oh
are you here now
[Music]
I guess you're not here
but seems like German kfp member
who's been lurking for a long time but
now not really lurking anymore
tonight
foreign foreign
you are here now and you were here a
while ago
thank you for being in kfp I'm glad you
feel more more like you know part of it
or like more
more
I don't know how to say
you have more courage now nice thank you
for the support
[\h__\h]
don't don't don't
I said I said tutu in German
at
stupid sassy chickens
[Music]
foreign
whatever
[Music]
thank you lunchbox
thank you for the pinky lawyer funds for
your inevitable Texas what
well on your upcoming songs on Spotify
what's the best ways for it to count as
a lesson can I leave them on repeat on
Spotify I really don't know how it works
on Spotify I would think that Spotify
isn't since it is a music like listening
app thingy
I would think that it's not like YouTube
where it like doesn't count your views
if you repeat it all the time
I I would assume that Spotify
understands that sometimes you like
songs so much you listen to them on
repeat so they should count it I would
think so but I honestly don't know
um
but if you want to be like extra sure
then I guess just uh since it will be an
album just like go for the whole album
on on shuffle or by the order instead of
repeating the same one no
no
um
yeah I'm pretty sure that it will be
pennies but even if it's just pennies
um maybe for like music department it's
more about the actual
um amount of listens
uh just like seeing the statistics might
um you know impress the music department
and make them think okay okay
takamasikiara we can work with this okay
um
yeah so just listen to it on whatever
you know service you feel the most
comfortable with and you know get those
stats up seconds
[Music]
next
and the the Minecraft Tunnel finishing
one I suppose
um
[Music]
let's try to not stall so much this time
oh my God
don't ask me
don't Twitter me
X is Twitter now
foreign
give me some time to explain please I
drank beer because there was some kind
of late afternoon business meeting and
back to hotel watch dream about 1.5
hours and just gone sadly and I'm real
Korean
uh
uh we we cook
we cook it uh
[Music]
um
team
Ole
uh
[Music]
puppy
uh yo
hi
I understood nothing let me translate
this
[Music]
is
I've been abroad for a long time this
year but I still miss cook pop
is it food
let's cook Bob
what
[Music]
ah
oh it's Korean soul food oh super fries
um and I never use a piano not polish
though this name is unofficial abroad
name uh-huh and it's an alias that my
Ukrainian friend gave me when I was in
high school don't worry he's still alive
thank god
um
Naruto
renat
are you here
thank you for the two pinkies which in
total is red Super Chat
no thank you for the support and don't
worry don't worry about missing some
times when I mention you or when I meet
super chats or show as long as you still
catch up with me every once in a while
oh okay
thank you
[Music]
thank you drive by shrimping negative
sales of a deaf man
oh
I'm happy for you nice improved spoon
how do you improve a spoon thank you
Nathan cotton oh God yeah this was when
I was talking about public indecency
uh your friend's story is very detailed
for a second hand account can we have
her on girls talk and is she single
my friend likes to stay anonymous
you make it a spork uh-huh
nice theme I don't know if that really
improves it because you can't eat soup
that well anymore with a spork
is a deeper spoon a better spoon oh
making a spoon deeper isn't it yeah
that's something
about
or wider
I'm gonna need to find with a spork
[Music]
I feel like you won't get much of soup
never say it's soup with a tuning fork
well then she'll never
get rid of The Hunger I think
or maybe
you know
I feel like
I mean I'm probably very wrong but in my
head
like Sound Vibrations the sound
vibrations of a tuning fork
cook Maybe
vibrate
the soup
into your mouth
I don't know one could try one could
attempt to do so
it work for try I guess
you can imagine what I'm thinking about
right right
yeah acoustic levitation
thank you
yes I'm a physics genius
no I'm not going to demonstrate it if
anyone is going to demonstrate it it's
going to be nerissa it's gonna be her
magic trick whenever anybody you know in
Japanese
um like media
people especially for Idols they like to
ask them if they have like some special
talent so it's good to have something
prepared so nerissa the best thing I
could recommend is giving yourself this
skill this special talent so if anybody
asks you so nerissa do you have any
that you can share you bring out some
soup and the the tuning fork and then
with the vibration of the sound you
levitate the soup into your mouth and
people will be so [\h__\h] impressed I'm
telling you
like for real
nobody can top that
I would stand and clap me too standing
ovation
mm-hmm
I think it could
hmm
[Music]
where was I oh yeah thank you Nathan uh
black Richard space waterfalls
[Music]
oh
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no
Jesus the gun drop thank you for the
pink hey free forever thank you
thank you but let's go I hope I hope kfp
will be forever
I hope so
I can only wish and pray
um
[Music]
would you know kai
Sasa
Nami
not my human eye
test of 29th action for the pinky hi
kiwawa next time you're in the US you
should definitely go to
Wienerschnitzel this is a jerk please
don't I just found out recently it has
nothing to do with the actual wiener
schnitzel and yes we call Wiener with a
w
and not the V what
and yes we call Wiener with a W and not
the V what does that mean you're
supposed to ride it with W anyway
sends me a tick tock ah
good night
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's a tiny story
good night
[Music]
okay
she does she probably doesn't know that
I'm streaming most likely
um
I'm inviting her to join Odana to visit
me in Austria
Santa
um um because she sent me randomly a
video
a tick tock video I didn't even watch a
video but I read the description of sad
which is a Austrian dessert special
from Salzburg a city
in Austria small City and she like asked
me do you know this and I'm like yeah
but it looks good but it's not really
like tasty it just looks good on
pictures and you should never order it
alone because it's just because of the
not very tastiness and because of the
volume of it you don't want to eat it
alone and she said oh no I'm crying I
thought it was gonna be really [\h__\h]
good and I'm like wanna come here you
could try it out and she's like I wanna
eat it
um maybe I should really consider going
to Austria and I'm like ah please come
please come this time
gave her a time frame and she's like
what and I'm like yeah you want to come
and she's like I'm gonna I'm gonna uh
see if it's possible because that seems
to be a busy time
yeah it's not very realistic that time
frame when when odena wants to come see
me is indeed
difficult time I think
but it would be funny if she could come
at the time when Elena comes here that
would be fun
riding with food yeah with like really
mid below made food I'm even at winning
it
it's just it looks pretty it looks nice
the food looks nice because it's like
it's like like some fluffy foamy dessert
in the shape of mountains
and usually it's like like three
mountains
uh and it's really big and it's just
like some some foamy [\h__\h] like sugary
foamy [\h__\h] uh and you eat it with some
Berry sauce I think
but it's just really mid
it just looks good
um
you do not do that Justice
and everybody who eats it austrians and
tourists everybody who I know
does not ever order it again
it's just not
not very good it's just beautiful I will
say you should definitely order it once
because it looks good and take a picture
of it
but don't eat it alone don't eat it
alone
so
scared to be alone with it yeah don't be
alone a bit
I did make
um Nina eat a lot of Austrian desserts
um in a cafe on the last on the last
days it was really only one day
basically
um but yeah for like late lunch
I brought her to like a cafe really nice
fancy cafe with a beautiful view and I
ordered us like she ordered Austrian
soup frittata which is like just kind of
a leftover food but she said this it was
one thing that she wanted to eat
um and I was like surprised I'm like
okay go ahead I mean yo it's it's a
really simple soup like
um I think uh just normal like beef
broth
um and then basically you make this soup
uh when you have leftover pancakes but
like Austrian Finn pancakes it's like a
between between it's a between between
French crepes and pancakes
in terms of thickness
um
and normally like we would have it uh on
like as a dessert or so and then on the
next day there would still be left over
so we cut the the pancakes Into Thin
strips and then we put it into the soup
and it actually really works so well as
a soup
then add some
parsley or chives I think parsley
and maybe some veggies like some Thin uh
carrots perhaps
yeah
that's an Austrian leftover soup that's
pretty yummy so she ate that and then I
ordered for us uh Apple Store
with hot vanilla sauce it was like
swimming and it was yummy and I ordered
the kaisersman my favorite dessert on
pretty much with
swedishman is basically like scrambled
pancakes
um which doesn't sound so special on its
own but it makes it special when you eat
it with the sauce it's usually either
applesauce or that's Vegeta which is
plums and like a plum plummy sauce and
then I also ordered zakatoate the soccer
cake the chocolate cake she was
fascinated by that
um
we ate so much desserts unfortunately
there wasn't okay noodle but I told her
about the game Noodle's existence yeah I
said next time we're gonna try this one
yeah
the cake was really yummy and I told her
that that when she gets to the airport
she should look out for the duty-free
shop and that has the the Saka cakes
that I always bring as a souvenir
because they're really good souvenirs
the little little cubes the Saka cubes
recently I always bring them you know
not only recently last year or two I
brought it even to the Maldives
I told her to get them I wonder if she
got them
yeah they're really nice as a souvenir
they're not as lame as all the other
Foods souvenirs because this is like an
actual cake
in a nice fancy Packaging
yeah yummy yummy yummy [\h__\h] Mozart balls
no one wants your balls
I don't at least
because lots of balls are like the most
popular souvenir here
oh you know what I did today was like I
I fell asleep at like maybe half past
four a.m I'm sorry I I just was too
excited all the time
um
and then she woke me up at 5 20 an hour
later
these past nights she's been waking me
up at 5 20 30.
way too early she doesn't let me sleep
at all oh and she just does let go and I
was like
[\h__\h] no I we we can't do this anymore so
I uh you know what I did
if I just close her off behind one door
I can still hear her very loud and clear
but I closed her off behind two doors
and I felt so so bad about it
but at this moment I I was just so done
I didn't have to
have for the cat feeder I need to get
special batteries for them I realized
that I wanted to set it up and I didn't
have them
um and I forgot to buy them uh but yeah
and I felt so bad
[Music]
um I'm outside
I honestly felt so bad
I had to
she continued to meow for a while longer
and I heard it really faintly
but eventually she stopped and she slept
there and I I woke up a couple hours
later at like nine and I was like okay
let's see I was planning on sleeping
more but I I felt so bad so I I got up
and I gave her breakfast
and I kept the door open after that and
then she ended up cuddling on my bed
afterwards so everything was good after
but yeah I might do this
um a few times maybe tonight as well
maybe eventually she will understand
that she cannot wake me up before even
the [\h__\h] Sun is up
you know
because it's just too much it's really
too much it was making me so mad
I you know I never closed the doors I
never close any doors I always let my
cats go anywhere
I always give them the freedom of
everything
um so that they can always follow me
because they always want to be with me
in their whole life they've been they've
been used to that
so I feel really bad
but she has to learn it has to be done
I'm gonna cry I feel so bad
um
[Music]
foreign
enough she will finally understand
that she can't keep on waking me up
early and earlier like it started with
like back in the day she would just wait
until I wake up
I miss those times and then eventually
she would like recently this year she
would start waking me up at like 8 A.M
then seven then six and now five
what the [\h__\h] and then and then first it
was only like she wakes me up once and
then she leaves me alone but now now she
would wake me up at 5am and then she if
I give her food she wakes me up again at
6am and demands more and like what the
[\h__\h] do you want from me
not only once
yeah
it's really bad I don't know what's
going on and then when I sleep during
the daytime like a nap she leaves me
alone
so
now
but chunky walking is always waiting for
me
this cat owns you
oh I don't want to be more cruel
but yeah we're changing her full
schedule I'm not I'm not letting her
control me anymore
again
I can't do this anymore
chunky monkey is so sweet but it's also
because she doesn't want
um wet food she only eats Kibbles and
she has access to them all the time
good night server blink thank you
ah no the noise canceling headphones I
can hear the cats
quite clearly
I think and also I can't really sleep on
the side with the headphones so yeah
um
you could get one of those Auto feeders
yeah yeah I did
but
um
I haven't gotten to set it up yet I
tried setting it up last night and then
I saw oh [\h__\h] I need like special
batteries like like really big ones and
three of them
no need to buy them
but
yeah at the same time I don't know the
the door strategy worked so
yeah D batteries
um
have never bought D batteries before
yeah I wish it would just plug into a
wall what the [\h__\h] why make it work on
batteries
that's so weird
uh-huh
they're huge
I hope they at least
um don't go empty so fast
ah
[Music]
a uh-huh
so it doesn't fail if you're gone on
your pet store well this this feeder is
only for 24 hours anyway
like it's full wet food and you can't
leave it in there because there's no
cooler you can't leave it in there
longer for like a night so you put it in
in the night time and then it goes off
throughout the day the coming day
yeah
there were some with coolers but they
all had like reviews of their cats
managing to open it
this one seemed relatively safe but it
doesn't have a cooler but I thought okay
if I have to set it up at night okay
that's fine
yeah I was thinking like smoothie is so
[\h__\h] desperate I can see her trying
to get into it
yeah
I I think it will be fine like people
this one people have been using it for
wet food as well
it's just you can't if it's wet food you
can't leave it in there longer than 24
hours really
so just prepare for one day and that's
it
it's movie so crafty yeah I don't know
if I should be proud of her and annoyed
with her or scared of her
anyway uh thank you I'll taste that for
the pinky again
WD thank you eating Mike Tyson's assume
foreign
what
are you talking about
I'm like pretty sure
uh she didn't
do the thing that you wrote at the end
link I don't know when and how and why
so I will just say that and then leave
it at that what the [\h__\h] Wicked Tunes
oh
[Music]
maybe you meant someone else and you
just subconsciously wrote the wrong name
banana
yeah
[Music]
Maple Leaf for the pinky
I just wanted to say you're amazing and
happy very belated birthday I was a bit
Mia during the birthday stuff because of
IRS stuff you're using so many
shorteners so just let me say we're all
proud of you and you're very inspiring I
love you platonically
at the end
that was unnecessary
what you gonna do what you gonna do if I
don't love you platonically
that's gonna break my heart
no but like you don't need to say that
man you're really trying hard to set
boundaries huh hmm
platonic zones
okay
nice okay thank you this is funny
um where was I oh yeah thank you for the
happy birthday
and yeah IRL stuff sometimes
can be unfortunately getting in the way
of these fun things in your life but
don't worry don't worry as long as you
still show up I'm happy thank you
right
[Music]
especially since English is your
favorite language after Phoenix and
Timken next project make that poem a
wrap oh I actually I mean I cheated when
I was writing the poem I was looking up
um words that rhyme
and just chose what you know I felt was
fitting to the story that I want to tell
sorry to disappoint
I could not think of
so many good words that rhyme otherwise
everyone does that thank God okay
that's how poets do it okay okay I I
hopefully good
um
that's not cheating okay okay
nice thank you
but yeah it turned out so good I felt
like a genius oh my God
wow
wow so so talented yeah I bet even Kelly
does that oh I wonder she must have she
must have mentioned like her her ways of
writing lyrics Before surely in her
streams
hmm
[Music]
unless you have photographic memory and
remember all words I feel like some
people some people could do it like
naturally like especially those rappers
that do like Freestyle right
like freestyle raps damn
that's amazing
Cheech
yeah uh
thank you thank you happy belated
birthday
I don't know if you're here now usually
when I say that they're always here but
I have a feeling you're not here are you
here
[Music]
I'm always like you're probably not here
and then they're here anyway
why are you guys
you got your latest birthday I'm sorry
I'm so late to say it
I hope you had a nice birthday
happy that you're here it's a miracle
you guys are always here
some miracle you guys are here
ah it was all right no don't look so sad
you deserve better
but but but you know what you get a free
kiss from me even though you just sent a
green one
a kiss to Cheerio up Ma
turn that frown around do it do it
do it
one time only freakies
I'm sad too
now you're all sad no no no no
no no no no no you can't do that no no
no I was sad too nobody gave me kisses
I was sent to when I was playing the
game
no it's the uh ah the big depression
wasn't there like a time they called
like something depression or so
it's the big depression the chicken
chicken passion
the Great Depression
was that some kind of like economy thing
also I don't know
I don't know
what's it in German
what's the great impression in German
the Great Depression German
wait what do you call it
there's no way it's called depression
oh that sounds so much better
medium-sized depression sort of large
depression
yo the German word is so much better
it's called World economy crisis
that like brings it to the point we we
like to in German language make things
very clear
we make everything very accurate
sounding
right so descriptive all our words are
so descriptive
okay where was I
say
um
for the pinky thanks for this beautiful
name boss I love you you're welcome dude
you probably changed it back by now
right you you yeah there you go okay
thank God I I
I didn't want to change your whole
identity there sorry about that
but for a little bit it was it was funny
for a little bit or was it in some way
let's be honest it wasn't even funny but
you guys are so nice and
I mean
and sometimes sometimes I'm funny but
okay maybe that wasn't so funny
was it funny
I feel like my my hang up jokes and so
on like those were quite funny and my oh
my nose is running do you have a leash
it was also funny
I'm quite funny usually this was maybe
not so funny now not one of my best ones
I'm ashamed
I'm so ashamed
funny unknown if anyone that I wanted
you to find it funny
[Laughter]
every another cult thank you for the
pink
pink I missed most of the stream before
emergency at work and then I passed out
why is the Wawa War unhinged unusual
what did I do this was at the end of the
Minecraft stream
actually
huh the time that it's showing me for
the Super Chat is like after the stream
kind of weird
um
I drank Red Bull oh maybe I did
yeah possibly
did I
I will need a lot of Red Bull next week
I think like maybe
two or three bottles because yeah all
those like weirdly timed streams
and then the one with fauna I'm I'm
currently planning to start it at like
midnight my time because she
um suggested me like certain morning
times that she normally streams in and
that's like midnight for me but it's
okay it's not gonna be like a super long
stream and I have to kind of mess up my
sleep schedule anyway next week so
whatever
I think for the
tournament I might
stay awake yeah
but for the Minecraft thing I'd like to
get some sleep and then wake up for it I
think I don't know how to do it yet
we'll see we'll see how my sleep
schedule goes throughout the night uh
the week
well yeah
we'll see how it goes
uh thank you for the pinky though thank
you
thank you everybody
[Music]
bum
so next we have no GTA double double no
super chats from the coming streams
because it was above GTA
and then the Super Chat croissants were
turned off as well
but we have some from the holotori of
collab okay
oh
uh other boy did I where did it go where
did I go
here
council is now all in Japan right
they're all in Japan right
I hope they're having fun like we did
when we were all in Japan
almost like nostalgic
but ID is also still in Japan right like
wasn't I saw like uh somebody doing off
collab with Ollie uh was it akidoso said
by Ollie and Anya
aren't they finished with their uh for
an ews
why are they still here
but I guess they're they're still having
fun so that's good
ah good for them nice maybe they still
have some stuff to do in Japan
we can't get Ollie to leave
[Music]
maybe gonna do hologram and hologram you
can do basically from anywhere
I also recorded that at home
useful word let's go
she's going to find Elisa for your hand
oh only wants to find the reason for my
hand
oh wait olly olly why me you love
everybody just uh
you can't marry everybody
we're starting the whole harem and what
you're the protagonist you too but I
also have my own Harem so I don't know
if I can join the like someone else's
Harem as the the what do you call the
people who are not the protagonist
because I I can't I can't like be the
owner of a harem and then
um
we all free can be at the center not
this
start another harem
the the mommy Harem I've got a lot of
like mommy's
um you know artists mommies
and real mommies maybe even I don't know
foreign
at my fingertips
um
but I don't know I don't really think
besides mommies that I'm much of a like
collector you know
I'll be in your hand and have my own on
the side oh oh okay you eh you'll be in
my mommy here I mean another mommy
though
no you're not in my hair I'm nerissa
what we have is different
I could be in your Harem though if you
want
eh why why you shop do you see yourself
as a mommy
um
well you might intern you know I can't I
can't have a relationship like that with
an intern that would be inappropriate
I would be very inappropriate in turn
zones
employing zoned no
not I will
I will take good care of you
I basically I'm adopting you oh
I'm literally adopting you
hey
you you are you may have me as like a
emotional support doll but you're
basically for me your your mind
you're my Barbie doll
you're my puppy
Puppy World
that
huh
she's not my pet no
no no no no no no don't misunderstand
[Laughter]
uh dressing you the other day
so
you dress Barbie dolls don't you
you dress them up you brush their hair
and you
what you what was it you raise them
everywhere I don't know
you can brush my hair and raise me
everywhere what what was that
what does it say undress me you can
brush my hair and dress me oh yeah yeah
yeah Oh I thought it always that it was
and dress me everywhere but it's
undressed me that was the thing that
confused me
mmm
spicy
[Laughter]
uh what
we aren't enough can of
what are you trying to say
are you Ken
see my my head is starting to hurt again
I wonder if this is because I'm still
sick but
weird let me read super chats guys
I wanna watch the movie I need to watch
the movie
I tried to find time maybe next week
I'll try next week maybe
I don't want to go alone
just another kfp.com
thank you for the pinky a goldfish
please oh that would be your snack of
choice
um
goldfish goldfish we're fine we have
goldfishes here too though yeah I think
they're quite International
no screens but they're as bright as
always
do I remember what health is supposed to
honestly no like this is kind of sad but
I I yeah it's like even too sad to say
it out loud but I don't remember what it
feels like to not be in pain
that's so [\h__\h] sad
I just accepted this state of life
yeah
and there's one of those
James McPhee thank you for the pinky
what a deal what were we selling
I don't remember this anymore
huh
thank you though thank you for the big
support thank you
selling a gold ah yo my pitch was so bad
I wanted to be funny I felt like I felt
so much pressure
um
because it felt like a big collab
and it was not funny
I couldn't think of anything good
it made no sense it made no [\h__\h]
sense what I was saying I don't know
where I was going with it
I'm proud of you pushing through and
accomplishing so much even though your
body gives you problems thank you y'all
I'm proud myself too
hmm
I told Nina some life stories uh at
dinner and she was like shocked that I
I've been for so much [\h__\h] she was like
how the [\h__\h] are you still like what
I'm like yeah I don't know
well it's nice to be
like acknowledged for that for yeah
getting through life
because I never ever
like it's really rare for me to tell
somebody
all of my
struggling life stories but for some
reason we went to that topic
um stories I never told on stream before
uh
yeah
I never I rarely I never do that and I
just told her all of it and she was so
sweet
she was so like
supportive and like
how to say she made me feel
like better about
um a lot of things you made me feel
understood and
um
I don't know
yeah
what the [\h__\h] everybody's crying
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank you oh thank you for buying shitty
pictures you shouldn't you should have
better control over your wallet really
thank you for the support
Expo 77.
[Music]
oh
um [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
girls
this is the kind of collab that just
brings a smile to your face Horror Story
love thank you
yeah
I'm glad I organized that it was very
sweet
had some time to burp with uh to burp
bombs
[Laughter]
superb birthday
that's where I was going okay
interesting oh God
laughs
got me up baby
can someone make a compilation of my
misspeaks
they're so funny
how the dangerous
ah [\h__\h] oh man
laughs
everybody
[Laughter]
[Music]
lots of trains
what's copulation I don't remember that
no I said compilation not copulation
emotions
when Nina called give me a special guest
ah
hahaha
[Laughter]
oh man good times
okay
[Music]
special okay
eggs eggs eggs
[Music]
that was not me Miss speaking though
that was Discord manipulating me
and my image
yeah
what what huh
Horror Story love indeed fried squirrel
you're so you're so right you speak the
truth hallelujah you should be you
should be a prophet
thank you so much bright screw mwah
zipline
thank you everybody for the Super Chat
on the holiday stream
bam
bum bum bum bam next is the outfit
review oh
the other ones aren't so bad but yeah
the outfit review is pretty bad
um
air
yeah we have to get through it [\h__\h] it
shine it
is
um
that was nothing
don't you me
it's always
it's just when you cry the the snot goes
down a little bit even if you try to not
let it go down
so it increased my flag um
my flag
creation speed
what am I saying where's my what's up
what
it was running yeah guys should have put
a should have put a leash on it if you
don't like it you show the photos on it
if you don't like it do you should have
put a leash on it oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
what's your problem with that joke
I just cried and you honestly gonna
criticize me from trying to cheer myself
up with jokes
you know I like to repeat my jokes I'm
very proud of them
let them let her joke
okay here we go guys
this is this is the this is the Super
Chat rating of the ages
let me bird yes
I'm not Danny with the bunny
a famous comedians they also have like a
routine that they repeat right nobody
nobody complains to them
about repeating their jerks
yeah
okay
[Music]
oh
okay here we go
okay here we go here we go
here we go here we go
human extensions
Studio wrap thanks for the pink uh
to the celestial boss congratulations on
your new outfit reveal thank you should
I reply in English or in Japanese
Thank you very much it was a a exciting
one it's been a long time since the last
one so
that was a big one
and it was a big special one I prepared
special animation for it even I'm so
happy you guys liked you know the outfit
and the animation everything so much
yeah
I hyped myself up to read two plus I
gotta have to
yeah
um I just wanted to
prepare something special for it and
since this one was so different from
like you know
concept wise and everything it was just
so different from usual
and it felt like almost a different Wawa
so I thought maybe maybe create a
different Wawa make it make it a
different lava
yeah and I had fun with it yeah yeah
swap through it
that's that's how it would have looked
like if swaff was allowed to draw it
from scratch and not like attach it onto
the existing body my legs would have
been so much longer yes
it looks so cool man
and he even like that one sword he put
them in both of my hands what
how am I gonna carry them but he seems
like uh I actually never interacted
directly with him except for those like
replies uh after the outfit reveal
um
but uh
uh like like I've obviously he also had
to keep it a secret that he's doing this
but Ever After the reveal he's been like
retweeting the fan art and and and like
writing like kind of like his thoughts
about certain aspects and all that
randomly on Twitter and and I'm just so
happy that he seems very happy with uh
being involved in this makes me very
happy I don't even know if it's a he I
don't know I'm just assuming right now
um sorry if it's if he's not he but yeah
no I'm happy that he's happy
that they are happy
the big flag of influx
ah
like you know uh they never like
designed something for YouTuber before
or like you know never created a video
before so I think it's the first time
for them maybe to get so much fan art of
you know one of their Creations like
that except for maybe the tales of a
rice DLC outfit maybe they got a lot of
fan out for that too but
um that's this like this huge amount of
fan art for something you created must
feel really nice as an artist
to see it drawn by different people in
different styles
oh they did make a v-singer oh
but I didn't see them ever like
retweeting any fan art I think on their
account because I've been following swap
for a while now
didn't see anything so maybe I don't
know
I think this this amount of fan art
might be the first time for him
so if that's the case I'm very happy
yeah because he seems very happy hey
so I'm happy hey
because like it could have it could have
just as well been an artist who just
does the job and then you know [\h__\h] off
doesn't care much doesn't really
you know show much interest
who knows I couldn't have known
yeah yeah he seems to really care hmm
so anyway continuing oh uh Studio rap
yeah
what's with the Roses oh
because the new outfit
maybe yeah thank you fancy roses
thanks for the pinky let's go new lava
style incoming the silhouette alone
looks fantastic I wonder what's new
kakul or we might get to or reveals like
the one doing GTA 4 I almost missed of
her gravy dyed not natural orange hair
ah no it's natural it's natural it's
just I I I I I I I I I I I I I I I I
whatever
excited for key alter thank you
the Lord wasn't cuckoo I would say it
was uh
it was
it was scandalous allegations right I
would agree with that thank you
it's not too crazy the lawyer wasn't too
crazy all right
what what
it just keeps on coming
no thank you
small Wawa
small Pandora
[Music]
thanks for the pinky
can't wait to see your new outfit
attention
hmm
thank you very much
you have to wait though there's no
choice
you also have to wait for the next one
or you'll have to wait
um
actually wait it's almost already August
gotta gotta get that going I don't know
what where what the status currently is
honestly let me check
what's going on with that
ah wait
[Music]
what
what is the status
[Music]
okay I don't know I'll check it out
later
what did I say it
right and let's say almost August I
meant it is already August
that's what I meant
that's what I was trying to say
a head horde
candy
please
I'm sure your new outfit will be 100 fat
possibly more than 100 chicken chipkins
aren't good at math
I don't know if you would call this one
fetch I would definitely
um call the next one more likely to be
fetched
but what even is fetchino who knows
anyway go go fetch me some fried chicken
right now hurry up hurry up
I'll run the wins Joel W thanks for the
red super chat I miss sending you a
super chat for your birthday so I will
send one now to celebrate this Milestone
with you it is always wonderful to see
how much fun you have with new outfit
reveals thanks for everything Canada
ah yeah you think so I honestly wish I
was as creative as Ahmed to think of new
things to wear new things to weigh new
new ways to yeah new ways and things too
to show off a new outfit
I wish
this was super creative and it had a
story to it yeah but unfortunately the
thing is like making an animation like
that uh the longer it is the much higher
the price will be uh if I could I would
have made it much longer
so I was like yeah I have something
prepared but it's so short it will be
over in an instant but thankfully it
left a great impression even though it
was so short yeah
mm-hmm
and I really like the cow carrot version
with like the sound effects I was
originally thinking of adding sound
effects and voices but once I had the
music I felt like it was already so
beautiful that I didn't want to intrude
too much
but then when I saw the version with the
music and the sound effects I felt like
maybe I could have combined it so maybe
next time if I make something like this
again
oh I was thinking of you know maybe
doing more of these animations to
continue the lore because I was like
inspired and I had ideas for Pia Kiara
Alters Adventures
um but
but I was thinking maybe maybe I should
crowdfund it
because if we're gonna do that it's
gonna mean
but I still don't know if um management
allows something like that
like I'm not gonna do 30 minute episodes
obviously but
um
ah
okay if we got your back okay
I was hoping you can crowd something
instead of paying out of your own
pockets and the good thing is with
crowdfunding that I don't have to you
know split it with uh the company and
and YouTube
like you know you guys can send super
chats and all that but like the amount
you're trying to send is not gonna all
reach the project so I feel like it
would be smarter to just like directly
uh put it all into like a crowdfunding
thing
um that would like be
smarter and Theory
yeah
it's just better for both parties
involved or all parties involved
are you allowed to open stream Maps oh I
don't know I mean but even with stream
Labs maybe maybe YouTube doesn't take a
cut but the company still takes a cut so
I don't know if that makes sense to do
that
might be the exact issue cover might
have with it with it though that's what
I've think too but who knows who knows
if it's for like a very specific project
maybe maybe
they could allow it I don't know I'll
check if I don't forget about it
I should write it down though because
otherwise I will forget about it let's
be honest
[Music]
okay I wrote it down
oh yeah we already talked about the new
cut make sure to watch it I didn't watch
it yet I have to watch it
yeah yeah ID Girls use it already so I
could but I don't really see the reason
to
it crashed again what's going on was it
crashing so often today
here you go and thank you
w
Silverado thanks for the red super chat
as well uh why not though
Dove tof tough for the weird word thank
you is a chat then hello Chad are you
dead wake up wake up wake up
I guess you're dead I'll continue though
thank you Silverado for the rest of the
chat mwah aha
that explains everything
oh is it ah
I was apparently questioning why why why
you guys send super chats
thank you thank you for supporting as
always Anthony oh chat back
hello welcome back I knew you were
listening I felt it sanctions
[Music]
another question
so true I'm sorry I'm sorry if I ever
questioned it I should know I should
know better
thank you for the support
thanks for the pinky congratulations on
receiving your six star Skin Kiana
good good way of thinking about it thank
you for supporting me and my new outfit
SSR q1
foreign
[Music]
I already sent a request for perms but I
was told to wait until it releases or
like until it gets closer now until
there is a release date I think
I think that's what it was
because there is no release it just it
came out today
eh
oh then it probably was wait until it
releases
what the [\h__\h]
okay one second
wait did I wait no I think I didn't that
was Dragon's Dogma
and fable
wasn't wasn't uh the other one Baldur's
Gate
do I have perms or no
do we
let me see oh where do I see it do I see
it here no why do I see it
uh
this is
so confusing uh
uh where do I see my perms like they got
this new way and this new site where
they show it to us
I don't know what to say it
um
[Music]
where where
oh wait maybe
[Music]
um
I don't [\h__\h] knowledge
well I don't know how to get to the game
permission thing
okay whatever I can't find it
I wonder if anybody else applied for it
as T-Rex Cali okay okay
no janma is sleeping let her sleep
she needs her rest
um
wife I guess get off my Wi-Fi thank you
for the recipe chat
you know how how back in the day old
people while I get off my lawn
Zoomer the new version is get off my
Wi-Fi especially because Millennials
will never be able to afford a home with
a lawn so
they will never say get off my lawn they
will only take it off my Wi-Fi oh my God
too real
uh realism comedy
laughs
ah get off my lawn get off my l-a-n that
lawn land
get off my land cable you're making my
internet lag
couple that was so German cable
funny I'm so funny
I'm sorry
ah get off my w LAN
this is so stupid in in English in
German we just say velan it's so much
easier to say it velan instead of w land
what the [\h__\h]
w w is such a stupid letter in English
London did this to me
after going to Comedy Store I aspire to
be a real comedian
hello welcome
I am just reading
super chatos right now
it's called Wi-Fi in English okay
anyway ready for koala as release next
year kiwawa es another Eden references
[Music]
another another s
espanol what
is Super Chat and for the big support
very generous I appreciate it thank you
Bruce Jenny Lee Duncan James Jackson is
now that you are an entire Adventurer
party what quest would you take your
party on
honestly that's literally something I
want to make into a lore video like
going on the quest kind of
um but I don't know if I would have cute
like alter kiwawa go alone or I don't
know
sure but probably it will get more
expensive the more the more complicated
the scenes get
um because like for this one I I
purposefully kept everything like quite
simple to keep the cost down
and so it was just you know happening in
the room
not much action
besides the little fire action
um
yeah
but
they are able to make some Muslims able
to make some crazy fighting scenes so I
kind of want to see that too
would be really cool yeah
I think all the Kiowa is strong enough
to solo Quest hell yeah I think so tall
or maybe maybe alter Q level could have
a a pet or cell like a
um companion
um
like a little phoenix bird
phoenix bird
like in like relatively small form
like not like
but maybe the size of like
uh her arm
a little bit longer than her arm
including feathers
like not so that she could ride on it
what about I guess it could be called
Kotori
but Kotori the Kotori we've seen so far
is Tiny and chunky and wouldn't really
be helpful in the fight I think
Ohio yeah
talking to akashiba for drawing that
nerissa Chihuahua
has been paying attention to narissa
because she's tall
I wish I was tall Mama lonely really
likes tall women
she still you know back in the day fell
for my charms I guess even though I
wasn't so tall
but maybe she will make a comeback
because of nerissa and maybe maybe maybe
she will draw me again
like in a couple couple scenario
get some stilts ah
yeah I do I do agree I miss my Maloney
art too she should draw us together
that's what I'm saying
[Music]
yeah I don't wanna I don't want a bag
when I miss my Maloney art
but never says height
is
helpful in this situation
hahaha
thank God you're tall
where was I
thank you Eric
you crazy man are you here in the chat
Eric
thank you for all the super Santos
thank you all thank you you're the best
I don't see you here but maybe you'll
catch up with the reading
um
oh Christine also Drew us together
just what now
if I go on Twitter or X will I see it
[Music]
I don't see it at least not right away
wow
where where
I'll just let me
oh I see I see so many like my my my my
my my my my my my my my my Twitter like
starting page shows me so many tweets
that aren't tagging me but are talking
about me
cute
so let me see I
Christina
[Music]
all right
why why why why why why why why why why
why what
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
what's the the ship name what what was
it what was it nitty20
that sounds kind of cute
um
[Laughter]
chicken soup that's chicken soup
I feel like I like it more but it's like
one word
but chicken soup is cute yeah
[Music]
Pawn you commissioned her for that
you did
no way
you did ah
oh okay
well thank you for supporting local
artists
good morning
yes
I'm glad you guys liked it you know
honestly I feel like um I was like
at some point I was getting worried that
maybe I'm showing like too little skin
and you know it'll be too boring ah want
more skin but you guys like it so I'm
happy
foreign
because like people nowadays when they
reveal uh new outfits they often make
waves by showing as little skin as
possible
I've noticed
and I'm going the opposite way
but I'm really happy everybody is
appreciating a cool ass outfit with lots
of armor
um
and it's giving us like really cool
different Vibes of Wawa right like and
although the fan art of Wawa in action
with armor and weapon is really cool too
so I think it was it was nice to go this
direction
[Music]
oh I mean as much skin not as little
yeah I guess I meant as much skin as
possible
to make waves yeah
Victorian tuber
wait is there a Victorian tuber or are
you just like joking around
Echo
Victor
Victorian Victorian tuber
no Victorian tuber it seems we have
found a niche
it is time to fill it
[Laughter]
oh my God
oh
no not coffee
real [\h__\h] Victorian clothing
not the cosplay stuff Ohio
[Music]
but honestly I'd rather go medieval
personally like sometimes I think about
the possibility of going for like a
Angeline style beautiful or like even
Game of Thrones I don't care medieval
outfit with corset and pushed Boba and
all that because you know you know how
much I talked about it before you know
how much I love the way medieval dresses
make cleavage look it's like the most
beautiful thing ever a green Arissa
so um
but then I I'm like I feel like um
I don't know I feel like as an as a V
tour outfit it might not work so well so
yeah I keep on I keep on pushing the
idea away it's just like a fantasy in my
head
I feel like as artwork
often it doesn't look so good unless you
go like real real realistic style that
really shows off all the details because
like one thing that's important with
medieval dresses is the fabric so you
would need an artist that is like really
good with like showing off real looking
different kinds of fabrics
fabric is so important
like showing off the texture and the
Shimmer
showing the difference of like satin as
opposed to other
Fabrics
yeah yeah
would be hard to do justice yeah that's
what I'm thinking
um
yeah yeah I don't think it would do it
justice these kind of dresses they they
look so good in real life
ah but art art is difficult unless you
go like hyper realism
yeah it might just not look good on an
anime character you know you know what I
mean yeah
so sad so sad
[Music]
valid point right no
no so this man
RTX on
yeah Mama Mama
um where was I oh yeah I'm here thank
you iron Vader thank you soon dies too
thank you
thank you for the rest of the chat marry
me oh I don't know if I can but thank
you I appreciate the the offer and the
sentiment
thank you Sam for the support mwah
thank you for the pinky it's my birthday
best birthday present ever love you wow
I love the outfit too you're so cute
thank you I'm sorry I'm so late but
thank you for being there on my special
day on your special day we shared a
special day together
um
but I hope you didn't only celebrate me
but also yourself
happy belated birthday
congratulations stay healthy please take
care of yourself
your family wants me oh no that's
[\h__\h] embarrassing
ah how dare you expose me like that to
normal people
scared me terrifying font
did they like me
your mom your mama
your mama liked me
of course she did
I'm a mom magnet
yo mama
[Laughter]
hey mama
get on the floor and move that booty
mama
Black Ops
um
thank you for the pinky Divine I love
medieval style thanks so much for this
welcome surprise oh we were just talking
about it although I would not really I
mean it's like fantasy medieval not real
life medieval but yeah
I love fantasy medieval too I love all
the medievals
thank you for talk glad you like it so
much
Rick Raptor that question
thank you for the pinky Kayla's living
her dream as a tails off emcee
yeah yeah yeah these days tails off
games are getting darker and darker
and um
arise so
it would fit into the recent tails of
games maybe
but
[Music]
now we have an outfit to lead kfp into
battle yay
I hope we won't need it anytime soon if
it's perfectly into ff16 yeah it
probably fits better into epiv Final
Fantasy games than into tails of games
actually
I agree
I think so too
um
so why with don't know just one yes
and pink bacon action Thai food decision
is
foreign
I was saying that
um this time I went for like a long
ponytail that goes to the side it's
fluffy and big and long but at some
point I feel like like a coroner Senpai
style ponytail would be nice too you
know the one she has for her casual
outfit
it's kind of short and it's like really
like you know straight behind her head
not like showing off to the side much
but it's so cute
I like that one too
so that one would maybe fit well with a
more casual outfit or maybe like a
school uniform or so
mm-hmm oh yeah you know that was
ponytail too yeah yeah yeah hers one as
well is kind of like more on the the
calm side compared to my messy big one
yeah Schneider thank you for the rest of
the chat absolutely amazing loving the
armor theme also both hairstyles are
amazing and I can't even start with the
animation just gorgeous thank you
thank you glad I invested in it yeah it
definitely was beautiful and worth it
and so nice to have something like this
it's so epic I really love how it turned
out
I want to make more I want to make one
more
but yeah I'm glad you like everything so
much thank you Manuel thank you foreign
we're so hype seeing it come up on
screen right I was so excited to show
you guys
I said I said German word
thank you for the recipe
how are you doing the outfit is super
cool Kiara I love it I love them all but
I think my top favorites are now this
one and the empress while one oh I can
see like a like a general
taste I think for you
um
I know I know what your taste is
by you saying those are your favorite
so like more maybe darker and like
fantasy looking ones
okay
I like those too oh
I feel like you know my casual one is so
versatile that's why I love it so much
and I use it so much because of that
so it's definitely one of my top top top
maybe number one favorite
but the problem is because it's so
versatile I may have been overusing it
so I'm trying to you know get some
variety although I feel like you know
it's more it feels more like that to me
than it does to the audience
because like I don't get sick of Peck
without using her OG outfit for example
as the audience
so I try to think about it uh in a
different way
even when I get sick of it you guys are
probably not not really tired of it
um
[Music]
it's just let it go
from my point of view kind of thing
so listen yeah
you like OG kiwawa huh
but right now I'm kind of OG kiwawa oh
God right now I'm oh Chihuahua just kind
of compressed
I need to save resources
small Lala killed very cute
froggy llama I need to bring back
program I need to plan frog I keep on
seeing like people posting program stuff
and I'm like ah so cute
yeah
froggy Wawa expressions and hands are
just the cutest thing oh my God
yeah the Frog birthday oh yeah
oh yeah
probably you should be doing that in VR
huh I haven't done VR in a while and
it's always such a bother to set it up
but
yeah I hate VR
but we should do that yeah
maybe at the end of the month or so
let me ride to Pomo
let's do rock birds and from Chihuahua
sometime
[Music]
but the other like VR stream we had
together was also kind of like a date
how do we differentiate this one
oh my God yes immediately replying
froggy well OG Wawa it doesn't matter we
just love Vala
you I love chicken
date season 2 Electric Boogaloo
so maybe maybe yeah we could maybe play
a VR game together like
yeah
I don't know what kind of VR came we
Arcane game can we play together
we'll think about it
maybe no
something that makes sense with two
people
you missed the pizza time it was it was
fun but the end broke me I had to quit
make sure to check out the archive
beat Saba
um
we are cooking can we like we need a I
need to look up collab games
stress building
yeah
um
[Music]
ah trip to Vegas and y'all have fun
don't oh
Vegas dangerous don't lose all your
money okay be careful please gambling is
something you should leave to your boss
be careful okay but have fun
um
I only gamble in games
[Music]
um
the pinky this has to be my favorite
outfit of yours thus far wow thank you
wow
I'm glad you think so I'm glad you like
it so much
definitely worth using up a spot in my
yearly new outfit plan I'm glad thank
you Eric neustrum are you for real
are you okay
thank you the short hair was really good
but ponytail ha ha
yeah I think I like ponytail the most as
well
I like the short hair too
it's good to have two hairstyles right
it's good
to have a choice
um
yeah
both are nice short hair is cute long
hair is pretty
yeah ponytail makes you look badass yeah
ponytails are just I don't know what it
is about ponytails
they're so good
thank you Eric you're the best
were you curious if I was streaming so
you checked it out and now you're
watching
my beloved
hello
[Music]
um
you were watching earlier too oh when I
was actually playing the game oh my God
have you tried it
it's so difficult
it's so mean
how are you how I need to watch Army
playing
oh she surely raged a lot I I Can Only
Imagine
but it's amazing she finished it like
big respect
I'm it was also panicking
ah of course she did
but her platforming gamer Pride wouldn't
let her quit like me
looks difficult oh yeah
but
poem was also quite the gamer promo
could do it I'm sure
um
yeah yeah
yes no would you not agree
are you are you are you
not sure about your gamer status
[Music]
I mean
yeah I would say you're a gamer your
game choices are also quite gamer like
all the wives are present
on my rifles no they're not wives
they're my my beloved friends I love
them
I just love them
so much
didn't you marry her last month
ah well I I yeah no I proposed and she
may have accepted but the marriage has
not been gone through officially I don't
remember having a marriage yet
no
we're on a different stage we're just
engaged if anything yeah
that sounds like that I was just
thinking that yeah
but then but then it's not us getting
married it's frog bird and froggy Wawa
getting married
which maybe maybe it's better that way
[Music]
let's make lots of frog eggs
but only after the marriage
I have I have my my principles
foreign
[Music]
character Vibes there with the outfit
which is fitting also the fingernails
are pretty cute love the color for
referral
also I think first hairstyles can still
count some of the short hair and
ponytails are always great yeah that was
the the the the debate right like I I'm
not sure I feel like I'm
I still need to give you guys like a
real real short hairstyle at some point
that really looks like short
like a proper one
yeah
this is
this one was like just like a shorting
or a short hairstyle
I'm going bald
how short are we talking
uh not like super short I don't like
super short
I like
um
uh maybe
Maybe
that's cute
like yeah somewhere around the middle or
the the middle of the neck or the where
the neck connects with the shoulders
undercut
s
I don't know about that
and I personally I really like wavy
um
hair in general
but yeah that length with wavy curls I
really like that personally
wobbly hair yeah
wobbly
oh of course
feel free to include me I'm looking
forward to it
and anyway thank you sorry I'm glad
you're enjoying the new outfit thank you
so much for the feedback and the support
thank you mwah Judy also with the right
Super Chat thank you love the theatrics
of the outfit introduction and your
outfit is so so cool the herpes hair
price hair piece is lovely I love the
other outfit so much 10 out of 10. thank
you
yeah
yeah the hairpiece is very fancy isn't
it so shiny
pretty pretty gems
thank you thank you I also really liked
all the predictions for the hairpiece
they were also quite Charming I would
like to take them all home with me I
would like to buy them all
and put them on a different one every
day unfortunately I can't but yeah
thank you Judy I'm glad you like it you
will see more of it I'm sure in the
future
until you get sick of it or maybe not
maybe even you will never get sick of it
hopefully thank you
yo I feel like Alida you
I feel like I I haven't seen your super
chat in a while so welcome back thank
you for being here
the armor the ponytail is so good I love
it yeah thank you
hi you're in the chat what's up
are you doing well
be doing well
how you doing
doing fantastic great I like to hear
that thank you for the big generous
Super Chat
I feel like the order of this one is
kind of random because it's got like a
non-stream time stamp
weird but I read it and you were here
you witnessed it all is good there's a
bell action ghost
dragon's fire Danke Schoen for the pinky
absolutely amazing and literally stunned
by your Radiance aha
o
wow Charming thank you
things broke for you that day oh no
oh no
maybe it was like overwhelmed with my
beautiful outfit
anyway thank you
drank for the sweet sweet
words
of support I appreciate it thank you
that's about thank you stamps
Skye thank you for the recipe chat love
your new outfit full-time Warrior let's
go yeah finally full time I'm finally
committing to full time
um
thank you for the big support
and also thanks for helping me find the
the the art artist how
it so fast
damn do you also just say fan art and
like me with the name of the the artist
as the file name
that's how I usually do it but sometimes
I forget it when I'm in a hurry
oh you use it three different image
searches oh but you didn't even have the
original picture wow
damn thank you that must be a good image
Searcher because the ones I used didn't
work
that's smart with the file name then
yeah yeah
that's what I gotta do because like I
have to save so many fan art so I always
have something ready when I make a
thumbnail
um
and I want to give credit to the artist
of course so I save it under the name
because otherwise it would be hard to
find again
so sometimes I just like scroll through
all of the art I saved and just pick a
really old one hey
this one I I chose because I thought I
looked kind of like I was going insane
like kind of like stressed out
because of the eyes so I thought it fits
quite well
mm-hmm
[Music]
it's quite useful when people draw me
with all kinds of this expressions
for very very emotional thumbnails to
get the point across
yeah
thank you Skye connections
love the new outfit the new hairstyles
are really cool thank you
um
I think we had blue before for the
empress outfit right
um as like a undertone color but
I think I I gave some ideas of what
colors we could use as a contrast
and in the end blue looked the best so
it just went with blue again
you could think honestly even from like
the the style of clothes maybe the
empress Wawa is the same Wawa
just in the same in the in the in
different more fancier clothes maybe
it's alter Wawa going to a party
you know
because if you look at the fluffy hair
from Empress Wawa it could honestly be
the the ponytail opened up
both like fluffy wavy long hair
do we accept this as new lore maybe we
should
yeah I think like alter Wawa fits
perfectly into the ballroom as well
it just works It just fits
what committee on the committee
blue does look really good with your
color palette right yeah
I agree although
with orange green should look really
good with orange too and I have yet to
really
make use of green I mean like there's
like a light turquoise right in my hair
hmm
maybe not like put like really green
green into my hair but maybe into the
clothes like a pastel green the dandel
is like also more on on the turquoise
side I would say
I want more of a like grassy green Maybe
um yeah mint green mint cream mint cream
mint greens what's in my OG hair
oh in the
uh in in the braids from the Casual the
Green in there is not a mint green
it's more like a normal
strong green but it's like only a few
strands
that one was pretty
um
like low-key
the hair stayed mostly orange for that
hairstyle
had some
some green strands but in exchange they
were pretty dark yeah
so for that it it kind of worked but hmm
hmm
green like suffers from Fire Emblem yeah
I feel like
if it's the whole head it works if it's
just a light tiny little bit it works
but if I do like
like the same amount of grain that I
have like mint green in my hair now with
that green I feel like it might look
kind of weird I don't know I have to
test it out
hmm
black could also work on oh yeah
but that would have to be kind of like a
emo edgy
and Wawa Maybe
to go black
maybe like a black tips like tips and
um
yeah
some black strands strands I can't like
change the com like the the complete
hair color that's not
not allowed
but I can change up the the accents so
yeah
hello we
thank you again for the recipe chat
wow
and Captain corn Club Duncan Alex Hedges
thank you
foreign
I've been hoping for an armored Wawa
since day one and this delivers in Spain
plus love the long Pony praise be to
swap the mazovid was great surprise too
I said welcome
thank you you are praising me so much
thank you so much
yeah there you go you're welcome armored
Wawa
finally
oh another raid
thank you
what
seems like we are a popular travel
destination
mm-hmm
and even though I'm just doing Super
Chat writing sorry it's not that
interesting unfortunately
for the recipe check I'm so glad you
like it
thank you for the sweet generous support
and Christy shaver thanks for the pinky
thank you Suave the outfit is beautiful
and cool yay I agree so true so true
so true guys everybody if you wanna
thanks love let him know in like a
Twitter reply
I'm sure he would really appreciate it
and be happy about it if you ride it
here in the Super Chat he's not gonna
see it I'm pretty sure
but thank you
Chad thank you for the pinky as well
and this outfit is freaking beautiful
and high spec I love it so much it's
really cool and it has some sexy
elements as well the tie the thighs
look amazing of course and the pattern
on the see-through fabric around the
shoulders is so gorgeous Keen outfit
yeah I like that part too
the the sheer uh Fabrics around the
shoulders that's one of my favorite
Parts yeah
[Music]
thank you
for it
yeah
that is
foreign
thank you
it's not really a tails of outfit
but yeah
I did
sneak in an artist that worked for tails
of
uh I can be selfish
in exchange for having to go with a
different artist
s
genius
genius just genius thank you Jim Tracy
I'm glad you like it wow
I was thinking you'd go for more of a
mage look
like even though I personally would
prefer playing Mages in games
um I feel like for you know me as a
person
taking
default Wawa as a base uh I'm just
supposed to be a fighter
a warrior
yeah
It's gotta be a warrior
I gotta attack head on
fight fight fight
Mila is a sword use the magic as well
yeah but um Wow Wow fight with blade
cut your throat
with huge ass Claymore
[\h__\h] painful
you just saw I'm a guest for under my
Frontier ah
today
just announce it was that not announced
yet I'm getting confused with
conventions
uh is that new information
okay it's new information
[Laughter]
ah is that one the one in Toronto no we
just had the one in uh
uh wait [\h__\h] don't say anything
I don't know anymore I don't know is it
the Texas one wait am I even going to
Toronto I don't know I don't
[Laughter]
I don't know it's the Texas one yeah
okay okay wait you guys know about the
Toronto Convention right okay
okay okay Toronto and Texas okay okay
two very different places
at all
because both is now public I didn't leak
anything
[Laughter]
yeah yeah yeah I knew it was something I
already I already yeah
it's already out there
hmm
no no European appearance plan so far
um
unfortunately
they don't give a [\h__\h]
I'm sorry
they don't care
thank you for bringing it up
remember when people accuse you of
leaking that there was an EU member in
Advent yeah and I was like no like
that's really not what I meant like but
think when you think you want to think
I didn't link it because it's not it
just didn't there was no EU member
but that's also not what I was trying to
imply ever
yeah
yeah I was just saying something what
did I even say
oh I think it was just because I said
that I spoke the most to narissa
was that it
and then people thought oh that must
mean oh yeah I said something about
because of time zones yeah but that's
just because you know there is a I mean
it was just a link you know doesn't mean
she's in Europe
oh no oh no yeah the thing that I was
really saying there thank you for
reminding me is because I was in Japan
when I first talked to them
and then you know I was busy and then I
was in Europe and yeah so it was just
like time zones that was like a
reference to the time zones I was in
just made it difficult
yeah
and just depending on when they were
around you know
the shocking thing is that nerissa wakes
up before noon EST
yeah she told me that she watches my
stream while she's working just like you
guys
just like you she's you guys
wait
oh
I didn't but maybe management was like
subconsciously inspired by my Advent
calendar when they were thinking about
you know what should we name this Jen
um uh Advent I don't know where I'm
getting this word from but it's just
like in my head for some reason
Advent would be cool wouldn't it let's
go with Advent
[Laughter]
Maybe
no I didn't it's a demon summoning I
didn't know about any demons at the time
the demon summoning I didn't know
anything about demons
I didn't know about demons
[Laughter]
that had nothing to do with the new gen
no no no no no no no no no no no no
really
I didn't know like
I think I mean I think I knew like a new
gen was coming maybe yeah but I didn't
know any details I didn't know uh their
names I didn't know what kind of
character they would be
um
but yeah
maybe I did summon her unknowingly
I summoned something
yeah they don't tell us until very very
very very very late last last minute
like like we will know that something's
gonna happen uh kind of early on
uh but we won't know their names and
their looks until
very close to the debut
[Music]
yes
which honestly is better that way anyway
you know you know you know you know I
was actually happy a little bit for not
being able to stream so much when I was
in Japan uh until like now because until
debut because I was like yeah
I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm scared to leak
something I'm scared to say something
by accident
so it was good that I didn't
stream so much
pouring tea
I'm really glad you did
yeah I mean I don't think they do it to
reduce the pressure I think they just do
it for you know safety security reasons
and
no whatever
they just
like to be secretive
here
little management Birds
all right then keep your secrets
management no they're not Birds I don't
know what I'm saying
I don't know what I'm saying
I'm almost done with these super chats
it's actually incredible uh my scroll
bar is like so so so so low
blah blah blah let me see let me see
um
[Music]
wait wait
no Okay so
don't worry I'm still here
but imagine Well fiata turns back into
normal Walla at midnight
that's why she had to leave
but I would like to end the stream soon
let me like scroll down see how much
ew there's so many pinks and reds
suddenly what the [\h__\h]
maybe I'll end it here
I got so far
I got so far so it's pretty good
[Laughter]
ew
it scared me
scares me I think okay we're stopping at
Jim Tracy okay okay
no
somebody
on the whole elizer we are at number 354
355. 54.
um
okay remember
I am going to check the expiration date
on my meat
and hope it's tomorrow
so that I can just throw in a pizza into
the oven
[Music]
tomorrow members only oh and I have a I
have a meeting
um
hey
I have a meeting
tomorrow
oh yeah I guess we'll do
probably Bell but I'll decide final
tomorrow when I wake up
um
Nani
let me see let me see let me see
interesting thing interesting thing that
you are suggesting
oh
not officially
[Music]
no
I cannot
I I can't
too bad oh well
thank you guys for having fun with me
tonight and see you tomorrow members
only stream and then on the weekend for
GTA GTA GTA let's go I'm so excited it's
been a while since we played GTA
I want to go
it's very exciting
yes
[Music]
yes yeah yeah
oh
[Music]
wow small Wawa becomes bus
we're so happy
[Music]