[Music]
so
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
don't uh be confused by the empty
box next to me um
for a little while uh i will not
be um showing the chat on my stream
[Music]
actually i'm never watching the chat on
on the screen
that you guys see anyway i'm always
checking the chat on a different window
anyway
so yeah um kind of empty
and uh like for for someone who always
watches
archives like me it's a bit
um i always like how the chat is on
screen ah but but but but the chat will
be replayable
anyway after after the stream
anyway good morning
good morning how are you
i i found a new drink
in the convenience store it's a
very sweet no
wow interesting taste
you're doing nice doing fine
today i'm playing
again minecraft oh by the way
does my voice sound a little bit closer
than usual
with usual i mean yesterday and the day
before i guess
does it sound a bit closer yeah
well well well my
my microphone is not on the tissue box
anymore
my microphone is now finally mounted
to the mic arm that i had before
because i ordered a tiny screw hello
hello thanks for the super chats i will
read them all again at the end of the
stream
yeah it's now mounted to the my car with
the screw that i ordered
the screw fit and the microphone
fits but now we have another problem yay
we have another problem
the next problem is the microphone is
too heavy for my mic arm therefore
although it is connected to my mic arm
it is being
held up by um
[Music]
a two liter water bottle
i i think it's two liters
yeah because it just goes down and then
yeah
so i think i will once again
go on amazon make another purchase
for a new sturdier
um mic arm
yay yay
oh i love this so much
[Music]
well so the microphone is
closer to my face than usual any
but still but yeah i still have to kind
of look down it's a bit of
a but i guess i guess this work
let me move a little bit just don't
don't fall
ah don't fall down from the water bottle
just uh it's just too weak
it's just too weak
yo vandal
yeah it just it just never ends
welcome back to stein's gate
uh purposefully
written a bit differently
and here we go again
no bgm eh oh oh i turned up to
thank you for telling me oh how about
this is it too loud
is it too loud because last time
you guys told me it's fine and then some
people told me it's too quiet and then i
remembered okay they're always gonna
have a different opinion usually always
felt like it's too loud in other cases
but then i watched the archive and this
time it was really too quiet
yeah but now i've i turned it up a bit
more than yesterday so i think it should
be fine
hey what what is this
yeah yesterday i took a screenshot
flexing with my shiny weapons
okay let's see what i remember from what
i learned yesterday
and we will not be using those but like
i feel i'm just scared to lose them
but in the end i'm gonna find more of
these
fancy weapons right
i'm gonna find more and i mean
i don't know should i use them
but maybe maybe not today because i
don't know what are we gonna do today
um i was thinking
um probably
we are going to i want to try find
a village and i want to learn how to
make uh like a far oh
how to make a farm and where i can like
make potatoes
and carrots can i sleep okay
and yeah let's see what else we can do
after that
but maybe we first tried to find the
farm
all right actually i have barely ah
i don't have so much to eat oh wait
can we do something about that oh iron
oh i'm still baking iron
are you winning kiara i'm winning i'm
totally winning
[Music]
bgm bob's too high dude that's a good
thing right
uh i can stick
wait i need um do i have more meat no
ah raw beef that's about it
right yeah oh well
we're trying to find a village they they
usually have food too right
so like some kind of food but let's make
this first
i'm getting used to the controls that's
a good stick
oh wait maybe need that
[Music]
ah maybe make a new pickaxe first
should we make a new pickaxe but with
what
uh this and what else we need wood
wood
was was it was any wood fine or did i
need planks i wonder if i got
is our planks okay
would you would you take a plank wait no
you need sticks you need sticks
no planks well i have some sticks you
take that
okay okay okay
okay now we got it okay let's make one
should we make another one just in case
i don't know you never know what's going
to happen
let's make oh oh no no no
just in case shield oh
oh [\h__\h]
need more planks i have five
wait is that enough maybe that's enough
maybe that's enough
[Music]
no one two three four five six
huh
tree there is so so few trees here
make an iron pick make armor
one oh i can oh one log makes four
planks i [\h__\h] oh okay okay
didn't realize that that was enough
okay one log and
nice and then these yeah
we made our first shield nice
very cool okay so we put that
here how do i use it
how do i use it
[Music]
so okay guys uh where
where is wait we don't need those stones
although i guess we could
use them to make uh to lead me back to
where i came from right
wait wait i remember um i remember
um there was a village
around the area where we first came from
but i never was able to make armor oh
okay do i need more wood for that i was
never able to
you know um find
the spot again where i uh
first started off
[Music]
what about stone didn't you guys say i
can make something out of stone
iron i need iron
i don't have so much
i can make this i can make
this i can't i can make this
oh i can make all of them oh
wow now don't die
[Music]
okay so i still think originally oops
uh i i always want to zoom out with
those a mouse scroller
and i think we're probably in that
direction
we came from that direction i think so
if we go there
then we might be able to find the
village that
i i when we were streaming i didn't see
it but after i was streaming i saw it
so
we will try to survive and find a
village it's a bit laggy right now
um should we also kill some of you
wait i've also taken some advice
on twitter for example apparently
you shouldn't spam and
you shouldn't spam like this
so i'm acknowledging it
i've gotten a huge list of other advices
but honestly do you think
i can suddenly remember all of that
those advices like 15 advices or so
what
oh i don't remember this
[Music]
i don't remember such a place did we
really come from here
hmm
yeah i saw irene there but i don't want
to go down there right now
[Music]
why not dungeon
dungeon spawner what
oh my god why is ender why is that
enderman here
what if i try to kill him
i remember something
how do you do it again there's horses i
want a horse
how does it what is something like that
where did he go
huh
wow okay
i want a horse how do i get a horse
can i get one can i ride it one
do i need to give it carrots though
in front of me no
i need a saddle eh can i make one
i have i think i have one letter
i have one single letter a letter
oh how cute any carrots god damn it
okay maybe maybe another time
oh yay uh well i'm just going in a
random direction now
i'd like to find the spot where i
originally spawned but i feel like it's
almost impossible
you don't need carrots you cannot make
sabbles okay
enderman my buddy hello don't look into
[Music]
i mean i wanna you you're pretty i wanna
look at you
[Music]
oh
dun dun dun dun dun
like a small tower i don't want to get
lost
oh i didn't even save my coordinates ha
ha i mean
probably they were somewhere in the last
wait that's not smart
there's no water here
okay never mind smart thinking
okay good that we made more
it's getting dark what do i do now
just gotta fight huh i think i'm just
gonna
fight
i'm scared well we don't need to run
away
like we did last time we are stronger
and we are experienced
is that the the one that we saw yeah
that's the one we saw in the
in the last stream oh nice
that means we're close or no
we
i think that means we're close
to our original spawning point
i want that gold dough but i'll leave it
there
wait can i with my normal pickaxe can i
get that
i just went around my house and yeah
probably
no okay okay then i'll leave it
okay okay we found some really nice
treasures there last time
that was cool is this really not
close to where oh my god so many
[Music]
wait i don't feel ready for a skeleton
guys yet
[Music]
okay right click right click okay
well wait oh wait wait ha ha
ha
we forgot the stones come on
so scary let's
[Music]
i just saw my tower
okay that was easy
uh wait
no no no no no no need to run but i'm
running anyway
wait why what does that mean where are
we if my tower is there
where did i come from originally i
really just went around
eh well i can't sleep now i guess
not
god
yes
[Music]
i really don't remember i wanna go back
okay so then we're just going in a
random direction to find a village
ooh cooked pork chop
yummy you gave me anxiety i'm sorry
it gives me anxiety too
so scary random direction time hell yeah
i'm gonna wait for the meat though who
knows when we will be able to come back
maybe we'll die from hunger we don't
want that
adventure stop picking it up
can i have a trash can here
[Music]
check coordinates oh yeah
hope you guys remember that
better remember it because i'm not gonna
let's go again
this time how about we don't go in a
circle hmm
i'll go over the mountain
actually that looks dangerous
drama
okay if we go over the mountain we'll
have a better view
everything will be nice oh there's so
many sheeps here
hello
nice
nice hello
[Music]
that was one hit yeah i'm getting
stronger
did i miss something
[Music]
thank you thank you for your offering
my dear sheep
oh there's a one of my stones
that don't mean anything right now well
we
keep on going here okay okay
to a path which will lead me to
nowhere probably eh i should probably
hmm
i guess we'll go down
is that the one we saw
previously that huge gap between
no that that's a different one
i want to see a village
i want to see a village i want to see a
village
i was here before i see the stones
are we going in a circle again no
well it was definitely hell and the man
in an area with those trees
so i mean
i would say wait why the water is so
clear
no how do i swim
[Music]
is this how you swim circle again
no i'm impossible
i'm going a straight line the whole time
it's a straight line no for real this
time
we're getting closer i'm sure
wow he's so
oh my god that sounds scary
i got a heart attack
and it really scared me
it really scared me
i've been clear close
i want to turn down the
the sound effect for that
which one is it is it hostile creatures
what what's hostile creatures
god gave me the biggest spook ever
they were always so loud anyway all of
them too loud
okay
um do you want to change something else
ah the clouds yeah i guess so
okay okay okay it's all good calm down
kiara
you will never hear such a scary sound
again
why aren't they even there
okay yes yes i think we're close because
we had
we had like uh the desert
as well in the beginning and we really
didn't go that far
it must be here
[Music]
right
yay
are you lost no i'm not lost
i think
[Music]
it was um it was however not in the sand
it not was not in the desert oh there's
bees there were bees in the beginning
there were bees in the beginning
maybe it's over there
sand usually yeah there was a village
close by
maybe it's over there
the single flower here is that so
so wow planet
we must be close there were also i think
a lot of moo moos around
and yeah not so many trees but
oh my god is it here
no
wait let's put something here i'm
definitely
never gonna find back
[Laughter]
i'm never gonna find the way back but
okay
i eat oh oh thank you i
i will definitely not remember that
again
where could we have come from
i don't think there were so many sheeps
though
i think we're getting uh
further away because i also don't
remember such a
huge mountain
it was um more flat the area was much
more flat fall of the desert
it's advisable to leave your core cords
on
yeah i can't read them anyway
remember the suicidal bunnies yeah i do
that was where was that
there was some really crazy suicidal
bunnies but
the grass did not have that color
it was more like that yeah
[Music]
follow your heart indeed
that's what i shall do
hello sheeps well
i mean even if we're never gonna find
that place again
we still um just want to find the
village right oh my god it's getting
dark now though
well that's a weird tree
hey what a cute bunny
wow it's so beautiful
pickle pickle pickle
[Music]
oh it's night it's night my friends oh
i didn't place any blocks
gotta place your blocks carefully
uh oh here comes the night again
scary scary
you can make a bed oh i guess i can
i just don't have i just don't have wood
should we make a bed i guess
i guess we can need a tree
yeah uh take take with me bed
oh my god
oops
but don't i need a i need another one of
those boxes right
is that enough
correct
oh wait so i need this box but first we
need to make planks
[Music]
no no bad oh yeah it changes my respawn
point
uh maybe not such a good idea
huh well we just gotta fight
it's okay sleep is for the week
right right
[Music]
no no this is not the whole life server
no no no
playing single single player
oh my god don't you dare
explode on me don't you dare
have some mercy i'm new to this
game okay i met may have
watched over 100 hours of minecraft
gameplay from a certain senpai
but i'm still what the hell is that
excuse me i'm a tourist i would like to
see
your beautiful nature those are some
weird
trees
this is not healthy looking
yeah we're definitely far away from
oh my god far away from
the original spawn point
leave me alone you stupid child
oh my god all these noises are so
disgusting
[Music]
are there some villager zombies
i've seen those before so
village clothes
oh my god
ah deserts oh okay okay okay
oh
that glass empire saved me it's such a
scary world out here
oh my god oh my god there's so many
enemies
hello hello just ignore me please just
ignore me please
i'm on a mission don't disturb me
i'm a full-fledged warrior
but i'm not gonna fight you
again but no treasure chest
no treasure chest this time oh hello
hello interesting
gold well am i safe here because it's
light
is this lucky this is the second one
wait wait wait you
how dare you poisoned me you little
piece of [\h__\h]
you poisoned me how are you not dying
is there maybe something under the sand
i wonder
oh
no
do not do not dig straight down got you
i got you
hmm
hey don't gang up on me
well i guess there's nothing here
besides one block of gold
i'll be back
see you later build a tower
okay oh yeah there's water maybe we can
make another tower
when these stupid
idiots leave me alone
actually good idea because then up there
they can't touch me
let's see the chords okey-dokey
let's just wait until it's day
crouch no crouching is for the week
well i can't see my old tower that's for
sure
the sun oh let's watch the sun rise
together my friends
is
so beautiful
don't don't bully my pc guys
don't bully my pc
you know i'm a phoenix so
i'm a friend of the sun i'm
a child of the sun
it's day and these
creeps are really disgusting down there
could you die
what are you doing what are they doing
they're burning nice okay let's
jump oh that's so scary that
sounds scary no no no no
no no no no no no no no no
no no no
fight fight me if you think you can
fight me well you'll regret it
i heard someone needs a new mic stand it
doesn't cost five hundred dollars though
i mean i think they probably aren't mic
stands that cost that much too but
oh my god it doesn't cost five hundred
dollars
i read your super chat later okie dokie
thank you so much thank you shane
i did it i killed all the zombies yay
[Music]
hello enderman he's so sparkly and
pretty and cute
the sound scares me what do i need to
get that gold though
hello i'm busy
i'm busy
i want to see if there's something
hidden
is there a possibility
no maybe not
pickaxe i should have made one
oh well okay bye
okay did i make okay tower okay
good we good we have a second tower
we are as um how do you say
establishing our dominance no that's not
quite right
we are asserting our dominance how do
you say that
not sure
well sounds about right
dominating the landscape oh yeah oh
that's a mushroom tree
i know that sometimes close to this
there's like a witch house or something
well i guess we didn't find the village
maybe we can find a witch house
[Music]
or maybe not
yo what's your feet i don't know how do
i see my seat
are you jealous of my seat did i get a
good one
i just thought i saw something cool but
i didn't i guess
well it's close really
i want kiara seeds
that sounds wrong that sounds wrong
don't do this guys you're gonna push me
even more bottom left
this is interesting like i like this the
scenery of like a mushroom tree
and then suddenly the ocean
very fancy
sheep
i want to see if there's something
special in this uh
forest if we are lucky maybe there's
something
cool in here right
but it's so hard to move in here maybe i
should be on
on top of a tree
right to have a better view ah
okay probably there's nothing here
smartest bird
thank you thank you so much
can i make mushroom soup out of those
trees
what
is it phoenix basically just a fire
chicken what a question
no i'm much more than that
i'm much more than yes you can well i
can make soup out of those trees
what what here we go
vegetarian lifestyle what is better an
axe or a
pickaxe ah i dropped it
i dropped it
i dropped x
i dropped it i keep dropping it
the brown one
oh it falls down i don't want to go
[Music]
okay
okay we'll just pick it up on the ground
well there's not so much dropping but
okay
can i eat them raw though
ah
no okay but i guess uh it was easy to
make soup right so
oh so many mushrooms yay
wait there's so much no that's flowers
okay
this one does not give me mushrooms oh
it does ah
cool i mean i hate mushrooms but awesome
yay
okay use your sword
i killed my first skeleton i think
i think that was my first
whoa
so one second oh my chair
oh let me drink something are we doing
good
are we doing a good exploring
feel like a really professional
adventurer
[Music]
mushrooms i'm not gonna get poisoned by
the red ones right
i think they should be fine
is that what is that is that a sheep
nope okay one two oh god damn it
thank you
people keep uh saying to not backseat me
and in some way i mean yeah
but i need your help
i need you i'm stupid i i'm very
um dependent i'm not as
independent as i probably should be
goddammit my axe is gone well i mean we
got enough mushrooms
but from which direction did i come from
hmm from where did i come from
do you know
[Music]
uh
uh we probably came from there right
[Music]
what are those coordinates gonna tell us
do you probably know more than i do
get some redstone and make what what
to your right
go right why what is that on the right
side
ah
my sword is about to break
i don't like forests
stress
[Music]
oh my god the night is coming the night
is coming
okay do you know where i need to go
oh one hit
make a tower i already just made the
tower
go run to the west go left golden
didn't i come from here
build a little house eh
do i really need that
[Music]
protect me
okay is that good enough
[Laughter]
are they gonna come from above
spiders can climb
[Music]
it drops on me
he poisoned me again
oh i made him a platform don't come into
my house
oh my god oh my god
[Music]
huh
where do i go where do i go
keep moving okay but i feel like we're
going in the direction where i came from
[Music]
also i don't have my blocks anymore
i don't have my blocks
i need blocks
but there's only sand here i don't want
sand
well
horace stream it feels like a horseshoe
what is safe
how isn't there like water zombies in
here too
don't like sand because it gets like
everywhere and then you shower and then
you still have sand everywhere
fishies maybe let's get some fishes i
need a new sword soon though
i'm gonna probably drown while i'm
trying to catch these fish
i don't know how to swim faster
yeah this is not gonna happen what is
not safe that's what i thought
especially if i can't swim properly
i don't see any zombies here
double tap w double tap w to swim faster
like this it feels weird
double tap forward it it's not doing
anything
ww and what ctrl
oh
i did not look at you i did not look at
you i did not look at you
no
oh my god i'm scared no no don't shoot
me in the water that's not fair okay
we're good we're good we're just doing a
little swim swim
we're just doing a little swim swim
don't mind me
make a boat yeah we could make a boat
but am i ever gonna find a village
am i ever going to find my village
fly with your phoenix wings i wish i
could
can i eat in water
there's no need to die because i don't
necessarily want to go back right now
i mean eventually it would be cool
i'm going back to where i came from
right right now it's not what i want to
do
[Music]
hello
i mean there is no blocks from me here i
did not
have i didn't place any blocks here well
hey let's let's get some blocks from
here
ah the shovel is better for this house
never mind me then
where the hell am i guys
where the hell am i yay
[Music]
no i don't know when to go
but the coordinates that you gave me is
that supposed to be my home i don't want
to go home
oh
[Music]
it's getting brighter again i think sun
is going up
hallelujah hallelujah
i heard there was a secret what is that
court that david played and pleased the
lord
what is that but you don't really care
for music
do you and it goes like this
the fourth the fifth hello
oh my god what that's a fancy village
hello
friends please save me i don't wanna cat
oh my god hello
i found a village okay now don't hit him
right click
i don't want to hit you how do i talk to
them again
you don't want to talk to me can you not
talk to me
hello hello they don't talk to me okay
i guess it's not that kind of rpg oh
thank you i'll take that they won't kill
me for taking that right
i mean i don't know why i would need oh
it's it's horse armor
what is that oh
thank you for your gracious offering
i call him i think
what
did someone just hit me
the cactus oh
those stones are so pretty
[Music]
could it be that there's like a pyramid
here too
oh wait we should eat don't you have
food guys
can i eat that i make i can make bread
out of it right
steal the belt didn't i do it
what belt at the belt
why why why would i do that
take a bed but i don't wanna i don't
wanna change my
spawn point
still right click the bell why why
why
why why
why why why
what why why
why oh what
what did that do for me
what did that do for me don't panic i
don't want to make them panic
hello
yay phone thank you what's that book
i don't need books do i
oh thank god i mean
hmm
more houses yay hello do not have a
chest
okay wait was i in here before
oh more bread and the fancy stone
emerald
hey nice farm you got there hope they're
getting enough water there
otherwise i'll have to take them with me
what nice village goal number one
accomplished it's a bit of a small
village but
imura
i guess that's it bad i guess i can take
one just in case i change my mind about
the spawn point thing
that's it give it to me
steal everything no i don't even need
more but
no i don't want to kill the mummus i
don't want to kill them
[Music]
take the bell but why would i do that
what does that do for me
why do i need the bell
do it eh hit the goal no i'm not gonna
hit the goal
and that's not gonna do anything good
for me i'm sure about that
take the belt it's just amusing to you
okay
okay please don't eh
semi-rare item what what does it do
i can't place the flower interesting
okay belle nice sand not so nice
bed nice
new shoes i got some new shoes
actually i need oh i do have another
sword nice
well that's smart minecraft that is
actually i respect you for
being that logical
i don't have any more blocks i'm never
gonna find home i could get those blocks
there
gucci slippers hell yeah oh throw away
that
you yo
[Music]
that's some fancy stone there is that
something special behind there the seeds
i want the seeds
it's just decorative okay
well you never know maybe maybe there is
something fancy in there
i have some weird stomach egg i don't
know why
maybe it's my posture again
[Music]
hello
eat you eat don't tell me to eat just
kidding i should probably eat
more stones please
go to the top oh
maybe i will
how am i gonna get up though how am i
gonna get up
not thinking so much about this
well i just want stones right now
yeah so many stones neat
they will help me find my way again and
probably end up being totally useless
but i will not give up my home i will
not give up
or forget where i came from
i will never forget
i mean i forgot actually i don't know
where i came from
i don't know the coordinates but you
know it's just a
way of speech
i didn't wha wha what are those
coordinates
i know one five six seven two two three
feet what
what everyone copy that i don't know
what it is but copy that
this is my house no this this is no no
this is not my new house how do i get
out of here
let's try to get out of here
honey please go home no
we haven't done anything besides finding
a village
wait am i going to the right direction
make torches
am i going in the right direction right
now
maybe not
oh my stomach hurts
[Music]
am i really getting lost in a mountain
that i just wanted to visit it must be
up there
it's up there i just wanted to go in
here to get some stones
is it too much to ask
come on let me out of here
let me out of this oh that's home
really is that those coordinates are
home okay
well i have them copy paste it
oh my god just let me out
that can actually give you damage but
that's funny
[Laughter]
[\h__\h]
uh
get your items back how am i ever gonna
make it in time
lesson learned no what what was i
supposed to learn
lessons and blocks of big gravity okay
i learned that well yes i have learned
[Music]
that
no there's no way i can make it i
you know how how i am with directions
also we don't have
food probably
[Music]
okay we don't have food
my stomach hurts
let's get food
[Music]
i am so sad
why hello stones
why i wanted a
i wanted to go far today
start farming oh my mushrooms are gone
my mushrooms
pink
[Music]
hello i'm using an enchanted sword how
you not dying faster
stop running
okay what do we do guys do we go for
another village
please make a map oh
okay i guess i can do that what do i
need for that
i need to make paper right whoa
stop stop stop stop running
nice
oi why are the cows running so fast oh
my god
one more please
yeah they really know how to move
hahahaha
funny oh there's so many animals here
wow we can make a lot of burgers out of
that for kfp
did you guys see the the fan art that i
retweeted
uh before the stream with all the whole
live en girls in my uniform huh that was
so cute
everyone has to wear that sexy uniform
everyone has to oh wait my sword is gone
my fancy sword is gone how did it break
so fast
is there anything good happening here
like anything
gold swords break instantly
oh come on
[Music]
come on
decoration only paint pickle
wheat farm
[Music]
my saddles are gone
my saddle is gone
[Music]
wait what do i want what i'm looking for
what am i looking for
huh six
let's make a sword
that was really really sad
a pickaxe
where's the sword i don't see a sword
where is that well i guess we can make
an iron sword
um
welp that is too bad
huh
find a cave make a farm hurt something
okay let's make a farm
here but a farm of what
what and what do i need to make a farm
like what if i want to make a potato
farm
first i probably need a potato to start
with right or wheat how do i get
wheat i don't know i didn't see any
wheat around here how do you make weed
chicken farm close the doors yes sir
will do
you have seats oh get potato from
village
which village the village we just saw
it's gonna
take a while to get there
see it's oh grass break grass
oh
i can make a wheat out of that and then
i can make bread out of that
is that how it works
oh wow that's
that's interesting but so
but for every other things like carrots
and
potatoes i first need an actual carrot
and potato for that right
to start off with
i wish i had a carat potato
[Music]
i wish i had one
no do i have enough
zombies can drop it
[Music]
well well well okay so now we just place
the seeds here
wait maybe make it
place it next to water oh
smart bombing 101 with minecraft
wow
[Music]
i want to make it like clear here
so that there's no other grass okay so
here
is good
oh i can't place it
make a hole hole
how hulk
[Music]
did i say it right i'm gonna make a
shtick
again where are the sticks
i don't know there we go
and the hulk is it whole
i feel so bad saying that
where did i get that i went from
oh yay so is it like
no that's not how you do it
how close does it have to be to the
water
like super close or is this fun too
four blocks five blocks nine blocks
that's so
you all are saying something different
but i guess
where it turns into this color is still
fine
oh
[Music]
my first fun
yeah i'm making my first farm
i wonder if my papa is watching he would
be proud of me
i think
did he write anything in the chat today
i don't remember seeing him
go to sleep okay wait look my friend
wanna
plan everything
[Music]
sleep
good morning don't jump on them okay but
i can walk on them right
wow look at that
but i have to wait longer right okay
let's make more
wow
[Music]
let's make more
we
but they want to go on an adventure that
is like
further away i want to go
to a place that i have never seen before
and there's a lot of them there's a lot
of places that i've never seen
never time hmm that's not the kind of
place i want to go to never scary
[Music]
i don't want to go there
i want more and one more
okay
so how long does this take
[Music]
don't sleep on the nether uh
why why was that
just stare at it okay
oh it did do something
a few days go yeah let's go to the ocean
but what did i do on the ocean
i wanna go on the ocean
road
find fish hmm
look for another continent
[Music]
but i wanna find another village
but it's such a long way to go
[Music]
and it takes so much time
golden axe
too early yes silk that
is that is that good to have silk touch
on a golden axe
chicken mining yeah
well i guess we need more iron and stuff
yeah that is true
that is true
[Music]
god damn it just keeps coming it just
keeps coming
okay then let's go a bit mining we can
do some talkie talkie
yeah is that enough food i guess it's
enough food
okay do we go mining in the same place
you can disenchant it do i want to do
that
make torture oh yeah oh yeah
i think i still had some right you can't
go mining without torches right right
right right that's true
you know yeah you never turned my hat
when do you think
when did you last watch my stream i have
my hat back for a while now
what no where are my torches did i have
much oh i lost them
that's right i lost a lot of
a lot of torches
um well
i lost like 50 torches if i remember
correctly
yup yup
f f goodbye torches i'll miss you
i go really attached to you
mining for coal yeah and for iron yeah
and maybe some other fancy stuff
[Music]
what am i doing can i not make planks
out of birch log
can i not make planks out of that
oh i can
okay now make more sticks
[Music]
shift click to take them all well too
late
and now
we got some more coal all good
[Music]
[\h__\h] oh my stomach hurts so bad
wow why does it hurt so bad
maybe because yesterday my dinner was
two pieces of chocolate candy
maybe that's why
yeah yesterday i didn't really i didn't
really eat much
let's go mining oh wait
i mean i already ate a muffin today
[Music]
yes i support the kinder bueno diet
thank you
um excuse me what are they doing here
what does that mean
what what does this mean
what what what
stay away
they're invading my village
don't go close okay they're friendly
yeah yeah of course they're friendly
i've seen them in pekora streams i know
i know
i know what those guys do
i know i know very well
let's go this way
there's a village nearby they appear
yeah i know there's a village nearby i
just can't find it
what is that iron i forgot
i think that's iron
nice we found iron really fast oh copper
no
iron okay
not so much thank you
itadakimasu thank you
yeah i'm gonna go deeper
let's make one one way maybe
so we don't waste so much
see i have the technique i learned it
i know how we do it oh yes
more i run more i run
warning what are you warning me about
press f3 for coordination but i'm close
to my home
i don't need that
not digging straight down and making a
staircase
me smart
get diamonds hell yeah but i think do
not have the wrong
in pickaxe for
getting diamonds
you're proud of me because of minecraft
iron pickaxe so if we find a diamond
we'll just come back with an iron
pickaxe later
sounds good i think it does i think i
went too far there
yes
ah mine two twelve
why twelve where's why why why
why why why why ah i'm at 45 now right
so
[Music]
now i'm at 44. wow that i gotta go
really deep huh
this is so confusing
okay let's find diamonds
diamonds are a girl's best friend
you gotta go real deep here
[Music]
don't
almost breaking
my pickaxe is almost broken how far
are we 34. we're making good progress
but this is not boring for you guys
is this not boring me just digging and
digging
we should talk about something at least
no this is great are you for real
are you sure this is great you say this
is great are you
are you serious no not
what well you guys are very easily
entertained
then
i wonder if i'm also that easily
entertained i mean
like if it's if it's pickled as
streaming
then i could watch her for hours like
that
especially before going to sleep but
anyone else nah nah
also why why does my stomach hurt and
why does my head hurt why does
everything hurt
why
[Music]
i need an iron pickaxe oh
hey well look we got so much iron
where where are we oh we're close
and
[Music]
be careful of lava oh yeah
oh be careful
maybe let's take some space
i heard a train
because i'm laying an egg no i told you
guys
phoenix's don't lay eggs
should i tell you again how we make love
i told you the story before you don't
remember
yes okay i hear lava
or water something like that
when two phoenixes love each other very
much
they
and rub their
bodies against each other really fast
and then they go and like get really hot
and then they get so hot that they go up
in flames together
and then you see some ashes
but then out of the ashes you know as
phoenix's do phoenix's rise from their
ashes
but this time it's not just those two
phoenixes who made love to each other
rising from their ashes it's also a baby
a baby phoenix so
they multiplied
yup that's how it works i never did it
before but
of course i never did it before but
there's also nothing rude about it
we're at six oh we're much too deep just
like this story we went too deep
we went too deep just like this story so
this is 10 and this is 11 this is 12.
i see i think there's water here close
hmm eleven is better than twelve
let's go this way
too deep
nine is better than well some say twelve
some say nine
some say eleven so oh can i
can i get that with my x or do i really
need an
iron axe now
iron okay
one second please i'll be right back
wow he went so deep
my head hurts
[Music]
her
is this where we came from maybe yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
neat
was that spanish i tried to speak
italian but
similar close enough oh it's night
hello
rude
go away i want to sleep
actually oh no
where's my iron are here and
you good night
good morning what's happening
i don't like this sounds
okay so we want an
iron pickaxe right
yeah and uh
hmm
what style right
[Music]
how's my wheat doing
huh
how dare you how dare you
my weight
wow these stupid skeletons
i think is this one done or not yet this
single one
is it done
don't walk over oh but how am i gonna
how i'm gonna harvest it if i can't walk
over it
not ready okay
huh you can't just don't jump okie dokie
make shield again yeah
make a shield
nice make uh maybe one more
iron pickaxe make
make some shoes
shoes
then make a
can i make leggings
i run leggings seems legit to me
although i don't want to cover up my
beautiful clothes
[Music]
a bucket for water why don't why do i
want water
for like if i meet lava
for farming for lava
oh where is the bucket
huh did i miss it
oh i don't see a bucket oh [\h__\h] it
yeah that's i feel like i'm wasting my
iron
stupid bucket okay is it is this how i
how i do it i go
there
with my bucket and i go
sip neat
it's useful i guess so yeah but but here
everything is getting uh uh
water so i don't need to
i don't need to water it right
water the winter
put the bucket on your head
and no need yeah one is ready is this
one ready
this looks ready
no yeah no yeah
it's ready
no oh [\h__\h] it looked ready
uh wait maybe it was ready huh it was
ready
yay way we can make bread can we
with two wheat
no pan no then one more
[Music]
okay
oh it's done we all we have all the iron
but that
ended up not being so much after all
well
[Music]
ah we don't have enough for a hat
anymore do we
oh god damn it okay
you go here i'll get some more
[Music]
bye-bye
plant seed oh
okay yeah before we go we should plant
the seed and i think yeah one more is
ready
this one
yay okay okay but i need i need a
like do i need a hole to plant it
did i need a hole for that
no oh
okay
[Music]
now we can make ourselves bread
uh where did i put it here
[Music]
taste test
and goodbye brad that was it that was a
short
but nice treat
[Music]
so proud tastes like bread
yeah pretty much there close the doors
you say close the doors
bye bye wait five oh i ran over it
oopsie
yeah next baker gold cake oh my god what
do you need to make a cake maybe an egg
and wheat
i could imagine that would be necessary
is this where we went yeah
milk and sugar oh yeah let's make a cake
sometime soon
drink some water i'm gonna drink some
really sugary drink though
hydrate
hydrate nope nope it's actually cuddle
pizza
but a special oh no no no no no yes yes
yes i don't know i don't remember what i
can use this for it's not as useful as
other things i guess
but still we get something
new
okay we use the other one better right
now
again we just stay in this area i guess
because we are on 10 right now huh
i wanna stay here maybe
ah
is that always should i make one more
stone axe
torch yes sir
iron is good okay
oh
hello lava there is a lover that i kept
on hearing
maybe finally we found something
interesting
[Music]
how do we get there
now be careful
be careful
i'm here to mine some good stuff please
thank you
thank you spam torches
it's already bright here no
i guess not
that looks like a really nice pool it's
like a
like a sauna or like a onsen
onsen
let's do some lava diving
i could use a hot bath actually i think
after the stream today i'm gonna take a
hot bath
i think like usually i'm not the the
bathtub what about you guys
shower again yeah me too like when i
take a bath
and i usually i use some fancy oh
i use some fancy bath bombs or whatever
but then i like get so impatient even if
i
bring my laptop with me and i start
watching some
decorative streams or some netflix
i still like after 10 minutes i'm like i
want to get out of here
i can't stay longer than 10 minutes and
but then i feel like it's so
such a waste of that expensive lush
bath bomb because they are
i would say they're expensive like
what is it maybe like five dollars or
more for a bath bomb
so i want to stay in there longer
yep
should i pour a bucket over this
yeah do you think i'm so stupid that i
would
like step on the lava
you think i'm that stupid
yes interesting
oh
[Music]
that didn't do much
pick up water it's kind of far away can
i pick it up from here
oh i can oh
no i lost it
i lost
well but can't i just uh do this
oh yeah that works too
but it's getting so dark
no more lava
darkness the darkness is
inside me small brain excuse me
excuse me why
hmm i guess i harvested everything
should i just keep on digging
bird brain excuse me that's
i i take it as a compliment
[Music]
homer
on digging should i keep on digging
where are we on twelve
but maybe we can go to the other side
too
there was another lava pool over there
but there was nothing else besides that
but maybe maybe
just dick straight okay
is that really a good idea though
oh did we connect or no it's a new place
yay why are you face bombing
thank you for the super chat
try to swim in lava i did not try to
swim in lava
can i get back my stuff or is it like
lost
please don't tell me my stuff is lost
don't tell me my stuff is lost
it's i can it's still there right it's
still there
it's still there right
no no no no no no don't tell me it slows
no
no then
[Music]
um
i don't wanna
i don't
[Music]
i don't want to start all over
oh no one
[Music]
i need to get used to this this is
minecraft
this is minecraft right
you die you lose everything you gotta
get used to it
i guess
but
[Music]
i don't know if i can keep on playing
i don't know if i can keep on like this
i mean
i still have some stuff and
what do i have i have a little bit of
iron
i have a wooden sword i have a golden
hill
and a golden axe
i have some sticks i have some blanks
i have lots of stones
i have one some iron nuggets can i make
more iron with the iron nuggets
yeah how do i do it do i have to put it
in here no
let's see probably yes
one more no
okay that's all right now it's not it's
not like i want anymore
wait what am i doing it's not like i
wanted anymore iron
thank you
well that should be enough torches
and now um
we need an iron pickaxe and maybe
maybe a stone pickaxe
why is the stone
maybe one more and maybe one
no okay maybe not a bucket
a bucket ah can i make a bucket no
i can't make a bucket it's okay
i don't need a bucket did you think i
needed a bucket
[Music]
let's take my wooden sword
and that's about it
that's about
do i look like i need a
is this bucket i think
is it is it done
yeah oh yeah i think
yeah why can't we make one more bread
one more bread and then we go mining
again
pam
free bread wow that is so much that is
gonna keep me
alive for sure well they get done so
fast i just
hope oh we should probably yeah
while they're all getting down we can
make one more bread maybe
nope oh maybe yeah
[Music]
it so i learned how to make bread
okay
[Music]
okay now here we go
again
actually look you want to go somewhere
else
i want to go somewhere else i felt like
there was not so much i could do that
but actually now let's continue there
because we don't have so many axes
we don't have so many axes right now and
uh i would have to go so deep that it
will probably break me a few
yeah i need to dig a bit more here
take everything you see
turn off auto jump why it's really
really useful
why do well why why should i do
why did i turn it off
[Music]
that's good
autumn killed me oh
did it what
i will never forget auto jump how do i
turn that [\h__\h] off
so it was not because i was stupid not
because i was not
careful it was because of the [\h__\h]
auto jump
watashi no says
[Music]
excuse me what is with my language
i'm speaking beautiful verb language
well there's nothing
oh yeah i did that and then i went oh no
oh it was there it was there
well this is where i died hooray
nice memories and so
um there's something up there
oh
yay bats are they
are they dangerous
yeah i thought bats were not dangerous
magicka
oh you give me a shuke
oh my god
oh so much up there
oh my neck hurts gold gold gold gold
always look up
guys never always look down
oh
wait i did that right right
i that was how i was supposed to do it
right
oh okay
yay two gold
nice nice sounds
i don't know what i'm going to use it
for but hey we got gold
let's harvest that too
[Music]
oh did it stop there does it stop it
stops there
huh maybe we do some more digging here
where are we we are on 28 oh that's
quite high
let's go lower again
oh that was oh
this is how you get lost no
it's not so hard to get out of here it's
not such a
goat can be used to make huh
gold can be used to make an array of
golden apples are the most powerful food
in minecraft oh really
so the thing i want to make with that
gold is golden apples
what that seems like a waste
she noticed the message oh yeah i'm
looking at the chat looking at the stuff
you right there
of course
when you can swim in lava with a golden
apple i
highly doubt that i
highly doubt that
golden um oh yeah i need golden armor
for never that's
right i learned that
that is right that's what we need gold
for
it's actually true i call that
[\h__\h]
i call that [\h__\h]
but maybe it is true
oh guys actually um your guys's
guys's replies on my tweet yesterday
cracked me up every single reply to my
tweet
yesterday was like um phrasing
uh kiara uh phrasing
uh phrasing
you know that was totally intentional do
you
and there was nothing wrong with my
phrasing i was a minecraft version until
yesterday
i was a minecraft virgin and minecraft
took my minecraft virginity
that's just how it is i it was correctly
phrased
totally there was no problem with my
phrasing there
absolutely no problem
why do the smallest noises scare me that
much now the connectivity
what am i hearing
oh i destroyed my stairs
i think it's there
water where is the water
it's lava it's lava of water
but i only have
i guess that would be a smart move
where is it
it's gone
ah subtitles point to the source
how do i turn them on it's below you
really
i'm on seventeen well we gotta go lower
anyway
[Music]
be careful okay don't worry about me
i'll be fine
probably if i'm going to die again
then the stream for today is over
don't you die
oh no
i hear lava and water now
i think
it stopped it stopped
huh stop stare
current objective survive hell yeah
and maybe find some useful stuff like
iron
apparently my pronunciation of iron is
wrong
someone has mentioned that
really bgm please you don't
don't tell me you're not hearing the btm
again
you'll hear it oh yeah you better hear
it
how boring would it be without a museum
now where the hell is that water and
that lava
and get back to the iron topic what are
you how are you supposed to
pronounce it then
it stopped again
i'm really bad at finding things i yearn
iron i say iron oh what oh
okay so i say iron and it's supposed to
be iron
that sounds stupid i yearn
iron that sounds so stupid
it's iron guys you guys are wrong it's
iron
it's iron
my axe is almost dead now
oh yay wow
my pickaxe
am i even gonna be able to get back oh
wait i almost jumped into the lava oh my
god
come to me
i wanna oh damn it
oh yeah
wow
be careful
nice
oh
[Music]
what do we have here
nothing
nothing wow
a lava and a waterfall
the lava fall and the waterfall
nice
thing i like the sound
look it broke
we're done is there anything i gotta
remember here
oh there's a lot to see oh my god look
at that i want to come back here
with where's my
where did i come from did i come i came
from here right no maybe not oh [\h__\h]
why did i did i come from here
yeah yeah yeah yeah oh yeah
hope we find back here
[Music]
wow why did i dig like that eh
i'll never i'll never find this place
again
maybe i will maybe i will i'll try my
best
no we'll find it we'll find it we'll
find it just gotta follow the lead
did i come from here
my goal
no no no no
this is where i just came from
right this is where i
just came from
this this is where i just came from
so where did i come from before
where am i
i don't have anything oh wait oh
i do have one more pickaxe
okay let's get out there first though
because we don't want to die again
[Music]
we don't want to lose our stuff again we
want to keep it safe
but this is weird oh because here's the
lava
how did i
i obviously didn't cross that lava
out here oh my god
i almost missed that that that's
how really i ever gonna find that spot
again
remember this spot there's a pool here
and then you go like here okay
okay left or right
be quiet oh
i found it i found it
hi
[Music]
oh my god this is such a maze what did i
do
hello i'm outside
wow it's so bright and beautiful outside
why would i want to
ever go into a cave like that again
oh my wheat
maybe that sounded wrong
[Music]
now plant it again
going well lots of bread hooray
nice
okay what did we come here for can i
make this here
oh wait wait is this how it works
is this how it works
am i getting my first golden bar
wow
one more one more
okay have fun there
huh okay what else what do we want to do
make some pickaxes about we need the
iron for that
huh i think though
maybe we'll leave it at that for today
maybe
[Music]
no now i want to eat something
yeah i'm a bit in pain
generally
well oh today's tuesday
so wednesday and thursday
wins oh wait no wait but today is
tuesday yeah yeah
yeah wednesday thursday
all right uh
yeah let me close the door
and just leave this here for a while
anyway can you keep on no okay
well well well
so i think we're gonna do a super chat
reading
it's really lonely to not have to chat
there
you all are being so so good i wanna
show the chat
um oh wow and
one a second i will get the super chat
checked
and
then we can have some chill super chat
time
[Music]
instead
but i hope everyone enjoyed the
minecraft
stream today i feel like i didn't get
anything done
but i don't know maybe that's just me
okay
how do i
[Music]
um
sorry one second please my friends
[Music]
so
this takes so much time
sorry please give me a minute
please give me a minute
[Music]
m
okay i think i got to the point where it
started
and now yo
[Music]
copy paste
thank you guys for waiting
okay get the link
okay i have
a lot giving it
to the managers waiting for
my check
[Music]
at the place of the chat for the time
being that's actually a good idea
i don't know how long it's gonna be
because like for everyone who missed the
beginning we're not um
we've been asked to not show the chat at
the moment
for a while i don't know how long it's
gonna be
but hey i bought some new cough drops
let's get one before we start the super
chat rating
yeah i need to bgm up was it too quiet
please don't tell me it was too quiet
the whole time again
well
what was it going to say oh yeah the fan
art thing i'm gonna
actually recently i'm not complaining or
anything but i i haven't been getting so
much fan art
i'm not complaining but it's not much
i'm not complaining but i'm crying
so i don't even have that much to show
you
i'm checking the hashtags every day
but it's not that much
[Music]
foreign
but i appreciate every every little fan
art that i see i appreciate it very much
thank you for taking your time and i'll
check out how to
um do like a slideshow or something on
stream i wonder how that works
hmm
no art can match my beauty that's that's
not true
it but everything i see on every fan out
that i see on reddit i basically
mostly i've already seen it on twitter
already
yeah ame has like a slideshow right i'm
gonna ask her or cal
kelly also shows the fan art but is it a
slideshow i think they both do something
like a slideshow
um are they on it
[Music]
hello
is this twitter 2.0
no reddit at least is like
no it's definitely different
oh yeah i do have a lot of fan art with
my wife
there's like so much so
much better maybe like 50 percent of
kiana fan art is
chiara with cali
which is also really cute i every time i
see something like that
it's so adorable it's so adorable
i love how you guys are shipping us i
ship us to buffing cali
is not shipping us
i don't know why she doesn't
i don't get it she should be shipping us
nobody i see how she's liking
those pictures and retweeting those she
definitely
seems to enjoy it she likes to see those
pictures
[Music]
foreign
hmm yeah she ships it in a tunzen way
it's so cute though it's so so cute but
i'm like surprised because up until now
i've never seen maybe it exists and i
just haven't seen it but i never saw
a fan art before where me and callie
kiss
and i feel like that would be something
that already has been done
but i haven't seen anything like that
before
have you tried cliche ways to make cali
fall for you
like what writing a poem maybe i should
read her pull him but i kind of i
already requelled her with a really
romantic rickles song
so i did already low-key request
an artist like i i kind of hinted
at him like like an artist that
one of those i just who kept on drawing
me and calling
and i i replied maybe you guys saw it i
replied
um um could you maybe possibly
draw me and callie kissing and he's like
oh oh oh okay
oh i'm on it
[Music]
i didn't want to like force it onto him
but i feel like because
that person he already drew so many
fan outs of me and callie i felt like if
any
anyone he was gonna do it
i'm sure he wanted to do it but maybe he
just felt like
i would think it's inappropriate or
something but i want to see it
hmm i want to see
a fat night of me and callie kissing
you just need my consent you don't need
callie's concept
because it's just for me she's fighting
with it
i mean anything beyond kissing
maybe i don't want to see that because
that's between me and callie
i i'm not sure if i want to see anything
more than kissing
illustrated
i mean yeah maybe some cuddling yeah but
yeah you know nothing like
nothing too much you know
that's between me and kelly i don't want
you guys to see our private moments
our sensitive moments
looking
foreign
i wonder if there's any artists in the
chat right now
that's a really good really good noodle
really good um
cough drop
oh we needed we needed like we need a
name
for our i was thinking of that you know
how you give couples
famous couples a name like brangelina
but i couldn't think of anything that
sounds good with me and cali
caliara i don't know that sounds like
carbonara
that sounds like some spaghetti sauce
chiariope
[Music]
ashes and dust well i think it should be
a combination of the
tony moody tony moly
tony moly i think i i saw something
similar to
that name before what was it before
tony murray is funny but my name isn't
even in there
tony mori my name is not in there
you
that's maybe too short
[Music]
i guess that works because yeah that's
not that doesn't even sound
weird maybe our official shipping name
could be takamori
thanks
[Music]
callie doesn't know about it but yeah
she doesn't need to
taka
bye
mori
[Music]
okay now here we go
i will start reading the super chats
[Music]
well maybe we can fill the space with
this too
[Music]
here's hope here's hoping nothing goes
wrong this time
to help getting a new capture card
congrats on 250k
thank you yay
i'm i'm really glad we reached it
but this is not where it ends
we keep on going k f b k
maybe we need a kfp emoji
wait let me actually
actually one second
okay wait wait wait wait wait wait let
me let me do something
oh wait that's from the first one oh god
damn it
no i already read those that's from
yesterday
there we are
may you get some experience in minecraft
before the faded day you collab
alongside tekora until then
you might not remember but a week ago i
said you are not only my favorite
feature about
quickly becoming one of my favorite
creators on youtube sadly i have to
retract this channel because instead you
have become the clear number one wait
thank you thank you
[Music]
would have to agree with that statement
clear number one in my heart as a
content creator now what
looking forward to the future tanto keep
being great i love you
brandon wilson thank you i wish i could
be a phoenix too funny thing though
someone once told me my spirit bird was
a dove
what do you think about doves i like
dubs
dubs are super cute
i wish i could give them a home or
something
sorry i'm still eating my mine cough
drop
no no
and doves are yeah what dubs are not
pigeons
i thought tops are pigeons
and work today was a disaster but i
always knew i have
kiara's dream to fall back on and make
me happy again before i head to bed
oh and someone requested a kiss super
chat so here's our offering
no no
no no no no no
only red super chats get kisses
i'm sorry i can't give everyone a kiss
no pudding
south black berndan
thank you dave thank you good morning
hope you have a wonderful week
thank you you too mate
i mate is that that canadian
hey mate thank you
lucio scyther
[Music]
goodbye tissue box bye bye
i have two pointer thank you soon
why can't broken get a too hot
because like originally i did that
because they
didn't write anything in their stupid
super chats
and then i felt bad because i can't like
really react to them
if they don't write anything because
what am i supposed to say besides thank
you soon
so then i gave them a kiss oh and but
i'll meet you ladies you later see this
is a case of
short super chat where i can't say
anything
so i'll give you a kiss instead
dirt bag phoenix thank you
thanks
[Music]
on 250 000 subscribers never forget that
we love you
for good and bad streams because of your
wonderful personality you make our lives
brighter by being you
thank you thank you
i i am ashley at the moment i'm quite
happy
because of you guys i am you guys know
that i like to look at
everyone's opinions and you know the
internet
but recently i i'm actually managing
to only look at the good sides to not
look at the bad sides i haven't checked
out one of those bad sides
for uh a while now
so i'm mentally feeling much better
just ignore the bad side i mean i think
it will always be
in the back of my mind like oh i wonder
what [\h__\h] they're writing
about me today but
just gotta stay on the good side and
then everything around me is happy and
wonderful
and positive
you just ignore everything else
good vibes only yay
[Music]
the golden sword you found isn't really
that strong what
yeah it's gone now it's gone
zombie sausage
[Music]
on camera captain pepper jackson
packaging while you are crouching you
want fall off latches
oh yeah i know that i know the the
crouching when you like
yeah yeah i know what it's useful for
but i didn't use it yet huh
i'll try to use it next time when i when
i need it
tyler morgan thank you and v gamer for
11.
joshua wait bottom left emote when how
am i supposed to do that
how am i supposed to make a bottom left
emoji
what are you what what is that going to
look like
[Music]
ah the arrow
well you already got an arrow like that
oh think about it joshua flores thank
you
and you can shield creeper blasts and
block skeleton arrows but it will take
up the durability of the shield you also
need a iron
pickaxe for the gold block okie dokie
thank you
one trick i used to make a really tall
spiral staircase
and and make one in each cardinal
direction to make a great search could
you
could that help here i wonder what
you're talking about
i wonder where what
a tall spiral staircase
make one in each cardinal direction
to make a great search i don't know what
you're talking about
do you mean a big tower well why would i
need another tower
ghost 200x thank you general piccolin
oh wait yeah more people are telling me
to build towers in this super chat
channel from the very beginning to
the present and to the future you bring
joy and energy to our lives
we will always continue to support and
love you for who you are
wait let's actually you know what
oh need something else now
um
my second bgm
we'll always continue to support and
love you for who you are the light of
the phoenix is your channel glory to the
kfb viva la kirara
carricky yeah you're always so
motivating
i think you really deserve the title of
the general
sk danke shin gum blade knight thank you
thank you spec
[Music]
i know you had a lovely voice but with
the new mic it's very very
apparent chin up kiara one step forward
at a time thank you
and when i get closer to the microphone
i'm closer i think
senpai thank you thank you
thanks for the super chat
don't worry you don't need to say sorry
for not being able to donate more
papaya
[Music]
sorry i'm too poor to do a red super
chat but i did become a member so i hope
that makes up for it but don't worry
about it
but thank you for your support thank you
for the industries
industries thank you oh my god that's
the big one
i heard someone needs a new mic stand
cycle of you getting down on yourself
though other weak new jobs can be scary
but whole life has a way of picking the
most amazing talent
that is true they saw something in you
that maybe the community or even you
haven't discovered yet
don't make me cry never doubt yourself
ps i challenge the canadians time to
bully her with kindness
thank you so so so so so so much i will
definitely buy a new mic sand because
this one just seems to be too weak i
don't know
i tried to make uh to to um
you know there's some some things
on the side to make it more loose
or tighten it and i think i tightened it
as much as i can
but the microphone seems too heavy for
the mic
arm seems kind of weird
yeah i tightened everything
oh well well thank you red song
thank you i love you
but yeah as i just said um recently i
i've been feeling quite alright i i just
gotta stay away from
places that make me feel bad about
myself
although sometimes it's also just myself
sometimes it's just myself but yeah
yeah but you're right um
definitely there must be a reason why
they chose me and uh
i mean i do think that i have i do think
that i have what it takes i do think so
hmm but yeah
it's just it's just um when you're in a
position like this you often just
start to doubt yourself even if
uh others think there would be no need
for it but you just can't help it you
know
just can't help it but i'm all right now
i'm not canadian rich but i'll try i've
always wanted
i already answered that one why do
people think that canadians are so rich
though
the most i can give but this torts this
is always a new computer
don't be afraid of asking the community
for help with one no no no no no no
but like i mentioned in the previous
stream i do have a better pc and i don't
think
the current one that it's it's rented
the one that i use now
but i don't think that um
i need to upgrade it because i have a
better pc somewhere else which i will
eventually get back
so yeah but for now this pc seems good
enough for streaming
[Music]
yes my life is worth it you have a stone
pickaxe what
what is your name stone pickaxe
thank you thank you
sorry i can't send more but i just want
to say you're my favorite member and you
are so talented and cute so please just
know we all love you
thank you you're so sweet i love you
i love you omni thank you
don't think i'm done i'm sorry i led to
your death
is that where i got um
killed by the sand above me suffocated
to death
it's okay stone pickaxe it's not your
fault
captain papa jackson cushion became my
free eleven thank you
sure paper thank you for luck thank
[Music]
yeah torches could be good too for
making a a mark
blue phoenix thank you thank you
students
for
japanese bros
and sisters
oh you don't know magical
[Music]
i'm so so surprised that so many people
just watch the stream even if they don't
understand it
[Music]
okay
oh the popcorn chicken no i didn't see
any popcorn chicken
around my area yet but once i find it
i'll try it
seth also i don't go outside that much
recently
sapphire kitten thank you kiara hope
you're doing well today yeah
your streams are always a highlight of
my day and cheer me up hope you're
having as much fun
streaming as i am watching vivalaki yaga
get yourself something good to eat
thank you
i need something good to eat today
i wonder what i should get maybe some
pineapple pizza
okay
oh ramen would be good oh yeah i want
some good ramen
but there's no no good ramen place close
to me
fernando thank you
[Music]
if you do not eat i'm going to send you
all of the money i have in my bank
account i don't have a job either so
please eat
it's all right it's not like i don't
have the money to eat yesterday i was
just um too lazy
to get food because it was like it was
like really late
and i was wearing my pajamas
and i i was already pretty tired so i
didn't want to go
outside to the convenience store to get
food i was just too lazy so i ate some
chocolate and went to sleep that's
all
yeah sometimes i do
go to the convenience store like it's
two in the night or even three in the
night
sometimes i do but yesterday i just
wanted to chill
and i had nothing in my fridge anymore i
mean actually
actually i did have something in the
fridge
i had something in the freezer but i was
also too lazy to make that
because i would have to wash my frying
pan
so i decided to just go to bed hungry
get a dishwasher that's not so easy in
the kind of apartment where i live in i
don't
even think it's possible there's no
space for a dishwasher and
uh i don't know no no no i'm not gonna
get a dishwasher
i'm moving again soon and then later
i'll be moving again soon
i'm i'm moving a lot uh generally
my hobby is moving my hobby is moving so
it's not a good idea to buy such things
[Music]
papa telling me to eat food
that's such a such a papa thing so
such a thing that the papa would say
[Music]
papa is worried about me
hmm
[Music]
ariel smith found 71
blizzard
joshua v train by train
between just want to let you know you're
doing wonderfully and i hope you're
enjoying everyone's favorite vlog game
i am enjoying it it's quite frustrating
too but
i gotta get get used to the fact that
losing everything is quite uh
common on minecraft
so i gotta get used to that but just to
me it's like very shocking
it's very shocking for me to lose
everything
thank you not if you get good okay i
gotta get better then
pairing it funny
face palm i still love your best friend
and why did i i don't remember what is
your facebook
thank you
that's efficient brain you humans can't
comprehend with your enormously wasteful
oversized braids
exactly i mean
you gotta look at my huge eyes they
already take up
a lot of the space in my head
so of course my brain has to be a bit
smaller
yeah i mainly like okay papa because of
the way kiara says his name
what why i say it normally
yeah but just because my brain is small
it doesn't mean that it's
bad
[Music]
taking it before the super chat reading
has actually really helped a lot
[Music]
feels much better than usual i think
i'll need it every time though i don't
know why super chat
reading is so exhausting for my fruit
but
it's good now with the with the cough
drop
actually that really worked well
[Music]
apparently
and
[Music]
thank you for your ideas i'm surprised
you guys needed me to hint that
on you i'm really surprised that there
is no banner
of me and callie kissing yet
takamoti otp takamori otp
do you enjoy the harvest moon story of
susan's rune factory games
asking me as if i'd ever have played one
of those
i'm sorry to disappoint you i have not
played that before
but again we have more opportunities to
play those
in the future
luka umbria thank you
[Music]
you can change your name now to takamori
otp
blow cali a kiss
kelly i love you
i love you i love you
ball of positivity that i know for a
fact you're changing some people's lives
i'm not one of those people oh really
that are in dark places so i want to
dedicate the superchat
to those that love you about can't super
chat
that's so sweet why are there such sweet
people like that
don't thank you and me but them instead
thank you to everyone who cannot super
chat me
you seem like the kind of person who
would um
[Music]
give uh like some money to
someone who's like on the street asking
for food
a good person very good person
thank you no nine thank you shin your
streams are so much fun thank you for
all your hard work this super chat made
in honor of broke gang and underpaid kfp
employees
hell yeah i mean all of the kfp
employees are not underpaid but
negative paid
all of the kfp employees are paying me
to be able to work for me so yeah we
kind of have a weird system it's very
original but it will lead us to success
i'm sure
[Music]
once i get my page i gotta get my
revenge until then viva la chiara yay
thank you i recommend putting a can you
really do that i saw that in the chat
like people telling me to put the bucket
on my head can you really do that
wait does it like get dark and you can't
see anything anymore
is is that what happens
that would be fun no
i'm just meaning oh
and that would be a fun few feature
jovan hanson thank you and thanks for
providing us with one stream school
salesman
chris house bean cruise it's rick
you could end world hunger and somebody
would starve themselves in spite
you're doing great wait wawa
i don't understand i don't understand
you could end the world i could end
world hunger and somebody would starve
themselves
i don't get it
here's another one for everyone that
can't afford to and would like to convey
their appreciation and love for you
have confidence and believe in yourself
or at least believe in us that believe
in you
yay thank you dan kishan
you guys are so sweet
love me some chicken this is a short
message
so you get a kiss
[Music]
thank you for your support i really
really really appreciate it
you finally joined your membership
welcome thank you
thank you thank you you have what it
takes when you stream it's always
when you stream it's always joy when
you're happy we're happy
when you're sad we are sad that's not
good that shows that your community
that the community enjoys you you just
being here is all what we need
i know it sounds cheesy but it's true
true for the boys in the discord and
chat
forcing me to give you kisses huh
[Music]
just wanted to let you know how much you
brighten my day i struggle every day but
i always look forward to your streams
thank you thank you and i appreciate
your support
pector lin thank you shane thank you
andy thank you when's the next karaoke
stream they're my favorite
maybe next week not this week i think
i'm too busy this week and i think
probably
if i do karaoke streams every week i
mean i would enjoy it but you guys would
probably get
sick of it and also there's um
there's so many songs i want to sing but
not all of them are on our
copyright list not so i can't even sing
all of them
and i feel like a lot of songs would be
repeating itself so i maybe shouldn't do
it every week
it's my favorite
but not every week
every second week i would say maybe
i i personally would do it any time but
i just feel like it's too much then
an archive oh yeah yeah we gotta do that
oh maybe we can do one of those this
week
um for membership only
[Music]
i don't know what's
if i do it membership only i guess i
could
keep the archive and then just not have
it monetized i guess something like that
i'll check weeaboo andy duncan lord
pinball thank you
i love everyone in the whole ibm you
probably have the most house on fanbase
huh really that kind of support doesn't
just happen it's a credit to all your
efforts so far
thank you everyone is really so sweet
like all the love is
oh making me feel so loved
after brit butler dancer never failed to
put a silly grind on my face thank you
for being a ray of sunshine
well i am a phoenix after all the bird
of the sun
all the time don't be discouraged when
the when things don't go well we're
always behind to support you
thank you
[Music]
i think that's it
and that's it thank you everyone
captain pepper jacks thank you sing
every week
[Music]
why am i so tired why i have no energy
today
last minute gang wow
thank you everyone for coming today
i hope you had fun did you have fun
you better have had some fun pinto flat
tank
[Music]
you did good eggs i like how
in the end for the super chat readings
almost everyone who's here is a member
the members stay until the end and also
some non-members thank you everyone
thank you to everyone and i totally
understand if you can join the
membership that's totally fine don't
feel
don't feel like you need to i'll try my
best to give you
good content no matter if you remember
or not
again captain pepper jack's thank you
sir
i can't wait for you all to hatch and
become big chickens and then become
chicken legs oh
takamori otp you changed your name yay
thank you
all right that's it guys thanks everyone
and tomorrow
uh i'll think about what we do tomorrow
and yeah i love you
and in the end together in german we say
thanks sweet gamer for your love and
dancing
[Music]
bye bye
food
and take a bath i'm gonna take a bath
over a high toka
[Music]
you know what i noticed guys because of
obs because i'm actually like singing
on time to that music always but because
of obs there's some delay so i noticed
when i watched the archive that the
humming is always delayed and not with
the
actual ribbon it's not like i can't sing
along the rhythm okay don't get me wrong
there's just some lag actually let me
fix that maybe i can fix it right now
[Music]
still delay
after
anyway bye bye
[Music]
hey