e
e e
[Music]
oh
he oh
[Music]
fore
welcome everyone to the 31st episode of
Hol presented to you by your host
takanashi Kiana it's the first time
we're turning the tables and
interviewing e and members the number
one detective of H live is leaving
behind a huge Legacy so let's learn all
about it and welcome Amelia Watson
[Music]
kiky hello hello oh my God that went
relatively smoothly I think I hope hope
you heard all of that the way I intended
it to be heard
K yeah yeah wait wait wait she'll be
she'll be there soon she's almost there
KY uh it's been a while since the last H
talk and we're so back and this time
we're you know changing it up this is
the first H talk episode where we are
doing it the other way around usually I
translate Japanese members answers into
English life at the spot uh so that
Japanese viewers can kind of get an idea
no that English speaking viewers can
kind of get an idea over the Japanese
members you know if you don't know them
too much but this time we're doing it
the other way around uh English view
yeah I guess we did Advent we did do
Advent okay um but you know solo
interview this is you know different so
H We'll be asking questions in English
but I will be trying translating a
little bit in between for the Japanese
viewers they may be sleeping now but
they might watch the vaud you never
know where are you where are
you okay okay see there's some people
awake at 5 a.m. then what all all the
things I'm doing and saying are you know
okay it's going to be forgiven right so
please excuse my translations in
between uh so yeah whole talk is a live
talk show with the purpose of
interviewing and live translating mainly
Japanese whole life talents but from now
on also English talents to bring this
much wholesome knowledge to oversea
viewers or Japanese viewers as possible
brought to you by your host
that was the whole introduction okay
[Music]
now
K
yay Watson oh yeah con Watson would you
mind doing your your proper introduction
ction please okay hello everybody I'm
Amilia Watson from H live English a
number one detective yeah and
service yeah oh that was it you ended so
fast oh s did you do your wink I didn't
see yeah I did I did do it
again a
cute here we go a cute
angle so than you thank you are you
excited to be on Holo
talk yeah yeah I think it's really
interesting too because you know I I I
helped you out a little bit with
remember when you first set it up and
long time yeah so now I'm finally here
what did you do thank you for having
first time what did you what oh uh I
made the intro ah you're right oh my
God that the old intro thank you so much
well no no you still use some of it like
the phoenix flying to the desk and
exping we just placed a lot of like uh
it's it's hard to notice but there's
like in the new version the current
version there's H life members hidden
across the sceneries but yeah couldn't
take out the phoenix flying in there
that was
iconic see like I'm me that's not the
only way you've been helping me you know
like remember when you were like sending
me vectors all the
time yeah yeah yeah that's true I mean I
still would be but I think you up
signing up for that on your own right I
kind of did but then also I kind of gave
up on it because when I downloaded the
vectors on my own I still didn't really
understand how to turn the parts that I
want into pngs yes you have to yeah
convert
it it was just too complicated for me
but I just gave up on it oh I'm a tech
support yeah now you have a lot of
dedicated kfp that can help you so yeah
yeah yeah I make get to work whenever I
can so all right we're going to be
asking you a lot of questions today and
we're going to watch some clips and
stuff it's going to be a fun time um so
let's get into it hey now because we're
doing it the other way around the
questions on the screen will be Japanese
guys but I'll be reading them out in
English so don't worry about it uh okay
so well first question is a pretty
simple one what have you been up to
recently
oh uh recently I've just been kind of
preparing for all of this I guess and
you know still trying to have fun and
play games and read and I've been
walking my dogs a lot reading what have
you been
reading uh some fantasy books and stuff
can I know which one oh I don't I don't
remember the title I don't have it right
now but you don't it couldn't have been
too good if you don't remember the title
I didn't I it's the same thing with
music like like I I'll know the this the
lyrics but then I forget the song title
or like the artist I see okay oh that's
fine okay so uh
well I'll keep it I'll keep the
translations kind of short to not
disrupt too much so okay can I go uh on
on on walk your dogos I want to walk B
oh yeah yeah that' be good actually my
uh smaller dog Mickey she's been uh
obsessed with bugs lately like on the
floor so she gets like some weird uh joy
out of seeing the bug squirm around so
she won't listen to me I'm like
he no she just like sniffs them my cats
attack bugs on the ground that's that's
good yeah there's some bugs they're
Predators yeah yeah their predators are
cats it's like their main yeah HT them
uh that yesterday my dog was smelling um
a bug that had like spiky stuff on it
and it touched her nose and she was like
sneezing but she's fine yeah was it a
caterpillar um I think well it just had
something spiky I didn't take a close
look I was like hey what are you doing
but she yeah she didn't get um stung or
anything better to stay away uh
it feels weird to translate to Japanese
so weird so unusual normally I translate
to
English it's good it's good yeah H
speaking of this is not anywhere in the
questions but like um I did want to kind
of touch upon your journey of uh
learning Japanese cuz at the beginning
what words did you know like Kon maybe
or so uh I knew like very simple words
like thank you
sorry
Dy stuff from watching anime do you
think you improved cuz I think you did
yeah I I I don't have good speaking
skills well I think I have the same
problem in English where I don't know
what to say a lot of the time so while
learning Japanese I also had no idea
what to say uh but I I feel like I'm
really good at understanding and picking
up um audio cues and and like specific
words that help gain like context for
what might be people might be talking
about yeah I that's like when a few
times we were together um you would keep
trying to translate for me but then I
would already start doing what like
staff or somebody was asking I could
understand but I I don't I can't
translate it like you I just kind of
have a feeling for it oh yeah that makes
sense though I'm I'm
[Music]
no yes yes yes all right let's move to
the next question I'm interested in this
one too I don't know if I know the
answer uh how did you discover H life
and why did you decide to
join ah yeah I I think it's pretty
similar for a lot of people where on
Twitter there were some trending clips
of different talents from Hollow live
and then it happened that just a few
months after those clips were trending
there was also um auditions open that I
also found on Twitter so or X I guess um
um and yeah I just decided to join
because it's like well this seems like a
lot of fun I don't really have that many
people to play with especially cute
girls like that was definitely something
I was missing in my life more of that so
um that's also the reason why I really
wanted um you know play games with
people and have a fun time and you know
I really like Japanese stuff too because
kind of a you know weeb nerd
otaku so it touches upon that too a
little bit awesome so when you were
watching those clips do you remember
like which whole life members Clips they
were uh moo Senpai Coco Senpai and also
soda Senpai soda Senai oh yeah and what
else I think there's probably more too
but I remember right now
yeah the the big S thank you s for
bringing Amma in thank you
M yes yes yes uh the next question is uh
interesting usually I ask it like the
other way around um but is there
something you wanted to convey to the
Japanese speaking viewers but couldn't
until now due to the language
barrier something I wanted to say to the
Japanese something I want to
[Music]
say uh I think it's probably pretty
common that they find that foreigners uh
have a of interest in Japanese culture
and stuff and I think I'm similar as
well uh I don't know there's something
that seems kind of magical in a way
about like some Japanese uh like
mythology and the Aesthetics of a lot of
um like Japanese art and stuff like that
so I really appreciate that um
especially visiting Japan I think it was
really cool to see it in person cuz it's
different seeing it online versus seeing
it in person and yeah I'm really
grateful I got to do that and also I
think it's really cool cuz this
something people talk about in Japan is
I really like it sounds weird but I
really like lining up behind everybody
else like kind of following the queue in
Japan whether it's for it's for like
getting off the train or going up this
the escalator or something like I feel
so integrated into society oh that's
that's funny I never heard someone say
that
before but it's so organized right yeah
I love that too because cuz like
probably the same in most countries like
people don't line up on the side to
enter the train and they don't they they
don't stand on the side to let people go
out hell no why would they yeah anytime
I take public transportation out I just
think about ah it's in Japan it's not
like
this I see I see maybe maybe people can
learn from that culture please stand on
the side I honestly do like in Austria I
will I learned from Japan so I just
stand on the side and wait and I think
people appreciate it too now yeah we
take the first step for
Change Change yeah
[Music]
okay okay okay all right let's go to the
next
question are you
ready we're getting deeper and deeper
into it so um what is your what was your
favorite kind of stream to do like game
streams or FPS which kind of gaming or k
like chitchat or collaborations or VR
projects what was your favorite oh
favorite uh probably just uh regular
gaming streams I
but I have a very short attention span
so I end up uh you know I play game and
then I'm like ah I want to play another
game kind of but but then also I don't
know it's kind of hard to pick cuz I
really like doing karaoke and Zan
streams always turn out really fun and
then yeah collabs are like oneof a kind
like memorable streams that happen like
I can remember every single collab and
yeah you can remember every single one
yeah I think think so
H well how how would you do that that's
so so
many I respect
easy okay what did you do uh uh on this
day two years ago who did you collab
with if you collab with someone I
probably okay I don't know what that
exactly I just remember you know the the
the fun that we had
yeah no I'm sure you do you you got good
memories for sure uh
[Music]
so uh okay so we you brought up that you
also like kadal streams but your
favorite is um gaming streams now yeah I
would say that your fans's favorite kind
of stream a lot of them would maybe say
k so regarding that because I think you
had quite the journey how did you feel
about singing in front of lots of people
in the beginning and will you continue
your singing Journey everybody's so
proud of you oh oh thank you thank you
well I think that uh sorry my I don't
know my dogs are running around right
now okay we love
that
um they distracted me I forgot what I
was going to
say uh yeah KS oh yeah I think that uh
teammates I like locked them in a room
and I strapped them down and then made
them listen to my karaoke to the point
where now they're like yes please
another one another karaoke and uh so
that's good and then yeah at the
beginning I was of course really nervous
cuz I never really sang in front of
people um and yeah I do plan to keep
singing cuz I like doing it a lot and
yeah that's pretty much it okay okay uh
wait camera oh my God uh she say
my oh my God my USB is so annoy oh my
why man you don't hear it can you do
tech support it's like every two seconds
it's doing B just just like push in
every single USB that you have it
there's nothing to push they're all
pushed in I'm not even doing anything
right now uh maybe it's an internal
problem with your USB port needs to be
replac I'm scared Hug
Me Maybe one of the little the little
connectors are loose on your motherboard
um oh my it won't
stop what did I do what did I do what
did I do hey let me disconnect my
keyboard does that do something nope um
uh oh my God oh my God to I'm entertain
them this is worrying me I don't want a
blue screen what's up chat how is it
going what are you guys doing did you
eat breakfast yet well I guess for some
people it's kind of
early is that a
word yeah uh it's correct it's correct
Yahoo what the [\h__\h] oh fish sandwich
[Music]
oh I don't know what to do
uh it's 4:00 a.m. for you
early yeah lunchtime technically yeah it
is lunchtime or early dinner I
guess what
[Music]
the this is still I can't hear it can
chat hear it it's nonstop like every two
seconds bo bo oh yeah you can mute oh
yeah okay well I don't want to mute it
because then I don't know that it's
happening f
right click on the on the system you
know sound settings open the volume
mixer yeah okay and then mute system
sounds uh I don't know how fine that
really is but wait
uh wait where they here
yeah okay I muted them but if I suddenly
get a blue screen you know just sorry
just wait for me then in that case okay
no worries it's fine okay uh where where
were we
uh but we talked about your Kadoka
streams yeah is there like one go-to
Kadoka song that you
have uh one go to karaoke oh well yeah
there's everybody knows like kiss me
that's like the one people request the
most uh non something non the Richer uh
yes six n the Richer yeah I love that
song too yeah that was a really good one
you sing it so well
it's an
classic so cute thank
[Music]
you uh what's the title just kiss me
yeah kiss me six P non Rich no kiss
me please listen to sing it sometime
everybody from the arives I'm sure
there's Clips everywhere there's so many
there's so many versions that I've done
so
so many versions of of Amy singing the
same song Loop him Loop him forever if
you want I
guess
okay next
question
is oh H you also have a lot of nonv
tubing hobbies that I think make you so
endearing like your interest for
terrariums which I really want to make
terrariums too thanks to you um but
which one is your favorite out of the
ones you have made so far oh my favorite
I remember there was one I made for a
Valentine's Day stream where I I
commissioned like uh specific assets to
kind of build my own terrarium uh but a
virtual terrarium and yeah we did it
together it's like a stream activity and
it was really cool did you perhaps bring
it with you wait I think I have it right
here under the table here oh oh there it
is where did it come
from wow she's so prepared she brought
the terrarian liver here it is because
it's virtual yeah we can Si size it up
because it's virtual look how cute it is
k w it's so
cute let me explain in Japanese
it's so cute what's the theme of this
this one is
investigator uh got a little uh statue
in the middle and yeah it's just to you
know be relaxing little little terrarium
like a kind of a little time capsule if
you will oh he's so cute you should
create it in real life yeah that would
be good that would be good yeah but you
got a couple of real ones too how many
do you
have uh probably like at least between
10 and 20 yeah I don't know the exact
number can I keep this on my Holo talk
table forever oh yeah yeah I have a
bunch I have a bunch of these so I made
extra you can have one really yay it's
really nice decoration it like Blends
nicely I want to make it like this
size
versatile yeah W it'll be here
forever
I'm yeah I rarely update the whole talk
Studio to finally a little bit of a
little bit of an upgrade yeah something
new yeah I want to make a terrarium too
do you have any like advice for making
terrariums like anything that maybe
beginners mistake to avoid or
so um make sure you get clean soil that
uh well it's going to grow mold probably
oh uh even if it's not even if it's
clean yeah even if it's clean just don't
put it in real sunlight because if you
put it in like actual sunlight uh it
will get even more algae or it's not
mold it's just like algae that kind of
grows in a wet environment like a
terrarium so I would say just keep it
with like indoor lighting oh interesting
I'll keep that in
[Music]
mind seems logical but I need to hear it
thank
you okay and next
question is tell us about the creation
of small Amit which led to all of our
Smalls oh yeah I mean technically I I
feel like I can't really be credited for
the creation of small am because I was
not the artist behind small a obviously
was Wy and then from there seafoam boy
who who's uh you know has done a lot of
3D models for our events and stuff um
they were the one who made the 3D model
and I remember seeing a gift that they
posted on Twitter where it was like
small Amy running around inside of a
computer screen ah yeah H it it uh yeah
it was really cute so I just contacted
them randomly over Twitter and I was
like uh hey I was thinking maybe we
could use this model because we had
already had like a different small Alit
uh for VR oh so yeah oh but I guess yeah
I guess there's two small am because the
VR small Amy came before the regular
small Amy that we see today oh wait I
wonder did it look very different I'm
trying to
recall yeah it looked a little different
it like the the VR small was not as kind
of wide and Squishy it's like a more
kind of like a condensed skinny oh and
yeah that one we want them to be chubby
yeah that's cute it's cute but oh yeah
so I guess H was the first H was the
first 3D artist for a small VR yeah I
see I see very interesting some history
there that we might may have forgotten
[Music]
people have been asking uh and I don't
even know if you know the answer to this
but people have been asking what's going
to happen to small am who runs around at
the
Expo oh yeah actually I'm not sure
because I know that there was uh more
stuff kind of possibly being planned
with that so um yeah I don't know I do
hope that a small can continue to make
an appearance but no promises of course
I I I think everybody is hoping to see
that yeah yeah we can't we can't let her
lose her job she was enjoying it so much
but honestly I feel like um because what
you're doing is not a proper
graduation uh there's a higher chance of
her remaining and being able to keep her
job yeah I think so too right
[Music]
yeah I'm excited to see her again
because you know not only she would lose
her job but also her caretaker would
lose her
job I yeah I suppose so we don't want
that so you guys maybe you can assume in
the future inside of the small am at the
Expo maybe there's a real Amit hiding in
there yeah definitely don't tackle the
small Amit don't tle her don't rip her
head off don't do it please don't no
what am I saying there's no one inside
there uh yeah it's just small Amy
operating it like a Mech
yes okay okay uh we all love small am so
uh besides small arm there's also a lot
of other great Creations
um I kind of want an overview and I've
been sent something so let's move
over here
T yeah there is this
amerse this is a really extended version
of it I was going to say it's so there's
a lot of things in there I can't yeah we
will go through it now am you and me
okay and you have to explain to me like
almost everything uh okay I see I see
that like
Gosling right which is like not the
goling himself but like I didn't want
the movie but joy yeah and there's uh
small am but in our cute VR CH idle
outfits on the left yeah yeah that was
for um I think it was a birthday mini
live that I did yeah oh cute cute cute
because there is a low poy like taller
version of it too what what is that am
on top
of uh the buff
kitchen oh the one that's really messy
up or what happened to her wait cuz
there's two really messed up explain
both of them uh the pixelated one I
think that one from a stream where I was
using like a capture card with my laptop
and or or no no no you know how
sometimes if we use like VD o ninja or
something yeah uh it'll get like some
weird uh bit rate stuff that happens I
think that's from that oh no yeah and
then the other uh small that has long
legs that one is from
streamware I was experimenting with
filters oh I see guys I know the BM is
gone over here it's don't don't mind it
it will come
back we see an elephant am I think yes
interesting what's the I like that one
what what is that feet arm in the
top um that was when we got the ability
to attach like props to ourselves Ah
that's the first thing you did
yeah well I was just I was just doodling
on Small's head trying to figure out
like what would look good here and I
just ended up drawing a foot I love the
noes
though is so good actually right next to
it on the left side did you only end up
using that once or more often because
the first time you used it I think was
with me yeah yeah um it's because yeah
we it's cuz we were hanging out in the
summer I think and I wanted it to be
like oh we're going on a camping trip
and so I think we each had sleeping bags
um you you had one too didn't you I
thought orange one I think so yeah yeah
sorry I actually messed up everything I
moved so many layers at once damn it
it's okay it's just a bit messed up now
um yeah that was so cute because we did
we did a little off collapse stream kind
of spontaneously cuz you came to my you
came to my hotel
room and stayed over
spontaneously yeah well I said I could
sleep on the floor because uh yeah I got
there really late so I was like shoot am
I just going to get I already have yeah
I don't know no why do that I don't know
it all worked out it was comfy and you
didn't bring a sleeping bag I guess but
yeah actually I remember on that trip I
lost a lot of stuff and I was like what
the heck why I why did I lose all my
stuff I think I lost my ID I lost like a
pin on my bag oh not the
ID yeah because I was traveling it was
also oh my God annoying that I lost my
ID okay let's see what else ah ah
um some fans pointed this out too in the
like questions uh you like at some point
you were into making some weird like
centipedes or so out of your
style yeah that was
funny yeah I don't know just just trying
to it's like Legos I kind of wanted to
treat you know the live 2D as uh Legos
and build different stuff
so oh I think that's my am version there
in the middle yes it looks like small am
in The
Sims I'm sorry I made you look like this
I don't even remember making you look
like that but you know it's realistic
yeah
no uh what else what stands out here oh
I love the the what what is that another
centipede with small on and there's a
spider
on yeah what uh oh some interesting dog
mupp that was for Halloween
one year of n VR chat yeah what there's
oh my god oh I love that one that's my
favorite one I think the laser one yeah
I was looking at that too just now
that's a good
asset what were you lasering with that
it was the chat I was lasering the chat
of course
no oh you wait you have a space suit but
you ended up getting a real space suit
yeah yeah that was at the end of an
outer World stream I think you look so
sad oh yeah that's yeah there's some
terrifying ones down here um the the
black one of the red eyes what what
happen
yeah um that was just me uh trying to
change the color on some stuff uh and I
I messed with the settings a little bit
too much and yeah I maybe it was around
Halloween time I think terrifying and
then we have a potato am I think and
next to it some weird what is that with
the teeth
oh a vampire am with
a Vampire was that also a Halloween
costume or so I think so yeah I love
this one in the middle because wasn't
that for like Oprah din or something
some game you played yeah yeah I was
trying to match the aesthetic of the
game when I saw that I was like how did
she do that in OBS I love the look you
gave yourself it it blended into I use
uh I use green screen kind of and I just
I green screen like my skin app out and
a green screen like my coat out and then
I put like a filter over that to change
the color over it oh so cool I see I see
Paladin announcer Amelia
Watson yeah there it is wait never
sent oh and amongus how does it feel to
be forever like inside of
amongus yeah it's really cool I'm glad
I'm glad I got to be part of that I have
your skin so I'll forever be able to
dress up as you oh thank you thank you
that's the times that we play Among Us
ah I like this one because that's from
our off collab in fre
studio right it was just a figurine what
do you call these figures
again H oh I actually don't know their
name I bet somebody in chat does it's
like those little guys that you pose for
art yeah yeah yeah is the B one the
mannequin mannequin a mannequin yeah did
you play Euro Truck with those at the
bottom oh yeah the the one that's not in
the truck that was for the Mario Kart
tournament that we did yeah yeah cute oh
my God the Super Chat
one uh yeah I uh I wanted to thank super
chats with like a super chat reading
stream but I didn't want to read the
Super Chat so I just threw something
instead yeah easy I will remember that
work around and maybe I will use it
myself cuz I'm still very much that's
the good content with
that what oh what is the one on the very
left like you in a bubble or
oh yeah that was me drowning no don't
drown why were you
drowning
um uh I'm not sure not sure there's no
explanation to some of these things guys
just accept it uh our best boy
Armando yeah we love him so much oh that
that the like orange red one she she's
kind of cute
uh yeah yeah oh yeah it's like a a spicy
hot
wing hot Cheeto yeah did you too many
Cheetos yeah I think so oh did you do a
bathtub stream at some point uh yeah
that was an asset that I had it was like
a really tiny bathtub that I put on my
desk and then a small was sitting in
there was that when like bathtub streams
became a thing like uh not bathtub um uh
the jacuzzi streams or whatever became a
thing on Twitch I think so yeah I was
like a little bit after it's kind of
like a parody I guess oh I see the many
arms casual um with feet on her head
neroid I my neroid is still not colored
what the hell ah
wait oh yeah when I did your cosplay
yeah cuz like early in the days um there
were not many kiata cosplayers yet so
there was like a group picture of four
out of five myth cosplayers and then you
you you edited yourself in cosplaying me
and those was so sweet of you so
thoughtful of you so
cute you know got to complete the set
yeah so true nowadays we have full sets
I'm happy about
that oh my God there's so many
interesting ones it really shows that
you like to have fun in your streams you
like to mess around and be
creative that one's so cute to with the
headset oh yeah yeah that's the official
headset right yeah that I have on my
outfit so cute I love the
Buns what else Bama is the best ah yeah
Bama is Fan Favorite
yeah might be my favorite too what's
your favorite but you said uh which one
was it the laser one out of these okay
but that's more like an assd I would say
right I like that that one that's that's
Mom that's waving it's like it's
actually a GI it's doing a dance from
Club Penguin that one that one's one of
my favorites
Joker scary
scary C
cake was that on your
birthday uh yes cute oh and there's
puppet Amy version number one that one's
good too that was for during your stream
yeah yeah yeah yeah you revealed it for
the first time
there you were cheering for me it was so
cute cuz I was like dancing right and
you were cheering ah yeah yeah that's
good one so cute oh wait that reminds me
somewhere I saw puppet on ah the puppet
that I did with the bucket teeth oh yeah
yeah yeah the teeth I'm so sorry I feel
like I just somehow kind of messed that
one like the teeth up because I love
your teeth they're like so charming and
I wanted to recreate that it was so
difficult oh was good it worked I like
it yeah nowadays the the the myth
puppets I've used them so much by now
that they're kind of falling apart oh no
you got to you got to put them in like a
glass display case and keep them keep
them pristine they were weren't they
yeah they they were on display
at last
year right which was so fun I love that
they gave us like a chance to show off
our Creations I was very proud of MRA
yeah that's so cool yeah at four Fest
maybe at yeah yeah oh what was it yeah
for Fest and then another different one
I also had something on display I think
snowman arm how how come I can still
recognize you in
that which one the
Snowman oh it's eyes it's small yeah
there's not much left of you but I I
don't even I have not never seen that
before I need to look it up that yeah
that's from a holiday
stream sorry yeah I wanted to ask about
that it's kind of similar to the bubble
where is it the
bubble where I lost it but what what
happened with slime
am slimee fell through the cracks and
like a grate on the floor on the street
is that how she became slime how did she
become slime
mama uh she got bit by like a sewer rat
or something that was covered in slime e
so she just went back home really it
sounds gross but
oh why did you do that did she give you
assets to become no I stole it from her
was it around yeah it was for collab it
was for
collab and then I gave her my hat oh
really did she wear it yeah yeah cute a
oh there's so many yeah look at this
forever there's did you find this on
Twitter uh I was asking uh the F oh ah
that one I was asking them to send me
like an overview of the am and this one
already existed because they made it for
you I think from anniversary or so what
what the hell is this another drawn
puppet sock puet oh yeah yeah yeah that
was for
thumbnail and then oh I like that small
Amit that's like a triangle triangle oh
that one yeah yeah that one's probably
my top top five or 10 she's in a power
stance cat am is so cute oh my
god oh
shoulder wa is that a reference to
Family
Guy maybe yeah maybe yeah it's like my
twin but they're just like a growth on
my shoulder he's so good did how did did
you cut it off or how did you get rid of
it yeah I sawed it off it was very
bloody just yeah just a little bit it's
more puss than
anything
you okay I think that's enough let's go
back sorry that took a while because
it's so interesting so many cursed and
lovely Charming
AMS which one's your favorite guys huh
which one there's too many to choose I
would say yeah there's a lot there's an
option for
everyone and all right all right next
next next next question back into the
groove okay and speaking of different
versions of am there's also been many
cute am outfits can you tell us about
the process of creating them with na'vi
Mama and is there anything you want to
say about her you can do that later
would you tell me about like did you
just let her do her thing or did you ask
her for specific things ever I think for
yeah pretty much all of the outfits I
was like uh here I have an idea for how
maybe this outfit could look and I gave
her a really terrible looking sketch and
then she made it into something so
beautiful that you couldn't even tell
that it came from what I made wait for
which one was
that uh the spacit one maybe it was for
the spacit
one and I think also the
kimono I really love the kimono I love
the colors in it and I love that you
it's just fascinated me that you came up
with this thing of having the the bag on
your head the fish bag I think it could
be credited to there's like an artist on
Twitter for uh the first casual outfit I
remember we were doing like a review of
the art people were making for the
silhouette ah and I think one of them
had a fish in a bag on the head and I
was like oh I like that oh because they
thought that the silhouette of you
wearing the Bubba hat yeah may have been
that genius whoever did that absolute
genius do you have a favorite out of
these
um probably the kimoo I use that one the
most oh yeah that one's cute I just
really like you know with the space suit
like no one else would think of that I
feel like no one else would ask for that
it's like so specific and unique and but
it's really versatile cuz you can use it
as like if you're racing or driving or
like an operator in a game I don't know
exactly oh you're genius I love it it's
so cute
round head
ball what bald no no ball ball oh okay
yeah I remember like uh when the spacit
was in the making I actually uh I was in
Korea and I was hanging out with Nai
mama in person and I was like we were
talking a little bit about you you know
and she told me she was barking on this
space suit for you and I was like what
she's getting a space suit that's so
funny
yeah also did you have anything to say
like a message to Nai
mama uh yeah I have so many things to
say to Nai mama and about Nai mama I
think she's so talented and everything
she draws is just like ah the cutest
thing ever you just see it and it kind
of makes your chest like a so cute and
uh I always look forward to seeing more
of her work and watch her grow as an
artist and I always be following her
and yeah I'm really grateful that I got
to have such an amazing I think
everybody's you know Halas and Papas are
really amazing but Abby mama just has
like this certain cute charm her art and
yeah I'm really grateful to uh you know
have represented that in a way bring it
to life even
more I haven't been translating I keep
on forgetting now let me
Translate for
[Music]
I have to than Nai Mama too because she
created you and your beautiful cute
teeth yeah thank you na mama the Amy
smile so cute Namy
Mama all right all right and now we have
seen so much of your cuteness uh one
thing that we also saw on the uh picture
that we looked at was like feet up am
right oh yeah it was somewhere there we
didn't touch upon it but let's touch
upon it now uh you also came up with a
lot of vtuber acid ideas such as legs up
on the table and other cool things uh
how does it feel to be a trans
Setter uh well I don't know cuz that was
a while ago so it's not like I really
feel like that anymore I guess but do
people still use like leg on TBL assets
and stuff maybe not but I I wonder like
there's still a lot of like assets being
made free assets like especially hand
assets right I wonder if there were many
before or if you kind of already
inspired that too
I'm not sure I do know that uh maybe it
was from a stream where it's probably
just some random Super Chat stream where
I was saying uh Hey artist if you're
interested I think it'd be really cool
if I had like a hand that I could attach
like this or they even went as far as to
make like a foot that came up where I
picked up my hat with my foot with my
toes
so um I think probably the legs up on
the table was inspired by like that art
like the art that the community has made
so it's kind of like this cool feedback
loop where you know we talk about
something then they make something and
it goes back and forth so it's really
nice actually like I saw you come up
with so many and I was always thinking H
I want to kind of come up with a post
myself too uh but I don't want to do
like exactly the same as yours but I
could never think of anything really
original brain
empty yeah uh
so for
[Music]
you know I also really liked I think
kind of out of that came that one asset
where gauda was like uh tummy down on a
couch with her legs in the back like
going back and forth yeah that one was
quite quite intricate and really cute
yeah I remember her using that I think
that is something that she kind of uh
you know came up with herself but maybe
inspired a little bit yeah I think
possibly surely she had her own idea but
I think it might have been
subconsciously at least inspired by
perhaps was there a favorite one you had
out of these
assets uh the laser one I guess yeah but
I didn't really use it that much was
that one you used a
lot uh I feel like there it's probably
the Hat one I was talking about where
like the foot is lifting the hat off my
head yes yes yes cute
FootHead okay H okay next question I
think um chat will enjoy a lot if
there's some teammates in here which I
assume teammates where you at
and I mean yes what's your favorite
thing about the
teammates uh favorite thing about
teammate and let's
see it seems like they get along really
well with each other and I feel like
that's probably the thing that I would
want most out of community cuz sometimes
there can be like some bad apples or so
but I think even if you treat them you
try to treat them like a normal person
and kind of still be nice to each other
um and welcoming that yeah that's that
is a sign of a good community so I
always see teammates talking about how
they met so many cool people whether
it's like at an event or just online
hanging out so I'm glad I'm glad I I I
hope that everybody has been able to be
a at least a little bit kind to each
other and also have a good
time yeah I'm finishing and also M no
problem investigators like the Gators
are very cute and I like how people will
take that and uh kind of make it like
their own mascot and make their own
version of themselves cuz I really like
the color green it's so cute there
they're so cute I love them so much oh
and you know uh technically Gators and
kfp are kind of related they're like
cousins oh okay reptiles and birds
pretty closely related oh I well I guess
you know we also once we dinosaurs or
something like that uh why we don't we
all stem from
dinosaurs kind of not I don't think so
okay maybe not
uh I guess no I'll take it back uh well
um okay let me translate uh
[Music]
yes she gets it
yes very cute I think like in K it's
kind of similar like I also always hear
them talking about um finding a really
great community so uh I feel like yeah
that's like generally in Holo Ian
everybody's so open and friendly and
they meet up at events and they're
hanging out they're going to eat
together or they're practicing chance
before the concerts and stuff so cute
yeah everybody is getting along so well
and everybody everybody's so T so right
yeah h it's nice to see good job guys
good job for good job keep it up a good
Community yeah keep it up so this there
well we're finally reaching our first
clip uh yeah I have um yeah I always
kind of prepare some clips um I have a
special clip
on okay this one will be a little bit
embarrassing for me because it's really
old and it's a collab between us two
that you you remember all your collabs
so Sur you remember this one too uh let
me get rid of the
amerse um yeah let's just watch it and
then I have something to say to you all
right it might not make sense at first
but all right here we go to the right
side of the clock um do you see like
something that you could move or
something like
that okay that made the
peee thing come out there are three
knobs on the clock and then on the very
top one there's four strikes which are
in the 10 11 12 and one spots as if the
circle of the top knob was 8 clock how
many do you have on the other two six on
the bottom which are in from 9 to 2 and
on the third one uh three as if it were
11 12
[Music]
okay okay okay uh sorry I kind of
I really uh don't want to interrupt
right now but I really need to go to an
aisle
meeting oh okay I'll be fast I'll be
fast I promise
sorry back sorry I'm back I'm trying to
figure out what each knob does my middle
one changes the the speed of the clock I
guess it only changes
the um this make sense the circle thing
in the middle that goes from left to
right uh it looks like it's just moving
normally on my side can you exactly tell
me at what Rhythm like just oh yeah
faster huh M
mhm
tick tick okay I got that one I think do
you have ways behind that like behind
the that clock that's
moving what behind the clock that we
just like the um adjusted the ribbon
what is that called pendulum Chimes oh
yeah Chimes okay um in what position are
it does look different on your screen
yeah our right one is higher than the
middle and the left one but the left one
is higher than the middle oh look I
think I got that one too
um we did we solve this of the knob um
makes the bird come out right but I have
three different sounds so when your bird
comes out what sound does it
[Music]
make okay okay okay
testing it open
y did it oh my God nice work oh my God I
like that one that one is nice is that
how we were supposed to do it yes yes
moated
uh
so yeah it's quite old um the reason
that I'm bringing this up is I have a
confession to make H at the time of this
collaboration which is like two or three
years ago probably three years I did not
know how to read clocks and I was just
incredibly stressed out by the situation
we were in and I thought oh my God in
order to to solve this riddle I probably
have to know how to read clocks so let
me quickly excuse myself on the toilet
and look up the solution there um but
the solution turned out to be something
where you don't have to read clocks but
I ended up just like reading the whole
thing and then I knew everything uh so I
cheated but also it's so embarrassing
I'm so
embarrassed you looked it up well yeah
cuz I thought like it would be so
embarrassing if I can't because like we
had two different povs we see different
things and so we have to communicate
what we see at all times and if I can't
even tell you what time it is because
that's probably the first thing we would
consider we would think like oh surely
it has something to do with the time on
the
clock but yeah um did you think it was
weird at the time no no I don't think so
I mean you know things happen that
happens quite often in collabs you know
where's got to go to idle meeting yeah
but was it not weird how I came back
seemingly so much SM
no I guess I didn't really yeah I didn't
I didn't think of that I didn't think
you would do that that's all yeah
normally I don't think I was that useful
throughout our collabs of this game
like yeah it was always quite hard to
find Solutions about our brains yeah
that's a tough puzzle game yeah it was
really difficult but yeah so by now I
want to clarify I learned how to read
the clock uh oh because of this um yeah
I think this one really stressed me out
I was like this can't happen to me again
on stream what if I really am confronted
with something in the game again where I
have to read the
clock I cannot get out of it anymore in
elementary school anything you didn't do
like little worksheets where you had to
learn the time I think
like um not really like sometimes rarely
it would come up in like English class
like normally English class yeah like
they would check if just as an exercise
to know if we know how to say the time
in English cuz first language is German
and then they would like point at people
in the classroom and like you read it
out you read it out but I was mostly
always lucky enough to evade that evade
avoid that yeah and never be called so
and then sometimes in math class I guess
it would be in some rich
um well you wait so you guys there's
clocks there right yeah would just all
never I have this thing where when
there's no digital clock around I've and
I really need to know the time and I
don't have my phone or anything either
and the only thing there is is a clock
on the wall like a real one uh I will
like maybe ask someone I will pretend
that I didn't see the clock in the room
like I'm looking around I'm oh I wonder
where the clock in the room is and I ask
the person next to me or so like hey do
you know what time it is hoping that
they would look look up and say it out
loud but sometimes they just point at
the clock and they're like yeah there
look and I'm like yeah thanks now I know
I I totally know the time now thanks for
not saying it out loud but it's easy
it's easy now that now that you know it
right like it's not that difficult oh
yeah yeah yeah I I really wonder why it
took me so long like nobody ever like
when I grew up like digital clocks were
quite a thing and phones became a thing
so I don't know I kind of got out of it
but anyway this is I just wanted to
confess to you it's not really about me
not knowing it but I I just wanted to
say I'm
sorry I forgive
you but yeah if you guys want to watch
that it's a pretty old collaboration we
did long time ago it's on our Channel we
were here or something like that yeah we
were here
together yeah good times good times
that's good one yeah really I'm I feel
like you suffered through it because of
me We Beat It we beat it no I think we
beat it but remember that one
uh time I think the most painful one was
like I was like in this room where the
water was and there was like electricity
and stuff oh yeah yeah yeah there were a
lot of painful ones but I'mma died at
the
end oh oh yeah I guess one of the povs
always was doomed to die yeah yeah yeah
story-wise you pushed me off a cliff I'm
just kidding
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah all right let's go back um you know
what time it is
am what time is it it is time for the
holot talk speed
round let's go I have adjusted some
questions but most of them are same and
you shall answer them in a speedy way in
a spe I have to give an explanation or
no no if you say something funny I might
touch upon it at the end but uh
generally just short answers uh put you
on closeup oh
that's get rid of it for now uh are you
ready y all right 3 2 1 hot or cold
weather cold weather rice or
noodles rice Denny or
ihob
uh ihob oh Twitter or
Instagram Twitter everybody always says
Twitter apple or orange
juice orange juice mm climb a mountain
or run a marathon climb a
mountain PC or console
PC pineapples on Pizza yes or
no not if it's hot pizza if it's cold
pizza it's okay oh
interesting spicy or sweet
food
sweet tea or
coffee uh tea and vacation at beach
Paradise or in a famous Metropolitan
City uh Beach oh beach beach let's go
sleep naked or with clothes
naked favorite holiday like Halloween
Christmas Easter
Etc Halloween I guess Halloween also I
guess uh there's um what's the what's
the one we Thanksgiving Thanksgiving you
like Thanksgiving uh yeah Thanksgiving
is okay okay uh oh uh sorry the graphic
is wrong oopsie uh Walmart or
[Music]
Target heym what's Kmart did you say
Kmart W Walmart guess Walmart okay
texting chatting uh or talking on the
phone when communicating with people
texting yeah giving or receiving
presents
giving and walk one station or take the
train walk oh wow so sporty what's your
blood type if you know it h i don't
remember if it's O I think it might be O
negative or something like
that and what is the color of your
panties I'm not wearing any oh no way I
don't believe it I don't even believe it
I guess it must be my black spant oh oh
yeah
nice thank you you you passed you passed
it wooo then what grade did I get um A+
or o
minus oh okay yeah blood type like
generally I usually ask this to the
Japanese girls because it's very common
to ask someone their blood type in Japan
did you know horoscope yeah
exactly so how did you find out your
blood
Tye um I think I was like like as a kid
I I knew what it was like I just asked
randomly it's impressive that you
remember yeah I only knew it once from
like blood donating and then I got like
a card or something but I I lost a card
and I don't remember my blood tab
anymore you don't remember it's just one
letter isn't it yeah but there I don't
know like I didn't you know think of it
I didn't think much of
it all right was there anything else
stood out like did you say IHOP or
Denny's IHOP it's the place where they
got pancakes and stuff right yeah they
do a free Pancake Day free Pancake Day
yeah I remember after school like
everybody would walk to ihob and we
would all get free
pancakes what you don't have to buy
anything else no I think they would make
you pay for a drink that's how they they
get you or you
have that's just fair fair I I would I
would go for that what a deal
[Music]
all all all right all right all right
back to the normal
questions we're like okay a little bit
more than halfway or halfway
from where where 60% yeah
this is a bit longer than I thought but
I'm enjoying my time with you so I hope
it's okay me too it's okay okay so
second half is kind of supposed to be a
bit more serious guys let's get into the
good stuff yeah so am Amilia Watson you
created so many special VR projects for
us which one is your favorite and what
goes into planning these feel free to
answer in a detailed manner uh favorite
[Music]
uh maybe the Christmas one we did that
one was really nice uh do we only do one
I think so yeah
a yeah I think the first one um because
that was I think I want to say that was
the first one that we had the camera
system set up for so there were so good
yeah there were a lot of nice shots
compared to the previous ones that we
had where we were just using the
handheld camera mm uh
yeah so I guess and we decorated the
tree everybody took their time to like
design the balls right
beforehand yeah yeah there were
different 3D artists who worked on like
all of the ornaments that we use and
then of course Cil did like the
background and took care of a lot of the
kind of Aesthetics for the Christmas
map and then I guess what goes into
planning them huh
yeah um well usually
I will make like really kind of terrible
looking Ms paint drawings of how I
imagine it would look and how I imagine
it would be and then of course like
seeing who would want to participate um
you know talent wise and then planning
from there is like uh does everybody
have a model is a model in theme is it
is it working properly does is the
tracking working properly making sure
like we would do a lot of testing for
every model to make sure that nothing on
it was you know broken in VR chat um and
also we always tested so much and then
usually we would meet up like you would
ask us to meet up maybe an hour before
and you would F down an hour before is
enough time but my God we always had
delays because there were always so many
problems that appear right everybody's
having some kind of
issue yeah I I think at first like a lot
of us were really excited to use full
body tracking and stuff but with VR full
body track there's quite a lot of issues
that you can run into and even though we
would have it set up before stream kind
of ready to go and then as we're kind of
you know preparing to really go live
then somebody's like um my arm is not
working what do we do and then it's kind
of really really fast um Tech Solutions
trying to juggle multiple things at once
so we can try to start on time or try to
figure out how long it will take before
we can fix it and get everything working
we made people wait a lot but it was
always worth
it wait sorry this will add more to your
translation but uh I had a lot of fun
designing the camera controls that we
ended up using that now we've used for a
few VR things and I think even other
people have used it too for their VR
chat I've used it also for my easter
event and also my uh collab with you
know others I've used it a lot so it's
been very very nice oh oh thank you yeah
I think fauna like fauna Raina Iris oh
way to oh even beyond the
branches yeah yeah so I'm glad I'm glad
that's why I made it uh hoping that
other people could also benefit from it
and of course I didn't do the coding or
anything from it but um I did design
like the console and kind of layout for
how it should work so somebody could
operate it and yeah wow like the
blueprint basically I don't know how to
say that in Japanese but oh well let's
try okay
[Music]
m
yeah um do you ever get stressed out
when you're like cuz I'm always worried
about you uh in the VR streams like like
there's like so many of us girls uh
sometimes you know it was just myth but
sometimes it was way more girls and
everybody's having issues do you get
stressed out when everybody like
everybody's like can you help me with
this and then while you're explaining
something to one girl there's another
girl
like how do I do this I can't hear
people or I can't see people I actually
think that that part is fun for me I
like the multitask where it's like the
manager will be asking me something the
person or like whoever is doing the
camera controls asking me something and
then also talking to like the modeler or
like the you know the person who does
the code and then I'm also talking to
you guys but for me like in the moment I
don't know my brain just goes into this
kind of calm state where I just uh I see
all the options equally if that makes
sense and then try to think about them
all at the same time and I know for me
it's kind of like it sounds weird but
kind of calming but really satisfying
also once we get all working so yeah
yeah pays off so true but I feel like
you must be so stressed out every time I
was stressed and like I tried to take
over my first things like I think there
was one like one time you were there I
think anyway for troubleshooting and
also uh just participating maybe too but
another time I had to do it like without
you and I was so nervous I was like oh
my God I don't know I'm I'm going to
freaking die because I'm so scared
without am what am I going to do yeah
but you did it right it work that out
well HMA helped me out a lot too thank
youma yeah well HMA learned a lot of
that stuff from me okay sometimes I mean
I do appreciate Emma of course but
sometimes HMA will tell me back stuff
that I already know and I'm like I know
that already okay I'm the one who taught
you that I think HMA is really excited
to be able to help you out and also like
learn a lot of these things and yeah
yeah you know PMA is kind of goated now
like one of the most uh useful managers
out there yeah I think Hemma will
continue to well I hope uh continue to
help other talents too for if they want
to do fun stuff in the future cuz I
think I did kind of help it help make it
easier um because yeah going into it
there was a lot of stuff that was people
had not done before in h life so there
was no precedent set and it was kind of
like they had to you know management had
to discuss if they would allow like
doing this or that and in the end kind
of just you know let me do a lot of
stuff but as you know yeah there were
some rules and stuff that they've
implemented since cuz yeah now that
we've done more stuff it's also like
okay now we have guidelines and yeah
yeah yeah that's true but we're still I
feel like VR chat is really a big
playground for us that's fun
[Music]
the I'm a way the I'm a way is the only
way yeah I feel like VR Pro projects
they are uh to me they're like really
like I want to do more but it's kind of
scary because there's so much to handle
and when you're not around I like I
don't have all of the tech knowledge or
the confidence so I don't feel like
there's projects I want to do but I
don't feel like I have the confidence
for it quite yet so I'll try to do some
stuff you know continue your legacy see
a little bit but yeah yeah the I'm way I
I might I might DM you and be like I'm
yeah I don't mind anytime I I uh I get a
lot of questions from like pretty much
anybody uh you know they'll just send me
questions and I'm like yeah I can help
so it's no problem I I like
helping thank you so
much all right let's go to the next
question okay besides 3D in VR you then
went as far as making your own 3D Studio
is that something you always wanted to
do and what kind of content have you
created with it so
far uh yes well I guess it kind of also
happened because I know you wanted to
find a way to do uh your concert yeah
because we couldn't use a Japanese
Studio yet yeah we we had our 3D yeah
but we we didn't have access to the tech
to do it and so my brain is always
running in kind of like problem solving
mode how can we solve this problem and I
really like researching new tech and
stuff so I I don't think I ever thought
that I would go that far um because I
didn't even know that you could go that
far with it and so learning learning
more about it like I I I did know about
a lot of mocap stuff obvious there's
like the you know beginner type of
YouTuber stuff like connect and you know
regular face tracking and hand tracking
and stuff like that but yeah learning
more uh on how to do like bigger scale
tracking was really exciting and um yeah
I really like working with that stuff uh
hold on I'm reading the question to see
what else there
is yeah so you didn't always want to do
that that was like something that came
up by me wanting to yeah I didn't set I
didn't set out to do that specifically
but it just kind of was like a whim and
I just followed it and you know it
really really worked out and that's kind
of how I do a lot of stuff which is
probably not a good idea cuz it can be a
gamble but um I find that yeah when I
follow my passions it tends to pay off a
bit uh you know I still remember um like
when we were still in the corona phase
um there was a time where I feel like I
don't know we kind of maybe got
frustrated or like lost our patience
with like ah we we have to wait so long
to go to had to do a 3D debut so you
were thinking a lot we had like meetings
and you brought up all these things uh
like you know Solutions how we could do
a 3D debut from home potentially and I
was like oh I'm really trying her best
to make this work because I really at
that point I was still hoping to just do
an early 3D deut like we've been waiting
so long and you know I just love how you
were always trying to make things work
for us and you were so cool like it was
like oh my God she has so much techn
knowledge yeah and some of those things
like the the option that we thought
about you thought about for using it
potentially for a 3D debut at home we
didn't use it in the end but it became a
solution for home 3D for all of Ian at
the time before M guys um right so every
we can talk about that a littleit think
we can what the hell do it yeah yeah so
it it was like a solution that I found
that I mean there were other YouTubers
that were doing it so I was not the
first one but um I think the the company
also took a little bit of a gamble in
terms of investing and getting that
solution for everybody because it was
something that I I had bought on my own
and I I would have like a meeting with
some of the tech of the company like
Tech uh people in the company and I was
like look we can use it like this we can
send data like this and um yeah it
pretty much showed them like how uh
versatile it was and I think off of that
they just invested in it for all of Ian
that has 3D so yeah I I honestly don't
think I don't think that the home
3D uh would have become a thing so early
at least for any of us I I don't think
it would have been on cover's mind to
provide us with home 3D especially the
reason why we got it at the time was
because because of Corona we couldn't go
to Japan and and even once we were able
to go to Japan we still just didn't have
as much opportunities to use the studio
because we lived we live overseas or so
mostly and the studio is fully booked or
whatever so just to give us like more
ways of doing things uh that was like
really great that you had brought up
these things and presented it to the
management so it was on their mind and
they were like you know okay maybe maybe
we should do this and they actually
considered it and made it a thing and
bought the solution so yeah I think even
people oh yeah even people still use it
today so I'm glad that everybody can
benefit from that yeah legendary I'm
going to translate that a little bit to
Japanese so
[Music]
C
yeah I'm I'm really grateful guys if you
did you watch it do you guys remember my
first FR birthday life it was so high
quality thanks to a and Ka thank you
yeah I'm glad it turned out well
remember we had a lot of struggles back
then
too
yeah I'm a studio built in a cave with a
box of scraps you were yeah she was
literally dancing on a flattened huge
cardboard box yeah that was at first I
was still dancing on your carpet and
then yeah that was pretty hard so then
we laid out a c a
cardboard but that was still kind of
difficult yeah g and Ena were helping
out too even FAA drove by at some
point a good time so
experimental right yeah it was cool yeah
I was always worried that like you know
I was troubling you too much but you
always say that you enjoy like
experimenting with this kind of stuff
yeah I think that's what's the most fun
is like doing stuff on the Fly kind of
you know I I like that I'm glad to hear
that well um not only I have benefited
from your 3D Studio but perhaps the one
who has benefited the most from it is
you
yourself you have had a lot of fun with
your Fredy stuff uh whoever was your own
Studio or the VR Stuff Etc uh have a
little clip that sums up your
shenanigans oh
okay to the right side clock o the clip
play it again that's the different one
are you ready for some it's a pretty
wholesome clip gonna warn you okay okay
let's look back at a lot of am Frey
shanans let's go
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah this will be
our cute oh also cute
didn't I call in so many times during
that stream yeah yeah you did I
remember and I sent you flowers at that
time Ah that's right yeah yeah I had a
bug in them and I kept
it oh
Chef yeah that was really fun I watched
that
oh what a
Chad yeah what a cool guy oh he's so
handsome I love how he's running I love
how he's
playing such a chiseled chin
wow oh
[Music]
wao c yeah that my
favorite you
[Music]
died cute so
cute a look at her go
[Music]
so
cute
yeah ah so small so
tiny that was so
cute that was my Easter stream yeah yeah
you can see camera system working well
oh
Bubba yeah oh oh oh Bubba's got the MS I
wonder who's dancing in that thing
you oh [\h__\h] I'm
worm the worm our cute low poly models
yeah yeah oh break dancing break dancing
oh
yeah oh oh wow better than
one oh me trying to floss I
cannot I don't have the coordination I
think I don't know why close enough yeah
oh the P
service yeah
Frey
W oh that's call commenting on your
dog she was like what the [\h__\h] is
that ah this one's so cute I love the
eyes yeah and oh I think that one always
looks like you're frowning like sadly
because of the hair eyebrows hair is
that eyebrows is that the hair I know no
it's the hair it looks like eyebrows
though
yeah
trampolines oh this one was hectic do
you remember setting up during this yeah
oh my God ah I up
collab yeah yeah I'm
in ah yeah this one was really cool too
oh no
no we
[Music]
are a dance
moves I love the outfit swap yeah that
was a iconic stream I feel like I like
that one a lot
too that's what
you
hey cute ah yeah this is the last time I
used my studio in full you prepared so
much for that yeah I really like how it
turned out ah cute yeah Halloween stream
all the new models too so
cursed a ah this one I really like that
one too
360 okay that's the cover Studio yeah
yeah and that's our
[Music]
four man yeah this second one was made
by Kazuki the first one was made by Cow
Car those clips and thank you so much
for helping out yeah I specifically
commissioned these clips for uh maybe
they'll upload them afterwards so yeah
they should they should uh so that was a
a lot of fun amen moments in Freddy I
feel like you're really shine in fredie
because you're so dorky in
fredie ah thank you thank you I'm I mean
you do too like you're dancing I always
look forward to seeing your
performances I'll continue doing my best
in such gy energy yeah well well I can't
keep up with your Gremlin energy though
I wish I had that
energy it's so good it's so funny yeah
and all the ideas you came up with you
know I really like the 360 stream that
we did that felt so intimate to me
yeah that that one was also really a lot
to figure out um cuz I wanted to get a
directional audio which yeah was worked
for a lot of hours trying to figure that
out I'm glad it worked out though and I
think that one that was in the re-upload
right you had the directional audio Yeah
the directional audio Yeah Yeah if you
guys are wondering about that if you
ever missed that because you're a newer
viewer it's uh the the like high quality
360 uh directional audio version is up
on her Channel as a reupload as a video
not as a stream so I think you should
watch that mhm was it our second
[Music]
anniversary uh which one what the that
stream was that our for our second
anniversary oh I think I want to say
third no really no it must have been
second yeah yeah second cuz it really
feels like a long time ago yeah and at
the time we didn't have an Ian idle
outfit yet so we want our own ones we
got some simple ones yeah I really I
really like the aesthetic of how the
whole stream turned out really cool so
cute the first one the first ey love fit
more or less we're making everything
possible together with myth even things
that seem
impossible you can do it yeah all righty
all right H thanks for the lovely clip I
will now ask you the next question
okay
yeah um have your impressions of the
myth girls changed over
[Music]
time
uh yeah I think so for sure how so cuz
when we met each other we never got to
meet in person until like what after a
few years of
meeting and I think that's that's kind
of interesting because we get to know
each other onine online first and
sometimes the way people are online
versus offline is like a little bit
different but I feel like meeting each
other uh I don't know it just felt
natural like how we usually are and um I
think a few of us are pretty low energy
so maybe it's hard for other people to
tell that we're the type of people that
it takes a while for us to get
comfortable with others but I think we
have already reach that point and Beyond
where we could just hang out on a couch
and just like I mean we did that we just
kind of hang out and relax and just talk
about stuff and you know such a like a
relaxing energy that um we can have
sometimes together and then yeah I does
that answer the question no I want to
hear it more
specifically oh for like each person yes
start with I don't know um
cie uh with Callie
[Music]
what did you think of her like At first
what kind of person did she seem to be
to
you and I don't know she seemed like
really cool right off the bat because of
just her music ability
and um you know I just know her as cie
and cie is very cute and very cool at
the same time so yeah I guess that was
my first impression of her and you know
she's like kind of goofy a little bit
Yeah and but you would say that is more
like something you found out later on
right yeah yeah you learn how how much
how goofy she is I kind of wrote the
same thing yesterday in my chart oh yeah
yeah yeah and really grows on you I feel
like she has a really endearing
personality too yeah so cute she's so
funny are we going deut order soara next
sure
okay and let's see first meeting
you I feel like right away maybe you
were kind of a little obsessed with K
more than anybody yeah I mean so I think
um yeah that that also is like uh
learning to trust each other and opening
up to each other more and not just with
me but you know with with everybody um
so yeah obviously learning that yeah I
like your sense of humor which is pretty
straightforward I think it can be
surprising for some people but I like
that about you andk you um let's see
what else oh I think you're you're
really honest about like how you feel
and stuff which I think can be difficult
to do I don't think people realize how
how hard it can be to kind of show like
how vulnerable cuz everybody feels like
that like we all feel like that way but
it can be really difficult even for me
especially like I'm not I don't feel
comfortable a lot of the time to to do
that but I I do admire you for being
able to do that and talk about a lot of
stuff that can be difficult to talk
about but you handle it so well because
you have a really nice way of you know
dissecting things and talking about it
thank you I'm it's nice to hear okay
next next
Ena
Ena you
know yeah to know Ena
more she's so sweet it's like uh you
know right off the bat I feel like uh
Ena and I are similar where it's kind of
hard to get to know people at first
because we're really introverted
introverted and getting to know her more
like she's somebody who no matter when
or what if you ask her for something or
like advice you know she'll try her best
to always be there and yeah I'll ask ask
her for advice for like some things or
if it's like I'm drawing something or
the one who's usually being asked for
advice you also go to people to ask for
advice yeah yeah cuz Ena Ena has a a
good amount of tech knowledge too like
we both strike 3D stuff so um sometimes
like we would talk to each other about
things like that and yeah I really trust
her opinion a lot when it comes to
especially like art or design or uh 3D
stuff yeah that's true yeah yeah she's
very technically knowledgeable indeed
but also the art yeah that's her her
specialty I see I see uh what about uh
go uh good I definely got to know her
what I want to know your first
impression ah first
impression well good and I kind of yeah
I guess it was a while ago that we met
but
um he good is also quiet when you when
you first meet yeah I think she was
really quiet but she was also how do I
say
like she had like this childlike wonder
I mean she still has it she still has it
for sure childlike wonder you mean like
she's like in a in a good way she's
childish you mean yeah like she was uh
not really I remember talking with her
at first she was really nervous about
streaming and she was she would always
be like how do how do you do this like
how how do you manage to be a streamer
like you are and I I would I would give
her you know I was like you got to you
got to rely on the chat you know a
little bit and you know give some
commentary here and there and um yeah I
mean I think she's always like that and
she's definitely opened up to me more
over time too and we got to know each
other pretty well so yeah I think all of
us have gotten to know each other really
well and I'm really grateful for that
too
M okay okay now you would say maybe
she's not so quiet anymore at least
towards you right cuz you said she was
kind of
quiet yeah I mean I'm also I'm also like
that too so I can understand where I
think we both just go into kind of like
our our little shells sometimes and we
have to recharge so I I understand that
more than anything yeah and yeah I think
like uh it's important to be comfortable
around each other
yeah understand each other too yeah
agreed all right that's a lot to
translate I'll try to keep it
[Music]
short
for
[Music]
for for
okay okay that's roughly it nice work
yeah
okay I'm trying my best here um so weird
all right all right all right um we
we're getting pretty long here so let me
move on to the next question but some
sweet words thank you so
much and next question is there's always
been a joke that when you go on a break
you're fetching a new Jen well anyway
what would be your advice for new
members um advice for new members that
you're currently fetching right uhuh
yeah uhhuh yeah totally I was
say uh always do things try to do things
your way as much as possible I think
there's like a lot of hurdles that you
will
encounter and just remember that your
fans I mean like the viewers they're on
your side and yeah they always they
always try their best to support you and
I would also say just be prepared to
travel a lot be prepared to sing if you
don't sing you know you know get singing
lessons and if you don't dance you know
start start learning how to groove
because I I remember I mentioned this
before but for my
audition they were like um do you sing
and I was like I I can sing I guess like
I I could try to you know I could try
getting a singing lesson or
something um so yeah I I'm sure now that
uh you know Ian is on its way to
becoming more and more power powerful um
that that's something uh you know H live
also looks at too more so uh so yeah any
more advice for future challenge I would
say though that I don't think while the
company tries to do like Idol stuff like
singing dancing I don't think anybody
expects anyone to be like really good at
it like that's true that's true yeah I
think the fans also really enjoy seeing
girls who more new to that kind of stuff
yeah have their own flare and exactly so
you don't have to be good at singing or
dancing at all you just got to enjoy it
just be interested in it yeah have a
thing for it all right is there anything
else you want to say otherwise I'll
translate um yeah just do your best and
do your best until you can't anymore and
then you know maybe take it easy for a
little bit and then do your best
again okay sounds good and
so for
[Music]
you you've been saying good things there
actually way I'm impressed was good
advice oh thank you yeah I think it's
important too like you got to you got to
try to do your own thing even if maybe
they put some hurdles uh there right in
front of you you still got to try right
yeah exactly got to be stubborn about it
yeah okay and next question is a bit
maybe maybe a sad one I don't
know well what will you miss the most
about being in Hall
life uh yeah number one for me it's like
immediately this is uh what comes to
mind is I'll definitely miss uh you know
all of all of Ian and I ID and all all
the people that uh you know we get to
play with that we get the honor of um
you know being next to standing next to
on stage so yeah I I know we'll all be
able to still talk to each other and
keep in contact and I hope if you guys
ever need advice or anything I can help
you but um I I know that I'll definitely
still be playing games with some people
offline but yeah it's really an honor to
be able to entertain next to you guys as
well so that's definitely something that
I will miss
yeah yeah I thought so that's like the
biggest Prospect of you know being in a
company like this you can hang out with
all these other girls and have a fun
Merry time with them yeah cuz
everybody's so funny and so talented and
they have their own quirks and they're
so unique and yeah it's hard to find
that kind of qualities I guess sometimes
yeah and
[Music]
I will contact
you I know you will I
will yay yeah well thank you
Al thank you for doing this you you will
miss some things in whole life and you
will also be missed
greatly oh thank you thank you well
moving on we have yes two more questions
and then a nice
surprise so what's good that
be next question is O did two questions
are like questions I always ask but
they're always interesting to hear um
because we get get a little bit of a
deeper look into your uh activities what
struggles did you deal with in Hol life
and what made you go on
regardless uh probably well yeah I
definitely had some health issues where
learning you have like a pretty big
allergy to some stuff and you know
dealing with like lowered energy levels
versus what I felt like the viewers like
chat deserves like I I definitely wish I
had um a better output sometimes in
terms of like what I could do and I I
feel like that's something that yeah
people have health problems can face uh
especially here you know cuz it's
everybody's like always on the grind and
as you know H Al there's always people
live and you really want to keep up and
it can be um a struggle to feel like
you're not doing doing
enough and other than that I would
say um probably recording like uh
performances sometimes or recording
songs for covers uh for me it's you know
I I I'm really Harden myself in terms of
learning the proper pronunciation for
Japanese and and so for some talents um
you know they'll learn a song and be
able to record it in like what maybe
like one or two hours or something I
don't know but when I record it it takes
me a very long time and it's really
frustrating because I'll listen and I'm
like why brain why can't you just
pronounce it like how it's pronounced in
the song why can't you do that so um
yeah for a lot of reasons it has to be
you know the pronunciation needs to be
on point so that can be that's true
especially people sing together not just
you it's got to sound the same mhm yeah
I understand that must have been rough
but you did so well you you you got so
much better at Japanese and singing and
everything but the allergies man the
freaking
bread yeah the freaking bread always
gets
you hello stay away from it am I do I do
yeah you're staying away from it by
giving me bread cuz you gave me the
bread plushies true yeah yeah I'll take
them I'll take them away from you so
that they don't stay close to you thank
[Music]
you for
so so so so yes yes yes waku I
understand you
Army but I'm I'm so proud that you
powered through all of that yeah
actually what got you through all of
that
oh
um maybe oh definitely the chat you know
like a teammates and wanting to deliver
as you know best of an experiences I can
and also my dogs they keep me a lot of
company your dogs yeah what about your
cats well Henry is uh well yeah and my
other cat I mean they're troublemakers
they're cats are not the same for me as
at least my my dogs they're like uh what
is it called it's like when they're like
Comfort animals like when you're feeling
anxious or something they like sit next
to you and you know try to help you out
so yeah no I I would agree like you know
I only have cats and they give me a lot
of mental support but if you have dogs
too I'm sure that yeah they would be
more actively coming to you than cats
yeah yeah and they sense your stress and
they're
like yeah yeah yeah your dog bu bu hey
good boy good Bo who's a good boy who's
a good boy he's taking a nap by my feet
right now a bo bo so
sweet soon he will get hugs and
tros yes well thank you to the teammates
and to your pets for taking care of you
mhm yeah okay um the next question is
the last one did you translate well I
guess you don't have to translate I
think Mama okay okay okay well roughly
all right and the next question is the
last one but don't leave yet guys I'm
I'm going have something special for you
so I always ask this at the
end what does whole life mean to you
I think what comes to mind is such
unique personalities right and then
seeing all those unique
personalities make connections with each
other and form like special
relationships and yeah and and as
viewers you know as fans we get to enjoy
that but then also from being inside of
Hol live uh yeah it feels it feels
really amazing to be part of that and to
get to talk to those people too at the
same
time okay
[Music]
wonderfully said Amy well said clap clap
clap thank you thank you it's true
actually a lot of uh times when I ask
this question I will hear similar
answers but yours was something I never
heard before oh really oh
yeah
yippee okay
well um originally I didn't plan to do
these interviews as like kind of an exit
interview it just so happened to be but
um I I kind of like that because it
feels like a a nice conclusion and I can
like ask questions that I normally
wouldn't ask that are that feel more
like how was your experience so far and
I don't know it's just a kind of
different kind of interview and um thank
you so much for um making time for this
and thank you so much for answering
everything at length in
detail and of course thank you
for well you know our years together
amen you were the best freaking
colleague I could ever ask
for I'm glad I'm glad thank you so much
for you know not just today but yeah for
uh setting this up for all the fans I
think it's really interesting cuz we
don't have yeah this is like the only
type of interview thing that we have at
least on Ian side even on JP side no we
don't really there really yeah not not
in this scale I would say yeah M well I
you do so much work you do like four
people's job at once while streaming so
thank you thank you for handling it all
no there nothing compared to what what
you always do when you do VR streams and
all that and I really wanted to again
say thank you for making my first proper
3d concert possible in the first place
like without you that wouldn't have
happened and that was so much work and
you suffered through it with me and the
result was so marvelous and yeah yeah it
will always be something that we created
together we created so many things
together that I think we can all be so
proud of yeah and who knows you know
with projects or whatever I'm sure we'll
be able to work together again
someday and maybe secret you will be
controlling the cameras in a future VR
stream oh I don't know but
oh we'll see we don't have to tell
anyone yeah you guys will never know
yeah all right um sometimes when the
guest wants to do it we are we get
blessed on H talk here by little musical
performance and am is currently so busy
but she still is taking the time to
perform for us life totally life
here oh let's go let's go I'm a
performance are you guys
ready get your P lights okay are you
ready do you need to like drink some
water okay I'll drink water
[Music]
okay ready oh and also with that we say
goodbye so thank you guys so much for
watching uh I'm want to say like some
last words and
goodbyes oh yes uh I hope you guys
continue to watch more interesting Holo
talks that I'm sure will come down the
line and of course like I said before I
continue to support Holo Ian and
everybody and and yeah thank you guys so
much for watching and hanging out and I
have a stream after this so let's just
go what kind of stream a gaming stream
going to finish the Oblivion DLC oh
Oblivion Amelia bson yeah all right yeah
that's a Legendary game series of yours
and I'm glad you're finishing it
otherwise it would have felt well I I
did finish the main game it's just a DLC
o putting a lot of work on yourself
there
well then make sure you guys to watch it
I've been saying like you guys you got
to watch every freaking remaining I'm a
stream or else I will I will go and go
to your room and I will punch you T some
people will enjoy that though no no no
no no don't don't let it go that far you
have to watch every single remaining
stream no regretti spaghetti all right
okay yeah now I'm you go hop on stage
all right but before that we say in
German we say
I'm she
remembers goodbye guys enjoy am
performance that's right I'm not just a
detective I'm a time traveler watch
[Applause]
this hey hey
[Music]
when we first met hey hey I wonder what
you think of me the image was set hey
hey it was a perfect narrative But as
time went by I forgot to hide the laughs
that came so naturally through lows and
highs I'd wonder why I ever thought you
would leave now no matter where or when
we are I know it's you I can count on
magical
mythical nothing can stop us now let's
go take a do to where the time go up up
how should I know why it seems when
you're here with me the clock will stop
spinning up up up doy doy Hearts Beed
faster toi friends forever it's clear to
see that this mystery was solved
immediately you got me
W hey
hey it's been so
long since I laugh so hard I cried now
you came
along it happens almost every time that
I hear your voice I'm left no choice but
to let you know what you mean to me SP
spiraling time skipping the treasure
memories now no matter where or when
we're from our friendship's elementary
case Clos now you know nothing can stop
us now let's
go where the time
go how should I know why it seems when
you're here with me the clock won't stop
spinning ducky ducky hide speed faster
come doding friends forever it's clear
to see that this mystery was solved
immediately you got me though it day
we're
older what the future holds is not not
not for us to know yet it's gone gone
gone before we know it so let's solve
the
question we can make each second CH Taco
last forever la la it's now or never
Chu where the time
goak how should I know why it seems when
you're here with me the clock would stop
spinning w w docky doy Hearts be faster
to your friends forever it's clear to
see that this mystery was solved
immediately you
me that's right I'm not just detective
I'm a time traveler look at this
[Music]