[Music]
[Music] Happy
New Year [Music] Happy New Year is English Happy New Year I
understand that
[Music] Thank you
house
[Music]
Hey
[Music] I'm
nervous, after all, it's been normal until just now  I was talking
to a senior like this.
OK to introduce yourself in English Hello
[Music]
My name is this, Inugami
[Applause]
[Music]
OK to introduce yourself in English
Please
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] I
haven't. I've been sweating a lot today. The smell of sweat is so
good, isn't it? Everyone, huh
? The smell of sweat is so good.  I don't know how to say it in English,
but it's
amazing
LOVE
LOVE Private life The
smell of Kyoto is so cute
After all, it's dog-dog.Today we're
going to do a one-two switch, but before that, I
thought we'd talk a little bit since it's my first time.
Talking, I just
noticed.
[Music] I feel like my hands are
more open than mine.
Thank you very much. This soup is so delicious.
[Applause] I
was surprised, but
it's so cute. It's
not straight, it's like this.
It's like this.  I like that. It's
cute when you're particular about it.
[Music]
That's how you say it.
[Music] Even if it's
the first time, we met for the first time. On the 31st, we had our
first first contact.
Yes, this is a senior viewer next time. I want to ask
you if you're there or not. That senior is
always like this with the people on the invitation side. But
yeah, you
know, he's shy. It's quite true. I don't notice it at all right now, and I didn't notice it at all the other day either.  I'm really shy,
but I feel like
people are looking at me as a character in a game, or maybe they're
looking at me a little bit. You're
beautiful, you're not viewing me.
[Music]
[Laughter] You're
beautiful, aren't you? Yesterday, Marin-
senpai.  I'd be
happier with the Final Fantasy that came out of Resident Evil,
but Resident Evil's
characters
are cute and beautiful,
right? Well then, let's get Marin to turn into a zombie
and let's defeat him together.
[Music]
But Marin-senpai Mario  He's kind too,
but hey, I
punched Marin-senpai's butt,
and I think I did some kind of teasing on Twitter.I've
never seen the anime before,
so the cat told me about it a while ago.
That kind of inthe Chitty Chitty Bamba
Ah
[Music] I
saw the one on Twitter It
's public,
so Hokuto Everyone was the first. Maybe my viewers caught up. The
way the hot dog is drawn isn't really normal.
But it's already on the floor.  The
fire in the living room is so
hot that
the two of us can eat together.I've never
had it cooked before.My
favorite toppings are
toppings.Sometimes I
have onions.
[Music]
Toppings,
uhm, it's okay
today
instead of No. 9. I
like bars.
[Music] I
don't eat, but
tiara's toppings are like this.
Toppings, these are toppings. You
can eat them.
Hair, that's
nice. By the way, I bought some food earlier too.
There was food, but I
ate a little bit of it, but I
was also hungry so I ate it.I went
to the studio earlier, so I
went to that studio today,
goto studio.I'll
translate what they say into Japanese.
[Music]
Today I went to the studio,
and I met Nice and
[Music]
Yes
and Daygiffemeyou
something. I
got you something as a present today. I
got you a present, Dekiru-chan.
Well, there's nothing more to talk about.
Hey, Nodoka-
san game.What I got from Nodoka-san is
amazing.Eh, hey, hey,
grasshopper, officer, and dorayaki.Edorayaki
is an English word.
Please search for Doraemon and
Doraemon
[Music]
That's right, I'm talking about
sweets
& gifts. This is a sweet snack. Instead, there's a
game.
Umeboshi Umeboshi Baby
Baby gave me
maple Umeboshi. It's a little salty,
right?
Wait.  The way he speaks is
genuine and
happy. I
often see him behind celebrities.
Um, is the
fuel okay?
[Music]
Audio Balance The
volume balance is OK, Senpai,
so you can rest assured.It's
sour, but this is true.It's sweet and sour, but it's
true.It's
sweet, but
Moebius.Okay, let's
eat the umeboshi.Let's eat.But it's a big bite.Eh,
it's a bit big to eat it all in one bite.
Yes, that's
amazing.
Wait,yes.
[Music]
[Music] It's
okay to use a tissue. It
's surprisingly sour. It's sour. Ah, wow.
[Music] It's
surprisingly sour.  I
like umeboshi. The
BGM says it's a little loud.
Ok. I've
only eaten umeboshi once in my life.
Well, it's the second time. But it hasn't moved at all.
Maybe it's the first time. Well, it's already the first time. Ah,
Lipton Lipton gulp.
Drinking Lipton Chiara
It says there's also umeboshi, but the surface
is honey.
The moment you put it in your mouth, it's honey. When you bite into it, it's
inside.  A lot of
sour man came out.
Yes, where
did you go? I
ate that hard one. I guess I
shouldn't drink it.
But I
shouldn't drink the seeds.
[Music] It's
huge.
If I were a robot, I would
n't die. It's okay.  'Cause I've
been drinking all my life It
's true, it's okay Show me your cool
[Laughs] You're
worrying too much
It's coming from your head
Amazing
[Music]
That's it.  It's
dangerous, so I'll probably do it next time.Okay, maybe I should do that.Okay, that
little thing makes me
wonder if it's a big deal.I
want to give it to my body, too.The food is
n't just in my mouth,
it's coming out of my butt.  Yeah, I'm sure it'll come out. It wo
n't hurt. I'll tell you if it comes out. It
's important. Have
you ever done this? I
eat the seeds, the huge seeds of the pickled plums, and the seeds of the watermelon.
Watermelon is a different kind of watermelon, is
n't it? If you don't try it, you won't swallow it. And you do
n't gulp it out much. It's better to leave it like
this and not eat it so much. It's
okay if you
do that once next time.  It
's okay if it's only once. How many times have you done it?
Next time, do this.
Blue maroon, come on. Next
food, slack off. I'm
sure it's an English word.
Surprise.
How do you say it in Japanese?  I'm
so angry I'm sorry to eat it. I won't
eat it. Is it
flavor or chestnut?
Oh, wait, this is like this. I
like it a little more. For
plain and
cream, I want flour. That's good.
That's brown sugar, that's
black.  Or brown sugar.Which
one
would you like?Eh, black tea.Japanese, not
here
.
Maybe there's still some left in your mouth
Delicious
Delicious changes again Mummogumogumogu
Eh, you
can say this.
Look, it's already coming out.
Hair Please
use your current Japanese.
This is my senior's streaming room, but what the hell,
what the bench.  It's
amazing, is
n't it? It's not like you're gaming, it
's a bench that seats about three people. It
hurts your back, so I
remember it. It
hurts your back, so a regular chair is better.  I
wonder if it's
because I've been there for a long time
[Music]
[Applause]
Wait, I can't see my eyes, so I
can do Holotalk.
]
Victory I wonder
what month it is, the end of March or the beginning of March.
Please.
[Music]
[Music] It
looks really interesting. It looks
interesting. It's interesting. Let's drink the cow's milk.
Milking my father
Yes, I
want to milk my milk.
[Music]
Yes, all you have to do is have the right husband.
That's the existence of this game. Yeah, I
forgot.
Check out this senior's meat 3. You
made it for me. I
can use Photoshop right now.  Because I don't have it now,
eat it,
eat it, thumbnail
[Music]
Japanese
[Applause] [
Applause]
[Music]
[Applause] [
Music]
[Music]
Umeboshi too. I
ate it because I thought it was sweet.  I
was surprised, but it
was delicious. It
was delicious.
[Music]
Mickey, it's okay.
Hmm.
From the amazing banknotes.
[Music]
Everything.
Mickey Mouse. I wonder
what happened.
But after drugs,
Star Wars started.
That's
not it. I like it, I
love it.
I didn't watch that much, so that was the
first
movie I
saw when I was little.
Hey, even though I don't remember, you were all 4 Route 4
[Applause] The
story of the
previous story The previous story In Japanese, it's
Very Berry
[Music]
Past edition Ah past edition
Comment Azama
Past edition Well, it's definitely weird  Well, I guess I'll watch it too.
There are some characters and movies that I like.
Ah,
[Music] I've
seen them
all. I haven't seen them all, maybe just the first one. I've seen them
all. I've seen them all, and I've
also seen the statue bits after that, so I
like them.  What is it?
How many hours has it been
? It's quite long. It
's a prefectural plastic game, and my partner is
a senior. At least this senior's favorite one.
Ok Google
[Applause]
That
fantasy type is Aski Fantasy,
but I was wondering if he
liked the type after all.
But I
guess I'll see it next time. I'll
watch it today. I'll watch it today
. If I have time, you
can tell me about the futon situation.
[Music] I
was surprised. When I
looked at where I slept, it was
quite
small.  There
was a big, shabby futon, and there was also a
bed.I was
thinking of buying a new bed, but I haven't bought a new one, so I do
n't have one yet.The
next time I go, I'll buy a fluffy bed.Today, I'm going to buy a fluffy bed.  It's
nothing special.
Yeah, I don't play games. Let's do it.
Okay, let's turn on the power for a second. OK
[Music]
Yeah, but games
are fun, too, after all, Koume-senpai.
Officially it's Gamers, but I
don't drink at Games.
But I'm a gamer, right? I speak
English. Let's have a showdown.  It's the kind of
thing that just moves around and melts away.
I wonder if I should just do it in a random way. If I do it in a random way, I might end up losing karma. That's right. [Music] I'm a little unsure of myself.  The
strap follows the notebook It's
okay. I
can see it in my mind's eye.
[Music] [
Music] Let's go. [Music] Let's
go.
[Music] How to
do it Wait a minute and
watch Let's take a look at the email type It's kind of like this It
says spicy I guess it's difficult
[Music]
Press the button too Ah, uhm, this is probably here The
type on the side is OK I
don't drink  I'm
with those who have complexes.
If all you do is eat, you won't drink. You can
press the embarrassing button.
Hold the Joy-Con upright and hold it.
[Music] Is it
okay to do it with both hands? You're the
one who's bored. The
rhythm of the top button and that button.
That's right.  Let's
change the way we do things a little bit.
Press
[Music]
[Applause]
Start
It's like this, I've done it before, I've done it in real life, listener, I've
done it before, I've done it before,
at school,
when I was little.
Well, what was it like? So what was the
chat like?
Everyone was just a kid, so
wait until then. This senior just read the atmosphere and was
late. He's
not late. He's
not late.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Something like that.  Hey, do you want to play the next game? Yes, you
can choose. One-two
Kinko Breaking and
Cool, not that.
This too. We have to look at each other.
This is it.
Heart
[Music]
Shotgun OK.
Please press the L button It's
always funny
Cute
[Music] I was
hitting the ground
because Tiara is kind too, ah, we're on the outside too. It's a
small wood.
Aim for the opponent's heart. It's
cute. Sorry.
Cute
[Music]
Back to back,
turn around and hit.  Okay, this is OK
Back to the Future Separately OK Something Please turn the center down, yes. It's
difficult. Should I
turn it to the left? It's
difficult, yes.
[Laughs] It
hurts.
What's going on? I wonder what's going on with this. I
don't really understand this. Oh
yeah, but thank you just in case. Nice
nice. I'm going to do something like Shirahatori or
Shirahatori
[Music] and
do that
[Music] Is
this happening [Music]  [
Laughs] If you
defend like that, you're defending and attacking.
Ah,
but you can't see it, but how do you
catch it? It's about timing.
This is amazing these days. It does
n't matter how you hold it.
[Music]
Knock out my head!
Get ready.
What's that? Get ready.
[Music] You can start anytime. Come on. [Applause] [Music] Okay, everyone, get ready. We'll do it until we die. Character: There's no opening, right? [Music] [Music]  [
Laughter]
[Laughter]
[Music]
Goodbye
[Applause]
[Laughter]
After all, seniors like you have done this kind of
thing.
What do you want to do?
[Music]
For now, let's just do this for one of the cats.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Let's
go. Use your favorite score.
Shake, shake,
a little
bit, a little bit more. It's still
okay. It's still okay.
[Music] It's
still okay.
[Music]
After this.
Take off your clothes, you'll
be drenched, but
what's best
? Hmm, baby, put it on twice.
Okay, this is my senior, my baby,
this is my cell phone, this is no good.
OK, the
gunman is back
Faceboy
There's this sensor there, so it's
about 5 cm.
Make sure you don't move your hands and head during the game.
Etc. Sensor
[Music]
[Music] [
Music] [
[Applause] [Applause] I'm going to eat half of that again. 67 Wow, it's dirty. It's okay. OK, press it one more time. You can move the camera closer to your mouth. [Music] [
Applause]
[Music]
Or
[Laughter]
My  Channel
[applause]
[Music]
What kind of thing was this? I
remember. It seems like you're in a lot of pain right now.
Take it, it
's winter, shake it, shake it. I don't care about your
legs.
[Music] I wonder
if you'll take it off like
this.  Why don't you put it
up? [Music] [Music] I'm not running, but if you come, I'll face you right away.
At the entrance.
[Music]
[Music] We're
all together. I'm
screaming just as hard, but I can't even feel my throat anymore. It's
okay.  It's
fun, it
's like this
[Music]
Which one is better? Oh,
don't get in my way
[Music]
Alright, alright, alright then,
OK
Strap, OK Be
careful of your surroundings Yes, be careful of your surroundings and
spin
[Music]
Whichever is faster?
Ah
[Music]
Senpai, I've done this in real life.
[Laughs]
What bank?
[Music]
Turn it 90 degrees and
if you feel a different vibration,
hold it back Okok
[Music]
No, no, no, no, no,
no, but I have to wait
[Music] I can
feel it
SE Oh my
god,
where are the men
[  Music] Is it
the best of all time? I've
always been
getting money. I'll
give it to you later.
[Music] Let's
take a look at what I don't understand. I can
feel the sum in the other person's eyes through vibrations. If you don't mind.
Please open the cups at the same time. The one with the
highest number wins. It seems that you
don't know who you are. You
only know who your opponent is, so if you
think that yours is higher, the
player on the stomach will roll 12. At this rate, the
player on the left.  Yes, you'll lose. Let's
just lie a little and
make the other person reroll the dice. If you say, "I don't care if your eyes are small,
"
please reroll the rice.
[Music]
Eh, wait, I can hear it.
Check the total.
Eh.
Make some comments about the total in the other person's eyes.
Yes, it
's okay if it's true or you don't feel it.
Chiara: I do
n't think you need to reroll this, Tiara.
What happens if you shake the cup upside down?
[Music]
That's not what you're saying.
But it's not different from before, but it's okay. Eh, it's
cute, but it's
definitely changed for the better. Eh,
even if I wait, that number that pops up...
Yeah, it's
this one or that one. I do
n't think it's this one. I'll
take a look at it once. I'll take a look at it once.
This is the winner.
I'm too dumb, but I think I counted the guns, but I
guess I was wrong.  It's so close that it's too bad. Eh,
use the vibration to
check the total in the other person's eyes.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
I felt the go, but it was low.  You
said you should try it one more time, right? I
thought it wouldn't work if I did that.
[Music] It's
cute. It
's a game.
Check it out.
[Applause]
[Music] It's
better to shake it. It's better to
buy it.  Okay,
I think you should shake Kiera as well. Please
open the cup at the same time. Yes, I
really
think Tiara would be good too. I think it's a good fight.
That's a good fight.
[Laughter] [Laughter
]
[Applause]
[Music]
How about that
? It's better to roll. This one is 99. Let's
do both.
[Music] I
can tell the other person that there
are a lot of tiaras. 11 is also a lot. It's
true, it's raining like this. I rerolled it. It
's a 99. It's conveyed to the other person that there is no Daiso.
If you don't mind here, I do
n't know if I'm really saying it
[Music]
No,
no, no, I guess it's wrong. Is there another one? Yes, yes, yes, that's it
[Music]
Vibration
At the end, check the total of your opponent's rolls.Yes, this is
what I like, Senpai.It's better not to roll.I'll just leave it like this.If you don't mind, I'll take a
bath.I'll let my
opponent know the result of the rerolled dice.It's a
fun game, isn't it?  You
must be tired with a smile on your face.
[Music] It's
fun.
That's how we did it the second time we won.
Isn't that what real anger is like now
?
[Music]
Now that you have to choose one or the other
Stop your hands in front of your chest and
do the Katakuri.
Pay attention to your surroundings. Yes,
beat the rhythm with both hands.
Chest  Please don't hit
me [Music] From now on [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] This is so awkward Who's going to show up first? [Music] Okay, this is the kind of senior I am.
When someone calls me, come on, come on, I'll go to the bathroom and turn off the phone. Eh,
there's some delicious chaos [Music]
So let's face each other.
First, what kind of
sound is that? [
Music]
[Music]
That's it. I saw space after all. It's
cute.
[Music]
Only outside.  Look, it's just a little bit like that. It's
not a mask. What?
Okay, okay, yes, press it. Yes, the
characters are good too.
Please shout. You
have to make the sound you're making now.
First,
this one is wrong.
Cut it off quickly.
This one is different.
[Music]
[Applause]
Finally, the person who wins the last mini-game will
be today's winner, okay?  You can choose the one
you can do, or you
can choose the one you want to see without the exterior.You guys
haven't played any watching games,
right?I don't care, this is difficult, but
when everyone gives instructions,
raise the flag as instructed.  Sho
There's boxing, too.
[Laughs]
[Music]
That's it when one of them is finished. I
don't have any experience with either of them, but
[Music] I
press the button, stand up for each one,
and
hold it down for a bit.  Keep pressing it. It
's moving firmly along the woman's face. It's moving quite a lot. If you
want to use your right hand, let's
rotate it along the face.
[Music]
[Applause]
No, it looks like we're
going to take a break.
Maybe he's in
good spirits, since he's shaved his head.What
mini-game did you like to play against the enemy?I
guess this is a game where you can make out with this senpai.After all, let's
give him milk one more time and then do some boxing.Finally, give him
milk.  When you're done squeezing, we'll
fight boxing,
and then we'll box. OK, OK.
Please stay far enough away so our hands don't touch.
[Music] Just
do what you're doing. It's dangerous. It's
dangerous. It's dangerous.  That's the
one you've got.
So let's face each other and
shoot faster than we can spit. Straight, straight
[Music]
[Applause]
Squeeze the milk.
Milk.
Milk. Let's squeeze it
out. Let's go to the milk.
[Music]
[Music]  ] I
squeezed it carefully while looking at my hand,
and when I woke up in the morning, I
squeezed it all together.It was
delicious,
but I didn't like it.You wouldn't drink it, right?It's not just milk,
but just that feeling
makes me happy.  I feel
like I'm going to throw up after drinking 7 bottles. I'm sure it was fun. Come here like you're a
real cow. Let's squeeze some real cow poop,
Dad. I
want to squeeze it. Well, well, I
invited you, but I thought we'd do something more fun.  I
guess they do girly things
in Austria.
Yeah
[Music] I wonder
what it's like. I'll take a
look at it.
The cat is also a
puller. I
want to see it.
I love her, but she won't do it.
[Music]
Everything.  Let's
buy everything together Yeah,
like an adult
Because babies are difficult Yeah, let's
get a pet Let's
get a pet Let's get a pet
Then I'll buy Chiara
Yay
[Music]
It was fun It was
fun It was amazing [
Music]
[Music]
[Music]  Even if you
go out and get popular, you'll have legs. I'll
probably not let you ride like a princess.
On the contrary, it's dangerous.
Roller coaster In English, it's
called a roller coaster. In English, it's called roller coaster.
And yet, the roller coaster also conveys that feeling.I guess that's true,
but for some reason, there are places I'd rather go to than Disney.
There's no new Nintendo. I have to go. I
saw it.
[Music]
Where
was it? It
was terrible. It was so big, it was terrible.
Wide: Hmm. It's not very wide, but it's kind of like that.
Express yourself to the fullest in a limited area.
Wow. That's how
wide it is. It's wide.
When the voice said that, there were a lot of children, and I
laughed. There
were a lot of children, so the
brown color of the child was nice.  You choose, you're
not a child,
right? OK.
I was only able to do a little bit. I'm
kind to my senior who prioritizes learning.
When we're together, it's time to say goodbye.
[Music]
Hey, then.
[Music]  I do
n't care if it's in the sewers or something, it's dirty underground [Music] I don't
care if it's ok [Music] [Music] [Music] There's no way I'll hate you, I've grown to like you even more Ah,
Love Meter
[Music]
Just keep going.  I think I'm going to fall asleep in it.But I
have a futon that's fluent.Hmmm,
Tenape can speak English.Those feet are
so fluent.Tiara is so fluent.I'll
give you a futon that's fluent.
[Music]
What if the futon is a futon
? It's so flimsy, it's like a carpet. It
might fly away, like a magical carpet.
Okay, so before the futon blows off,
Tiara should just sleep on it. I wonder if she'll
sleep on it. First,
where do you start today and every day, Senpai?  It's
really early,
so it's probably close. I've been working all the time, so let's wait a little.
Hey, let's wait a little
. I'll get ready.
Hold on, ah, let me lie down.
Wait, everyone, wait a
minute, everyone, wait a minute. I don't
like this.
[Music]
It's okay. I'm
not going. Wait a minute.
Okay, that's the end. Wait a minute, everyone. I'm going to
put Chiara to sleep. Now,
how do I get her to sleep?  Hey, I have
n't been using it lately.
[Music] I
have it somewhere, so I'm going to put it on my futon.
[Music]
I'll use chroma key to extract it, and I'll put this on my futon.
It's really dark. I'm going to use chroma key to remove this as well.
[Music]
I have to say goodbye to everyone.
[Music] If I
sleep in this past, that'll be
tough. I'll
fix the swinging.
[Music] I can't do
this anymore. I'll say goodnight.
How do you say good night? Good night
Bye-bye Ending
[Music]
[Music
] [Music]
[Music]