oh
hello hello hello
hello hello hello hello
hey hey can everybody help us
[Music]
oh very good you guys here
i learned that from you oh you did
wow that's actually that makes that
makes my heart uh
be very fast
[Music]
my ears are blessed uh i have to
yeah i gotta just hold on i'm gonna give
you guys a good old privacy
panel for a second oh god maybe
take all the time you need
[Music]
technical difficulties
big girl face big glare face
um very cute
so we're gonna bump kelly up kelly can i
get a yo-yo
hey yo yo very nice that was actually me
speaking very loud this is me speaking
normally hey hey what's up
this sounds perfect watson can i get a
yo-yo
yo yo yo yo
[Music]
hello
everybody should be up quite a bit
better now
all right
we're gonna beat each other up right
that's what this game is
apparently like mario party
mario party nice excellent so like board
game and mini games
yeah but fun collects cups i think
a little bit oh okay okay oh goblins
goblins goblins i said we have one right
here
is that a creme brulee a lot of coffee
oh that's true that's a gentleman
you know the difference
it's cute uh can you guys see the maps
on my cycling street oh yes yes yes
paradise okay our this one
looks cute and bright boy cute time i
played this game like here before no no
no no
i've only played it once and i don't
remember having a fun time
it's always a fun time with halloween
make your way along the board to the
treasure chest is that the goal
um
oh epic music though
oh so i think you need a certain amount
of keys to open a chest
there's a goblet and you keep it and
then it's like a star
finding oh can i look at the big game
is there a way to look at the big map
did someone know
um
i don't know actually there's a way to
look
on his map i don't i don't even know how
i don't even know how to move oh wait oh
with the mouse oh
there you go there goes the chicken lord
did i get an item you did not
[Music]
thanks chat thank you too late but
i'll take it
is that calling master huss funny way to
write what is death sense today
you're gonna do yourself would you like
me to steal from your intruders
not sacrifice
hey hey
i don't like this flawed
is that you baby
stop messing with ina i don't have to
punch you sensei
kelly it's your turn all right here we
go cowboy
whoa whoa dick
cowboy is on the mission oh no nice
is that yeah oh you can choose
directions oh okay okay
i see a skellington there's a
skellington
um let me see i'll go this way
damn it oh hey one of those the master
has finally arrived the space is now
yours what would you like me to steal
from intruders who land on this space
i don't know what the blood is used for
not sure i have no idea
i gotta adjust the audio again sorry
guys
oh you're good no worries g
shut up i just really know i wanted to
make sure
you your mouths
if the audio is fine and then trust no
one else but manage your son
is the game online anything
please let me know i'm checking discord
now also am i still too low because
a lot of people are saying that i can
just speak really loud if you want
[Music]
i'm i'm trying i'm still trying not to
pee though that is quite a funny thing
it's quite a
two i got two
oh i hate this oh no
okay gotta remember where the thing is
sound is good thank you guys all right
now we play
cool okay guys first one off the map
uh
move cowboy oh oh the cowboy
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's gonna be a win freeze summer time
no watson no i'm coming
off
[Music]
give me
i
[Music]
regret it i'm just going to eat it with
the right dishes girl
but it looks gross it looks like an egg
into it like a banana
yeah it's yummy on the inside
wait my master's arrived the space is
not yours or would you like me to steal
from intruders there's a lot of
death sensei is really busy today should
i take wait
did we go over this blood or keys what
does it mean what is that
we'll find out genius or to open chest
i think you get the goblets but i don't
know what the blood is oh
i think blood might be your health
because there's health like you can take
damage
all right i'll take you give me a key
death sense hey what's up god damn
desperate
cactus
okay oh when you need a key in order to
open up the ch
okay you got it roger
i got this one okay oh yeah this is good
right yeah
i like more of these
well i mean you'd quit your job so they
got to take up your shift
what are these actual goals golly
quite lucky
your chest will be mine callie no
no you can't know what your
does anybody in the chat know the name
of the glasses that the inna's character
has
i don't i can't oh my god
weapons where's your boy
these are like those are like the dice
that i used in in dungeons and dragons
right
yeah that's right they do kind of look
like they look like
they feel like maybe oh well it's not
below your enemy's tank and force them
into the water below
oh no i see okay
aim shoot left right all right all right
that's right
oh good world of
tanks okay ready
it's manageable it's easy enough
cali yeah okay
duh how do you never mind hey
oh my gosh i can't even
where am i where am i oh i blew myself
up
a lot i'm just gonna i'm just gonna
stop it
[Music]
oh sorry just kidding
oh
fascinating all right will you get to
the chat yeah
of course not no i went the wrong way
rocket thank you could see
that all right i came back to life
wait nice
how do you use the items just like offer
to use them at the start
i don't know
all right give me those keys
but the side coverage all right here we
go
she's running oh i'm angry
what does that uh the skull do please
tell us
i have no clue actually oh
maybe the present christmas i don't know
what it was
nice lucky hmm
is this a full time
i think i can hear myself yeah you have
full health
you see the number underneath your
placement like the fifth place
ah that
hey
[Music]
oh
there's actually a eurobeat version of
hinotori my song
i want to hear that mm-hmm
oh yes oh yes
[Music]
drifting sucks i suck at it sucks if
you're bad
[Music]
i
oh no i'm stuck
no smell you later look here is the
first looks like yeah
out of nowhere go down
oh no am i going the wrong way yep
[Laughter]
guys oh i had a 50 50 chance on that one
huh wait why am i all the way back at
the beginning did you win
i don't know i have to i'm going around
again oh yeah
me too oh
oh my god oh please no i'm going to
throw up
kelly it's you versus me huh no
okay i'm one first now all right but for
how long
uh that's kind of relaxing oh my god
these controls
i mean i think that's the point but it
is unfortunate
not a way
[Music]
dude i have no clue no but it's also
about not
running into obstacles and it says four
for me five for cali
three two three four amen
i guess there's five laps oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank you oh
oh oh it's a little too short does that
ring yeah
no no no i just punched the cowboy
oh what a shame or crying shame
[Music]
the turns are interesting i think it
goes by like the
mini game like who who gets the most
keys or who's in like first
second place and stuff
no oh never mind i can a remote
controlled
explosive eggplant
explosive eggplant one two three
uh what i want keys or bullet i want
keys
yeah you know it's the one
that doesn't know oh yes
is that a bunker
[Music]
all right i gotta use both hands for
this shoot
okay so you just play with like keyboard
and mouse no not mouse just keyboard
this keyboard i see it i'm not good at
shooting
it's gonna be fun wait okay
there i go i died did you crash yeah i
crashed right into the ground for you
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no yeah
it just like does it automatically i
have yet to see oh it's going straight
[Music]
not just me doing sudoku
and they respond do you have to stop
there or is it also but just by walking
by at one time
no you have to stop
[Music]
[Laughter]
karma all right max max max roll
one we have a gun oh a four
can i use the gun okay
yeah dang it you have a little item bar
at the bottom
tactical cactus disguise where cactus
disguise protecting you from the next
damaged instance and top portal
and i want items i'll cactuses up ah
[Music]
you're good cowboy you're awfully quiet
over there wait if kelly's voice
does ahmed also explode
oh
[Music]
like this
but once you captured a field that no
one else can take it
oh sorry i was reading the i don't know
i didn't know
what wait a minute huh okay nevermind
all right well you can't run on bears i
see
i don't think so i don't think so you
gotta secure off your perimeter
you know it's wild god
i can't even say happens between hard to
see
yeah mine is pretty similar to calories
unfair
[Music]
the eyes that cali chose looks like
glasses i just got
sunglasses shades okay one step this way
hi please don't hurt me oh no
you can only do it at the start of your
turn
smile
[Music]
drop it be happy to damage other people
but where do i drop it
wrecking ball i came in like a sorry
from seemingly nowhere and takes out
your target
interesting but like is it can i oh
oh i can use it on anyone
something about that so yeah oh this
[Music]
game
gee i like how all three of us are in
the room
howdy sheriff oh i see the shotgun
listen don't do this g please
wait what do i wait what do i do i get
keys out of it if i show you right
i think so you just lowered their uh hp
probably
maybe some keys share
him but it is holding on to some cheese
yeah we can only go forward huh really
the no hard feelings wait can i shoot it
up
yeah sure you gotta try
no
i didn't know you were gonna kill her
yeah yeah oh wow
sorry you know i didn't think it was
gonna be that bad
let's see paint taco
she's plotting and i know that's why
she's quiet
that's why she's so quiet
i love it i don't know i can't swim i
can't swim
this is like in the playstation game
this is the level with the dragon
you get to ride yeah
for wizards big bets who's gonna die
first oh
buttons
[Music]
oh yeah yeah oh that was early
they planned for a lot more it seems
like
a real gamer again
you're winning too much
she was a wizard before maybe yeah
[Music]
isn't that something that you're used to
yes
i'm not complaining
can you like not go to the oh oh no
what what what happened drowned
because you can't swim
oh come on wait so let's just
it's karma oh gosh
i want to get really far away from here
real quick
collateral doesn't really look like it i
would hit myself probably because i'm
worried maybe i want to go
but she's going to die anyway next turn
but
it is in second place look at all her
keys she has yeah but she's gonna be
she's gonna die from the water though
yeah that's true
hush let's do something about the
upcomer who's making me very nervous
yeah oh my god
fine okay let's go let's go
i'm gonna get you back for that kiara
looking forward to it but um no matter
if you kill me i'll just get back up
again
am i gonna i know the best like and
don't start remember that
oh you only lost it go go go go go go
yeah yeah i should have used an item
all right what items do i have
uh oh sheriff no no
i can't even be angry
[Laughter]
sensor how could you the betrayal i hate
this
this is not a real shoe that's a lot of
damage
hey that blasted me off to the graveyard
going
i see it shows you though in the
interface in the very bottom left
and the beginning of your turn oh i see
did the people who made pommel party did
they make
tabs does it look simple i think
something
this reminds me of when eno was playing
here and she was doing the hacking level
oh yeah oh that's messed up buddy
oh there's they thought that was someone
else
that's nice i just hate it
why does it keep on changing come on
oh
yeah i'm dead
oh can you push people
i don't think so
oh
[Music]
the flood is over oh i want to use an
item
you have so many open this present to
find out what's inside have you been
good or bad i don't know maybe
give me present please open i've been
good
[Music]
damn it now i'm so far away what is this
oh this is this
explosion exactly
what would you like me to steal i still
don't have a single one of those fields
everyone else but me has one all right
let's see use item
uh-oh what does this do eggplant remote
control explosive eggplant move towards
your target and detonate
you've been good or bad wrecking ball
comes out stimuli north
and it takes out your target
now listen we can talk about this we can
talk about this
i spared your life ma'am you did you did
you owe you one
uh ma'am oh
i had to do it too i had to do it to him
no hard feelings though now you're going
to roll cowboy
you're right okay
gimme
how do you look at the map i keep
forgetting to use my items
you i get anything that goes there no
oh why don't you get keys taken from you
is this random what are you doing
me hmm no oh that was my space
oh oh i see
where is it raise the chest
the
there's only a couple places where it
can be so oh
okay well i still have one item
that i i'm i'm very low uh i'm only
fourth so i got it i got a fight
oh that's a good one it's an aoe yeah
but i think everyone is far away from me
yeah maybe not now
[Music]
okay let's go let's go let's go let's go
let's go
oh oh
everyone's getting pummeled
what does that even mean is that an
actual english oil yeah
yeah it means to kind of like beat up
someone oh
in german it means like uh someone who's
fat
wait what what nice
um what is this game what
i'm not going to win this one this will
be something
hey what the hell huh wait i was still
alive
where am i oh
just in general you just die eventually
it's just how many hits in you can get
out run into walls or what
what oh what is this
dude i don't even know what's going on
uh revenge what
target inaudible
no oh
[Music]
what does it do it sends you forward
like more movement oh yeah
she's going on a trip
everyone's getting beat up
are you planning something what you can
do
okay
dang it sorry guys but you have a gift
maybe you
oh
ah so you can choose one that you're
good at if you know the actual
game oh that's true yeah i
see his boat oh just kidding
i guess i'll die all right um
nice i actually want their blood
[Music]
what you gonna do gonna
you better not be thinking about using
any items song
oh she's she's switching places with
someone
oh oh nice yeah
but everybody doesn't have enough keys
and she does though don't doesn't it
always cost 40.
it might go up every time how do you use
it how do i
enter go yes i think it's escape
i don't trust you the way you said that
is a little
cute i think hughes is cute i'll kill
you you
[Laughter]
i know her tricks don't worry
wait a minute is this something that we
want girl already has one chalice he
once had none
god damn it bamboozled
sorry i just have to win this oh
morphing maze how cute
here comes the part of the game where we
beat each other up
[Music]
oh it changes yes that's what the
morphing means
change quick god damn it
[Music]
this is really cute
oh
[Music]
is there really no key left there has to
be some
[Music]
oh oh hello
i
[Music]
oh am oh man i'm kind of scared
a remote controlled explosive eggplant
mhm your target then detonate
let's see remember you're going first
though we'll go after you
if i take everyone oh oh
[Music]
okay low roll low roll
oh no i'm scared of kira's shotgun
yeah should be
a good noodle have you been good have
you been a good man
[Applause]
he's
[Music]
oh no oh someone didn't check them up
though
there's no reason to use that okay
six
[Music]
[Laughter]
what does
[Music]
wait you're summoning something it's
soggy what is that
it's a rabbit it's you're in the ground
now it's a lucky rabbit
yeah what does it do oh just wait
[Applause]
and kill you that's awesome
monty python bunny oh that's why she
wants sale
she needs to get put into jail again
ride your whiteboard
oh you trapped people you wanna
do donuts and trap people ah
wait i'm not i'm not sure if
okay don't do it to yourself either you
can do it to yourself
oh i didn't have to do anything please
there we go
okay
come on
[Laughter]
i forgot about that round three
go right
that looks way fancy i didn't even think
we just all picked up
i'll win again finally my first win
oh this is happening what's happening
some something appeared i don't know
what
oh present uh
let's see what's inside have you been a
good chicken
always thank you tomorrow's mother's day
and i'm everyone's mom
oh
bye my chest bye bye ah give me oh
no no no give me no no no
and i have enough hey yeah yeah yeah
so nice what do i have a wrecking ball
eggplant practical cactus disguise
okay oh not this
thanks thank you
that should be okay to just roll wait
[Music]
wait actually it's not tomorrow for me
it's already today
mother's day oh no death
use item what's this
that's protecting you from the next
damage instance and swap
portals cannot use other items while
cactus i'm a
i want to be a cactus
[Laughter]
[Music]
and they're full of water and i love
water you can eat cactus right
yeah i think if you take out the prickly
parts that's fiber though it's good for
you
oh am i going for the safe route
i use a map again use the rocket
oh god the ancient ones compel you
[Music]
better
very nice they're nice y'all are good at
these kinds of games
there's only four turns left too or like
three turns though
yeah where's the next one oh it's in the
it's in the water
damn it why didn't i just stay in the
i'm close
i'm such
oh god what the heck was that why didn't
you
oh
[Music]
no
believe in yourself
oh
[Music]
all right sheriff all right full house
holy cow nice pretty sixties anna holy
cute
oh no sheriff you had the red
she had the perfect dang it
how do i aim and now you have the other
one
now where's there
another cactus oh what
i got another cactus can i get this
that's all i care about for a gift
um good taco i'll see
have i been a good taco today
oh and she's gone
to the shadow she's in the void
what this doesn't stop you from getting
your keys taken away
oh yeah uh
is watson and everybody
i'm in the shout out
i'll just roll okay
she's rolling with it oh
nice
i'm coming for that chest
you're gonna die though no
[Music]
[Laughter]
uh one two three oh okay you know you're
just sitting in the box i wonder
yeah she's in time
the days in the uh the refrigerator
what's up
[Music]
in the seafood section of the year uh oh
i was like like red
i see it's like you want a hot potato
ah tomato potatoes
yeah yeah the tiles get destroyed every
lightning oh okay
you gotta run okay who's oh yeah
society
[Laughter]
[Music]
she's trapping us in oh
[Applause]
[Music]
running away until the end but if i have
to shoot at the end then i'm
it's over but i can survive very long
yes oh
wait somebody's gotta stop watching
i'm gonna keep those for now
let's go somewhere okay
will you be tossed in the chest is over
there oh wait but
i think you'll land past the chest i
think so yeah uh-huh
oh is it um always like past the chest
or just like somewhere on the
other side on the face it's always the
same thing yeah for your land
um okay whatever no i'm just gonna i'm
i'm someone's
gonna get it before me probably anyway
i'm still stuck in a box
[Music]
it's a little cramped in here and i'm
never mind i don't have anything damn
yeah
[Music]
like coming back and snapping back to
reality
what did you see did you see the light
or only darkness
that's fine i have a lot of health
if you're not careful she's going to
have first place because she has yeah
what's the keys that i
do but you're number one but if you're
not good
you
[Music]
you don't even have a proper tail you
don't have a shotgun
pee on your bed
[Music]
yes that's what a real cat will do i
can't i can't
okay i need to calm my heart down a
little bit sorry
you're welcome chad
oh my heart oh no
speech oh my goodness a hundred okay
oh no just a little short oh there she
goes okay
[Laughter]
let's see what items they got always the
same
let me be clear this is a little rabbit
yeah kind of terrifying this is just
chilling is that fun
i dare you let's see
no it doesn't really matter too much
i was petting
if you don't want to end up a bit crispy
you will need to keep track of your
player in the dark while dodging the
steering spotlights lastly you're
standing wins
feisty i don't understand what i just
read
don't get spotted stay out of the
spotlight ah okay okay thank you
it's actually police helicopters you
want to go into the spotlight because
that's like you you're on stage
it's even idle music yeah
i wish i knew where i was oh my god oh
oh this is my tactic chef get out of
here
no my quarter
oh my god
nice music
[Music]
in the car did you see it yeah that was
dope
look at that skirlington oh beautiful
oh no thanks for coming to the concert
is there only one parent left oh my god
[Music]
oh man it's neck and neck ah
damn it i thought it was in first oh
okay
oh unreal unreal monkeys
unreal engine it's cool i'm happy to be
in a cactus
no reason to use any of these i really
want to use my shotgun
see there we go
[Music]
i forget where the chest is go
to the right
oh no she's on to me
thanks for inadvertently telling me
which way
oh you're pretty close oh yeah damn
yeah nice i think i understand why i
have the least keys
um do you guys see that i got locked out
of my apartment yesterday
yesterday the day before this weekend
yeah yeah
how did it feel i forgot kelly
oh that's my knees inside at the moment
first time i realized
at the exact moment when i closed the
door i was like oh
what happened to me because your name is
kingi ara
you'd have some oh and it's like i don't
know i lost my keys
anyway what the hell man i'm sorry
so anyway i started
there she goes it's only one turn left
anyways so i'm like
gotta gotta let it all out
she's right
that didn't really change anything
anyway okay
what's this the last turn yeah
any last words detective
oh i'm still going to win anyways
[Music]
that's the spirit
please she got
[Laughter]
all right let's see what do i got
i'm useless right now deadweights
[Laughter]
[Music]
well we gotta try it out
okay who got the potato under the united
are you got the potato
where's everybody else you guys are
hiding i
i saw you know okay
come here
i dropped it it
oh
[Laughter]
i see
oh
i'm dead
[Music]
up
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
present
[Music]
explosion it's under launching
and she's going to get out of the
kitchen
felt good to do oh she's flying over
here nice
take her kitties oh is it kelly
[Music]
gonna be maybe it'll be there's gonna be
chance
it's the final turn you can you can
dream
oh you still haven't rolled i'm
i'm not there oh cute
all right let's see
um damn
i think i just have to hope for the best
but hope i roll low i guess
i need four keys
wait no i don't
[Laughter]
hey watson yeah
you'll get what's coming to you it's the
last garden bread
celeste my god
what you doing in here
[Laughter]
i think you get them back though oh
dynamite still one
okay oh i'm gonna die
um you can't go to the canyon
oh oh glorious
ten keys we're gonna get the keys
yeah you're gonna get your keys if you
get one more key then
oh yeah yeah yeah no take her out
well i'm the last one maybe i can do
something
i can shoot what's that is that nuclear
waste barrel
yeah what is that what i just oh this is
multiple
turns though
does this go does someone know how far
the magnet goes
you can see that's my next shot you
don't have a magnet do you
oh oh it looked like i had it okay oh
wait
nuclear waste battle poor nuclear waste
on another way of loading their hands
and head
preventing them from using items oh no
that's useless
okay well um yeah there's nothing i can
do
except becoming a cactus
yeah i'm cactus that's what i do there's
one more game
oh yeah one more mini game i like the
minigames actually this
is kind of fun a little scuffed but fun
well present
i can't really do it
okay now what can i use um
nah kelly's soul health is not worse
don't waste your giggles
all right can you get the thing for me
buddy
can you do it for me oh useless
i think this i guess this is the end
this is this is the end ladies
awards therapy points
[Music]
welcome
oh
she might be in first place now she got
a challenge she is
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
um
[Music]
what it feels to be a winner like yeah
all right
all right look at my case i'm the
sheriff
let me out it's okay we'll party with
you right here
we'll bring a party to you
[Music]
hey what is this
okay come here
please make me a knight i'm the sheriff
[Laughter]
also should we make our announcement now
yeah i don't know we have time for yeah
i guess we should
do it let's do it announcement who's
we ready an announcement everybody are
you excited can i get it let's go
let's go let's go let's go let's go
all
take right away kelly okay good ads you
have the thumbnail
i'm ready okay so guys
it's hollow live it why is okay we're
fine
english
have been waiting for this for a while
um but we have to announce that hololive
hololive english myths first cover song
is coming out on the 15th of may
what song could it be take me home
it's country at 10 a.m jst on the
official hololive
english channel so make sure you check
it out and you're there for the premiere
thank you for the beautiful artwork yeah
hi thank you yeah i hope you guys
anticipate it
yeah look forward to it yeah we've been
wanting to show it to you guys for a
long time so a really long time
a really really long time so hopefully
hopefully things will go smooth
and uh we can all enjoy the premiere
together i can't wait yeah i don't even
remember
when i recorded this
[Music]
the day i think it was it was like
october it was oh
so we're very excited to be sharing it
with you all
um and yeah please anticipate it look
forward to it
same thing that i just said right there
pass the ox
yeah blast it in your home but don't
annoy your neighbors too much unless
they also really like hole alive and in
that case
them down the rabbit hole yes yes
but don't be too forceful but still you
know
all right then everybody yeah i think
that
i guess that's it if anybody else has
anything they'd like to
shout it out now
on the day of my outfit reveal and on my
channel i released
a song cover as well a song covered with
gouda
yeah yeah i could about free
yeah a lot of work was put into that
especially the music video everyone who
watched it was
i gave really nice feedback so if you
haven't watched it yet
what why why why why it's really amazing
and actually there's a cameo
of every other i don't know if you all
of you guys watched it but
uh you were also in the music video yeah
all of you yup
it's very cute it's really cute super
cute
my first a cover with uh laguna
so please check out my channel if you
want to listen to it
you know yes
anybody else um
let's see i had i had two things
okay first of all guys for my birthday
merch
you guys have approximately one more day
to order the birthday birthday it comes
with um
it comes with uh dakimakura and a big
poster that's actually hanging in my
room right now
um and three cute buttons and then also
you get a voice pack and a special
edition
vinyl
yeah the artwork is very beautiful it's
the artwork from
my album cover i think that you guys
will enjoy it
at least having it in your in your home
to hang it up somewhere even if you
can't actually play
it it's going to be a very nice looking
record so i recommend and then
um yeah you guys got to get on that
because there's one there's one day left
to get it before it goes away forever
um forever yeah i mean i
i would really love to release things
individually someday but i just don't
know if i can
yet because it's not a sure thing i'm
just recommending it to you guys now as
much as i would like to make it happen
it's kind of out of my hands we'll see
what happens in the future though
um and then the next announcement i have
is me and erica senpai's original
song spiral tones
yeah yeah original song we wrote an
original song together and it's gonna be
on
rika senpai's channel um we're actually
having a collab
together on that same day which is
tomorrow actually we're doing we're
playing a game we're playing super bunny
man together
[Music]
and then we're going to premiere the
song and also
there's an event going on for the song a
campaign
if you will so you guys can get involved
with the song
in in your own creative way if you get
what i'm saying so stay tuned for that
no yeah okay give the video lots of love
that's really exciting wait an original
though
yeah yeah an original mm-hmm that's our
original collab
yup so we both worked really hard on it
hope you guys will enjoy it
um go check it out watch the premieres
it's happening i'm going to be there
hope you guys are there too
yeah that's all i had to say hi thank
you
[Music]
bye
a draw festival but that's in a couple
weeks so
oh oh um
after my birthday oh what is that
birthday 20th is my birthday
please look forward to it
so excited birthday taco
birthday i'll get a taco salad for my
birthday
[Music]
what would that even taste like okay
i guess that's all from us
thank you guys for unless you have
anything watson
no um no okay thank you guys for coming
and watching us play
pomo party and thank you for the support
the big surprise and then oh this week
maybe yeah a little bit this week like
it was really exciting
thank you everybody for watching all of
our outfit reviews yeah
it's a lot of fun it's super hype like
having all the events and stuff so thank
you for watching us and supporting us
exactly throughout the week everyone did
like their streams in such a unique and
interesting way like special to them
i thought it was so cool everyone really
shined like during their streams i think
i didn't have a dull moment
in anyone's streams they were all
fantastic you guys killed it
and i love your outfits you're all cute
af
love you guys curious
so nice everyone has my outfits now i
was waiting for this
big hype for life fashion week
yes it was so fun
[Music]
yeah so i guess that's all huh i'm gonna
go to sleep after this
good night yeah three hours of sleep
but you know what it's worth it to play
games with you guys yeah anytime um
yeah world of darkness it's gonna be
interesting i think at the least it'll
be interesting
thank you
[Music]
streamlined
you