[Music]
n
a
[Music]
n
hey
KY y
KY
[Music]
hello
oh it's so
beautiful this goddamn bgm is just too
beautiful I can't help it
how you guys
[Music]
doing
[Laughter]
[Music]
hi
hi thanks for the right Super Chat P
thank you we're playing
again sky
today the hat is put in place where it's
still a little bit too big a little
bit this is perfect size if only I
wouldn't move so much
let me move
myself over here there we go perfect
where's my controller although I still
don't have I still don't have joycons
man I still don't have like I mean this
is great but I I need
joycons
joycons can you imagine like with these
with these controllers you know you see
how the the thums are continuous moving
can you imagine someone like animating
joycon assets and like having to move
around like this the whole
time you have to do it like that
otherwise it doesn't suit my fighting
style cuz I legit like when when I fight
when I use my joycons and Skyward Sword
I go
like I panic all the time
man I panic so
much today today I would like to you
know relax a little bit and be calm with
okay I want to be careful with
okay
K and just calm F attack everything in
front of
me just got to be careful careful yeah
careful with
K careful K come careful
k H that's
me good luck with
[Laughter]
[Music]
that softly with Grace yes graceful with
a K
Grace calm
careful
graceful pinky
no
gracefully graceful
graceful yes yes yes well well well I
also got my chalky milk I wonder if I
can wait let me let me go toasu real
quick and find me some chalky milk
chalky
milk CH Mir let's see if we find
something no only a bar of chocolate I'm
not going to drink drink a bar of
chocolate
Cho choco no choco uh caca
caca IA if I type that in then it should
find it that's how they usually call it
okay nope what if I just write in
CA there we go it looks
hot
hot uh looks like
coffee H this is the only thing I can
find M let me put an ice cube in
it h Co
c
c let me just put ice cubes in it and
then you'll get the
gist and a straw or a good idea ice
CU oh nice okay perfect and the straw h
stoo
I no that's that's
no
[Music]
a think I have to use this
one do it like that make it small and
then cut some off and then put it like
there Perfect Look at that y
[Laughter]
[Music]
self selfmade ice coca would you guys
like to
[Laughter]
try you guys want a sip let me give you
a sip hi there you go slurp
[Music]
please oh yeah we have a drinking emote
we have a drinking emote Now's the Time
to use
[Music]
it I reminds you of a song If a Japanese
song
[Music]
thank you for the membership welcome
Exquisite my emotes don't work and it's
just so annoying why does stuff like
that never work I don't get it I don't
understand this actually looks like ice
coffee with a straw but who drinks iced
coffee with a
straw wait never mind actually I guess a
lot of people
do I guess a lot of people
do I'm just not a coffee drinker it
wasn't my
first
thought I was just looking at this thing
and wondering who drinks with a straw
out of a mug and that's just I've never
seen that before I think
and when I close the stream today I'll
probably the stream will probably be
something between 5 to 8 hours oh and
since you are a Korean bro let me tell
you I have to I I said yesterday that
I'll do my Korean dual lingo stream on
Monday but actually so um the whole
permission deadline thing has become
very strict uh these days and and um uh
um so some let me explain to you guys so
you understand a little bit but some
games for some games we have to ask full
permission free work days ahead and I
didn't think that Duolingo was one of
them uh but yeah and free working days
um in
jst so also got to consider the time uh
Zone as well the time difference and and
Japanese holidays have to be considered
as
well uh so yeah yeah I know with duing I
know it's weird I wouldn't have expected
that and also with dingo we even have to
have the stream uh already on on like a
reservation already 3 days ahead so
anyway it's not going to happen on
Monday because it's it is first day
today
but it's still kind of too late to ask
for permission so I have to do it on a
different day and du lingo
Korean language not not
[Laughter]
Monday
[Music]
uh
okay
uh uh doing do
[Music]
lingo I will study
Korean
language
on a different
[Laughter]
day
[Music]
okay thank you Google son thank you so H
with that said we will play uh a million
hours of Skyward swore today yeah are
you guys ready for some Skyward Sword I
got snacks here too H snacks snackles I
got a sandwich and I got uh uh I got
chocolate cookies chocolate cookies one
short
[Music]
stream
for okay okay let's get this started uh
also I picked up something from the post
office
today um the the presents not the I
think not the letters but the presents
that I received at doam me at least part
of it
arrived so um I I brought that to my
apartment uh today uh before the stream
let's
[Music]
go happy birthday so chat oh happy
birthday I will read it properly uh
later on I hope uh we're here because uh
we uh I got tired of finishing the
dungeon was there anything else I wanted
to do in the city we can do it now
before I go back into the
[Music]
dungeon same
time let finish the third dungeon what
have you got there to drink Mrs bird um
is it not obvious I tried it could be
either IC coffee or ice cocoa but I
don't drink coffee so it's ice
coca hello should I buy something
a gratitude gr oh yeah I've never
actually like given them to the dude uh
I have to bring them to some dude
right where the hell is he again I
[Music]
forgot is he like somewhere around the
graveyard take your wood shield with you
oh why why n graveyard
okay is this is this what I what I see
here is this the famous
wait a
[Music]
second is this the famous drifting
feature that the joycons have or is it
just me shaking insanely y
it cuz I've heard that joy-cons start to
drift or tend to
[Music]
drift I'm just
shaking okay I I the stick is uh does
does the drifting not H wait so why did
I why should I bring my uh wooden
Shield why is that better in this
situation analog is drifting
[Laughter]
off iron is bad
a okay I'll switch
it oh what kind of voice did I do for
this dude I don't remember at
all I don't
[Music]
remember wait a second wait a second
shut
my
uh oh yeah like like that like that I
think oh you've gathered quite a lot of
Gratitude Crystals haven't you how
magnificent please take this as a token
of this Demon's deepest
[Music]
appreciation you have the med a
wallet uh the Hefty capacity oh of this
wallet allows you to store up to 500
rupees in it
all I'm still going to need more GR
crystals to become human please want you
AE a poor unfortunate demon in
me gracious me that is a prodigous
quantity of GRA crystals you've brought
for me oh another one this is such an
appallingly insufficient reward that my
cheeks burn hot with embarassment but
please take
[Music]
this
I'm still going to need more gra
crystals to become human please want
you shut
up oh okay okay sound like a
h hey nice nice nice we got a we got a
new heart container
bye-bye
bye-bye 10 out of 10 voice acting yeah
but this for this one I only pushed a
button not much that I have to do so I
wouldn't really praise myself for
that let's go up
hi nice
butt no just kidding he doesn't really
have a specifically nice butt I would
have to you know see him in a swimsuit
or something like that which I don't
want to do I'm not interested in him
okay um so uh switch to wooden shield
and then we go
[Music]
back the wild
link yeah he's I mean and face wise I
guess it's just you know the art style
that looks a little bit weird on his
face cuz like I think I think what
bothers me about his face is that he
looks like um he got injections in his
lip in his upper
lip I think that's what looks off to
me and um the the things under his eyes
that are supposed to be like like like
not eye bags I know what it's supposed
to be but it looks like like he has he
looks just
[Music]
old
molded
clay my I think the breath of the wild
uh link is pretty damn hot yeah uh okay
H item lady
[Music]
hello
ah it we to uh
switch okay and we got two empty bottles
we could bring oh we could bring
a one of the potions which one should we
get M maybe
one this one was for health and for the
shield
right heart and
shield we haven't before
four four hides yeah I guess why not
let's take that
[Music]
one ble we're going to be using the
shield a lot more today I hope I want
to I want to use the shield more often
instead of running away like a panicking
chicken and then I want maybe this
[Music]
one and normal heart potion eight hearts
yeah
remember to go to Beetle who the hell is
Beetle again and what why do I want to
go
there can also upgrade the Potions by
talking to husband
oh I think the potions are fine except
maybe the shield one could give me more
Hearts than four at a flying shop why do
I want to go there should I buy
something what what do I want to buy
from him let's we don't need an upgrade
right now we're fine we're fine
[Music]
where is the
shop that
[Music]
sign I think I saw it but I got to go
from this
side a wallet upgrade I think right now
my wallet is pretty damn
[Music]
big he Nice
Shot come down come down like
Rapunzel rapun
[Music]
last that's an interesting way to write
that German swearing in
Japanese ah
heart yo why do you have that dude
oh wait life medal he means that's a
heart container
no wait a second was that another a
heart
container heart heart
container heart challeng 800 I actually
have enough money for that life model
metal
what a hardner that it takes up one slot
oh I don't know I guess I don't want
that m you don't know what about this
thing what was that
again what should I
buy what is that
again oh I think I want
that cuz we are lacking space yeah yeah
did you race price
oh unbelievable
unbelievable oh my God
okay yeah you're are welcome I guess
also um did you guys see I think he has
nipples it's just very satisfying to see
male nipples right
[Laughter]
now we're always looking for those male
nipples humans have those yes no that's
not what I'm saying it's it's like in
other
jrpgs male characters often don't have
[Music]
nipples yeah I don't know I don't know
why all right shall we
go oh wait from here where should I go
from
here uh how do I fly again
sh that was
[Applause]
close Mario has nipples in say
okay where are we going which light is
it the red one is it yeah no wait this
one this
one oh yellow light this
[Music]
one I always forget how to write this
these things
go go go go why this feels so nice
woo
y let's
[Music]
go wait wait we could check out a chest
we could check out that wait we have
three chests there to check out wait no
change of
plant
[Music]
uh that one is wait which
one over there I think right
no over over over there that one should
we fall into the hole no it's it's right
there it's right there ch ch ch ch chill
chill oh oh my
God we made
it open up
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh another
hold oh okay more Hearts will appear I
guess like when I kill mobs and stuff
but wait does that take up one spot in
my Adventura uh
pouch it does o that's kind of lame so
if I open up the other Treasure Chest
right now and they have an item that's
for the adventure pouch I might not even
be able to pick it
up should I go back to skyloft
once it goes to Stars automatically if
it's okay
ni what a service that
is let's take that and put one there and
take that and put one there okay
[Music]
go don't fly into the
tornado there must be a star well I hope
so I hope they don't make it over
complicated
[Music]
[Applause]
it feels
good
y about the way whole talk this this
week is not even that much to prepare I
think because except for the questions
obviously but how I's not going to use
the stage
she didn't want to use the stage so I
don't have to edit like a whole thing
again I think I think hatama was like
flustered when I sent her the whole wall
of
information like you could do this you
could do that after already sending her
all the information of what what else I
need like the thumbnail and the video
and all
that it's not going to to do live
cooking no I don't think so but if you
want to see her do some live cooking
just go to her Channel she does that a
lot and I'm actually going to do that
next week too
yeah so I've decided to make like a like
a pretty PDF file instead of sending a
tech a text wall on Discord and I'm
going to do a PDF file of like images
and stuff that going to it's going to
look like what's the word
for
just so that you
know
just so that it doesn't like scare
you off when you receive the wall of
text after being accepted into whole
[Music]
talk a no that's not
it
there we go now
e every time what is this it's it's
probably underneath
here
uh
okay uh oops
uh okay I would also love to talk about
the whole how aai hat became Hat story
but I feel like hat wants to stay in
character so I'm not sure how much we're
actually going to get out of that she
probably takes this whole thing very
serious oh
nice I'll I'll try to get something out
of there but we we will have to wait and
see prepared for the
madness
[Music]
just gon to say like what who is that
who is what never heard of her she did
that last time wait I opened that
before ah it's not there I missed it I
did she did that before when I was with
her in the meme uh R meme reveiew right
I was like and she was
like what are you talking about
Tak is this
thing up
here
[Music]
what up
higher the door no
here ah
so okay I got it
oh oh ah nope it's not going to
work cuz I I have to
land uh up there huh I can't get there
from here so jump
again
God is she in the
room it would be so funny to have like
both of them sitting on the
couch yeah I'm just really bad at
controlling the sail clo as well where
is it where is it do
do wait where am I where am
I no I want to
chill
I'm just going to try
now oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
nice nice good wonderful Landing
couldn't have been
[Music]
better oh another one we're just missing
one
[Applause]
more
woohoo ah
[Music]
nice okay let's go to the
dungeon over there the yellow
one fourth chest on Sky
LOF you're saying there's
a
another heart container in the
sky one more
[Music]
H why does it feel so
slow fly
[Music]
faster big red heart big red heart mama
big red
heart
big
red beig R hide a beig r
hide one active chest in the sky
[Music]
Loft
really
[Music]
Doo angle down go fast oh yeah I know I
know
even the in the bazaar or near oh did I
unlock it
really well I might want to check it out
[Music]
then ah Free
Fall what if we land on oh we
can't I want to land on the
bazaar Bazar
did I not already get the chest uh
that's in the bazaar or did I just look
at
it is it here ah okay no this one is not
activated then there was another
one I have no idea where where you're
saying that one is
[Music]
though check the map oh wait there's one
over there but that one also is not
unlocked ah that
one in in cia's house no somewhere
like on the other side oh yeah I can't
get that one but it's on the map you
mean the other one
right you mean the other
[Music]
one
is it in
here need to swim on the water
oh
okay okay well then we'll fly to the na
desert let's
go
myself why we're going again to the
yellow one right yes turn
around fly under the sky L
[Music]
oo
yeah can we can we can we for once try
to fly through one of those holes up
there
no no way I can do it
uh I feel like I'm wasting more time but
try get
first I
can't I cannot do
it seems like it's impossible for me
it's too
small it's too narrow we should make it
bigger
[Music]
okay let's go we have reached the hole
in the
sky
uh uh George where I we go this is is
this where
the uh dungeon is should we go to desert
George
North okay
so I wanted to go to
George sorry I wasn't you had to do that
for me my dear uh whatever name your
name was
Fe it's hot in this desert actually not
a we should save
once cuz we got a heart container and
other
[Music]
stuff my my hat you mean my helmet no
I'm not wearing my helmet today we're
done with that
uh there it
is I'm back I'm
back
Mas helmet are gu it's over oh no all
the mobs
respawned should have seen that coming
fight ah might have been
[Music]
fine oh where are we last
time very far think I don't even
remember this place uh should we go from
the side I don't even have to do
that did all
[Music]
reset
bumps can I use this one too does it
have to be
the iron
one let me
try
switch no you can play the switch
version without motion control but I
tried that too thinking that motion
control will not be enjoyable but the
motion control in this game is way
better than playing it with the Pro
Controller because it's the game is just
made for this
purpose
so yeah they they developed it with the
thought of using motion
control it's not going to work otherwise
I think we kind of stopped here
no I think this is where we stopped I
came through that door and then I was
like uh I'm going to end it here so we
got to going to get over there but that
looks like a crazy long
[Music]
desert oh it has paths like outside okay
and a treasure chest over
there strange should we can we Mark
anything no we can't we cannot Mark
anything can I walk here
yes
um wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait
wait where's my where's my where's my
where's my
[Music]
shield where's my
shield
oh there we go
okay ah wait wait wait let me kill you
[Music]
first ah not sure about that nope nope
no oh no I missed again I'm so bad at
this uh
[Music]
okay now where see bowling training yeah
I need to play We bowling
[Music]
again
ooh little hole got to turn into little
[Music]
Bales got to turn into Bales be a rat go
through these
tunnels what is there what
nothing how are you today Cara I'm doing
fine I woke up and
um I had to clean my kitchen immediately
and uh uh made my my cat's
toilet cleaned that and then I went to
the post office and then I went to the
supermarket and then I did some research
on hatama clips that I want to use for
whole talk and all of that in like 3
hours so I was like a little bit
stressed out but here we are I also had
breakfast so that's
that
yeah kind of busy yeah because I knew
today would be a hella long
stream got to get some things done
before
[Music]
that always inspire me with how
organized you are well you kind of have
to when you got so much on your
plate and kind of you're forced to be
organized you know I I I he didn't I
originally was not such an organized
person but now I have to
be so I don't have yumy yumy
yum I don't have much choice
okay
uh ni
okay okay okay
chill
can I blow you away
no it's like let's go
okay we did we did
well go over
[Music]
there
freak okay here we go now we blow that
away again cuz there's another hole
another hole and one of these things
when they when they're on their back
like that they're kind of
[Music]
cute
no quick sand yeah quick sand is even
worse than normal
sand
thanks for being my background noise
you're welcome thanks for being here on
my stream B your would
[Music]
work was that smart to go through that
oh oh should should I have gone that way
first I I don't remember what there what
what was on that other
side guess we're going to go through
here it's a lot of sand oh de oh dear oh
dear let's play a little bit of uh
Luigi's
Mansion although it makes no sense
because it seems like we're sucking it
in but we're actually just blowing it
away but it disappears
it makes no
[Music]
sense makes no
sense
acknowledging what what is underneath
all this sand just some
[Music]
coins
oh yeah B
oh oh no no no no no no no no no
no explos
nice Mama enjoyed the stream yesterday
oh she was very very very excited
afterwards you know I told you that she
was probably already sleeping while I
was doing the Super Chat reading
but turns out she wasn't I think she
just got some food afterwards and then
stayed awake cuz she said she was was
just so excited at at 2:30 a.m. or
something like
that uh she and when I was like chilling
in
bed what ah when I was chilling in in
bed at almost 3:00 a.m. I checked my
messages and my mom was just wrote to me
like oh I really can't sleep tonight
what do I want
that uh maybe instead of the heart
po I'll take it
again let's go yep
okay yeah but I I understand that like
after such an exciting stream uh I
understand that she was like too excited
to fall asleep and she said um
at at
2:30 a.m. she wrote to me like oh man
now I'm so excited I can't sleep I got
to watch the whole stream again cuz I
want to read the
comments so she probably was awake until
what 4:00 a.m. or something I I
destroyed my mom's sleep
schedule
uhhuh she normally goes to sleep like
around midnight I think no go
away
[Music]
no oh so much for
that go away go away
[Music]
nice I'm in the No Sleep Club
yeah but yeah she was really really
really excited she wrote to me yeah made
her so happy to do that it was a lot of
fun
yeah so I'm very glad she enjoyed it so
much for me it's everyday happiness and
every day can't sleep every day staying
up until 5 6
a.m. it's just every day I can't
see partially partially because you guys
also make me
[Music]
happy but it's it's
just like routine by
[Applause]
[Music]
now I love you guys does she look at
Reddit no I don't think so but I sent
her the fan art that people were making
some of it I sent her some some of the
fan
art
[Music]
did she like any portrayals of herself
and particular she didn't say she didn't
say I'm acting like a personified air
purifier a what do we have
now is this the same room oh yeah it
must
be now we're here okay now hold let me
drink some chalky milk slurp
slurp
yeah money Drew her in those weird
Minecraft clothes as well but it
actually looked good when she drew
it why does everything look good as long
as Mone draws it I want to be an artist
that that's good I want to be a
a I can't speak I want to be so skilled
in art that anything I draw looks good
just like Mama Looney like no matter
what she
[Music]
draws can we blow that up or does it
work like
that you just see
it
huh stop stab stab oh oh oh it's moving
already okay I'll follow I'll
follow where are we
[Music]
going I going to stop
here
oh I
see how do I fight that thing again I
don't remember
uh
oh my God what the
ah those tin of things I don't like
them I don't like
them I know I know have some go for the
middle but it won't let me there we
[Music]
go exploded it
exploded
where
[Music]
money I couldn't get any of the
money I hate that where's my reward
I where are my
rupes
I have feel
okay let's
go okay we're done we're
done what what what oh no oh no oh I'm
going to mess this up am I oh
wait maybe if it doesn't see me it's
like I never was
here
[Music]
oh God no no
no no stop
this give me a
moment
[Music]
[Applause]
bastard F
man I spin right the spin the spin the
spin
[Laughter]
I'm sorry SMY I'm sorry I'm okay
mama is okay mama is
okay
[Laughter]
okay smly came to check off on
me I'm
[Laughter]
sorry what is it over there how do I get
[Music]
there I can't get there I can't go there
the lever put it's over there do I have
to
jump wait there's more LS ises that does
that one work
too is that not a different
[Music]
one I was not using that one did the
other one come back
[Music]
too it didn't
Beetle yeah but it will go like it will
move on forward ah
wait can I activate it with
like the
[Music]
Lea what is
it
[Music]
hit the stone in the car yeah but
like no that won't work cuz it was just
moov on
[Music]
forward it won't come
back oh no Dum
ass take this stair and go
left it's connected here it's
not what the freak just
[Music]
happened I was so mad I don't know what
happened it's like I was a different
[Laughter]
person oh
man
do I have to fight that thing
again I hope
not I rageed too much my voice
[Music]
hurts what happened to Kong I was
going to be calm
today
n i can Parry the laser
really
can you go
faster and then I hit I hit the thing by
accident in the very end and fell down
after already dying once and using up a
fairy it's
unbelievable freaking unbelievable I
have to
say
the hell what the hell
man wait is there
more um that's
time I hate those things I hate
them no no I'm not I can't even reach
you
anyway yeah I'm not going to fight those
I don't think I
can you can't see me la la la La
[Music]
okay
go uh what do we have
here
sorry you can Parry the laser
okay I'll give it a try maybe at some
point if I get into a situation like
that
again but like if you like if you stand
in front of one of those mobs and you
immediately get like the the first
hit then you're fine then you can kill
it immediately but if you're like if you
get hit by the laser first then it's
like an endless loop of trying to run
away from the laser getting hit from the
laser falling down trying to stand up
and the moment you stand up it hits you
again and then the motion
Control won't do the Slash the way you
want to do it so
annoying
so
annoying bubble
[Music]
bubble calibrate
calibrate I know I know the spin but I
forgot about the spin
yeah oh God another one of
those what if I go in there
first do I want to
go isn't that where I came from
[Music]
ah a
shortcut I see okay okay so we have to
go go that one wait I've also been here
before right when we entered
ah when we first entered we went to the
right
side okay
[Music]
okay let's
go wow this is so much fun walk in the
pack p
p walk in the
park by uh piece of cake
easy
uh-oh I will fight you I will fight you
I'm
ready okay yeah
okay yeah see this is how I'm
done I know I know but just
[Music]
like
wait I have to move wait wait wait no
I'm not going to fall out no I'm not
going to risk it no no no no no no
no okay what the
hell hell what the hell I I always like
instead of like like just going
immediately to the item I want to use I
sometimes just push it too long and then
accidentally choose one of those
items I want to go
[Music]
back feels so calming today are you sure
about that are you sure about
that
see I did it again even though I already
had selected I don't know what what that
weird habit of mine is I don't know why
I do that
[Music]
always ra K CL I think that was
irony oh God what is this
room
where we in this V
before Oh I don't think
so
[Music]
uh do we go all the way up
there come here come here okay you can
hopefully
deal so
so who
saw okay I didn't really see that coming
I understand ah I understand
now
okay maybe after that one blows I will
go
[Music]
what oh
no just have to
go for the middle and then I'm somewhat
safe but I don't see I don't see
ah go up go up go up okay okay and from
here okay okay okay okay I got it I got
it I got
it
y okay okay
okay wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait oh wait wait wait
[Music]
wait thank
you maybe some more Hearts thank you
thank you thank you
okay so what do we have
here another reset button oh give me
H oh I didn't need it anymore we're
fine
uh
what do I use
this ah okay makes that thing come over
here
so I don't want to go down oh I do
because it won't move
anyway okay maybe for
[Music]
later
uh doesn't make sense to go here first
rather than going
left nope okay I
[Music]
see
uh what did I
miss is there a button somewhere
[Music]
where
huh I don't see a like activation thingy
anywhere and I go okay I have to throw
those things in there but like wait wait
wait wait wait mother I don't
understand I don't
understand I agree but I also don't
understand as we like to say do I go
back
[Music]
up for time
Crystal yeah ah wait over there ah me
not hi hi hi hi I didn't see that
part
okay
uh
[Music]
uh see this is why I'm really bad at
sports class when it comes to Ball
Sports like oh my God whenever the
teacher would say okay today we're going
to play basketball or like dodgeball or
soccer or anything like that something
inside my
body did a flip a 360 or 180 or I don't
know it just felt like not
good the 360 in a really bad way not in
a cool and stylish way was like no no I
can't shoot balls I can I can't even
properly like catch
them like whenever someone would throw a
ball at me I would immediately
panic and uh
yeah that's my problem with dodgeball
when someone throws a ball at me I I
don't really have the choice of catching
it and throwing it back at at
them uh because when I try to do that it
slips away from my hands because I don't
have the confidence in the
grip so I always choose to just like uh
avoid and and like you know avoid it by
jumping to the side or
whatever uh uh rather than catching it
but that that means that it's just an
Endless Running Away wait what what what
the what the
uh it's not going to work like I can't
go
up wait I have to go the other
way
that don't make it oh my come look at
him oh my
God you want to fight again I'm behind
you
Bo okay now we just run run run
run oh that was close that was close a
now that thing is
here
[Music]
it's so unnecessary that there's this
tiny slip here that you can slip through
why is it not directly docked onto this
platform
huh and this platform is way too tiny
anyway there's like no space to
navigate man and and K so much for being
calm today I'm just mad do I have to
stop
here uh
no
okay
[Music]
ohuh no no no no not
again
hey come
back can I do any
oh I hit the microphone with my Chu
[Music]
on oh nice
nice nice nice nice nice nice hey come
back Beach
it a come
back come back and we finish you
off okay there we go and again all the
money drops everywhere besides on the
ground literally everywhere besides on
the ground thanks for
nothing
what what what did I
do what did I do what did that
do nice English thank you are you making
fun of me what did I
[Music]
say it's it's just the anger the anger
inside of me makes my English
worse I got to remember the
order two free one the order I open it I
could have opened it up in a different
order though
no but okay wait wait wait what the
not I still can't move on though can
I
is that oh wait maybe from from there I
can bring it h
okay no other way
yeah yep yep yep you got it you got
it yeah that's that's the way to go
woohoo
nice okay now we can move
on
okay I have
arrived next
Dock and we go in the blue
Direction all the way over to the other
[Music]
side
okay
uh
aha ahuh aha shortcut for
later or something I have is that I have
to use anyway cuz it's inevitable I
think so yes or do I have
to ah is that where I use the number
but how do I
know
two free one what's two free
one but how but does that imply that
this is number one this is number two
and this is number three so I do the
middle one first and then the right one
and then the the that
one is that the
order yeah really
okay okay stop stop stop stop stop
[Music]
stop stop
and is
it okay oh dear what is that
[Music]
again I've seen that before what does
that do again doesn't that
[Music]
like ah ah wait wait I can open those
doors already now but the order in what
when I activate them is important the
the the switches that are
[Music]
inside so anyway let's
uh open it up shoot y I know I know
trying to charge my blade okay don't
disturb me right now
hey
hey that does not work from here ah
[Music]
no no why am I here
now
[Music]
no see I can do it I can do it I can do
it if I want to do it it
[Music]
seems down it
down I can do
it now I go back up back up back up back
up and now I have to reset that
don't
I I have
to
[Music]
ah
a okay hey two three and one G it don't
make those weird jumps oh my God you
freak me out
link scare me your
stuns that are unasked
for okay
Susan something is
buffering you to you to
we're back okay that was just a a tiny
tiny little hiccup don't worry
guys hi hi
hi shine
sh
nice
oh
what huh
[Music]
wait it was it was this one first after
all how nice of the game to tell me
though
he
yeah this one and then the one in the
middle those are automatic jumps which
I'm partially really thankful for but
sometimes it's just like not what you
expect you don't see it
coming
okay we did
it oh oh is that the boss
key I think it
is I think it
is yeah but yeah Zelda has been like
automatic jumps for a long long long
long time right it's breath of the wild
the first time that they're oh dear not
implementing automatic jumps oh dear I
don't like those dudes I don't like
them
uh I don't like
[Applause]
wa are they wait do they stay in that
yeah they stay in that area okay
okay wait
wait okay I did that one the other one I
I think I have to
stab what the stay in your area you
little piece of go back go back
you're not supposed to
St you
I'm really really aggressive
today um calm down kada calm down calm
down calm down calm
down
okay
I I did it though I did it you
liar can't I SP for that door
idiot
stop oh is that the wrong
[Music]
side is that on the other side no it's
here okay wait wait no no no no no
no
oh okay
okay oh I hate I hate I hate everything
right
[Music]
now
okay I did
it oh my God oh my God oh my
God the usual panicking woo where did
the cist go where did that
[Music]
go all righty we got it that means where
next up is the
boss where's the
door where are we right now
ah shortcut down
[Music]
there where's
a uh uh is there a shortcut I want to go
for that
door that
door okay
[Music]
okay why why am
I okay chill chill CH chill for a moment
okay we got to think about this wait for
that to go away yeah
[Music]
run run run now we have the right timing
I think I hope oh y y y y y okay now
it's the right
[Applause]
timing okay is the boss difficult I'm
scared
mommy I am
scared then we activate that to go back
I think yes but I want to first I guess
boss is easy really
really
really supposed to be easy you know I
got to make it complicated again you
know me you know me new song for Mar
Senai made by you know me you don't you
don't make platform you kidding
no no no I don't like this oh no no no
no Cali Cali Cali go go go go go go go
go go go
a I hate
[Music]
this it's been 1 and a half hours and I
am I am already like I don't want to
deal with this anymore why is it
not moving autom medically now huh tell
me why are you not moving now I have to
turn you off and on again like my
computer
huh
[Music]
uh maybe we should get on it first and
then uh blow like it so L you last day
I'm
up I hate
it oh I hate it oh I hate it
it
[Music]
I
wait
[Music]
I I thought I was going to fall down
again all the way into the abyss so game
you can be very happy that I did not
fall into the abyss because I would have
destroyed everything around
me okay hi s hi
hii
beautiful why am I always so tired and
yawning all this
time
that's it e you're telling me that's not
it
CH that look like it
though maybe that
way no that's not it
[Music]
that way no
that's I wish I could just actually hold
it in my
hands
[Laughter]
the real bus was the puzzles we made
along the way
this will be an addition to the usual
[Laughter]
room think K
think
what
oh no
uh
[Laughter]
no this
one
oh first r was the first try I didn't
cancel so first
[Music]
trying open the
door kfp is here ky let's go are you
ready are you ready to
rumble
oh hello
hello hello
m a c be L for some fried chicken you
ordered uh with extra Sala
sauce hello uh what w what the
I didn't I just came to deliver
some
chicken oh it's a big version of the
small babies Oh damn thousand year
around need more dark what oh okay I see
it has two eyes there and an eye in the
in its tail okay seems easy enough uhhuh
okay do I have to stab it or did I did I
hit it no it was the other
one camera
did I get
[Music]
it I'm
standing am I
going oh the other one can I how I
switch the B the
tget
[Music]
wait what
sometimes gra stab when they're r
[Music]
or or do I actually not have to do I not
have to oh I don't have to stab it I
thought I have to stab
it oh
am I doing it put it
in okay I did one apparently this is how
you do it oh
okay me and
I come
here I don't see
[Music]
you I'm having some issues with the
camera but we're good we're good we're
good
[Music]
okay ouch
ouchy didn't see that
coming oh there we go okay I'm the God
now for the tail what are you going to
do face Two Face
[Music]
two I'm going to lock on
you I regret everything sorry uh what am
I doing in this space
oh wait do I have to blow on the
ground oh that's funny
Mas oh
oh
oh it okay I mean we can try
that I don't think I want to
though
no no not again not
again
ah I didn't hit it even once I
think come out here come out you don't
[Music]
hide oh there we go there we go so I can
also hit it when the eye is red huh
okay okay okay okay I got it no problem
so cute how it hid that
[Music]
though no
no I want to
[Music]
hide
suddenly I'm missing a lot of heart I
don't know what
happened
shoot you shoot you let's
focus where are
you where are
[Music]
you hey I don't like this face I'm not
sure what I'm doing in this
[Music]
face
stab
you guys said it was
[Music]
easy
[Applause]
[Music]
see I can do it I've been doing it all
along what the hell
man but like at one moment no no no no
no
[Music]
a no no no no no no
no I know don't get
[Music]
it I don't know what I don't know
there's some demons inside of me
today
yeah
okay I I have
[Music]
some some froat um uh thingies with a
salai what's Sala in English give me
that heart
container I get something caling from my
throat
now daliva
no Sage
Sage
to oh man oh my God what the was
[Music]
that I was
frustrated I can't scream less when I'm
frustrated came out of my
heart with all my heart and all my
emotions I yelled for you this was for
you I'm just I you know I wear my heart
on my sleeve guys and that's what you
like about me don't
you what is this room why is it so weird
now
okay
yeah well that's
scary
what that is SC they're saluting they're
saluting oh
cute almost there almost there oh Kitty
Kitty
he oh seven oh7
cute okay and we're going to get in
there and then go wow it's so holy
what's going
on they look shook
uh okay why is there no bgm it's so
spoopy
Z
yo I came for you
again what do I get for that huh for
running after you so
[Music]
often hi it's me Hi how are
you
[Music]
YY oh
dear
ah we're do this back oh
no
woo nice C
yo you Grace quickly go to the gate I
don't know how what I did for her voice
link I don't know how to play the harp
D I don't know how to
[Music]
it
okay can someone give me heart license I
need heart license anyone here who can
play the
[Music]
heart are you
dead thank you
douche he always
misses protect Zelda always protect
Zelda oh no I want to protect Zelda not
you I was saying I'm going to protect
Zelda oh for
sake do I have to fight this dude
[Music]
now link you must go now return to the
old woman at the sailed grounds tell her
what happened here she will know where
you must
go and know that we will like I'll
definitely see you again this isn't good
fing my
[Music]
promise I blame myself what did I what
did I do with this voice I don't know I
take pleasure in punishing you but I
have no time what the next time I'll
just be you senseless I'll make the
affair so excruciating you'll Dien
yourself with a shrill sound of you what
yeah I don't remember how I did
it it was a bit more crazy than that I
think
okay a report master I can no longer
detect Zelda's
Aura
du the moment the gate was destroyed
Zelda's Pres disappeared from my
readings you can no longer search for
her with your dowsing
ability Dallas companion instructed you
to meet with the ancient one in the
sealed
ground this corresponds with the records
in my memory I propose that we travel to
the seal
Temple seal Temple wait do you mean
the do you mean the one where the lady
with the big big hat
[Music]
was
sus that one ah in the in the big hole I
don't want I don't want the beetle I
want this
one
oh all right good with
me did you see what just happened
couldn't you have helped
huh why did you not help oh what you
made it inside you mean to say there's a
secret possession he doesn't even React
to what just
happened I was just about to give up and
go home when I heard this huge crush i r
back to find that the way had been clear
I we're not there just in that in that
specific very important moment you were
somewhere else on the toilet or whatever
unbelievable yeah have fun have
fun perfect timing
yeah I mean otherwise he might have been
dead now so I guess it's good for
[Music]
him okay
safe and now we go to uh the
sky I think and uh yeah or should we go
back to skyloft once
should we go back to skyloft or straight
to the hole in the
ground his face really disturbs
me
go could get the metal shield back
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
that was
quick
okay and let's get let's get our
new old
shield and I mean we could get another a
potion but I feel like oh she has a side
quest I feel like I always every time I
get a potion I later
on uh get a fairy and then just waste
the
potion
hi upgrade shop a and maybe we have
something uh
maybe stamina potion unlocked for that
Quest oh not hold
on for
[Music]
sure thank you yeah will come again
thank you you have a
quest uh-huh I guess we should do the
side quest why not
MH what do I have to do
nothing oh nothing she just told me that
the stamina potion is now available okay
I don't really want it
though yeah I'm just going to buy a
heart potion please thank
[Music]
you only one though I'm going to keep
one bottle
empty because maybe we'll find something
that we have to pick
up
ah stamina push ah for the quest oh for
that side quest
a okay in that case
okay you better not take my bottle
though you can drink it and then clean
it and then give it back to
me no I don't care I'm going to give
this to the boy
[Music]
in in that
building was it
[Music]
you did he just say I caught him in the
middle of his nightly workout
routine it's
uh is that a bug
[Music]
it's it's
daytime it's daytime and if it was if
you were in the middle of your nightly
workout routine you would let me give
you the potion wouldn't
[Music]
you oh I was going
here can I sleep on your
bed oh dear you got one of those ugly
ass cats
what happens if I sleep in here until
night what will he be
doing oh wait he has a huge cat tree
that's so cute where did your cat
go oh where did your cat
[Music]
go I keep my distance from Mia at night
there was that one time when she snuck
in to the academy after Nightfall I
would keep my distance from that cat at
night as well yeah I recommend that you
be extra careful when you go out at
night oh dear that caused quite the
commotion oh I think I met Mia in the
night
before so where
isge which one is fled's room shouldn't
I be hearing
his
moans I guess it's one floor
below got to listen to the
moans no I don't hear it right
now
gross
LGE oh there he is I got your starina
the potion
buddy oh all good
now just for you take
it really thank you I owe you
one
wow wo yeah I can feel my muscles
perking back up
already it's just that at this rate I
don't know if I'll ever get strong and
brly try your best
right that's exactly what I need to do
no more whining I need to push myself
yeah thank you link I'll make you proud
you'll see I'll be super Bly in no time
okay back your training come back soon
so I can show you the new me oh you'll
probably never change will you good luck
with that
though good
luck wait did why did I not give get any
where's my reward for
that where's my where's my where's my yo
where's my reward where's my crystals
come back another
night oh no not gruce no wrong room damn
it a
it you
okay it's driving me crazy I've looked
absolutely everywhere but still no
childrena H I do have one last idea
though have you seen the lights that
popped up out of the clouds a few days
ago so I say to myself Gru that thing
looks kind of fishy and one day it hits
me what if that Zelda down there and
she's sending me a signal it's a sign it
says save Me Gru you're my only home the
more I think about it the more sure I
get it it's Zelda down there and I got
to rescue her anyhow don't think about
trying to go down there before me I'm a
hero
remember I don't even know why I'm
talking to you looking at you just makes
me feel sad
again okay buddy
chill what do you
say I'm beginning to wonder if G is ever
going to pull himself out of his noow St
sure it's tough for him but I imagine
how I feel having to listen to him
moping all the time I can't wait to get
back to my
room
all right friends you like that voice
thises it sound a little bit like toad
toad
K thank you what a what a nice
compliment thank you I feel so
flattered okay here's my
room I'm
to oh he's still doing it I'll sleep
until should I sleep until another night
will I see the effect of the side quest
done
okay so uh not only takana but also Z
Link's um sleep schedule is now so
that we sleep throughout all the
day and then wake up at night
wonderful
D still
nothing oh should I sit on you like a
wait I'll help you
[Music]
out
hey I'll do my best and someday I'll be
strong it come back soon I I'll come
back
soon do I have to I guess I'll come back
like I don't
[Music]
know when should I come
back in the morning not so soon
I need you get further in the story God
damn
it
okay
okay change doesn't happen over night
that is very deep and very
true
yeah okay down that room no actually
haven't should I have gone at
night
Let's uh move on uh we're going to the
big hole in the ground no why why do
always go to wrong rooms big doors look
like exits to
[Music]
me I can't get there yet I hold
on
[Music]
okay haror line haror line oh
what wait hey no already I didn't I had
I just had to meet him during the day
outside or or not okay
whatever I thought that was
it all right calm down link calm down if
I'm not calm then at least you have to
be calm okay okay you can't be both of
us panicking
[Music]
24/7 okay let's
go forgot about the trash
can that doesn't mean
anything the fact that I sat on some's
trash can and then it broke apart is
because it was a shitty ass trash can
oh this is where you
[Music]
go you could say it was trash exactly it
was a trash trash
can
[Music]
oh this is
nice is this because I talk to him
please
help oh no oh
no Bruce why did you follow
me R
Landing I think I might have broke
something hey link seriously did anyone
ever teach you how to land without a
crash what's with that wait
[Music]
is birds tiny birds what are they I
don't know what to do with his
voice sorry if it keeps on changing what
is that
thing calm
down he's like me
now always not calm
the ground
chill what's going on here something and
out of town and all in a hurry so I
figured I'd tell you and you might lead
me to
Zelda but this it's so wild seriously
what is that thing over
there what with all these trees there
are so
many oh my God oh my God you're
exhausting me
gruce give give it to me straight I can
take it where are we still here
no what's the deal with this place if
there's supposed to be nothing below the
clouds what's all
this
link wow wow wow wow thank you link for
that explanation you didn't even open
your
[Music]
mouth coochie I did not now you
good you're kind of imploding my mind
right now but I think I get what you're
saying if I've got this right Zelda is
down here somewhere and she's
okay probably the birds are so
cute she's she's okay oh wow that's so
great
hearing that is such a huge weight
of he's he's really emotional he's
really
emotional you know link it's sort of all
right down
here his eyes look so sparkly this place
needs a name yeah a name fitting for
this ruged adventurous Wilderness r
um I don't think you have the right to
name this
[Music]
land no no no no no no
no let me see if I got this
right the old lady living in the temple
down the road from here knows where
Zelda
is I see
right link thanks for getting me here
you've done a good job you can head
[Laughter]
home big Gru will handle a search from
down out from here
on yep I'll track her down saf her and
then give her a lift back to
skyop and that ain't
happening then when we get back I'll ask
her if she wants to make her whole going
out Thing official and then the two of
us just two of us we'll get some quality
time
together anyway the point is your work
here is done I got it covered from here
now
now now it's off to find that old lady
you were talking about yeah you go on
ahead you can be my shield my meat
Shield human
[Music]
shield no problem did he go that way
what is
that what are those
things soccer
[Music]
balls wait a
second I want those
beetles got it oh that was smooth as
hell oh I forgot to upgrade some
stuff oh well we'll see how it goes
about upgrades for now okay the other
one left okay
rude am I going this
way um where am
I I this a
shortcut all right Bruce got it covered
well that would be nice to just lean
back and relax that would be nice
oh you got to be kidding me
granny you're messing with me say it
again I dare
you I only speak the truth you are not
the one who will save her the spirit
Maiden your Zelda can only be saved by
another it has been his fate to do this
thing and in doing so save us as it was
decided long before you were brought
crying into this
world shut it granny you obviously don't
know me well cuz if you did you know
that if anyone's going to save Zelda is
GR
how could it not be me plus if it ain't
me why would I even be here you a s
character that's why if I'm not up to
the job of being the hero just who
is me
me
hello oh now I get you link granny here
has been trying to tell me you're going
to be the big hero who rescues
Zelda what a joke look all I've heard so
far is a bunch of babbling about Destiny
but that's a lot of garbage I know you
you're no hero shrimp
shrimp you're using that as an insult
excuse
me
excuse you want to fight you want to
fight oh he wants to
fight oh green things link were you able
to catch up with
Zelda I see so the garden was there as
well was
she the one you saw by Zelda side is
known as
impa she is being sent forth by the
goddess to a Zelda in her
Quest the two have traveled somewhere in
order to accomplish ACC the great task
Destiny has set before them however now
that IMA has destroy the gate that they
used there is only one way left to find
them you must make use of the harp given
to you by
Zelda tell me link have you attempted to
play the harp that you received no I
don't know how to use it video game
logic can immediately play an instrument
that was put into my hands 5 seconds
[Music]
ago my sense is that you have not yet
familiarized yourself with it that's
right
yeah very well oh she's going to teach
me thank
you press X
okay done try straming you oh my god am
I really going
to what
[Music]
oh slowest jums said they match the
swaying of oh
okay wait
[Music]
wait there we
go am I not doing it right oh it's
beautiful
oh good you learn fast
yeah now for your next
lesson focus and play time with the Ping
of the circle of light when your timing
is right I shall join my voice to your
heart you're going to sing with me
listen well for the song I sing will be
of great help to you in your journey
uhhuh oh
dear
[Music]
wow w
w
[Music]
w that was
beautiful you learned the blad of the
Goddess it's a mystery Melody that has
been passed down from ancient times
[Music]
oo
oh what is
that what is
that oh dear the is that the harp
you hold is known as the goddess harp it
is a Divine instrument of the goddess
who once watched over this
[Music]
land The Melodies it brings to life have
the power to produce a variety of
strange and other worldly
[Music]
effects the great slap standing before
you is known as the Gate of
time it is the last of its kind in
existence the only portal binding our
world to the one where Zelda now
resides if you manage to open the gate
and pass through you will likely end end
up in the same place as
Zelda but you will need to endure many
hardships and put yourself in great
danger to awaken the gate from its
dormant
State through your journey will put you
in Harm's Way
link is that a proper English sentence
you must endure it is your fate as the
chosen hero of the
[Applause]
Goddess yeah okarina of time harp of
time is shaking I fear the seal has been
broken I expected that it would react to
you summoning the gate but I never
imagined the seal would break so quickly
Nana why did you break n bro no link
there will be time to explain later
right now you must hurry the bottom of
the pit outside okay let me drink some
water
though
[Music]
n open up
n we have to close the
N Gru oh my God what are you doing my
human shield
who what's with all that
shaking the whole ground is having i p
was supposed to be solid down
there oh quickly link check on the
ceiling Spike at the SE ning Spike at
the center of the pit there is nothing
natural about these Tremors that monster
could free itself at any moment
approaching the pit with
caution but approach
okay wait should I just jump down what
she she said approaching with
caution
uh I'm scared
mommy ah can we get some
bombs fill them
up
okay yeah it's a seal
n what do I do what do I
do I'm
scared I'm scared
[Music]
oh no it's a big black
hole oh
God oh my
God it's Edy evil GA it's
G the one from the K the other
day the
imprisoned a so edgy oh they has
feet you're so cute can I knew it the N
has given way I'll explain later but now
is the time for Action we must keep that
beast from escaping that pit it must not
reach the
temple uh okay uh wa how how what what
do you expect me to do what do you
expect me wait do I fly up and and try
to throw bombs into his M mouth
for I
don't tack him like this stop he will
step on me and I'm not into
that oh that's so cute though e that's
disgusting and cute at the same
time okay what what now you okay buddy
oh okay he still doesn't oh wait he has
back back seat
e ew that's is
[Music]
disgusting okay do I climb on you
now it seems kind of
absurd what do I
do oh
oh Nancy get back in there
n get back in there oh
dear what the stop
[Music]
it oh okay I didn't have to stop it it
stopped itself
okay I I thought I have to maybe throw
some bumps I maybe I can do that
[Music]
too oh hey that worked that's
funny he stepped on the
[Music]
B nice to the back
side
what
disgusting wait for it
okay the bomb tactic is a good one yeah
but it's not really
necessary as we can see easy enough okay
run run run run oh no not much space
here and slap back in
there
okay
nice down okay going up going
up maybe I went up a little bit too
far when will you
stop yum
it how far are we going buddy okay you
stop here
[Applause]
n
[Music]
n she's looking for her
husbands where are her husband this is I
have only KB employees
here it ouch okay he's is he more
aggressive than before or ouch oh my God
that feels like a new face he's faster
and
furiouser faster and
furiouser excellent English oh he's a
bit more Cal slow one
now wa my
go outou what wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait oh you almost you almost pushed me
down there okay nice hi yby
yie y y
[Music]
I'm coming
let
okay this is a fun fight I was so scared
but it was not necessary it seems the
scariest looking monsters the biggest
monsters are always the easiest monst it
seems not
bad easy
clap oh is that the end
it it turned back to
GAA no now it turned back to
eny
[Music]
wow
oh oh the scales dropping o and NY put
back into her
space
oh oh link strike to seal n in Spike
with a skyward Strike and restore the
seal quickly okay gotcha what the
[Music]
I'm on my
way oreno
[Music]
forever
then Spike sounds like a super
[Music]
move
what
oh
[Music]
Illuminati whoa he's got those
moves
w
wow this feeling of
accomplishment feels
nice meanwhile
gruce nice going
link H what are we looking
at no the impris had only just begun
toit weon and break its bonds I'm
impressed you were able to restore the
seal keeping it
captive unfortunately you have only
succeeded in buying us a little more
time in which to
act the beem mo you beat back into
confinement is a horror of unspeakable
power judging by what I saw I would not
be surprised if of the Nana gave way
again
soon so you were left with precious
little time so to complete the task with
which you have been
entrusted return to the NAD Temple link
there is much to
[Music]
discuss
bye-bye is she okay should I carry her
up back up
I I want to help
her yeah you are not a hero Gru I'm
sorry I am the
hero oh that was easy let just impli
that I did carry her like a
hero as you can see the gate is nothing
more than a slab of Cold Stone for now
just like in Minecraft it is
sleeping rousing it from its Slumber
would require great power
yes I believe a shot of Holy Light from
your skyward Strike might just do
it shall we give it a
try ah sorry to disappoint you boy but
for now your sword lacks the power
necessary to awaken the gate first you
and your sword must grow
together B Woods elen volcano and L
desert a sacred flame is hidden
somewhere in each of these lands seek
them out and purify your sword in their
heat
oh only after your blade has been
tempered by these free fires will it be
fully ued imbued with the great power
for which you
search clues to find the sacred Flames
have been woven into the lycs of a song
Precious to your people the blood of the
Goddess these Clues are your best hope
of finding your way to the
Flames this is where you start
backtracking huh I see I
see yeah I have to say it's a bit
disappointing that there's really only
those free worlds to
isn't that is quite
disappointing and the sky is also pretty
[Music]
small my voice
hurts okay we're turn this guy
left
okay n oh he looks sad
a
[Music]
what what is it
now I hate say even saying this but I
guess you got all figure it out granny
me well there's nothing I can do to help
Zelda I'm
useless okay
ah you sell yourself short my friend
you'll see in time that you have your
own world to play in all this
H oh yeah what is that R link go now
trust in faith to guide your feet your
mission depends on it as does Zelda's
fate
F
[Music]
okay
well I
guess I guess so can I take a seat here
cuz she was always sitting here will I
grow older if I sit
[Music]
here
this is the shortcut right maybe or is
it is it is it though but we want to go
back to Sky now
right okay great cor I found some what
butterflies o those butterflies are SP
of beautiful toes are swarming all over
this place this has to be the right spot
oh this could be a problem I cannot
carry a tune I could not create I do
have to play my
[Music]
harp wait where's the
harp where's the harp
ahuh
oh
what those boing boing
things oh no oh I don't like
those I don't know why but I don't like
them but that is it one of the talking
statues that ancient text spoke of there
is no mistaking it Bo oh thank you it's
giving me a
gift I don't like the way they boing
boing boing boing boing
boing
uh butterfli Stand Together around
gossip Stones like myself if you find a
spot swarming with butterflies play a
tune of great beauty and a gossip Stone
might just pop out of the ground with a
boing
what wait what what what you want me to
play the harp
[Music]
again or did he already drop
it oh it's so cute but I hate
it play the heart when I see butterflies
ah okay ah that's a sign
oh H by the way can I catch the feathers
of the birds did I do that
before no there
Birds damn it those are up too high as
well a damn it what am I
doing come now oh that was smart oh I
got two nice three range burps yeah all
right so this thing is
done well then how do I
[Music]
uh how do I get back I guess I used a a
safe thing statue wasn't there one
inside a goddess
statue I think there was one
inside
[Music]
yeah okay take me to the sky
please I did not see the option of going
ah ah not in here
huh
no need to be the orange one
ah
is there one
here where is the next
[Music]
one come on I couldn't do a thing I'm
totally
useless
[Music]
do I
left
[Music]
Oham I
left P
gr what what do you
mean what do you
[Music]
mean you're mocked on on the
map uh are those
things
uh
[Music]
okay need to get up
there I just take the shortcut again and
uh
somewhere there should be
one at the gor
okay catch blue birds I was trying to
catch any bird but I couldn't catch any
of
them I will keep on trying I will never
give
up never going to give you up never
going to let you
down going around around
and you
oh that that one God damn it I just ran
away from
[Music]
it it's only been 2 and a half hours and
I already feel
exhausted what is it these days it's
like partially like feeling out of
breath and I don't know I don't know man
streaming too much
[Music]
maybe streaming too much and having too
much to
[Music]
do p p
p is that a pizza
oven
no all right uh what was I supposed to
look for
[Music]
here you called for me
master yeah yes master what information
do you
seek you can use the treasure and
materials you find during
your that's not the kind of hint that I
was looking
for no no no I'm not finishing here what
the hell no I want to do
progress ouch
[Music]
objective no no no no
no to reach Sala you must enhance your
sword using the sacred flames of the
three provinces provinces evidence
suggests the bot of the Goddess which
has been known in sky for Generations
May hold a clue to the location of these
Flames analysis indicates your best
course of action is to search skyloft
and learn what you can of the
song nothing
[Music]
specific that's it okay so just run
around
randomly well maybe we can find the the
but there was some some butterflies here
too
right right there but no that's just one
that's probably not the right one I want
to catch it
though yeah I got
it I'm going to try
anyway is it okay if I already C caught
the butterfly
I don't think that's
[Music]
it well let's go into the bazaar and see
if we can upgrade
[Music]
something scrap
job yeah please upgrade we can fix the
shield too I guess
let's see what can we
do
[Music]
um be oh I can not do
it I cannot do that one
either I cannot do this one
either I cannot do that one either you
can also not do that one I can do this
one
wow I that's only something five five
more
bombs please thank
[Music]
you I need more
materials of
[Music]
everything yeah than thank you but you
could fix my shield maybe
maybe I get it fixed oh why
[Music]
not humble weeds and yeah oh wait not
that Shield oh oh my shield is full
really oh
okay well oh side quest do you want some
pumpkin silp people have been hearing a
woman sobbing in a dormatory oh okay I
tell you it gives even a big guy like me
to creeps okay at night we shall listen
for a crying woman that's just
me a what's up MOA why you why are you
crying why are you crying that sounds to
me like a Harry Potter Side Story
though the crying uh ghost in in in the
bathroom
stalls hello ah these past few days I
swear I hear a voice you tell me the
same thing wait is this connected with
the main clust or is the side quest also
is this the sacred flame that I'm
looking for can I put my sword into it
come on come
on I'm sure that's the
one no are you sure Grandma are you
sure that's a side quest okay is this my
room no that's someone else's room okay
well I guess we can do the side quest
first we have to do some side quests
anyway and if the game tells me twice
about it it just feels like
Destiny
yeah motion leaving on a jack plane
what
all
righty open your
closet money I thought a heart container
or something like that would be there
can I open it
again nothing damn it there's a bag
though there's a bag link you could use
the bag to have more
inventory all righty crying
woman I don't hear one right now she
probably go
upstairs hi hi
J hi
baby all I wait in the
bath meow meow I
know yeah yeah hi baby hi
why are you scratching my chair no what
is
it what is
it sorry I moved the microphone you want
to join me up here come up here baby
come come come come come come or
there
baby what a cute
baby okay where am I right now
let's go downstairs
again hello crying woman
[Music]
ohow hi oh sobody please somebody help
me I baby yeah it's not your mommy
crying I'm
fine meow
meow oh pap
please somebody bring me toilet
paper any kind of paper at all what are
you doing JN you're so cute but don't
don't stop you're so cute but
stop maybe
maybe paper do I have
paper oh
hello
paper have paper
do you have a
paper uh no I don't want to lie down do
you have
paper paper oh that looks yummy
Curry
Pap
paper another side quest needed go back
to day for
paper okay can I do that now I
wonder paper St time for paper
paper until morning time Jung what is it
[Music]
[Applause]
B she's answering
me oh hi she jumped on my
she's above my head now yeah
meow meow wait ow ow she jumped down and
jumped on my
arm what are you doing
baby meow did you hear that what is
itow
meow what are you
doing
M come up you can come up here come up
here
come
come baby you never listen to
[Music]
me she wants
attention ah hi
smothie welcome
hi movie is just
chill tras is just very
confused okay day time for paper is it
anywhere in the dormatory
[Music]
though I see paper here can I not take
that paper do you have paper
hi uh
what n you like
him I don't care I need
paper front
[Music]
door o you got
paper should I give it to her should I
not give it to
her blink it's you don't sneak up on me
like that I have a serious Dilemma on my
mind right now and you're distracting me
dilemma what you want to hear about
it normally I would never ever tell
someone like you but these are Tire
times I come to think of it you might be
just a person I need you seem to be
pretty good with the
ladies I can't believe I just said that
but whatever let's do this link I have a
task for
you h no so listen up your mission is to
take this piece of paper hi CH is on my
chair again yeah you can relax up there
sit down on my chair yeah
yeah it's a very important piece of
paper make sure you deliver it
okay you hear it crackling I hear it
too wait a second sometimes the sound
capture is
weird now it should be fixed yeah oh
what's your problem wait is this someone
else what there's someone in the
restroom at night who wants paper you
fool how dare you this is no ordinary
piece of paper it's a letter a very
special one at that I put my heart into
every word I guess you could say it's
sort of like a all right F some love
letter I will give it to the person on
the toilet and that is why you will not
under any circumstances ever allow it to
be used as toilet paper do you hear me f
[Music]
f listen up the person you must give it
to is a girl what wait is this like a
side quest where you have two choices of
what you could
do
uh well he's a he's a piece of so
I'm I'm going to give it as toilet
paper
or do I is there like a better reward if
I do it the other way like a heart
[Music]
container there's only one choice if you
think about
it I mean the person on the toilet came
to me first
so I don't I don't have much of a choice
it's
Destiny they asked me first oops they
asked me for
paper and now you gave me paper
you've been a shitthead to me until now
so that
means I will sleep until night read it
can I read
[Music]
it
uh
oh a heartfelt letter letter no I can't
use it
wait make sure not to use it as scrap
don't worry I'm not using it as scrap
paper I'm using it as toilet paper but
there's so many books here I could have
just ripped out one page of a
book and use that what the hell it's not
like that is the only option of paper
[Music]
here why does it have to be this paper
you know what maybe the person on the
toilet is the that girl so we would get
two uh flies with one uh
clutch it yeah I got the
paper he isn't it a love letter to
you there's no one in
here
and that's disgusting the water is like
brown yie
yie okay
Phoenix
phix
Phenix
Phoenix
where is the X where did you leave the
X I'm not angry or anything I just need
some paper don't go baby you can stay up
there ah a
baby no don't don't jump on my arm again
please okay I'll give it to
you oh okay me p I'm so
happy oh baby are you stuck with your
claw again are you sure I can have this
yes take
it oh thank you I will use it with care
but I'm shy so don't ask me what I want
the paper for may we meet again you kind
soul
okay sit oh
no
that is
uh what there's not even a flush option
here that's not how this toilet works as
if this was like a modern Japanese
toilet that flushes automatically once
you leave the toilet seat I don't think
it has that kind of Technology just
yet
no
way but now that I think of it the seat
was warm just like those Japanese
toilets just like those Japanese
toilets sleep
again fled is still
lifting no not night no I'm sorry I'm
sorry
I messed
up until
[Music]
morning T good morning so when do I get
like the reveal of what I have done
right
away
hopefully is he there he's there y it
should we talk to him
well just tell him we gave her the
letter we totally did
it hey hey link did you hand over yes of
course I
did you you you I want of your mind
seriously you gave it to that creep in
the restroom really you gave it to the
restroom
weo didn't I specifically tell you not
to give it to him it saiding five I know
it you fool how could you anyone who BLS
the path of true love deserves to be
kicked by a
bird a bird I hate you
link just ride another one whatever just
ride another one she didn't see it yet
so you're going to ride a better love
letter I helped you because that love
letter was
I helped you
[Music]
visit him at night
okay expensive paper but usually when
you buy a letter set it usually comes
with more than
just I puted the one WR wrong one
again probably has another set left over
he probably has one more talk to the
Headmaster first
okay during the day
okay uh Headmaster where the hell was he
again he was upstairs
right where the hell am I
[Music]
going ah head Master is blood
progression oh okay
then I will sleep
[Music]
first
night they don't have automatic sugar
cane
Farms I guess so but I see a lot of
books and stuff
here can't believe that paper but it's
rare here I can't believe
it wait where the hell is he uh Callin
and
stretch Gru is he in Gru's room wait
what was this what was his name
Colin uh oh wait you have a quest
too oh and see you link what do you want
with me oh what am I doing bugs I'm
looking at
bugs oh pretty not so pretty do you want
bugs from me books are amazing even more
amazing than Gru in a lot of ways oh
wait I'm not saying Gru isn't as amazing
as a
BG look I just really like books I want
to collect all kind of
books okay chill if you find a book come
and sell it no I need those right now
don't wor need them for like materials
right
now or or actually
not well yeah I mean not right now but I
say sure
generally save them yes okay he sounds
like a cycle he
does he does this might bug you a little
bit only one to do these deals at
night it scares me
no the oh
no oh he has spe specific deals per
night
interesting
interesting okay so uh we wanted to see
uh the dude is he in this
room it says Gru's room but he's in here
oh my God the the
hand
hey so the Love Letter did some good
things after all seems like you are
being treated well by the magical
hand
help oh you're the one from the other
day it's good to see you again actually
thanks to you I met my true love wait a
second yes
him it all started with that letter you
gave
me those beautiful words of affection
caused me to fall hopelessly in
love my heart is bursting with thoughts
of him I feel so excited so cheerful so
full of
[Music]
life
y not bad not bad that was worth
it
[Music]
wow oh my love I will always be by your
side
T I know she didn't say t but it is
quite
T
wow I I wish them a happy
life a really really happy and fulfilled
life
okay now we sleep
again so much sleeping link is so
healthy
now and he must have been exhausted by
all those boss battles and dungeons
so I think it's good to take a break
every once in a
[Music]
while
the Japanese people are um me me because
I said t and it's funny cuz it's like a
pun because of hand
[Music]
hand that was a good pun and I did not
even intend
it
good Japanese
pun very good one
quo okay where is the the head Masters
here
okay hello so about your daughter she's
never coming back and I'm so done with
this game
so you got to deal with that it's not
happening
just kidding I'm the hero o
money I'm the hero I will save your
daughter I was just I was just
kidding oh back link good to see you're
still in one piece so how's it going
down there are you any closer to finding
my Zelda nope not at all not even
close I see my dear Zelda things must
have been terribly trying for her down
there and it can't be easy for you now
either can
it what you want to know the lyrics to
the song Zelda sang on the day of the
wing ceremony how about you
Google it you know I'm not much of a
singer just the lyrics is
fun you just want the lyrics oh what a
relief it really put me on the spot
there for a moment I believe the lyrics
go something like
this oh you got by the servant of the
Goddess unite Earth and Sky and bring
light to the
land that's the first part but as I
recall there's a second verse to the
song is you guys already
down oh you
shout the two whirling sails the way to
the Light Tower and before you a path
shall open and the Heavenly song you
shall hear okay beautiful write it down
write it down I believe that's the whole
thing the Light Tower mentioned in that
song is a real place I'm sure you've
seen the tower in the plaza I don't know
a thing about two whirling sails though
it sounds like the song is suggesting
that if one shows these whirling sails
the way to the tower something will
happen
what I don't understand the
sentence but how do you go about doing
that what does it mean thank you I don't
understand either two whirling
[Music]
sails windmills
okay ch oh what show them to the Tower
move windmills ah
wait there there are windmills windmills
windmills uh outside that I didn't move
yet
[Music]
right
okay
uh one is like fairly cool close to here
I
think I saw it
somewhere it I I that one that one that
one
okay
move ah to that
tower that one right in front of
me like that one oh it went too far is
that good enough
I think it is cuz the light turned
on two
butterflies is that a
[Music]
sign am I too far
away free is a sign oh okay well then I
shall catch them
all come here come here you little
yeah okay
oh wait a am I getting back the quest
thingy from you hey thank you yeah you
see then if you don't have any like
rewardful me then stop showing me that
speech bubble
where is the
other thingy the other uh
[Music]
windmill where could it
be maybe up
here
no nothing
here what wait a second
no
oh what is that hey it's missing
up oh do you have
it yeah yeah yeah yeah you can turn the
windmill so that it can always catch the
wind no matter which way is
blowing but well there used to be this
little propeller attached to Windmill
wait did I not am I going crazy or did I
see a windmill uh propeller lying around
somewhere somewhere
[Music]
somewhere but
where but
[Music]
where the FL flew
off in the fire dungeon yeah it feels
familiar
I just Str the windmill has been
uselessly
itself okay
um I highly suggest you retrieve the
windmill propeller from the land below
reorient the
windmill
okay yeah yeah yeah yeah of course you
can fix it can I know you I know you
[Music]
can you dting okay i d for it
really no it's not gone for good I know
what's down there stop talking let me go
there a flying
robot
no no no no no no no no I just just let
me go there stop
talking I can't actually jump down from
the like
that's a joke right that's a joke I need
the
robot in the
bazaar I wanted to fly straight down
there I need it
what's savior of the world everybody
hey I H am the savior of the world
I hell am I hella am the savior of the
world okay no doubt
there hello uh is anyone selling a
propeller no not not a thingy oh what
are you say you're looking well these
days if I didn't know any better I'd say
you'd found the time to C all variety of
Magnificent prases come come closer if
it's treasure you seek I'll use my
mystical vision find out for
you no no just
no no uh who am I asking for do I have
to ask you
[Music]
something sacred
Shield excuse me
what that looks cool how
much I probably can't pay it I only have
281 right
now electricity fire oh it doesn't give
a about any of those automatically
repair itself when it sustains damage
oh we have to get this one eventually
500 that's not even that expensive but I
don't have enough money right now
sorry yeah yeah I'll get it
eventually wait was it you hey hey kid
what's up you look like you need to get
something up of your chest I think I
know what it is you've got a favorite
would ask me right huh ah it's about
this old robot my grandpa used to Tinker
around with you probably just came here
to make fun of the crazy junk guy for
believing in his grandpa super stories
right no I need it my chat told
me well get it l I've heard it before
wait that's not why you're here you say
you need to pick up something from below
the clouds of this robot do you know
what that means that means you believe
in my grandpa stories too don't you well
I'm happy to hear that someone else
believes me but I don't think I can help
you you see my grandpa's old robot
what's it called again
aha ah Scrapper that's his name he may
not be much to look at these days but he
was an amazing robot once I believe
you when you called him he would go
anywhere and haul anything sadly as you
can see now he's just an never busted
old honk of
junk but old gr still tell me this you
can get him working again with the
extract from the ancient flow it's like
oil of thisy to this guy but I've never
even heard of much you seen any such
thing I have
[Music]
something what you have one are you
kidding me that's
amazing what are you talking
about so this is an ancient flower I can
feel some slck oily stuff coming out of
its stom great with this we can fix
Scrapper wait right here we'll have him
up and running in no time
okay
a we're going to get one of those for
ourselves one of those cute
robots
oh don't we already have a Beetle though
that can do similar
[Music]
things uh be careful it's going to be
noisy thank
you what a second let me try to get it
like a little bit uh
quieter
and
robot
uh
uh uh uh
T is it to
loud oh this one is not so loud okay uh
uh uh
[Music]
I I am a robot and I'm messing around oh
dear oh my
[Laughter]
God okay I'll just I'll
just
I'll f it down like I'll just oh my God
oh my
[Music]
God I don't I don't need that I can be a
robot on my
own I can speak like a robot without
this stupid effect thank you I've got a
full tank of energy and I'm ready ready
to carry
anything we did it last time I can do it
this
time huh who is this screen clad
individual of small
stature poy Todd can you believe that I
guess I really did fix him this kid gave
me the materials I needed to fix you go
on say thank
you uh I sure it was him good well then
I accept my reluctant thanks to you in a
just of obligatory gratitude
chunkers oh he knows
chunkers hey now watch it that's no way
to talk to someone who just saved your
life anyway this kid wants you to haul
some stuff around and you going to help
him um uh this individual may have
assured my operations but I am not
inclined to offer
assistance serving children is very low
in my task priority I am a
hero master link materials from the
windmill have yielded a signal that you
may search for with your dowsing ability
use it to locate the Fallen
propeller you're telling me I don't need
this dude after all I'm just going to be
dowsing however it will not be possible
to carry the item in your pouch and
return to the
sky it as if
who are
you so I'm going to find it and he's
going to car carry
it your name is Fe should I call you
mistress Fe are you looking for
something Mr feet oh he likes girls
doesn't
[Music]
he I
understand at your request I will carry
anything regardless of F or destination
we he's in
love
Master we now have the means to bring
the propeller back thanks to this simp
you may immediately begin your search
for the windmill
propeller
okay Master short P I offer assistance I
can now detect mistress fees fart
waves D you need me ask mistress Fe to
call me and I will arrive with
haste okay how do you plan the recover
shut up it do not it's not of your
[Music]
interest follow me follow me is he
following me when I
[Music]
leave is he coming with me
I'm just going to assume that he's going
to be there whenever uh I call him yeah
okay well
then going to ignore you cuz you're
still not buff I'm going to talk to you
when you're buff
again and
down helicopter simp oo
crony I wouldn't call her simp I'm not
sure how how much wait nope nope she's
not much of s I
think uh we're going uh to the elen
[Music]
[Applause]
volcano she's mean to the other
girls is it really mean or is it just
being
some people just really like like to
exaggerate things that we do like the
same thing with me like how I interact
with the girls and how they interact
with me you say one thing that's like a
roast or whatever and then it's like oh
they hate each
other no I'm pretty sure that crony does
is not mean to any of these
girls
and I'm sure that they get along really
really well
[Music]
yeah I wonder if iris is scared of crony
because she looks like a ceiling fan
indeed you're right now that is
something that we can theorize
about where do we want to
go oh I have absolutely no memory of
where that thing was
Temple entrance thank
you
yes aha this time I called
it all right
um wait a second wasn't it like
here
no no that would have been too easy but
where have I seen
[Music]
it I could be ding yet wait a second is
that free free
butterflies can I do it from down
[Music]
here come
on
[Music]
there it is there it
is hello weird thing bo
bo so they always just give you like one
material is is that their
thing that
H oh wait no no no I want to never
[Music]
mind this
thingy
huh hold
on oh there it is there it is there it
is oh my
god oh thank you guys for giving me the
hint about it that it's close to that
entrance thank you otherwise I would
have been looking for
hours okay yes of course I would like to
do that of course why are you even
asking come on where where is it come
here little robot
CH a
cute
hi Mr I help he completely ignores
me I hope you weren't waiting long so
you want me to carry
this hey Master short bants you're in my
way here I said get out of the way move
get out the way get out the way
get out the way I will be waiting
for you up in the sky so don't take too
long uh-huh okay see you
later he's in
love master I suggest that we also
return to the sky and collect the
propeller as as
possible Okie
doie
uh wait how do I get back up
there not fall into the magma is
probably not the best option maybe I
just can run
here fun
hi okay
yeah
B I don't I don't think I can make it I
made
it
okay oh thank you very
useful
okay I just wanted to go back to the
Statue nice Dam you gotten good sh
really how
flattering she's a pro sassen oh thank
you yeah I mean I I do have a sword and
the shield and I'm trained with
it yep y I am a I'm a sword fighter yes
yes
yes your wild swinging works well hey
it's follow me oh
cute
what if we fly through that thing here
together I can never manage to do it can
we even fit for of course this time I
don't mind I also fail at it
so never
mind there we
[Music]
go oh perfect place to land
on here's that windmill propeller
that thank
you if you need me cl feel free to call
your service was horrible though so I'm
not going to call you anymore for
mistress feet I will travel to any
destination he just drops it
like
that oh isn't that the beat up World
Robert from gondo place oh wait just a
sec
second is that it is that's the windmill
propeller that thing was supposed to
have fallen down below the clouds you
was saying the whole story haded done
for G's family was actually true
yep just just put it on there come on
come
on just repair the goddamn
windmill bunk bnk bnk bunk emote
Doo now not to do it if you can find
somewh to spin the propeller oh I know
how to spin it honey
honey cutie honey cutie
[Music]
honey that way going to take a long time
to turn it all the way around you were
so close but you had to go in that
direction Hy
Flash
and there it
is here oh it went too far or is it
okay I think it
worked it just locks in automatically I
think
[Music]
what
what the
hell what is that mysterious
thing let's check it
out
uh
[Music]
aha oh by the way for next week when I
do the cooking stream I'm planning to do
lasagna for the first time I'm excited
my first self-made lasagna I hope it
it's not too difficult so it should work
first try right I'm excited
lasna that I can graduate the Frozen
lasagna Club but you know what I might
still eat eat it every once in a while
cuz it's like easy and it's actually
pretty
yummy wait do I have to what do I do
with that do I shoot my laser at it wait
a second do I need my iron shield to
reflect or or My
[Music]
Sword I don't know probably my shield I
the hype oh
we have to stand in this Holy Light
maybe
not um I don't know the lyrics anymore
but we're just going to fake it till we
make
it read there's a sign a that
one let's sound the goddess song beneath
the lights Radiance okay I have to stand
under the light
[Music]
okay
oh that was fast what the
hell I didn't even have to remember the
lyrics or the melody or anything at
[Music]
all wait a
second
what wait it's not moving
[Music]
properly why is he not making the sound
anymore
oh
[Music]
are you
okay I can't sing for you I I can't I
can't how about I sing and you play the
heart huh n okay what the freak is going
on no I'm moving it but it's like it's
the joycon doesn't it's not about the
Rhythm I know the Rhythm okay I get it
but it doesn't strum
[Music]
anymore there you
go
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
beautiful SS lag yeah think it is Sim's
language Master there is a high
probability that this beam of light will
lead us to the close as to the
whereabouts of the free
Flames I recommend that you investigate
what lies at the end of this beam of
light investigate that reminds me of a
first cab stream and that made me think
right now I wonder what kind of
collaboration stream the second gen is
going to
do what what their first collabs stream
will be like what they thought of you
know curious so you want me to go over
there and that that
hole
interesting council meeting ah yeah that
seems like kind of like obvious yeah a
council meeting will they discuss
humans and the that we're
doing I'm not a human though so it
doesn't really imply to me does
[Music]
it so
will they decide Our Fate
ooh but but I want to decide my fate on
my
own I want to be the
one who decides my
fate isn't there something about that
tals of arise the challenge that binds
your fate or something like that the
Fate that binds your CH what what is
this place
[Music]
n what what
what what is this
place what is this
place what is
this I don't even know how to attack
these things wasn't there a way to
attack during a fight thank you for the
membership
welcome wow oh my
OU
how it's a rainbow I want to go to the
[Music]
rainbow ouch I landed Softly on the
flowers how pretty but there's nothing
really
here oh well okay
Here We Go
Again Sid
[Music]
tracking y
okay uh should I land on the middle
platform there we
go
Master what do we have
here
master link I have memories of this
island it is known as the aisle of songs
signs bless you signs indicate that it
was left here for you by the goddess
Master however I'm unable to determine a
means of entering the structure ahead I
suggest you investigate the
area oh thank you for saying it in
German guys thank you
thank
you oh he's enjoying the rain hell yeah
rain rain on me I love that
song but I forgot the melody otherwise I
would challenge D MCA right here right
now rain rain on Rain On Me Rain On Me
rain on on me wa on me what is
this I knew it you have to hit
it but in a specific order or what oh
dear you have to like actually go
through those
openings and that is not my
specialty I'm going to break my sword
here
well
okay we have to figure out a
pattern we have to figure out a pattern
move them
[Music]
move this looks like Super Paper
Mario this is Paper Mario
oh in combination with this what does
that
do
[Music]
what after the rain R take the sent
pedestal to complete the bridge all yeah
I get that
I get then I have to build a bridge but
it seems very difficult to do
that oh my
[Music]
God like
uh
oh
oh one H the middle one and
uh and so the first one I want to keep
there which is this one so we don't want
this one to move
[Music]
anymore
uh no I have to keep that one up
though
uh but I also have to move the one
that's stuck up there now yeah no but
that another one will move again wait a
[Music]
second well uh you know what I move uh
the other one for
now as close as
possible M let see what
[Music]
happens move that one maybe a bit more I
don't know
[Music]
man ah but that one
I guess I I probably have to move that
one
again I mean that one is easy to put
back into the middle I
guess uh let see what happens
ah
ah now they would be in the
middle uh well at least they're lined up
now those two
um oh wait wait if I stop that one there
can I land them
up
yes now they're lined
[Music]
up but are they lined up too early will
that not help me if I'm M now shouldn't
they all me in the middle what did they
get oh smart it didn't even take me that
long
yo yay
[Applause]
solved it okay let's save here I feel
like we haven't saved for a
[Music]
while top right T thank you thank you
thank
you
sa what do we
have ooh I shall upgrade my sword here
will I get the master sword
[Music]
here hey I missed damn
it
[Music]
hey the
mou
oh that looks
funny master link I have important
information when you struck the crest
with a skyward Strike from your sword a
message from the goddess awakens deep
within my
memory the goddess intended this message
for you master these are her words as
she's going to sing again and dance
right there she goes woo he who seeks
the sacred Flames listen well for I
guide you from my place at the Edge of
Time the sacred Flames are free in
number to obtain them you must also earn
relics known as free sacred
gifts he's not
spinning you are the spinning
Queen for each trial you overcome you
shall be blessed with one of the gifts
[Music]
There She Goes you are the spinning
queen young and slim
only
machine spinning
Queen
[Music]
SP
y You Can Dance you can
SP having the time of your life o spin
that ass show me those legs so I spin
your
spine I don't know I can't come up with
lyrics at the
[Music]
spine make use of the power these gifts
and you will find your way to the
purifying sacred Flames now shut up and
stop singing now I bestow unto you a
Melody it will serve you as key opening
the first trial that awaits you deep in
the Wilds of faren
woods she's doing
parkour
[Music]
loving all these
Melodies that song is called Ferro
courage it's browsing Melody will guide
you I learned for RSE
courage
courage Master you must overcome the
trials set before you and obtain the
free gifts to reach the sacred flame I
have committed foro kage to memory now
you can use your dowsing ability to
search for the gate leading to the first
trial you must face as suggest you set
out for faren Woods as soon as you are
ready I was born ready several times
many times I was born many times yeah
wow thank you me
lady where where's the big big
statue I'm going to go look for it BRB
BRB I didn't find it okay let's
go
stop don't be stupid
link it's not down there yeah weirdly
weirdly
enough okay
so shall we go directly to faren Woods
H wait I still don't have my upgraded
sword I guess I have to yeah do old
obviously have to why do I think I would
get it in there cuz it looks so
beautiful and holy but no I have to go
through the free trials
first all
[Applause]
right is there any treasure on here
maybe over there will I be rewarded if I
go looking for it or
not could be there too but I just saw
some gates there what what is that
place what is that place Pumpkin island
has new side quest ooh
[Music]
n ouch what is
that
oh holy you gave me a heart
attack
me wait wait wait wait
SM they Hornet hell
yeah yeah yeah shut up I want to get
more I need
those where is it where are
you where is it a I left are they back
up
there I heard it damn
it come
on
yes you're going to kill
me don't kill me
oh I'm getting a whole swarm of it stop
killing me okay I have enough of them
[Music]
o
nice maybe maybe we needed some of them
for some
upgrades I don't remember I didn't look
that closely what we were
missing Mo move it move it move it
shortcut for some day
later guessing though that
uh I can only continue here once I have
that like diving
ability am I correct with that
assumption give me those
Heights
okay that Island won't have a side quest
to late G
come okay then okay that's a tiny tiny
tiny chest okay whatever I don't
care I don't care about it I Don't Need
It clown
Island clown island has something
new
really
I'm
leaving on a ver plane I don't know when
I'll be back again
probably in the later
[Music]
game
PTSD you guys
okay come on it's a beautiful song we
going to appreciate
it where am I going now elen
l or side quest the the Pumpkin island
you guys said
oh why not we already finished the
dungeon today we might as well L some
side quest right where was that Pumpkin
island over there pumpkin Landing that's
like King's
Landing gave yourself a really nice name
huh okay uh that
[Music]
way let's
Go sing it before going back to Japan
and we'll love it again I see I see that
makes sense yeah but I like the song
it's just a really pretty song I like
singing
it let's try to go for this
hole will today be the day is now the
[Music]
time wow that's so fast
no
hello I I come here in peace and
oo don't fly away
[Music]
there we
go give me some cool item come on Bo
boing thank
you
[Music]
okay now the thing is though I think all
my oh no this one is empty I have one
that's empty okay so if they want me to
deliver soup again that's
good don't they tell you stuff too is it
[Music]
so let's
see you have some wisdom to
share if you draw a symbol of money on
certain walls you can make an easy
fortune
draw
[Music]
and now Everything feels peaceful and at
Harmony
[Music]
again there was just some kind of
disturbance that I felt in the air you
know I had to do something about
it my job is done
here help pick the pumpkins oh no
problem this should be an easy one for
you kind Kina spends her afternoons uh
picking pumpkins pick picking pumpkins
is that like a tongue
breaker
okay
okay is that a
hint okay we're got to pick some pumpkin
[Music]
guys pum pumpkin pump pumpkin pumpkin I
didn't notice that that's
funny hi oh and con next to have has
been decided looks like you'll be
helping with the pumpkin harvest what a
relief which is funny cuz she has a leaf
on her hair
[Music]
band do you have any idea how heavy
those pumpkins
are oh yeah H yeah have quite those
noodle arms yeah yeah yeah just like you
Tak you think this is going to be a
piece of P pumpkin cake do
you let's make this interesting how
about you carry five pumpkins at once
you better take it slow or you'll risk
dropping them oh God do I have to
balance oh dear
balance like on top of my head I have to
carry five on top of my head over there
okay why do I have to do it like five at
once why can't I not just carry one by
one
huh
okay if you panic and start to rush
you're going to drop the don't worry I'm
not I'm not the type of girl to panic
over anything honestly I'm
calmness in
[Music]
person
yeah um
what what see I didn't panic I was just
confused one more time
please the other way
okay okay okay okay okay okay yeah yeah
yeah hi hi hi
hi okay okay okay no Panic no Panic only
calm
oh easy easy
[Music]
easy I want to go left yo I know your
pumpkins want to go right oh they even
move if I don't move that's
funny I want to move over there
guys can you
stop
[Music]
uh-huh don't fall down we're almost
there I did
it I just knew you would come for you
managed to carry them all I guess that
means you're done carrying pumpin oh I
want to do more I want to do
more I want I do more can I do it
again strong night oh thank you I am a
strong night yes
[Music]
yes that was just five pumpkins it's not
much
Harvest oh well I did it all right oh
you what should I have you work out next
H yeah you've got that interesting
looking instrument
oh I got it I've got the perfect job for
you but that job can only be done at
night wait until Nightfall and come back
and see me okay can I sleep in this
house well I yes I
can wonderful I will sleep right here
right
now oh no you guys are you you guys seem
to feel weirdly about this upcoming mini
game
[Music]
good
luck strange looking yeah yeah
yeah Kina is a
singer okay yeah that that sounds
fun goodbye
ears you might want to use a controller
for this okay I can do
that uh where is it h it's on on the
floor use your whole arm if I use the
joycons it is it so difficult try it
first
okay wait does she sing like super fast
and I have to like strum really fast in
Rhythm okay that sounds
[Music]
funny
make sure you're not playing too fast or
too slow okay okay go
again big sweeping
motions
okay I see I see what's going to
[Music]
happen you ready to
sing let's do it sorry I'm not even
reading it
[Music]
anymore la la la la
la la
[Music]
la
this
W she sings beautifully did I do
[Music]
it what did I do
wrong what did I do around that was
pretty exhausting okay I thought it
would sound a lot better when you played
it just cuz that's such your pretty
little in when you have there the
customers didn't seem impressed
evil my ribm was wonderful got the phot
the arms oh their arms I was trying to
be in ribm with the
music I was too fast yeah she's having a
good
time yeah
[Music]
okay that wasn't really looking okay
let's do it again one more
[Music]
time
okay
[Music]
la la la la la
[Applause]
[Music]
F oh
God toally saw that coming um did you
like
that
okay it could have been better could
have been
better
Mo oh uh should I not play during H solo
okay I should stop too oh besides that
was it
decent yeah one more
time
it was perfect besides that really it's
a solo okay
[Music]
okay la la la la la
la a
[Music]
sh la la la la la la la la la
la
[Music]
la I think that was pretty
good oh
come on come on come on come
on
you're kidding me you're kidding me
you're kidding me playing the solo which
one some people say play in the solo and
some people don't say don't play in the
solo use the sword this time can I just
[Music]
yeah oh
okay so young should I play during the
solo I was I was just I was
[Music]
just
oh oh W arms you can just follow them if
you need a guide to Riv pick a customer
whose movements are easy for you to
follow I mean the ones in the front they
they have the same Rhythm don't worry
about the dire just make sure you're not
blame to f nice speak sweeping motions
to strum when the customers stop moving
it's your chance of free sell does that
really matter though
okay
okay okay the people who told me to be
quiet during her
solo
Ben to the usual room of you to the
usual room how dare you deceive
me
[Music]
[Applause]
la la
[Music]
la la la la la la la la la la la la la
la la la la la la
la la
[Music]
la was that
good
la la
[Music]
what do you say about that what do you
say about that
don't thank God was that not good
enough
[Music]
my you're not happy with it but you'll
let me go with that
really we're done first TR
[Music]
we at a new
heart we're in second row
now oh I thought I have to do it again
to get like the big the big
reward well um I think we should you
know destroy the next chandelier as
well just because they kind of insulted
my work of art
right there I think that's kind of
rude
anyway
um 10 million fireflies you would not
believe your you would not believe your
eyes if 10 million fireflies L up the
world as I fell
asleep cuz they let the
open everywhere
come
back I'd like to make my self
belief that planet Earth turns
slowly it's hard to say that I never
when I'm
asleep cuz everything is Never As It
Seems yeah our first one let's get
another one let's get a bunch of
them
a got you going to get you too yeah
nice the other one is gone though okay
no time to uh destroy this field of uh
Caba yeah that's what you get for
insulting my
music just stre heart Challenger you got
no taste of music so how about you learn
it and pick it up and by streaming heart
Challenger for God's sake or Sparks or
whatever you want anything that's by
T it'll be good for
you anything at this point cuz you're
lost
Cara Revenge
okay
byebye
wo I couldn't call I couldn't call my
BB how do I have to do can't fly that
what the
um no they didn't see it yet so uh
let's just uh quietly go in there and
quietly go to
[Music]
sleep I money good
night good night
everyone let me
look uh for a
[Music]
moment
uh-huh
[Music]
okay okie
doie what do we do
[Music]
next wait can I get some fruit I have a
lot of cut fruit that I bought at the
supermarket and I want to go get it a
BRB there's some pineapple in there too
so maybe that will help me with my
[Music]
voice
you you
show
my cats are sleeping on my bed
oh the bedroom
[Music]
yes oh wait that music that she was
singing to is still still playing well
what the hell sorry I I think the
microphone was like
weird okay so we got all kinds of fruits
we got straw a few strawberries every
time when they do these mixed cut fruit
fruit they only put like one strawberry
in
there but there's also uh melon
[Music]
and what was that again
uh
uh grapes yeah and
Kies and
blueberries let's start with a
strawberry the best thing in there
[Music]
M
watermelon and
[Music]
pineapple actually that strawberry
tasted
like
didn't really taste good anymore
[Music]
y
I thank
[Music]
you yeah it just didn't taste very fresh
anymore m
[Music]
no I dropped the melon on my keyboard
now there's cat hair on
[Music]
it okay I think I got the cat hair off a
bit no not everything is sticky now just
two
[Music]
keys what oh I love I love these
um not the watermelon but watermelon is
here too but it also has
the the Honey Melon and the other melon
sugar melon what was it called in
English wait something with cop calop
calop that's how I remember that word
honeydew and calop okay I I was like
translate directly translating the
German word for
it Hy do is the one that's orange inside
right and calop is the one that's white
[Music]
inside the other way around oh then I
prefer um I prefer honey honey dew but I
like
[Music]
both wait no I'm talking about outside
are you guys talking about
inside honey do are you guys talking
about inside or out outside cuz outside
they have different colors
[Music]
honey de has green flesh it you mean
like white green white most it's mostly
white yeah Cel up is orange inside okay
okay okay okay okay yeah I prefer
honeydew in that
case but I like both as I said I like
all melons I Like Big Melons small
melons white melons red melons orange
melons
[Music]
I mean I really do I really
do y yep good melons Yum Yum
Yum e watermelons
[Music]
watermelons
she announced the that she's doing a big
solo concert that's so
cool that's so
cool in October
[Music]
right October 12th oh man I wish I could
see it I wonder if they stream it as
well they put some kiwi on there but
there's like a slight tiny amount of
skin still on
it I don't know if I want to eat
that there will be a stream ah should we
do a watch
along B them a s Bai concert watch
along it's kind of my thing isn't it
I've been doing it since like the first
[Music]
one again she
get so people are able to come in
person I actually didn't watch the
stream so I don't really I only saw the
things that were announced on Twitter
afterwards but was Callie a guest on the
stream cuz I saw her like on the
thumbnail like as a silhouette blacked
out what did she do did you just call
in I
really
did she say
like
[Music]
congratulations English challenge oh
funny
[Music]
mhm
okay
nope I didn't see any merch yet
no ah
[Music]
interesting what pineapple is so
good P
[Music]
Apple
except on pizza that's not
[Music]
true I have to say though the fact that
you can't fly at night is pretty
lame it's so lame like what's the excuse
for that aren't you supposed to be free
in the
sky God wait was I supposed to go to the
fen Woods
right go you can't see just put a light
on God damn it also what's with all
those lighting beams that I see in the
sky are they turned off in the night
can't see you
out oh
well well well where do we want to go
uh do we have to go for a temple
[Music]
again should
we we just go to the main entrance
and my left wing has to sleep okay that
that makes a little bit sense the big
tree viig tree
maybe viewing
platform
okay yes let's
descend B has
descended a report master link I have
detected the aura of the of a Trial Gate
nearby if you can pinpoint the origin of
this Aura using ding I conjecture the
song you learned at the aisle of songs
foro courage courage why do I read it
like that like
page will reveal the gate I read it
correctly in the beginning but then I
like jokingly read it differently and
now I can only read read it like that
kage
[Music]
piz oh man uh are we looking for the
right thing yeah okay what where is it
Loco under the tree by the way can I
reach that thing over there
[Music]
yet I can I reach
it I don't I don't really know there's
one over there too I can still not reach
those can I
damn
it o
[Music]
four oh wait that's not even
I it's not even the the stone the rocky
thing oh
then
[Music]
H
[Applause]
me
[Music]
it's not a forbidden
word something here is reacting to our
performance of A's carage I have
confirmed the appearance of a strange
mark on the ground I calculate a 90%
possibility that this Mark is a Trial
Gate as mentioned by the goddess statue
we heard from the aisle of
songs trust FR FR you sword into the
center of the mark and on the ground
before
[Music]
you okay oh okay we're going right into
it
[Music]
oh why the music change that's so cute
now oh I love it it's so
cute I love that soundtrack okay ready
sword his
eyes
[Music]
[Applause]
oh there what's
happening oh no no no no it's night time
scared we
[Music]
no I don't like this because this gives
me
um um what was that Zelda game the scary
[Music]
one that's TW princess this gives me
twil Princess Vibes and scares
me quiet
[Music]
as expected I cannot follow you into
this realm for this trial calls out to
your mind
alone you have green teeth by the way I
don't know why this is the nature of
places known as silent realms they are
domains of the spirit accessible only to
the goddess chosen
hero this particular trial for worst
Silent Realm tests the limit of your
courage your spirit has temporarily
separated from your physical body so
that you may undertake this
challenge to reach the location of the
Flames that will enhance your sword it
is necessary for you to overcome this
trial and undergo spiritual
growth just feel your
chakra are you feeling it
link it's a
flower flower power let me eat a straw B
to celebrate this
mhm
[Music]
mhm that one was
decent we got the spirit vessel this
mysterious plant represents your spirit
link Spirit link Spirit Tracks Spirit
Tracks
mhm that is your spirit vessel when this
vessel is full it will signify you have
successfully completed the trial
allowing your spirit to
grow this in turn will allow the goddess
to bless you with a new
power to fill the spirit vessel you need
to search for something known as the
tear
[Music]
of there are many of them spread across
this strange
world master do you see the glowing
object just in front of
you that is a tear of forr you will need
to collect 15 of
them however this is not as simple as
task as it see would seem your work in
this realm is referred to as a trial for
good
reason if you take even a single step
outside the protective Circle you stand
in The Gardens of his realm will wake up
and pursue you
master if a guardian manages to land
even a single hit on you your spirit
will shatter and you will fail the
trial well you must collect the tears
scattered throughout this area and fill
the spirit vessel without being hit by
an
attack was my explanation clear
Master
yes understood master I will be eagerly
awaiting your return in the outside
world may the goddess watch over you
master but like I cannot step outside of
this but how do
I how do I get it if I can't can't step
out of the
[Music]
circle
wait we're fine for a minute what is
that what is that what is that what is
that what is that what is that wait what
was the thing I just got the thing that
I just got was uh H this mysterious
enables you to see beacons over the
position of sacred
for
[Music]
quiet I don't know if I can do this
properly
[Music]
I'm scared
mommy uh I see one up there okay we can
do this
[Music]
easy I
unusual liquid substance that covers
that area as soon as the wake you C of
do
me hold me and it has certain
unique properties if you make a contact
with waking water the gance will be
immediately oh I will be
immediately alluded to your presence
pools of waking water allocated all
there they woke all throughout
the area I suggest you watch where you
st you could have told
me you kidding me wait what
happened okay okay okay if I collect
those things and everything's cool again
oh my
God okay okay
okay
okay okay um there's one all the way up
there now it's gone but I saw it I saw
it so I'll go out all at the
top it uh the flower pedals that are
like disappearing up on the uh top left
means that um the time is ticking right
until now it's filled up again
okay okay okay
okay so when that runs
out the things will hunt me right okay
oh dear wait how do I how do I pass this
y y y y y have to go from that side
oh I'm scared oh y don't run out of
breath okay we still have enough
time can I go for
here wait I can't go for here
either
salmon
no circle is safe yeah but can I
go
wait I don't know how I don't know where
to
[Music]
go a that's tiny
hole oh God oh God okay okay it's fed
back up okay oh my God
[Music]
um how the hell did you see
me I don't think you really saw
me no oh no you
didn't ah there's one over there hey I
kind of like this though it's really
spoopy but it's a nice uh uh different
kind of challenge although I
hate balancing on these things move
faster no just go like that
[Music]
go are you stupid or
what hang in there I'm
hanging okay
uh don't fall into the water again ooh
got some fancy stuff
there oh there's something there a bunch
of them
oh
God right in front of his face that's
spoopy oh okay up
here got to try to find everything um
close by
ASAP and don't just run around straight
ahead so so that I don't have to
backtrack afterwards and look for one
specific one for hours and now
hours something down here though and
down there so I I think I'll jump down
ooh right
here nice we're almost done
guys don't go for the green ones unless
you're little on time oh
okay you mean the white
[Music]
ones anyway I found
one they're so scary SC the way they
stand there is so menacing asserting
dominance no no no
no no
no wait how do you do that how do you do
that do I have to
a I thought the water was gone but okay
we were safe we were safe we're
safe okay this one go and oh I see
another
one I see another one we're missing
[Music]
one no no no no no no no no
no where is the the last one see now
that's that's an issue when you don't
see the last one I knew this would
happen I see it over
there oh
uh over there over there over
there it's so close we can get
it
me
yay
[Music]
easy that was easier than I thought it
would be you guys don't I'm just going
to assume that the next ones that we're
going to do are going to be more
challenging and
difficult oh
mhm oh thank you thank
you wait let me catch
[Music]
that where is the where's the blue
beam
all right we have no issue now we can
relax it's over there I
think wasn't there a hole on that
side right here
exactly
yeah collect all the purple things I'm
trying I'm trying the ones that I saw I
definitely
collected I suppose they're going to be
precious for crafting and you can only
get them in here right so
to get as many as
possible
yay
woohoo
oh water dragon scale does that mean no
one can dive
your power to explore underwater and
even execute a spin
maneuver
[Music]
what so glad we did that first try oh
hello behind
us sorry I'm eating
pineapple congratulations master link
that was absolutely Divine Exquisite as
they might say you have passed this
trial you now have the power to proceed
to the location of the first sacred
flame that will enhance your
sword the water dragon scale is one of
the D goddess sacred gifts the great
spirit of the water dragon has provided
you with the ability to swim freely
underwat the flame you seek is somewhere
Within These Woods
master I must conclude that this flame
is likely in a part of this area you
have not
explored perhaps something I can reach
by
diving hello are you
okay oh hello again I see you have the
water dragon
scale that's amazing I heard that if you
have one you can swim for the the water
like the dragon SCE through the sky
there must be places here in the woods
that you haven't visited
yet you should use the water dragon
scale to explore areas you couldn't even
get to
[Music]
before okay bcha thank you you literally
told me the same thing as that lady oh
is it right
there I'm going to deal with you first
St wait you didn't care for that oh oh
Susan
Susan go come
on I blocked it again hi I'm back hello
hello why does it keep on blocking
me now I missed it
f
wait God damn
can I not cut it
here
a interesting you changed your
position
skywards oh that's a good idea I
never think of that except for like
ritual kind of
[Music]
things oh oh I did not really give a
about that
[Music]
oh if only I
could
oh no no no no no no no you I've been
using a beetle so
often it's not working with this thing
for some
reason keep on bonking into
it
swim under it but swim I finally
did it
okay okay let's
swim and how to die there we go
oh
wow and do I have to go to the right
side is there a
hole there is ooh
oh oh wow I have a lot of uh breath
under water
thankfully and that one fills it up okie
dokie okay swimming feels not so bad uh
on the water with the motion
control this is like a tutorial or what
are you actually going to give me
something at the end of
this
oh
[Music]
hopefully oh yeah it's a kind of a new
place inside the great
tree chat told me something
interesting h
go
up hey go
up no
attack I don't know where he gets that
power from but okay
wow uh let's try this
one
bam I dropped him too nice
one before they annoy me when I'm up
there I'm going to kill them right
now I hope I don't need them for
something there we go easy sniper K At
Your
Service
uh can I reach that no of course not
which means I have to swing it
somehow
H oh come on just want to go back above
the
water
ah I wonder if you have some kind of win
thing oh yeah I forgot about
that
oh oh wow how surprising
[Music]
okay okay nice what about all these
areas up there can I get something there
no just
decoration what is bats okay into the
light oh we're
outside
[Music]
mhm oh I got a
better B
pepper another new item finally I'm
collecting some new items today it was
really desperately necessary
why am I
[Music]
here let me shoot
you oh it's
dead big
success and you leap over there please
link and go nice oh there's another
Spa makes a sound that my my stomach
makes when I'm
[Music]
hungry and shall we get the bees as
well nice oh yeah I
mean no no no oh
h no no no no no
no can you not around like
that no they all
disappeared we can shoot it
again we can shoot it again we need
those bees I'm really sorry but why are
the spiders
[Music]
back
[Applause]
yay y
yay why is it moving like that I need a
bigger net I need a net upgrade that's
for
[Music]
sure wait if I leave the
uh Nest up there can I get honey from
that in my in my
um in if I have an empty
thingy Empty
Bottle yeah how would I do that from up
[Music]
here what the hell some of these fruits
taste weird
ew ew what the
[Music]
what ah it's difficult to reach one
again turning
[Music]
around okay I need to
readjust for a
moment
[Music]
and can you guys say I could take it
like that
you have a great stream boss thank you I
am having a great
stream take them take them take that one
too still one left look I'm wasting time
here
go no why you do that you stupid
Beetle oh I took it I took it how do I
place it
down
how I what S I broke it
wait oh I got
it a hornet
lar a precious source of protein that
comes from a de horness Hive nice we got
one
[Music]
finally
nice okay now now I think we can
continue that is worth
it me
get a blue b
i e
to now we fall down for a little bit uh
speed us that need
removal I see you don't think you can
escape from my Phoenix
eyes don't hide behind the lime wire
plants it's not going to help you oh
I destroyed it there we go
okay now the question is can I survive
without the lme wire plant oh it's
already back well then no
[Music]
issue uh where am I going to land
here okay oh I think I did it could I go
even higher
[Music]
no hello we're back inside the treat are
you an enemy you definitely look like
you want to be stabbed in your
tummy
oh oh oh
oh
uh could I blow him up I
wonder
or oh a bomb at him damn you dropped it
boy you dropped
it
what happens he's he trying to go back C
oh this is
dangerous come
here dude he still doesn't have his
shield anymore though
so okay okay part two
buddy
okay um oopsy
uh okay
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
I can't get it I can't get it
right my shield is
breaking
oh my God
[Music]
I you almost pushed me down again give
me
H oh well that was a little bit more
difficult than it needed to
be safe
okay
yeah I do have a pink potion with me I
think those spider noises are terribly
[Music]
adorable oh hello you
blue oh dear what do we do a
[Music]
bit woo oh that's very close to the edge
man
okay W what do we have in here
nothing sus huh sus very sus all of
[Music]
them those
bats oh I got something special from
that one
noise why is the spider noise becoming
louder and louder is there a huge spider
on top of that
tree can I take this
one I can't it doesn't even care about
me being so
close what is that
sound you have reached the top of the
tree from this vantage point you have a
good view of the woods perhaps you will
see an area you have and
explored couldn't you have gone up there
and told me what it looks like
a master look up
there I have confirmed the discovery of
a new
Kik analysis indicates a 90% chance that
the sounds we have been hearing were the
loud snores of this Ki ah I thought it
was a
spider uh should I shoot it down I don't
I mean I could also grab it try to grab
it maybe although I don't think this is
actually going to
[Music]
work oh well it did not work how I
thought it would work are you able to
come down by
yourself what it I'm
Jing look at that a real life human
haven't seen one of you in a while
CL I used to call me ow now I'm just the
old K hermit I watch over this Forest
here when I'm not
nothing I don't know how you wandered
all the way up here but let me ask you
something can you really see me of
course I can what about you guys can you
see him he looks cute is that so well
then slap yourself on the back clock
you're not St kick my can't even see me
these days I think they're trying to
ignore you for some
reason but forget all that nonsense and
tell me what business does a real life
human have in these Woods The
Flame you're outet I'm talking to myself
or somehow I'm always talking to
myself if you think about it what you
talking
to you're out questing for flame to
enhance your s C so that you can find
someone important to you huh how about
that a human who can see me and seeks
the great
flank listen do you promise not to
breathe a word of what I'm about to tell
you to another soul I
promise all right I'll tell you but
remember it's a secret to everybody the
flame that you seek is most likely for
flame duh
yes yes for War's flame that Story
begins very long ago when the goddess
was still with
us a secret to everybody ah it's a Zelda
reference
oh the goddess gave the flame to the
water dragon a great spirit that
presided all of the fire and
woods the way I hear it is she left the
flame in the care of the water dragon so
that one day the mighty Dragon could
pass it onto the one from the sky you
see C I've got a hunch that the goddess
was talking about you lad well that
Saddles that you must seek out the
mighty water
dragon
ooh her Lair is deep in a lake in the
south of these Woods she watches over
the flame there there's a problem though
the gate that leads to that lake is
sealed shut to all those who judge who
are judged unworthy I'm worthy am I
not but don't worry C I want you out in
on the trick to opening the gate is it
my sword is it my
sword to open the gate you have to
channel the power of the Goddess ah harp
it's harp time but it isn't so simple
the symbol is incomplete to unlock the
gate you must make the symbol
hole the only way you'll know what the
complet symbol should look like H is to
First find that same completed symbol
somewhere else in the
woods the gate is down in the South so
it's likely that there's a matching
symbol somewhere up in the north try
searching this
x okay okay up there and then we go down
there okay is all of this SE into your
Headland do you know where you must go I
think
yeah then I wish you Sav Trav GL thank
you wait
out oh my God he looks like a mess also
very pixelly what the hell is that
texture on him I forgot to mention this
earlier but it's important her
Excellence the water dragon is very P
picity about maners so what yours
okay Chad do you also have your manners
with you I've heard stories of fox who
caught her in a fussy mood they ended up
as mid morning sex C oh dear we don't
want to be eaten do we we're still not
fried you guys are still that
fried soon
soon I probably taste like old c m see
yeah how you look like it
[Music]
too so don't let her know I told you
about foror's flame okay and remember
when you're in her Hall you'd better be
on your best I know I know I
know I'll be here napping if you need
some of my Elder wisdom no thank
you we go look for a
thing that is where's the X the x is
gone but I know where it
was cuz I paid
attention can I just oh yeah it
oh
shortcut wait could I
have fallen tried to fall down from this
platform in a way
that I could have gotten a new Cube
[Music]
or
No Yes
Fu I'm not going to go up there
again at least not for
now there are two both of them that I
can get from up
there and
I can always go later yeah
yeah all right so it should should be
somewhere here
[Music]
right oh you want me to just take that
from the
[Music]
ground
remember this well I I remember
that remember how it looks well there's
a circle in the
middle and now where's the piece that I
have to bring to the other
one Miz it okay so now I go
here
H okie
dokie can I go that
way
follow the light
guys thank
you can I swim upwards uh that waterfall
or is that like a breath of the wild
only
[Music]
thing
and full rest I'm actually fine right
now
Ste my shield oh I guess I could do that
uh what
N I like how he puts it on his
shield
sweet you don't have me cl tun damn
it oh got to cut those trees again they
grew
fast woo splitting those
trees o a chance for some feathers I
will not miss
it oh cute
BS
no I don't know you kind of have to be
like fast but you also got to be slow at
the same time it's very difficult wait
so I'm here now
but okay do I have to fight these idiots
first oh my God I came out of
nowhere don't
don't you know I didn't I didn't really
understand how this works after all am I
supposed
to draw how how can I draw on the
wall draw on the
wall
I did not know that that was a
thing oh dear you want me to draw a
circle that is
the
m with that shaky ass motion control you
want me to draw a
circle okay
okay carefully slowly beautiful Circle
oh
[Music]
dear they are very
forgiving thank you thank you game thank
you very very kind of you that was not a
[Music]
circle
what is it I going to laugh about my
circle as link your circle was absolute
mhm all
righty
[Music]
um perfect
jle thank
you
M
wow I kind of want to save but there's
no save point here so whatever I just
jump
in do a
flip
yeah no
oh beautiful
music link Gloria
Gloria good night and good night to
everyone who has to sleep thank you for
watching
ooh Lake
Florida all right let's just water so
much water water everywhere oh my god oh
oh it's FL flowing on its own
okay I have to go that way it seems oh
yeah wow there's eels are they going to
attack me please don't attack
me give me that give me that
yeah are you God
no way you look lame jell
your wait a second if they don't finish
riding jelly fo fish and I think the
Phoenix thing is like the same kind of
pattern the one that was called
feny gra original names yeah first
there's Fey now there's jelly
fu
okay okay I just have to avoid eye
contact and back
slowly you scared of
me don't be scared of
me y
[Music]
it wait am I supposed to like catch
you it
woo oh quit following me pest if you
don't move along I'll be forced to tell
her excellent salana Dragon about your
little
incursion what am I supposed to
do I'm going to follow you it's treason
to spin I have
to didn't you see you didn't see that
coming did you yep there's no way you're
going to be able to follow me now I'll
just do my spin again so what now are
you going to cry if you think you can
make it through just go ahead and try
okay jelly
Fu
okay how is that even possible listen
I've never seen a human pull off a spin
like that girl wait that's so water
dragon scale does that make you the EM
Emissary of the Goddess like the one a
dragon said hey I've got an idea maybe
you can help her Excellence I'll take
yeah about that it happened really
recently this weirdo came in here with a
gang of monsters and went right after
her Excellence my lady the water dragon
is a fierce fighter and boy did she
gobble up most of those monsters in the
first few
seconds thing is there were just so many
of them while she was distracted the
weirdo leading all those creatures
managed to wound her she's healing up
now but she says we don't have enough
special water for her to make a full
recovery special water is it bath water
so you could please talk with her
excellence and see if you can help her
out I'll even take you to her follow me
okay let's go
[Music]
do nice noise
link I want to get that one damn
it
oh no you could have cleared the path
for me honestly but okay no
problem let me swim in that dirty Mass
here can I save for a moment yeah
b or do I have to push those towards the
the the that hole to make them go
boom Sorry boss I'm late no problem
welcome to the Stream
Dam safe we're probably not going to do
much more though cuz I got to read super
chats
uh we will see about that hi I'm here
what now where are we going that's weird
I was expecting to meet up with my
friend here and the path is blocked with
a huge Boulder out those stones no
problem I think I know what to do I I
think I'm forced to take damage myself
as well but all right
we got to get into the right position
though oh oh there's one right there
yeah
nice let's
go oh I'm lacking air I need some
bubbles uh Yos okay is she going
there
I hello is this your
friend don't eat me I won't I won't eat
you where where's the Excellence me the
L Dragon no are you looking for her
Excellence you possess one of her skills
so you must be a friend to our kind I
will tell you where you can find her
oh h a little way up there if you want
to make a note of that that's probably a
good time of
it I'm another
hotel sure no that's not really
it there it is perfect
County
I didn't know they add voice acting to
the
remas it's voice acting by Taki Kar you
can hear it only on my stream very
special
effect it's a secret to
everybody okay no
problem uh where' she
go uh
let's look at at the map uh-huh here we
are so we got to go that way go ah we
have to explore make one of one of those
stones over there explode as well
okay
damn it I wanted to Ram right into
you that didn't work out I hear the
crispy noise
again I really should figure out how to
use my damn it no how to use the capture
card that's like built into my
PC really should figure out how that one
works um because I've been
using I've been using uh the Elgato game
capture that I've had for a long
time and it's just
yit
ah I don't hear it yeah it's only
sometimes it's really
weird but I feel like if I figure out
how the one works that is that is inside
of my
PC but I have a little bit less issues
[Music]
maybe why is is so
stupid
oh yes explode right here could you
please
[Music]
explode oh
man
it
uh oh yeah focusing makes it
easier
I was I shouldn't have praed that the
swimming was uh decent and easy cuz once
you have like a specific Target it is
not so easy
[Music]
anymore gra
it
o like at least I got some money from
that you my
show
oh hello you are exactly the one I
wanted to
meet no we're so far away and I'm slowly
dying respawn please oh that was
fast no
nice breathing icon reminds you of Mario
64 I guess so I'm just glad that the
swimming doesn't work like in Mario 64
the the controls yeah they're at least a
little bit better than the ones from
Mario
64 I can say that I'll give you
that but that's not a difficult thing to
improve those
[Music]
controls
got
it that was close that was really close
how am I supposed to get through
there what do you expect me to do
girl
it you can't get through shees you
humans and you bones talk about
inconvenience I guess you can leave over
the top of this
oh I see okay you guys really want me to
use this motion control wait what's up
there
though can I get up
there maybe in a moment
okay okay that was not even that
difficult wow perfect jump first
try it's call you amazing but I think we
both know it was the lot of dragon scale
that made that little stun possible H
all right girl all right okay I get you
don't like me that much I'm trying to
help you though don't be
rude I don't know if I can pass through
that
ouch I yeah I don't think so I have to
Fly Above
again
[Music]
okay go go go go go go go
go E what I did not expect that to
happen oh thank God there's a safe Point
here and I think I saw a treasure
chest like a burp fly like a burp flying
like a
BP
I don't know where my home is I don't
know where my phone
[Music]
is really like that
song There we go got his Plum
nice those are very special I
heard okay
now which way should we
go did she swim that way oh yeah she's
there but I want to explore a little bit
wait a
[Music]
second all righty what's over there
there must be something special here
you're going to drop down or what oh
it's a big
one woo so many and none of them dropped
a thing really no slimy drop at all not
even a single one that is a bit
lame oh wait oh that's what's over there
a I
[Music]
thought and
go your eyes are insane you she Tria to
just sparkling things Minecraft blocks
in a ridiculous distance but right now I
think everything was pretty reasonable
to see generally I agree with
you thank
you Cube unlocked
yada we can check it out maybe next
time we've been playing for five and
almost a half hours I wonder how much
longer we should go not much
longer
not much longer also I'm still not sure
about tomorrow if I will really do the
stream or
not uh I I'm not
[Music]
sure I want to go up
there although I mean I don't really
care that much about that golden
thing you you'll start the next dungeon
soon so you could stop and do it next
yeah that sounds
good no okay
whatever a break day
yeah yeah I've been trying to only take
one day off per week but it does get
very
exhausting oh we have to go down here
now all righty unaki I want some of that
e and eat
unidon
M before I went to Japan I I would have
never thought of eating eel but it's so
good in Japan unidon
yummy it looks a bit weird when you turn
the meat around cuz it's really really
like it has a weird color
it looks kind of
weird a not again why are you going
to make it so
inaccessible just go back and then
you okay what is
that can you swim straight for God's
sake go
uh raise a wheelchair around for
real I'm not a I'm not a fish or
anything I'm a human in this game at
least okay come on come on you can do
this oh
[Music]
did this gives me Super Mario Sunshine
Vibes ah there does are the monsters
came a they're back that's one of the
fish that we brought in here to and used
to attack her Excellence watch out
they're mean as they come how do I how
do I find it it doesn't look like very
mean but okay do I just bump into
it that's some kind of
infection okay let's try
this probably oh
dear what the hell was that was scared
of that's
it as if a goddess couldn't have done
something against it what what are you
calling yourself goddess
for what a weak goddess you
have if that makes you so much trouble
that you have to hide
oh man that's lame how do how do I open
a door open it up right
now don't waste my
time do
it at last we're here don't tell me I
have to find a
key you the key aren't
you her Excellence the water dragon is
just up ahead hang on just a second hell
yeah you are the
key
spoilers in the chat my dear
friends wa it's
okay we're we're I guess going to find
out
soon please
[Music]
coming she's a key just like
me
noise I have finally
arrived
oh
[Music]
M uh okay do I go to the
top oh
yeah it's going to take a while give me
a moment maybe I'll just explore the the
area a little bit that's that's uh
totally on
purpose you hey come
on
you must be kidding
me you must be kidding
[Music]
me okay I have to tell you guys it's
really not
easy it's really not
easy I'm like making the weirdest
positions with my hands oh finally
okay I just love water levels no water
levels should be banned from RPG games I
know this is supposedly not an R game
but it should be banned from all games
from all games is that all there is in
this whole
area telling me that's it oh God oh God
oh
God uh oh God oh
God oh that was
close St n okay if if it's a game that's
like literally all about that then I
trust them so much that they're going to
do a good job at it so that's
okay hello are you a
Pokmon are you a Pokemon I think you
are oh my God I want to just go up
there oh my God what he he landed but he
immediately jumped back in there okay
fin oh yeah hell yeah yeah that was
style you have a human face and that's
creepy as hell
nand is there any treasure over there
there is how do I get there wait a
second never mind goddess more important
things than that oh
no mind your maners creepy face she up
creepy
[Music]
face oh come on it was so
close why is it so
painful why is it got to be so
painful oh my God
finally
[Music]
was in
there
okay
okay not bad
yes okay is there any other
[Music]
treasure for now let's just go to the
princess queen goddess
[Music]
whatever
wait a little bit away from the platform
and
then okay it's actually that
[Music]
easy oh you there
human you have intruded my home a sacred
Place few are permitted to
enter there is no place for one such as
you and yet here you stand you will
explain how you got here and
quickly I am those with manners address
me as F Warden of the woods I was
appointed by the goddess
herself though my current stature
stature is less than well intimidating
shall we say know that you stand in the
presence of a loyal servant of the
[Music]
Goddess I say that's one of my scales
you have there
a sacred gift such as the could as that
could only be carried by the goddess
chosen hero but could you really be
him this raises
questions even with that scale in your
possession finding my hall is no easy
task how did you find
me ah yes that cacan old hermit
kiwi told you where I live didn't
he yo can you fix the audio real quick
girl it's messed up again I
don't know what
happened sh better honestly I can't
remember how many times I've told that
scruffy bastard to keep his
mouth shut that's the last straw next
time I see him I will eat the out
of him I will stuff first with some KF
pedo oh but I digress you've come here
seeking a sacred flame have
you yes I knew
it but I'll be straight with you a
shrimpy boy like you hardly looks the
part of the Goddess chosen
hero there is no doubt about it a test
is in order to prove your everything you
say you are shortly before your arrival
I was attacked by a pompous creature
calling himself
gim I stood against a self-proclaimed
Demon Lord but I was wounded in the
encounter the wounds he's given me are
stubborn things have been forced to
recuperate in this Basin of sacred
father unfortunately the healing
properties of the Sacred Water have
diminished and I am now in need of
another dose to freshen up my healing
bath bring me the container of fresh
Sacred Water that I
require do me this favor and I'll gladly
show you where to find the sacred flame
you desire what say
you I have no
choice
um I got to switch back
my my thingies
I am analyzing the water remaining in
the bin excellent I can now help you
dance for the water type you are
searching
for w
yea Master you have wisely elected to
carry an empty
bottle use it to carry the water you
seek yes I'm wise because I have an
empty bottle yeah M oh oh
dear if you continue down this way you
will find an exit back to the
woods excellent now run along one does
not keep a dragon
waiting wow wise interesting uh
creature um
but I
think I think that's where we will leave
it off and read some Super Chat
where was the saving Point again maybe
if we go out maybe there's one right
there let's
see
boom go up go
up sounds good save point forward all
righty well well well I think we did a
lot of progress
today um
yeah thanks for the stream though thank
you for supporting me and watching me oh
I see something says let's play The
Hub stream
sp there he
is hello boy
boy oh thank you for the item I
appreciate it what is your wisdom they
say drawing a symbol of love upon
certain walls will he your wounds well
how would I know like which which
wall it is what about this
wall let me let me W let me try that
[Music]
once but I I guess it will like kind of
like give me a sign that I can draw on
it cuz it doesn't work like that okay by
the way that's
beautiful I let's go
see wait is that the it is that it
though wait wait wait wait wait chill oh
no it's over there
this this place looks like it has holy
holy Sacred Water I guess that's not it
okay
safe yes please thank you you might
enjoy this next Temple don't tell me I
have to dive and swim the whole
time no no
no
no oh
it's a actually a really fun dungeon
really it's a cool Temple
[Music]
okay looking forward to it I guess um
thank you guys I'll take a two-minute
break and then we'll read Super Chat
shall we do it that way yes yes yes
yes everyone go take a little break
break if you need to go to the toilet or
whatever you're welcome to do that I
will go to an idle meeting because I
don't go to the toilet I go have Idol
meetings thank you for your uh patience
and your virtue and for watching this
Zelda stream next one either tomorrow or
next week um I'll have to really uh see
how I feel I'm sorry about that I will
guys let I will let you guys know as
soon as I
uh
feel I don't know uh as soon as soon as
I understand what's going on in my
body okay I'll see you in 2
[Music]
minutes
w
[Music]
I'm
back
M oh cute okay let me fix the
[Music]
chat love the Super Chat readings really
thank
you welcome back silly bird you're
talking about
yourself y
simulator h no
pizza no
Pizza righty
uh
yes okay good at DM
[Music]
me the ones uh that we have to read are
the ones from today and yesterday right
nothing from before you're like
y not not like not like in particular
no I'll keep the soothing Zelda music
running if that's okay with you
guys yeah I'm I'm happy I've been I've
been bonding a bit more with
G tails off super chats
oh oh I didn't read those
ah oh
really tails are super
[Music]
chats wait where am I H superh Tom Tony
yeah we got to cab again also I going to
collab with Amy again and finish that
game that we we played last
time uh but I think next week when she's
back it's already too busy so it will
probably be the week after that
yeah I think next week is a little bit
too much going on again as
always but I want every week to like be
special and have something going on
because uh
otherwise
otherwise I don't know it's not going to
be too exciting I want every week to be
exciting every week there should be
something
special
m but it's all also difficult somehow a
little bit to always when you do this
for over a year then it's maybe a little
bit difficult to always come up with
something special every week but for now
I'm still fine for now I still have some
ideas H but I don't want to lose this
like I I don't want to having routine
and all and chilling is nice and all but
I don't want to lose this thing of
having something special going on each
week
[Music]
nice
Taos yeah I think it is still special
yes or can you are you going to say are
you going to say that my whole talks are
not special and that my my K is are not
special are you saying that not not
every week that I that we are here
together is not special I think they're
special
having you here special oh come
on
special any moment with you guys is
special wait did I read the member's
only super chats I didn't did I oh dear
you guys said tails off but there's
actually something from before that the
members only super
[Music]
chats W you had the GIC phone super
chats oh okay we got to read a lot oh
god oh that's actually a
lot oh
y oh
[Music]
dear all
righty all righty I haven't been tanging
much today anyway I'm mostly focused on
the game
today couldn't really think of
anything to talk about anyway weirdly
enough even though there's always so
much going
[Music]
on tell good to drop the schedule oh I
think she's about to drop it cuz she
asked me about something about the
schedule I think she's going to drop it
like in the next few
hours you sure why why should I I tell
her
though give her time sometimes there are
like specific reasons why our schedule
is late and that is mostly not because
of us being lazy but just because we're
still waiting on some kind of
[Music]
information did you watch the Pokmon
thing no I did
not I didn't I want to watch it but we
have so many super chats to read let me
see what's the number what's the magical
number
today oh oh that's a lot yeah I don't
think I can afford wasting my time with
watching the Pokemon
presents
[Music]
Pokemon okay let me put out the
thumbnail of what we're
reading members only G
phone I wanted to do for next week
because the Mario Kart tournament is
next week I wanted to do a Mario Kart um
members only Mario Kart you know a
little bit more calm so that I can
actually learn something from it but
we're not allowed to
play Mario
Kart on members
only so that's not happening it it's
it's actually quite like I want to play
more I want to play more games of
members on members only streams but
there's a lot of games that I would want
to play but that are not allowed to be
played on members only so it there's not
a big Choice there but GIC phone was
amazing and GIC phone seemed fine so we
might want to do that again and Fall
Guys Fall Guys was actually much much
much more fun to play in Members Only
than it was to play um in not members
only yeah these rules are weird I mean
it it makes
sense because well then it means uh you
forcing people forcing forcing to get
your membership in order to play Mario
Kart with
them
um I I see
the reasoning behind it but it's not
really like I'm forcing you guys so you
guys are already members I don't really
think there's much like really anyone
who's going to join right now to play uh
uh yeah play Mario Kart with
me but it makes sense it makes
sense I I get it I get it I just I
totally get it
but I'm played Mario Kart on MERS only
before oh yeah that was probably
when when some things were overlooked at
a time where some things were overlooked
and probably probably Nintendo didn't
say anything anyway but it's getting uh
very strict these days
[Music]
mhm which is why I think you guys have
been seeing so
many um streaming
cancellations and delays from the girls
side I know I i' I've been seeing a lot
please don't be mad at them things are
getting very
strict
[Music]
yeah
members only even if the stream is
public I if I understood the correctly
I'm not allowed to do it like members
only
participation so um like the thing that
we did with GIC phone public stream but
members only participation that's not
possible with Mario Kart
par yeah or with like any Nintendo
[Music]
games which makes me think did I not do
something like that
with now with Animal
[Music]
Crossing I was H it was not members only
but it was like only chosen people right
people that I chose on Twitter I
think it's a little bit of a shame
because
with Members Only You just feel a little
bit more of a safety nothing against the
people here in the chat who are no
members but you know there have been
some trolls among the non-members every
now and then in certain streams of
certain games who just want to see the
world burn you
know
yeah
yeah so it's just kind of a relief to
play games with members
but yeah anyway it's all right I get it
I I understand completely it's
fine at least we can play stuff like
Fall Guys and GIC phone with members
only and I think stuff like sliver doio
probably as
well
yeah um I don't even know if we're going
to play Animal crfting on stream again I
really just have a hard time to spend
time on the game because if you want to
play if you want to play Animal Crossing
properly you have to spend so much time
on
it and you know I don't have that time
oh yeah among us as well yeah yeah
yeah
yeah I hope your German studies are
going well now that we know your German
ranking hle I've is now rank free what
the who is number two and number
one then huh and who decided that in the
first
place who decided the ranking hi is it
because of yesterday but that doesn't
mean that I would be number three what
the
hell good E I am
good well if number three is uh number
one if we look at it from an Australian
point of view then yeah you are right I
am number
[Music]
three let's look at it from a different
point of view you
[Music]
know this point of view
specifically where's my little
[Music]
chicken that's you let's let's flip you
as well do a flip
nice should we just flip everything
should we flip the laptop no I can look
I can see from
[Music]
here I'm streaming from Australia today
yay how's it going guys it's it's like
really cool here it's snowing
outside
wow I need a blanket to cover myself
it's so
cold so
cold
freezing and
bet jingle bells jingle bells jingle all
the way oh what fun it is to ride in the
one open say
hey good day
mate I'm a jet I'm I'm a jet jet jet
have you guys noticed that in the past
few streams I've sometimes said that I
will
jet I've been trying to show off my new
found
Australian vocabulary but I don't think
so anyone really um reacted to it I got
a jet
yeah that that was supposed to be
Australian
Australian never noticed it
I'm not a ceiling fan never heard an
Aussie use that well I have heard an
Aussie use
that I have heard an aie use
that that's where I learned it
from jet as in leave yeah I'm leaving um
I got a
jet I want to learn more
trying to scare up Iris no for that I
would also have to put on a Santa hat
and be like ho ho
ho oh ho
ho Merry
[Music]
Christmas hi let me move a little bit
over there why am I okay this is
good ah where am
I where did I
go I lost
myself I lost myself in the
void
no
[Music]
hello where am
I here I am I don't know where I went I
I
jetted I'm
back are you guys dizzy yet just chill
on my head I'll protect you okay let's
read some read some super chats y yo yo
[Music]
yo
okay
M
stank thank you
for wasn't expecting a cat so done oh
yeah I started out with having my uh
having smoothie on the microphone
purring for like 10
minutes Tel on the Teno
oh that's a good joke Teno means sealing
in Japanese with a J with a
j
yeah Japanese
[Music]
pun so anyway love the pur as ASM just
got done with my stereo Pur as ASMR one
cat in each ear
oh do they ly next to your ears like
next to your head oh I'm kind of jelly
about that like mine are really close to
me as well but it's not like they lie
down directly next to my ear anymore
they used to do that when they were
small and I think like male cats like to
do that uh as they grow up as well
they're generally like a little bit
more on the uh clingy
side they groom me too w
that is so sweet yeah but I think a lot
of female cats are yeah male cats are
cuddlier female cats like to take a bit
more distance which doesn't mean that
they don't like their owner but yeah
they're not as affectionate and clingy H
yeah but I think as my cats grow older I
think they will also become clingier cuz
that's one thing with cats as well my
cat is imaginary what the hell get
yourself a real cat that's much
better thank you Spanky
[Music]
fim kind of jealous I want to get a that
that's actually a reason why I wanted to
get male cats originally and I was
supposed to get male cats but upon
picking them up it was like oh actually
they're female and I'm like okay now I
got to think of new names what the
originally I was going to name them
something
else yeah but but I got to say the
female names that they ended up with
which is actually not chunkers since
movie they have actual names the female
names that they ended up with ended up
being like sounding much much better
than the male names that I thought of
anyway so it was probably for the better
yeah kind of rude of the burrito yeah it
was it was the whole thing the more the
more I the more time passes the more I
feel like that was kind of a little bit
bit of a
scam yeah I'm not sure if the cats that
I have are really the breed that there's
there supposedly are that they that he
told me they are I'm not sure of it but
I don't want to I don't want to make a
drama out of
it there's a there's a breed that looks
very very similar to the breed that they
supposedly are and I have this feeling
that yeah that it is the other breed
that it is not
supposedly but it's okay it's all right
what's you cat's age tal
uh three three wait a second 3 and 1/2
years I
think
bootle cats that's that's what I've been
[Music]
thinking they're not no they're they are
Eternal but they just still are young
they're going to be a million years at
some
point yeah they are Phoenix
cats I love them yeah even see I don't
want to make a big drama out of it
because I love them so even if the breed
is not really what it was supposed to
that's that's okay with me I love
them
Jim thank you for the red super
chat
super hey D it was really fun seeing you
at the mega con panel yesterday oh yeah
e you were there was also fun to meet a
few fellow kfp members KY employees
there thanks for answering my question
about your favorite accessories
combo wait you were on the
stage I don't remember I saw
everyone's face literally for 2
seconds but but the convention staff
supposedly recorded the whole
thing I could check
back
yeah they have a VOD from the zoom
[Music]
call now I'm so
curious cuz it's like it's it's it's uh
kind of like cool to be able to imagine
like who who who you are but but that's
a bit creepy I guess so um never mind I
will not look at
it I guess that's a bit creepy
we found GAA
what why did what what are you guys
talking
about anyway uh oh and the moment when
we alled the wave was great oh yeah I'm
glad we could do that again although it
was it was uh a bit awkward um I was
able to hear you guys but there was
quite some noise noise cancelling so I
also didn't hear most of the cheering
and the the things that people yelled in
the audience out of nowhere like stuff
like I love you and so on barely got
picked up so uh unfortunately I I was I
I thought I no actually that's a good
thing cuz I thought that the audience
was way more quiet than it actually was
after watching some Twitter clips that
were up uploaded um I I heard that you
guys were way way way more excited and
Loud than I uh
perceived
it perceived Perce is that is that the r
[Music]
one a k
cosplay no I didn't see one unless you
mean like someone in a chicken costume
and you're trying to roast
me yes perceived hum Hummer anyway fo
thank you for coming that's so cool that
you were able to come thank you so much
really excited yeah and I'm I'm Al also
I was also quite satisfied with the
questions that I got I got to be honest
um cuz I watched the panel from uh
Amelia and um there were some
interesting questions there but the
questions that I received I was really
happy with all of them I I I liked all
the questions they they were like
um like
like kind of
like I was able to have proper
conversations uh about those
[Music]
questions yeah meaningful yeah exactly
that's what I'm trying to say they were
meaningful meaningful questions
mostly
yeah no no no no no no no no no no no no
don't don't no no it's not not anything
about the
teammates um I think a lot of
uh very um simple questions got picked
on the first day and then after upon
having like a another discussion about
what kind of questions should be picked
I mean that was the first day so it's
obviously there's going to be made some
improvements on everything
afterwards yeah and I I asked them to
choose people with some deeper questions
I I specifically uh requested that
because of my personal
preference I asked for some deeper
questions that um yeah are where where I
I would be able to give out a bit more
information um we found good out what is
going on what do you
mean
[Music]
yeah the rule rule number four is
probably not a
[Music]
thing oh well well cosplay huh there
were a lot of good
indeed yeah um
continuing
domow thank you for the
[Music]
pink
fore
[Music]
elction thank you for the pinky thanks
for the K re broadcast cental I used to
be fan of M kinana so hearing you sing
singing her song really gave me a
throwback and the rebroadcast ending was
apparently cut off by the Ian Cal that
that was just
me by the Anor so here's my outf in for
it oh yeah you guys didn't even really
get to do proper of
do thank you I'm glad you guys enjoyed
it I'll be doing that with on archive
streams more often to rebroadcast them I
think that was a good idea yeah I'm glad
you guys are enjoying
[Music]
that wa
what thank you for the pinky
El you were awake at that time what
the during the read broadcast Koka I was
awake in the beginning to start the
stream went back to sleep or tried to
sleep and then woke up again to end the
stream and then again went to
sleep which was really really weird and
I don't really want to do it away again
like that I hope I can find a better way
to do it next next time kak danin big
wild beast danan thanks for the pinky
finally got to catch a stream and with
some smoothie ASMR Perfection thank you
you came at the right moment
yeah a that purring it just it's just so
nice something so soothing about cat's
purring I love it
[Music]
m I missed it again hope I can catch
next one ah tomorrow maybe no stream but
I'll I'll think about it
uh however don't worry if there's no
stream tomorrow then you have time to
watch the V
yay always sleepy for some reason Nene
diesel Dan Moon Dan GD thank you for the
pinky hi hotling enjoyed rewatching and
reliving the fs during the unar yeah
okay too bad fireflies did not work out
but the other songs certainly make up
for it especially last night good night
bloody Divine and exquisite singing
thank you I appreciate it thank you mate
thanks
mate glad you enjoyed it last night good
night was very difficult to sing um I'm
really surprised that you guys enjoyed
it but it is a beautiful song yeah it's
probably not my my voice that was so
special about it it's just the song
being so
good in it mate all good
mate thank you thank
[Music]
you Felix thank you for the red super
chat wow T I'm here to recharge my K
energy for the next week so that I can
survive through it this game has been so
great to watch thank you T thank you as
well regardful yeah it's a lot of fun to
watch and to
participate I'm glad you enjoy the
feelings maybe one day you can
participate in around as well don't be
shy don't be shy you don't have to be
good at drawing to participate in glic
zone yeah thank
you thank
[Music]
you
and penguin with pecked cap than thank
you for the red super chat T my favorite
painter AKA say that please tell me
off did I not already read this
one I read like a did he send it again
cuz I read this one
before or did I read it during the
stream oh okay okay well well I I
refuse thank you for the r Super
Chat time and D
penguin with a oh wait no I scroll
down thank you for two
pinkies just before your birthday I was
sent to the
hospital what's going on I have read
this
[Music]
before did you send the same message
again ah oh okay okay okay okay okay oh
dear ah you fought because YouTube lost
it or
something
aha thank you again thank you you get
some
[Music]
kissies this thank you for red Super
Chat that was quite the d Vu just now
yeah we're in the time
[Laughter]
Loop turning the stream at the best
possible time also deposit on a cat
stroller from Amazon let's go cat
life all the art that came out of that
was really cute in the GC phone stream
um I did uh I drew um a a prompt uh of
me H taking out my cats in a baby
stroller outside for a walk in the park
and I was I gave myself this cute
dress and and all that and twin tails
and all that and and some people made
some cute art
uh some cute fan art with that theme
that was
lovely really
cute I love the idea of going out with
my cats but they are stay atome cats and
I feel like it would be a huge step to
take them out I feel like smoothie would
be in for it but chunker is not so much
I don't want to stress chunkers out
against her will I kind of want to try
it out with smoothie at some point but
like not necessarily in a
stroller actually I saw
someone a popular Instagram cat owner I
saw her like having like putting her cat
in a in a cat stroller and then going
with that to like a park or whatever and
then like taking the cat out of the
stroller on a leash the whole time on a
leash and then letting the cat like roam
around a little bit yeah a cat
harness cat
harness we smoovie always wants to go
out that every time I come home from
somewhere and I open the door smoovie
the moment I open the door smoovie
immediately like squeezes her head out
of the door even if I only open it like
cenm and it's it's really high to block
her she often makes her way outside
anyway but it's okay like
um uh she cannot really go far or
anywhere at all in this current uh
layout of
apartment so I I I'm just like usually
I'm just like whatever I'm going to pick
you up in a moment after I drop down my
groceries and then I go outside again
and pick her up and put her back into
the apartment but she always just like
runs out there walks a few meters then
drops herself on the floor and then like
does does
this like she rolls on the ground I
don't know what it is it's like as if
there is catnip on the ground or
something she just rolls on the
ground it's so cute I guess she's
marking her territory
maybe she rolls on the
ceiling no on the ground on the
[Music]
ground maybe she's marking
H or the floor is just so
comfortable she's definitely playful
[Music]
yeah cat must not be Australian yeah
yeah she definitely is not
[Music]
Australian the floor is is lava yeah the
floor is lava which is why I am on the
ceiling right
now thank you this Laria GD D this L
again thank you for the pinky do Cat
strolls come in those side by side
bottles just like the stolls for people
with two babies uh I don't even know if
there's a difference between like if
there's cat specific
strollers I guess probably
yeah but I don't I don't know
man
don't worry though
because if I were to take out my cats it
would only be smoothie so I don't need a
side by side
model unless I get an Apple cat and app
cat and app cat and another cat and
another
[Music]
cat
I just want my cats to like once in
their life see what it looks like
outside and feel like real grass and
stuff on their
pause I just want them to feel
that and see that the world is not only
dis apartment you know what I
mean
yeah you changed your
name feeling the real cusa touch the
Kusa no I'm not going to bring grass
into my apartment on the ground I no
that's not it that's not
real cat-sized V
goggles put some cat-sized V goggles on
them hell
no moond thank you for the red super
chat K first let me apologize for my
extremely horrible drawings oh no I had
a great time though drawing used to be
very fun for me in the past I might keep
proving my lost passion thank you for
being my oie and all the fun streams
keep being an inspiration to all oh you
want to start drawing again I think
that's a great idea whenever I go on
Twitter and I see all the great fan art
like not only fan art but also original
art from any random artists that I
follow or that I see for other people's
favorites um I I when I see good art
like that it's just really really makes
me want to draw again just don't have
the time for
it
well art
motivation I definitely have it
somewhere in
[Music]
me next art stream when I don't know it
just makes me nervous to draw on stream
makes me nervous and I don't get very
far h
thank you thank you guys I I'm happy you
like my
art inspired to play the piano again wo
that's cool I wish I could play like
instruments at all I wish I would have
been
raised um to learn an instrument like
learning it now is like kind of too late
I feel like I mean of course you can
always learn an instrument
but I don't know
um I feel like I should have learned it
from younger times on but there was just
no no money I guess it was
financially that really
possible I don't have time for the UK it
would have been so cool if I could have
like done like weekly sessions with my
BFF cuz she's like really good with uh
guitar and she can easily pick up the
Ula for me and she's been even trying to
teach it to me for left-handed and yeah
but it's just not possible man maybe one
day maybe when everything is calm again
and I don't uh
have any schedule going on then if I'm
bored
I might pick up
[Music]
something don't stop don't stop just go
your own
[Music]
way
you taught yourself Japanese you can
teach yourself an instrument ah it's a
bit
different I don't know because I thought
my myself Japanese when I was very young
you
know anyway mundock thank you and I
think it's great keep doing what you
want to
do I believe in
you counting chickens
D thank you for the pinky it was the
most stressful thing I've put
participated in but I enjoyed every
second thank you for the experience yes
it was pmer that
pineapple CA I I remember something
there that was really entertaining thank
you this liia thank you also for the
pinky I only saw the Orlando con 2
minute intro clip that the convention
tweeted but good on you for giving the
kfp lawyers some more job
security let's be real though that's a
job you have for life for real though
congrats on another con thank you thank
you thank you another one is coming up
again
soon yeah it's really cool to be able to
do these
[Music]
things thank you thank you thank
you
94 counting
chick thank you for the
[Music]
r
and that's it for the phone Super Chat
thank you
[Music]
everyone next up is TA
of um
tails
uh where is
[Music]
it there it is I feel like I did a good
job at with the
thumbnail the demo test play really
stands out I need to use that kind of
style more
often it's like kind of simple but it
stands out really
well good
thumbnail I was proud of it thank you
I'm glad you guys enjoyed it but that
demo uh it's not enough I need to play
more I need to play
[Music]
more it's less than a month away so got
to be a bit more patient
Patrick
Das Felix oh thank you for the red super
chat as
always H I can't watch you can't wait to
watch you play tal of R so have fun and
I know I said that I want to try out the
tales of games but I haven't got too
much time for gaming no problem I only
played for a few hours in the past few
weeks oh which one I'm trying to get
more time for myself
though that sounds important you you
seem like you always have a lot going on
and very busy but but yeah take some
time for yourself
definitely and have fun with the tales
off games I'm glad you're you like them
I'm glad you're interested in
them I love my
[Music]
jaies I need I need a massage I haven't
gone to a massage in such a long time
maybe I should get one
tomorrow cuz my back really hurts man
should I get one
[Music]
tomorrow
oh get some stuff done and get a massage
instead of doing Zelda preparing holot
talk put smoothie on your
back
oh oh that would be so
nice that would be so good
a chill day is it is that
okay I don't
know I need some pain
relief no I've never tried
acupuncture
[Music]
need to relax I've also really been
having the past few days issues to brief
while I'm
[Music]
streaming oh thank you guys you guys are
so sweet you just so sweet what the
hell you're cleaning clinics in Japan
well yeah there is stuff like that but I
never used one of those before I don't
know I don't like it
they call it U
mimikaki I don't like that it feels
weird I don't know how like Japanese
people really like it but I don't like
[Music]
it
Mimi cocki Mimi
cocki that it just feels like like um it
feels it feels uh
weird
oh seems like mothers in Japan like to
give their children these uh ear
cleaning like
massages that's why they get used to
that at a at a young
age and it feels relaxing to them
because of that
interesting but what I've seen before
but also never tried is you know how
how there's like the there's a I'm
talking about a different kind of uh ear
cleaning where there's like some hot ass
fire or wax or something next to your
ear and then all that comes out of
there I'm sorry but I thought that was
fascinating have you have you seen that
before you tried that before
those are fake that's not
real that's not
real that ear cleaning candle yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah it's fake how is it fake
it's a trick
candle
[Music]
what what candling is a
scam
[Music]
y rocket has
launched the Kiana rocket has
launched Kaboom
Kaboom I have landed K rocket has landed
on Mars I here
now T chicken
cute don't worry the chicken has a
helmet so rocket launch no problem for
this chicken we need an Daka you
watching I think I need an astronaut
chicken of a astronaut helmet
we want to go to the
moon this chicken is not quite ready for
going to the
[Music]
Moon safety
first astronaut chicken sounds cute
doesn't it who who of you guys wants to
volunteer to go to the Moon with
me I'll be a rocket Phoenix rocket
doesn't it sound sound like a good name
for a
rocket me me you guys want to go to the
Moon I'll take all of you I'll take all
of
you fly me to the moon and let me
see what it looks like up there
let me see if we can build a chicken
civilization there a
kfp at the
Moon
kfp very
soon
[Music]
oh oh sh wrote to me when are we doing
Outlast
uh
um can we start with
something a bit
more beginner
[Laughter]
friendly that single player yeah yeah
yeah but we were going to do like like
she's going to be in a Discord call just
to call me and like help me
[Music]
wait I need to find the right uh
emote uh
to express my feelings with that there
we go it is begin of friendly hell no
I've heard that Outlast is really really
really really really
bad I've been told you can't fool me
people told me that Outlast is like
really really really really really
really really y
it and you guys know me you guys she
said no she said no she said she said no
I don't know what that means probably
means
no does that mean
[Music]
[Applause]
no
yeah now she
said well I don't have a heart monitor
[Music]
thingy I'm going to die in that stream
I'm like really bad with that
stuff I don't think good is going to be
much of
a calming medicine to me let me get you
link do I do I not have to like attach
something to my
body or she going to make me order
it
yum yum I'm going to
die oh
that will be so
exhausting that will be so
[Music]
exhausting
oh there it
is heart rate
sensor that's that's so that's too
expensive that's that's too
[Music]
expensive can't I cannot afford that
nope I can't can't can't can't afford
that too bad we can't do the
Stream
[Music]
she's
listening good I I will do anything for
you
so I shall I
shall I shall or or order
everyone say hi to
[Music]
GA come on Brave Warrior play the spooky
do the
scrim yeah I'm I'm a I'm a brave Warrior
right um part time part time Warrior I
have to play around a little bit with my
shifts I'm I'm I'm so busy um my my
shifts at kfp you know uh I'm a tantal I
used to be a full-time Warrior but times
have changed it's very very busy there's
not much much to fight out there anyway
these days
um so much to do every day so many
employees to fry um so many employees to
uh have job interviews with and and so
on but I I'm I'm sure I can um figure
out some way to um squeeze it somewhere
in there and in my into my schedules M
[Music]
what yumy
yumy I cannot run it
seems well well good I will let you know
once I receive the thing the holy thing
the holy heart rate monitor stream heart
Challenger Ty looking for the
sky looking for the
top Lord Alo the
moderator the
[Music]
moderator he's so
funny thank you for the red super
chat I appreciate it very much you have
been your friends have been very
delicious
[Music]
today was that again what was that name
again
[Music]
translate
opportunity Bon Malone thank you for the
pinky T you a certain chicken needs a
lawyer after wrongfully being tossed in
the usual room
is it
you I'm here to volunteer to be that
lawyer and bring Justice where needed
delar mentioned something about waiting
for jma's call too weird right
belar
belar he will not receive a
laar he has no right for a lawyer the
usual room is
justice
thanks for the
pinky
Andre insomnia thank you for the
pinky I'm so happy that you are playing
one of my favorite J G Series thank you
tento for all of the entertaining
content and keeping up also please teach
me about bazongas wait I don't know what
the what bazongas are I don't know if I
can help you with that but it's your
favorite J with you serious you got
amazing taste you got great
taste one of one of us one of
me my guys is
[Music]
booss did I say
that why is he asking me for it is it
because I said
[Music]
basas um I think you already know what
bazongas are chocolate
Andia thank you for the
pinky I will do a full playthrough of
tales of Verizon on my channel so please
look forward to that oh by the way the
PS5 that I'm getting I'm allowed to keep
it yeah so that means that we can do a
full play through of T of arise on the
PS5 not only just one episode or so I
get to keep it yeah so
cool no we're not stealing
it no stealing
kfp yeah that's so cool yeah cuz I mean
isn't the PS5 still really hard to get
even
now yes but gab wrote me something I
I
[Music]
know
getting
[Music]
from
sorry bonding with GAA okay everyone
look away I want privacy with
GAA just kidding
[Music]
uh
okay
[Music]
y I'm
happy
no you you could never interrupt
me I always will make time for
you let's talk soon I love
[Music]
you can't sing that song properly
anymore it's been so long since I last
heard that
song
gu
gu okay I'm back to Super
Chat Angel V world than was it Mega con
Orlando oo you did Super well and it was
fun nice thank
you
yo sweet Kate kfp D thank you for the
red
z i a fan of Tails and I'm really happy
to tend to play the game thank you I am
also a fan of Tails I know it's very
surprising and but I have to admit and
confess that I am
actually a tails off N I love tales on
the whole series yes
yes call me surprise a
[Music]
surprise
what so much effort for one
pose surprising wow I never heard of
that
before
wow wow what thank you say
that let's enjoy the journey of tal of
arise
together it will be a definitely a fun
and legendary everyone thank you
R
[Music]
alone I'm done with
those
now and next up we have Super Chat
readings super chats from
yesterday uh do I have the Super Chat
reading thumbnail somewhere here did I
not save it like a while
ago I feel like I
[Music]
did are you guys enjoying the background
music by the way is it not too quiet
should I turn it up a little bit
louder I hear the water flowing it's so
[Music]
nice it is divine isn't it it's so
chilling
[Music]
yeah
uh what the birds do you guys hear the
birds do you hear
them I hear
them 1 second let me save the Super Chat
reading thumbnail once
again good ga good you're still
listening to this boring uh Super Chat
reading
[Music]
stream I don't I don't think she
is you know since she's since she's
asking me for an Outlast stream don't
don't you think I should ask her for a
stream as well
good since you demand
a
h horror game stream from
me I shall make my
demands as well
please can we do uh
CL together with the Yamaha
[Music]
synchr y chat is going
[Laughter]
crazy I want to do that with so many
people oh she said
Focus
swore only in my presence
she said yes she said yes if you like it
you should to put a ring on
[Music]
itoh ah I will I will figure it out for
us oh good I tried figuring out before
but Japan the program has a Japanese
interface huh I didn't even take a look
at it yet but we'll figure it
out
n no problem there shall be no issue
nothing can stop
us
nothing
oh
no
I will figure it
out apparently you need a membership as
well interesting okay no problem and
Super Chat reading Super Chat reading
Super Chat reading Inception Super Chat
setion super setion super chat super
[Music]
setion
motion thank you for the pinky I know I
now have a lot more respect for your
ability to keep an audience entertained
while being upbeat for multiple long
hours with very little breaks you're
very cool boss well thank you where does
that come from but I think a lot of
people do indeed not really like realize
how much energy that takes
up
and I think
yeah it is definitely some somewhat of a
skill that you can definitely learn like
to talk and talk and talk for hours and
be like an audience Entertainer you know
yeah that's why not everyone is a good
MC on stage for example a moderator and
all that endurance
Queen speaking of endurance Queen yeah
cie actually did break my
record
well well well I'm not not planning to
break hers again anytime soon but uh it
seems like we have another mission kfp
we have a new
Target uh but it's like um I
mean I just always do these long ass
streams like if you count my my total
streaming
hours in all of whole life English I
think I am number
one and I think I have like double
double the streaming hours of cie I'm
I'm just streaming too much in general I
just stream too
much I don't know how many hours I have
but you guys probably know you you guys
probably have the
[Music]
data how much do I how many hours do I
have over a
thousand I have over a thousand
streaming
allies what what the
really oh my
God 700 in 2021 only oh wow holy
[Music]
that this all that's
insane that's insane oh my God why am I
streaming so much I can tell you why I'm
streaming so much there's something
inside of me that just
says I have to work
hard in order to make up for some things
like I feel
like that's my way of
fighting yeah stream as much as I
possibly can and take it as a full-time
job yeah I mean I I think
like if I if I
felt at at ease uh to stream less and I
would do
it but for me I feel this
uh feel like
I I I I need I need to stream more yeah
it's fun though I'm I'm definitely
enjoying it and
[Music]
um it's not like I'm forcing
myself there's there's some ambition I
guess but
[Music]
like yeah don't get burned out though
yeah that is always the risk when you
stream so much that is always a risk
yeah I'm going to be careful of that
don't worry I don't want to burn out so
much that I can't stream anymore at all
but I think
generally I'm Phoenix you know I've I've
been I've been in this business for a
long long long time way longer than you
guys and I'm used to
it and I know I
know how much I can take
and it's just like my part of my life
it's my whole life is like you know
stuff like this
so yeah it's just normal at this
point I have no more I have no more
chalky milk damn it tiny tiny
bit tiny bit was in there okay no more
CH
milk anyway anyway anyway thank you
motion thank
you
P thank you
[Music]
for
B streaming hours yeah yeah yeah yeah I
don't know the Japanese girls are just
built
differently I don't know how some of
them do
it coron Senai although I looked at
coron senpai's archives the other day
and I was like she has a she does long
streams but she also does a lot of
shorter streams in between as well so if
we talk about Queen of longest streaming
in in h life Japan would it be vatai
does anyone have those numbers like who
streamed at the most hours in Whole Life
Japan in this year I guess you can't
really like do a total of one because
then some girls are in her life longer
than the others but what about in
2021 is it V
really by far number one holy
wow indemn
[Music]
me is that wait a number three when you
mix Holo Ian and whole life Japan no
way no
[Music]
way I'm in the top five of all of our
life in most streaming hours well that
scares me that actually scares
[Laughter]
me oh my God oh my God am I
okay I have no
life oh dear you guys are welcome I
guess you're welcome for getting so much
content from me you never actually even
then even with this much content I see
some of you guys are like always like up
to dat and always like when I have a day
off you guys are like what should I
watch I have nothing else to watch I
watched all the
vods is is it still not enough should I
still stream
more it seems like seems like some of
you guys are always always caught up
that's
amazing yay yay yay thank you for
following me together on this on this uh
hell of a
journey no no more okay okay yeah you
guys need a day off too but sometimes
you guys act like it's like I don't know
like you act like this is like really
really bad when I have a day
off like not not like I don't know you
guys are like I miss
K I need more streams I miss
her I know I know you can you can have
you can deal one day without me right
right right right
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah just I don't know I'm actually
surprised that like most of you guys
don't live in the same time zone as I do
and yet you guys manag to always be
there um and and be caught up but no no
pressure on the ones who don't watch
everything of course not like but I
think the ones who are watching the
Super Chat reading pretty much watch all
of my
streams you guys are the real
chickens guys guys
everyone who's here right
now I will I will give you a
promise I will not fry you first I'll
leave you until I fried everyone else
okay as a thank you for your loyalty
you'll get a few more days to
live nice let's go yeah you guys are so
happy
about let's
[Music]
go
yay let's
[Music]
go you're going to be turned into soup
chicken I'm going to I'm going to let
you guys alive be alive so long that at
the end you're only really good enough
for soup mhm chicken
soup
a yeah until your meat is like really
really
I don't even know how to describe it I
have to ask my
mom soup chicken for Mama toi let's go
yeah my mom's going to teach me how to
make soup out of
you no no please mama I don't want to I
don't want to I don't want to do it from
scratch
mama I I can't
mama I told you guys before right that
she took apart like a whole like I'm so
sorry for the vegetarians and being
here
but my mom purchased a a pig and like
butchered it on her own like it was
already like dead but she took it apart
on her own and then froze all the meat
and had like meat for like
months but she said it was like really
really exhausting and she she
sent me pictures she was like covered in
okay this is pretty bad I think think
all the vegetarians here here are are um
unsubscribing I'm so sorry okay I am so
sorry I just want to kind of let you
guys know that my mom is really strong
and very very much a do-it-yourself type
of
person yeah yeah survival mom no I
wouldn't say it's not scary I mean hello
this is a job for PE some people out
there butcher that's just a nor normal
job and back in the day people had to do
it on their own people hunted their own
animals and they butchered their own
animals and they cooked their own
animals so it's a normal thing now when
you mention that now like my mom put you
the pig of course it sounds like weird
at first but if you think about it it's
just a normal thing it's just a really
really normal
thing even I freak out at the thought of
it but it's a normal
thing
yeah y yep yep yep that's how it
is you know one thing that I find uh
really fascinating about my mom when she
looks at a plant or flower she pretty
much immediately knows what it is what
the name of the flower or the plant
is yeah so when we when we walk around
in the city and I see a pretty flower
and I'm like Mama what is that flower's
name I want to get it for myself and she
can say h this is the name for it yeah
she knows her PL and her
[Music]
flowers
yeah she's she's very very very into her
garden she has a ton of like plants
and and trees and in her garden she
also uh cuts her own uh trees for her
own wood for
winter it's really exhausting
apparently but every time she talks
about doing stuff like that I get very
anxious because she previously um what
was it was it with with an axe she
previously injured herself a a while ago
I think it's already a few years
ago with I think an
axe but she's always like no no dieo
don't worry about it no shut
up but I'm almost like
Mom be careful
be
[Music]
careful it scares me though cuz my mom
also isn't the youngest anymore okay and
she has some some health issues too so I
don't want to do I want I don't want her
to do like really exhausting stuff like
that anymore but she keeps on doing it
in her home and I'm too far away to stop
her from doing it and she kind of like
she has to do it like she's like kind of
renovating her her own place um her own
house for a long long time
now step by
step I so much to
do reminds you of someone she will do
stuff like 14 hours of Minecraft
yeah yeah some days eh physical
exhaustion Sometimes some days mental
exhaustion through Minecraft
do you think of living with her no I'm
very much the type of person who leaves
home at uh 15 16 years old and then
lives alone ever since then although
there happen sometimes in between where
I lived with for financial reasons only
I lived with
roommates um
but uh I always always aimed for living
alone trucks of thef was
high yeah now I live alone as well and I
mean there's definitely been many times
where I felt like pretty lost because of
that but I need that feeling of privacy
and
freedom H although there's there in some
way living alone and having to do
everything alone also takes away a
little bit of freedom but at the same
time it gives you a lot of freedom and
yeah the Privacy is a big big
part yeah um you know you know you know
how much I loved rmt she was a great
buddy to live with very understanding of
my activities very interested in it and
very
supportive um but first of all I just
feel nervous when someone can hear me
while I'm streaming like on in the room
next door it just makes me nervous and
anxious second of all I didn't want to
bother her too much with the noise and
all that kind of stuff and F of all the
room was too small the internet was bad
so I had to
move but I love her I love r& tan
yeah she didn't even mind the 2 a.m.
streaming yeah even when she was
sleeping I was still able to be mostly
as loud as I was normally but I was
holding back and that's not good I
shouldn't be holding back myself uh
because of others during streaming
because that's just going to not be
natural anymore at some
point yeah but I still love her and
we're definitely going to go on trips
together again just like how we went
together so grease
[Music]
yeah so
rmt I'm glad you in RT are still friends
me too me too me
too guys I have a
ah you know the the cooking stream I
want to do next week I have a very
special surprise I just want to say that
I just want to throw that out there
there's there's one detail that you guys
are going to
be very um humored by I
think I don't have like a super cool
cooking layout like Cali has but but I I
prepared something
[Music]
else um but I do want to get like a
kitchen background at some point I'm I'm
planning on commissioning someone uh but
it's going to take a while until it
actually is
finished I want to get a cooking
background and I also want to get like a
kfp office
background but that one will take a
while as
well I don't I have like absolutely no
vision though of how I would want my
office to look like I have no idea maybe
like um ichiban's office in Ichiban
Holdings in
Yakuza like really really really
successful uh 50 million
[Music]
billing but but I don't know that's like
maybe a bito boring like it should be I
don't
know not
sure a
chicken a chicken Butler
Millennial
[Music]
Tower KF St sport in the background
oh a good idea
come maybe we should do a stream where
we think about what we want the office
to look
like like normally I don't I just don't
like asking for like ideas and stuff on
that because I want it to be a surprise
like when I reveal it but I'm really
clueless about the
office so I need I need your help I
think interior designs
dream members
only I like it thank
you okay I really should read more Super
chats been taking it so
easy well well if we don't stream
tomorrow we might as well stream longer
today
[Music]
right guys to
the
# Sims we could pre-build it in Sims
yeah that's that's a good idea actually
too but
yeah like as a general layout we could
pre-build it in Sims and then later on
add some details in Photoshop or
so so Spanky of Pim D thank you for the
Super Chat in celebration of sup being
back on and also my cats are sleeping so
I'm
bored you shouldn't be bored when
they're sleeping that's the best time to
pet them
endlessly cat said I had to go first oh
why thank you for the red super chat D
thank you thank
you thank you yeah super chats are fixed
but YouTube is still being stupid every
every day Sky D Felix thank you for the
red super chat d a stream which I can
watch live is this real life is this
just fantasy jokes deide it's really
nice that I can catch a stream live
during the weekdays probably can't stay
till the end but it's good enough for me
sorry it was only a Super Chat raing oh
man sorry but I hope you liked part of
it yeah wait that's actually really
short yeah because the stream got cut
short peton dangas Alo dangas that's it
actually that's those and now I read
Minecraft from yesterday which is a lot
a
lot this is a lot oh
[Music]
dear okay I try to
not tangent too much for a little
while
P Chi red thank you for the
pinky and to like the exploratory side
of Minecraft and RPGs I thought I would
recommend my favorite Minecraft mod
Twilight Forest it features multiple
bosses and dungeons
oh I wonder if we can still use stuff
like that I still don't know because
like we can use we can use uh you know
shaders but I don't know about
mods Twilight
Forest
uh uh Minecraft Twilight
[Music]
Forest let's take a
look
oh he
[Music]
not hold if we if we run we still have a
bunch of things to do in Minecraft if we
run out of things to do then I see that
stuff as an option also the stuff like
Sky Block and so on that kind of stuff
like once we run out of doing things
then I wouldn't mind doing stuff like
that
[Music]
yeah yeah on the personal server oh yeah
yeah that makesense
sense the Japan over had a mom it has a
mom it had
before there was a what the mik
one Nana didn't know what rickell was
well that that seems uh logical Japanese
people mostly don't
know
H it's its own Di Mansion oh it doesn't
even need a new world
really that's
cool just a texture
P interesting yeah thank you for the
pinky Felix S thank you for the pinky as
well oh two pinkies that's one red thank
you can to have fun with Mama toi or
should I say Grandma toi anyway it's
really heartwarming to see your have
wait a second wait a second Super Chat
reading super chats were not over there
actually they are starting to mix here o
oopsie uh it's really hard for me to see
you're playing a game with mamaon and
this reminds
me that the first video game I played
was with my Dad he stopped playing games
because of work and I do hope I can play
with him again I bought I brought my
switch with me last time I went home but
I hadn't got a chance to play with him
definitely will play with him also my
mom the next time I get home I'm sure
they would really enjoy that yeah I feel
like like my mom also was like really
really excited I think because we just
haven't like played anything together in
such a long time it is a way to bond
with your family as well so why the hell
not I think you should do it I'm sure
they would love it yeah ELO M hel these
are from the Super Chat
reading uh how many are there I should
probably switch back to Super Chat
ring okay one second there are a couple
a couple of
[Music]
them let me just put them next to one
another cuz they were up at the same
time this Laria thank you for the pinky
so glad I took the DD
route smoothie and chers and madori yeah
DD DD with in kfp
right then it's all good got to support
the whole kfb universe
every character in
it pet oran2 D no problem don't worry
El happy beled
birthday it's out of the blue but it was
my birthday yesterday your stream was is
a perfect birthday present for me thank
you for the fun stream
oh thank you happy
birthday
Alo Ashton Morgan
[Music]
miss someone um requested TR for and I'm
actually interested in try I actually
downloaded all of the try games I
purchased and download downloaded them
all on my
switch to play them at some
[Music]
point jaob or than soon penguin with a
ped cap than soon ran Striker D motan
thank you for the pinky employees
already simple for
gentle how many # voke # Yol are needed
before chickens learn their
loyalty
wait you have something in your name
here m it says K
supremacist MH are you calling out
yourself did you all see raina's new
outfit best part Tanto can't accuse us
of cheating cuz it's holot
toi
a yeah I mean I'm I'm generally quite
happy if you guys support hodori yeah
yeah I I wouldn't say that that's
not this cheating but I Al wouldn't say
that it's a bad
thing you can watch whoever you want in
her life no problem yeah if you're
interested in anyone else watch their
streams I mean I I I watch I watch uh
other people's streams sometimes
too and um yeah if you find someone in
gen to that you like more than me that's
just natural and uh you're welcome to
uh have them as their as your ooshi I
wish you a happy life and um just forget
that in the end you will still be fried
because you're still a chicken so that's
something you cannot Escape
[Music]
mhm white kada no white kada is just in
your
[Music]
dreams Casper don't call her
Casper she's not
Casper she's much much cuter than Casper
even though Casper was already hella
cute and disgusting at the same
time
cha I should just call her
Casper
Casper a you guys are so sweet but
really don't the the new members are I
think I mean I don't know them that well
I don't know they streaming style and
skills and all that but I'm sure that
they will all be really really
amazing so I understand if you want to
support them please please support
them oh my God I can't believe the the
debuts are this
weekend it happened so fast so
sudden
M it's so weird because like they joined
our Discord a while
ago um not so long ago but a little
while ago and ever since
then the Discord has been so much more
like
Lively which is exciting of course but
it also makes me feel a little bit like
a certain era has ended you know what I
mean this this era is exciting too I'm
looking forward to this era as well but
but the era of only us
five is over and that's just a really
mysterious feeling cuz it felt so cozy
and warm with us
five and now it's suddenly so
many yeah so many there there will be
like so many streams all the time there
will be a lot of overlapping as well I
think now that it's 11: instead of just
five and uh overlapping is definitely
inevitable
now and uh
yeah a lot of a lot more collaboration
possibilities too though
yeah I'm excited for that more
collaboration possibilities more funny
couples who knows what kind of funny
Dynamics will come out of that what
happens if you combine in Kiana
with Bales and
GAA what what what will
happen What happens if you combine Ena
with M and
[Music]
Iris we will we will know
soon
yeah myth kids no shut up that's not the
kind of biting that I
me yeah but yeah those kind of things
are definitely something to look forward
to I
think it's just
uh
changing
changing maybe this is how gen zero gen
one Gen 2
felt after a new generation was added
I wonder if they had a similar
feeling now for them it must be like so
normal and routine that all the time
there's new like Generations added
although this year oh nothing was added
just yet
but yeah they haven't added
anything new this
here so weird I feel like they were
dropping so many generations until
2021 but yeah I wonder what kind of
feelings they
had back in gen one when Gen 2 was
added oh I mean like within uh whole
life Japan nothing has been added in
[Music]
2021 yeah I think it's good that they
kind of like slowed down a little bit
that's my personal opinion CU I feel
like it's we're already so
many we are already so many and like if
you put all of us together whole life
English whole life ID whole life Japan
if you put all of us together it's only
so many I feel like yeah quality over
quantity is uh something you
could um apply to
that well it feels like a family
don't don't need much more I mean it's
always exciting to add more maybe maybe
one gen per year is maybe the ideal way
to go for me personally but but that's
that's uh your personal opinion I would
say what do you guys think how many gens
do you
think are should be added per year for
let's not say Holo Ian and Hol IDE let's
just say Hol life Japan cuz cuz I
already have so
many
one just ch one per year one to two two
two a year one a year most people say
one maximum
two one per
year yeah I think they're fine if they
just add one per year now it's not
something I can decide or I have
influence in which is totally fun but I
think the way they're doing it at the
moment it looks good to
me one every 2
years wow you guys wow one every two
years is a very slow
pacing they should build up other
branches first
oh dad is
also good opinion yeah yeah yeah
yeah maybe maybe new
branches cuz like I personally was
thinking like
hey recently influx in Korean viewers
whole life Korea
when whole life Spanish oh
yeah I heard that a lot of people are
like hoping for a whole life espanol or
something like that I guess there is a
big request for
[Music]
that although I don't know I don't know
if that will ever happen like even if
they make
that
H it would be cool though you could have
them like somehow Fe them
after like I don't know SP
Spain uh Spain and
uh
like uh uh also yeah yeah
[Music]
uh
uh Latin
America
oh like have like some like I don't know
I'm I'm sure there's like some history
there like I don't know maybe you maybe
they have some some
legendary
Legends myth
mythical things in their
books like gods or Spirits or whatever
that they could fee something
after chup super CRA what is
that let me look it
up CH
CRA oh
god
oh
[Music]
uh that's like a weird ass alien
lizard the
oh my
God I'm not sure if we need
that chupacabras is said to attack and
drink the blood of livestock including
goats what about whatam
[Music]
is literally Goat Sucker from Spanish
superer to suck Cabas to goats oh God
this a legendary creature the folklore
of parts of the Americas with its first
per pered sightings in reported in
Puerto Rico in
1995 you're telling me that someone has
seen a chup CRA before in
1995 that's not even that long ago
so that's kind of like in the modern
world you're telling me someone has seen
something like
that
they're
real
as my mom would say it
really iron Mouse saw it
they're not it they're it's not real
100% real it's not real they're real not
real you guys they're not
real they're not
real
look behind shut up and that's like a
Bigfoot thing well they could that yeah
that's that's like Hol myth they could
join the Hol myth family how about H
myth part
two my Holo myth and Holo live
[Music]
espanol oh my God you guys are killing
me oh oh my God yeah let's have big foot
in there as well
it's Bigfoot V is going to be best
friends with GAA I see it coming they're
going to be
BFFs oh
no oh no oh
no okay let's read super chats I need to
finish this my body
hurts H what is this Korean name I need
to translate translate Korean
[Music]
come thank you for the Super
Chat happy salary in Korea has been
pushed back please solve it
quickly yo where are my Korean
Representatives a 604 D
midnight
B Jesus
[Music]
Morales what's I'm Dan Dan account name
Dan oh wait what I was a
pinky thank you for the pinky
come sometimes I laughed while watching
your broadcast Clips something Korean
translated may you always be a bright
Phoenix and if it's okay with you can
you tell me just one word to Che cheer
up fighting what I'm
[Music]
fighting I I think uh in Korean they
like to say fighting in in in Japanese
they like to say fight and in Korean
they like to say fighting
fighting and both of those words are
English Al Dan Dan D my name is Sarah
dvin thank you for the r
ofasa dropping by for a second to be a
chat and give this super chat at work so
can't stay uh can't stay looking forward
to the VOD I'll catch you next stream
though thank you you mean the Minecraft
one thank you thank you for being here
thank you for supporting me I hope work
wasn't too
exhausting I hope it's somewhat
enjoyable for you thank you for peeking
in even though you're busy I appreciate
it very
[Music]
much black fruit and
d a horror week like
Ena
uh so you really want me to die don't
you really want me to get a heart attack
and
[Music]
suffer if anything that would happen
around Halloween but I don't know if I
can do a full
week maybe that will be the week where I
magically Take 5 days off and stream
only two days because just because I
want to take more care of myself you
know not not for any other specific
reason that is still the horror
[Music]
week as zombie
d
[Music]
V sa Turtle than
soon I would support that fair
compromise R not
[Music]
running John Smith D wait we WR that one
uh wait what about this
one
[Music]
sh me
me thank you for the pinky how about a
shooting horror SL suspense f e a r do
you think the ring girl is
cute do you want me to Google that f e h
[Music]
are oh let me add the game to
them oh God no what the oh that
ring girl
no oh that ring girl dead space
definitely not cute B shock cute dads
walking with their kids
oh that sounds cute Resident Evil 4
actually has cute girls oh
so Bioshock and Resident Evil sounds
[Music]
reasonable thank you for the pinky I
like the
ideas W cat's ear w
[Music]
d
thank you for the pink your first pink
Super Chat for you I got a new job so I
can't see a stream all the time a I
won't find other bird don't worry I'm
glad to be your kfp I bought your voice
pack o can you give me a name uh with
food in kfp oh like kfp melon or other
food thank
you oh no problem okay okay so first of
all congratulations on your new
job yeah you might get busy but I hope
you don't forget about
me now for your
name
uh
kfp
[Music]
cfp
c c
[Music]
MRA
no
K KY
lasagna you are now the kfp
lasagna I love you can I eat you right
now I'm going to eat lasagna tonight I
think yes yes yes yes lasagna today's a
lasagna day like last night at 3:30 a.m.
I was really craving lasagna I was so
close to making lasagna at 3:30 a.m.
even though I already ate pizza but I
was still hungry cuz I didn't eat the
full Pizza on
stream I didn't eat the rest of it later
either but boss it's not Monday that's
okay it's okay it's Monday somewhere in
the
world only if you're a time
[Music]
traveler
you know because I'm using the Zelda
music in the background and the
background noise my gaming hours are
going to be very
long so don't judge at the end how long
my gaming hours
are I didn't play it for that
long AR f
magic
r
what's
I'm thank you for the red super chat my
first red card for you K I go back to my
race and my belonged Place have a many
many good stream day thank you
[Music]
come
I I
[Music]
for
please watch My Stream every
day please watch My Stream every day #
voke #
yolk yes yes yes yes
[Music]
yes okay okay okay easy thank you for
the red super chat m
looking for the top d d Dominic D thank
you for the pinky PA result from kfp it
support
[Music]
people what this PC power button story
happens more often than you think and
here for me who's trained in it
oh you aren't stupid it's just Tech
thank you I actually today when I tried
turning on my PC I had to press it three
times again even though I pressed it
pretty um
strong
um but uh I think it's really like
somewhat stuck something in there is
just stuck I mean I don't know what it
is
but
yeah the yeah something is weird so I
will not blame it on myself
anymore did you turn it off and not oh
wait a
[Music]
warranty I probably
do but it's in
Japan it's okay it's not so disturbing
like now that I know that I just have to
press harder and press longer and press
more often then yeah now now I can deal
with it but before I felt like something
inside was broken and I felt helpless
but this is okay this is still something
that I can deal
with yeah
yeah of
fancy my name is sodin dang angel thank
you for the red super chat don't you
ever feel useless you bright in all our
days more than you know it's not a
coincidence all these chickens are here
watching you together thank you thank
you Angel you are literally an
angel thank
you m
my sweet sweet chickens put it in rice
you mean I should put my whole PC in
rice it's pretty big that has to be a
whole bathtub full of
rice angel thank you for the sweet and
kind words
really very very sweet thank you I
appreciate it Albert school thanks soon
tyan thank you for the pinky we love you
and the reason people are willing to
help is that they love you we'll do what
we can just like they will everyone has
weak spots no one is going to be perfect
the fact you worry about your friends
shows why they're willing to
help thank you no I I just
have insanely kind
[Music]
friends thank
you thank you I you got
[Music]
my
nose CH thank you for the red super
chat in
is it is shown that magical people are
not able to use technology properly so
it just proves how magical you
are okay that must have been the best if
I had to give an award to these super
chats for being cute and uh
cheerful in this situation I have to say
you you did it the best mate that that
is uh pretty adorable and funny it has
humor and it's cute is that is pretty
damn
cute that is very
cute you get 10 out of 10 award good job
he takes he takes the crown
yeah you get a golden yo for
that thank you Chief logical Paradox D
Dominic d g d thank you everyone for all
the sweet messages I'm sorry for like
being so dramatic about
it I'm okay I'm okay
guys Hansel 2002 than thank you for the
red of
chat uh what
uh I hope my friend's wife won't divorce
him should we take the trip to doomi
next
[Music]
time or maybe she'll just ban me from
his husband for the rest of his life boy
does she hate me for taking her husband
to do Stu that sounds like a a personal
thing that you guys have to figure out
privately I don't know how to help you
with
that uh but I'm always glad when people
can come uh to uh support me at
conventions but if you're far away
please don't do anything stupid or crazy
that is not in your budget or not uh
like manageable in your schedule or
whatever or just generally impossible
please don't worry about
it as long as you here hanging out of me
in my streams then I am
happy yeah Mr
Mr Dr kasic excuse
[Laughter]
more uh yes yes YouTube dump this is by
the way where these ones are not mixed
in anymore I
think looking for the top Dan D so much
for Susan fixed it it's so ironic cuz I
put it in the
[Music]
title danan Dan G thank you for two
pinkies I still to can't believe that is
how I finally get sent to the
H yeah you didn't even do anything it's
like precy
cautious cage not from in
subordination head Nation but out of
fear that I would feather leave you K I
promise that I'd never fly this Coupe
that I would always follow you my Aussie
[Music]
I don't intend on going to beak on my
word and maybe unforgivable bow but I
but I would never turn tail on kfp I
don't understand you're imprisoning me
though just look at M she's adorable
ow don't just don't you just want to
adopt her into cine and introduce her
toi so you want to like FL with after
all
he's a liar saw his Twitter replies a
not a h well then he must stay in the
usual room then he must stay I trust I
trust what you have said uh she is very
cute though
yeah she's a very cute owl maybe we can
get her um to work at kfp a little bit
as a part-timer
part-timer I don't know how good ow will
taste when
[Music]
fried cuz you know what happens with
people who work at
[Music]
kfp
no I don't know man like we have to try
it out I guess but we can try we're
going to try it with Trevor G eventually
[Music]
so and then we can judge whether or not
we want to fry m
Nashi M as well what are we going to
call her anyway nanashi or M what are
you guys calling her if you would have
to call her something would you guys
call her n or what's going to be her
[Music]
nickname
M we just call her
who
who who is
[Music]
M
Nana m m Nana
n the council calls her
mayay really
interesting that that's funny because
there's an
idol from Hello project for her name was
mayay and now I have to think of her she
was a really good singer
H I'll have to think about it what feels
natural to
me it's going to be a difficult
situation difficult difficult
decision yeah yeah that is very creative
uh
[Music]
m
call cron corini I should call her C I
want to call cron c c croissant
ciss C where a stupid name oh man she's
going to be
[Music]
suffering don't call it late for dinner
why cuz she's like time
related she's never late she always
arrives at the time that she intends to
arrive on like
GT Tom Tomic 1199 D Anonymous
247 Ras Dan Al Dan em K 1702 Dan Citrus
Solutions Dan Mage D Argent night D
thank you for the pinky the Super Chat
is from mama Hello mama
oh don't worry she will be receiving
[Music]
it after YouTube takes her cut dear
Susan wants a cut of it a cut of the
cake
Elsie no no Blondo thank you for the red
of
[Music]
T you have a beautiful s s so so wherby
you can build a bookshelf or fix a
computer is irrelevant remember you're
stronger than you seem and smarter than
you think Dy Dy thank you for everything
you do you're deeply appreciated now
let's go Mama Minecraft thank
you thank
you that is also so sweet what the hell
thank you blonda
BL your words touch my heart and give
big kiss to
you very
sweet you're so sweet it makes me
speechless thank you I hope you enjoyed
the Minecraft stream of my
[Music]
mama thank you for the pinky this Super
Chat is from mama Hello mama wait is
that not the second time you sent that
you sent it twice Dela are you are you
okay did did YouTu mess around with
the well now now you basically deserve a
kiss from my mommy because it's
basically a red Super
Chat how could I me than thank you for
the red super chat aasa for Phoenix Mama
such amazing mom energy redecorated your
apartment yeah leaving your course she
did do that didn't she reorganizing your
storage she did do that
too oh my God now that you say it feel
like I'm being brainwashed and
manipulated by my
mama like outside she she put a sign to
tell me that I should put like carpet
everywhere and the Torches
underneath she did reorganize my my uh
chests and and she decorated the
apartment which is however the old one
which is basically just a storage no
need to decorate that one it's not
supposed to look
[Music]
pretty but okay but okay aren't we old
brainwashed by our mama you mean
brainwashed by me it runs in the family
it seems
yeah
but but don't you guys enjoy it yes you
do you enjoy it because you're being
[Music]
brainwashed
i k s n i p d pillar next is D volock
101 D thank you for the pinky oh thanks
again for meon Orlando you were there
seeing all the support and love from
everyone made me tear up I talked to
loads of people and L A Lot hello Mama
toi thanks for giving us Kiana we all
love tento and appreciate your existence
that is so sweet thank you that's so
cool that when you were there I'm glad
you were able to experience that cuz
it's a very very special experience and
who knows when you get the chance again
to go to a place like that thank you so
much
mhen JL
[Music]
mati
than abdom Prime thank you for the pinky
20 minutes in and already so much fun
here's some money to buy your mama a
nice Lum
St and some extra for the familian
casset amazing to have a mom to play and
talk about video games for my mom
everything is a Nintendo
oh still love you Mom love to all mam
Mama's
everywhere wow I'm a
what a what
a bad time for am to be on a vacation
huh thank you Abus Prime than you very
much
appreciated Matia for
Kar bugaria be careful what you write
into your super chats the overload
overload d r Chelly alv
small opportunity eager s mad H Jackson
FB thank you for the
pinky oh God I'm getting really
exhausted we have like 180 super chats
left also I hear the crispy noise there
let's switch it to this okay we send our
thanks to Mama toi for being here today
and for bringing such a wonderful
Phoenix into the world this stream was
an absolute blast I'm glad you enjoyed
thank you thank you thank you very much
I'm glad everyone ex was so excited
about it even though she was not in
voice chat everyone still enjoyed it so
much so I'm looking forward to bringing
her in again at some point thank you you
were also welcoming very sweet my mom
had a blast thanks to you guys as well I
think she really enjoyed like having an
audience and that all really like
her AG P El
wey naked chicken Elbert SC Slavic
fellow dangan Petri dang Jesus thank you
for the pinky will Mama to marry us
please she's she's not really interested
in marriage actually so I don't think
that's going to
[Music]
happen
sorry small brain thank you for the red
super
chat bye Mama told you something nice
with this thank you you guys are very
very generous
thank don't worry she she she uh she
will
receive fgh Magic Fish D James MC thank
you for the red super chat as well F's
potential to get her own morning star
necklace oh yeah that's right is it was
that a Morning
Star oh yeah yeah yeah that's about the
when we talked about when I talked about
uh taking my Mom's necklace from Lord of
the Rings cuz it's so pretty and I just
I just can't ignore sparkly things in
the
bathroom the aror necklace
yeah yeah yeah maybe I'll get my own one
good idea I need more accessories and
jewelry anyway I I don't have like
anything
man barely anything
and the few things that I have are like
made out of plastic really really the
cheapest stuff ever to need to go
shopping a little bit but I don't go
outside anymore so it's like what am I
buying it
for chrisop D Unity chat thanks for the
pinky got a cut super fast uh due to
some planning calculation reasons for a
little bit but today I must do it no
problem no problem please take a little
break if you need it
greetings to Mama Tony you two have a
great Dynamic you have an amazing mom
and she did an amazing job raising such
a wonderful daughter thank you thank you
thank
you why is it
German why I know you don't even speak
German why did you have to translate it
to German it make me read it
why
why this
[Music]
you can do it I guess Uma is the but I
don't I don't think she will like
that better don't do it om is the German
word for
grandma
H oh yeah it actually doesn't sound
translated sounds natural good job on
the German but it's embarrassing for me
to read
[Music]
it thank you though thank
you g sh thank you for the r Super Chat
never right or no stream has already
exceeded expectations thank you boss and
Mama for a fun time pleased to see you
mama and thank you for raising such a
wonderful fun creative but most
importantly golden-hearted person that
we all believe
in yo you being extra Charming today cuz
my mom was there huh aren't you thank
you for the kind kind super sweet words
we did get up end up getting a lot of NE
right though I want to go um get some
more next week or so or the week after I
don't even know if I'm going to play yes
I will play Minecraft next week too yeah
yeah I think I'm going to go get some
more netherite then got to get some more
TNT though first of
all my throat hurts so let me take
another throat
thingy I'm getting tired now how how
long has it been it's been 8 hours
woohoo KY let's go 8
hours the usual takasi Kar is
back I like how you wanted to ride time
up the Ian server but you wrote titty up
Ian server don't worry the the Ian
server is getting tittied up
soon when Ian generation 2 is
[Music]
coming that is a great typo that is one
of the best tyos I've ever seen cuzz it
just makes sense
just look at
genu oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
man oh my
God w we 101 to
[Music]
Lang ah flu 1989 dang and c d
I've seen that Meme where GAA and Ena
are like surrounded by generation 2 um
but BS doesn't look like she has a
huge
chest so I don't think let me look again
let me look again let me
[Music]
inspect they look oh wait actually never
mind they look kind of big
ah they
do yeah they do oh my God there's
literally
[Music]
no what about Nana she she doesn't have
like
insane I no no no she has she does have
cleavage
H wow the the badona
ratio is very unbalanced in whole life
English
very
unbalanced and um just just asking
but
Callie totally totally talking about
body
size uh tall tallness but kie is not
the tallest one anymore is
she
[Music]
crony crool looks
um
taller maybe even
[Music]
Sonna C looks
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
be
that's all I'm going to say I'll leave
the rest to you guys Ty D TR D penguin
with the peaked cap D Chris D black rich
thank you for the red super chat a you
see we had a lot of people asking my
mama uh that if they could marry my mama
but here is black friction asking if
blackin can marry me can I marry k a
well that's a no but still it's so sweet
that you're
asking m m
Mah you'll always be in my heart
[Music]
though Kamia sends a red Super Chat as
well asking Mama ton I love you can you
be my
mother it's interesting how you're
confessing to Mama Tori but by asking
her to be your mother
it implies that you're either planning
to marry me or to be adopted by my mom
and become my uh brother/
sister I am not sure what your plans are
but nope you are my employee and I
cannot have such relationships with you
unfortunately than for the red super
chat
[Music]
swe
H yeah Cron's legs though holy and
someone said it in the chat but like I
mean this is partially the art style
from V
Aran but that body is
smoking oh my God I just really love all
about that
design absolutely genius
design absolutely genius I love the
weapons that she has too and the boot
booies I love the
boies and the the tights they're not
really tights it's really interesting
design I love the skirt I love the poofy
poofy uh
sleeves they they kind of um the design
with the poofy sleeves the sleeves
generally I don't know why but they kind
of remind me of
um I don't know something like Robin
Hood for some reason
I don't know
why I like the
hairstyle I like the the art style I
like the eyes I like the weird clock or
whatever that's on her
head man I love all of it I love all of
it I love the color theme it's just
kills me it kills
me kills me freaking kills me oh my God
all of the designs are really really
great
though
I'm a sucker for good Aesthetics suck a
sucker I'm a sucker for you I'm a sucker
for
[Music]
you Jeff b t Sky thanks for the pinky
mama told you have a wonderful talented
daughter you must be very proud of her
hope you can hope I can see you in K
future stream again oh I think so you
will you
will thank you thank you thank you
thanks to you guys she's not against it
she's very very open to the idea so that
is because you guys were so well behaved
and we had a great time because of that
thank
you not applicable Anon
stim I like this idea um uh cuz the
Diablo 2 so this person here writes you
and Mama should play Diablo 2
resurrected when it drops next month
so the thing is like I played Diablo 2
resurrected closed beta closed
Alpha previously on my stream it's
coming out soon and um it has an online
mode and my mom was such a
passionate uh Diablo player back in the
day and I told you all of those stories
of my mom playing it and me trying a
little bit on her account but being too
scared to play it
properly so it would be so cool to play
with her I'm sure she's going to play it
when it comes
out I don't know how the online mode
works though but she she would be a
great addition cuz she's going to like
totally carry
me she's going to carry me so
hard
[Music]
yeah carrying kids is what moms do
she carried it for nine months a couple
games of Diablo is nothing no no no no
that's not how phoenixes uh
procreate I told you guys before I was
not in her
belly that's not how it
[Music]
works
yeah
it's much F much faster much much faster
yeah yeah they rra each other really
really
fast like like when you when you try to
make a fire with a stone and a and a
piece of wood no wait that's not the
same thing no if you try to make a fire
with a piece of wood and a piece of
wood I think something like that that's
what I imagine that's the speed that I
imagine
[Laughter]
yeah what the hell am I talking about
black f d for D race smash 176 d endert
d p d Malo random
[Music]
D thanks for the Super Chat welcome can
you help us stage an intervention
for K has abusive relationship with
YouTube this where we at it sounds like
you were
you are on YouTube's side what the
hell we need an intervention with
you maybe you are Susan maybe you are
YouTube Maybe This Laria is
YouTube get
him get him get him C what I'm
[Music]
choking
I'm okay I'm okay now I'm fine thank
you any news on Hall mantion oh no I
haven't thought of that in a long time
totally forgot about that so much going
on I want to do it maybe maybe um maybe
in in
Winter
G this thank you for Pinky what the hell
man what the hell the origins of the
how do I pronounce this
word I heard it
before feud
feud feud feud feud feud feud
feud feud
feud feud feud feud that's the
Australian one Feud that's a British one
Feud that's the American one feud feud
feud feud feud feud
feud feud feud sounds funny sounds
funny H and origins of the feud are lost
in the maps of time but we need to end
the cycle of YouTube kada bong exactly
wait now you on my side after all so
did I Mis
interpretate wait wait a
second Mis
interpret wait that's not a word
misinterpret
misinterpret to misinterpret
misinterpret did I misinterpret you oh
finally I got that right I was I was I
got that one wrong so often
misinterpret
misinterpret it's on the
T okay okay
[Applause]
okay learned something new learned two
new words like the pronunciation of
[Music]
them
Lexington the lion
D I think she wasn't able to read the
chat the or the super chat or so uh
during the stream but she as I told you
guys today she stayed up all night to
watch the archive of it to read the chat
properly so I think she did read it
after
all I get that though like um in the
first few weeks months of me in whole
life I would rewatch my own streams a
lot to first of all like like see like I
don't know to like reflect on how I
streamed and also to read the
chat I did that a lot in the beginning I
don't do that anymore cuz it's just I
mean it's been too much time and I got
used to it and um I'm already like my
mind is already full with so many
things but I used to do that got a lot
too
so h i get why she would want to do that
especially if it's her first time it's
so exciting to read everyone's comments
when so many people talk about you
yeah H Brian Sean
danin you know de is pronounced debris
right no I did not
know are we learning another word
ancient de I didn't even know the
meaning of that word now I know it's to
debris
debris debris debris
debris talk to me more debris oh
thebr
okay
deis
debris deis deis but but this one though
debris
oh so
flirty flirty debris me when I see
debris after the TNT
exploded
debris oh it's debr over
[Music]
there bones meon my name
isin Brian
p is this Super Chat reading ever
ending sa cop
by zero steady norion nor noran steady
noran um thanks for the pinky Mama
played Mor wnd right how do you know did
I tell you guys before but yes she did
which of the 36 lessons of Vivic is your
favorite I have no idea I can ask her
now no I'm not going to I'm not going to
you can try to ask her next
time I don't get the joke unfortunately
cuz I didn't play
it it said Morrow one that's what I
said Mor one Mor shut
up step by step okay hello this for the
pink you go action Quake the most base
of Quake
mods I that was also something we talked
about didn't we wait what was Quake some
kind of
game some kind of game that who my
mama uh told me
about
Quake
[Music]
uh-huh I looked it
up it just it just doesn't
uh when I look up these games they just
mostly don't really speak to
me aesthetically it's just like a gun
and
monsters I'm so sorry
but when I see those screenshots I
that's all I
[Music]
see where are the end in
I I mean I'm sure that
there's more to it or at least some of
these
games but that's probably why um I just
it's really hard for me to develop an
interest in these kind of
games but don't worry I'll give
something something in that genre a try
at some point and you guys can then be
satisfied and and uh quiet about it
afterwards mhm and then we'll probably
mostly go back to our usual
genre cuz I'm not going to suddenly turn
around my whole Channel and play
completely different games out of
nowhere just because some people asked
me to do that I am taka nashik kiar and
I play jpgs and if you don't like it
well you don't have
to I'm not forcing you to watch my
streams if you don't like it you don't
have to be
here
understand yeah don't make me into
someone that I don't want to be there's
so many other people who play those
genres go play the uh go uh support them
go uh watch their streams there's so
many out
there I don't know I don't know why I
need to play them I mean I'm to give
them a
try gladly I'll give them a try with if
I find one game that speaks to
me um that catches my interest I will
give them a
try but I'm not going to change my whole
like it's not going to change cuz that's
just what I like I mean some of you guys
like brokoli and some of you guys don't
like
brool
well it's just yeah part of my
personality
H and you see because I play so many
jpgs happy things happen like me being
the official ambassador of the tales of
arise English region well I kind of said
that wrong the official ambassador of
the English region for Tales of
arise I wouldn't be getting that if I
were playing a ton of uh shooting
games in games and all
that yeah I know you guys are very
supportive of when I play thank you
thank
you thank you you should give Xeno Blade
a try I know I want
to
[Music]
so so so so
yeah I don't need to play games from
every single genre do
[Music]
I octopath travel up I do I do really
want to give octopath traveler a try but
I don't know I'm still waiting on those
permissions man the Japanese girls have
been playing the Square Enix games for a
while now I'm still waiting I'm still
waiting still
[Music]
waiting
when permission Doo but um we're going
to be busy anyway now in September with
Tales of AR rise for for now we're going
to be busy with that so let's see where
that leads us Elvis thank you for the
red to CH K can you ask your mom if she
can take care of me because because with
you I'm always
jailed in the usual room and with her
I'll be free I don't know about that
Elvis
[Music]
she
um is going to eat you eventually too
so when you are a
chicken adopted by a
phoenix your fate is the
same doesn't matter if it's me or my mom
and my mom is a bit more um brutal
then I am with the whole procedure too
so you might want to rethink that
Elvis
yeah Amilia s than small brain thanks
for the pinky mamaon is OG gamer yeah I
guess you could say that red shark D
black richen thanks for the red super
chat this this stream has been amazing
and I see mamori is amazing with her
tastes and games Hanah thank you for
bringing her on this has been so damn
good based Mama apparently she's based
yeah
okay I can't I can't really tell but
from your point of view a lot of your
point of views apparently she's based
glad you and my mother-in-law are having
so much fun together o o black f o my
ocean knows how to create amazing
streams what what are you implying black
fore o what
happened Bas dope super lit yeah yeah
that's my
mom black fishan are you okay are you
okay were you did you hit your head
yesterday or
something JK Mr Man another good
username 360 d lambard l lambard d d d
thanks for the pinky yeah this collab
was amazing your mom is so funny I love
that she loves chicken so much it's
perfect isn't it it's just
perfect H I hope you can play together
again also please listen to your mom and
play Mass Effect please do you want any
new type of chicken up for your desk yes
I want yes yes the astronaut chicken and
um M maybe how about a made chicken with
an apron and like a little uh cleaning
thingy like the the the one that you use
for dust thingy in its hand you made the
astronaut oh my God I'm going on Twitter
right now I'm going on
Twitter I'm going on
Twitter oh my God Christina lanita also
Drew
something oh look at
that
[Music]
am
rocket oh my God where's the one from
D wait that's so
cute
wait that is so
cute oh my
god oh oh come on Taca you make Cy chy
milk
what oh my
God looks so good oh my God it's
[Music]
C oh my God it looks so
good oh my God oh
[Music]
chicken he
chicken it's so killed it has it
has
boots can it even can chickens even walk
in
[Music]
Boots my God wait why did I Del the
other one cuz this one is not sitting so
I I could keep this one standing here
and the other one sitting on my head
where the I lost the other one where
where is the other one where did I save
it I lost it I deleted it where is
it where is it where did it
go where did it
go let me look for Dam M with
a
chicken chicken where are
you I can't find it it's too many
chickens
I've lost sight of my
[Music]
chicken
chicken she
[Music]
retweeted
y
chicken
Revival of the
chicken nice comfy it's a bit bigger
than before Oh my God the astronaut
chicken is so
cute it's just standing there it's just
standing there looking into the universe
and it's like one day I will conquer you
just how I conquered
kfp it thinks to itself it's conquered
kfp but it really
didn't it was
me cuz I created
kfp yeah okay super chat back to Super
Chat
don't thank you for the
chicken I love them so chunky conquer
s
that chicken wants to conquer s right
unless you like chickens Ellie
Smith Nel thank you for the
rent yo mama loves neighborhood EV B you
know you know the game that was my
dam when I was a child a we child
Clayman f is still a banger today hell
the whole OST is a banger it is such a
original funny awesome weird ass
game like I was really young back then
but like I I remember it being very
weird very very weird but if you guys
don't know it if you like weird games
it's worth checking it
out thank you can you get permissions I
don't know maybe
but maybe we should do like a Nostalgia
week at some point where we only play
old games that I played when I was
younger I want to play Sims 1 at some
point too on my channel cuz like Sims
playing Sims 1 is an adventure in
[Music]
itself yeah I love Sims
1 I love Sims 2 as well Sims 3
no Sims 4 is okay Sims 1 and Sims 2 were
the best ones cuz they also had the best
um expansion
packs and n i kiss it for you
kiss a kiss to
goon spank thank you for the
CH thanks for doing a mom collab fun and
educational and we definitely won't
remember any embarrassing stories from
your youth I mean she didn't really she
didn't really provide much embarrassing
stories next time I I I make her prepare
some more
stories beforehand the kitties love
watching Minecraft for some reason he
that's sweet that is very sweet you're
welcome to send me pictures of your cats
watching me I enjoy those kind of
pictures very
much cutest fan girls ever cutest fan
girls and Fanboys Sims Busting Out was
my favorite wait was that the one on the
GameCube cuz I played that one too and
it's it's really really good yeah it's
funny I want to play that one too
again the teabag one was hard to hear
for me as a Brit oh I'm I how do I
apologize in
British how do I say I'm sorry I I I I
apologize wait let's let
me S sa mate o o sorry
love uh par pardon me uh uh
apologize
let me
see to apologize to apologize that's
very British to to
apologize to apologize that's American
to apologize to
apologize it's too late to it's too late
to apologize it's too
late it's too late to apologize it's too
[Music]
wa
what wait a second
um wait a second
[Music]
um and
okay Never Going To
Give You Up never going to let you down
never going to C around and desert
[Music]
you
wait um
[Music]
yeah
okay we know strangers to love you know
the rules and so do I awful commitments
what I'm thinking
of you wouldn't get this from any other
guy I just want to
tell you how I'm feeling got to make you
understand Never Going To Give You Up
never going to let you down never going
to run around and desert you never going
to make you cry never going to say
goodbye never going to tell a lie and
hurt
[Music]
you it's like audio stuff
voice oh
beautiful wait a
[Music]
second that's that's difficult that's
not
difficult that is difficult
wait a second I have I have a
[Music]
plan I have a
plan
uh what am I
[Music]
doing what am I doing with my life what
am I doing with my
life
what am I doing one second please please
hold please hold the line please hold
the line please hold the
[Music]
line
okay
[Music]
uh I'm working on something right now
it's going to be
beautiful it's going to be
[Music]
beautiful
what okay okay this already took me too
long so let's do it like
this never somebody is
GNA
give you oh
[Music]
never somebody is
GNA
um
let
you
down that was that was no GH
[Music]
only beautiful that was a was a cover
version uh of of
dict.cc uh of never going to uh give you
up then we're going to let you down
you're welcome that took me a long time
to
make never never somebody is going to
give you up never never never never
somebody is going to let you
down music has B to whole new level a
whole new
level okay back
[Music]
toats somebody some
somebody somebody
[Music]
wants I need to
stop
[Music]
I'm never going to finish these super
chats I'm never going to
[Music]
finish
oh
a thank you thank
you for the
warning okay I'll be careful looking for
the T thank you for the pinky it's cool
Mommy can see you surrounded by fans and
friends she let you travel around since
young right in unconventional but she
wants to see you live your dreams if you
feel like you have to depend on others
remember your badass mommy believes in
you thank you very sweet of you Rand d
and d and jimy j j r
extrem thank you
is DLC
mik
alter
Crimson D Kitt Jeff the
Phoenix Oh Holy One something odd seems
to have happened to a village the
villagers are adamant that they
witnessed a second holy bird and some
even woke up to find themselves stuck in
a boat on land if you ask me it seems
that the villagers may have burned a bit
too much insense during the prayers but
the villagers seem ecstatic that
phoenixon now has two Mighty guardan
dieses y I hope you're going to enjoy
what mama has in store for you I hope
you're looking forward to that my Mommy
wants to build some make some
Renovations with phoenixon make it
really really pretty so it's going to be
even better an even better place to live
in than it already is I mean look at the
satisfaction rate in
phoenixon 150% out of
100% yes D
is yes German for thank
you
m Andreas
TR
for the
red and good day hot wings GT and SK
thanks for this m collab mate you both
were great mama is based edgy based and
edgy yeah was that outfit she was kind
of
edgy H hope you get to do more collabs
in the future kindly thank her for
bringing you to life you are such a
blessing my wonderful Ohi take her out
sometimes every time we meet I I like to
use the opportunity to have mommy's food
to be honest because I usually don't get
that otherwise well it's been many many
years since I got something like that
daily um so I I I I just and my mom
enjoys that my mom likes cooking I don't
yeah so but yeah I I'll take her out
someday I guess but I want my mommy's
cooking I can take her out if she can
take over the
[Music]
kitchen in whatever restaurant we're
going to I just want the home cooking
yeah thank you for the red you're so
lovely thank
you yeah midnight thank you for the
pinky thank you so much for this
wonderful stream it was really fun
brought back some nice memories of
playing video games with my mom a long
time ago oh you did that too I'm looking
forward to the next time you play
together as I'm sure it will be as
amazing as this one I am sure with that
too thank you so much for watching our
stream uh supporting us and enjoying it
so much thank you I'm really glad to
hear that t fro thanks for the pinky
D no it's
German h do I do I have to read that for
you said it's from my mama
to please don't hate
me well I'll I'll read it
[Music]
silently kind
[Laughter]
it was a nice buildup indeed yes yes yes
thank you and you sent another one let's
read that
one and
[Music]
seeis not sure about that
froo oh where did you get that idea you
think you're a phoenix or something like
that are you a little bit confused
what's with all these confused chickens
these
days uh okay just keep on believing that
um but but but enjoy each day as if it's
your last one okay don't forget about
that just because you think you're never
going to grow
oh if you think like that then you're
not going to make the best use of each
day and that's not the way should live
you should you should live like you're
going to die tomorrow all righty I
turned it into some really deep deep
thought thank
you p
s Ty dang Shan that cool dang my name is
San
dang panto panto
Ro red e d rain wolf D James D RS D wi
CV d ping Channel LEF
El R thank you for the red super chat oh
my God it's already 1
a.m.
[Music]
more oh my
god um going to turn off the super chats
right
now been 9 hours we could if we continue
reading like this we could beat Callie's
record but no I will not do that today
today is not the
day
n that is more than 8 hours and more
than 7 hours in more than 6
hours so
so the H Union is the most ha and
wholesome thing I agree if that will
ever to happen warms my heart to see how
special these moments and bonds feel to
you right now love you T thank you love
you too but you know what you know what
would be even more titty if there never
was a reunion because we never part
ways but that is well that is not
realistic
but that is unfortunately not very
realistic but let's let's let's think
like that for
now let's keep it that way for
now thank
you
[Music]
El you're going to Europe next weekend
to study for a weekend only or for like
longer it's not even my first time going
abroad but I'm kind of worried this time
anyway it was really fun stream why are
you wored Europe is awesome please enjoy
yourself here I don't know which country
you're going to and each country is very
very special on its own but don't worry
about it you'll be fine you'll have a
great time here and enjoy yourself I
wish you the best of luck peace lights D
Ty you thanks for the red super chat
thank you for the love and support Eden
D Alec and music Tanaka thanks for the
pinky Canadian snacks oh I already read
that one thank you
again opportunity than LC Lain than you
soon Mr Cas than soon uh yes I have yes
I have seen a walk through of a 2d Zelda
game before I'm pretty sure I
have
thank you for the
[Music]
r Wait this a Skyward
Sword uh it has been Skyward Sword for
like since 10 super chats ago or
so for the
pink oopsie well I guess you also sent
the red one so it's
okay
[Music]
and uh where's my
thingy oh my God this feels like
endless Eternal Super Chat reading
continue continue
d z w thanks for the red super
chat oh God thank you
you
I've been going back and back and
watching a fire emblem streams and it
made me want to replay the game for like
the eighth time wow really you're a big
fan aren't you last night I beat it on
maddening difficulty with Perma death
and got zero deaths what you know what
you're doing damn I could not do
that thank you for showing jpg some love
looking forward to TA thank you I am
glad to be doing that I am a proud J prg
[Music]
fan thank you and holy
respect respect man that sounds
insane sounds like a very very difficult
play through thank
you whenever a new Fire Emblem game
comes out I want to play
it thank you random spy for the pinky
hey atten today's my birthday just back
from the birthday party birthday night
best time for kada and chill
I love you Del series it's fun as F
thank you happy
birthday happy
birthday y hope you had a great
party hope hope you got a lot of love
and appreciation for
everyone birthday very special day your
day thank youan for spending it with me
as
well means a lot to
me
[Music]
Jackson FB thank you for the
pinky is the Ruby Jo getting old no it's
not I'm off work today because I'm not
feeling wor well but your stream's
helping me feel a bit better thank you T
oh I hope you feel better soon enjoy
that one day off of work take your time
to get better watch some of your
favorite Netflix shows after my stream
is
over
than here name thank you for the pinky
hey K my brother sent me this but I have
no idea how to pronounce it oh yeah I
already read that
one that is kind of like
a uh yeah German swearing kind of a
Australian
swearing and looking for the top D where
find the D every d
Lord AR pcho ro ro BL thank you Jackson
FB thank you for never pinky M Gru video
One
never what the hell why would I do such
a thing also it's supposed to be for
animals
only animals only we're making a
zoo oh I think I saw that video
too the investigation of the Minecraft
hole the Frosted
Firefly thank you for the red super
ch
[Music]
guys can I stop here this is where I
would have to
refresh I'm at the point now where
um where I I copied the super chats at
the end of the Zelda
stream I can't I'm I'm done I'm so done
I'm so dead thank
you thank
you
um I don't know about
[Music]
tomorrow let's just take it easy
tomorrow M okay thank thank
you let's take it easy tomorrow and work
on some things I mean I'm not I'm not
going to I'm not going to take it easy
the hold day I'm going to work on whole
talk and
stuff got to I got to I got to put the
questions together
urgently
yeah thank
you
SC thank you everyone for the sweet
support hope you had fun
today
yeah fourth dungeon soon we're right in
front of it that took us a long time
today to get from the end of the third
dungeon to the fourth dungeon but we did
that that weird like different dimension
thingy in between the shadow shadow
realm
yeah I and we did good progress yeah 5
and a half hours or so oh my God
thank you I love you all thank you my
sweet
chickens
yeah
[Music]
yeah uh maybe maybe a tiny gorilla
stream maybe maybe but don't don't don't
uh get your hopes up don't get your
hopes up
okay thank you everyone very
much
than and in German we say
[Music]
monkey see you tomorrow not tomorrow but
see you on Twitter probably I'm going to
going to make a sun
lasaga thank
[Music]
you there he goes
wow
ch
man he made
it he went to the moon we all
thought it was
impossible that a chicken goes to the
moon but here you have it here you fuing
have it don't let your dreams be
Dreams Just Do
[Music]
It
just do
it
[Music]
bye-bye