[Music]
do
what so loud
cakey
everyone
hello good evening look at those fixes
they
up they did a fixing but was that before
or after my last stream
i think it's i think it's new
or is it no it's not been that long
since last stream has it i think it was
before
why are they showing it to me again and
you know account blog inflow
significantly reworked i'm not sure
about that last time it was definitely
kind of
annoying well anyway
hello everyone welcome back if you
watched the
uh it takes two stream
uh if you missed it what
that was honestly so much fun
combat
[Music]
that was three and a half hours of so
much fun with a great game with cali
and we're going to play it again maybe
next week
if it works out um schedule wise on my
side
it should work out but i'm also a bit
worried about hosting it because next
time it would be me hosting it and
before i move
i'm not sure about my internet
we'll see about that oh you know what
actually i guess kelly could
post it on my channel uh anyway
anyway
i didn't think about that option um
anyway we're playing among us today
together
together don't get banned again yeah i
don't know honestly
like normally that should be fine
because people have done it before like
i think amin did it
with gouda
it should work somehow uh
anyway today everyone who joined last
week
or ever at all please don't join this
or today we want new people come in
uh everyone needs uh everyone should get
a chance
uh if you were in a game with me
ever before don't join today
don't join please okay
[Music]
so
and um we're going to play on the
which server it's north america here
let's but
well i'll we'll see if i'm able to get
in let's see wait
let me hide the screen again for a
moment it's in a right now but we'll see
if i can get in because last time it
didn't work oh wait i did get in
hi okay america
let's see i will tell you guys yeah it's
always the
lobby always fills up in one second so
i'll tell you guys i'll i'll
say the number out loud and you guys try
to
type it in with me and do your best
well maybe you're lucky but
minecraft okay then now i know what you
guys are talking about the whole time
um today it won't be a long stream
because we also
already played uh we i already streamed
for three and a half hours on kelly's
channel basically
so it won't be that long and maybe one
and a half hours who knows something
like
that uh let's do a few quick rounds okay
oh so i don't know how much i can use my
brain right now because
i just took a 40 minute
nap with my kitty cat which was
so comfy
so soft heaven ah
so yeah i'm uh maybe not hundred percent
here yet
you wanna hide
that is like the best snaps you can take
is while having my hop my hands like
buried in the fur of my kitty cat
oh my god
[Music]
okay i was ready for the number uh any
server and a server
let's go we'll change the number each
time i'll change the code i'll change
the
the server each time after each round
okay
just make sure to not join again if you
joined
if you ever joined the game before with
me okay let's get a lot of people in
uh okay let's go
you like universe
g like
s like spaghetti
be like bolognese
and like napolitan airs like elf there
we go
welcome welcome
yeah i was just talking about pasta and
all that kind of stuff
[Music]
emotion hello everyone
what you said well i said it to na
what do you mean you use of it by the
way it's useful oh what
except north america for me
okay that's weird oh well i'm actually
surprised that you guys got in how did
you guys get in
it always says and oh
oof how did you guys know that i'm in
europe now
i just well i guess yep makes sense
because i wasn't here last time and i
didn't change it
you guys were just reading my mind okay
you guys these are the smart people
everyone this will be a good round
because everyone who figured out
it's gonna be europe anyway are the
smart people shut up motion you're smart
but also you're in the usual room so
actually you shouldn't let me kick you
real quick you shouldn't be allowed here
today
okay so
just kidding just kidding i mean i mean
i mean
don't worry you're stealing around today
it might depending on how you act today
you might want to stay in there a little
bit longer let's see about that
oh okay wait let me change my my
position a little bit
big bigger is better right i mean
i mean i mean with me you know anyway
ah let's go uh turn off stream everyone
turn up stream please
[Music]
yeah you might you guys might need a vpn
to connect to the eu server but i'm
going to try to connect to
an a server after this round but i think
it will not work
we will see settings should be fine it's
still the same as last time
although i kind of want to turn off the
at least
one more long one because the long ones
are absolutely
unknown can i like say zero
you know what i'm going to do that i'm
gonna say zero
what's what's a common type ah i think
yeah i think i know okay you know what
five short tasks zero long ones is that
is that problematic
one long is fine since the map is huge
okay okay
okay one the short tasks five
fourth it was for before wasn't it
i'm not sure what should i do
why are you guys even still listening i
told you guys to turn off the stream
uh a room time uh oh my god okay let's
go
uh five five short ones one long one
let's go
turn out the stream turn off the stream
let's
off stream
turn it off
[Music]
okay oh last time i didn't even get to
be anything i was only
uh crew mate
oh god i got no do i have those shitty
electrical ones again
no oh that one no
okay is it always the same number this
is uh seven
six so now
one let's see how long i need for this
one now
this time five wait ah
hello brad don't kill me i will kill you
if you kill me
oh that's the one two
oh
oh my god i must be this one
three yeah
uh four and five was in the beginning
though
oh wait maybe not you know what five
oh my god we're almost done hopefully no
one gets killed yet
so i can finish this [\h__\h] seven no no
no no six yeah oh my god
counting with kiara see ben
i did it oh my god i did the longest one
early enough
okay okay where are we going shouldn't
all these doors be open now
uh we are going oh here's one more
i'm busy see the problem of that one i
never know where that
is uh but okay i'll see i'll try to find
it
uh i'll try to i'll try to find it
where is this where is that oh [\h__\h] oh
they want to go there oh
hey hey i was the first
i went
in four two nine six okay
the bone meat started putting in the
cold earlier than me
but didn't finish before me do you think
that he's that impulsive
he's
okay what the [\h__\h] that was early you
shouldn't kill me that early
what the [\h__\h] squid
what do you mean hello squid
oh say hello to me
i am dead i am dead why is no one
wondering like oh my god kiara is dead
they they don't even talk about it hello
your attention was dead
you tanto's dad
hello hello
we don't see that they don't see that
i'm dead
what do you mean oh this person says i'm
grayed out
well a second oh bone meat is gonna
sound ces because the second after i did
something with him i died i don't know
it doesn't say i'm dead no i'm really
dead
i'm i'm i'm that dead
hello i am dead
i've always emotional things it was
black because
oh no oh no
oh no oh i said i knew i knew he would
think of that's us
oh
[Music]
that's nice guys
ah that was too early i just got done
with that stupid long task i shouldn't
have done that to be a long task
stupid zion skip they're skipping okay i
gotta do my best as a
no
i still have my casper voice on oopsie
god the window doesn't fit at all what
the hell
window why are you not fitting there we
go
i don't know let's go here i can go for
walls
see there's my body motion that's it you
want to work
report it no
wait do did he even see it
did they even see it
maybe they oh yeah taking a shower it's
a ghost
oh i'm so i'm a dirty girl
now i'm a clean ghost yeah
so clean turn that [\h__\h] on
hell
report my sexy body did you find it now
or not
oh
yellow was running away from it but i
only know that science
is the imposter get my message
across now it's okay i showered
oh call and gay
my stream is not even in 4k
my stream is one what what is it what is
it
i don't even know
[Music]
quick guys self report wait who recorded
oh brand you know what
you lie you cringe
i mean i feel like it could be a
self-report who knows
what the ghosts want to kill yellow wait
what did yellow do that they're kicking
him out
what because he ran away they're they
actually been leaving that okay
i guess so oh
what's eating plaster or not we will
never know
or maybe we will know in a few minutes
okay bread onion
tomato patty
bread [\h__\h] shouldn't close it like that
brand is that bridal penny
brand onion tomato onion
bread bread
onion tomato this is really difficult
is it like that yeah okay
woohoo we did our carefree job
let's see let's see oh yellow who got
kicked out is following
a green wine
what's up here what's up one time i
can't do anything here
um i'll go somewhere else wait my
my telescope ah i did all my tasks
why is he crawling was he following
i forget the caller's name green green
green
oh wait now i got some tasks
download kelly's lubes
guys did you see the um
did you see the the the fan art oh that
mamaloni did of our managers
it was so cute
oh there we go
with emma jenna and jja and i'm
surprised she got the
the managing manager distribution right
because you guys some of you were like
she got it wrong no she didn't get it
wrong she got it right
it's always been like that
it's just in the beginning there was
only enma so
uh gouda and amma referred
to their manager as enma
because genma i and i invented the name
genma but gemma has always been there
so just to explain that but there is
they
they we all in the beginning only said
edmund but you know
it's actually correct the way she drew
it
yep you
the way it is it is what it is yep
and it's so cute that is so cute us as
babies and those cute jumpers oh my god
so cute so cyan what the [\h__\h]
and last one is sign yeah knew that guy
was sucks when he walked in from
from the left and showers and never
trust anyone who walks into
you showering
galaxy brain not only really like mama
only is
god she's a god
and then also while me and kelly were
playing intakes too
she drew that fanart that i retweeted
guys if you're not on twitter you're
missing out on a lot of stuff
that fan heart is so cute it's gonna be
my next thumbnail
so what's going on here guys can you
figure out who's the last impossible why
did they do an emergency meeting anyway
how many people are oh oh yeah
four four people left only tasks left
okay okay i'm gonna do my best as well
um okay but that that
was yellow really and one of the
imposters
could have um in my opinion could have
been well so i guess
several one of the current bad ones were
killed by
ah
some of the current ones were i guess
killed by yellow okay makes sense
yes they skipped yes yeah okay
[Music]
they would have lost if it was otherwise
now at this point okay
oh school engine room uh tincture's
still alive i'm not alive what do you
think
what do you mean
[Music]
let's win what is that
what there's a task where you can dress
them
oh i'll have to do what it's uh above oh
uh hi
[Music]
hi there we go nice very fashionable
eight four five six four eight four five
six
four okay
am i going to be the key to winning
what where am i
am i going to be the key
i'm done one more
oh yeah it never ends
it's going to be me i'm going to save
okay you let's look at him is he gonna
be able to kill someone
he's gotta be real careful he's one of
the smart
oh where's he going he's one of the
smart cookies because he figured out
that i was gonna be on the eu server
there he is what i did
go away
is he acting as if he can't get through
look at this we can get through
what you gonna do
oh he's waiting
on it
i'm completed i'm done
stay together you still stay together
stand together
stay together
don't don't leave each other now
don't leave each other
okay oh buzzy's gonna he's gonna think
it was motion maybe
no okay okay okay
okay motion says it's science okay so
now what does what does green say
okay they figured it out
yeah those [\h__\h] doors that's why they
are the thumbnails today i hate those
doors stupid toys
they're so annoying i'm actually
surprised i didn't get to open one of
those stupid doors yet
this time well because i was a [\h__\h]
ghost the whole time
no no what do you mean no
let's go let's go report round do
something
vote vote vote vote vote
again
yay we one wait one
ew nice
[Music]
gt i guess talking like a real gamer
i know you don't say that i think it's
cringe anyway okay no i'm leaving
actually bye bye guys i'm
opening a new one okay
see it says north america but i guess
it's not really
it's okay let's select the europe i can
try
north america but i'm probably gonna get
kicked out okay
i'm going to try okay
[Music]
let's see oh it worked
okay okay
let's go and you guys are
mad because i say it's crazy probably
because you always use it
never mind don't worry it's not cringe
it's all good it's all fun
i am gonna say the code now ah can you
still chat oh that's a good question let
me test that now uh
yeah i can i don't it's not gonna
stop working when people enter right i
can chat now so
it should be fine okay
okay code j
like japan
see like
china set like zebra
zebra tea like tango
be like belgium act like france
welcome
okay this person is getting kicked out
right away
oh
should i click kenjo don't worry i
actually kept you in
and i will forgive you because obviously
it's a typo
last week you were in the asian center
when it wasn't working oh
did i never test out the american server
so i'm ntr county see
monkey okay are we 10 out of 10.
hello everyone some accounts are blocked
it only work oh it's
i depends on the account not on
i thought it was a general thing oh that
was an
actual book like my account doesn't work
on eu oh for real that sucks
okay okay well
then uh we know now that it works on
uh the n a server and and the user i
hope they fix that though
okay close stream everyone
let's go let's
go
uh don't don't kill me so early
by the way
i mean i'm not trying to be salty or
anything
but me as
the streamer shouldn't be killed so
early
it's okay to kill me no promises [\h__\h]
you do this
just kidding okay no no bullying no
bullying let's go
i can't prove my see last time i never
got to be imposter
and uh here we go again
uh okay we have a task in the armory
oh but i can't walk through there uh
four and put them here
what the [\h__\h] are you talking about hi
tease
um engine room got something here
the thing is though that now they're
actually really listening to me
and refraining from killing me only even
when they're alone with me
because i told them to that means that i
am not a reliable source of information
what the [\h__\h] what is that chase
because i would say like oh i wasn't
looking at this person this person
didn't kill me you know
but i mean i'm crewmate yeah
what yeah me too
what do you mean just making sure
everyone knows what the [\h__\h]
huh
oh oh oh okay
why why was that necessary
oh and that stupid meaning
unnecessary what
that's either a 11 year old child
trying to sound funny or
or a troll but that could again be just
a child
i don't know let's see let's see what
happens if he ends up being the imposter
then
okay then i don't know what that tactic
was
why did i start out here again damn it
should have started out somewhere else
oh well okay going up to the vault
at least i'll try to
so yeah i was trying to come here i'm
playing with puppets again no i'm not
actually uh
someone turned off the lights let me
turn them back on
where is it again ah wait it's already
fixed
eh i'm confused
okay i'm going to the showers picking up
some towels
[Music]
what
oh my god
what time is there i didn't realize hell
typhoon oh he's
not watching the stream i would hope but
yep okay
what where is that where is that what is
that does it here
yeah is it always here
three seven eight zero five yeah
left side okay i fixed it you're welcome
i am safe i think we can all let me get
let me
know here bye bye suckers
ladies first okay
hello yellow i don't know why
what are you doing here oh well you
could kill me if you want to but
yeah yellow i guess it's safe
yellow has been following me around for
a while but why is yellow
come here with me yellow come here move
do something
[Music]
oh we got our dead body the first one
yeah he that's very nice that would kick
that one
very nice who whoever
killed pink good job
yeah light kill yeah there's two
imposters and it only killed one
yeah we're getting the task one soon i
guess
maybe one maybe you maybe it's bugged
and
we only got one imposter is that a thing
that happens
like one of them passes oh no that is
probably
yup i
and then am i i guess i could say the
same thing about
yellow may leave
me perhaps
yeah yeah and yellow probably good
too yeah
yeah i i have to agree yellow
seems a bit sad to me by covering me
and being alone with me trying to get on
my good side
but he's probably fine
he's probably fun yeah we could probably
do task victory
he yes tasks lego
he asks
yes judas uh what we always mean
uh i mean
i i think that's interesting because
that's kind of what we kind of
talked about too
but with me as you can see i'm saying
but it it is it could really be that
he's
yellow it's just trying to get on my
good side who voted for someone there
when she says shut up
did someone vote for me
did someone vote for me what the [\h__\h]
voted
i'm being framed
horrible horrible horrible treatment i'm
getting here
a vert crash course a vert crash course
of earth crash cause i'm on my way
i'm on my way
again i'm saving the day why is no one
here
why is no one here seven three
one one six what what six
two three two one ah okay
i guess that was too slow who did the
one on the other side
oh dead body reported
two people that knocked tyson rest in
peace
couldn't move that whole round it weird
ripped hyphen
i did the crash course thing
on the right side
i was scared of what he was getting
trying waiting to get me
green is safe even though you say that
even though you couldn't
move blue was near me definitely
innocent
i was glitched couldn't move damn sounds
rough
that's rough buddy
uh uh japan side had that moving issue
too what do you mean with japan signed
i didn't stab anyone
ah okay judas try clicking
the gear when
meeting is over
just pick that up from the chat trying
to be helpful okay
because i am not sus i'm helpful tanjo
as always
[Music]
what why are you assuming that my chat
was helpful
and not me that was totally mellow
oh come on jonas that
i i wouldn't know ever
oh yeah yeah okay you know what judas
actually plays this game really
seriously
so it's good um that he's in this round
like
he actually really probably keeps note
of who's quiet he's probably really
writing those notes down
in his death note
why and brown being the ones quiet
compared to all of us
that is true yeah yesterday completely
quiet did they ever write anything at
all okay once
uh huh yeah but white
definitely didn't say anything and i
can't
uh i can't vouch for
any of them either also sea monkey looks
like riso senpai and as we've seen in
its takes too
scribbles are kind of sus
but maybe maybe white yeah if he if he
hasn't talked a single time maybe he has
that bug
where he can't talk can't write in the
chat
oh sure okay here we see brown and she
probably get away from him
he might very much be the imposter oh
[\h__\h]
okay he he walked past me oh
okay i did it
who was that next to me what
it's close i'm scared
it's open here now
wait is this here no it's not yet okay
the lights are back on
there's a bunch of people here
interesting
open the [\h__\h] oh oh i can open them
that's the door okay thank you for
opening that stupid door i hate it
i forgot that that door was one of those
stupid [\h__\h] doors i thought someone
closed it
can you not open that door let me help
you
[\h__\h]
you are welcome how are you not you just
gave up on it
brown dad okay oh interesting
i say white is one of the imposters
then it's not brown okay then yeah
right down the hall he's trying to frame
me
maybe i didn't do it
self yeah actually you might be self
recording yeah
yeah ah it's probably not
wait oh [\h__\h] they killed
judas because he talks too much
my god
okay blue is at least saying it's not me
oh my god oh
we lost all but but but but
but maybe task complete possible
soon
this is probably white at least white
i would i would i wouldn't even mind
voting for light even though i have no
proof
but come on black what the [\h__\h]
because he's just been so quiet
we have to vote i'd vote
i don't wanna i don't wanna um
influence everyone okay
um
i vote white i know
do we really have to vote um
i don't want
no proof but he's been too
quiet and i've never seen him around
evil
and no one vouches for him evil
so yep
shut up yellow it's probably you too
yeah it's probably yellow
i've been in love with yellow in the
beginning but we
we don't know he might have just done
that as a cover-up
oh [\h__\h] oh scattered what the hell okay
but he was
he was ejected okay okay
um cat hair
okay uh okay we got one
over there
get that one yep okay
someone turned out the light so what do
i have to go down i want to stay up can
i stay up here
do that quick quick quick quick quick
quick quick quick
okay now someone turn on the lights
again nice thank you
oh and something down there okay let's
try to get there quick
i'm done soon with my tasks
what do you call these cards employee
cards
is that what you call them like with
those that you can
get in some employee id card or
something like that id card
okay thank you very much everyone ah
what
let me get the one down there i haven't
seen i haven't
run but oh blue is here i haven't ran by
anyone anyone else why did blue not go
down
with me why did blue not been maybe did
he think because i'm doing it
uh are they what what what what
what what
okay i did it no don't kill me now
who was that sound i did
it all my tasks are complete
all my desks are complete give me a new
one
don't give them
who was it white and
white cyan that was a stairway to cyan
white and purple ah
task complete no it's clean
very clean oh they took quite some time
in the beginning
trying to kill someone so it took them a
lot of time but in the end they were
kind of speeding up
wait there was only three people left
alive
oh wow and one of them was me
nice nice one
okay bye bye oops
ah oh yeah that's kind of sounds some
tough to be an imposter
but good job
okay next one
10 fps to shut up i'm i'm
i'm trying my best to be as high fps as
possible
am i not like looking okay i mean it's
i wouldn't say it's 10 fps you sometimes
sometimes you see some
some hits of 60 fps but it's definitely
not 60fps
oh that's not private without uh yeah
we're doing uh
n a again mata
americano wait
when did i hide the game have you guys
seen it at all
did i hide it just now i don't remember
hiding it just now
did i hide at the whole game
just now okay i forgot him i i didn't
show time memory
okay i'm going and i'm going in guys
uh what i don't even remember
are you [\h__\h] around with me now i
just went in and now you're bugging
again
shut up you stupid [\h__\h] okay we're going
europe after all
let's see how that works
okay europe worked
that's gonna be tough if i want to do a
big big
collab on on among us again if they're
just
bugging fix it please
okay code let's go the code is
a oh like orange
it's like
snake g like
georgia jay like japan
said like zebra is like for france
[Music]
welcome welcome everyone
good catch here yeah yeah yeah yeah
you have you got hair
hello
ever okay um i
i i said don't kill me
right away but
um like i wanna last round
i i was a lot able to stay alive until
the very end because of
um i me saying don't kill me right away
or if that was just a coincidence at the
end but
you killing me
generally is okay so don't wait
too long just because i
said so
okay stream close please
okay yeah don't kill me don't kill first
round only i guess
okay yo that's cool
let's go kill me but don't kill me
exactly that is
my logic i
i'm okay this has got to be around where
i get imposter right because
i i maybe there's a bug where
with certain accounts you can just never
be imposter
let's see close the streams guys be
good people okay
[Music]
i mean i i i feel relieved but
it's kind of lame
a bit lame but okay
i'm really but the first time i get in
plastic i'm gonna be so panicked
it's gonna be very panicky
someone turned all the lights again god
damn it
uh wait i can turn them uh is it fixed
okay
okay towels get in there beautiful i'm
gonna buy
a whole fresh new set of towels when i
move
but i wanna buy them in store what kind
of towels do you guys recommend
any recommendations i'm actually quite
serious
asking that question but i don't think
anyone can actually give me
recommendations
soft ones fluffy ones but it's they're
not
too fluffy it's also not good i'm just
saying
charlie's towels that sounds wonderful
uh who died
already you love it
flappy white towels i'm not
asking about colors
well tail towels are great nice and free
free
they're not fresh
anyway found body involved top left
pink body you know the way that yellow
describes it i mean he is also the one
that reported it he just sounds very
safe so it's definitely not not a
self report right the same for pink i
thought
since i saw him on the clock do it in
the cockpit
very tasky okay
uh well well flyer falls as a reference
to gandalf also with the hat i
understand it now
gandalf gandalf
it's just got it now
yay
[Music]
um i don't know what to say but i'm
sounding sad because i'm not saying
anything
i've been picking up towels
oh that [\h__\h] countertest yeah
so you're running right from around
company i wasn't confident
cat hair and cockpit please i don't want
to go there i hope i don't have to go
there i'm already like overloaded with
catching although today i did
um i had some weird energy today that i
normally don't have especially
not on streaming days like normally i
just
stream and then chill back in my bed but
but today i woke up and
i i started you know
i get out brush my teeth no first i
always eat breakfast first and then i
brush my teeth because i don't want to
brush my teeth and then have that
disgusting taste in my mouth i don't
know about you guys
do you guys brush your teeth after oh
before breakfast
hmm
same same after after before before
that's so interesting why i definitely
prefer it afterwards anyway so i did
that
and i then i uh i i went i
actually i i went out to the supermarket
first to get something for my breakfast
because i just wanted some fresh stuff
and i also got something to cook
tomorrow and
i'm making um carbonara with uh
uh chicago what's sparkle in english
german bros help me out here please
the long long stuff that's either white
or green
and in very pop asparagus yeah i'm
making carbonara with asparagus which i
think fits really nicely
uh yeah i'm cooking up tomorrow for me
and my roommate because she often cooks
for me which
is really sweet she often just cooks too
much and lets me eat some of her stuff
um oh wait the lights are off i didn't
realize
uh so yeah i did that and i came back
home i had breakfast brushed my teeth
we're kind of late but yeah whatever
and then i i started actually um
cleaning up my room and i also did the
cat toilet i did so much
so many things before my stream
normally i just like i just
chill especially if my stream is like
that early
i don't really do much before my stream
yeah but yeah i was productive i'm also
surprised thank you for sharing
my surprises
[Music]
energy
what's up here one more that person okay
that's not much more fancloing
blue blue talked a lot that's kind of
sad that he's gone now
just i find a second body this time
right to the main hall
all right it's okay i trust him
right to the main hall and the task is
with towels
oh i was on my way to
the vault right now
the only person i saw once
on the way there was red
i think i saw no one else
eating breakfast kind of sucks it was
not much it was not much but
to my room i'm making uh omelettes with
asparagus because i i want to use up
those asparagus so i'm making omelettes
with asparagus
and like bacon and and cheese and and
asparagus
and then in the evening i'm gonna make a
carbonara without asparagus sounds yummy
doesn't it
that's really good
so yeah i'm proud of myself i cleaned
also i cleaned my carpet
in my bed from cat hair there was so
much
i have a pretty fluffy carpet and it
really
like it has like a pretty bright color
so you don't really see the cat hair
that well
but it definitely catches a [\h__\h] ton of
cat hair
so i tried my best to get rid of some of
that cat hair and then i also vacuum
cleaned my room
and yeah as i said i also did the cat
toilet which i don't do every day i need
to do it more often but yeah
i don't do it often enough i have to
admit
but i did do it today even though it
wasn't like
fully full with poop yet
it was pretty full but not fully fully
fully full
so who's us
i do not know we're not voting are we
we're not voting huh two people voting
for white
we didn't talk for that through is he
getting kicked out
no again who voted for white
no i'm not neglecting my cats but the
only thing
you know you guys know how much i love
my cats i think
the only thing that yeah maybe i'm
neglecting a little bit is the cat
toilet yeah
i wanted to get one of those automatic
cat toilets i i saw
um i followed some cat instagram
accounts
um and some of them like they're really
popular so they get
sent like some special uh oh i'm
really close to that thing nice they get
sent like you know these automatic
toilets and stuff which is really cool
and but they're really expensive but i
want
hella i wanted to get one of those so i
was looking on amazon but i talked about
this before actually in my stream i have
one that's worth it
i mean those that wait am i not done
okay um okay black seems safe
what was i saying yeah and there's like
automatic toilets
that look like a space thingy or
whatever like a space helmet or so
no those are really expensive there's
some cheaper options too but i read
all the reviews and it didn't seem like
it was really working that well
i don't know if i should get one i don't
know
but uh oh wow wow black what the [\h__\h]
are you gonna kill me no okay oh black
is definitely safe
anyone
uh oh purple no don't leave me alone
how did that just happen did was green
also there and just killed bl
black right aft like at the same moment
when purple killed me
what happened i want to understand
wasn't there still like so many people
wasn't there still so many people alive
in the last meeting
so i guess they went off to get white
and then
get went up to find black and me and
before
i we could find the find the right body
and what what about yellow
what
how what the [\h__\h] happened
what happened explain
i want to see that from a different
point of view
records yeah me wow
uh uh oh
oh and there is a possibility that there
was only one left but then that gives
you an automatic win
oh okay okay okay oh good job
wow we can't wait to play seven but
we're always making a new lobby
okay new lobby european silva
but i i can try again i'm gonna try the
american one one more time let's see if
it kicks me out
america high temperature
oh no you just translated wait i got in
i got in
i got in okay
american server good then everyone who
can't get into the european
[Music]
okay let's go f like france
p like philippines
j like japan
oh i like road
or red yeah red i like italy f
elf
welcome
[Music]
you were not were you in last week
miss fest you are amazing
uh you are getting a promotion
promoting promotion from promotion
what why did fist you
did they why did they god
why didn't why did they fist fisty
misty this why did they
censor the fist and the y
mist face
[Laughter]
painless
it's good that i can decide who pays me
more huh just kidding
ah yeah game
music sucks listen only
to kiana
okay anyway
to alex really
oh oh how what the uh what
are you guys friends are you guys twins
yeah what there is there naturally
there's one imposter
well then the note can't be alec
is the imposter obviously
uh my music anime music hmm
[Music]
no i i wouldn't say so
because it's not like an opening landing
or ost
from any kind of anime
[Music]
so i would say no anyway i know it
sounds like it but that doesn't make it
an atom also i know i look like an anime
but that doesn't make it anyway
can someone else get in because someone
left it still says 10 out of 10 dog
let me count one two three four
five six seven eight nine oh come on
two people join instantly oh wait i'm
one of them right
okay okay okay okay
okay okay let's go close stream
let's go i always forget that there's me
okay
lunar says he can't talk
well that's a problem that's a problem
because you will not you will
you will beat us like if you were the
imposter then you
you can say as an excuse oh yeah but i
can't defend myself because i can't
chat if you guys know that you can't
chat because you have the book then
please don't join the game
now it's i can't help it if you
if you didn't know that you have it but
still
um anyway don't watch the stream that's
for sure
but don't kill me alec
so let's do this guys wait i'm crewmate
again by the way
i asked this before but is there such a
bug where you can
not become imposter whoever
this is so loud
[Music]
rng i mean i i have to say i'm kind of
relieved but it kind of sucks from a
from a
streaming viewpoint although
maybe not i guess it's both is
interesting right or do you guys think
this is boring because i'm not
becoming a imposter this is is it boring
or is it the same
in like the same amount of interesting
to you guys
no matter if i'm crew mate or imposter
okay it's interesting giveaway
really buff is cool okay egg open the
door
open it oh my god okay
oh [\h__\h] those [\h__\h] doors
took us million years to get here we
didn't even all have to come here
meanwhile people are getting killed ah
okay only one though ark is dead
who was with us it was like
insane yeah yeah okay yeah
for some reason we went before people to
do the lines
your lisp thing you've got going on is
pretty cute i don't list
do i that's the first time i
hear that piano are you a redditer i'm
quite active on the
whole i've read it but besides that i
have no idea how right it works i don't
i don't really like it
i don't feel it i don't understand
reddit so i only use the whole live
reddit you don't list yeah that's what i
thought
crewman is more interesting
but from would you rather watch your
homework from the kids perspective
you know that's uh that would be
interesting are there horror movies
there probably aren't horror movies with
a killer perspective right
i mean i don't watch horror movies at
all
i feel like that's also that's also the
thing but i get what you're trying to
say
no please do not recommend
any other reddits
here thank you
could always be that it's the
self-report could always be
everything is possible
also by the way guys i'm taking tomorrow
if you guys are aware of that right the
only reason why i'm doing two streams
today
is because we are streaming on kelly's
channel we we streamed on cali's channel
today and i was like
okay if i don't stream on my channel as
well then that's like two days without a
stream on my channel that's why i
put um two streams today
i've been thinking you know
dungeons and dragon streams hello
everyone we're doing something like that
can we organize something like that it's
not dungeons and dragons it's something
similar
but we are working on that i found a day
off potential thank you i'll be cooking
and i'll be also
checking out my new apartment again for
some reason i just want to show it to my
roommate we're just
chilling we're just going to check it
out and then
maybe bring some stuff already there
while we're at it well i mean why not
because we're probably
um yeah we can carry something okay this
is the most disgusting
task ever
i don't even understand how you do this
these [\h__\h] sounds too
a bit more come on i don't have time for
this
oh it's going back no
[Music]
ew
[Applause]
ah sorry don't agree i i did not take a
dump or anything that was not an idle
meeting
where should i go i don't know
he better not be in the chat later
saying kiana took the biggest
[\h__\h] dump on the toilet it was stinky
when i walked by
i'm gonna get mad if you do that
yo shh something's on the sun lights off
again
i don't shower wait i don't get there
like that i have to go here
here here here up here
let's go i have cat hairs in my face
complete and now let's go left side
we got a bunch of tasks over there and
one up at the very
top hello was that scion passing by the
thing is when you look at the map while
running
you will kind of miss out on what's
going on
the egg yolk drops when they kill me
punch okay i was just going to say punch
find me you know the white one but
he bent it just as i said that so now we
know it is a
white and yellow
so white and yellow
yellow huh
[Music]
yep yep
i am oh i am
[Music]
am i scaring you you gotta say yes
otherwise i lose my confidence as a
ghost
boo boo
[Music]
am i super scary yes
give me a ten out of ten where did kiara
die
i died close to the burger king in the
kitchen which is absolutely
fitting and
thank you thank you thank you
[Music]
oh ghost punch
brown and white no no no
yeah we'll come in at last second too
but
i watch brown vent well yeah white says
it's
brown brown is not oh my god
oh no they're framing each other
please believe it's it's not brown
no
i've seen both of them it's yellow and
white
i'm just gonna this might end and bad
i hope they i hope they vote fell well
oh no oh
i love it
[Music]
that's what everyone no wait well yeah
but we
wait yellow zoom out [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] oh no no
well but but the ones voting for brown
was probably yellow and white
oh man we've got a problem they're all
saucing each other now
oh [\h__\h] you know what i'm gonna remember
that when i'm imposter i'm just gonna
frame someone i'm just going to say
he vented i silence even though like he
saw me
okay i guess yeah when someone sees you
venting you should you
that's the person that you should
probably sus
try to sus and say that it was not me
it was him and maybe you can brain [\h__\h]
him
so bad that he even himself starts
believing oh
brown emergency button okay
no new dead buddies did he see him bent
again
why white wasn't a button
you mean loud emergency [\h__\h] interesting
interesting
if you're hired a crew accusing brown
why aren't you trying to blow them up
uh-huh brown is trying not to get me
voted out
i saw him bendy trying to paint on me as
i'm trying hard
i'm running white dumb brown okay okay
get right
out of here wait i'm getting confused it
was white and
yellow okay okay white and yellow
what if i hit the button it will look
like gas lighting
which button are we talking about
emergency funding
okay yes one imposters out nice
wait did youtube like kill my stream for
a moment or
like i see something weird going on
okay where are we okay let's do some
tasks fast
speed no okay didn't happen
okay youtube didn't do anything
okie dokie
oh number one
let's go up here
ghost chicken i am not a chicken
that's my member's number
employee number going straight down
there's something down here
is it the wi-fi thing oh yeah
oh i didn't know there was an outside
place here too
oh
that's us yellow calls the emergency
meeting sucks oh the
gamer is getting very very um
what's that in english again
best friend he's getting desperate
oh yeah no one's the photo sprout
um come on vegama
that's not necessary if one was trying
to bring the others
then one is definitely not impossible
let's just
what good punch
what do you mean good punch oh
they're having a conversation
well at least at least it wasn't right
who killed me it was yellow i will never
forgive you gamer
oh no oh no
we need green to believe brown
wait is green something brown right now
i didn't think that that's right i guess
yeah yeah yeah okay
because they were busy killing people
push the button after that true
long cooldown for the button okay that
could be true too
ah
i am i'm done here
how are you doing here doing fine thank
you
boom boom
this controlling conversation what who
is who is he saying in controlling
conversations
[Music]
he was just trying to help
that that was yellow's influence that
oh my god oh
[\h__\h] and that's that might end really
badly
um we might have an issue here
wait doesn't it say total pass complete
why not why am i still doing these
things
too powerful he figures
everything out yeah and they uh they
kick him out
oh no let's try to fight oh there he is
oh no there's someone
no one here let's see what he does
a gamer he's he's like he's sweating
right now
he's stink stinky sweat oh
i can't do that one right okay
wait wait wait
[Laughter]
[Applause]
yeah yeah granny's like all the way over
to the last time
oh thank god wait did he just kill
someone before zion walked in and zion
didn't see him killing him but he saw
the body okay
did we do it after all
ah that
that's taking him out right
[Music]
to because everyone was saying everyone
this was the first
round of all of them everyone was so
suspicious
of other people
wow a very sad round
indeed oh man they all got trust issues
we game will never forgive
oh man okay well thank you guys
yeah yeah yeah watch heart challenger
and my new song convert
[Music]
okay that concludes
it i think um sorry
it's kind of short but this is where i'm
leaving it at
uh
what
should i i'm trying to figure out if i
should read super chat today if it's not
too much you don't want to read it but
oh yeah you know what it's really not
much we can totally read it
okay then let's wait some super chats
and then we will
uh sign off for today and you won't see
me for one whole day guys can you deal
with that
are you okay are you gay
you're gonna miss me probably i know you
will maybe i'll upload a small video
anyway let me move over to the
to the chatting screen
[Music]
again sorry if you couldn't get in but
next time next time there's always a
next time where you can try
so no time to lose
going straight over here
i'll be lonely kiana i understand
very relatable
it is what it is guaranteed
tomorrow on a guy oh probably not
probably not i already have so many
other streams this week
um sorry sorry but two streams today
and i think the day after tomorrow we
also have two streams
i think or any other day there's another
two stream day
so i'm actually you know giving you guys
a lot of streams so yeah
we only have the ones from today's
stream right so
should should be fast oh wait casper
super challenge
it's a casper super challenge
gospel
[Music]
okay wow it's really not much we could
do this like in five minutes but you
know me
you know me and my tangents
okay wait they need we need some bgm
there we go
um
okay let's go
collab poem however
i sent out a deadly quest to make ten to
my wife
the promise of her lovely fight
sustained me through the strife
i finally arrived one night and pledged
to
her my life reflected in her eyes i saw
oh [\h__\h] is that a scythe it's kelly
because she's the only one who's going
to marry me
nice wait i'm kind of small here
nice poem
thank you who wins
collab with a hudo thank you
mr casper's dancing my heart still hurts
from getting booted from the match
last stream so i'll just be a casual
viewer today i know you'll give us a
great show thank you i hope you guys
enjoyed it yeah
i mean it was a short stream and uh
unfortunately
not not many rounds but i hope i hope it
was okay
uh we can have some short ice creams
every once in a while right
um
what's the [\h__\h] kitten for the tour and
it takes two
thank you ah wait zappa kitten
you're in the usual room yeah yeah
you gotta stay there for a while and
learn from your mistakes
you've always been so good but you
called me um
[Music]
a cartoon chicken on twitter and i saw
that
i see all of you guys tweeting even if
you don't ask me
be careful be careful okay
human exactly just stop being bad to say
hi and say that you're beautiful and
wonderful mama i hope you won a few
games today we'll be rooting for you in
my dreams thank you
kiara's predictive sketch finish my
daily reminder
thank you thank you actually that really
helps
genuinely finished out thank you for a
red super chat
wow it was nice to see you
and callie are having fun together my
takamori energy was filled once more
and as always hope you'll have fun with
us and among us thank you i did have fun
and
it takes two is like
i i didn't really do any research on
what kind of game it is i didn't watch
any like videos on it i just watched
like two minutes of video through that
for that from another person's stream
only two minutes but so i really didn't
really know
what was gonna come like how the game
was gonna be
but it's amazing it is
so much fun
like it's like it has it's like kind of
i guess a platformer but it's not a
painful platformer
it's very forgiving because you don't
get like game over like not much unless
you were like uh
dying at the same time as your partner
but that's still then
it's not really a game over
[Music]
um the graphics are really pretty the
co-op works nice
it's it's it's it's like it's not
but even though it's like so forgiving
and the platforming part is not that
difficult it's still like
um like the puzzle puzzles if you can
call it that
the riddles are also not too obvious
sometimes
so you have to think a little bit it's
very cute
and fun it's so much fun like there's so
many like
portions of the game where where you
like like
like ride on on the rail or like you're
right
you're flying all that kind of stuff
it's so much fun it feels like a
freaking
adventure park somehow
[Music]
the rails are fun yeah
i'm so glad that that game came out
recently
it's perfect i love it it's so much fun
i i haven't had that much fun in like
a game collab in a long time like actual
like
not fun because of the person who's with
me i mean of course
kelly being there made it better but
like i mean having so much fun because
of the game
simply because of the game alone wow
that was that was really good
hands over rice tangent for the youtube
only bros okay yeah
uh during that it takes two
collabs it seems like there was an
announcement during it i saw it
afterwards right away
on twitter but tales of arise
now has a release date
[Music]
you know i am as you probably know i'm a
huge tails off fan
and a while ago there was an
announcement that there was going to be
an announcement in spring
and i was like i was so hyped that
everest i thought okay does that mean
that the game is coming out in spring
no but here we go we have the
announcement now
that tales level rise the newest main
uh ship wait how do you how do you call
it again
like it's its own like world how do you
call it again main ship game
is that what you call it
flagship flagship mother [\h__\h]
all this [\h__\h] i mean
flagship okay i guess
there's a bunch of uh ways to call it
mainline main flagship the newest
flagship game
tales of horizon is coming out on the
9th of september which is
um around like the one year debut
anniversary
ah a little bit before because i think
one year
debut will be on on the 12th right or
like
14th of september
12 12 for me 12.
yeah and so everyone mark it on your
calendars
even if you don't care much about
themselves turns off is my
most favorite uh game
series in terms of arrives it's going to
be amazing you have to watch it
while i'm playing it
hey this is
yes maybe not maybe yes um
time passes by so fast somehow we will
see
how the next months go if i ran out of
the game then yeah
we might maybe try a different tales off
game before
but the ones that i have permission for
at the moment are all games that i
already played
so i don't know i don't really like
playing games again that i already
played before but with tails off games i
would maybe make an
exception i started the tails game
because of you it's fun
nice which one did you start
which one did you start tails is a must
watch yes it is
it's gonna be amazing i love tales of uh
games
so much and heads of her eyes has been
looking pretty damn fancy
from what i've seen up until now the the
main character lady
looks beautiful
looks so beautiful and the graphics look
so nice
i'm so excited ah
and it's so soon uh actually um part of
me [\h__\h] maybe
maybe at the end of the year maybe
december who knows
i was being a bit hopeful that maybe
it's gonna be out there in autumn
september automotive late summer i guess
it's autumn
maybe she looks like a serious lilac
gun i thought so so that she has uh
similarities to lila i am
yep nice one someone who knows a tales
of dysteria
lisa oh my god well then that's really
early it's really early
i'm really happy about that i'm pumped
i've been waiting for a new tails off
game for such a long time
um
oh my god i'm gonna probably like with
tails off games i want to get the most
out of it so i might even do a lot of
side quests on my own
accords like on my own choice like i
really want to get
as much as possible out of tales off
games now
so i'm so excited i'm so excited
[Music]
is the tail of a bit darker than tis of
cesarean no no
no no no no no
telephonia and tales of uh
cilia 2 are the darkest
the darkest tail valve games out there i
would i wouldn't even say
ah no no they know about the same
darkness
tales of symphonies where i start off
the stream uh and there's older tales of
the games but it tastes terms of
symphony is one of the
most popular older ones one of the
ones that made tails off popular
overseas is tales of symphonia but it's
not the
first one no no no no but you can't
really start anywhere
except not celia too you wouldn't need
to start at celia one but
you can't start anyway it's no problem
symphonia was also yeah my first one on
gamecube
yeah okay let's go uh anyway i was
reading
i was reading felix says uh
super chat sorry i got distracted for
some reason
did i finish that one up already did i
did i
answer it completely i mean there wasn't
really much to answer
let me read it again it was nice to see
you and callie are having fun did i read
did i read it oh my god i got distracted
oh my god felix i'm so sorry
i got distracted
kenzo it was nice seeing nice to see you
and kelly are having fun together
i did i did okay i'm so sorry my i got
distracted my brain i don't remember
things
my attack on my energy was filmed once
more and as always i hope you'll have
fun with us
i guess i did read it
i guess i did okay well felix here
another kiss
thank you daisy thank you
vampire i can't stay and watch boss due
to some iran but i wish you
a long survival and if you're imposter
again i was known a poster the whole
time that just reminds me thank you
vampires
again didn't get to be impossible what
the [\h__\h]
i want to practice being an imposter
because otherwise
if i do a big collab and i get to be
impossible the first time there then i'm
gonna be [\h__\h]
oh no oh no
oh no you're an imposter in my heart i
guess that doesn't sound very good
impossible stressful yeah i really agree
with that
um
the great
amongst couches because you are so
[\h__\h] king
awesome i
like that i like that
so [\h__\h]
i love that i love that
thank you haven't played troll monster
thank you
[Music]
what spirit vet thank you
nagel thank you for the pinky now i'm
confused so jay chad has kelly yep emma
has
inaudible
thank you emotion thank you
i got into the first game sally you died
so early but it was still fun to be in
the game excited to check the archive
now
felt like i was the third impossible
during the game though and i have no
idea how i survived
well why did you feel like you were the
third one
did you feel obsessed on your own
yeah that's why i told you guys that my
manager is always so busy and shouldn't
watch my streams
like when it's in in the middle of the
night for her
i told her she has it really bad because
like she's managing three girls
overseas all in like different time
zones
and yeah her also being in a different
one
that is really [\h__\h] tough
that's why i feel so so sorry you said
gentleman's responsible japanese sound
so i never said that no
no i never said so
that's completely different from what
you said before no i never said anything
else no no
nope you guys must have imagined it or
made something up yourself or like heard
heard like i don't know some weird
rumors and thought that i said that
she needs a raise yep
no she's really a great manager
[Music]
anyway now that you guys have finally
found out the truth
no more confusion no more confusion
but he said 200 talents we assume
but japanese because we also assume i'm
including a match by emma well i don't
understand that sentence
yeah i only said that genma the jay in
genma does not stand for japan
that's what i said i think maybe that's
what you guys misheard
that yeah my point was
it doesn't mean that jenna like manages
me and callie
just because she has a jay there yeah
so anyway rather dance back as soon
it doesn't matter anyway though it
doesn't matter who manages who
you guys know way too much at this point
anyway
you guys are getting way too worked up
over the managers you guys should care
about
the talent i don't know why why
every manager now has some kind of
design and
fan base and all that
[Music]
you guys are getting way too much into
it okay focus
focus on the holo en members it's five
members okay
i'm a you know gurda kelly me those are
the five members
focus get your head back into the
and onto the most important things the
reason why you guys are here
but always appreciate the managers of
course they're doing some hard work
okay sorry i had to drink some water
[Music]
see you guys have crashes on jtag and
and like everyone
oh man you should have a crush on me
what the [\h__\h]
am i not good enough for you guys
anymore
[Music]
mochi sugar
well you will never get here like that
reggie steele thank you soon that's nice
back to back streams god damn
i hope you're taking care of yourself no
worries i i ate food in between
i was so like like living
like a good life today i was doing i was
so productive before the stream and even
in between those three
two streams i ate dinner and had
a nap and made my thumbnail
so i i've been doing quite well today
i i don't know what's going on today
you keep commending other people who are
working hard and doing such a great job
you definitely no slack yourself always
looking forward to your streams viva la
yada thank you not
now as well is that a red super chat by
the way
i don't really know that currency but
you did write a lot of text so it
could very well be a red super chat
i think it is actually probably it was
oh you know okay
that's nice thank you thank you for the
sweet message
thank you well i do have to say i do
slouch off a lot like i go i get very
lazy
a lot like especially um
before streams and after streams like i
i i chill a lot in my bed with my cats
watching stream
watching videos and stuff and i do
[Applause]
i do criticize myself for that a little
bit i i need to
do do more things
i need to yeah
be more productive maybe that will
change a little bit when i move
who knows
but me cooking uh every once in a while
is already a big improvement
i've been making breakfast on my own
sometimes recently
so tomorrow i'm gonna cook as well
so let's go let's go improve my
own lifestyle shouldn't be so lazy
it's schnitzel breakfast food no it's
not but schnitzel is yummy
good food for lunch or dinner
love that you're cooking yeah yeah
carbonara is one of the few things i can
cook well because it's not that hard
to make that
can we have cooking streams oh when i
move i'm going to try to do something
like that yeah because uh we did like a
chocolate making stream recently
and oh my god just got like a million
discord messages
oh there's a collab
being planned not by myself
but i'm in it no no i'm not gonna say
anything else
i'm not in trouble don't worry don't
worry
you guys what the [\h__\h] you guys know
about it how
did bother me if i talk about it
did she talk about it oh my god you guys
know the exact members too
[Music]
as we talked about oh okay it's not even
secret okay
yeah we're doing a collab with me what
am i sent by
eofy senpai and kelly for people collab
watashi takamori yeah
uh i guess she chose people uh who speak
some
japanese because it's all members who
speak
who speak japanese we're doing a collab
um something next month
look forward to that i think it will
probably be on whatever
channel
[Music]
we
simple on it
or am i forgetting something
i think it's my first yeah it's my first
one isn't it
yep no i was not
i was not in that humongous collab
there's a few people saying among us but
no i was not
in that one that was uh other en members
i don't i don't know it was uh who
i'm in i'm in cali
we're in there i wasn't in there
there's always some people who like
think i was in that collab i was not
no yeah i was i never come up with
anything that will be the first time if
i don't do anything before that
yeah uh residency
[Music]
henry stickman um i don't know i'm not
planning it the frogger thank you
new maps look nice yeah
oh maybe you should tell your friends
about the update
cass found a friendly mouse thing or
something something right
again does he mean well of only staying
before six hours
sorry i got excited when i was reading
that because it scans my scanspong
[Laughter]
well that's so i was getting excited i
was getting excited was it so painful
it doesn't sound like old cars but maybe
i made it too high
what not the not the real customer yeah
i don't know maybe it's not the real
classical
purple picture oh yeah he doesn't have a
profile picture it just says see
did he did he never have a purple
picture i'm not sure
when you died the first time you were
gone for six hours oh
oh wait he said that because i turned
into a ghost in the plane and he's also
a ghost
ah oh he's so cute
even if it's fake i don't care it's cute
i miss casper
that's so cute
yeah sorry casper i wasn't there for
that long but i'll visit you again
[Music]
and i somehow killed y'all while i
bugged and only used quick chat
for the game thanks for the game you're
colorful hook papa sounded amazing thank
you oh wait actually i didn't realize
though
yeah in the beginning someone told me
that someone couldn't use the chat and i
forgot about that later in the game but
it wasn't even that obvious you only
used quick chat
good job i didn't i forgot about that
later on that's how well it breaks out i
guess
nice one alexandrian
kf girl can't read that it's luke thank
you soon black
start function
random collusion with mrs thank you for
all the uh promotion you did a great job
nils osterman thank you and brazilian
dossier
i have a friend who's behind on his
child support payments because he super
chats too much
could you please talk him some
responsibility into him he's a big fan
so i know he'll listen to you
[Music]
is that like serious are those child
payments supposed to go to you
uh and i'm not gonna
i'm not i'm not gonna get mixed into
this
and i'm not i'm not gonna get like you
know in
in include
in in yeah
um i'm just gonna say
uh be careful and be be um
be um not careful um be um
i can't find words right now be
um responsible thank you guys you guys
are so smart
be responsible with your money
yes that's all i can say
uh jw duncan judas action i died so you
can live and when i died you still
roasted me
[Music]
i'll you'll see more in the future
whether you like it or not
thank you judas thank you for being
there it was actually um
sad that you got killed later on because
you actually were
um you know very serious about the game
very helpful
yeah what the hell kiana is far to say
so to kill and the game knows it
that must be why
yeah i don't know i mean i wouldn't mind
like getting
impostor at least once you know to get a
feeling
um although i do feel like i can never
never um probably figure out those vents
like
even in the old map i never really i i
i'm not one of those people who knows by
heart
which vents are connected with with
which vents
so i will just use them like randomly
well you've been responsible with my
money
funny misspent
uh you're close to a third of the way
for the game oh right
what it's not long huh is it
so maybe three three more streams like
two long ones one shorter one it seems
um okay well next one is on my channel
or we try really hard to finish it in
three streams
well today was three and a half hours
next time we can maybe make it four
hours if we do well and then that last
one until the
end twice as long as a way out
it feels much shorter now than the way
out if you say that that was almost a
third of the game
we how many parts do we have for a way
out five
four
definitely not only two parts
three it was only three oop
wow okay that's also pretty short okay
well i guess we can finish it
rather soon then hmm
[Music]
there's been a misunderstanding i didn't
mean to write the cartoon c
word and then type heavenly angel with
an amazing voice he doesn't sexy
it just spelled very similar in my
language it was autocorrect
i will let the chat be the judge of that
oh does that like kitten deserve to be
in the usual room yes or no
he's used to six kids before through
okay it's that five kids and it seems
like you have no choice
and the majority says that
you will need to go to the usual room
i know yeah definitely our kitchen is
generally a kind so
i know i know he's a good kid yeah
he's a he is he is but he has to learn
his lesson
see because he's a kitten he still is
kind of cheeky
and uh likes to
likes to tease his mom but
he's like playing around you know and he
has to understand that
he has to respect his mom so okay i will
say one week only i think i said two
weeks before but i'll say one week okay
i lowered the sentence
okay
[Music]
the game is perfect for the both of you
and thank you for the stream my tacoma
your heart is full again the immortal
stream are
great i hope you get some rest on your
day thank you
yeah i think the game is wonderful i'm
really enjoying it
it's actually sad that it's so short but
i love these kind of co-op games where
you see both
angles on the on the screen it's
really good for streaming so i wish
there were more games like that
i hope they make more quick fast fast
red pizza duncan if you guys know more
games like that please recommend them to
me
skydiving
i'm gonna miss monster hunter rides and
since four because of my schedule so can
i have approval to stay in the usual
room for two days just for meditation
why force germany
is like that oh
really i don't know that thing
dragon's crown any side scroll won't be
there not [\h__\h] that
i don't like side scroller beta mom
sorry
lego lord of the rings games
sorry can you pronounce gemini again
yeah
[Music]
was that wrong
germany no i said germany [\h__\h] you shut
up
don't make fun of me step our kitten
down
you forgive me and i'll get you that
deep feather out you tried
shut up shut up daniel thank you
thank you for the pinky
gemini whatever shut up all of you
roses is
chicken that's right now
yes please do not send me to the usual
and i had to do it after hearing all
those poems in the last week
you are now going to the usual room you
did it on purpose
you did it knowingly you're going for
one week you're not going into this in
the same room
as that by kitten because everyone gets
their own room
so i hope you feel the loneliness
i hope it was worth it
in berlin
huh
[Music]
sorry just told the story to my german
bros
about getting my phone stolen in germany
[Music]
why is she saying words which don't make
sense it's german learn it
watch my german learning stream
neither to the hotel yeah that's scary
because someone sent me a greetings from
berlin which is where my phone got
stolen
is um that's okay i'm talking
fill in the blanks thank you black
search and donkey stern you have 67
dancing thank you for the
thinking you should be responsible with
my my money
okay i am i'm trying to be responsible
yep
[Music]
thank you for watching little lebron
games thank you
honestly akira and corona collab has got
to happen sooner or later i think that
will be entertaining don't you think
uh yeah i think so too i mean eventually
she will hopefully
um do me the honor to be uh on hall talk
someday um
yeah of course i want to get older all
the japan members in home talk and
even a normal i don't i don't know if
she's interested but even normal collab
of course i wouldn't
i would never say no um
and
that's it guys we're done and i will now
take
one day off and see you guys today after
tomorrow with
i think what's today what are we doing
today after tomorrow
shout out first ah yeah we're doing
shadow voice deck building oh yeah so
that's actually what i'm doing tomorrow
too i'm gonna open up the game again and
see if i remember
uh parts of the game
how did you learn english so well i
learned it in school only but
i always like was very active in the
internet
when i was younger too and used a lot of
english like in mmorpgs and stuff i
guess
when i was younger so hmm or like in in
i don't know i don't know i guess i've
just yeah
used it a lot in my free time as well
thank you and i was also very active in
school in the english classes
i really liked it so it was fun studying
english in school
yeah yeah yeah and so yeah
thank you guys for watching today hope
you had fun and if you miss me that one
day
when i'm not streaming you're welcome to
stream heart challenger and my new cover
if you haven't watched it yet
has everyone here watching is there
anyone who has not watched it yet
raise your hand if not say yes if you
watched it no if you haven't watched it
is there anyone who hasn't watched it
no no there are ones
really only a few ones but okay
great you are uh now
chosen gd direction by the way unknown
duncan
you are chosen to um
go watch the new song cover that i
uploaded
two days ago no yeah
yesterday yesterday it was yesterday
yesterday
in the morning yeah if you haven't
watched it yet please watch it
it's in my music playlist as well if you
go on my channel and scroll down a
little bit
there is a music playlist with four
songs in there
a film around memory thank you
now fluent thank you
apple's total is yummy sorry for not
watching it if
you did not to be under aussie dancing
are you crazy
what i wouldn't have expected that from
you
go watch it right away immediately
what is going on why why did you not
watch it yet
it's like just okay it's a long cover
it's six minutes but still that's
nothing what the [\h__\h]
randy duncan thank you
you make songs yes i do i make music too
please listen to my music
mario's entire family packaging what
more
acoustic songs in the future i don't
know maybe
it was kind of fun to do it and it's
kind of refreshing and
and and something else if there's a song
that i want to cover
and it fits an acoustic cover
then why not i guess
well done okay good night guys um
take care follow me on twitter subscribe
watch the songs some music videos yep
yep thank you thank you i'm glad you
liked it
and in german we say
au 5000 i love you all so much judas
thank you
what why you only play games reviews and
once every couple weeks you make other
con
yes yes i do
[Music]
how do you say thank bye bye guys
bye bye thank you for all the support
jessie ling donkey and shut up
be careful of what you say i just got
here don't leave
you can watch the archive now how
exciting is that
bye bye hot wings thank you bye bye
black rich and dangerous room
fall out new vegas is that is that not
an fps game
i like to join twelve thank you thank
you i'm glad you like it
jake it's monkey thank you no no we're
not doing this again no we're not
president of zankye yep you better genie
duncan
chris we're not doing it again
it's an rpg first person are we all
hi thank you soon
bye bye bye
[Music]
in
thank you guys
[Music]
really lonely
black fortune duncan love you too
one of the the best games ever which one
the fallout one
bring your dance
[Music]
uh