so
hello
hello chat are you there
can you see me
yes come in closer hello hello are there
any investigators here today
hello hello yes coming closer coming
closer i have a mystery to talk about
there seems to be
mythical creatures on the loose here
let me just see if you can hear me let
me see if the void is transferring our
our conversation waves right now
monday
yeah
yeah okay
okay
all right
hello everybody
my name is
and today a mixture of two ingredients
that i can't say on stream
everybody's microphone is on now oh dear
could it be
one with purple hair oh my goodness
yeah that one
could it be
you're on that side oh man
look at that chat it's
what's your name mythical creature
i am uh
[Music]
inaudible i i work at branch number 537
of kfp
oh i see maybe that's the language you
speak at kfp hmm
wow
kikiriki i can't wait to learn more
about your intricate language of kfp
what was your name
okay
yeah
i like it sounds like something martian
i like it let's see i wonder
who could be next do you hear something
it sounds like
doom
death
despair which one sounds dangerous
hey ricky
[Music]
dangery do you
ever iggy
you
who could it be
oh
oh my god is that could it be
nice to meet you i am a deps
apprentice or a
takanashi
wow where do you come from
you're so tall from hell
oh
okay oh wow
do they have flames on that
it's the underworld
[Applause]
do you hear something i don't know what
is that sound could it what is it what's
that what is it it smells like fish in
here is that one of you
is that the natural odor of hell well
they say that fire has sulfur which
smells oh that's egg never mind that's
true
could it be volcanoes volcanoes
i smell face unwashed hoodie
what
is that soul
who could it be
smelling like unwashed hoodies man i
wonder who it could be too oh man oh man
guess who it is it's the one the only
garage
[Music]
hey what's up my name is
number one number one shark
youtuber on the planet earth
memes
memes and middle finger
you speak
where do you come from goriope
i come from it uh at
um at
uh the land the place to be at atlantis
which is the place to be hello
hi
hey guys i know that you must ow [\h__\h]
monitor
anyway
anyway um hey guys i don't need to recap
i'm fine i'm good hey everyone this is
just the natural form of my body i do an
interpretive dance for you all and um i
have
something to admit oh david um this hair
is super cute i love it because you know
it's just the true essence of of gariopi
but actually
i have another hairstyle to show you
another one could it be oh gosh i'm so
embarrassed oh moe moe kun here we go
oh wow
[Applause]
[Music]
atlantis does him seem to have a knack
for making very cute people so
wow
well on that note it appears
we might be missing a potential
additional mythical creature
and one mythical mythical creature i
believe i came here to investigate
mythical creatures so you better all be
mythical
i remember saying someone who looks like
it could be
[Music]
who could it who's left what could it be
something big and um
potentially we need some tentacles
tentacles aren't missing
some tentacles
um
i mean we're all supposed to be here on
time so i don't know i don't know where
i don't know it's too late
what did we tell you about getting in
the suit for this stream watson oh
camera's not on
oh my god
oh there she is
i'm so excited oh watson we're excited
to see you but that's that's
that's not quite right
i want an autograph please that's the
famous
that's the famous confess
well yeah where did staff go where
what did you do to them did you eat them
she ate them yeah
watch out
she's not talking are you okay but i
guess that's realistic because small
amount in the festival also didn't speak
at all yeah that's watson in the suit we
gotta move the show on he wants her
we're all alone watson take the suit
take the hat off at least so you can see
your chica
take that off take that off
we want to see the real army um
oh my god
oh my
holy [\h__\h] oh dear
oh
oh that was kind of [\h__\h] up
[Music]
[Applause]
so
[Music]
[Applause]
hello hello hello hello hello everybody
we're back
yellow oh coffee and my little sharkies
we appear to be back is everybody
okay we're live
what just happened
we got this this
what are you
in
it's the last musical creature
waiting for bubba kim ba-ba
boo-boo
ah boo-boo i see it i see it yeah yeah
yeah what i am
uh
ominous
what
[Music]
it appears that everybody all the
mythical creatures are here now
everybody gathered
we're all here yay
yay
hello everybody
does anybody want to
show off their outfits a little more up
close
i do once i get my hair together yeah
yeah
okay
from from from uh
uh uh the order where we came in
with these okay okay we can do that
hi
[Music]
cute
oh my gosh you're adorable
look at your little
[Music]
oh what is this camera angle oh wow that
was pretty cool do that again bubba
whoa bingos stay hey there you go
where's that one who knows oh it's the
it's that one it's focused on me though
all right we'll just stick with the a
camera then that's fine okay
okay
there we go
[Music]
my dream came true because i became
really
sexy today i always wanted to get into
kelly's clothes
what was my dream
oh yeah congratulations
like you do a good job working in the
underworld i will say
yes yeah you haven't been you haven't
been working for them for a while so i
they needed someone to help them out so
i decided all right i'll take the job
i'll do it then
fine i'll do it myself
um
i would say that there's a little bit
something missing in the bling-bling
compartment
i mean um but look at those sexy legs
nice legs legs legs oh they go all the
way up wow
very nice
spins
yay
can we do that for ena one more time
just cause
[Music]
cute your color palette works really
well with this
the orange it matches your hair
oh
i guess
i feel so like yeah girly but i love how
the colors look on this one
actually that's all the pigtails yeah
bubble gum like bubble gum colors
hold on hold on i got this hey guys
into my stream do you guys like do you
guys like memes oh dude big jokey wokeys
no no don't say that
don't i mean actually no it's just a
signature part of you all right that's
true
there are many other fantastic qualities
like i can sing very beautifully and
like uh like stop softly listen to my
reflect hold on no please continue
please continue
[Music]
anyway do you guys like this hair too
cute yes it's cute
i want to see the shoes too show the
shoes
you got to review the shoes
i love these kicks this is actually a
lot how i dress like when i'm not like
when i'm just chilling in my house like
this is what i wear like just a hoodie
no pants wait are there pants on this oh
i got to check my pants
on
i'm the investigation number today so i
can happily say that there are no pants
under that screen is it just
where is that that those kind of clothes
it doesn't look like she forgot to wear
something but when callie is wearing it
it looks like she forgot to wear a pants
the power is short
no i just got the spanx this is what
happens all the time when i go out to
like especially during the hotter
seasons in japan because i mean let's
let's face it i'm a filthy [\h__\h]
gaijin so when i wear i wear my shorts
and i wear big shirts people look at me
like what the [\h__\h] is wrong with you
they're like we don't do that here i'm
like but why it's hot and then i smell
my shoulders
if you're wearing shorts and it's hot
you freaking idiot anyway but that's
that's me uh gariah p i'm super tired
from dancing yesterday yet suddenly i
feel genki because you ladies are here
with me
little finger memes memes memes memes
[Music]
you're more than a meme to me though
girl i promise no thank you i appreciate
that treasure treasured friend yes touch
touch touch thank you thank you
thank you careful with that hat thank
you oh yeah i have to return it hold on
i'm speaking up should we see uh
you guys already got a good enough look
at me didn't you
are you sick of this
great
you want to see amelia don't ya well i
guess this is partially amelia hello
oh
[Music]
compliment the coat
it wiggly wiggly
just like everybody likes it
we switched clothes but we didn't switch
bodies
bubba
i'm gonna beat
[Laughter]
i am a menace
[Music]
actually filling out the top part of the
dress
that's true
for the first time ever no offense
excuse me you're gonna stretch it out
enough
[Music]
you know salt on a chocolate chip cookie
they put a little bit of that and it's
good
i love those wings though
and there's
like a corsage in the back corset
corsage corset yeah
who did that who closed that for you um
it was good yeah she helped me dress up
thank you that was nice it looks good
nicer
i love it i love you guys oh my gosh
yeah you really do fill that out huh
i was gonna say do you guys feel like
playing a game
yeah i came here
uh one reason and that is to force you
to do my bidding and my bidding today
is twister
all right let's play some twister you
guys ready
no oh ready as i'll ever
ready
let's do it ladies let's push the
twister button how does that sound
[Music]
all right who's ready for twister
twister my bad
okay do you guys know how twist two
sorry twister cause it was two stars
it's been a long time but i feel like
the rules are
self-explanatory yeah okay hey bubba can
we get thank you bubba
thank you
all right
this is the twister whale jet
i will be spin master the first round
i'm going to spin and determine what
foot or hand will go uh there
what suffering awaits our fellow miss
members today
i have a question yes what what does it
mean what happens when somebody falls or
if they mess up is there like a like a
punishment or do they just lose
there's no punishment there's no
punishment for this game no i didn't no
not for this game but yes if you
last one standing wins if you fall over
out of exhaustion or you slip and fall
then you're out and you have to leave
the mat
sound good
okay yes all right as four players i
will twist for you
and also spin the wheel
on there not for the first round i'll
let you guys enjoy the first round
all right all right the first time or
the second time
i let you guys spend your first uh go
because uh
i guess that's only fair so who wants to
go first
i'm already twisting so i guess well
okay there we go spin that
all right do i just click on it yeah all
right
left hand on green left hand green
why can't i go all the way to the ground
okay do your best
do your best
who spit
there we go
we can get all tangled up awesome
yeah watson tangle with me
become tangled okay wait do you have
enough space for this yes
okay inaudible next follow me okay you
know go next go next
left hand red knuckle where it is just
the beginning chat
before soon tingly twisty mayhem will
soon arrive
hello
do i just push it yeah click
go go
all right we're starting with lots of
hands today
god that's the worst hands [\h__\h] suck
oh it's just gonna get better just you
wait all right i'm gonna spin again for
kalei be mori
awesome let's go
[Music]
how the [\h__\h] am i supposed to do that
figure it out
watch where you place yourself
and yeah i know we're all friends here
it's okay my face is right in here
i think i've lost the game already
now where'd i go no it keeps i'm
blacking out
we're good
no
i can't go any further
she doesn't even need any twister
prompts she's twisting
i broke my headset hold on a second
don't worry chad i made them sign a
waiver i'm not responsible for any
injuries that happened during this trip
anyway let's spin again for amelia
what's up
[Music]
it's like you guys are scared of the
center of the mat that's alright though
we'll all become close friends closer
friends okay who's next
[Music]
left
ah there we go
from here
let's go
okay
hmm they appear to be afraid of the
center of the mat i hope this changes it
all right callie up next
spinning for cali
let's see what we get some center mat
action perhaps
left foot blue all right all right
[\h__\h] hold on
okay even in the real world just this
would not end up
not a world that exists where this works
she's manipulating me she's trying to
get me down
i can't even steal my hands and then
green that's all the way the [\h__\h] over
there all right
reach i just found my bottle of jack
daniels
and i really should have moved
you didn't do
uh left foot green
left foot green
it's easy
it's cause you're on the outside of the
map doofus nice
okey dokey who next we have
[Music]
okay can i okay well well then that's
easy that's just easy get you bigger
space
that's easy
where did you go
you
[Music]
okay
kelly are you good you kind of got it
yes god i'm fine are you stuck
oh i'm great just don't even worry about
a little
that's more accurate
okay spinning for cali
everybody seems to be doing okay so far
this is impressive
please get my hand off the drink oh
thank [\h__\h] all right
who's
[Music]
you're in like the marvel superhero
landing on the ground pillars yeah
i'm squatting i'm squatting
[Music]
oh you've got like a pose going on too
now that you're not clipping it
okay i'm clipping it to cali's calf this
might save your wetson your next move
nice yellow is left foot yellow
go to the right side i didn't have any
right side movements
the game of chance who knows how i got a
right side one
oh good it's looking pretty crowded in
that right hand corner
you guys started over here you should
have started on that side
okay rapid fire who's next they're going
all over the place
yeah here you go go go go go get you on
the right side squatting
[Music]
spinning for enough stretch and stretch
and stretch
stretch for that kickity kick
oh dear
which one's harder for you inaudible
my trackers are all over the place
your body your body looks like a knot
right now
what is that creature
basically hi
it looks like i'm actually inventing new
mythical creatures to investigate
yeah this is a this is something like a
blood-borne boss that you're creating
right now
she's ready to be uh implemented in the
elden ring
myth will get the job
regardless rest all right who's next
ena oh no cali
nobody's falling yeah this is surprising
save me you wanna start yourself no no
no no no
no okay all right
that's fine i can do that i can work
with
if only good i could push us like it was
real life right then you would be so
happy that we could fall down oh yeah i
could threaten to come and tickle your
armpits or your ribs
[Music]
let's see
what oh right my right foot oh okay
okay
well you can't move around you can't if
you place one hand down it has to stay
there ideally it should stay in place
oh wow
you're so tiny like a little cinnamon
bun
it's pretty cute
spinning for gyawa
yes blaze
i need a change in position you guys
stretched before they stream
[Music]
uh-oh they're starting to crumble okay
right foot blows okay
okay how how how how how how
um
is my butt allowed to touch the ground
yeah we can't tell it's good oh god
and i'll just be chilling here okay oh
wait you mean like in real life no you
gotta keep it up the ground because
that's
of course that's what i'm doing
okay let's spin again
spinning again
but if you guys sit then you're not
gonna fall over as easily because you'll
be chilling
so i guess if your butt hits the ground
that means you're out
no no no my lines are holding me up in
the air because i'm really strong i have
muscles
hold on
yeah yeah
he has a left foot
hi
okay let's go green left foot green food
oh
[Music]
oh no
actually i know how to win this game
uh-oh
don't tell him i'm good
oh
aha and appears an obstacle has come in
for the last two remaining contesters
competitors could put it could put ka
puts spin the wheel who's next can we
not touch wherever she's on i guess
sounds good
i think maybe
i'm next i'm next right hand green don't
touch the reaper in the right hand green
don't touch the obstacle
can i go on the same spot as my other
foot is on oh that's a good rule i'm
going to say different she keeps on
moving she's blocking all of the blue
all right i'll stop moving sorry i'm
trying to make myself like you know more
more of an obstacle for you but now it's
fine
that's okay that's okay
there you go perfect kiara up next
what's that fancy camera what you got
for me what you got for me oh you can
turn the rail up
left foot red
left foot red okay
oh my goodness
all right
spinning for watson
is pretty flexible but oh his thumb is
hanging right in yellow
nice
nice nice watson's pretty good at
pretzel nice okay
yeah
i still have nothing on my right hand
yeah you're lucky left hand
yellow all right uh oh
here's a very close by easy peasy right
hand still free though
all right rapid fire let's see watson
i guess if we go long enough you both
win if neither of you fall
left with blue
i guess can you not take off stuff i
don't know i kind of have to
yeah oh my god you just look like a pile
of legs
[Laughter]
[Music]
foot blue
live on blue yeah
avoiding the reaper obstacle
oh
also i guess if you've already placed it
though you can't place it again there
there's one way to go about it
a different one does it have to be a
different blue ideally unless you're out
and then you just have to hover it
i really like how twist it where or two
still works in my domain it does a
twister has different rules than twister
exactly
left hand
game
yes what is it left hand yellow
so it has to be different yeah
oh
how else am i going to get you to fall
over all right
okay fancy
what is it this time
right hand red
okay um
oh that's so hard okay
uh
yeah i just gotta change some things
oh wow the moves the moves
what's it
huh
knees
right foot red
swinging can i move like or my where my
limbs are
it'd be funny if you didn't but
nice
[Music]
on the beach for some sexy instagram
photos
oh that's the center
[Music]
okay
we might have to cut it down three more
turns whoever last inning
left hand
green
oh
okay oh that was simple yeah oh my
watson holy cow
you're looking like a supermodel
left hand red
left hand red red oh okay well now we
have a problem because uh there's for
some reason in the real world there's a
door there somehow how did i get here
okay
well this is actually pretty and not
anatomically impossible right now for me
[Music]
um maybe if i go through my leg all
right i got it
oh my word
she's finding a way it's getting kind
[Music]
amelia watson oh
okay
i can't go through here
i dearly know if you can't reach past
the reaper then i'd say hover whatever
limb you're supposed to oh she's like
sort of on it i can get a finger on it i
guess i um
[Music]
ass can i take that one
if you're daring enough to put your hand
there i'll let you have that one
all right
watson
like yeah right foot i'm sorry
little bit red right hand right jeez
right foot blue
i'm okay what what what what what red
food red right
red food red
[Music]
that was a tricky one does that mean
watson is the winner amelia wins
twisty pretzels
do you need a hand
celia pretzels
a good game
all right it's good i'm gonna join the
twister yeah yeah yeah
youtube right yeah you know
yeah sounds sounds good everybody up for
a rematch i don't know if kelly's mind
if i [\h__\h] won out you could be a
dedicated barrier go ahead and slide
into the center here yeah oh let me just
swap
the dots if she's on it um here i'll try
and like just pick up space like uh like
i'll like decide where i'm gonna
see a challenge
could it be the right hand side or
perhaps yeah i guess if you cover like
half
redemption
you can still win
all right first one but if anybody's
tired don't feel uh don't feel like you
have to if you want to set it up
ten hours yesterday ten hours of
non-stop movement so i'm just gonna lay
down on the ground you're still in it
don't worry
who wants to go first
oh dear i'll i'll go first
okay spinning fur camera oh i spin it i
spin it okay splint it
a sponge
is it spinning
[Music]
i like to start with a foot very good
all right
i'm on it
hi
should i step on you
if you like
all right uh you don't want to go next
good i want to go
okay in our next
who could it be
what could it be
oh dear hand red uh sorry right hand
blue
red and blue oh dear
hi kelly oh jeez
let's see
i didn't stretch before the stream
either
you mean you know
what tell us but nobody did
did it spin it's not spinning from mine
it's fun for me
okay
[Music]
yeah it's a good workout we spend a lot
of time sitting so all right that's true
next we have kiawah
all right kiara's next let's see what
[Music]
okay i'm going in my squatting pose
again oh dear i'll go under under cali's
five if that's okay excuse me you're
allowed you as long as you ask
permission first
i'm gonna touch
okay
next up
[Music]
we got left uh left foot red
left foot red
red
oh it's already on red kind of
boom okay
all right
all right next up
and let's put blue
[Music]
okay i don't you tail on the wheel
though so hold up is anybody's butt
directly
are you are you twerking over my dead
body
maybe
hi
oh no callie don't die you're so funny
don't die kelly i've never been so
honored oh no kelly you're so sexy don't
die
oh my god
they're waiting for me
oh sorry
all right kiara next up
yes oh this is i am ready
uh what i got put green
left oh
green oh no
[Music]
okay my legs are cool
what is it next up we got right foot
blue
foot blue sorry oh wait chiara's hand is
on it uh
wear pants tj style
uh can i can i go oh is it frozen
it doesn't look like it's stretching
that bad but off stream it's really
stretched out here right foot yellow oh
does that help
it bring some hands she needs her hands
otherwise it's too easy
okay
yeah that's not fair she doesn't have
any hands on the board yeah
whose face is this inna
all right next up
she had easy mode on
i don't think i have anything on my left
hand yet still i think i made a mistake
facing backwards
okay next up we have inna spin the wheel
you look like one of those wacky
inflatable arm flailing naked behind us
left foot yellow
happy april fool's by the way everybody
oh yeah oh my god what happened to my
tracker
yeah
i mean now it's already a second for me
but yeah yeah same well it makes sense
appropriate
what's wrong with your eyes this is
wrong
something is very wrong okay well let's
go fast
[Music]
you do look naked behind that
left hand green
i think something broke
wait what were my rules again i can we
can't use the same dot we already used
uh
yeah that's what you said okay did i use
this one yet
yes that's how it is in twister because
it'd be pretty hard to memorize which
was which that's a good point all right
we'll keep it like this because this is
hard enough it is
[Laughter]
[Music]
my hands all my hands and all my legs
are in
i'm please
kelly's place
you know we have hey don't say it like
that
left hand
oh
okay you know technically i was out
first so it's all good
good at your left leg doesn't even seem
to appear to be on the board i think my
tracker's on a pile of clothing
i'm flexible you gotta see on the fourth
you'll see i'm flexible i promise you're
just doing yoga it's called the corpse
pose right it's
[Music]
please somebody save me
you did this to yourself girl you know
yeah
wait can i reset once because i feel
like i'm a knot
that's pretty so fun aren't you enjoying
yourself
[Music]
i think it was both hands on on blue one
on one on blue and one one leg on blue
and one on yellow okay just put it down
on the crowd
next up
you know where's the wheel forget it
please hurry up
[Music]
oh my god
the physics were too good
it's like it doesn't
physics don't apply to the shark's tail
i thought that everybody was doing huh
what
that pose it was a jackal pose or oh
jesus
all right next up for kiara
yeah
[Music]
girl might have to tap out
i'm huh win this one
it's uh right hand blue
i'm already on the right hand blue so
can i just spin again
[Music]
okay
i have a question did anyone anybody get
uh fooled for this year's april fools or
did you
not get uh
so i went i came back from 10 hours of
rehearsing for my 3d birthday live
supposed to be greeted by um a shitty
soundcloud rapper who broke into my
house
tape on my mouth and then jacked my
channel and stole it from me so that was
kind of yeah i guess like i guess you
could say i was fooled
oh are you the fool
yeah both both of those things
didn't someone else somebody else also
said yes right oh yeah yeah
my manager they said that they were
gonna quit they said they're gonna turn
in their resignation on
on monday and i was like no
i don't know if you didn't get paid
enough
[Music]
i
can i tell you something
that she will not
quit until all her talents are have quit
as well
[Music]
but that means also that she'll be in
hell for much longer
[Laughter]
yeah she works really hard yeah love
love gemma
love love love gym
suffering i might have a job this week
yeah i can't do this anyway
are you not completely stretched out i'm
so stressed
give me the win
left foot green
oh god
oh
[Music]
that's because you know i'm just very
very very very very flexible extra
flexible
have fun
oh something
that's not sitting on an invisible chair
follow me finding a good god that
twister that she was asking for for a
long long time
that was very fun
[Music]
i'm not sure i have energy for my
twister right now ah
that was really difficult for me
it's okay we'll have a revenge match one
day together yeah
one day this is the warm-up
[Laughter]
[Music]
should we have a quick
reset
yeah
all right
okay should we go to a brb
we'll be right back we're going to brb
we'll be back in two seconds
[Music]
uh hold on
let me fix this
so
[Music]
hmm
so
[Music]
do
you
[Music]
we are back we are live
ready and live and ready this one on the
other side hello we're here
where the camera at
which one are we on here
oh it's on this one hello hello chad how
are you doing
oh that one okay yeah
how are you
[Music]
yeah
hey everyone you guys filling up for
another game perhaps yeah yes any time
with you
i wonder what i have about my slaves
fun game to play what kind of spooky
antics do you have popping off
i got some
junk
[Music]
also known as rock paper scissors
yes let's do it
i'm ready i have something special
prepared for this duncan pond game so
let's go ahead and uh take a look real
quick give me a second
let's go okay all right everybody move
out of the this is uh
yeah
get ready for donkey pong
[Music]
oh yeah yeah
baby tannoka
down
[Music]
pow
i think like in front of the camera like
this
right here hi bubba yeah that works
dang it how is that let's do we have a
bracket or something or uh we're just
gonna do random pairs we can do random
pairs yeah i do have a little bit of
spice to add to it additionally do we
need some all right we're good we're set
up we're good can i give you guys some
junk and pond trivia
sure yeah
do you guys i think all of you guys know
the idol group akp 48 right akb
you know
i don't know if they still do it now but
they definitely did it in the past they
did like in like a big arena with
thousands and thousands of uh people in
the audience they would have a a stage
in the middle and they would do like a
huge junk and pond tournament not a
concert
tournament with like hundreds and
hundreds of akb-48 members because it's
more than just 48 members it's way more
and and then um the winner the final one
it was it's really dramatic like it's
crazy dramatically like it's everybody's
sweating when they go like ah
and they like i interviewed them and
they're like i thought so much about
this and what i should do
because the price is to become the the
center member for uh the upcoming single
and they kept on doing that
and they really wanted me in the middle
because that's the one chance that even
the not so popular members get to be in
the center yeah
it's so dramatic really fun wow that's
hilarious we should do a hollow life
well we may not be fighting for the uh
the center the center pose but i do have
something else up my sleeve to make this
a bit more oh you have a prize
interesting
[Applause]
well
nope guys just look like you don't have
fame and glory
a little bit of a prize
okay shall i turn off toaster
oh yes
yeah okay yeah
boing is it all for let me see what you
guys see on the chat the chat well let's
bring out a
not this this little gem here i like to
call
b
the b cam
the wheel of onion
a carefully chosen carefully chosen and
thought out wheel of uh various
punishments that will be applied
will be applied
to the loser of junking pawn duos so why
does one say die gouda i guess you're
going to have to roll and find out huh
what are we going to do
[Music]
oh yeah
oh dear
yes well who would like to we should
start off going in pairs then what does
this say where's let's say
what's this one it says amelia watson 10
jumping jacks
what does that mean if somebody else is
you just one twister i don't want to
hear that you can't do it now
this is perfectly fair don't worry we
tested this it's fda approved let's do
it
we're just gonna have to spin the wheel
and fire it out let's start playing then
shall we all right
all right let's pair off let's see who
should we do
i want to play
let's do callie and watson and then ena
and kiara oogie
good and i'll sit and marvel at my work
all right
you guys know how duncan fun goes
on camera
bubba's still learning the alphabet give
him uh cut him some slack
best he could do is
okay
do you guys know the rule of rocket
paper scissors everybody
yeah i think so
just in case
uh what are we singing though is my
question like are we down like game
jungle and then on pawn we throw it out
yeah
uh paper beads rock rock beats scissors
and scissors beat paper best of three
good luck okay all right ready let's do
this [\h__\h] all right
ready all right little fingers crossed
paper
scissors shoot
i already was bothered
[Music]
this is supposed to be scissors oh you
beat me okay so belly is
if you put your finger on the buttons it
tracks your thumb too oh nice okay cool
yeah oh come nice oh holy [\h__\h] okay wow
that's awesome i didn't know that
great okay ready i'm ready okay
damn it you beat me
is that a gun
yeah
no
callie
[Music]
she's going to spin the wheel
don't worry i can probably
i can fix that it's your face
no my feet are in my shoes
excuse me you know who else would you
model them off of you know
anyway well it appears that the first
punishment has been the first blue
babies
how do we like it
can we get a close-up on amelia why come
here watson come show everybody
mr
[Music]
yeah i guess some people like this
that's true yeah okay
why are your feet
what's the problem with feet they're
just like hands but they touched the
kind of seemed normal to me like they're
very sensitive
a special feeling towards them or
anything maybe now you can't get caught
by the fbi because they uh they don't
have your foot finger foot
who wants to go now they're still
grabbing yourself like you grab his head
with neck it has a foot
everybody
[Music]
okay wait uh uh sh should i say it you
know or would you get we could try to
say yeah or sync it up maybe if you
wanna
uh okay so i have weights
and you're wrong
my feet are gone
yes
[Music]
what is that
oh this is rock sorry my thumb was none
rock okay
one for you
[Music]
oh that's so sweet oh my god it looks
like they're kissing wow somebody
screenshot that
someone will spin the wheel
do i get to
my own future okay i'm spinning
[Music]
what is it with the feet
it's my friend
okay so
they clap them
sit down and
shut them clap your feet sit down point
your feet
you're flexible you're perfect to do it
wait hold on oh there we go nice oh my
god yes you're beautiful
that's not a [\h__\h] bubba i mean i
don't hear them
i believe i heard some trackers smashed
together i think that's there we go
nice it looks like a workout oh wow and
callie you're you're okay
all right show off
look at me look how physically fit
extra high ladies that's right
feel it in your core
[Laughter]
all right
match huh oh the winner's bracket yes
play me oh
winner goes up against grinnell okay
okay oh so it's cali versus kiara now
oh yeah okay we can do that
yeah callie versus
put them up you know put them up i'm
ready to fight yeah
[Music]
music
yeah i'll do it i'll do it again if
you're cool with that okay are you ready
chad here we go
here we go
all right
ready uh first i'll do sideshow good and
then i'll say
which gives us a little more time okay
ready
all right ready
all right ready here we go oh
oh
[Music]
all right let's go let's go what will
the punishment be what will it be
all right here we go
do i win big bucks no whammies come on
boys
if it's something good
[Music]
what if the reaper dies oh oh
oh
no
oh this is sweet sweet irony
what happened who could believe this
happened to me
are you good
bro are you good
i mean
[Music]
oh she
okay who won the match
[Music]
all right let me just warm up my hand
here okay wait paper rock
paper paper rock
scissors
scissors okay
now we're holding okay
ready
bring it who's yelling drunken bun
[Music]
yeah okay i go
junk and pull it okay yeah yeah yeah i
mean the
that's rock there's also rock both rock
all right
[Music]
you know that's right i've got
beginner's luck now
ok
[Music]
bear
playing against you
[Music]
is it spinny
yes
i think it's glitched on myself oh there
we go it goes it goes
there we go
hi
is it clear
yeah also because i don't see it change
yeah
i will spin
yeah basically what i did all yesterday
yes oh and one that doesn't exist never
mind oh yes this chair totally doesn't
exist
lots of hover squats yesterday oh yeah
look at my core workout you know
looking great
wow you know oh i can't believe the
chair look at this he's so strong
look at those strong legs
[Music]
wow
no no we already
you're a hot
if you anger the whale you'll wreak the
punishments reap the punishment
should have been not getting to spend
the weekend wait who is
[Music]
this is a sight to behold the weenie is
in the way of the oh what's nekodoko
oh what's next oh dear
oh nico coco
coco
oh geez oh geez everybody's spinning the
wheels
[Music]
your feet are back you can give it
another here let me let go of her spin
girl's going to spin the wheel yeah look
good or spin girl's going to spin the
window
oh
[Music]
hello chad oh i guess we're just
spinning the wheel now everyone just
became
[Music]
[Applause]
i just want to be weedy
she wants to be well i wasn't expecting
them to want to spin the wheel i'm not
the winner anymore no they punish me
you still have feet for hands
again
i think we just have hong kong left
yeah
and the jumping jacks for watson yes
that was
you don't have feet for hands anymore
you skipped it
i guess we're waiting for hong kong
[Music]
what is
and i didn't turn into a cat uh oh
jumping jack jumping jack
i want to join the hand feet crew well
join me
in the fake
defeat oh
i wonder if we can all get weenies oh
never mind i'm no longer weenie oh it's
gone
kelly's a
[Music]
physical
i don't know however
long please
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh my god
no it don't
wait i'm sorry bob ross that was really
good
[Music]
[Laughter]
no okay
[Music]
i saw
hey happy april fool's chat
oh yeah happy birthday
everybody
crazy mother f word
you guys are nutty and so we're out my
forehead
oh
project on her own oh emma you gotta do
some jumping
[Music]
oh dear i think you have another 10
coming
okay keep going
1.
[Music]
i'll never be a cat
i want to she wants
to be honest next time we get amelia
jumping jacks i should be good at doing
them because she's dressed up as alma
what i can't hear you i have feet for
hands
oh dear oh no no i appear to have feet
for hands this whole
unfortunately that was cute
i want the cat yes i never get them this
game is rigged this game is [\h__\h]
great it's a game of chance
with slightly larger chance for feet
hands that's all
all right
um
you're watching you're watching
[Music]
that's on your
holy cow is that a backflip now you're
focusing on me
no i'm not bad
i wish i could give them to you i'm
sorry i want to become
sorry
[Music]
well we could spin the wheel all day but
if you guys are ready
ready to wrap it up then uh you're
probably gonna see it
i stole your spank
oh amelia nicole right here right here
where are you amelia
come give us a video
[Music]
[Laughter]
you'll get it you'll get it
this is the spin this is the one i know
this is the one this is the there's the
one this the one this the one this the
one this the one crashed oh i'm begging
no oh welcome back
all right just don't give up don't give
up don't give up
will kiara ever get to see
herself with cat ears in the guru's void
[Music]
we may have to find out next time
uh you just can just do the ending and
i'll i'll try to do it while it's ending
uh well everybody uh thank you
thank you for coming to
thank you for coming to miss uh second
april fool's dream
i hope
i hope you enjoyed yourselves
[Laughter]
we will see you all again
real soon
maybe a kawaii or maybe talking ashikya
will when they get her cat ears but
until then it doesn't look like it
alright guys uh
thank you so much everybody uh
thank you to everybody who helped out uh
make this stream what it is including
all the myth girls uh
uh
anything else anybody has to say other
than goodbye
my birthday's in a couple days and i'm
doing a 3d concert feel free to come
it's free and i'm announcing the biggest
announcement of my career so please come
if you would like to see sounds pretty
maybe some
yeah maybe some en friends may make an
appearance uh to participate in a fun
little game oh so um please come check
it out
[Music]
anybody else
all right everybody
thank you again
we will see you guys
later thank you for watching bye
everyone goodbye everybody see you later
bye
goodbye
[Music]
this program was made possible by
contributions to guru from viewers like
you
thank you