[Music]
I'm going to restart my see really quick
because my capture card is trying to gas
light
me which just
thinking saying it should be connected
to a 3.0 USB which it is but it acts
like it's
not but it
[Music]
is so stream will be down for a few
seconds
[Music]
are we
back it's still
saying connect to 3.0
USB but it's like where it always is on
a 3.0
[Music]
USB
I I did try different ones and it is a
blue there I tried two different blue
USB ports far as I know blue USB ports
are
3.0 of course I tried
it I don't know I always already tried
so many
[Music]
things
oh I think it
[Music]
works ah it
worked had to crawl to the back of the
[Music]
PC okay okay
okay got a little bit
electrocutor
[Music]
no but like I don't understand the front
one here one second FR
ones
[Music]
yo
hi yo sorry for the wait the like the my
my game capture card was always for
months it was connected to the front or
like more like the top um
USBS and no some I guess sometimes they
work and sometimes they don't but look
at me I look cute oh my
God I'm ready to
snowboard yeah I I tried this with
different outfits it only works really
with an outfit where I can put my arms
up because of my right arm I mean if I
go like this obviously it's not
connected anymore but like this it's
kind of
fun
yay yeah it kind of works cuz I mean the
dandel also rep represents the
mountains yeah you just have to deal
with it that my face is a little bit
covered and I can hide behind it
peekaboo
peekabo
[Music]
peeka also I have a headache
again uh all day I might as well take a
painkiller
but I don't know it's probably not going
to be a long stream like what can you do
snowboard a little bit and
then
uh it's still there it's such a weird
headache no I not I don't know what Adil
is this is this is EO profan IBO profan
yes something like
[Music]
that eight hours of snowboarding N I
doubt
it I am excited to go snowboarding uh a
little bit I I hope it's going to be
fun getting visions of snowboarding dle
versus this meow skateboarding nun memes
oh yeah somebody can draw
that chunky wonky did you hear chuny
wonky yes me lady oh it turned itself
off again come back I'm going to be
using um my
gifted Panda controller not my uh Pro
Controller
because um of reasons because of reasons
exactly that is
why what
can you hear this it's pretty loud I
think uh for you
guys there you go yo look at I I I
really wanted to I I'm going to probably
be doing more of these streams in the
future because I want to play these
games that are on here I want to play
Yoshi's story I want to play
this maybe Star Fox maybe we can have
like these all as like one off one
stream only games how about
that one game per
stream you have permit for all those
well it's Nintendo I think the only one
that might be difficult is the Pokémon
games but we have kind of like blanket
PRS so should we play excite bike 64 as
well
sometime I really want to play Pokemon
Stadium though I got I'm going to check
maybe there's different rule for the
ones that are on on here m golden eye I
don't know about Golden Eye I wouldn't
be interested in it anyway also I want
to play the old Mario Kart and I want to
play the old Mario Party oh there's
Paper Mario too and Tennis I know that
the tennis one you can play online right
like a couple of these you can play
online right not even couch Co-op but
like actually
online Dr
Mario so o Ma's mask I I want to play my
Jo's
mask this is so blessed like there's
actually like such a good like choice of
games but we today we are going to play
1080s
snowboarding that was originally
released many many years ago for
Nintendo
64 and I
wonder is this what I was looking
for because there is a a
suspicion
[Music]
who 10 stop bu oh I think the sound is a
little bit iy go is
it should be fine now
oh no that I think I played this
like cuz I'm not sure did I play the
GameCube one or did I play the Nintendo
64 one but this feels very familiar to
me too maybe I played
both
a let's
go what the audio is so bad I can't
understand what he's
saying okay
oh we can play English or
[Music]
Japanese I'll turn it down a little bit
for for
me Nostalgia hits hard let's go what is
this match race time attack trick attack
contest two oh wait does this have on N
it's Sur only couch Co-op
right there's no way that there's online
co-op right for this no way
is
there audio crackling really I I don't
hear it I think I feel like I fixed
it there there was no I mean yeah back
then of course not but some of these 64
games now have online
co wait I need to I need to
check ah no that looks like
couch
[Laughter]
what okay I guess maybe we can play this
with like waya or narissa since they're
visiting me
soon we can try all kinds of couch Coop
games like from here that would be funny
okay so I don't know I might just going
to go for match race match a select
level normal I guess cuz I never I mean
I played it before I think but like I
would say now it's pretty much I can say
I never played it before cuz it's been
too long I don't remember playing this
so well oh know the controls work your
body select rer they don't even say the
names do they have different
stats let's go for the
girl oh it's a Japanese girl akar haami
oh they our stats technique Bal balance
is very good power is not so good
work your body work your body Ricky
winterhorn he's from Canada but he has a
German name
vorn work bu well I guess actually could
be English too winter horn winter horn
it's the same in German
actually W Bud W Budd I highly recommend
you play AK oh is she actually good
for the crackling is killing like are
you sure
wait I don't hear it what about what
about now
guys I hear fire
crackling that's
it now it's good no okay okay okay
different wrong audio stor okay okay
Balance power jump oh technique and
jump it's full with this guy
Ricky kiky
Ricky k Kimi
Kimi k k is like yeah not really like
perfect at anything he doesn't excel at
anything but he's like mid at everything
he's not bad either maximum speed oh
Dion
Blaster cuz he blasts through the snow
like no one else she what's up what's up
Rob Haywood has has also pretty good
speed actually like everything is pretty
good with him too hi but yeah we'll go
with the girl even though she seems kind
of
mid oh we can change the board too is
there one that looks like
mine uh that's pretty blue it looks like
a way
board what about a Ouija board why are
they all
blue okay these these ones are not so
blue okay then I look at the stats oh
wait took this is
n okay let's look at the stats oh
acceleration
[Music]
respawns oh this one's
bad
man is there like a meta board this one
this one looks good as
[\h__\h] Luigi board
yes where is the Luigi board what why is
this one so
shitty like why would anyone use this
one push it
in work your body work your body work
your body work your body will work your
body
hey oh you think it balances out the ah
Moy hi Moy let's go
snowboarding oh what is this regular
goofy what do you mean what do you mean
goofy is the Dan like if you stand on
that side does that mean you're a goofy
one work your work
your are they saying like this is for
left-handed people and they're all goofy
eh what do you mean what do you mean
what are you trying to say huh welcome
I'm regular okay aari hayami versus Rob
Haywood aari hayami hey you didn't even
say it so bad how you didn't even you
didn't even tell me the controls o was
that a jump okay that's jump okay a is
Jump how do I do anything at all can
I how do I do I can I do a
trick what I wasn't explain
anything I like I like it I like Rock
Your Baby woohoo yeah this feels like
the the scenery is really familiar to me
y out how how do I how do I go do curves
w w I did a flip somehow or can I go
over the
[Music]
houses
no come on come on get over there too
bad I died I
died I died I had an accident this is so
traumatic for me
husw I [\h__\h] died
let's go can I do like in Mario Kart can
I like get a like a quick start like a
charge
[Applause]
woohoo I think he kind of bonked himself
too
[Applause]
no okay let's try to do what he
does I like I like I like that woohoo no
no I can't see him
anymore come back
me my biggest rival my snowboarding
rival my Nemesis ah oh [\h__\h] this is my
Nemesis the walls are my Nemesis oh what
what do I actually have to jump can I
just let myself
fall ooh the controls are I mean not so
bad I guess curvs is just we we
[Music]
we but can I what do you call it again
in with the cars when you do a curve and
it goes
like you
know wow smoth this comfy yeah Dorito
can I
Dorito oh oh [\h__\h] out oh no no
no last jump a big one right into the
ocean let's go oh there's another one
yeah no I died
again
no
ambulance ambulance I need an
ambulance robwood how do I land
better I got to lean forward like can I
even are you talking like RL
snowboarding to me or what I'll [\h__\h] oh
good yo I wrecked
him how do
I maybe we have to tackle him again
I maybe that's the only way to win kill
the
opponent oh he did some wait how do I
how do I do that
again come about that these curbs
are oh he fell me too let's
go how did I do the thing again oh I
have a back camera means I have eye eyes
in my back head oh oh wait this what is
this this that's that's a increasing
speed I guess should I press that also
when I
land use your turtle shot I actually
[Music]
check oh what how did I how did I not
crash here oh my god let's go I can do
it I can
[Music]
survive yo okay I think pressing that
this button helps actually the what is
it
ZL I think it
helps I lose yeah but at least I didn't
die game game
over well why don't we race the other
ones and then see how it
goes what this music is so Super Mario
64 is and this menu gives me those vibes
to
[Laughter]
why is this music so Super Mario 64 is z
l crouches yeah yeah so I guess that's
what I'm supposed to do to either get
speed or when I land I guess I do like
if I think about snowboarders when they
jump like that I do think they Crouch
when they land yeah so
what wait I get free
letters there's free
spaces that's all I get for my name what
if I have more than free spaces now what
I can do though is I can name myself
kfp free
spaces uh my name is uh uh my name is my
name is
kfp so that was a game over and I go
back to the main menu
okay bud I don't think we're ready for
hard or expert courses let's
continue maybe may even with a different
Rider maybe that was the issue you
know maybe we need someone with higher
speed yeah like you k k come let's just
give it a try with
you
acceleration yeah let's use the Taho
155 welcome are there any people in the
chat who can
snowb
ayami I only
go I only know how to ski but even that
is kind of iffy woohoo ow why did I fall
maybe I shouldn't press it all the time
that
ow
wait is the red the the HP I have left
or is the green the HP I have
left I'm so
fast don't randomly I wasn't
[\h__\h] okay I think green is the HP I have
left no
[Music]
what hard to get good
guys how do I get good my speed is
impeccable
w must be
[Music]
away oh no
oh no no no no no no no why why why
[Music]
oh why does he not jump anymore like a
doesn't work as a jumping button
[Music]
anymore didn't even go over the
Finishing Line why did I lose again why
are why is it so difficult
oh byebye M oh wait I get another try
nice oh I'm against the girl all right
all right I'll show her who the boss
is oh oh
what why why I was crouching there's a
training
mode
really I like I like boom it goes
boom I like that [\h__\h] I like that [\h__\h]
is that what they're
saying Beyonce Mariah
K it goes
boom nice curves I mean at least my
curves are pretty nice I would
say just what what I don't
understand I I can't lean back there's
only like this
crouching more or less crouching I ohou
okay let me see is there something else
ah huh how did I how did I switch just
now it's okay just killed me
[Music]
already and a big jump hey nice landing
and a big no jump okay but we still
landed oh
and yeah oh okay maybe we're getting
better maybe it's really just like the
timing of
certain pushes of the buttons need to
beim we get another try ready let's go
let's go let's
go increase
speed oh oh that was
[Music]
close Ram her Ram
her oh we pass
her oh
[\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh be careful boy no she
still again [\h__\h] [\h__\h] get out of
[Music]
here I didn't know what I
forgot W oh
a oh what you going to do what you going
to do when K comes for you bat girl bad
girl what you going to do what you going
to do when Kare comes for you hey
hey oh kind of really [\h__\h] slow right
now we need more
speed go straight go
straight woo oo oh okay this could [\h__\h]
me up
completely
why the [\h__\h] did I not
jump why why you know jumpy but at least
you know
crashy oh
[Music]
God I really messed up at the very end
oh my God
yo uh maybe you can't jump while
crouching yeah I'm guessing you have to
jump first and then Crouch when you're
in the air again yes k
Kim yo welcome to Crystal
Peak go oh that's the Speedy boy isn't
he something about him no uh his
something about burst or what was it he
said he's bursting through the snow or
so oh
oh I see I follow you my friend how do
you do that
how does he do the cool tricks tell me
why is he flexing so
hard oh I'm I'm catching up though we're
on par
now
[\h__\h] that's what I get for bumping into
him from behind oh [\h__\h] no what are you
doing what are you what are you doing
little
[\h__\h] see I remember this part I feel
like I remember these
Maps I at this this right side yeah yeah
yeah
yeah I feel like I remember these things
why is there a reflection of
myself oh what the
[\h__\h] where is the guy no he's so far I
can't see him I'm going to
lose ooh these
bumpy oh no what the
[\h__\h] yo yo yo oh no crash no crash
wa and almost to
goal can we do a good jump no what is
the
timing oh ow [\h__\h] oh nice nice
recovery okay nice try nice try I think
I agree age with
that shredding some powder baby let me
try
again look at him look at my look at the
the polygons on
him the minimum po
polygons I didn't die yeah I made it to
the goal and that is a big
accomplishment yo let me let me go next
so is there really a training
it yeah there is I'm
blind work your body work your body work
your body work your body work your
body yeah fine with the same
things will they actually teach me
something or o half pipe or free let's
go
halfpipe follow me guys what is
melancholy is that the name of the song
oh look wait what's this trick list what
do you
mean
oh oh they want me to do a a trick
that's called Melancholy well how do I
how how though
how how do I look at
it okay
ah
o
huh
huh I don't think uh wait is that
supposed to be a be it's a be right and
then the joystick to the
left that's what I'm doing I have to
jump too oh what
not enough speed
probably speed speed speed speed speed
speed wait I'm supposed to jump on the
half PL right what the
[\h__\h] I don't know
how e it's
over I need more I didn't get to do
anything but I did learn something I
[Music]
think ready not a hold not a hold do
what about free does free just have
nothing just a normal round I need some
ah yeah okay this is what I need let's
do this and
jump
oh I don't agree I don't think I did it
cuz I'm not seeing
anything also no no
speed where is the
speed method
not
oh
stalefish 180 air R and to the
right 18 oh
she I'm jumping to
late oh wait I see so
off like it takes quite a while for him
to take off after I activated it
oh0
oh let's do a
360 360 oh
noo 360 yo I I pressed it I'm not
holding it and he's still doing it
though what if I hold it but if I hold
it he just kind of
stays doesn't really feel like he's
jumping this is I think the right way
360 what else do we have oh what oh we
go so far to get to
360 wait no what how did
what 36 what I don't understand what how
can I do that I end with to the left
or ready
go I need more momentum I guess so yeah
I don't have time to do all of
that 180 no that was a 5
40 I
swear let's get some come
on 360 oh [\h__\h]
wait
next one next
One
360 ah
[Music]
[\h__\h]
360 I can't get any higher press Crouch
right again before you land okay
okay
do
360 there's not enough time I barely can
get
momentum and
jump oh okay if I keep on crouching he
doesn't do it okay okay okay okay hello
hello
360 I can't I did go back to crouching
though 180 180 2
180s that makes
360 they don't math right now the math
don't be
mapping ready hold jump and release and
jump
higher okay I
try let's go let's
go you release
one it's R got I already landed how do
you do hello
helloo 180
360 180 plus 360 I think it's 540
okay 360 I really don't understand this
this combination can we go on to 720
maybe oh uh one full like two two full
circles and then a
be oh wait
wrong no wrong
joystick I'm too bad at this I
can't who
who
what h
ah no no oh no
no
what no wait I forgot I forgot I forgot
one important thing okay this this is so
overwhelming to me right now I'm Tony
Hawk yeah but in the snow and Tony Hawk
in the winter uh R and the circle circle
B but still keep are going
right
uh
uh no
what
[Music]
360 180
360 yeah now I pressed it
twice
[Music]
M
360 I don't get
it how about trying The Baby Steps
first wait well baby steps well which
ones
M okay well let's go let's try to go
from the top how to do a
Melancholy easy oh
Melancholy yeah I did it now can go next
now
method
uh uh wait uh right and B
okay wait I forgot to jump
too yay I did that before anyway I know
how to do it
no I can't stick The Landing even though
I go back to
crouching only use those easy tricks 90%
of the time really okay maybe we don't
need to go like until 1080
degrees let's go to the
Indie right side and B okay e easy g
g looking good no
scrap no SC y
woohoo a t grab
sick wow who's like the Tony Hawk of
snowboarding [\h__\h]
stiffy oh oh oh and a mute grab oh she's
on the
roll MB mute
grab stalish
I can do that too no that was a sailfish
wrong you don't get
it sish selfish Indy nose bone funny
names man
indone sea white oh I feel like maybe I
heard that
before okay The Landing probably is so
bad because I have no
speed ah okay I think it only moved on
when I actually did it without
crashing
oh
180 ah [\h__\h] dude dude you crashed Wawa
we won't count that
one I don't know what the [\h__\h] that
was I mean I don't know it personally of
course
not go a very decorated Olympian
decorated
huh
decorated I'm thinking I'm trying to
think of a a joke here
but 180 no
why no no no
speed
18 okay okay okay that was uh good
enough it seems
even though I didn't even
jump
18 oh I did it
again and I did ah I did it again but
the landing I know I can do it I just
got to believe in
myself and believe in the snow the god
of snow oh
ow here we go 360
no why okay you guys have to explain to
me there was speed there was
height what's the
problem what if I don't jump well I
didn't really count it's a good jump
tried jumping
earlier
360 I I mean maybe I should maybe I try
about crouching at the end cuz so far
I've always been crouching at the
end
ready who
tilted right before the you landed as
the trick
finished oh so I'm too late with my
trick
[Music]
360 what I finished all that ready I was
done I can't Lean
Forward not to my knowledge
what 36 now I did it really late I can't
do it much earlier than
that 36 well now it only worked because
I was like so close to the snow to the
ground cuz I jumped so early 3 see that
there basically was
no I was not even in the
Air
180 wait what do ah they want uh ah they
want the 360 the other way around okay
cuz now I always go to the right no I go
to the right right
go no I'm moving the joystick it doesn't
go back or forward right now I'm going
back now I'm going
forward well okay maybe a little bit
360 oh okay we're back to the
540 360 uh but I don't understand do I
have to like let go of r
or
[Music]
364 it seems like I kind of did
it I mean I did even more than that
apparently
360 I don't know how I'm
cooking cooking this
snow
36540 ah no why must I crash no come
on go go go go 360 no no no no I don't
need ah wait did it switch to the other
side or is it still the same as before I
think it is still the same
so what is it
3640 no it did switch cuz wasn't it
first to the left side ending it on the
left
side it did it did make progress right
progress
[Music]
ch
hello hello
[Music]
questionable do I go
again6 okay I do think I have to let go
oh it accepted that even though I
crashed seems like I have to let go of
the r once and there like two completely
different inputs
basically
360 no wait uh b b after or while doing
all of that what do you
think
360 how
do
360 to together with the second AR yeah
I'm trying that exactly that
360 but it doesn't take
it no it's already the end make this
endless give me an endless Mountain that
never
stops the dream of a snowboarder
go even I had trouble with it see it's
not just
[Music]
me
[\h__\h] try figuring out how to land I
don't know sometimes it works sometimes
it doesn't with these bigger jumps
360 I don't even know what we figure it
out
he saying I'm on my
[Music]
own 180
36 oh
to I landed but I lost a lot of speed
to
360 now I didn't land
now
huh that was a new combination at
least we like to see
the
180 he's going to have so many
concussions after this sorry K
skin 36
540 I mean 360 and 540 is like 1,000
okay
hellooo how do you
do that hurt can you get your [\h__\h]
together
now should we try these other things for
now because I I I can't get those
stupid flips right oh oh they won't let
me oh 1080 a do I have to finish that
one until I get to do the more fancy
flips do I have to ready what if I
already know how to do it what if I look
up the combination
H where we got
to we got to do
this 36 by
40 no idea guys no
idea
360 are the others for the pipe track
oh I feel like you should be able to do
flips here too
36 you need to line up your board
perfectly I mean now it was in the
middle at the end and I still crash does
it have to be like side
[Music]
was taking a nose
dive okay I'll
go okay wait I see I see I see I see I
can't really Lean Forward while I'm
boarding on the snow but when I'm in the
air not a hold wait
oh wait wait ah wait [\h__\h] I missed it
again we're getting there boys and
girls
ready go how what do you say like you
first have to crash in order to fly or
something like
that literally quite
literally
okay let's
land whoa I thought that would be too
much okay let's com combine that with a
jump
360 no that's me what do you mean why
was that not
good 180
oh wait I don't know what what that was
supposed to be
she
[Music]
jumping oh
[\h__\h] too
ambitious
no 180 no uh after the 180 360s Landing
still is kind of difficult
180 that was only because I was so close
to the snow
[Music]
oh
360 oh
I am the master of the snow I am the one
who controls the
snow the snow is my land the snow is my
country the snow is my homeland the snow
is
my my my
bed my domain
3 oh never mind it isn't it isn't it
hates me it's my hell it's my personal
hell my jail cell this is how I do my
flips
since the game won't let
me 360 no why I was doing perfect
Landings
before 360
okay think it's got to just be really
fast inputs oh oh so fast it wasn't
registered
360 no at least the jump wasn't uh the
the crash wasn't too bad
[Music]
oh did he say y baby y baby like s o
nice
landing release the jump when you hit
the solid red
no which one was that mean solid red oh
oh nice
save0 wait is there another one no
that's
[Music]
it the end
end ready
go
okay it's all about practice guys you
got to get good
360 I don't get it I'm leaning forward
but like there's not even like the
animation like immediately
Landing
[Music]
360 maybe that's I landed on this fluffy
snow
ow get go upwards go upwards fight the
fight the hill fight the mountain you're
the master of your own Mountain
I want more
speed
360 I hate
myself here I go again Channel y
Mario yo no this time I had at least
some time
but
360 what do you mean what do you mean
what do you mean that's not good enough
for
you in a race you don't want to do
tricks right anyway so
ready go but I want to stick the [\h__\h]
Landing
anyway although in the race that we we
had some of the NPCs did do tricks a
little
bit let me get absolute
speed
nand
360 I can't do it maybe with a different
board I I don't know maybe it flips
better
18 even with the 180s now I can't do
it
oh yeah that's for the 180 for the one
80 I have more time in the air
360 I don't
know I'll just um go racing
now
ready you used to play the girl it's
kind of easier really
yeah can I oh no it just restarts
here let me quit
we can try switching to the girl and see
if it's really like very
different no no no not trick
it no
no
sorry this triggers memories I'm happy
to hear that those are good memories
right work your body work your body work
your body work your body work your body
now that I know you know what my problem
is maybe we can choose a suitable board
edge control
response Flex for maximum
Flex I mean that is still like a great
allrounder
though I mean there's nothing wrong with
this board
[Music]
honestly maybe I should be going goofy
stance ready maybe that's my issue so
she's wearing orange and yellow she's a
[Music]
chicken oh I just Dy from the
list wait what about
tweak
okay let's go back to the
360 it doesn't feel different at
all ow ow ow ow ow ow
[Music]
ow
I'm leaning as much as I
can oh now she didn't
need
180o hello
[Music]
360 I mean but if you look at the
difference between 180 and the 360 you
see for the 180 I at least get some time
to lean for the 360 most of the time
there's not even that like freedom of me
to move around you know what I
mean
cuz she's still in the like default
position
[Music]
180 late as [\h__\h] why did you not
recognize the first one
H hello hello how
okay I guess we're not doing it
again
180 can we just say [\h__\h] the jumps and
uh just go
racing
36 she really just won't do
it
[Music]
360 last one last
try
[Music]
360 I don't need a to do tricks
ready 180 I 1080 I wish I could do it I
wish I
[Music]
could let's
go let's get those courses done I don't
really care because I didn't feel a
difference but we can go
no I want someone
faster who's the fastest among you guys
yeah it's you Dion Blaster there that's
that's the name
yeah Dion Blaster welcome blasting
through the snow on the 1080
snowboard can't do 1080
ready go but that's not what I need
anyway let's go we're going for the win
[Music]
ow okay no tricks no tricks Wawa you
don't need
tricks assert
dominance
oo I'm coming for you
buddy what is that is that can SC whoa
oh stop showing
off is there such a thing as being too
fast ow ah oh maybe there
[Music]
is
now I'm I'm I'm gaining control over
[Music]
him St to get to know him we we're still
strangers you
know oh almost
[Music]
stumbled
oh oh he crashed this my CH ah this my
chance this my chance this my chance
come
on no what I died no no I wasn't done
yet why is my career already over didn't
even get started Blaster versus kuk
kimachi okay kuk ready I'll show you how
serious I can get
okay
mhm yeah you see that Landing
sick oh look how secure I am on this
board it's like I hot glued my shoes on
the board yeah yeah yeah not that that
would be any secure any more secure than
the
traditional ways of No you little [\h__\h]
get out of
here this is my mountain mountain
WWA oh [\h__\h] hell the speed is insane
actually no I can't let him win no no
crash crash crash break your bones I
don't give a
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
off trying to give me Mario Kart Vibes
here
no I think this dude might actually be
too fast it's actually insane let's see
maybe the NPC will crash
again maybe maybe maybe maybe maybe
maybe we can still do this if we speed
up no
[Music]
no the red shell no I want to send him
over a blue shell Red Shell is not good
enough for the damage I want to do to
his
spine I
[Music]
no I want it to be cool no there the
there goes the
boom no can I
restart what why do I have to register
this I don't want to register
thaton Blaster verus kimachi
ready
go
I no
no the snow has been manipulated I think
somebody put some [\h__\h] in the
[Music]
snow it's trying to kill
me it's too slippery it's too wobbly
it's wobbly snow made from wobbly
[Music]
water
waa that was big that was big what and
dare I Stumble
[Music]
really
beon mustard Dion was his name was
it I
like I like that thing
I like
that this is
[Music]
unbelievable maybe I should change
characters after all maybe this was too
ambitious oh he's kind of waiting at the
oh no he's not he's not like you guys
gentleman enough to wait for me at the
Finishing
Line
Dion Blaster versus kuk kimachi not
ready no not ready okay I guess we keep
on going forever forever and ever why
why I'm angled downwards what more do
you
want see this time was
nice my board blends with the
snow it's like I don't even have a board
it's just me my
fees I don't need a
[Music]
board my feet are the
boys yeah yeah wo w w w wo wo
wo parallel to the ground yeah yeah yeah
I get it I get it I mean kind of hard to
tell
sometimes
okay let's go a bit faster if this
really accelerate anything I don't know
[\h__\h]
no can we get a good jump do we get get
any speed out of
jumps she's right there no wait for me
you
bastard you want to be my
board the kiky keyboard
well I don't know I'm quite happy with
my my board this one's honestly the
design is so
adorable if only I would have been
taught snowboarding from like my
childhood on but I only was ever taught
skiing
ready
[Music]
go oh oh oh oh oh he he crashed to
though
[Music]
I want to see him crash
again oh he does like cool
switches why like what what and oh even
now he did a a
trick in what kind of situation would
you want to do
this does does that help me somewhere
[Music]
somehow I learned nobody before skiing
but enjoyed skiing
more shut
up I used to enjoy skiing until I had
that
accident that
was really [\h__\h]
scary I'm going to switch
again
to my old
rounder accident yeah you don't know the
story
accident
ready go that's Noah
[\h__\h] oh are we up against the
girl
woo
oh look at me go
OU look at my style points I'm still
behind her what the
hell let's copy copy what she
does okay at least we landed no no no I
was about to what is she doing she's
going over the houses is that a
[Music]
shortcut o
o okay we still have a
chance
maybe please
no this woman where is she I see her on
the map but I got
distracted
oh what was that what was she
doing what's she
doing
nice
huh she was like doesn't even even look
like she was moving she was just jumping
around winter she was blocking
me go unfair jery are you L you watching
this oh
don't go there don't go there she
doesn't do it
either probably not worth
[Music]
it [\h__\h]
man
no it's over it's so over
guys oh maybe I should have wait this
time she went
[Music]
left seems to have forgotten about her
shortcut yeah this is a pretty bad
[Music]
run what how did I recover from that so
well
can never give up she might still be
jumping on the
platform for style
points n
oh it's so close though it's so close I
feel like we can do it we
can
kimick is there course selection I
haven't seen one I wish I could select
it I want to see like what courses they
have maybe some are more familiar to me
I like I oh I'm I'm in front of her
now hey you will not pass this
boy you shall not
pass says
gundo oh God oh God oh God oh God oh God
oh
God
no no w
oh we keep on bump oh nice nice nice
they keep on bumping into each other
this
[Music]
time still behind me careful wa be
careful don't let her get to you
mentally or
physically she's still behind me no no
yeah that was on
purpose let's go let's go let's go
either you die or I win or both I don't
know ideally
both and here we go wa win wa
win do what I never managed as a kid I
do it for you I win for you you the
reason why I keep on
going that was ruthless right it was
violence maybe that's what we needed all
along
violence maybe snowboarding is all about
violence oh I like this
[Music]
snowstorm nice landing still kind of
feels like it slows me
down
what oh
oh nice nice nice curve nice move
curve no that was oh but we keep on
spittering sliding for the
mountain
no [\h__\h] it could have like been a road
block for him so close so close so close
oh he goes to the right side I barely
can but that's okay that's okay
oh what the [\h__\h] is that what are those
lines those L squiggle
lines oh but we're still kind of on the
same look I'm I'm first still am I
[Music]
not no no die
die
die die die why want you die yo this
track is so difficult oh my
God Nintendo 64 [\h__\h] yeah I'm already
losing it's okay it's
okay oh the ending is kind of the same
here H almost there's a like okay couple
more ramps never mind maybe he uses them
and
dies
what what the [\h__\h] was
a no I put the one no now if you lose
the second one you have to redo the
first one again don't
you why do I get to redo the first one
so many times not the second
one it's okay I'll continue working my
body right before the Finish Line what a
way to die man
ready go
why does he get a way faster start
H what okay get out of here you get out
of
here I felt insulted by
him just by him standing next or
boarding Next to
[Music]
Me Maybe This is like oh
Get Wrecked maybe this is like therapy
for me to feel safer in the snow in the
future get riged die die eat the
snow that I peed
in hope you like
it like these curves like IRL I would be
way too scared to make curves like that
but it's so smooth right
now no no no no no no no no no no no no
no ow
no no
no what the controls are off I I
swear he's still
[Music]
there I wasn't throwing I swear
I wasn't trying
to
ready go [\h__\h] talk man he didn't help
after
all you know guys I I've seen this like
crazy uh like video story I'll tell I'll
share it with you now it's about
snowboarding maybe you guys have heard
the story
too you know people who snowboard for
like not
like actual courses that people planned
out where they you know make the snow
flat like here and take care of the
course some people they snowboard
through like more like the the
Wilderness the wild
snow yeah and I heard the story where a
guy snowboards through like these
there's like a lot of trees like a lot
of thick tree tree fckery mhm I'm going
to win I'm going to win going to win and
suddenly he
notices like the whole snow like
everything is like really really really
fluffy and big and like there's no flat
snow what I mean
okay yeah people die in Avalanches there
like so he finds someone who's like he
finds skis that are like it looks like
they're sticking out of the ground and
then realizes oh my God there's a person
there so he stops and he makes his way
higher up and there's a video of
this you see it he makes his way up go
to him and then like dicks him out but
it's like it I can't say in inches or so
I don't know
but like insane amounts of snow like
he's really really deep in it takes him
a while to actually get him out of
there is actually terrifying like he was
just snowboarding and
suddenly he's stuck in the
snow and about to die but this guy
randomly finds him like the chance of
him finding him in the first place is
like really
low but can you
imagine the relief of that person who's
been stuck in the snow and ready to die
and then somebody digs you out somebody
finds you randomly and digs you out and
then they're like oh are you okay it's
like yeah I'm okay
sorry just take your time I guess like
he was really chill about it seems like
it yeah he was alive he saved him if
that guy wouldn't have found him we
would have died just just so happens
that that gu was
also
just actually like he wouldn't even have
normally gone that route I think he said
was like he separated with his own
friends a little
bit that wasn't the the normal path he
would have
[Music]
chosen damn
it
yeah really chill about
it ah
whatever nice
try snow is much more dangerous than
people realize for real yeah like that f
is so scary being stuck and he was like
head over like stuck with his feet
looking up and his head downwards like
literally doing a head stand
ready
go wa we get a second chance now is that
like a total amount of lives oh is it
the snowboards I have at the bottom of
the screen I don't
know why do we get a second try now I'm
confused and first and first I'm first
one thing that never happens in Mario
Kart only inated snowboarding that's the
only race where I ever get number one in
life o let's
go
[\h__\h] oh I think he also crashed I heard
it
nice oh I think I understand like this
side has eyes oh he also went this way y
it the [\h__\h] why did he not crash
[Music]
you will crash eventually oh this is
also this is also IC
see
icy there's a cap- up song that's called
icy oh [\h__\h] yo this part is so stupid I
hate that
[Music]
part can we gain some more speed if he
attempts to jumps
[\h__\h] I'm so done for if he attempts to
jumps and and and crashes and maybe
still chance but oh I feel like he oh
yo yo yo
y I saw the future I can tell the
future finally for the first time we're
going to the next
round I saw it coming he gave me an
opening the Golden Forest
oh oh nice
music oh [\h__\h] this is fast oh [\h__\h] okay
calm
down get behind me ah I slowed down why
too
[Music]
much
woo Banger music I love the sunset
too oh oh oh what the
way what okay this is the kind of place
where that guy was
stuck Head Over Heels
literally we're going left I join
[Music]
you I wouldn't be surprised if I lose
because it's my first time up
here oh oh oh no let's skip that let's
skip that I don't need that in my
life what what is this
what I know that like this like really
fluffy snow is not good for skiing or
snowboarding but I personally kind of
prefer it I feel like I have more
control in it which makes no sense to
people who actually ski really well like
they say mm-m n-oh I don't know I'm feel
like they they hold me back and they
have a firm cuddly grasp around me the
[Music]
s ah [\h__\h] and I can stop easier if I
want to
interesting I
lose look at
look
she changes into this like low polygon
model for some
reason I love that not bad but first try
yeah yeah
yeah it wasn't too bad yeah it's in some
parts that was really really
Speedy dangerously Speedy but almost
more manageable than the second course
in my
opinion where a reflective over
W ready uh to be found when I when I'm
like dying what do you
mean I mean I wouldn't try
to you're killing us get out of here I
wouldn't try to ski in like in between
those all those like trees and all that
I wouldn't dare to that's something that
crazy people do not me
[Music]
maybe we're lucky to have the lady as
our oppon opponent for this first one
because that could be a secure win
unless I Trumble over my body like
this still can do it she'll crash right
before my
eyes and she'll call me a witch because
I made it
happen but I'm just
God just God and I will I will get
Justice uh uh commit to one side yeah
okay and skip the
jump oh God this the snow is so
wobbly here we go here we go here we go
for the middle
and I don't know if she ever fell
but I recovered
yay yeah as everybody's
Koshi is proof that I am God
mhm is there an austring character by
the way I don't think I looked at all
the names there was a Canadian and
American and
Japanese two Japanese
actually where the where the
austrians or someone from Europe is
there anybody at all from Europe because
like I feel like like to make a game
about snow Sports winter
sports I got to be in it I mean not me
but like someone who represents
me there's a
British I need to play
them a British man yo okay okay I mean
that's at least closer to me than the
others I am after all almost
is listen to my
accent can you tell okay this this part
will probably [\h__\h] me
up oh God okay
okay nice curve
waa oh God ah but we have a good
Advantage like we're pretty far ahead of
him no
stress oh this
part
stick The Landings stick The Landings ah
I didn't stick the last one it's okay we
still have we're still we're still quite
far ahead okay okay okay okay okay wa
let's go
wa no no no no no no yo yo yo yo that
[\h__\h] yellow bar the wall the yellow
wall it gets me too often
okay I still win okay all right that so
far no losses I win and I win not even a
retry kuk kimachi verus Dion
Blaster was that the British guy oh oh
he heard me talking about
him that's a bit embarrassing oh what
the
[\h__\h] where' he go
already oh did he like jump over that
left side was there something where you
can go
over it's okay it's the it's the really
Speedy one on a on a really Speedy
course I feel like that will be the end
of
him no he's already so far ahead never
mind I got to I I'll be allowed to try
again right if I lose please
please
been going so smoothly so
far familiarizing myself with the
courses this song is in Smash
ultimate
what never heard of it I don't think I
heard it before is Smash Super Smash
Bros ultimate the one I also play
[Music]
I don't
believe no okay if I die I might not be
allowed to retry right so let's be
careful just stay alive ha ha oh my God
that's so fast
stay alive stay
alive do we got to retry Yi yes we do
okay so those snowboards on the bottom
those are my
lives n
hold oh god
[Music]
oh yeah he goes left there doesn't
here
oh there he is
yeah nice interesting Landing
nonetheless oh what the [\h__\h] the
trees how do you duck what let's go
let's go right side in the future that
didn't have that tree I think oh
[\h__\h] this one's so
tough
yep guys you know before the
stream I did it I melted the chocolate
the nou got chocolate and and uh
decorated the rest of my cookies with it
so I'm
excited to eat them I have them in the
fridge so maybe after the
stream they'll be dry so then I have
some sugar glazed ones and some
chocolate glazed
ones yeah but I had so much chocolate
left
over so I was like what the [\h__\h] do I do
with this I ended up uh making myself
hot chocolate which was kind of
mid cuz I guess the noua chocolate
doesn't really fit
Kim and and then I I made myself some
chocolate fruit I took one of the
tangerines and I dipped all the
pieces [\h__\h] oh this time he went right
side let's go left side
then no I dipped all the Tangerine
pieces oh oh
oh into the chocolate that was really
good though that was better than the the
hot
chocolate yo what the
[\h__\h] the those jumps over the trees
are kind of rough and I'm dying hey look
at my damage already uh wait right
side left side much shorter you mean in
the very beginning the left side or this
left side that I have where I chose the
right side just
now the problem is they have a tree
there that I have to crouch under and I
don't I don't know how to
duck cuz I'm a chicken
it
uhoh Wawa's death soon but don't worry
about me guys I can revive easily
[Music]
I mean I'm kind of getting better at
this course as
well am I
not oh look at all those Landings no no
no dying anymore oh
God yeah
yeah that's
okay the voice
over why did they have to make such a
weird
effect you duck by going quack quack
quack quack du
du
okay
um
well I don't know guys you want to see
more because it's already been 1 and a
half hours
and I don't know I'll try the tricks
really
[Music]
quickly do I 1080 I can't oh what I have
to do the tricks here on this
course I I forgot all the tricks
already
them what what what is this check time
extension oh what plus 20 seconds
why what time extension but I'm supposed
to do tricks right
180 yeah 180 that's almost a 1080
missing one zero and I mean a zero is
really nothing if you think about
it I tried to go over but doesn't
work
180 I'm just randomly pushing
things wait I can't do that that
that that train is so
narrow if you want to give me a course
for tricks then give me more
ramps ow at least I can die here
my 200 go what what what's wrong with it
time
extension that look at those oh it
doesn't count cuz ah I
see
what no
no [\h__\h] no it did count nothing
counts need to stick the
landing I think it should
count this is so sad no hey my score was
1,600 not
retry kuk kimachi kuk Kim
watching okay okay if I just don't have
too much
speed
okay here's a
chance
what even the panda controller won't
take my
input all the controllers hate
[Music]
meion oh oh ah ah ah no I can't that's
so difficult to get on the
train not with that speed man what if it
Go righted Side
here it's icy oo
interesting I think I saw a tree coming
from the right side oh no SC oh no no
scrap time extension why
why
no okay at least like this I I can get
some easy points out
man Improvement 300
points where was the trick wa where was
the
[Music]
trick yo 500 points yeah don't need a
ramp I can do tricks on my own nice try
I am the trick pony of
kfp
mhm I only played the GameCube one good
soundtrack yeah I think I played the
GameCube one too I feel like I don't
know both seem familiar to me so it's
hard I can change the course wait can we
see PE we had that one we're so
L ah no these are the training courses
wait this one let me try this one one is
that like a big ramp where I can do a
million tricks oh this is so scary this
is like one of the scariest Sports
it wait I didn't even get the jump
right wello this this this this this
ramp isn't even that big that's kind of
disappointing the ones they have in Offa
are
insane
no SC
me
no don't boo me you
suckers you try this you're probably
going to
die
Melancholy we should look our pictures
you don't know have you never seen those
big ski jumps oh hey I wanted to try it
again no no why why did you send me back
to I
press break my ankles i' break more than
just my
ankles okay here we
go I was doing things I was doing things
I
swear I don't know what that was work
your body will work your
body nailed
it here we go here we go here we go look
at
this what no I even land
it I never landed before this is what
this is what happens when I actually get
some more air
time
wao wo whoo wo this is my future okay
maybe you know there's so many different
ways of of you know skiing and
snowboarding and and you know different
you know different courses and all that
maybe snowboard jumping is where I
belong about 1080 I don't freaking know
I have to press the B button for that
one I don't know how to do
that here we go here we go here we
go nice TR shut up shut
up I don't I don't know there's ups and
there's Downs okay
it's a freaking roller coaster my life
my career is a roller
coaster what I for what why
I wiggle yeah wiggle wiggle
wiggle wiggle wiggle wiggle the INF
famous wiggle wiggle wiggle wobble
wiggle
huh
oh there we go I landed again y
wo that was a celebration
jump wiggle wiggle wiggle do you guys
know that K-Pop song that was like
popular many many years
ago they go like wiggle wiggle wiggle I
think wait how do
I nice try I I'm so consistent and
stable
wow you win some you lose
some that was wait no I think I'm
thinking of something I don't
know I'll look it up later for you
guys how wait how do you do things
again
no I'm pressing R I am I swear to God
believe
me kuk kimachi
go 180
360 ow a at least I remember it
now nice try I fixed
it I I know the Jason dulo won but oh
[\h__\h] I
canceled no I never win snowboarding
snowboarding is kind of scary to me as a
skier I mean my my snow transport method
of choice
ow would be
skiing or honestly
sleding I just want a
sled that's the safest maybe for
me but I always looked at the
snowboarders and thought they were the
Cool Kids on the
Block
hey what's going on what's going on can
we all just forget about all the all the
failed jumps and the only thing that
remains in history I will actually I
will cut the stream I will cut every
fail jump out I'll just keep the ones
stick to the landing and we will have a
5 minute stream how about that cuz I
can't take this I can't take this I'm
ashamed this is like ruining me and my
my my career as a Pro
Gamer and
snowboarder
360 it'll be a really short stream yeah
well well I want to show my chocolate
side as we say in
German I did land the 720 I have no idea
how I
did I have no
idea oh where's the jump where's the
jump where's the
jump little
be yeah it's the joycons they're they're
messing everything up
I am pressing ZL while Landing
360 what I'm leaning forward so much is
that too much what do you
want nice try shut up I don't need you
pity the lag yes the lag yes yes
yes k kimachi a our SE that's right our
separately true true true true
360 nice
try I had some cool moments
right right there were some cool moments
somewhere I'm done I'm done I'm done I'm
done I'm
done I
quit today my snowboarding career
started and today my snowboarding career
ended
no I'm satisfied oh what the [\h__\h] is
that helicopter
doing if there wasn't a
helicopter I know now why I was always
so so bad because the helicopter was
like getting in my way and and
disturbing the airflow around me look
how close that helicopter is imagine the
noise and the just the general
disruption like air particles snow
particles
everything it's not
natural it's not how it normally feels
like you
[Music]
know
what are they
saying
tarding let's
go yeah I don't know I was expecting
today to be a short stream anyway so
this is fine you know what I think I
have the right
attire go here no not
[Music]
here
here or
[Music]
here here's
fine where am
[Music]
I
let me adjust that a little
bit
okay I'm so hardcore I just snowboarded
up this mountain yeah I didn't
walk I snowboarded upwards yeah that's
how hardcore I
am
thank God I have this background this
snowy nice background I haven't used it
in a while so this is actually quite a
nice a nice
chance oh Felix na do did I write that
on
purpose Super Chat reading now
snowboarding career
ended it is what it
is I had fun though but yeah it's kind
of difficult uh to get good but you guys
also were like oh I could never do this
either blah blah blah so it wasn't just
me yeah it was for New Year's Shrine
visit like kind of that was the theme it
was from my kimono reveal originally
remember that's a long time ago my oh
that reminds
me they announced it right right yeah
they did yeah yeah with the Silhouettes
they showed that admin's getting their
kimonos right o I'm excited I saw them I
saw them all
[Music]
already I will not say anything but I'm
excited yeah ad Kim I'm
happy because at least the kimono with
the kimono will finally have like more
or less something
matching not just their default outfits
that probably don't really match much
well but with kimon if we do collabs we
can do matching kimon no anyway let me
turn this down it's freaking
loud but we can keep it running in the
background you have a favorite which one
is your
favorite
oh it's hard to say honestly
there are some that I didn't see the
final final
Final completed version yet I think and
just like uh almost final so I won't
judge it I'll tell you afterwards once
they all reveal it I don't want to I
don't want to say anything
now also I'm probably really biased
anyway uh yeah I guess from the the
Silhouettes you guys can already like
make some smaller judgments
mhm
yeah I thinking back about my kimono
that's so nostalgic I really I really
love this background and then I did this
little stream of the fortunes the New
Year's fortunes remember using the whole
Life Application that we
had getting some Callins and all that a
that was sweet back
then uh yeah I love monkey twin
Tails but I don't know there's like some
kind of like regretful feeling that I
have because I I originally wanted a
more like fantasy looking
kimono and I never got it so I don't
know I I still like it I think it's
still a nice kimono but it's just not
really what I wanted
so that's
probably like when I look at others
kimon no I I get a little bit
jelly yeah I wanted like burned edges I
wanted it to maybe have I don't know
feathers and and burnt edges something
more like fantasy looking like like
Callie's
kimono that one is good
that stream convinced me to join kfp
what really thank
you seems like a case of the grass is SC
maybe
but well
yeah but after that
I I I I Tred to be more how to say
not demanding but like when
I like I'm not the only one who who says
I want this and this and this you know
so it's fine to do that but I just
accepted it back
then and now I don't now I
don't I say what I want and it has to be
that like back then we got so many
outfits in like one year and now we only
get one a year which is totally fine
like making more than that was kind of
crazy anyway but now I get only one per
year so I want to make very sure that it
is exactly what I imagined it to
be oh ah it's the cobal thing already
over wait when did she do it did was it
like happening while I was
streaming I I recorded a little singing
for b ball the other
day for like a
k with uh with me and and Kobo and Kelly
one little
song it was last
night was it during the countown no wait
I feel like I saw the stream
reservation there there it is
oh it's already 13 hours ago she already
had two more streams since
then what the
hell right let me check I want to see
how it turned
out oh she's so cute wa she started
without a loading
screen oh I like this background what
the
[\h__\h] what he she's muted oh no she's
not
cute let me find the one okay first s
first
song she's so cute are we at the end or
something like that no where
here we sang her own song and she has a
full version of it now right so I was a
bit worried because I can only sing the
short version but it was fine we only
sang the short
version
let's somewhere here is it I think oh
okay here we go ah she's so cute oh
there I am oh Kelly send only vocals I
guess
y let's go Indonesian s
[Music]
she so cute and pretty is that
M it moves quite
[Music]
nicely
Callie sings it in such a cool
way guys she's holding the
mic her
expression why is she like that so
[Music]
cute
thank you for coming to my birthday he
yay yay
K's just so
quiet love you love you too
mommy oh that was so cute I feel like
normally like when Cali does these
things she also like she doesn't just
sing she like frows in some some chants
and all that but this time she didn't do
it I I did it thinking she would do it
as well now she's like like just there
as a picture and just like singing her
parts and very
seriously she gets angry at Kelly for
not saying anything if you keep watching
really
really oh yeah cuz the picture is still
there you're not going to say anything
to your
son she just looks at
her it's your it's my
birthday
no not even a word not even a word
brh brh for real
man she's so cute [\h__\h]
serious she's okay what
whatever bro yeah kick her out yeah kick
her out lame what the heck
man bye-bye dad next time I want come to
your birthday oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] wait what
did she sing of Nissa
yeah
oh wait is that plastic GL uh no
uh oh yeah it is
[Music]
right a I love I love The Vibes is this
really with mopi it doesn't look like
it's like spazzing out as much as uh
others when they use
mopi
interesting so cute wait I can't stop
saying it like she's so cute
like she's a perfect example of M of
what mum said about like cute
aggression I'm just playing games oh
know it's
plastic is isn't the buget the feature
so true I agree with that I love the the
weird spazzing out of
M it has its own charm for real for real
but it just doesn't really help me much
cuz I want to do dancing dance dance
dance did she get the suit that shall
not be I don't think so it's probably
just
[Music]
m this
song
[Music]
cute okay okay I should stop listening
to this sorry that was
curious H how I feel about Fu raing you
as naughty for Christmas uh it's kind of
rude cuz I'm even the one who gave them
the idea for the
video and I'm the one organizing the
calendar they put me in a
naugh at H talk I was just doing my job
I asked them the questions that I ask
everybody but it was funny to me cuz
like they I was the fourth one I think
they raided first uh they went for am
and and uh GDA and so on and then they
raided them all is nice and then I I was
thinking oh are they going like for like
just give everybody a nice because they
don't want to like be mean or something
and so I was like thinking I'm gonna get
a nice too because that's surely what
they're going for and then then they're
like yeah yeah I know what she's going
to get right yeah yeah 3 two 1 naughty
I'm like what the [\h__\h] what what do you
mean naughty what did I
do suddenly yeah when they get to me
they started giving out the naughties oh
really they also gave C gave C naughty
but honestly I was thinking like um
maybe it's because like I would say in
myth they're the closest to me and cie
so I think they just didn't want to like
they they how to say like maybe with
closer people even if they're senis it
would be forgivable to give them a
naughty so you know what I mean what I'm
trying to say like I see it as a
compliment because they feel safe enough
with me and cie to give us a naughty
nice cope shut up it's not a cope no no
no no yeah more comfortable to Bandit
with exactly exactly you don't want to
like you know get on the wrong side of
someone accidentally by making a jerk
which I don't think would happen but you
know just just I would probably be
careful too who I call naughty and who I
call
nice h
outstanding cope but also cope no no no
they like me they like me and that's why
they gave me a
naughty yes yes agree but it does sound
hey it's not a
c what's the video we're talking about
um uh this uh Advent calendar video from
last night holoen minus advent.com uh
check out all the day every day every
day until Christmas it's being updated
with videos from Whole Life English
members check it out check it
out we've had quite a big variety so
[Music]
far might be C but she speaks the
truth why is f there right well n also
has been in some
videos minus Adent but with Advent it's
math we're
mathing minus no don't worry they're
included I just want to keep the same um
URL I wanted to keep the same URL you
know so that nobody would steal it also
that's also a
concern we're missing a ton of short
videos yeah for real like some are not
even that short some are 10 minutes long
the that one was also 10 minutes The
Naughty Nice List and then uh our horon
with like uh narissa M and me was also
minutes somewh shorter somewh longer you
know like a good balance some are
shorter just because they make more
sense being shorter and I I told them
anyway like they don't have to be long
at all just little little nice itsy
bitsy tiny
snacks of nice funny um little videos to
you know be happy about you know cuz
like for a real for real Advent
calendars it's also not like like when
you open a door you get like a present
that's worth 5,000 bucks no usually
they're like really cheap you get pretty
shitty things out of Advent calendars
normally so I would say our Advent
calendar is already Superior by
default anyway let me get like a new
track from audio stock I want to get a
some some Christmas or winter themed
track that I haven't used
before h
F maybe F instead of
Christmas Lego Advent calendar is good
oh really I'm happy to hear that there's
a good one out there that's
good wait
I'm oh that's kind of nice oh
[Music]
it's kind of nice it's pretty up
beat I'll take it for
now looking for the loopable ones I
didn't write Loop let me write
loop it's a good
beat Padu p
[Music]
that's not
Christmas this is not for you Hip Hop
For You hip-hop
winter
kind of nice a slow
f
nice I'll take
[Music]
it I
like
I kind of like
it what's happening we're looking for
[Music]
bgm but not it is there even Christmas
and dad doesn't quite feel like
[Music]
it
cute oh this one's apparently kind of
sad well this RPG music
man could be in a tales off game maybe
Tales of
Symphonia puzzle game I don't know about
that although T off games have some
puzzles
[Music]
it's not very
Christmasy
[Music]
no
no cute RPG this one says RPG even
anyway let's go with the ones that I
already
downloaded we have this and we have this
by the way if you didn't see my Twitter
I announced the first guest of my uh uh
3D live concert that's happening this
Sunday it was Aki say bye yeah yeah yeah
yeah
yay yes I wonder what what song are we
doing with Aki
standby look forward to it please had a
lot of fun with her together and really
bonded with her again she's such a sweet
sweet I love her and the way her twin
Tails bounce is so
satisfying
yeah do you want the hip-hop one or the
more more upbeat
one sleep twerking
hip hop up be hipop hip hop okay okay
okay okay okay okay okay no more
snowboarding I'm going to read the super
chats like you have never seen before
I'm going to get them done oh oh she's
going to get them done oh oh let's go
Super Chat time Super Chat time he every
day is Super Chat the time she reads the
Reds she reads the pinkies and if she's
in a good mood she reads the rest as
well oh Super Chat time Super Chat time
we all want to be there when it is time
for the super chats he he
he I really want that chew what about
you are you going to get the chew it's
not about you it's about the WW tell me
more more tell me more tell me tangent
he he what up what up everybody Welcome
to the tangent time did I say tangent
time it is totally not it is super chat
time Super Chat
[Music]
time I'm
vibing K's been real quiet since this
dropped fire spitting bars what do we
got where where where where have we left
of do you know the number do I give you
my number no no what are you thinking he
he you must be sinking into the rabbit
hole oh
[\h__\h] and sleep talking I think sleep
talking super
chats need the rap Battle of
cie no I'm terrified she would destroy
[Music]
me you would make a great rapper back in
the 80s and '90s why why only the 80s
and ' 90s why not
[Music]
now thank you
guys I mean I just can't think think of
words that fast maybe in German I could
think of words faster
but yeah this way it's kind of difficult
I I like creating these different beats
and rhythms though oh Kelly also said
she's not good at improvising but I
don't know about that I feel like she
has a natural
Advantage sham you can do a med stream
for one you to select it before ah yeah
right
right there was a menu for that in the
very beginning before you choose the
game you can choose between single
player uh two players or which is couch
Co-op or
online true
o did you hear Raina rap to the ace
atoria music
no confess your eternal love to her in
the most aggressive sounding German so
she gets confused
honestly I could say anything in German
and all of you would be
confused a c freestyle Co-op not a
battle but freestyle with various F why
did you say
Co-op we're not talking about a game
right you're confusing
me P slaps
right it's quite nice but it might get
super repetitive let's start before it
gets repetitive Jacob 47 D sh your boy
Steven Adams to you as well D he says in
a red Super Chat the
following hey he hey I've just made it
back home to North Catalina North
Carolina from Fort Worth where had my
first time in a V panel in anime
Frontier I've got too excited that I was
screaming my lungs out and almost lost
my voice I enjoyed it though thank you
for your fun time
takamore big love
hug thank you oh North
Catalina is that a typo or does that
really exist North Catalina let me look
it
up north Catalina I guess oh is that a
Los Angeles I found an N Catalina which
I guess yeah like oh that is in Los
Angeles h
you legit have the voice don't
stop you guys are flattering me you're
going to give me an ego ego
boost you went from Los Angeles to Fort
wor that's that seems like it's really
really far did you go with an airplane
probably right I feel like I remember
some people saying they came
from uh from over there yeah so far
thank you for going such a long way to
see us at the panel screaming your lungs
out huh I'm so happy thank you I'm glad
you had a good time maybe maybe you did
went this far because takoni is worth it
right I would say so that was a great
panel I feel like both for both of us it
was great even though cie had to do it
at like 5:00 a.m. yo she did her
best a normal car trip for you as
Americans yeah yeah yeah I I feel like
you guys when you say oh it was just a
5H hour
drive you guys are really like oh just a
5H hour drive but I'm like what what do
you mean just that's
crazy here we have like
different con conception of what is a
long drive and what is a short
drive we should consider experimenting
with a song that has a little rap mixed
in Oh you mean for my future music you
want me to do a rap
I mean you know I I mean I wouldn't mind
doing something that has like rap verses
and maybe a a singing chorus in the
future but definitely not in the
upcoming one because the upcoming one is
finished and there is ah there is
something like a wrap in there actually
but only a small part you might not even
notice that it's supposed to be a wrap I
think it's supposed to be a wrap a
little
bit
a 1 hour drive to work every day for
me I guess in like America but also in
Australia I heard people do this a lot
they just it's pretty normal for people
to go uh to work even if it's like
really far each day like an hour or 2
hour drive
[Music]
even damn I don't think
I like I would try to get a different
job like that doesn't
seem productive to
me I think in the uh past for like
School uh just because there was really
no way around it because there was only
this one school I could go to for what I
was doing I think it took me like an
hour to get
there but it was comfortable in the
bus but like you know I feel like
if it was about a job I wouldn't want to
do that
uh yeah 4 years you did that you
commuted for four years so long
expensive housing so you live further
[Music]
away I
see yeah I mean 1 hour I guess could
still be like pretty
realistic even within Austria that that
is still like somewhat tolerable I would
say but anything above an hour if I had
to do that five days a week back and
forth
nah
yeah maybe start doing that and and
eventually consider moving closer to the
job if that's a
possibility yeah 1 hour each way is like
adding 20 yeah EX exactly you add to
your workday man don't even get paid for
it I'm on
congratulations I'll try to get to you
let me read these super chats thank you
again your boy stepen
Adams hope to see you again at some
panel sometime Cruz Jim Tracy for the
pinky thanks for the Fantastic you were
rocking it today and it was a cool touch
to pre-record some backing vocals yeah I
had to because I felt like otherwise it
sounds
so uh lonely like for our original songs
usually they Al also always create like
a Cara Oki and instrumental with backing
vocals but I didn't have access to it uh
for those songs at the moment so I
figured okay if I have to use the
instrumental without any backing vocals
let me make some
myself so that it sounds a a bit more
exciting especially for a song like the
one from Martin
Senpai yeah if there's no cheers and no
AO and no sh in the background
then it's not the same it's it feels
wrong bang bang oh I didn't have so many
actually I I was trying to back my
vocals up here and there a little bit
but it was n much
so but wasn't my rap
fire I nailed the rap I practiced like
most of the songs because I didn't have
time in the previous days most of the
songs I learned on that
day like the the ana song and bang bang
I learned on that day the M song I
learned on that day the the waya song I
learned on that day honestly almost
every song I learned on that day except
for the ones I sang
before was so difficult I was singing
for hours before the stream my throat
was
hurting oh she tweeted about I saw that
she sent me a DM about it I didn't see
that she
tweeted oh I was going to sing I'm your
treasure box but then I ran out of time
to practice it as
well it's you can't learn a
song that fast if you really want to get
to a level where you can sing it without
any like you know singing along to
someone is easier than singing without
anyone in the in the backup vocals you
know what I
mean oh my hello beep is here one second
guys let me try to open for
them
I'm back I brought one of the chocolate
cookies that I had in the in the fridge
let me
try
M yummy
yummy I added some some sprinkles too
actually the sprinkles might be
overpowering the
chocolate yeah they usually deliver this
[Music]
light actually I added I put such a fake
chocolate
layer I thought it was too
much
but m M it's not too much that's for
sure glaze or chocolate the glaze
ones
taste stronger like like the the glazing
the sugar glazing is stronger tasting
than the nut right
now so H it's a bit more
impressive than the chocolate covered
ones
H they're both good
though snowboard yum
yum yeah it had this weird Taste of
apricot that but I like it
anyway oh
continuing where were we I am so H for
your concert it's going to be totally
worth the
wait yeah I think so too I actually
today got a look at the first cut
basically and yeah I watched the whole
thing
um mine also I don't know it's not final
like it's still missing some things but
mine also might might not be exactly an
hour which I'm really surprised about
because I had so many
songs and still some MC's in between and
like we timed all the
MC's uh while we were doing them I had
like a timer in front of
me uh but yeah the current at the
current moment it is still uh a little
bit too
[Music]
short I don't know if we can still um
get it up to a full hour we'll see we'll
see
yeah I I don't know how we could have re
realistically recorded another song to
fill that up because we already had two
full 10hour recording
days and if I had to do one more song
that would have also meant I had to
learn one more song and that would have
been difficult for me too but like also
just generally from a logistical
standpoint it would have been kind of
tough to squeeze that
in yeah you know was also less than an
hour
no
mhm H well we'll see we'll see it's not
final yet so was good last here oh good
us too a that was you mean her you mean
the
one that you mean her birthday that one
that basically was made not by cover but
by
P I would say that's that's different
com comedic loading screens that's the
thing there's no loading screens it's
just like you know quickly moving on for
my uh 3D deut there were a lot of
loadings in between
right um this is not the case for a
birthday so everything like moves on so
fast to the next song to the next song
to the next
song There is basically no transition
and yeah
thinking looking at that I think the
transitions
quite uh add add quite a lot to the
time anyway I'm still excited I when I
was watching it today it felt long
enough but looking at the the the
timer CJ sit down thank you the pinky
pink canp let's go and bear thank you
ooh wait this is for the oh yeah this
was for the music video okay okay thank
you hope you guys will listen lots to
sleep
talking it is such a Bop I love it so
much also like the the Coro very much
and I even I changed some of the Coro I
changed the the dance break a little
bit yeah you can't see it in the music
video I hope you can see it
someday look forward to it one day I'll
be sleep twerking in my dreams sleep
twerking all these nights it's
you I'll watch it at least twice that's
about an hour I think that's the way to
go yeah do that recommend Dax Jaden D
Bruce J Le D GD d p Alvaro Max D Trevor
G thank you for the pinky ponytail kiaha
yeah she makes the comeback woof I I
mean did you just woof Trevor you're an
owl I mean wow so beautiful absolutely
gorgeous love to andv the outfit design
is so good sleep talking is too good
great work thank
you I wasn't sure if I should really go
for a ponytail because it kind of
overlaps with Sparks but it's a very
different ponytail it's a Ariana Grande
esque ponytail so it is definitely
giving different Vibes I think
right Ponyta is just chef's
kiss Thank you thank
you chicken's woof sometimes haven't you
heard now that you say
it uh hey
hey oh this beat is so good anyway thank
you to D I'm so happy you like it I'm
happy I I
hit the how to say your taste buds
correctly space water fall than soon and
's L than in for the pinky don't worry I
just started reading so I can read this
I respect your hard work and effort
props to everyone involved this was damn
good I might just become a k fan at this
rate
H should we tell him
should we tell him or should we just let
it
go n let him dream should we let him
dream how do we break it
to let's let's Let It Go just this once
I let it
slide miss you D the gamer Creed Dan
thank you I'll read the uh the ones from
yesterday from Holo
parade and I'm kind of scared right now
because I realized I
didn't um lock the
door and recently smoovie has been
trying to jump up to the handle and open
it again all the time I don't know why
suddenly she's trying it
but I'm feeling paranoid right
now go
lock it's probably fine okay if you
insist
okay I locked
it I locked it but also smoothie even
though she would have had the chance she
was just sitting chilling and sleeping
in the chair that she always sits in
right right next to my chair of the
dining
table like when I eat breakfast or
dinner I sit on my chair and then right
next to it there's another chair and she
always like takes her place in
it so I can t her while I'm eating
you're my
sunshine 6: a.m. in Korea
huh never trust her I never know but
recently she's been incredibly cudly she
does wake me up every morning
basically EV consistently every morning
and I go back to sleep after but that's
okay because like when we when we go to
sleep recently she always um she changed
her mind on what her favorite spot is
right now so right now she's always on
my left side on top of the memory foam
pillow and so I fall asleep while
petting smoothie with my left arm and
chunky wonky with my right
arm let's go oh we already finished
sorry we didn't get really far
though yesterday I kind of like I was
petting them and I was watching Home
Improvement while kind of
like half sitting up because I wanted to
pet them
properly and it was so
relaxing I like dozed off immediately
and I realized holy [\h__\h] why am I
already sleeping what the [\h__\h]
no it's so relaxing Home Improvement and
two two cats at my side like my
[\h__\h] imagine me having my arms around
my cup P one on the left one on the
right on my bed me in the middle I love
my cats I love them so much and they
squiggle squigle
squiggle I want to rap to this beat yo
yo yo
yo rap got Persona that's
me squiggle
wiggle cat
booty fluffy cutie oh cat booty fluffy
cutie
Mor moral D oh wait I didn't put up the
thumbnail hold
parade there it is I'm probably not
going to play it anymore
uh feel like it's it's gotten to a level
of difficulty where I'm still enjoying
it but like it's difficult
to move on on stream so I think I'm done
with it for now no I have my fun with
it I'm satisfied no no no even got the
Wawa played with the wa yeah it gets
like pretty grindy now so
mhm maybe I'll play it a little bit more
privately but not on stream moral D the
game of creed D Psy D mud arcade D blue
Destiny d boo 7 to fre
Dan oh okay well okay now that makes
sense yeah pointing out the the part
retriever in the name of a golden
retriever makes a lot sense holy [\h__\h]
simple generic
entity
dude thank you for all the memberships
who what's going on why why what made
you do
this 50 memberships I don't even know if
there's so many non-members in the chat
she what a
[Music]
Chad look at
them put your hands up in the air if you
want to get a membership try to catch it
like at a wedding when they throw the
the
bouquet try to catch it fight fight over
it tackle each
other
who's going to be the Lucky
Chicken
nice yeah memberships will be very very
valuable this weekend cuz on Sunday
there's a members only Encore for my 3D
birthday end of the year
life that you will only be able to watch
if you have a membership yeah
so it's now or
never the wab coin stalks are
rising more valuable than ever byy
now Waba
coin oh more memberships thank you where
was I uh H thank you danan for the Super
Chat and happy happy happy birthday to
you congratulations
ations or like almost congratulations
you said it's the 20th o oi you fooled
me I thought it was already well done
early happy birthday ja 47 Dan Uranus
Aquarius Dan Unity CH Dan
and AR thank you oh wait I just get it
now Unity Chad I I think yeah I I see
the resemblance of the
mannequin to the ASMR microphone the KU
100 I see it oh thank you H for more
memberships oh and UF mod yo you guys
are crazy thank you thank you thank you
thank
you and I don't stop coming and I don't
stop coming and I don't stop coming and
it don't stop
[Music]
coming hey future ASMR from right I can
reuse it I can recycle it Unity chat
thanks for for the pinky then be is
fantastic it's visually stunning and
perfectly captures the dreamy and sexy V
of the song yeah I was hoping for that
absolutely beautiful probably the
hottest wava version in an MV so far and
now we got the concert hype such a great
time to be kfp thank you yeah I really
got to say thank you for the artist
drawing the illustrations so well yeah
he didn't have much time either but he
did his best with the small small small
small amount of
time yeah gum shrew is God shrew got
through yeah he delivered he gave me
like a lot of different drafts too even
though there was so little
time like different poses like I say I
want I want wa on the phone and he sends
me four different versions of Wawa on
the
phone so I really appreciate that when
artists give me so many many choices but
must be a lot of
[Music]
work anyway thank you so much Unity chat
I'm also really excited it's so soon
it's this week the time the waiting time
is over pretty
much thank
you oh it was you I'm so happy to see
like you guys again in the chat first on
the panel and now in chat thank you
thank you for being
there Tassimo thanks for the pinky the
MV was fantastic and definitely pretty
sensual and I love it I feel like your
hard work really paid off your for your
entire album you should really be proud
of yourself Ki I'm also looking forward
to your concert on Sunday thank you it
was definitely like a big lesson that I
learned with this first album like if I
ever make another one I think it will be
even better because
I For Better or For Worse I learned a
lot of things and only improvements can
be made from here on out I
think but I'm glad you guys really enjoy
the album and its
variety I don't know if I will make one
next year probably not I think I'll
focus on having singles
again but I'll continue doing music for
now on on a slower Pace probably but it
won't
stop got to extend the Wawa
discography also making one song is just
so much easier than making a whole
album thank
God Eternal Le D thank you so clar thank
you for the red super chat hi Teno your
POV album and all the mvs are also
amazing thank you I'm blown away and
admire all the effort you have put in
you always have such a creative content
too if it's ah yeah this was the one
with the polar R okay so I'm not making
polar WS now uh I hope that I remember
this when I will be making polars maybe
you guys can also remind me um but don't
worry you don't have to pay
again I will make an exception because I
I don't I feel bad there must have been
a misunderstanding cuz I probably had
the word Polaroid on the screen or in
the in the in the chat I had it pinned
that must have caused the
misunderstanding
yeah so we'll we'll get you a polar you
just have to wait a little a little bit
uh next ones are going to be for
Christmas
so wein this year I think thank you for
the membership
welcome so I hope you can wait thank you
so clar James Jackson D Jim Tracy d
space waterfall d j d The Great Ghost d
dongan m d dongan always delivers those
cool
news s space water
Sky Bruce Le than morally immoral Dan
and Hol Lulu than for the pinky I
already cheered you up I hope that
worked hope you're doing better now are
you doing
okay I'm I'm sad when I see you guys sad
you
know so I hope everything goes
better
upwards even if this year was
rough it's almost over just a little bit
more just a few more steps guys 2024 is
right over there do you see it it's the
light at the end of the
tunnel the For You tab was a mistake
yeah the fo tap shows me lots of
messages that aren't not even tagging me
probably just because like no no problem
for the ones who are doing it but like
certain kfp members that I do follow
like
artists uh like with those connections I
I see it and you
[Music]
know uh I I wish I could it's okay don't
worry about it like at least maybe
sometimes I can stop someone from you
know hurting themselves or leaving kfp
or so just because they don't feel so
good at the moment and and and me seeing
it and reacting to it may actually
be
the the one thing that they needed but
but I can't always be the one you know I
can't always be there for everybody and
that
is difficult I don't want people to have
those expectations
[Music]
either cuz I don't think I can live up
to
[Music]
them wow wow
wow yeah
so if you see someone from the kfp
Community writing sad sad tweets please
cheer them up for me if I can't do it
and please speak for me I think you will
all speak for me if you cheer someone up
that's what I would
do just say I think I speak for kiata
when I say
come don't give up
fight yeah yeah yeah
okay I think now we can go to the Super
chats from
today we are catching up let's
go yeah I do I do feel you know very
connected to you
guys members beauty salon oh members
beauty salon oh oh oh
maybe I'll read them in the next member
stream okay from
today
jacob7 oh I talked about it during
Pokemon
Violet that's crazy chcken monkey
Mo I keep on wanting to like flow into
the Rhythm when I read
something I feel like I could fall into
the Rhythm at any
[Music]
time Prince of Denmark thank you soon
for the pinky I was at the panel oh and
singing new songs alongside fellow kfp
was the highlight of my
year since you don't remember the Super
Chat read for holo parade huh what does
that mean you won't remember telling me
to double to do double b a [\h__\h] you did
it at the panel end in the group for
[\h__\h] no I don't yeah I don't know when
did you do it I was watching the
audience a
lot wait the group for the one that
management basically sent
[Music]
me let me let me look for the photo is
there someone doing bunny ears like I
told them
to ah the one I
retweeted
wait where's this
[Music]
picture oh was it not in this oh it
wasn't in this
group
um where did I get
it maybe it was in my oneon-one chat
with
JMA oh yeah there it
is
MM
bunny no no no one's doing it in this
picture that I have wait there I guess
there's another group
picture the after panel photo well who
tweeted it it should be in my time on
okay okay okay okay let's go to w
Twitter the hot spot for all the good
stuff Squall Squall
Squall squ
squ scrolling
uh no uh a this one
ah I see you you're doing it you
[Music]
remember oh these people are so
cute look at my cuties I love them so
much T come
[Music]
they're so cute I love them all I love
them I love this one and this one and
this one and this one and this one and
this one oh you can't see
huh you can't see it huh I was pointing
at you you you
you anyway thank you Prince of Denmark S
I didn't notice it at the panel I
probably I probably yeah already forgot
anyway sorry but now I know now I know
thank you for listening to my orders a
very diligent chicken you are thank you
and I hope you enjoyed the panel I will
say it was also one of my highlights of
the year so yeah very understandable I
hope we can repeat something like this
next year
see you again hopefully Daniel Kel D MDB
dun two year
anniversary yay thank you for supporting
me for so long MDB rice of RAC golden
Boom
D MJ D you are d i a t Wings CV
D oh oh that's mean your boy Steven Adam
[Music]
than oh I see they have me in as a
spirit what does that mean
spirit dragon war
AC
Dom for the pink quite a few N64 games
that would make for shorter streams like
this shame you can't do a medly I wonder
maybe I can because like generally yeah
it's not
really something we should be doing if
it's like you know
different like games from different
Publishers and all that but this is from
the same publisher so and even kind of
within the same game aka the N64
emulating thing on the switch so I could
see how maybe it would be
allowed I'll check if I can mix them
I'll ask and I also ask if uh even if
maybe I can play the Pokemon games
even oh yeah and I did see the the GBA
ones as well so much Choice like
honestly since they added all those
older games I feel like that added so
much
value to getting
the well it's a membership plus
expansion so yeah
yeah for off collab streams I want to
try those those out and that would be
especially nice if we can play several
ones in one
stream George Martinez than Unity chat
than soon I agree I
mean I I've probably yeah wrapped Doja
cat songs before in my K
streams armor nambo thanks for the pinky
there we are I've reached you Ki today's
my birthday and I believe it's all
already been four whole birthdays with
you wow thanks for always helping me get
for work love kfp got to see the
panel at AF and it was awesome screaming
my lungs out with the hype left you were
also in the left corner like everybody
who like almost everybody maybe except
for one person that I heard back from
since almost everybody has been in the
left
corner
nice yeah I'm so so glad I keep on
talking about it you know how much I
enjoyed it too so thank you for being
part of the reason why it was so
enjoyable thank you for everything and
please continue supporting the Wawa and
happy happy birthday I see you are a
child of the
winter
congratulations and Merry Christmas soon
as
well yeah it was my hype Squad I was so
proud of you
guys you guys were hyping up the whole
Hall rapid Apple than you soon Gary Gaza
than you soon thank you so much I think
I'll refresh one more time see if
there's something new oh space waterfall
than
soon a that is a sweet way to end it
thank you space waterful and boohoo 723
d
Jet Force gemin oh that was yeah I saw
that one too not one that is familiar to
me though care you forever love you
while I love you too thank
you congratulations birthday birthday
birthday it is your
[Music]
birthday let's blow out those
candles I hope to go to another CL in
the future I hope so too conventions are
really fun even like I hear so often I
hear from people who go to these chanels
that oh this is my first convention and
I'm having so much fun so like even if
you've never been to
one if there's one somewhat
reachable from where you guys are I
think you should
go I mean especially if whole life is
there especially
then
it was my first convention like 8 years
W I'm glad we could drag you back
there going to conventions was also
before whole life was like my my
favorite thing to do um with my friends
um nowadays it's a bit more difficult
and kind of different anyway like the
whole it just feels so different and
less I'm less comfortable I'm less free
I'm less Carefree like n it's not so
nice anymore
but if it wasn't for that I would still
be doing that so I hope you guys can
enjoy them you know I'm enjoying them in
a different way now when I go there as a
as a guest as a
performer it's different that is I
really enjoy
that that's my
cope but it's not like I'm really
attending anyway yo I'm most of time I'm
only virtual I wish more conventions
would like bring me there in person but
I guess that would be insanely stressful
like I don't think I would really want
to fly out just for a convention to
America imagine all the trips I already
have in my year and then adds to that
having to fly out to them if you think
about it that way it's a huge advantage
to be a virtual you
like if you're a normal like whatever
actor voice actor that gets brought to
these conventions as a guest you have to
fly out to them
usually now for us it's normal to just
be there on the screen so we can
comfortably do it from our homes so it
is a huge Advantage this way I can way
more efficiently be at a lot more events
throughout the year than someone who has
to travel there in person yeah
the iPad idea yeah I wonder I want them
to do that with us yeah I want to I want
to move around a convention I I got to
ask them if we can make that possible
sometime next
year yeah I want to walk around but I
feel
like I feel like that's maybe a bit
difficult because I the if there's
kfp there or like whole life fans
they'll probably be Sur rounding the
moving iPad 24/7 constantly and there'll
be like this huge
crowd yeah around it and following it
and and that might actually be
disturbing to the
convention and the people
there me and my Coupe a flying drone oh
that also sounds crazy that sounds
good that's
funny to imagine
[Music]
that I don't know I don't know how it
worked for iron Mouse no
idea maybe she was more usually always
in one spot didn't move around much
maybe who
knows yeah crowd surf I could do crowd
surfing
a but then what if someone breaks the
iPad we'll suit them no no that's uh
that would be [\h__\h] if someone breaks
the iPad
imagine we need to put the iPad in like
a a case that
has
a the glass that you can't shoot
through and munition
proof
yeah bullet yeah bulletproof this time
baby I'll
be
bullet
prooof okay we're done with reading
super chats I'm glad we're done uh
somewhat early because I want to go cook
and I also
uh want to rest
h
I'll prepare the tweet I I I'll be uh
scheduling all the announcement tweets
to go out at the same time just as this
one today which I I think it was 9:00
a.m. my time I wasn't even awake but uh
I'll be scheduling them all so keep an
eye out open for
it ah yeah I guess I'll post it in the
community tab too maybe wait I was I
noticed when I wrote that Community post
yet yesterday I feel
like it doesn't yeah that's like look at
me posting my schedule
4,400 likes and then me sleeptalking MV
linking that one basically but linking
it through YouTube from YouTube to
YouTube it's not even a link going
outside I think it gets shown to yeah it
doesn't show up in the subscription box
does it
huh the SCH
does I I feel like I would understand if
YouTube like blocks Community posts that
link to an outside website but it's a
YouTube post that shows you a YouTube
video like I'm I'm advertising within
the platform and yet it kind of like
Shadow bands it by not showing it how
did you guys even find it if it's if it
wasn't in the subscription box where you
just like notified on disc or something
like hey kiaba posted something on the
community board how did you guys see it
yeah the VIS visibility is
terrible I've noticed it before whenever
I like advertise a video or so it really
doesn't do
anything a Discord B checking
manually that's so so
[\h__\h] like why YouTube
why literally there's an option when you
make a community post it gives you a
choice do you want to upload a picture
do you want to do a poll do you want to
do a quiz or do you want to add a video
that's already on YouTube why block it
so much huh why not show all the
subscribers this thing what the
[Music]
hell so
sad everything everything's broken man
everything's broken I'm so done it's so
frustrating some people I'm subscribe to
it never shows yeah I mean for all those
reasons you guys have to follow me on
Twitter at least on
Twitter you pretty much should see what
up all the time unless you follow 5,000
people that tweet all the
time yeah Meanwhile your PO yeah exactly
the poll holy [\h__\h] like even the members
posts do better than that one
video oh the me wait what about the
members wallpaper because I see now it
also doesn't has have so many likes but
I don't know if it's because it's a
members wallp a members post or if it's
because there's a link to G
file did you get the notification for
that
okay did you get it in your subscription
box that
post
yeah yeah okay okay okay okay good good
good
good but I think it varies with when
when I'm scrolling down now
some streams that I posted about in the
community
board seem like maybe they did get shown
to people like for example the Lo roboco
by one when I was saying hey I'm on I'm
on this channel here with Robo
Senai that
one no although still like compared to
the tens of thousands of likes on the
other
posts but then there's this one oh why
is there this one
schedule
[Music]
from two weeks ago that has only
4,000 likes
versus no okay the one from seven days
what's happening what's
happening oh no never mind never mind I
I added too many zeros well that's
pretty
normal anything under a thousand seems
like they don't put it in the
subscription
boxes anything over is
[Music]
probably the visibility is probably
there
yeah okay well well enough
science thank you guys for keeping an
eye out for for what the Wawa is
doing I just put your December
wallpapers my thank you on that note I
want to say I talked with the artist
about my Pawn moment my oopsy do and and
and they found it really funny and they
offer it nicely uh cuz we we were still
at an early stage of the draft um so
they were like if you want I can I can
totally draw something else still
maybe they'll finish the the Christmas
one afterwards as well it will still be
after Christmas but yeah uh we'll work
on a New Year's themed one now instead
so no Santa WWA in
January yeah y
y it was really funny though when I
realized that I'm stupid stupid that was
really funny the moment I realized I'm
stupid I was
funny okay guys in German we say I the Z
sorry the stream was maybe a little bit
lame cuz I'm really bad at the game but
what can you
[Music]
do it is what it is but it was still
kind of funny looking back at such an
old nostalgic
game would have been better if it was
the GameCube version to be honest
probably
Avalanche
a thank you such a fast
reaction thank you zing bye-bye see you
the day after tomorrow for uh the crony
collab is that yeah I think
so let's go hey hey hey hey hey bye-bye
happy in thank you good night love you
guys I miss you I miss
you don't go don't go give me don't go
no where are you going where are you
going where where
wa doesn't work like
that where are you going where are you
going why are we going where are we
going don't
go why can't I not move everything I
want ah where no where you go no
everything's
[Music]
fading I will miss
you I won't forget
[Music]
you it was nice knowing
you
you know when you turn off YouTube when
the stream is over I sit in the virtual
void all
alone all alone
imagine I'm like a game character when
you don't play the game I cease to
[Music]
exist well
What a Sad
[Music]
lore