happy Halloween man I love Halloween me
too I'm a Christmas girl it's all right
Nissa you never sent me that picture of
you in your costume oh I ended up
feeling sick so I ended up not changing
and dressing up after all it was really
depressing for me I know I wanted to die
you can dress up yeah you can always
dress up but now I'm looking for like I
want to find a cute dress to wear for
Christmas just go naked no you can't go
naked it's Christmas yeah it'll be like
a Christmas present no like Merry
Christmas Shivers put a ribbon around
your body that's like some fancy Laie
type you guys are sick you're sick well
yeah I am sick actually