[Music]
so
do
[Music]
so
welcome back to
later
alligator kumbama hello
hello
how are you guys
i had a nap so i sound a little bit
tired maybe but it will change
soon i think
it was was a comfy coffee nap
um
[Music]
oh you see my mouse there even though
i'm not in that window funny
funny how things work
there you go there we go
later alligator
part two because
it was just so cute
it was just such a cute game i wanted to
get the other endings because you guys
said it would be enough uh content for
another stream
[Music]
hope you guys are all doing well
think i know
you know who else is cute yes you
actually
[Music]
actually actually one thing let me put
on my
my feathers uh
[Music]
no
i put on my feathers i feel naked
[Music]
you see my mouse movements i feel
embarrassed
and um
[Music]
which one was it this one i wanted
the wrong outfit
[Music]
should i change my outfit
i'll change my outfit
i want to hug a pillow today
[Music]
this one
i forgot what i was wearing last time
i don't recall
but
today i feel like
this
like this
burp on hand and burp in my arms
i i was wearing the og oh you're right
oh
okay not today no i don't feel that
today
i'm feeling this today burp on head and
cuddle burp in my arms
um
fuzzy cozy cozy
[Music]
okay
ready to strangle no
nobody's doing any strangling here
there can never be enough verbs yes
exactly
so today we're continuing this um i hope
uh i hope it works i hope it saved
properly that i ended it once
let's see
it's so cute
okay yeah it gives me an achievement try
try again i suppose that means uh
yeah okay so we start from the beginning
and we should i guess um try to not talk
to anyone who we talked to before
um because that will i guess just be a
waste of time the goal is just to talk
to everyone right
[Music]
but he knows i'm coming back for him oh
did you come back for me
yes
yes i did yeah yeah
wait is this like the what what point is
this because he says the same thing am i
just supposed to like go they're not
gonna tell me the whole same story again
which is good i guess yeah
the whole um shenanigans from the
beginning he's not gonna tell me that
again i suppose
so he just wants me to go out okay
you're free to explore now but does he
know
that's
is it implied that he already does it
that this is after the birthday party
[Music]
already done the starting talk okay
i know
[Music]
the little hands
i guess they're like gloves or socks
[Music]
it's so cute
the paws the shoes why is there a sword
has there always been a sword
uh wait why why was i supposed to look
at my bag
ah i have 18 out of 43 family badges
uh five other uh 48 puzzle pieces i
don't know if we can get all of them i
don't really want to focus on those
just click around a little bit for a
puzzle piece here did i i think i did i
did get one puzzle piece here before
maybe
quack
i guess in every room there's one puzzle
piece and every
screen no i can't find one here
okay let's go outside
past the piece is not required
just a family badges i guess so i guess
once we have all family badges it's
considered completed hello
did we talk to did we talk to him
i think we did
[Music]
let's go to a different part of the city
we didn't go to the memorial park i
think and also not to the unsavory part
of the town
like
but we also didn't quite talk to
everyone in downtown either i
think i think there we have let's but
let's go to the others where we're sure
and if we're still missing someone then
we'll go back to downtown
i think
so here i don't think we've been here
i need to beat the granny bus
will she come again oh
yes she will come again
oh did you say something
i see you over there writing my cards
young gun but i ain't giving them to ya
last time i was giving a card to it was
long before you were born and now look
at me i'm old see what sharing gets you
aging irreparably
not sure if that's really connected lady
yeah get a rematch
it was only luck anyway for real one day
your skin is sucked close to your
skeleton but then you turn around and
boom your jowls are hanging down past
your collarbones which are now hollow
inside is that what you want hollow
color bones with the nest of daddy long
legs inside then stop staring at my
cards
uh
it's already checked so we don't have to
do it ask anymore
although you could play me for the
information as long as you don't stare
in my cards when you say kiddo think you
can beat me no mate hell yeah
my
let's do it again
on your turn clicks to take one of
constancy's cards and then she'll take
one from you any matching pairs will be
removed the player left holding the old
maid lose it easy card game one of the
single two games that i know how to play
now
man
beauty before age okay last time i think
in my first turn i grabbed her old mane
don't stare at the cards yeah yes it's
because you're doing some shady things
with them huh
okay okay okay okay we got a king i
think
that card looks funny
i want this i want this merchandise
i want those cards printed out
doesn't matter what you take
okay
um
i like this one yay
ah there's no chance that we'll lose now
i mean there's one more chance that we
might lose one more
but i think we're fine
[Music]
uh three cards to choose from
parade cards
um i'll mess up are you ready yet
[Music]
wait one more one more
oh [\h__\h] oh no no no we're done we're
done okay yeah cause she has to pick the
last one
[Music]
i'll catch you next time
now give me the information old lady
you like to talk anyway don't you
and share it with me family back oh geez
we'll learn everything about that's
family
and then we can marry him because then
everybody in his family knows me and
then and then and then and then it will
be okay to marry him
sorry guys i'm gonna marry a crocodile
uh uh another crocodile um
uh
whatever the hell that was
and then we'll get into the title to the
title it's in the title how can i not
remember the word
[Laughter]
all right all right don't get too cocky
there kiddo those eyes don't see as well
as they used to when i bought them off
that plague doctor in the mid to late
18th century
what about marrying the babies
ah
they are my babies i can't marry my
babies they're my children just how old
am i none of you dang beeswax
i got my own beeswax to worry about you
know from the back bees
anyway the event is tonight and me and
my sister rue are both gonna be there
what more do you need to know
i'll get the heck away from me and stop
staring at my cards before i give you a
knuckle sandwich mmm sandwich
i just had a
um a toast with
egg
vegan vegan
vegan egg spread on it i like eggs right
it's yummy
that's pink knuckle which i bought from
a great butcher in the bath alley behind
the sizzler it's real good so i don't
want to share
be
[Music]
i just wanted to i just wanted to learn
you in a city so big there are bound to
be parts of town that our little city
i'm talking seedy though city tough guys
city tough guys who eat the seeds of
things without spitting them out onto a
napkin politely what even like a peach
scene what the [\h__\h] that's tough that's
that is tough
that is very tough and so just be
careful
don't go clicking around oh no [\h__\h]
i forgot i did that last time
don't go clicking around in the back
alleys or anything you never know what
you might find
sounds like an invitation
he's nothing let's talk to him first
man you got any change for novelty
tie-dye apparel
well it starts out i can like feel your
energy from here
i'd say what's harshing my whole thing
right now
but the truth is i've recycled some
really gnarly bagels for lunch today out
of the dumpster behind my furniture
store
my mellow has been for early pre-heart
dude
why would there be bagels in the
dumpster of a furniture store
oh
bro pillows
bummer
listen
who am all goose
hasn't woken up at noon in a van under a
blanket felted equally from stranger
lint and candy wrappers
it's no wonder i got into the wrong
dumpster if anything it's fade
[Music]
i'm aiden it's totally chill to meet
you.com.org
i sort of knew someone would seek me out
today i'm like a bit of a clairvoyant
according to some sub forums i visit
online
plus i own a somewhat unsettling amount
of powerful crystals their potent
energies course through me to my inner
core
which is great since i spent the last of
my thoughts on some suspiciously
expensive crystals in my inner core a
super starving man
yeah crystals are looking nice but you
know you're just getting scammed they
don't do [\h__\h]
they look nice though
you can also make them out of hot glue i
saw a video of someone making like a
really fancy looking crystal i have hot
glue
it looks realistic
did you say path
is pretty cool guy
kind of dresses like us preschooler
though even um
if i'm being realsies
my little sister lizzy is dating his
cousin so i guess you could say we're
kind of like a family
your little sister is dating his cousin
well i try to remember that
i might just you know put the family
badges everywhere randomly
again you can say anything to strangers
really no one can stop you
the event that i already know what it is
please tell me about it tonight oh dude
i'm sorry i really can't tell you much
i've been sworn to secrecy
i could actually oh we're gonna have a
game too
i'd probably tell you a few things if
you do me a solid first you see those
suspiciously expensive crystals i
mentioned earlier well
those little mamas were also
suspiciously powerful from just three
nights of holding them even when i had
to get up to do pee i felt mystically
charged enough to access my innermost
self but in my tireless questing for the
crystals concentration arts i just don't
have the time to shower or dust my
pewter miniatures
besides bathing is a way for the man to
keep us down
you should be sliding across the floor
an oil slick of your own creation like
nature intended
yeah yeah
yeah
my aromatic scent keeps away a lot of
unwanted company like solicitors and my
father but invited others
i'm talking about flies these little
buzzing buzz skills keep arching my
mellow they're making it impossible for
me to concentrate on my inner light to
do it in the right if you know what i
mean
if you could just swap them away from me
while i'm getting my meditation on
they'll be happy to do your solid in
return so will you be my sponsors yes
i wanted to make a fly thingy um fly
catch thingy thingy uh slappy thingy for
uh with hot glue the other day was sorry
my glue gun is um
near died so if you have one for me that
would help i didn't bring my own applies
to what i had clicking flies in order to
attack them with a slight fly swatter
hornets take extra hits don't swat
butterflies or aiden okay
i try my best
see that i do have friends
[Music]
oh they shouldn't get too close to him i
see i see
[Music]
oh
it's happening what's up forums we're
right i have to keep going okay
okay okay okay
at least you reset
oh
maybe maybe you know what i might want
to play this um
let me move the window over to my um
a draw at a
[Music]
a monument to his own
hubris
agencies oh this is before you still as
a stash because he is one of those now
apparently he reflects on how crystals
are nothing to be traveled with as well
as how they're really cool as you expect
aiden's soapstone exterior you know that
but i can never play this again the next
time
i i think it was solid
i'll be gym loud okay okay okay
i needed the solid
i made them solid
until next round bob do we not get the
badge you know the still lingering smell
of buddy couch cushions and patchouli uh
perhaps she's still in there after all
damn it i'll oh damn it okay
next time
damn it
next time i'll use my drawing tablet for
that
i say oh they're vibrant
brother i don't think they're background
they've got that suit on perhaps a hobo
king
oh you may be right sister you there
hobo king come here a moment
honestly brother what are we even doing
in this filthy part of town
even breathing the air outside this city
watering hole is making my scales lose
their highly regarded luster
i agree sister but you know as well as i
that we had to find an unbiased bonehead
for our beneficiary so anyone that is at
the estate was out besides you know how
weary i grew up literally everyone we
know in the whole wild world
shall we talk to the stranger with the
briefcase then
yes yes as long as it's not someone that
gives me the dreadful horror of being
known
huh
who are you
princess a real princess
that's nice i will not be a princess
brother there's nobody doesn't seem to
be aware of who we are oh yeah literally
what i just said i don't know you're
sorry
indeed sister perhaps with that
pinstripe style they've spent the last
30 years so locked in a storage cloak
closet with their fingers in their ears
and their other fingers in their ears
eyes and fingers yet still in their nose
that is uh like playing twister on your
face though
kind of difficult i didn't do that
obviously since i released that perfume
this year
obviously
i'm princess valentino heir to the
valentine of fortune and this is my
brother prince valentino why am i
starting to sound like a valley girl i
didn't want to do that
he's also the air since we're
twins i'm the evil twin
they couldn't test for that scene and
you know it prince
you're both evil probably
pat wow he's our second
cousin that's like a cousin but
thankfully a little more removed from
your gene pool
the amount of dna shared between us is
blessedly on the shallow side much like
your personality sister
prince you're such a cut-up
much like how i cut up your invitation
to the met gala this year and fed into
the cat
oh
what
you're too good to be at the met gala
[Music]
what but the theme is here was the
monopoly mascot
you mean
the dude in the white suit
with the stick
i don't know mittens is the third is on
a strict diet for your failing kidneys
he has very thick eyebrows
and slick hair
well now you're going to have to be more
specific i attended a lot of events you
know
about balls galas exhibitions princess
unfortunate performance art shows
if you're speaking of last week when i
walked the runway for guild's fashion
fishery rubber pants for moist
alligators i'll have you know i got a
ride up in the magazine spread for
highlights for children
anyway if you're talking about tonight
we have no qualms spilling the whole
secret to you oh
then as if only you do
the smallest of favorites oh of course
you want the favor sure what is it
you see overlapping daddy passed away
just recently from poison related pump
complications uh
yoda
[Applause]
aha from the ghost they're the the
children from the ghost who got killed
by his wife with poison
oh
right
[Laughter]
you know the natural way
the way he just looks looked like he
kind of knows it was the mom
they're in on it
maybe they're in on it
because it's an inheritance oh my god
we're splitting up our shared
inheritance but we could really use a
mediator
and someone to protect my beautiful face
from my dear sister's punches
it's true i punched super duper hard
if only we had some help dividing up
daddy's precious possessions i'm sure we
could tell you the information you seek
oh we're gonna do math or something like
that
so will you help us or do you have a
hobo king duties to tend to
no um i'm not a hobo
divine twin inheritance oh they're twins
okay i'll play of course
split the perks between the jerks use a
checklist to assign an item to each of
the valentino twins you can't leave
until both twins are happy so pay
attention to indicator bar okay is there
time
[Music]
for well let's get on with this daddy's
not getting any more alive
i like a dress and her shoes bootsies
i'm already bored
okay
minks though doll sounds like something
she would want to wear i simply couldn't
my conscience wouldn't allow it
but it clashes terribly with everything
i own and
it'd be up all night i'd be up all night
worrying about it hey so you don't want
it
i'll give you a hat though how about
that oh she likes it
i thought a secret society had i
wondered if it had been lost after the
swat race
she sounds okay with that
do you want the armor
uh shiny damage and empty well it
wouldn't be totally out of place with me
i suppose
okay
but it really sounded like she doesn't
want it right
oh cozy just the kind of thing i like
warming made for the suffering of
another okay and he sounds happy about
it
wine
how about you
this really brings back memories
remember when we rolled up tipsy cousin
clear in the wine cellar after luring
her with the promise of an even finer
vintage oh how we left
she seems okay with it a vinyl
uh this is not really about weight
though right it's just like item num the
amount of items so we have two two now
um let's give the vinno
first to her
oh yeah she likes it there's mostly
combinations of halloween sounds effects
sound effects and screams so yes please
give this to me okay what what are the
videos of that kelly she she likes
vanilla she likes wine she likes uh
probably hats like that
um a photo
well it's a conversation piece i suppose
uh would would she be happier about it
oh she doesn't want it yeah okay maybe
this one i guess is neutral maybe it's
maybe there are neutral pieces
we can still switch it around if we want
to what about a painting oh he likes the
painting
wait look at the top i just noticed that
now
was it always that that much on the left
side
oh this would be more of a masterpiece
if it depicted something important like
me or perhaps me
does she not like it
oh she likes it with more and now it's
more even
okay
um
sack of cashton
fathers beloved cartoonish sack of money
it reminds me so much of him cold hard
and beneath my flippers
okay his facial expression told me he
likes it
uh um
parrot she likes the parrot
i spent hours training him to eat 50
dollar bills in front of our governors
as she cried sweet chocolate memories
whoa oh cute
killed parrot she has a burp
i'm gonna call call it kiana maybe
sports car will probably be really
expensive
what happens
oh it's only a little little thing here
pass you don't like it okay
i need to
sneeze um wow she's getting a lot of
stuff how about earn a vash is for you
oh he likes it at first hearing we put
daddy in melted but luckily this one is
from the funeral home's new poison proof
collection
hmm
these twins are evil let me tell you
that
um
crystal orb
she doesn't want it okay
but does it matter if i have to do it
evenly then maybe it doesn't matter if
they like it but let's see
oh she likes the blade okay claymore oh
but the sports car is so tiny it was
just that's what okay was not a real
sports car
okay
um
i need one more thing on her side
no
but she does like it more than him
so if we instead uh
give one more thing ah the painting the
painting we weren't sure about the
painting how about this
big difference but he likes to
he likes the painting
at least this time
give it back she likes it too
maybe the photo has less impact
it didn't
change
it didn't change
didn't look like it changed
[Music]
the girl was happy about all these
things
but how about this no
i'm not he didn't like it and it doesn't
make it even either
and was
the wine
oh yeah wow that fills it both up
okay that that means she was already way
over the maximum a fine vintage from the
year i was born daddy was saving it for
when i became an admirable member of
society good thing you died and i can
just take it
[Music]
i mean there was no way of losing this i
guess
i got a family badge a member bag and
another one oh jeez
nice though
that's all of daddy's things and i feel
quite pleased with my whole
and me as well why i'm such a in a good
mood i'm almost feeling feelings again
seriously brother help pedestrian you i
know i know please don't tell any of the
servants they'll start asking me for
silver dollars or whatever they eat
these days i guess we should thank you
pinstripes and tell you what you want to
know about the event
but we won't your reward is our smiling
snoots
[Music]
sasuka
how was i thinking that they would help
me
now get out of the car before we ring
the police
[Music]
they uh
they might get poisoned one day too for
being so evil and cocky
[Music]
not by me just saying that if you're
mean and cocky to everyone you might get
end up being poisoned too by someone
what are you who are you raoul
hey you gotta watch new notes for my
cigarette in general
it's kind of dark out here that i've got
a spooky ghost allergy you ain't seen on
you right
oh he doesn't really okay or do we need
to talk more often
if you want to get into bar
bub
you're gonna have to co cough up an id
or anything really coughing up stuff is
generally an adult thing getting older
and glamorous
oh is that implying i can't get in wait
i need to sneeze again
[Music]
ah
nope it's gone it left me hi guys
hey what you looking at
are you trying to listen to our
exceedingly private rooftop conversation
beat it creep
okay i guess we can just enter nice
i hate when it happens me too
oh
cute place i like all the neon lights
and the
juice works the jukebox not the juice
box are we gonna play dart
i can throw that from here
yo you're huge you have such a tiny face
for your huge body let me talk to you
cute oh
i didn't see you down there can you move
about two centimeters to the right the
placement of my eyes is particularly
wacky
[Music]
i'm waiting for a call but my phone has
been pretty dinked up lately i wonder if
it will even come in
maybe i should ask
oh my god
it's ddr in the background
oh my god the music come on everybody
check it out
you follow me
damn man i should ask the bartender to
use the phone here oh that's not going
to work since i stored the number i need
here
in my broken phone
how did anyone even get by before modern
cell phone technology how did they send
each other messages or watch videos
about people drinking a gallon of milk
and then throwing up
i guess i'll just have to write letters
now and film myself barfing on vhs
just like the pilgrims would have
he's like he looks like a pyramid
man
it's okay even when you look like a
pyramid you're beautiful
i would like to um
get on top of you
sorry
call me tell jared i don't really like i
don't really get it though honestly i'm
not even the tallest jerry that i
personally know
[Laughter]
oh he's the illuminati oh
now i just i've never seen a pyramid in
real life before you know and and and i
i want to you know
visit one
oh yeah music
time to become perfect
[Laughter]
you know
you might be able to do it the japanese
people are professionals at that at
making um weird shapes out of fruit like
uh watermelons you know
you guys can do that too maybe if you
put yourself in while you're while
you're an egg or maybe as a chick you
can put yourself into a form
like a triangle or or a square
try it
all things to be good at yeah
fruits are not chickens well sure
but both can be eaten both are food so
both should be able to be shapened
yeah mold yourself
get a hold of yourself move yourself
yeah let that info sink in for a while i
can see your imagination running wild in
your extremely visible eyes
oh pat the alligator that's my little
cousin all my cousins are little to me
even the older ones pat whoever is
particularly small maybe that's why he's
so skittish that got a guy that tiny
could slip into a crack anytime or get
lost in a medium-sized mouse hoe
like a borrower or something
very specific
also i love the face of that fish
not amused
oh you're going to that too i tell you
more about it but the sad truth is i
jotted down all the deets in my phone
here but the dang thing has been on the
fritz for over a week now do i have to
repair it
yeah yeah do you guys hear the music
properly
ever since i got back from the ghastly
mansions of the rich and dead i did on
my vacation what what's really ghastly
is the distribution of wealth among the
populists
and the dead you list
i don't know what i'm going to do my
phone is my last literally
same
i don't have a rich inner existence or
anything it's mostly all saved on here
in the form of a dream journal and
pictures of good breakfast i've had i
don't know how much of a tech person you
are but do you think you could take a
look
uh we really have to fix his phone
magical ghost in the cell
[Music]
funny
i get that reference although i never
watched ghost in the shell
or read it it's originally a manga right
uh if i'm not wrong i might be wrong
i got one reference let's go
actually i think in the last episode i
also got one reference
so
this is one of the games with um a
bigger amount of references that i
understand thank you to the creators for
putting in references that i get
we're in the same wavelength it was a
manga
yeah yeah they made a realistic anime
out of it as a
movie right is it already was it already
released
with uh who is it like uh
some famous female
actress scarlett johansson or something
like that yes it was scott jackson yeah
uh oh sky joe you call her scarjo are
you close with her and is
she like your bestie
you have her phone number
calling her scar joe
man that sounds like she has like she's
like from the
from the yakuza cell having scars it
sounds like a yakuza nickname
the like a guy was called joe
who has a lot of scars they call him
scar joe
there's something fishy about hold
jared's flip phone flip phones i used to
have one in japan so cute investigate
his apps and files to find the stories
of the mysterious malfunctions
yeah
i said japan because i had one in japan
but i never had one in austria
i it went on the first a couple weeks
ago when i was on the vacation can you
fix whatever's wrong my phone is my lap
line to everyone
yeah everyone else sometimes tall jared
is too tall to hear the voices down
there
oh so you gotta call them in order to
hear them okay
what am i supposed to fix
looks fine
this gray and this screen isn't helpful
at all what do you think ghost mode is
oh
unlock to enable ghost mode
i don't know the password yet do i
notes
oh i'm just not warning you some of my
notices are pretty personal
can look at it dream person dream jungle
oh i was in the woods and i was running
on all fours and there was a monster
chasing me i'm at school and everyone is
making fun of me because i forgot old
meth
don't worry i also forgot all math all
of it
every single number
i am hungry i'm looking at myself in the
mirror and except my ex and except my
father is looking back at me he turns
into sand and i'm holding two hems
and fish islands is it's the best dream
ever fish hands
you can eat them
how exciting groceries
eh what let me check
chris bryce's legend moving your paper
down
good breakfast dirting spray pee but not
the bubba
small hat he wants a small hat too he
likes ham
cute
game ideas a spooky game about free kids
in a bad summer camp a cute game about
he's working on a video game a cute game
about a sweet knight who gets to escort
four hot princes down the mountain
i don't know down the mountain okay
a silly mystery game about alligators in
the city too much work
i think someone already had that idea or
someone's
no jared someone stole the idea from you
the game exists now
man you should sue them you would get a
lot of money out of it probably
or who knows probably not probably
probably they would overpower you
yeah
because you have no proof that you had
that idea already early right
a german game about mega piles fighting
over the fate of humanity and kissing
that also sounds like something that
exists
oh what is this okay i can't look at
that can i write a new note oh
i'm able ah okay your phone is acting up
a little bit now
um when train
you train
soon
this is the third train schedule app
i've tried but i'm still labeled
[Laughter]
oh
i don't know if i can help you with that
um
video time
oh i should do a stream where i just pop
bubble wrap paper
not paper bubble wrap when i get really
stressed i watch soothing videos it
calls me calms me uh
thank you for watching my channel sorry
i didn't upload last week i just really
subscribed let's unsubscribe
uh what
some people like sunny days and some
people like rainy days like the forecast
when it's just like this pretty good
pretty good it's pretty good out
today 75 next day 81 after day after 80
fun
is this like a secret cold
thank you thank you thank you for the
red super chat
um
pictures
you're going to look for my photos
should i okay no i'm sure there's
nothing too embarrassing in there
let's take a look oh your little sip
joanie
hello
chrissa mmm
he likes to take food photos for his
instagram
oh cute look who are those
oh it's a selfie in the mirror
would you look at that as a fella yeah
pretty handsome you fill out the mirror
nicely
i'll give myself compliments every day
it's like a workout for your self-esteem
is that supposed to tell me something i
don't know
oh i could delete the photos
that was a good breakfast i believe you
how about vacation
i mean mine are pretty good already sure
they're amazing oh yo
enjoying that vacation with those mini
sunglasses
okay
i think
that's always just gonna be his face
because it's so huge
you're bigger than the mountain dude
you're bigger than whatever that is dude
you're bigger than the moon dude
and my phone started acting up after we
went to this weird house oh
99 creepy crescent
that says
it might be that the reason for it
maybe
maybe because you dropped it because you
were so shook
um so uh please don't mess with this
wait let's go go go go go
a lot of pictures here that i had to you
you lose yeah okay oh wait am i supposed
to delete the haunted house for a little
movie
uh that looks um
familiar too like uh
i feel like i've seen this one before
too ah nice ah
this one i don't know
it's just so cool
i don't see your face y'all
cowboy babe up oh
oh okay this is dragon ball
ah this is is this this is your own eyes
and the other one is something else
don't you think that looked more like
something um i don't i don't like
i know that's free i'm sorry sorry oh
sorry i don't watch these animes
i miss i mix something up right i know
three i know three
i didn't watch it though
right the swimming show
wait he likes
oren high school club i know that one he
likes all these
cute bullet animes
screenshots oh
what happens if you load that
guys try loading it
i can't load uh qr codes
do you have a web discussion no i don't
guys can you load it can you scan this
try try try
maybe that's the code maybe that's the
code that i have to input i don't know
do it it can't be it have it has to be
safe it takes a you to youtube video
which one rickroll
it plays a youtube song
it's going to some stair beyond to see
what
it's an old animation
ah yeah i gotta um advertise your old
works here i respect that
oh wait that's it i don't know
okay what happens if we delete the
this one
what was that
did you do that with my phone
yeah but i think that was fine
no it's not
the truth is i don't remember any
passwords ever
maybe
did i do something good about no maybe
that was like
a warning
eh calls how about calls
i don't look at my calls and i don't try
to call anyone either i'm sort of
really out of minutes
only 22 seconds left and i still need to
call my grandma okay internet internet
spin one card
ally google
don't look at my search history okay
wait let me look
breakfast nearly breakfast many pancakes
sleep sounds what's the best password oh
i can actually ah
ghost oh
interesting because of the haunted house
as well
and it i think
and i would have thought of it i'm going
to forget about it immediately
aha you did seem to have forgotten about
it
unlocked enable ghost mode
with the password ghost
i could have guessed it also because
like i thought it was such that here up
here it says goes to
yeah funny
ghost mode activated is that good
wait we still didn't save the uh uh
do
like clear the the riddle
uh
what happens with the vacation photo
it's gone wait what
ghost mode
wow we have a new
we have a new mode okay wait i really
don't understand this game
huh
am i supposed to see something new oh
this doesn't do anything here
gotta find ghosts oh
ah there must be a ghost here come on
now
would there be a ghost here
oh
okay
huh really am i really looking for
ghosts
right in my eyes
get rid of it okay
okay okay i think the first time it
happened was um correct
was good
you saw that i saw it i was definitely
strange okay okay okay i'll get it now
we found um
we found a picture we did uh
we deleted two pictures wait do we have
to delete another one
wait this is a different qr code look at
that that that makes it a different qr
code no
i'm not sure i think
i think now it's a different qr code
try it guys
was it the same oh okay
oh
no i didn't find anything here
so
like can i do ghost note here
[Music]
i'm guessing one more thing i'm supposed
to find unchanging photo true
that's kind of sus
wasn't in the vacation now it wasn't
normal photos
do you think there's something strange
about my breakfast um
oh wait i see it
really slightly oh wait i it appeared
more when you wait a little bit longer
okay
[Music]
isn't that the dad
oh god next time i go on a vacation
it'll be something safe like go guarding
or nude [\h__\h]
no more creepy old badges of dark
legends secrets is contaminated by the
vengeful souls that reside with it i
swear
yeah don't go into haunted house it's
really dangerous man i feel like i've
just moved two bubbles on my live at
back cause to the left after all that
that was super terrifying can i have my
phone back yeah i hope it's i hope it
works now
man [\h__\h] ghosts everywhere looks like
you fixed it it's nice to have a
functioning phone again it's like i'm
reconnected to society take that
actually looking people in the eye and
talking to them directly
thanks should i say random friend ah
we're his friends
i never knew i could fix the phone
that's [\h__\h] up like that
okay
it's a lot of work since the family is
practically made of food allergies and
intolerances but i'll manage thanks so
much for all your help i'll see you
tonight
can you have wheat oh i'm fine
i'm fine i i can eat pretty much
everything in theory
oh i don't have to have to go back
hey it's me bad the alligator the one
with the hat hello pat
it's almost ten can you come back
someone came over to my table and
threatened me
with a good time
they gave me a coupon yeah we've heard
this story before
tomorrow
here's a couple that i got last week if
you come back i'll give it to you no
questions asked
[Music]
sure him we didn't get this option
before
[Music]
i'm busy
sorry pat
b
she calling me a [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
[Music]
like maybe two hours later
oh we were discussing
okay okay no press maybe when you come
back you can take a look at it maybe
hello
no
and now two hours later that means i'm
wasting a lot of time just talking to
him
i need to meet these other people how
about you you're not supposed to be here
linda
you look very small
i'm waiting for a blind date so if you
see anyone that looks like i love the
bae let me know
[Music]
oh please
leave me alone unless you want a knuckle
sandwich
seriously do you want it it was the bar
special of the day but i got the heart
to eat it now because
because the nervous guts
anyways what do you want i don't really
have time to talk right now i'm waiting
for somebody
no maybe there are no show oh he's gone
off the bed
it's him he's not magical
people call me the knife on the on
account of my design containing sharp
edges
and how i poked my eye out in a freak
jackal lantern carving extent back in
the fourth grade oh [\h__\h] in the fourth
grade
and cause i'll catch you
[\h__\h]
out of the extra care
if i catch you in the hall without a
pass
i'm a guidance counselor for miss petty
snoot school for snobby and gifted
middle schoolers
the nickname is just there to scare the
preteens to be honest
my morning voice
[Applause]
yeah i know pat who's asking i alright
right sorry i'm a little socially
anxious right now
and basically all the time
i've known that since high school and
the seniors got paired up with a
freshman buddy to turn to run the
three-legged race
i was the gym teacher tied the rope
around the relax pat flipped out and
thought he was being kidnapped started
running like a maniac down the football
field with my gym pad still pants still
attached to him
so i got my other nickname birthmark
[Music]
thank you for that information that was
all i needed to know
since then we've been good pal suspended
love that we're a little guy
ah
he's not mad at him for doing that
ugh you keep pestering me did not tell
you i was waiting for someone
this is how i sound after smoking
cigarettes for 50 years
but i don't smoke
so
it's a
an alternate timeline
i gotta be honest with you i ain't
really waiting for nobody i'm just here
at the bar to practice being casual and
meeting other folks you know uh in a
romantically like manner i always seem
to say the wrong finger and scare other
gators off
and i was was i supposed to know
complimenting someone's bulging neck
veins was weird
she looked real cool
but anyways between work and my somewhat
bad personality i don't care that much
it's so hard to just meet people in an
unweird way you know i wish i could just
practice or something
hey wait a minute that ain't a bad idea
if i could just find a buddy to practice
dates on it could be
way more ready when i could be way more
ready when the real deal comes along
i know you're only talking up to me
because
that sets you up one of those weird
wildling goose like chases but i got a
lot of friends to tell you the truth so
maybe if you help me practice so i could
help you out too
what do you say you want to go on a fake
date with a rusty ass like me oh um i'm
i'm kind of taken by pat
he just doesn't know it yet but okay
mack that knife make him blushy by
getting mushy
all right
dating sim
he goes up take a lonely lizard out on
the practice date okay click to decide
where to go what to do oh now we got the
evening
what can i also dress up like ah that
sounds like one of those online um flash
barbie games that i played where when
you first dress up you choose what to um
to choose what to what to wear and then
you choose where to go with your date
that was fun
online barbie games best
hmm
of course i played those of course
all right how do you feel about the
change of setting let's head over to my
workplace and you can help me out there
all right
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh my god
okay
we're in a different game now
welcome to the hallowed halls of the uh
my hand my hand even my hand is a normal
hand now
the alligator international school for
gifted youths
the kids are on a break right now so
it's only us lonely administrators
oh wait wait i'm the only one
i need a big favor from you
let me see i have a meet cute
tomorrow
and i don't know what to do or say or
feel my friend karen who works in the
front office set me up with a friend of
hers
i'm not usually the blind date type but
she says he's really dreamy tall which i
like and big which i also like bread
shoulders
she says he's a cool cool quiet type but
he has a sense of humor and a big heart
wait who's talking is he talking or am i
talking
he's talking right
his hands oh my god his eyes are too
realistic
[\h__\h] it
his hands
between you and me she said he's a real
dragon in the door
it it is a reference
yo
[Music]
i didn't believe you guys
i thought it was just a random alligator
with an eye patch
and i'm playing the game literally since
yesterday
what
another reference i actually
understand
oh my god
oh my oh my god
again
or
a real dragon in the doji i mean
he's gonna he's excited about me meeting
kenya right
[Music]
if you have my drift i get it now i
wonder what she told him about me
uh all this negative thinking is messing
with my mojo
you seem like the strong sun type on
you're cute enough that it intimidates
me just a little please you gotta help
me practice for my big date i need a
boost of confidence and i need it now
yay
i mean i'm cool thanks
karen arranged it all with my date we're
going on an adventure for stand out to
dinner and afterwards who knows
that you left
[Music]
is he really like this sonic
so um
what kind of adventure would you take me
on impress me
[Music]
is that a wrong answer
is there wrong answers here
but i feel like it would be ironic to
take him to a zoo
this fanfic is wild
it's not
sometimes
there are wrong answers probably the two
ones
eh
i can't fail it oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
impress him
maybe the beach
[Music]
you have to do this part five times oh
[\h__\h] ah
i think
eh
guard
they have no idea there's like no hints
and they all seem fine in theory
i if it weren't me
if it were me
um
i don't like zeus that much they're kind
of boring to me
um
botanical garden
i've been to a field they're nice
they're nice but i think i would prefer
the beach because i i rarely can go to
the beach
[Music]
let's just do what i would like
here's a guide great let's go well come
on i can't pretend we're going somewhere
if we don't go somewhere oh we're
actually going
the whole school is empty don't worry
oh we're just walking somewhere okay
hey the beach is pretty nice there's no
page we're just imagining it
that's a sweet idea okay i like the idea
oh no it's not really the beach we're
playing pretend remember
but it's only our first date i didn't
bring a towel or swim trunks or
sunscreen somebody got to go naked buddy
plus we're going to the dinner later
also isn't that your natural
what do alligators live in
i know i guess aliens live in lakes or
so not in not on like
ocean beaches right
they don't they don't live in
they live in the
sweetwater not salty water today that's
at least what i would imagine swamps
swamps and rivers
[Music]
okay okay then it's not his natural
habitat okay
am i going to be all sandy at the
restaurant
oh okay we're walking along the
boardwalk well that's nice
we should be riding on the horse imagine
two alligators riding on the horse along
the beach
wouldn't that be beautiful
mystery day probably looks great in swim
trunks
i wonder if we'll ever find out if
kirill looks good in swim trunks i can
imagine he does
some crocs live in the salt water
saltwater crocodiles are the only
crocodilian in life to venture see
so romantic
i'm glad we're doing this it's been a
while since i've been on a real date
like wait wait with this fake face it's
probably gonna fall in love with me
accidentally
everyone i date these days just wants to
watch a tv show on an old couch
don't
netflix and chill huh oh very wrong i'm
not above staying and i'm getting cozy
but i think i think the first date
should be really special you know
oh what's this
you brought me a present
are you imagining that too
well that is a change of pace
old-fashioned but in a nice way give me
a give me oh
so far he seems pretty girly i feel like
he would enjoy flowers i
personally also want flowers
out of these options i think
let's go with flowers
[Music]
there's a heart and likes oh [\h__\h] i
thought i had to click it
karen didn't warn me i was going out
with such a strawberry
i'm getting a little hungry do you mind
if we head to dinner we're first trying
this maybe
they were first trying this just by
going with personal preference
a reservation well you came prepared as
a dress to impress i see that shirt
really brings out your eyes
it's so stupid
it's not too much i'm trying to role
play but it feels a little silly
you're doing great though
sorry
i mean i'm blasting bombs stop
where did you want to eat i heard you
required the foodie
um
i
i want to eat somewhere fancy
but maybe this once we shouldn't go with
my preference
um
this one's tough
this one is tough
i think he's fine with not going to a
fancy place
[Music]
fancy on the first date yes
maybe i mean i like all options
i like them all but okay maybe on the
first i mean whatever can be something
else too
i would i would be impressed though
something cozy is fine cozy is intimate
um
chicago
[Music]
but we're completely ignoring the cool
option
a cool place
what is cool mean just interior or it's
like the food really like um
instagramable
he might like fancy to have a special
first date yeah maybe
maybe
i mean he's from the yakuza they always
ah no not sure
they either go to a fancy place or they
eat [\h__\h] instant noodles there's no
in between
whatever
[\h__\h] ah
[\h__\h] ah maybe he doesn't like it ah
yeah i got a table there yo i got the
[\h__\h] table there uh-huh uh-huh
he might be impressed
chess dude's the fanciest eatery in
alligator brooklyn i heard you need to
call mom's head to get a table there oh
gosh i'm super underdressed oh sh ah
do you think the matre
d
is going to judge me there's no way i
can oh i'm playing i'm playing i'm
playing [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
yeah let's go somewhere else yeah sure
i just know some noisy nancy is going to
get me get me kicked out for looking
like a puppy you don't look like a party
okay let's go somewhere i'm sorry i'm
sorry i'm sorry
no no no no this doesn't kill it
completely
i think that's probably like
it can't no it can't be wrong one wrong
answer kills the run
[Music]
okay okay
oh
seems like we went for
the school cafeteria
oh this is more like it so do you come
here often
you're sorry
i'll barely make it out of the house
myself these days
i'm so happy to be here meeting someone
new
give me a cup of it
oh
uh i think alligators really like
getting compliments about their teeth no
their tail too probably though but the
teeth are isn't
ah
i think
i think i'll go with the teeth
but isn't that a weird compliment saying
someone's teeth are nice
i think it's kind of weird but
but he probably likes it
okay let's try it
oh [\h__\h]
i knew it was weird
oh thanks
you have a nice smile too
[\h__\h]
how many how many uh mistakes can we
make here
come on my date's gonna be more charming
than that sorry i was kind of guessing
that it would be awkward weird but i
thought you know alligators they
they have really sharp teeth and they
eat things with that i mean
i'm going to pretend you said i was cute
and move on
that's what i meant
i feel like i can really be myself
around you it's been a while since i've
done this i mean not a long while it's
just it's just hard for me to meet other
alligators so i don't do this very often
stop laughing this is precisely why i
wanted to practice
what i'm trying to say is i'm having a
really good time with you
if you don't have any plans after dinner
wanna come to the spring festival with
me
sure you've lived an alligator in new
york city for how long and you've never
been to the east river spring festival
then you have to come with me there's
food carnival games and the whole thing
ends with a big fireworks show
all you say is put the checking head
over
flag down the waiter then let's get out
of here
okay
sorry i'm being such a kid even when we
lived in alligator jersey my family
would drive into the city for the big
festival thanks for indulging me as a
reward you get to pick the first thing
we do
uh oh
no no i've been coming here since i was
little it's your first time what looks
fun to you oh this may be our last
chance to not mess it up because we had
two mistakes
first
thing to do at a festival
i usually i think i always go for food
first
um
[Music]
so play a game
well we just went for food so yeah let's
not go for food again let's do a game
yes
okay
oh i love carnival games karen told me
you were pretty competitive
not like in a bad way
i'll tell you what if you wouldn't meet
a pla big platypus doll i'll definitely
be impressed is that a separate game
a reward win the game first buddy and
then we'll talk
he's um
he has quite the imagination
[Music]
what a night he's delusional but i like
him it's okay
a guy in the bear costume and all the
pretty lights you know for the first
time i you really seem to be warming up
to the festival i'm really if you had
fun you never know what this kind of
thing
i
i really wanted you to have a good time
to be honest i wasn't sure i was even
going to come out tonight
is adam
is that supposed to have a double
meaning
a lot of people are scared of me would
you believe me believe me
it's not like i'm some kind of scary
gang he's getting closer roaming the
streets at night and showing up wherever
repeatedly challenging the same person
to endless street brawls oh don't get so
close is he going to kiss me or kill me
while slowly building my reputation as a
mad dog who will fight anyone and
anything relentlessly punishing all who
stand in the way in in a way of my
personal goals is that a description of
good old majima
it looks like the fireworks are starting
come with me i know the perfect place to
watch
even them even those are imaginary
as i tell you the view from here is
incredible right it is
he's known as the mad dog yeah yeah
i think i
just by seeing him and like a dragon he
did seem pretty mad
[Music]
i love me
had fun tonight
hope you did too
for karen's sake i mean she takes
matchmaking really seriously and she's
been hounding me for months to finally
meet you
oh why am i talking about karen right
now come on just say the right thing i
guess what i'm really trying to say here
is i'm so
i'm so glad i met you
you seemed like a great person and it
was cool hanging out we should do this
again sometime i think we cleared it
okay speed run
unbelievable [\h__\h] we know some of the
right answers
great how do you feel about change of
setting let's head over to him okay
oh okay
[Music]
i think the beach was a neutral answer
but before we go the wrong one let's go
with it again it didn't seem wrong i
think there's a good answer a neutral
answer and a bad answer
because now there's no hearts but
there's also no angry marks
garden did you guys look up the right
answer
i don't want to cheat like that
um
flowers he liked flowers
[Music]
the restaurant though let's go somewhere
cozy this time oh it's a neutral answer
i guess
oh sorry i didn't read the text i'm kind
of um tired of doing the voice now sorry
mom gotta gotta be easy on my throat
let's just clear the game
um so perfect was wrong
how about
this
okay it's neutral
oh man i thought you were like me
telling you we have a long tail
[Music]
okay well at least it's not a wrong
answer
neutral is still good i hope
[Music]
uh let's go to the festival
uh
game was that neutral was that
did we get hearts for that
i don't remember
did we get a heart for
game was good
okay
yeah yeah okay okay okay
[Music]
and then
what was the last question
ah the compliment i think
no wait i already gave a compliment what
was the last thing
oh no that was already it
neutral is not good enough
okay
we're going not to the beach
but
to the garden
oh [\h__\h]
he doesn't like the
um
but why are there two nursery on oh no
he likes it he likes it
omg says
okay okay
zoo was indeed a bad answer
yeah i thought i thought it would be
awkward to see other alligators behind
fences maybe
flowers
okay
uh
like cozy was neutral too or i think it
ended up being neutral
let's go somewhere cool
right
[Music]
yes yes okay
and your scales are so shiny
you're welcome you're welcome
[Music]
so far so good
game was fine so let's go for a game
again okay
i think that was the last one
prison for animals
oh so temporary memorial i got an
achievement you guys don't see it but it
seems to be a
reference to
[Music]
only took me a long time
look at him now
that was actually kind of freaking
magical i see he's falling in love with
me now
if i'm being totes real with you
well i really feel like i learned a lot
actually
oh geez
what a sweetie pie
i feel kind of funny
kind of floppy in my goods
but must be that knuckle sandwich coming
back to haunt me
yeah that's the ticket
that said i don't really know a lot
about the event but i know that i'll be
there at least on account of being
invited by pat's mom maybe we can hang
out at the event i mean not like outside
of it like it's a thing
that's your laughter
what a character
oh my
so do we tell the girl that
i wonder if that does anything
they're tall handsome and a very
successful lawyer just like me you're a
lawyer too
oh wait you're waiting
you weren't oh maybe it was him after
all the other guy with the caterpillar
eyebrows
what are you staring at some put those
papers away before a young can clear out
your scope
what do you think you're tough guy or
something you think you can roll in here
in a pit stop suit not dissimilar to my
own age
a sheriff passing glance of me
and i don't also i really i really don't
like being looked at
eva in public i always take it as a
threat
like in the bus store and the train
ourselves i feel like there people look
at me because they
like
think something negative of me
which is probably thinking too much into
it but i still don't like it and um
and the thing is in austria compared to
japan
many many more people
stare at others
even when you stare back at them they
continue staring even when i give them a
look like this
back
they continue to [\h__\h] stare they
don't read the [\h__\h] air the room
in japan people mostly didn't stare at
me or if they did it only stared at me
until i stared back but here they stare
continuously
i hate it stop staring at me
[Music]
well you've got another thing coming to
your party and it ain't nothing good
around these parts i'm the toughest guy
you're gonna meet
so don't think you can sible into my bar
and lock eyes casually with me across
the room you'll be sorry when i pull
those babies out and make them into twin
yakis
for a moment i thought he meant um like
actual babies in my tummy
i suppose you mean my eyes or oh [\h__\h] he
means my
eyes is he a yakuza too
oh let's guess what the red sauce is but
you ain't
nothing
no i mean implying the character has
babies
my name is bobby blue eyes and don't you
forget it because it's going to be
answered on your tombstone wait on your
tombstone would be your name my name
would be uh
just because i got confused about our
society's rituals surrounding mortality
doesn't mean you can look away
we're having a conversation here oh now
i'm not allowed to look away
what
pet that little jabroni is my first
cousin once removed kind of like how i'm
about to remove your eyes
it really has something with my eyes man
he really likes
eyes at the same time really dislikes
them
as i mentioned previously in the
conversation
no i don't think the red sauce thing was
too far
maybe it was a bit too fun
i'm testing out some new tough guy
material tonight so it's a bit hit or
miss ah all right yeah you're just uh
acting right now testing your material
okay okay you're not really that mean
are you
[Music]
bobby ain't spelling family secrets
um we'll see about that you have a game
for me unless
real proof you're tough to me the
toughest guy in alligator new york city
it ain't gonna be easy though and i'll
make sure it does so let's see when we
play a little game called free finger
philly
because we don't have more than three
fingers okay
i did
no i'm an alligator today excuse me
this game is reading me
reading me too easily mirror this kaku
without getting a boo boo nice to meet
you
i'll play
carefully watch how bobby stabs the
table copy his pattern on the other side
be careful to avoid your fingers okay
is it like a like the knife between the
fingers is that what we're doing
you're ready for this tough guy
okay
oh wait is that mirrored or
yeah no
[\h__\h] okay it's not my rent
[Laughter]
what was that watch me
sorry i had to test it out
okay
i think it was here
uh-huh
easy
okay round one
oh you did that four times that's
impressive but how many more times do
you think you can pull that off
well as many as you want three rounds
probably round two
why do i have a different thing now wait
was that
here
okay
okay easy
hi
hi i'm so slow now
why did i change your knife
hi
fine
okay easy pattern the first one was a
bit more difficult dude
gotta make it more complicated than that
maybe next time i'm gonna have like a
real knife not a butter knife oh [\h__\h]
well five times not bad but let
something happen shall we
oh oh dear
next time i stop myself it's gonna be
probably a bloody situation
i don't know where i got that from i
don't know
what is that that was terrifying
terrific yes perfect for a tough guy oh
let's keep going yeah yeah i'm not
playing with spoons here
boring [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
now that is enough yeah be careful i
might just accidentally cut your fingers
buddy
let's see how tough you are when they
cut your ububies
uh one and two and three
and four
one more huh
i have a photographic memory
just kidding i don't but this is too
easy
nice
oh another one
okay okay i remember everything
two times here one time outside one time
the other outside and another one here
nice to meet you indeed
hey not bad kid got all the way to six i
bet you thank you real tough guy with
those increasingly ludicrous knives you
really had on your percentage
well check this out
you thought i would read this personas
huh
[Music]
that is so
cute
ah
collateral damage in my heart
oh my heart
oh my heart i pulled a little a little
better than this little ball finger
[Music]
i may never play bass guitar again
critical it's a [\h__\h] critical
critical hit man in my coconut broccoli
knives
they'll believe me with my bad night and
my mystery i am in misery
the silence is slowly killing me oh yeah
you only got me mountain response free
spots spots
let me blow
them up in the mopping them up we got
them all except the bartender
harry
i've not seen you around here before i
think i'd remember a face like that so
distinct and clearly visible
oh
you're not gonna talk much more
what's a tall drink of water like you
doing in a place like this
everyone else here is more a riddling
half glass of yogurt up run up if you
know what i mean i have no idea what
you're talking about
yeah i guess we're done here
i think we're done here
[Music]
let me know if i can get you anything
like a drink or a sammy awkward shoulder
massage
yeah i think we're done
the exit
i was just gonna say the exit isn't even
really there
i got two puzzle pieces here oh i
thought there was only one in like one
location
okay
um
next location
i guess
yeah next location but do you guys mind
i i need a moment i think i wanna i need
to fill up my
my humidifier it hasn't been running uh
and i feel like i need it today
oh sure
this goes down oh you don't need this
skirt you have me what the hell
let me just fill up my
humidifier brb check the montana
[Music]
water water
oh
[Music]
okay
what
one second
[Music]
me
hmm
[Music]
who's the cutest cat in the whole wide
world
it's movies
[Music]
who's the softest cat in the world
smoothies movie is the softest
who's the fluffiest that's strongest
but the softest is smoothie
[Music]
um
sorry i picked up a cat along the way
picking up those
kitty cats
yeah they're both the cutest
[Music]
all right is there puzzle pieces out
here too
yeah
and actually it's easy to find because
what
well that's not a secret oh wait i can
go for the alleyway
i like girls girls girls i like girls
girls girls i like girls i like girls
girls are cute girls
my hit single
it's my hit single girls girls girls
watch god not come let's get that
let's go in are there girls in here
eh
[Music]
uh-huh
um
[Music]
oh we're learning about girls who are
like big girls in the history
[Music]
first lady of physics
there are indeed girls here
i was expecting some kind of cabaret
dr wu
proved a theory of physics that reshaped
how we think of subatomic particles
that's so awesome
but wait there's more
oh
oh oh
wait that's a puzzle please not
okay oh okay
is any one of these gonna give me a game
i wonder or all of these
are they all family i doubt it
hey you know my beloved movie franchise
space flight episode seven return of the
guy remember when banana again cloud is
revealed to be the guy it just feels
like people really misunderstand his
character
is that a reference i don't get it
she's so cute and around
oh this is also affirming i'm
approaching max validation makes me want
to strike right out of here and start a
revolution
i love around years
i'll return that advocacy talks
all up and down the east coast but this
one by far has the best lemon square and
brownie selection
sounds good
[Music]
excuse me i'm currently trying to take
notes on the material so shoot okay
are you sh
am i in the long room this is definitely
not a support group for people who have
grown too emotionally attached to
it sounds like a problem that maybe some
of you guys have
just kidding you can never be too
attached to kiara
it's okay
sounds familiar
[Laughter]
hey emily
yeah
you want to go get sushi burritos after
this i know we're trying to save money
but i hear the siren song of the
sushirito calling me
you had me as hey
cute
same story
confusion the fusion of two stars
crashed food so different from each
other and it's so delicious as one
i wonder what other tasty combos of
cuisine were missing
like ships from tonight
i don't know you're enjoying the food
over there ah share some with me
welcome please sign our guest book
oh i would like to
sign here for a mailing list
and cookies
sign here too right here right there
great i really need a cosigner for my
small business
the faulting gail that's what they call
me down at the credit union oh it's a
fraud
is there any there we go
girls girls girls girls girls girls
girls girls indeed many egg girls so
what about you
oh someone new have a seat we're just
about to get started
oh no okay i guess there's really no
family members here oh go on
wow wee
[Music]
i guess they're not here okay so time to
leave
click the empty chair have a seat
[Music]
oh wait okay
now we have to listen to that again
hi
hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi
hi hi hi hi hi hi yeah i just got puzzle
pieces too
no i clicked on it but no no it doesn't
do anything
[Music]
two puzzle pieces but no family badges
okay
okay okay
guess we found like a secret there
uh then we're done with this area
because we also talked to them
[Music]
what okay
i guess how do we leave again ayah here
ah
another one
yeah we're doing fine now
we talked to the alleyway guy yeah but
he's like dead now he's solid we did him
a solid remember
so i guess we don't have time pressure
right now we can just uh continue going
somewhere else now um
this was the
this was the unsavory part of town right
let's go to alligator memorial park
oh
[Music]
next time next time there's one up there
i need to remember oh wait we weren't
here before
please don't click and drag on the grass
[Music]
thank you for the hint now i know that
there's more to this ah ah we were time
limited last time we only talked to her
so there's still a lot to do here
wow nice park eat emergency i love this
oh there's our guitar playing friend
ah
scared
is that a
hint the
[Music]
grass what are you doing behind those
bushes creepy
there's probably a puzzle piece here
come on
found it
what about you in the back
oh no here's something neat
oh i like pavilions like that
like and sound of music
hi
did you know um did you know this gazebo
here is haunted by um like 100 million
ghosts
it's true my cousin giovanni told me
that's why i'm playing over here
wait valentino he's um
he's uh um yeah from the valentinos from
the prince of the princess uh that we
met
you know just in case i can meet um i
want um so we can be friends oh he likes
girls it would be nice to have a ghost
pal instead of being ghosted by a pals
oh
no why won't anyone ghost you cutie pie
[Music]
but my mom usually calls me the other
one or who left this here
poor boy no it's being neglected
why
sometimes bonnie milligan calls me
squids at reese's
my teacher says it's just cause she
likes me
but i think it's because i sometimes
smell a little fishy since my bedroom is
the spare utility freezer on the back
porch guys can we have a fundraiser for
him
there's a lot of fish in the freezer
[Music]
i think that's my cousin like the cousin
that comes after cousin
like the sequel to the cousin second
cousin i like that he shares his
meatballs with me and always plays fun
games look at him you're so cute i want
to squish his cheeks
so happy
[Music]
pat is a nice guy he makes him happy too
like this one time we both run in
circles to see who could do it the most
part one and i and only for up a little
he's so cool
i'm so so excited because i get to see
pat and giovanni but i'm not supposed to
talk about it because it's a surprise
shall we play should i play with you
i might talk about it a little if you
play games yeah let's play games with
you i want to help you oh you you're
lovely you should know that
when i'm playing hide and seek i've been
practicing okay hide and seek yeah you
hide i seek okay don't worry this time
this time
you're not gonna have to hide for
72 hours because no one actually was
looking for you
i can totally see that happening
him going to his mom and be like mommy i
want to play hide and seek and she'll be
like yeah like she'll be like yeah okay
one two three four five and then she'll
just not look for him
hiding sheesh
this kid thinks he's hot stuff at hide
and seek wait for him to hide and then
help him win okay
okay
[Applause]
[\h__\h] accident ready
wait am i not supposed to find him
wait why is the alive gone
am i supposed to
like give him like the feeling that he's
such a good hider that i can't see him
one more okay maybe that's it okay okay
i'm sorry
i mean okay
he laughed he giggled
how long are we doing this
there we go
i ain't so good it looks everywhere
except for well
one more one
oh my god
oh oh
is this bush new here i don't think that
bush was here before are these
skyscrapers they're totally new
is that a real alligator or a puppet
precious boy
thanks for playing with me
i win we both won we both won
and a lot of fun maybe tonight a team
and we can play together again i love
you ah
it's a surprise but giovanni told me
there might be cake i haven't had cake
since the last time my mom remembered my
birthday which was
well anyway thanks again come play with
me anytime
[Music]
i will remember your birthday if you
tell me what it is
oh man
let's talk to this guy
mandy
but according to my hat the song i play
is sweet and if you don't agree with
that i do not give receipts
[Music]
no game
the breeze the side is she sighs the
fountain cools my manduin does holler
so it's no surprise or clever rules that
i expect a dollar
oh i got no money with me i think
[Music]
i was having a neat emergency but i got
pulled in by mandolin mandy's serious
siren song as usual i love listening to
him play and when he tells me to stop
sitting so close and rhyming couplets
huh
what a guy
[Music]
oh
wait did i basically just steal some of
his money
make a wish guys make a wish
i'm throwing money into the fountain so
that you guys can make a wish
pew
pew i love the sound it makes
i wish that was he wasn't so poor
he ah
he's nice of you
[Music]
that's oh yeah i almost didn't see that
one
hey don't look at me
okay okay we're not looking at you yo is
he grilling some noise mate
here's the one that he was hiding behind
our little boy
hey yo credo how are you doing today
my other day above the ground right
just a little mortality joke for you
since i can only rely to my subconscious
fears through deflection
hi deflection i'm dead
i don't even know
that i'm doing it some days though are
better than others and though today is
one of the better days let's see this
big guy right there a sweet piece of
meat metal uh he's a grill mess maestro
300x and the indisputed king of the
finest grilling technology man has ever
known
can't wait to fire this baby up and do
some proper firing he's such a dad
all i gotta do is figure out how to
start it
and cook with it
and hopefully stop it before the rising
flames consume us all
y'all be better not get too close we
should just silently walk away
my student's calling mr mom jeans behind
my back but you can call me tony
tell you the truth though you can call
me whatever you want so as long as you
don't call me late for my dinner
i've got this by two organs of intense
meat and radioactive food colorings for
several decades my best besties are
behind me
of course i know pat that's one of my
boys
the smaller one of them the smaller one
of them that wears a hat he's a good kid
but a little skittish a bit of a hair
trigger on him but when you want me i
think that one could have used a little
more time in the oven
i got my affection for heartless
critique i learned it from my father
[Music]
oh
hi my father i'm dead
oh wait that's pat's dan
he's a nice
nice dad
[Laughter]
[Music]
he's got the same eyes
those cute eyes
and pee and eyes and he's got similar
gestures actually
do it huh not sure how much i can tell
you about that unless you're talking
about my wife stopping her yammering now
there's an event i'd like to see
well actually i love her very much and
deeply appreciate the mutual respect and
the fashion that is present between us
sorry i only know how to communicate in
relationships for dated humor that stems
from the sexism present in sitcoms
oh
understandable yeah
it i guess it um
it
makes you uh copy it
if you watch it too much
maybe i should start reading those
square things with the paper oh comics
books uh
yeah maybe no i mean there's some
probably some
bad ones there too but also some good
ones
anytime you seem like a gator that knows
their way around the world let's say
hypothetically that i need a little help
getting this beautiful machine going
maybe my lips get a little looser when i
hear that fine just love me being cooked
to badly perfection so maybe you could
lend me a hat kiddo
uh
i've never
used the grill i've only been
the person to that
ate the food that came off the grill
the only thing i can turn on is uh
uh
uh what's it called again i i i can i
can use a yakitori grill
and and uh i forgot
uh what was the word again
magic pixie dream grill uh i mean uh not
the micro now not a microwave
now the minecraft the one with the
little shovels underneath
[Music]
not a fire pit no request yeah yeah
yeah i'll play though save this grill
masters from different disasters let's
go
problems keep spawning on this terrible
grill hold the correct tool over a
problem for the for two seconds to fix
it oh
okay fire extinguisher for fire
some air thingy for
uh
this
and whatever that is for whatever that
is oh dear okay
i don't know if i can remember that
let's try special problems and obstacles
i think i'll have to retry this a few
times
now get this baby going alligator
what a machine
okay a bucket oh my god
round one oh god
uh
problem
ah this one yeah okay good
yeah easy that was fast
yeah okay okay i'm good so far
hi
oh it goes away so fast i like it in
propane
ah
okay
[Music]
are you away with the fire
okay i think we're getting it i think
we're getting the hang of this i'm gonna
turn off the gossip and see if we can
really get it cooking okay oh dear it's
gonna get more difficult i gotta look to
the sides too
good good good
uh oh my what
i'm fine
[Music]
what's gonna happen
sus nothing's happening
kind of suss
what
what i don't see anything
oh [\h__\h]
wait i don't know what [\h__\h]
what is there go away
wait wait wait
wait wait wait what what what what's
happening what does that mean
oh my god
[Music]
what
blizzard on the tv
oh
blowtorch
okay
i think we can do it
what's with that bucket
[Music]
okay one more
try i almost first tried it
not my fault
go away fire and you go into
speed
bucket is essential
for what
everything dad has a frog bucket not a
hotel
frogs huh and there's gonna be on the
grill too
okay
oh yeah keep the hamsters running
what what does that mean what
uh
eh what do you want
don't fall asleep
what is what does he want
what does he want to get it it's a new
problem
[Music]
i need to blow this
cool him down
oh this is happy hallelujah
okay
isn't the danger gone
okay okay thank god oh my god
the water no the fan was fine apparently
we got him up and running again
wait what's this now
marty's
yeah
left side
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
okay i think i think it's all good i
think it's all good
man that was difficult
no the woman in the tv was fine i think
oh my god
thai hands ahead almighty saying i'll
build it
[Music]
thanks for helping me out today kiddo
about the event i can't say too much but
i gotta brag about the balloons i got
for it my boyfriend just loves those
cold food socks over there probably why
he loves his old mad hair so much too
my body is aging rapidly no one can stop
the forward cycle of time save tonight
kiddo hop don't be late
alrighty
whoa
what the father
he has that really strong dead energy
doesn't
he little giovanni
oh
[Music]
i'm not doing anything
i mean well that's not exactly true oh
i'm standing here um existing somewhat
my my snow just running from rockweed
allergies i'm not doing anything that
has to do with the soda machine though
nothing at all
[Music]
bug cream
mmm obsess i wouldn't drink that i need
me some dr pepper and some iced tea
oh i'm so funny just a totally cool
gator teen who hangs out at the park by
himself with the soda
he really like soda maybe yeah maybe we
should hook him up with virus
[Music]
you made my my cousin
yeah he's great i used to play a lot
more when i was a little kid but i still
think he's pretty cool sometimes he'll
meet me at the mall food court after
school and we get nachos
unless those intolerance oh my dad
doesn't let me have that stuff usually
because it makes me blow chunks
but pat doesn't mind holding my hoodie
back while i spill
pat is such a good guy
he's a total bro yeah
he is a bro
bra
even oh
huh
you know about it don't ya everybody
knows about it oh okay okay you got me
i'll spill my guts when i said i wasn't
doing anything earlier it was sort of
maybe definitely why
you say i saw the machine right there
trophies i'm a bit of a cool connoisseur
and this fountain in particular is a
beaut
all the best most classic flavors sodas
sorry they stopped making them in the
90s ah
sick lemon i haven't heard of these
flavors
it's like time stopped here holding my
pickle my purist organs in carbonated
bliss
once at this very spot i mix the soda
combo so great that the last of my baby
teeth disintegrated with a slight
whistle noise
sadly no matter how i try i can't seem
to get the flavor right again you should
drink water
you should stop drinking so much soda
that's probably why you're so nervous
so i was kind of hoping you'd help me
rediscover it maybe if we figure it out
i'm gonna help you with something
okay i'll do my best mix up the drinks
and see what he thinks hooked on tonics
okay sounds like a fun game
[Music]
try to follow giovanni soda instructions
move the cup to the right to see the
recipes then up to the fountains to add
a flavor
okay
when you're ready click on giovani to
start his taste test okay okay okay
i'm just trying out recipes
you have one recipe called those are
disorders i've already invented
how can i make something totally new and
different i don't know it feels like a
lot of pressure oh so i'm not supposed
to go by the recipes
am i not supposed to go by the recipes
because i'm supposed to make something
new
i guess um
it tastes a dentist ah okay never mind
i can't remember what it's like only the
dentist ira
that's s sun
plus lemon face melter
and do you want it or not
okay
do the recipes
dentist plus lemon face melter
okay
stick lemon
here's a face melted leo drink it
i'm cute
wait um okay i was not supposed to do
the recipes
yeah yeah okay because now i have one
life less okay
okay
so we are making new things what is the
recipe okay just i guess sure in order
to not make what's on the recipes
what that's right i remember dentist i
right now i hate this soda it tastes
like chemicals i need to wash that taste
out of my mouth give me the first one
fruit one oh coming up
coming up
there you go fruit number one for ya how
does it taste bubbly
orangey oh yes the sweet sugary rush of
the fruit one
the fruit one is the best most delicious
most addictive soda of all time it's my
very favorite maybe i can take
inspiration from one of my old recipes
can you look at my recipe card it made
me a cool guy too okay
uh
cold cola and fruit one
i like the way
he writes things down it's so cute his
little memos
so adorable
oh it's literally coming out in ice
cubes
all right here we go
must taste absolutely fabulous
oh
it's spiraling flavor yes this is
masterful you're a genius pasta bunny
let's use cool guy juice as a base but
how do i make cool glasses even better
that's the question oh no i'm cracking
under the pressure of my own success i
know how that feels i do that a lot in
games
let's try mixing cool catches and they
smell them together maybe does that
sound good
who got you some face melting time
smelter okay so we start with cold cola
and then fruit lemon a fruit one
and then dentist and the lemon
yo this glass can't even hold that many
juices
i'm sure this is not gonna be a sugar
rush for you
dangerous territory buddy
it's okay but i expected it to be better
take this let me think what's wrong with
this soda mix maybe i'm just bad at
mixing so this i guess it could be a
wheat flavored
does facebook have the bad flavor in it
the one from earlier mm-hmm combine the
two recipes again this time take out the
flavor i didn't like
the uh i didn't like was
dentist ira
alphago
yeah okay
okay
so three ingredients
there you go
drink a buddy
yeah shake it good
that's perfect totally nailed it
i'm going to name this drink
purpose delight
thanks for your help we did it oh that
was pretty easy
okay
it didn't mix the bugs bug cream in at
all
yo he's so excited and he's really high
on sugar i think
you're so that makes these skills i
truly are forced to be recognized
oh jeez
well good for you
i knew when i saw you there was a sticky
pimpled teen inside you just waiting to
be learned how to make the perfect
sugary concoction i've been preparing an
extra special beverage for pet it's
gonna be a killer you are awesome i mean
not like it will kill him he does get
pretty startled easy though some of the
most tend to make him dive action movie
style outplayed glass windows it's
pretty cool thanks again for your help
flavor master see it's not thank you too
i need a fruit candy now it's about time
oh man
pat
is it time
am i being forced to go
wait i think now i have a cat hair in my
mouth
oh well
oh well it's got it's it will be like
that
[Music]
it's amazing
it's almost fine i couldn't really use
your help do you know anything about
shoes and the wearing of them they're in
perfect could you meet me and come meet
me at my hotel room just make sure you
ain't full ah shoes the shoe thingy okay
all right
guy pretending all my
a statue of that full stream
no i'm busy sorry sorry we already did
that in the previous episode so we're
gonna as as we seem to be able to just
spend all our time getting to know
people
sorry pat
sorry
[Music]
elevator music
there's a good one
like real safe extra extra step did you
bring any hands and ties of band-aids
hello
let's just ignore him
he just talks too much our little pad
friend we're busy we're busy to make him
and get him the biggest birthday party
ever
[Music]
jp
that club looks like a duck
hey she must see my
[Music]
tell me more about it you know dad cloud
looks like two ducks
she was so much of a
so many supers all right he only looks
at the clouds what about you
gentle lorenzo
bro lean brolin broly bro lean i'm
begging you too please give me a hand
901 902
903 yo he do be lifting
well that's the highest number i know so
i guess that's enough
that's a weird
number and to stop that
oh
sorry bruce fiend i didn't see you there
shot in a total shadow by the mother
lift of my beefy board
you're not going to start hitting me
with a bone like the last one are you
don't worry it happens to me all the
time
you said um
become my personal trainer maybe
please
although i can't i i i i will have to
stop counting after 10 you know i can't
go up to 903 sorry you'll have to adjust
to me
10 is maximum please
for anything
me people call me lorenzo on account of
it being my name i'll walk downtown at
the brother fitness center at mini mart
being inspirational aspirational and
non-recreational i'm very serious about
my jumpers then
i get that i'm serious about my job too
can't you count 10 90 times no no no no
no i can't after counting to 10 one time
i
i i faint
uh um
unfortunately i need a break after that
pat bro that's for my real big bro well
not real being big it's kind of a mild
to medium sized bro as far as alligator
brothers go he's like the mid-size sedan
season of british
meanwhile i'm like the sport utility
vehicle of brothers assertively large
but a little empty feeling inside
[Music]
don't we all feel empty inside
i do
event you mean tonight to tell you the
truth bro relax you keep on changing my
name
i always want to secrecy on my own over
a bottle of whey protein and the stack
of those muscle magazines i keep hidden
under my bed my strong jaw is strongly
closed his strong jaw
so
closed
okay which bro am i now
no despite my problem for a gmo free
lifestyle i'm having a muscle tissue
issue muscle tissue i could use some
helpful
do i need to give you a massage
you see my visceral hugeness
and perfect health has been causing a
totally terrible rift in the most
important relationship of my life
that's right i'm talking about my bird
who's my best brew in the entire bralexi
it seems like alligators like birds a
lot you know the parrot and now this
bird one of the very few other animals
that show up in the game it's like we
have a natural
um connection going on
yeah yeah yeah
it even has a hat yeah it's a cute bird
see tiny tear is seen tarantino he just
can't seem to bulk up you're trying to
make him buff too maybe an account of
his name but also because of his loving
watching television and complaining on
the internet instead of complaining at
the gym like mike i've tried to help
little terry here beef up so he can roll
with my impossibly huge crew but he just
hasn't reached his full potential birth
tension we called as potential
um i can't stand to force my favorite
broski literally and figuratively leave
my enormous shadow
he's like flexing in every sentence
about how buffy is damn
i don't know if he even notices it
so what do you say bro stamina
can you do me a solid and make it more
so um
last time i tried that they turned into
stone but you don't have to know that
i i'll give it a try oh
that's that's me
before you find your bar to get with the
squad flappy bro
[Music]
click to make the bird flap his mighty
wings collect healthy foods and proteins
to make him strong
avoid the exercise equipment it hurts
yeah relatable [\h__\h] that's it
okay this is the kiara working out
flex those wings let's go swoleness oh
my god okay
why don't we get uh we want the food
right oh no no
[\h__\h]
burger
okay that's fine the top is fine
okay
it's really difficult
that's really difficult
hey
what is that
[\h__\h] i miss it again
but it seems to go on endlessly
as long as you don't
that was close okay come on get that
okay okay again
nice level one completed oh
my legs are buffed up oh my god
keep it going terence is into it okay
okay round two be more careful now
it's gonna be more difficult okay
whoa
not a single head look how above my
chest is mushroom strength is my
emotional maturity this is just an
expression of my larger commitment to
self-care
let's get those burgers apparently
burgers are good for getting buff i
always knew that oh oh oh oh first
banana oh god it's so fast i don't even
see anything oh [\h__\h]
oh
[\h__\h] uh
man we don't even see it coming he's
gonna be lucky
[Music]
[Applause]
i'm so proud to i always knew i had that
potential
yeah
do you even live bro
you're dead
[Music]
now now they look like a perfect couple
together look at them yeah
posing flexing those arm muscles
i'm flexing my eyes look it's as hard as
i can to keep tears away from flowing
but it's only barely working i guess
maybe what really needs to bulk up is my
ability to deal with positive emotions
and also my cough so it stopped falling
over my front over from my balance-like
core about the event tonight well it
doesn't have a way and i can tell you
death don't worry though i'm bringing my
own scale and have only been eating
protein bars and dehydrated iceberg
lettuce in prep
i'm gonna look my best for my little bro
thanks again for having me out uh me and
my terry out here brolivia
every time we're popping a particularly
grenade squat we'll make sure to think
of you
thanks
self thank you so much oh unknown
is it are we done
[Music]
i was just wondering since we've been
texting a bunch um
have you heard of the live street
station at all
i mean i didn't think so
it's um well it's been closed for a few
years not a lot going on there since
then
i still got some of the most beautiful
architecture of all the underground
stops in the city in my opinion
i really wanted to go there actually
um if everyone stopped right there maybe
i could meet you eh
why is unknown hitting on me really
no pressure or anything you'll probably
have to really help the conductor out to
even get axes it's
it's pretty ungrounded
[Music]
a secret character to meet unknown
waffle we'll find out who unknown is
okay i was actually on the floor that
time but i had fallen
related to laughing
anyway haha don't worry about knife
street you can forget what i said if you
want
we gotta meet him is this does that mean
we met everyone besides that person
maybe oh no we didn't talk to you though
but maybe you don't do anything jules
welcome to emergency where are you
hungry with urgency today
so
this is reference to
nah
slices which comes when the chips are
selling and you're going to add the size
on if you mean your deductible okay i
just doesn't seem to be a family member
if you're having a really emergency
close the game and go to your local
urgent care or greasy hot dog joint if
you're looking for dessert dance for
more sweet emergencies deal on the
fourth street dog get out of here
okay
i'm not related
i mean that person or the fact that we
just got that message from unknown i
feel like it would make sense
because i think
[Music]
we've seen everyone so we need to get on
the
on the
thingy
i guess they will meet everyone in
downtown too i think so
so let's say we go back to
there okay let me get that puzzle piece
let me get that puzzle piece this time
for real
there we go
what's with you guys any more puzzle
pieces
oh someone knocking you can come inside
ah
time to go to 9th street
oh hello there i don't usually get
visitors in the control room like this
[Music]
it's actually quite nice to have some
company besides the various rodents are
gently trying to eat my feet and ankles
oh [\h__\h] that sounds tough
the trolley company uh told us
conductors to start taking rat poison
foot baths before coming into work in
the morning yeah
i don't know if that's good for your
feet there must be a better way
wouldn't you know it all that did was
anger the rats and give me a trench
flipper exactly
there must be a better way
you know the trolley health plan doesn't
cover a trench flipper or gout which is
why i had to stop bringing my usual
fried ham bones in for lunch
i made such humorously oversized
lunchbox bench box
but not my humorously oversized joints
damn i can uh maybe give you a cat or
something for those rats call me clancy
it's a pleasure to make your
acquaintance unless you're in here to
rob me in which case i'd ask you kindly
not to take the dollar off in my breast
puck
no i don't need that money don't worry
about it
that's what my afternoon knows my
licorice snack liquor is that that black
stuff ew
i don't like licorice at all who here
likes licorice
i wonder if it's as 50 50 as you know
pineapple pizza
[Music]
do we say licorice licorice not me i
don't like it i don't i do i don't mean
oh it seems pretty fifty fifty
now i wanna do a poll
do you
do you like
liquorice size
yes no
okay go
for me it's a big no
[Music]
like iris
it seems like something she would um
yeah make a joke out of
but this one actually full once works
well
the others are stretches mostly but this
one would work well
maybe she should uh put out licorice as
merchandise
lick iris
[Laughter]
wow it's so 50 50 again
a little bit more no though
oh
don't tempt me with what
oh i hardly know her okay well you don't
have to you don't have to
okay
red licker is i don't know about like
red licorice i only know the dark one
[Music]
hmm
it seems to be an acquired taste indeed
okay thank you guys for voting
thank you
if i go down then i'll turn back into a
pumpkin
i'm just pulling your leg but i don't
want to chance it don't pull my leg
i'm chilling right now pat my grandson
grandson
grandpa
a funny fellow dad always wearing his
little hat and a bandana makes him
really recognizable though you know like
for marketing and such funny fellow that
pat
he's a cutie pie
the biggest kitty pie i've ever seen
now hold on even an old bag with my
memory remembers he's not supposed to be
spilling the beans my wife roo told me
quite clearly that i'd be in the
doghouse if i did and it's really
uncomfortable out there and full of dogs
real i think we've met her
before
say i could use a youngin like use help
with a little problem i'm having maybe
you could do me a favor it's about the
rats i'm not gonna eat them
that's for sure
i was going through my trolley
instruction manuals i found a few flyers
were torn up from the last time roo put
me in the doghouse
uh just uh married people's problems i
suppose you know how dog likes dogs like
to rip up things like manuals homework
and stable marriage is all
i'd like to restore them but the pieces
could be all over town now by gum since
you're already snooping around for
patrick could you keep an eye out for
trolley manual pieces
it's kind of late for that though it
okay it is a mini game is it is it a
mini game or a straight street car named
his flyer
okay no it seems to be a mini game okay
okay i thought it was like another side
quest
um
let's see what we can do
oh it's a puzzle
okay this kind of puzzle i can handle
the one where you have to slide things
around
no
that is my biggest enemy
um
start with the counter pieces this is
hopefully not like the puzzle in the
usual room
there we go
[Music]
uh i need a left side piece
what it i have no more left faces
all right let's do this
am i not missing some pieces that's the
thing right
oh wait are these the puzzle pieces i've
collected so far
that's why i'm missing things
oh so i can never complete this game
until i have all the pieces
oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] i'm so close though
well now i want the puzzle pieces too
we're only missing three pieces i feel
like you guys could even tell me where
they are
ah you only need 16.
three pieces short
[Music]
thanks again for helping an old
conductor out look forward to seeing you
again
wait are you not going to tell me that
i'm straight where's the knife street
how do i get to the knife street
pat
what is it
hey
stop ignoring me as bad please i need
attention
i know we haven't figured out what the
family has told me the very secret is
yet
but maybe we walk there together i'd
feel safer he wants to go now is that
okay i'm on my way no wait i need to put
in the family pictures oh
wait maybe there's a possible place
possible please puzzle please puzzle
please possible no no
we talked to you before
well hello unpleasant evening my good
job i didn't mean to startle you oh no i
didn't mean to start with you
you see it as within my very nature to
sculpt mysteriously around corners and
like in deaf salads as my mother was a
mysterious slipper designer and my
father was mysteriously absent
found one
[Music]
two missing two missing
okay i guess we gotta go to the party
ones
hey but
[Music]
hey but this
is this force now because i really met
everyone
or
um
because i wonder for you surprisingly
you want to finish a puzzle hello
about my best friend another one of my
best friends
okay
maybe i missed the is there a puzzle
here i wonder
is there any puzzle pieces here
investigating for rolly
yeah it's only the wallpaper that's
distracting
no i don't see any
i'm guessing there are none here
oh yeah
i haven't met them all
yeah i haven't met unknown am i all the
time i want to meet unknown
oh well
party time everybody
[Music]
sorry for ignoring you bro
so sorry but it seems like you figured
out
your problem with the shoes yourself
good job buddy good job so proud of you
i'm so glad you came back i've just been
guzzling tap waters and stress eating
these funny crackers their way to crave
me even though i'm not going to wear
them i want and got all my shoes out
anyways i think just for the company
it's scary being alone in here you know
the event is about to begin but maybe
since you're here nothing bad will
happen
are we doing the maze again
this counts as something bad happening
on you
scary
do you have a flashlight i'm scared of
the dark you know flashlights for
slightly less so
i've heard this before
hey you found one do i look like that
one video by alex and the queen
hopefully with this we can make it for
the corridors of the hotel to the
bathroom ballroom where the event is
safely
just walk really close to me okay well
we have no way of telling who or what is
out in those twisty holes
don't worry i'll protect you
i already know the way i think
maybe
love the music here
[Music]
why did i get surprised
oh damn it
don't be scared cuba
how about here come on here
[Music]
oh probably probably not the right way
or is it uh
no no not we'll have them um we won't
desert disturb them
oh no no no scary thing to look at oh
we're back we're within a circle
running in circles
yeah
down here perhaps no this is a dead end
oh my god
it's easier said than done even though
i've done this before but i don't
remember
eh
maybe i do have to go here hold on can i
no
down here i didn't see that almost
[Music]
here maybe
oh
was this the right path
yeah it might be
yeah it feels closer mandy was there
mandy rocking in the loading screen
there we go
happy birthday
[Music]
everyone is this everyone this is
everyone
we're so
oh
i don't i don't want you to feel like
you're bad at hiding but i want to talk
to you
oh hi again you found me
thanks for always playing next time i
look for you
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
all right you can look at my cards but
don't go around telling everyone you
meet about it copies
if thank you i like you look at my heart
very curly little one
would be coming over here trying to get
a peep
don't let the greater public masses look
at my cards okay okay i understand
[Music]
the dentist i was getting a little too
literal for me
because
of the soda of messing up your teeth
[Music]
and so i got grounded from soda for a
billion years and i'm only allowed to
have fizzy fruit like crack which is
just carbonated water that the lemon
sneezed in or something i already missed
a sweet sweet chemical burn off dr soda
pickling my small internal organs
oh man it's better for you though trust
me
who else is new uh
let's do our
our new buddy
who fell in love with me totally because
i'm so charming understandable
uh thanks for earlier i ended up
canceling the
date because
we're not cause i was nervous anymore
because he left me i was actually kind
of wondering if
um
you weren't free
i told you
i can't even read anymore i'm just
almost embarrassed yeah
yeah
um you're new
[Music]
tell anyone if i want you so early and
they'll break your kneecaps into another
pieces that the old paint can't blame
for john
oh [\h__\h]
i was sad
oh that's so the painting is so cute
oh cute
bird
oh talking to lorenzo okay i want to
touch the bird too
i want to sit still for this long it's
harder it's harder than that time i did
that squad the phone and my pants split
dude the meaty glute option what
what
at least
at least then i got new yoga pants and
raised a hundred dollars for guys
without thighs
[Music]
it's an important organization for yoko
okay i'll get that
you're new to i think i think no no
you're not yeah yeah i get it i get it i
get it
uh
your new pyramid uh friend
[Music]
uh i'm only over past that abandoned mrs
hooper dude's home for a spooky one
thousand eight hundred shoulders of
course and i would wouldn't you know it
my phone stopped working it
all it does now is seeing ring around
the rosie in a slow haunting manner and
try to order a stick and hoop with my
credit card
his phone is broken again i need to
repair it again
um
you're new
uh this is the worst party i've ever
been to
it's simply dreadful even worse than
last year's
and get out of here
you unthankful little [\h__\h]
even worse than the wrap party for the
gucci modeling shooter
that's gucci adult-sized baby bonnets
for strange alligators
even though it's in the release party
where they fought my ex-boyfriend the
house music dj run through the river
claymore i for sure wasn't anywhere near
there of course but how awful
simply dreadful
and am i
did i really get everyone in here does
someone know
[Music]
i'm dad
i would love to
what did we forget talking to
[Music]
you're not new i think i talked to
everybody who's new
uh where's pat got it there
[Music]
my beloved
ah the one that turned to stone ah
okay okay okay
okay
ah
your special my special friend too
follow time
for your time again
this time i'm gonna be
this one
because the the snoop it looks like a
heart it's
cute and
this one
and this one
[Music]
that it looks stylish again
oh
i like that hair let's do this one
did i do glasses last time i'm gonna do
these oh they look cute i look cute
[Music]
oh pretty eyes
oh
okay let's do like this oh fancy
oh i like the round tee if they're cute
let's go with them i would hurt nobody
with those teeth
looking fetch so fetch right thank you
wow so many i'm so close to greatness
and completion there's not much space
for me um
one second
oopsie [\h__\h] uh maybe on
maybe on that side
everybody wait i'm like myself a bit
smaller
[Music]
there we go
okay i'll be here
and snipping too
[Music]
okay
snipping two
and cheese
yay
[Music]
wait wait one more one more one more one
more
one more
[Music]
cheese
oh cool that one's better
that one's better
beautiful
ah safe
sift
[Music]
i wonder how many are missing
the stone guy and the unknown but
besides that i can't think of anybody
oh
wait wait
is that true ending
what give him a hug give him a hug
huh
i
i could never
do something like that to my
pet
no
lies
fake
is that true
no
this is how it ends
with birthday boy going splat you might
still make a lens
and you may yet still save pat
what do you mean safe huh
[Music]
why
why did this happen why is there a bad
ending
why
did i do something wrong
i'm gonna save him
the family tree
it is not the true ending it's
definitely a different ending we didn't
have that before
i need all the badges
why did it not happen before then
[Music]
i unlocked bob's nap time more mysteries
await you more
bob's nap time
but wait there's more what
oh my god
there's more
how much more
bob's nap time but bob is the is the
waiter here no
check the tree i will
okay
hmm
damn
okay let's go outside
[Music]
and uh
talk to mom also i want those two puzzle
pieces
was there one more here no i don't think
so
mommy
or maybe maybe we should do it
afterwards uh after we get the
last people but okay we have enough time
now i think because we talked to almost
everyone
i do have to do it from the beginning
i hope not
okay
all right
they see me rolling down there uh let's
start with it with a youngling you are a
cousin oh nice
little giovanni
oh
occupation puberty
i don't know i don't know where you go
you just gotta test it out no you
wouldn't go there
no really
no
oh wow
gentle lorenzo was a brother of pat what
the [\h__\h]
maybe i was told that and i forgot
uh you're together with your bro but
wait uh here
yeah this one i know
you're also here
and then the small one who's been
neglected
also goes there where are you there you
are
wait oh
think
you're stuck okay ah i don't quite
remember where you're supposed to go
avoid the knight knuckleball
oh oh the knife guidance counselor
guidance counselor
um
i don't remember
there we go
influenza exactly that is what she is
you're one of the oldies but goldies
and then you
hmm
who are you again
ah
you are also a dad
and our pyramid
oh pyramid perfect tell jared some
blocking monolith
oh wait i'm so sad i'm always sad
apparently
wait are we missing aya oh dad
oh wait no that is not that old uh where
where is your bag here i know but you
would go here obviously
two time tony retired dad loving life
beautiful
okay so i'm missing one two three four
five
one of them is maybe the unknown person
one of them is the solid guy
um
one of them maybe we're gonna find out
with bob's side story
okay five people missing
um
oh yeah we failed the game in the tram
too right
okay okay okay okay
so let's go
uh
[Music]
it was the unsavory part of town right
and
wait
[Music]
yeah i need to play with you
still missing some pieces he doesn't
even talk to me the whole story anymore
okay
um
what was this again
huh no wait it's a puzzle piece thing
i'm so stupid but i have one more now
damn it
i mean okay i'll try to find two more
pieces
i didn't mean everyone downtown
well let's do him first
i hope i don't mess it up again this is
like this is one of the few ones you
can't repeat so
[Music]
let's get solid dude
oh not solid
oh wait i wanted to move it over yes i
hope that helps me putting it on my
drawing tablet
i'll do my best i'll focus
don't want to fail another time
okay
let's go
this should work this should work
oh but it's pretty big the screen is so
big here now
okay but it looks fun
very accurate at least
aimbot on sniper kiwawa it's happening
the cell phones were right let's go
round two
[Music]
it doesn't even get reset at that point
so that's kind of stressful but i knew
that that was happening
[\h__\h] i killed a butterfly i think but
that's okay
[Laughter]
he's enlightened
i'm starting to feel the cosmos oh god
there's one more round isn't there he's
picking up wi-fi oh my god how are you
doing then
don't miss it
[Music]
the bees the wasps i was slapping his
face by accident oh man
oh yeah it was so close
holy [\h__\h] he's he's reached a new level
of enlightenment
hello my star joe
we're chris
the crystal channeling and staying
modestly hydrated like advice on social
medias i've been able to reach my most
powerful form
what a freak
i'm still the eight and you've known and
adored for so long
so long with a new more powerful aiden
haven't been paid in weeks
i'm so hungry
ah just kidding i don't feel the human
desire for food in my new astral mode
hey
did you just hear an ice cream truck
oh no reason i just like the song
attract place it's a real ball
no i'm not crying
i can now tell you a bit a bit about the
event now since i'm
a being of pure energy and knowledge
given form
but also being that's like extremely
good at keeping secrets man
what little i can tell you is that it's
a concerns path for a certain reason
that's really all i can say i don't want
lizzy to get too mad at me for spilling
the beans she's got those angry little
sister hands
even beings of pure peaceful energy are
average to tiny sister punches
thank you again for your spiritual
guidance all you have done here today
will not soon be forgotten at least not
for the 45 minutes of short-term memory
i have hey did you hear an ice cream
shop
oh it's a tough one
all right is there any puzzle pieces
here left oh yes one more one more one
more
should be manageable
we did definitely talk to everyone
inside though
so let's get uh moving
to downtown maybe
am i missing someone in downtown
[Music]
we don't need to talk to him right now
because we already
three other people
huh
but i didn't meet here really oh i guess
we ran out of time here too because we
uh we went to pat
wait that's the sleepy pens
i talked to you george before
um
[Music]
are you new
let's go into the antique shop i guess
are you can i talk to you wait wait i
just saw another puzzle piece
i'll check it later oh
there's more than ah there's more than
you need so you don't have to find all
of them i can't i got it now
i was uh
thinking that that might be the case who
will we not talk to
hmm
leonard
oh we talked to leonard
we talked to you
i think so
i've been waiting here for an hour
yeah we talked to you
sorry
uh
eel we don't need you anymore
[Music]
is there another room
no no i'm good
[Music]
found another one and there was uh one
here oh my god i'm on the road oh wait
this room what the [\h__\h] or is this
outside oh
no i want to talk to you what
[Music]
there's a lot of puzzle pieces here holy
[\h__\h] you can like farm puzzle pieces
oh yeah
i can't talk to anyone here there's no
one here
i mean not not untalkable
okay
um
[Music]
or did i miss something
like funny
[Music]
activate that not a rule so i need to
seal the deal on the big set i'm talking
huge
but we talked to her someone else
somewhere else no
and keep an eye on my granddaughter
napping and let me know if she's getting
fuzzy napping
it's not about bob's nap is it because
bub boy is a waiter you know angelface
is a very good girl so i don't insist
but you're having any weird promises
okay that sounds like a mini game though
and then we get maybe the the
uh that girl's
uh piece maybe okay okay okay okay this
is new
watch a totally normal baby just doing a
babysit nothing worried about it that
sounds really sus to me we did not talk
to him really
maybe we get two puzzle pieces from nana
rue and the baby
don't let ghosts possess this baby tara
go target goes by highlighting them with
the ghost finder on the right
damage goes by using the monitor
functions or with the brightest light
okay
[Music]
where how would i highlight them
what
here
and now
what
but i don't know i'm gonna i'll get it
huh
wait i'll let you almost stand
ah
okay
took me a while uh
okay oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
uh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] oh okay we get some chances oh
god oh god baby is possessed
the baby is possessed
bubble bubble walker john i'm sorry
oh they even have the right colors on
there okay okay okay round two okay
we're safe we're safe but the bar did
not get reset
the health bar
get rid of those
okay quick
pink quick
oh [\h__\h] there's so many
quick
yeah
make it higher again i want the blue one
oh go go go that one goes away with that
one okay okay
i have a feeling for it now
ghostbusters
i'm a ghostbuster
i'm a ghostbuster i'll take care of
those ghosts don't worry about it
referee
mini games are so well done in this game
i love them
oh sheesh
oh my what
are you [\h__\h] kidding me
um
uh [\h__\h]
[Music]
no
i can't do it the second time today
do you know anybody hold on i'll get the
yellow pages [\h__\h]
no let me do it again
ah
pat what do you want
oh can we skip everything and go back oh
man
uh
[Music]
but when we do have the
um
puzzle pieces
oh god but but now that i know how it
works we won't mess up um in the first
level anymore the second time
so we have two more lives that
we can uh work with
[Music]
i'll afford to restart the game ah cause
like it saves after a game huh
that sounds like a cheese strat
safe's coming in later alligator
ah that took a couple tries oh
i might do like everything too
oh that's just him okay
and how many people are we missing if we
if we consider that we might get two
family badges from that babysitting
maybe maybe two
and we're missing
one or no nothing at all maybe i don't
know i mean
um
i want to meet unknown
how was i supposed to meet unknown i
thought that the 9th street i thought we
had to um
[Music]
uh
completing the puzzle unlocks the other
area is that so
i guess let's go to the fun district
[Music]
oh sorry about that
sorry
no i have them all i have all you need
buddy
i'm completing the puzzle
[Music]
this one and this one there we go
complete though
i know that looks really nice there's
still some work to be done though click
that arrow if you want to move on to the
next flyer you can always click back to
see the previous one of the spirit
[Music]
maybe you can do something with this as
well it doesn't go with any of my flyers
[Music]
come back anytime you want so i did meet
or you guys said i didn't need the
puzzle pieces so that would mean that
unknown
is not part of the family
maybe
[Music]
all right let's go to 9 street
new area
oh you meant i didn't need all of them
like that oh okay okay okay that makes
sense
aha
so their minds
to my new
friend yes
sometimes it's really hard for me to get
my thoughts out through my snoot rather
than on paper and i'm sure you've
already noticed this is not for me right
it's just just something someone dropped
[Music]
i know it must have been it seemed out
of the blue to get them truthfully i was
just so lonely when i saw your number on
the scrap of newspaper behind the cans
here that i dialed but all the
information had been torn away i don't
know who you are but i guess that's fair
since you don't know who i am either so
this is unknown
unknown unknown
the thing is i've not tried to talk to
anyone else for such a long time not
since sarah passed away really she was
all i had in the world and all i needed
to it's funny how sometimes you have
everything and then in an instant things
change and everything is different
everything is too different now without
sarah yo are you okay unknown
i spend a lot of time not moving forward
actually we're talking to you today
telling you things about the city oh
oh man
it really made me feel like i could try
to
like if i went out in the sun
it would still be there even if sarah
won't be the kites would still fly with
colorful tails alligator chinatown would
still smell like baking chestnuts and
even the river would still be flowing
even forward just like time and just
like me
it's making me feel a bit emotional man
oh
thank you for not pushing a stranger
like me away when i reached out it meant
more to me than you might ever know
wishing you the best your friendly city
guy
danny
is that your real name that would be
[\h__\h] creepy if that was unknown
but oh
danny
why did you not show me your body when
you stay unknown
you should have shown me who you are
puzzle piece
sentimental yeah all right let's hope
for our new family members uh
oh yeah
wow soda
oh nice one right at the trash can one
more
pure
wonderful possibilities yeah
reuben are you a family member that
street station hasn't been open to the
public in a few years now nothing's the
flooding on earth to tell ruins of an
ancient piece of red society
they were already in the iron age and
everything okay doesn't seem to be a
family member
what about you gary hey bye you wanna
say something interesting
you look like an alligator of good taste
i can tell just by the very visible
expression you're giving off
creator of high cleaver of luxury few
can afford
you may have just what you're looking
for my friend you see this coat here
nice ride got it at the creeps warehouse
semi-annual state
i have some interesting words inside it
as well as my bus pass which is less
interesting but it has a fun puffy
sticker of a hot dog on it but yes my
wires things you've never seen things
you may never see again things you wish
you could see again but can't because
i'm busy doing laundry and watching tv
shows about superheroes you may be
wondering is he wearing clothes under
there and the answer is sort of but
that's beside the point
he seems to be a family member
a very sexy one my bus card has the
killer birthday sticker on it yay
that's what i want you guys to use it
for wonderful
let's just call me gary for now okay
google gary trustworthy gary gary ain't
never had to fly
i mean like for sport i always eat any
fire hurt you know circle of life for
bug eating alligators and all that
understandable i guess
at pat the alligator you don't know him
i mean family or nothing but we took a
pottery class together at the yucca
nice guy kind of twitchy though we keep
in touch and i secure
i used to use ice to cue you
good old times people nowadays don't
even know what that is
a reference i understand one more thanks
to being a boomer
msn2
[Music]
my mom was using it too are you calling
her a boomer too huh
okay scary knows about the event gary
knows about everything going down in
ireland here in new york city events
meet and greets catch covers jack and
jill baby showers gary knows about all
this stuff yeah [\h__\h] you guys are booms
too for knowing about isaac
but gary ain't no squealer if you want
info you're going to have to do a little
something something to me
i don't trust you i don't trust you at
all
so would you
look at my paintings
trying to get into art college
so it's been my turn to draw pictures
for a living and reside on the poverty
line crying a lot
i've been practicing on my own on my own
helping the old gator masters but i just
can't seem to get it quite right if i
show you the real painting of my
fortress sounds like animal crushing to
me let's go
i i
um
i'm not sure uh
if i can do this without you guys help
though
for animal crossing i also always had up
i had to look it up on google
it would really help to get some honest
critique i could stop softly about later
on my left bed so when you look for my
portfolio of course artist elliott
novice is seeking critiquing spot the
difference between the original painting
and gary's forgery hmm
[Music]
these are really hard oh damn
well at least i have you guys me no
that's
when you've seen enough click me to see
the other painting that's also very good
switch back and forth as many times as
you like and spot a difference click on
it but if you get free wrong my feelings
are really gonna be hurt ready let's go
oh there
i need to spot the differences i i see a
difference there
on the plane but
wait so he tells me what the original is
and what the forgery is
oh all i have to do is spot mistakes
that's all
mistakes in the forgery
on the bottom
purple flower
i see this one where you see purple
flower on the bottom what are you
talking about
ah
are there more than one mistake yeah
yeah yeah
kids on the bottom true oh there are
more
there's more than one
okay well so let's see this okay and
this one
and this one yeah okay okay free free
ah there's more there's more maybe the
umbrella no
[Music]
i'll find it i'll figure it out
ah i think those people have different
colors of hats no what
no no actually
no it looked sass to me but
no
dreams maybe something with the trees
a purple flower in the center what
people flowing up
oh
there was something with the umbrella a
different umbrella okay
flower
two more mistakes
[Music]
get her in the water oh nice
okay last one i'm gonna try to find by
myself
there must be something on the bottom
left
come on
maybe the mountain yes the teeth i was
just gonna say the amount of teeth
that was high
nicer
okay oh man oh my god okay uh
where do i even start
ah i saw something
these ones
on top of the door
what about the windows or that
i saw something again uh here
that little boy looking out the window
[Music]
flower ah you're on the flower
yep the flower the flower
okay
left side
there's so much to look at here
oh i think
yep yeah okay
that tower here
two more
[Music]
probably
something on the bottom left maybe
[Music]
stairs no
tail
the hands no
maybe not maybe something here yeah yeah
i'm still missing something here
look at the right side
no
[Music]
okay one more
last one
i'll find it
you guys finding it
the last one
[Music]
last
last one
and probably there's another painting
after that too
i found a lot on my own i'm gonna look
at the chat the candle candle
aha
thank you
okay okay most of them i found on my own
shall we good okay wow wow wow
wow that's a huge picture japanese style
damn
okay
one two three four five six seven eight
let's look at the teeth
oh my god the eyes
okay the eyes
here we go
the heart
ah
skeleton has no hearts
the peanuts peanuts peanuts are fine
uh
the lady on the left was about her
something about her probably is off
i don't see anything about her being off
though
what about the three thingies no
oh this one is difficult
ah
the facial expression
[Music]
i thought they were actually going to
show us paintings like like mona lisa or
something
well this is fine too maybe the bones
[Music]
maybe don't
there must be something off of that lady
something something
no
her rope the big sleeve is off
oh it is i was looking at that before
but i didn't notice it
oh one more one more
[Music]
maybe
no
[Music]
that one was difficult too
huh
it's probably something with the bones
what is it
green checkered pens yeah
oh i did look at that and compared them
but i didn't see that either what the
[\h__\h] you're right oh
yeah they're more even more checkered
matcha
i got a family member badge
how many do i have left now i i lost
count
thank you for the feedback i can't wait
to incorporate it into my next painting
series and i was thinking of switching
over to drawing cartoons
but you really convinced me to stay in
the course on painting and not throw my
life away gary feels a new lease on
living
wait is that are they roasting
themselves
because he says it would be uh throwing
your life away if you were drawing
cartoons but that's literally what the
people who who made the game are doing
there's one more at i'm straight
huh
you're missing
this is self-rules i think
all right the event truthfully it's my
first professional gig drawing the
invitational ah
that's my even paid me ten whole dollars
for it which is five dollars higher than
my listed online commission prizes nice
other
so generous
well but they didn't throw their life
away they made such great game and they
worked on other great things
gary's really moving up in the world
anyway friend looks like i'll be seeing
you tonight until then watch yourself
but there's no other family member here
right
i can't
i can go for the door
oh don't tell me there's someone in the
casket
is there a puzzle piece no
big mama
come closer
that's the one that we are missing at
the very very very bottom of the family
tree probably
yes let me see your face she's so old
she's like literally already in the
coffin
you made it
so far to come here then again i've
learned that everywhere you go that's
the farthest you've ever gone
true that's a interesting thing to say
or it's a vampire
i guess i could be that too
i'm as old as time itself you're not
ready to yet know the depths of my being
yet
can i come back later
my great-grandfather no it is it is old
in his age not i don't think she's
supposed to be a vampire she's just dead
my great grandson fruit of my loins
fruit on the vine
[Music]
a mere drop in the great pond of self
that lives within each one of us fear
not the ripple that grows within if it's
fate that discourages you let the cards
be your guide
uh huh that's very deep i don't get it
wisdom comes from knowledge oh you also
have cards oh tarot cards are what what
cards are those
i'm playing another card game to learn
boy you must come closer sit and light
the candle game time
oldest thing
here called and smell both balls huh
all right face your future it
oh
[Music]
okay so she's just laying me on some
corn
maybe this is the key to not being the
killer
show me what the future holds for me
please
ah
see how the flame breaks the darkness
the light provides one a new perspective
of the time and space in which we are
granted this fleeting moment together i
will be all the cards
it's a long arm
uh-huh
it's the same
they're all the same oh it's just ah
that's just the backside probably
the future is in your eyes young reptile
choose okay
this is the back side um
left
ah
the leftmost card first you are
thoughtful but without focus your own
carelessness can make you stumble
cute
camouflage
is this always the same cards or is this
random i wonder does someone know
lilo
observe
plan
when the time is right you're coming out
will take everyone by surprise
is that a hint of me being a killer
because i was observing
there are multiple cards i can't
remember
[Music]
okay
well i'll go for
this one next
a good second choice when you're my age
you'll find comfort and randomness it's
fine to let
fate guide your hand
[Laughter]
god he's surviving with the dead
dinosaur
posing with him
you don't have to change you've already
outlasted the worst
let stability be your strength
oh yeah i feel that kind i feel this one
[Music]
they say the last card is often the
cruelest
let's see
brewmation what
this is a time of reinforcement and
rebuilding but worry not winter cannot
last forever how does she know it's
winter still
and now that she knows it's almost over
and it's going to be springsteen how
would she know
how does she know
[Music]
how does the game know what if you play
this on summertime
incredible
[Music]
what does it all mean
nothing perhaps after all you have been
able to make your own destiny until now
you seem like a good egg i'm a phoenix
yo
i'm far from being an egg i don't even
hatch from an egg
i hope your future is full of
joy all these references the game knew i
was gonna play it one day
let an old lady give you a little
something just for taking the time to
stop by for a chat
there we go
i want to check if that was the last one
no it can't be we're still missing uh
the ones from yeah um but in i mean like
if i have actually
um if i'm still missing
finding one you know
you just need the
the baby yeah
may these words be a talisman you carry
across your
heart thank you for your wisdom
and your creepiness
i am out of here
because i think i need to restart anyway
because if i'm only missing one piece
then i just gotta
do another ending
really unfortunate that that is one of
the few games that i can't um
wait i don't need to go there anymore i
can't uh
repeat
otherwise we will be done here
probably
all right let's see what we can do
let's get the confirmation that we're
only missing one
[Music]
party
here girl perfect option big mama bc
what did it say
to be unending and absolute
yeah i want to be that too someday
oh wait you're probably up here yeah
makes sense
popular comic book convention
[Music]
hey we're missing two
two
that's a 39
but real is this real yeah
the baby goes
well the baby
goes here i suppose
who goes here oh yeah the conductor the
conductor didn't give me his thing yet
why what
what
will he only give it to me
after
getting all the puzzle pieces
i finished the puzzle
i need all of them but i don't okay so
this is the only piece i don't really
need maybe
because you guys said i can get the true
ending without
without the
puzzle
not sure
well hey how many puzzle pieces well let
me look into my
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh okay
there's one more
ah there's another one
i didn't look very well before it seems
[Music]
oh maybe even there i missed a puzzle
piece
time to click everywhere a drag up is a
good idea
also play puzzle please please please
pause the puzzle piece please
[Music]
yeah
because we started out here and i didn't
really know much about the puzzle pieces
yet
[Music]
let's go to the arcades
where is the purikura booth huh
you know everything about pretty cool
now don't you guys
sorry we already played before i don't
want to play with you anymore i don't
have the time for it sorry even though
you were fun and cute and adorable and
one of the first people we met really
adorable i love you you're cute i'll
never forget you anime girl
don't worry one day you can be an a real
anime girl like me too it's not
impossible
it's not impossible i became an anime
girl too oh i've always been an animal
girl of course
uh any puzzle pieces anymore
oh oh what was that
no nothing
[Music]
i think
okay
i am so
determinated
deter determ determin
that's her mind determine the
determined
the term
determined determined
to finish his [\h__\h] now come on okay
sorry that was mean it's not a [\h__\h]
best game i've ever played i'm just
still very very um
feeling intense and passionate right now
there you go
[Laughter]
um
well while we still have time we gotta
look for puzzle pieces so
where was i not um
doing a good job at finding them maybe
here
determined
determined yes i did go to the girls
girls girls girls girls girls oh wait
you don't you don't wanna
oh
you don't wanna you don't wanna get me
out
oh give me your peace
no
[Music]
wait oh there is another game to play
a new puzzle to play
let's see if we can complete it
[Music]
ah i usually don't like playing puzzles
but this one this is kind of fun
okay
oh man
can we really find them all without a
guide or something
one two three four
yeah okay
bye bye see you again friend
ah yeah it moves a moving puzzle i
wonder if that's really a thing that
exists probably somebody already
invented that and created that
that's funny but i need a puzzle piece
ah
[Music]
did i find everything back there
i'm not gonna go inside there anymore
oh nothing nothing nothing nothing here
how many am i missing now
20 faces
how is that possible
let's go inside maybe we missed some
inside
19 pieces missing
[Music]
oh oh
no that's just you
ah 18 pieces how did i not get that one
before
18 pieces missing
huh you don't want to talk to me okay
[Music]
no
yeah we got the exit one
i think that's it in here
once you missed downtown
downtown
[Music]
okay let me look
i think you only need to complete the
second puzzle to get clancy's token oh
that would be great
oh hello nice seeing you again
[Music]
don't worry i actually don't want to
play anymore with you no no no no
i'll pass
thank you though
anything else in here
i feel like i've looked many times i'm
getting there yeah
i'm good at scanning for them thank you
ah yeah we haven't looked around much
here either i guess for puzzle pieces
that's true
bugs
lots and lots of flies what about flies
considered bugs
[Music]
found you before
perhaps now inside the antique shop
antique shop i feel like we found
millions
and we can look in that one more time
[Music]
i'm gonna look inside one more time wait
flies are bugs okay
[Music]
um
oh
that's new but it's not a puzzle piece
i'm pretty sure
oh
i was gonna say i'm pretty sure we found
it all but there's another one 17 pieces
missing
no we had this one before i saw that one
before
we look here again
try the baby game again i can't and at
the moment i think i gotta start a new
game unfortunately
16 pieces missing
[Music]
oh i saw that before
what okay
oh god i thought i couldn't redo it
anymore
i was wrong i was wrong okay
okay first round is okay
um
what color are you getting orange okay
get out of here
first round ain't a problem
[Music]
oh man that last moment man is really
[\h__\h] difficult
[Music]
what are you blue green
can you get out of here
ghostbusters who do you call kiwawa
if you have my number if not then sorry
you gotta end up possessed possessed
round two
um
okay stay on top of it kiwala
i wonder like in the
sometimes it's better to wait a little
bit maybe because it kind of wastes some
time to wait for them
oh god the blue one is coming fast
[Music]
okay
oh so many of them
i'm not ready for round three
okay okay i'm not ready
[Music]
um holy [\h__\h]
okay okay
[Music]
[Applause]
on top of it just gonna stay on top of
it guys
this is how you bust some ghosts baby
this is how it's done
when
more ghosts in town not in my town i
protect this town and i protect pat no
matter how much my character wants to
kill him apparently
i'm back oh and look at that sleeping
like the tiniest baby is baby tiny angel
what a baby also has pat's eyes sorry to
ask you was such a borer but i do
appreciate you helping an old gala i'll
tell you what any items of water fire
will be related damage or 10
off just for you don't say nana ever did
nothing for your kid
okay let's try the puzzle again
i think now we're um
now we have enough puzzle pieces for the
that puzzle
someone said that might be enough the
second puzzle might be enough to get his
badge i hope so
because i don't know how i can get
that much more pieces
quick math
okay was that was he a puzzle piece i'm
not sure
uh
[Music]
fun district is where we're going right
let's go although i'm probably still
missing some in the park probably
who are you you're cute
she's sitting on the floor like that
and some crazy people in the tram and in
the subway sometimes some crazy peeps
okay
yeah
two plus two is four what
do i have them
i think i do
i think i don't
fueling up the trolley i know i was
forgetting something bugs invited you
may have just saved his old trolleys
conductor's career
as for the event i'll be transporting
most of the family there myself on the
trolley to help set things up these
things take a little job you know i'm
sure you'll see when you get there
thanks again for all the help saves and
this your stuff so can i stop killing
pat now please
why why why did we go from happy ending
to bad ending i don't get it
[Music]
i got them oh yes yes i got them mommy
can i be part of your family now please
adopt me
i i got to know all of your family
members man
that deserves some kind of reward
doesn't it
and the last puzzle piece in your
softwares and non-software cute
don't eat hot glue though
trust me
good old cleansing beloved charlie
cardraba
there we go let's go play that
look at that beauty
and an achievement when you hear your
your family
they say i'm family now in the
achievement
wow you got everyone how wonderful it's
so rare i get to see all these faces in
one place without some kind of casket
involved
you did an amazing job i'm so proud that
you're friends with my patrick thank you
again see you tonight yeah yeah i see
you tonight
go to the party patrick are you ready
and do you need help with your shoes
again
it's me again
shoes
[Music]
no
let's go to the party now i'm ready
can i like shorten it
or do i need to play games in order to
[Music]
frozen off
i i get that if you're listening with
headphones maybe
or also without headphones probably
don't worry it's not your phone
is that i feel like i just saw something
like that was something here but maybe
because of the card i was passing
look for bub yeah what was that with bob
right
bob's side story what's good
you need a nap
i forgot what voice i did for him hello
esteemed guest how can i help you
take a nap until ah
that's what that is
okay let's nab i love naps
yo
yes can i get a room please maybe
there's puzzle pieces in the room
of course we have several units
available that could suit even the most
discerning alligators many sleepy dantes
and many sleepy timetees as well should
you require a little extra help on your
journey to snooze city
yeah i'm good with taking a nap right i
got everything i needed
should be fine
yes jeans
i'm a bird napping hell yeah i am
oh
puzzle piece puzzle piece puzzle please
there ain't no puzzle pieces here it
seems
good night
that set a good catnap or alligator nap
in that case
i'm gonna go to the party
please please let it be a happy ending
in the true ending
yeah yeah i know i know i know bob it's
all good i'm i don't i'm not surprised
by nothing here
sorry it's okay don't worry about it oh
i got you i'll catch you bro
why was his face not lit up this time
navigator the power's out
let's got him
do you know that way
let's find the way
the third time i think this is the first
time i'm doing this
oh [\h__\h]
at least this side i wasn't surprised by
the clock
just pat just pat
um
i went down but not right we're gonna go
left
and right was just a circle
uh not this way
[Music]
that is
terrifying
[Music]
ah
i always almost miss this
[Music]
that is the right way i think
on my way to being adopted by this
alligator family
time
[Music]
and oh there we go i was easy
faster than before okay let's see
please please
ah
all the love is so blinding
wow
happy birthday to friends
oh my baby
oh
okay we see the baby bubble bubble angel
face
and um
saskai
you're new gary actually i got into the
community college liberal arts program i
can't wait to support my parents and not
always
you're new
solid guy has ascended doesn't even need
a chair
hello star child may interest you in the
flyer for my upcoming crystal yoga class
we're going to stand on our heads and
really give it some chords
also going to be free pizza pizza
mom mama mia and who else
yo the conductor
well it's gratitude for the help earlier
youngin thanks to you the only doghouse
i'm sleeping in these days is a
metaphorical one it's made of two tin
beds pushed to the opposite side of the
room
no no no oh and the coffin is playing
cards always made against old maid
i knew i saw something special in you
but your time is not yet over well i
hope pat's time is also not over
do what you must but unless you do
there's still a chance to set things
right oh oh it sounds like quite a hint
to me
[Music]
how do i set things right
um
i think that's it
that's it
she knows she knows what i'm planning to
do
huh
[Music]
what
you get a puzzle piece here
magic
is that the only one in here
[Music]
it seems so
well okay pat
hat pat's pet
[Music]
what skin
i would also skip before
[Music]
i'm so happy i wasn't getting rubbed out
i was getting birthday clowns
thank you my special friend father the
last vogue oh girl
oh yeah we're making okay
i still want this one
maybe these ones
do this
the round glasses
we're getting cuter every time
pink hair
pink tie
pink eyes or brown i guess i guess
they're brown
i like the round ones after all
okay
and i'm getting in as well again of
course oh [\h__\h] oh there's really
i guess i can be here
[Music]
right
i'll make myself small
yeah a bit bigger
okay
it's hopefully the last family photo
saigon
uh ignore the hands well i'll put them
away for you guys uh oops wrong hands
there you go
cheese
[Music]
ah i got a good one
alligator two free dot jpegs okay
okay now
it's
the moment of truth
we will now see
what's gonna happen
[Music]
oh i could be between them
oh nice okay let's go
[Music]
no
stop it stop it stop it stop it
[Music]
what did i do wrong
saxophone so jazzy
you can't do this with me yeah why push
him at all if like in one millisecond
you're gonna change your [\h__\h] mind
what what what stupid
i thought i had to do i had to do it all
over again
likes me oh
[\h__\h] team
[Music]
well i can't believe you were a hitman
that had the change of heart at the last
second and pulled me up to safety i
especially can't believe i accidentally
hired my own head man to kill me on my
birthday and now you're in my house
routine
that means he wasn't that crazy after
all he he actually really
kind of felt that something was gonna
happen to him
we all thought he was crazy and cute
crazy and cute
what an increasingly large pool of
unlikely circumstances congregating
really though you won't believe how this
all happened
why it was just last week when i made
that faithful phone call
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
i am one who can kill any guys you need
call me from her to help i leave a deep
[Applause]
ah
i'm you guys need me help leave a
detailed description of who you is
[Music]
on his ear
yeah this is me killer
i that is four feet tall with two
[\h__\h] feet cool hat great bandana from
alligator new york city
birthday on the 16th i hope you feel
better why did you
why don't you even say all of that
bachelor of hit gator sciences
oh my god look at all those weapons
it's mikey arsenal
love you bye he loves me even though he
doesn't know me
it was a big misunderstanding as they
can't believe i was the one who wired
you i guess it serves me right always
being scared of someone else to get me
true truly the only one out to get me in
the end was me
no no no i mean everybody makes mistakes
that was a really um grave one though uh
grave
oh [\h__\h] no no
thank you thank you thank you
i can't
whoa
that's like super mundo deep deep i
definitely gotta tell dr duper about
this break for next tuesday mama mia
anyways all i can say is cheese and
crackers i'm glad you have a heart of
gold in there
and arms of gold which with which uh to
save a falling alligator
oh mandy
the sound
hey rooney
been accidentally hired to rub me out i
can't you believe that
it's not hard to believe it was you oh
your brain is like a thief and you're
kind of a ding-dong
he's so
i wise
you liked meeting my whole family
you did so much for all of them i bet
you dale wants to for you a surprise
buddy guys i want one i want one
hey i know would you guys want to take a
quick photo to get already dead but okay
this has been the most stressful
birthday i've ever had and i want to
remember that stress forever
and i probably will in therapy mama mia
[Music]
oh man
we're so cute oh look at us all friends
all not getting rubbed out or hiding in
their favorite hotel rooms
so entertail at the hotel with
friendship nothing greater and so i beat
you farewell and see you later alligator
mandy you said it mama mia said the
thing
i said
[Laughter]
[Music]
ah great super good
the end oh
i can't take a photo for you
i'm taking another photo or maybe i
should join in oh it's too late mamma
mia
alligator
45 accidentally what's happening oh man
you can go outside now
what do you mean
what does that mean
[Music]
wow
small butter that's the family that made
the game
they did such a great job
i love it
[Music]
i loved everything about it
oh are there the telling are they
telling me to stop playing the game and
go outside it's kind of late man
nah nah nah nah i'll stay at home but
thanks for the offer
thanks for the sentiment emotional
support provided
not a little
special thanks
we didn't
yay
oh that was so lovely that was so
charming on a charming precious game
[Music]
i'm glad we went back to finish it
you're so blessed guys
oh it's wonderful
yeah
just finished
you're so cute
i love the art style i love the
characters the humor holy [\h__\h] all those
jokes the the
the couple come up with all the jokes
themselves they're really funny
[Music]
four hours yeah
i did it in four hours today
[Music]
yeah i love point and click games um and
this one was a very witty and charming
one like point-and-click games there's a
lot of boring ones and there's some gems
out there and this was one of those gems
definitely
[Music]
i like i like good point-and-click games
though
yeah they're chill and
i mean usually they're not that
i mean they have some good riddles but
usually they're not as challenging you
know as alden ring for example but
the mini games are so much fun too
man
i love it
you guys are throwing out some game
names now but i don't really know most
of them
[Music]
well
um
maybe the uh developers watched again
last time they were watching the whole
stream apparently if you're still
watching i want to say
what a lovely game i love it if you're
making a part two or like another game
one day call me hit me up i wanna voice
it
i wanna voice it oh yeah starship
titanic um still nothing
so that sounds anyway um remember that a
hint about
from the casket lady about the coffin
lady about it not being winter anymore
soon
[Music]
well
let's move to my office shall we
[Music]
it's spring baby
oh [\h__\h]
oh
it do be spring though
i lost
i thought i prepared everything properly
apparently i didn't oh so
oh we don't need this little friend
right now
okay
and the chicken on the top right you see
it is throwing the uh cherry blossom
petals it's a it's the last last minute
really really quickly quick background
thank you ian excel
hey
cherry blossom it's finally no more wait
to here
because in the last stream i mentioned
yo i guess
i guess it's time
i guess it shouldn't be snowing anymore
and then eden was like okay let's do a
spring one really quickly and um only
took him not even 24 hours
and look at that look at the whole talk
um tapes we're almost out of space man
[Music]
[\h__\h] we gotta put it in a different
shelf then we can still like maybe put
some here but then they're separated huh
you gotta figure out something there
uh
maybe
maybe move the these ones to the bottom
and then more tapes here
or move all of these here
and then have all the tapes on these two
shelves that should be enough space
maybe
he works fast yeah
lovely spring themed office he might
still just uh change some things still
um
switch something up
also my cats are back because i
uh put everything in place again
everything should be in place now
except we don't have the christmas video
but i guess that's okay
i should put uh dreaming choo choo
up there maybe
maybe on this big one i always have the
my most recent song cover maybe
maybe maybe
how do you improve perfection
uh you want to make it more obvious that
the chicken is throwing the petals so
there's gonna probably be some uh flap
movement
oh
[Music]
yeah it's kind of a museum it has like
hints of what's been happening but
that's all thanks to eden exile cause
like
yeah he puts everything together all
those details
really really happy about it
thank you thank you
it's so bright now i like you know
actually
see i want to show you a difference here
this is
a normal version
see there's even like a
little bit of a
lot it's literally slight lightning
change like it's more a bit more sunny a
tiny bit more sunny
see these changes isn't that fascinating
all the tapes look at the tapes building
up there
oh my dreaming tootsie got added up
there too i just realized
nicer
[Music]
yeah he's really good with lightning i
noticed like i really like the moody
lights also in the in the christmas
office as well
or the halloween one was great too the
halloween one damn
going to need a bigger office soon
[Music]
i might i might have something to work
something similar
wait for it
[Music]
soon tm
sun tm
[Music]
always working on improving the office
i love this place so much
what happened i have i have someone who
always helps with the office thank you
that's really so cool like having having
changes all the time i sometimes don't
even have to ask for it and it just
happens wait i should put the chat on
the screen
sorry
there it is
so now we have all seasons we have a
spring version we have a basic summer
version we have a
i guess we don't have uh autumn maybe
this year we got an autumn version too
with leaves falling in the back i don't
think we had an up but we did have
halloween i guess i don't need autumn
because i will always just put up
halloween until halloween and maybe a
few days after halloween
and then we have winter on christmas
separately and and new year's eve
yeah
all the seasons
[Music]
so happy thank you so much for the work
for the hard work
so many offices yeah
hard at work at decorating the office at
all times very fittingly
all right we're gonna read super chats
here
uh
[Music]
i missed i stopped reading at some point
yesterday i'm gonna keep the bjm playing
is it not too loud
[Music]
yeah that's right thank you for
reminding me
pj m okay okay jazzy fancy b jim
from later alligator
don't we love it don't we all love it
is fine okay
thank you
[Music]
now let me
open my super chat also i'm sorry i was
confused because you guys were also
confused we were both confused um
tomorrow is the vr chat collab um
yeah
tomorrow and on my channel 9 pm my time
so be there or be square
will be triangle i don't care be a
circle if you want to be but just be
there okay
[Music]
i still have to
try to relearn the choreography quickly
but i mostly still remember it so it
should be okay
the choreography of what i'm teaching
amy because it will be a dance
teaching
lesson stream
we'll be there for sure thank you an
octagon
nice fancy
you want to stand out don't you
i'm square no why
i'd be listening from work for sure okay
actually excuse me for a moment i will
go to an idol meeting really quickly
okay
[Music]
talk to kotori
instead
[Music]
do
and wow
hello
i met smoovie again she always wakes up
and says hello every time i leave my
office
[Music]
thank you for waiting thank you
i was afk
[Music]
let me let me take another fruit candy
frozen fruit candy
[Music]
so how are you guys doing right now
is everyone doing well
mina genki
[Music]
by the way my total play time was 9.1
hours apparently but
i wonder if they count me being afk like
this
also as playtime when i'm not even
playing just playing the music
going all right chill pretty fine still
at work man
but i'm glad you can watch even when
you're at work thank you
terrible because now i'm at work you too
sleepy just got my wisdom teeth oh [\h__\h]
i still have to do that at some point
might pass out anytime soon
oh
is it late over there are you in an a
time zone or what
just vibing watching my own scene ah
thank you
chilling at work watching my lesson
relatable
relatable i used to do that at work i
was watching pickled assembles archives
my old job
good times good times thank god i had a
not so busy job at all and i kind of had
a lot of privacy too
but that was also very very
uh
on alert
because people would walk by my office
and i would be like oh [\h__\h] put down the
food act natural like natural i'm
working
to tap tap tap on the keyboard tippity
top
[Music]
well hey it's not my fault i always did
what i needed to do in my shift it's not
my fault that we're not busy
[Laughter]
[Music]
it do be like that
totally working
um
now i work from home
and no one can judge me for not doing
work i mean i do i do not slack them
like i do my [\h__\h] i do what i need to do
and i don't i do a lot i do
that is totally different there is no
slacking off
actually the problem with working from
home is
that
you don't have that
my physical therapist said the same
thing you don't have that you know that
that switch like you go home you arrive
home after work and you're not at work
anymore
when you work from home then you're
always at work you know and you always i
always think about where goal is like
when i'm in bed watching netflix so many
times i'm like can't even focus on
netflix because i'm like my mind is
still at work and i i take out my phone
a million times and update twitter and
all that twitter is twitter's work too
for us
[Music]
social media looking at comments reading
all your comments it's work too all of
that is work social media interactions
work
so there's like my mind is 24 hours at
work and that can mean
mentally taxing at some point
not taking a proper break that's why i
need you know i need some proper
um
vacations where i don't even have time
to relax because when i have time to
relax i i have time to take out my phone
and look at it i need a busy vacation
where i do like like stuff like i don't
know go skiing or or
go swimming but like like i don't know
proper activities like i don't know
diving or something
or
or i don't know
just something something that
where i can't touch my phone
[Music]
that's the only time
where i can really for a little while
um
take my mind off of it
that france that france trip that i did
the paris trip last year and when was it
november october something like that
that was the first time in over a year
since my debut
that i
was able to take my mind off of work for
about a day
[Music]
because i was like
really busy talking and when walking
really immersed in
in being a tourist
it doesn't always work though
don't install the twitter app i can't do
that
because i want to update you guys at
least once a day
[Music]
it's okay though um
i'm i i hope i can take my mind off it's
a little bit uh on my next break though
do you love paris and do you love
friends um i have not seen much of
france yet and even paris i haven't seen
that much yet
i've seen some of the important big
sights but
i'm sure that there's more to it which
leads me to something i guess my manager
said is okay to say
um
so that people don't have their hopes up
anymore um just just as a
as a heads up uh
japan expo is not happening for
uh
me or anyone in whole life yeah
i'm not gonna talk about the reason or
whatever but just just to let you know
because i know that there's some people
some french fans who were hoping for
that to happen and i was so happy to
have you
have the support of the french fans
you guys made that hashtag
um and i really appreciated that
i'm so happy but i hope maybe we can
meet in another um convention or so
another place
yeah might not be japan expo but that's
okay we'll meet another time okay
at least you know yeah it's better than
keeping you on your tippy toes i think
it's better to be able to tell you
[Music]
i hope i can provide you with some other
good news soon
[Music]
um
oh god
[Music]
should be somewhere here maybe
there is no exit
thank you for pinky
what is
for the stream
is that the beginning of the sentence or
second super chat i think that's the
beginning like your style and game genre
of choice it's my it might be niche
audience but there is a lot of people
who enjoy it keep it up potential i did
not buy the ticket but have a good time
at the best potential or you can still
buy it if you want to by the way for the
online viewing
if you change your mind
thank you for the pinky and thank you
for the support dankeshen check it's
monkey dankeshan cow carrot duncan
i want to congratulate you for beating
margaret thank you
regardless of what you decide to do with
er from now on uh the growth and
potential you displayed was amazing and
i'm happy that you had fun playing it
when you weren't suffering
thank you
at least um
the pain that i go through in eldon ring
is something temporary
um the time heals
it thankfully i i
when i look back on elden ring after
streaming
i
i don't associate too many negative
memories with it so it's all good
[Music]
as i said i still wanna
um um play it a few times
mario
[Music]
super mario 64
might be a different story although
recently i've been thinking about
um playing 64 or sunshine again
uh just for like a random stream in
between
i kind of want to
hear the music again and be in the mario
world again
i know it might be tough and a lot of
anger issues might come up again but
i just i don't know recently i feel a
little bit like meeting mario again
and killing him several times over and
over and over again
oh
we could do another race challenge for
that yeah
yeah yeah and for the sun yeah
we must aim for the sun
a mario will put my foolish ambition
serious
i'm sure mario is able to do that yeah
my foolish ambition of playing mario a
mario game again in the first time in a
long time in a long while
he should be happy that i want to pick
up his game again
um
he's gonna show me that it was a wrong
choice probably
but yeah
thank you cow carrot thank you so much
i'm happy here to see you so blue to see
you so often here in my streams thank
you and you're making so many clips
thank you so much
thank you thank you soon
nice to have support from a really good
clipper
yum yum yum
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you always
here probably wow
you got a lot of time on your hands huh
kft clippers always uh have a history of
getting really busy and then leaving me
it's kind of sad you better not leave me
called carrot
cow karen don't go
don't go
don't leave me
it's okay though no judging it's okay
people have lives too
but don't leave me
buddy i see you there buddy buddy buddy
buddy when are you coming back
i see you there
you're still there partially though so i
still have hopes for you
[Music]
oh yeah next set yeah yeah
um there's a couple there's a couple
and just today i saw you know there's
this spanish a translating uh clipper i
just i i got recommended
um even though i don't i'm not
subscribed i got recommended like the
the community post that they made
about um being more busy and not being
able to clip so much
but it didn't say they were gonna
completely stop they had good clips too
they had really good clips too
[Music]
even if you don't need spanish subtitles
um
they had really good clips too um
kfp
yeah was that the name why
us probably
i don't know what that means but
it's the kfp spanish clipper
[Music]
this hero oh
where are you my friend
i wish you all the best with what you
gotta do you gotta ah there you are you
gotta do what you gonna do i like your
clips i've been watching them
thank you
no i've noticed you a while ago i just
never i guess uh said it out loud i've
been watching your clips though
and i appreciate them you're doing a
good job too
yeah
my my kfp clippers
at least i can rely on them when it
comes to um
[Music]
clipping me in a
non-reputation-destroying way
thanks guys i love you
certain scientific [\h__\h] thank you for
the pinky
money
money thank you for the money thank you
for the donation donkey [\h__\h] oh it will
be invested in that cherry blossom
throwing chicken up there thank you very
much
hope you enjoyed the yakuza stream black
friday
frey
thank you first time in the stream of
mine oh
welcome i hope you're also here today
maybe maybe
doc joe said thank you for the pinky
tantra sets off my fever and pushes all
the right buttons
i'm not surprised you're fantastic
tension thank you for the spontaneous
yakuza okay you're welcome
man they have really great songs how can
i hold back i cannot i literally cannot
hold back
see so it's gone long ago it's not about
being say so
[Music]
but yeah
it's okay it's okay i don't want i don't
want you know
[Music]
it was it was a joke
with a jerk but it's low-key true but
it's a joke too
it's okay i'm i'm not that um
mad about it
it's joke put down salt beef with anderi
everybody
beautiful andorian
[Music]
you know what i want to do that i might
want to ask a clipper um for help with
um
i want to do
um little little clip compilations
that serve as
um with an extra voice over and so on
from me yours truly that serve as an um
explanation to certain memes so like i
wanted to do a video about what's the
usual room and what's casper and what's
the hashtag will hashtag yolk and how it
got created like i always wanted to
include like clips of where it
originated from
there's i think someone like cow carrot
actually might be perfect for that
because yeah
you you're like an archivist art archive
per person
yeah like maybe like five minutes uh
five minutes i think would be a good
length
to explain
the memes oh yeah bottom left i guess we
can explain that too but then say at the
end that we don't really use that
anymore but i think it's still okay to
explain like what that was because yeah
um
sounds interesting i know
[Music]
i have a lot of ideas but it's just with
so many ideas and being so busy it's
hard to get them started man
[Music]
some things you know they're so normal
for us but for newcomers i wanted to
make it a bit easier for them
to understand the memes without having
to ask yo can you explain to me what
that means because i think like a lot of
people they just
don't even feel the courage to even ask
about like what does this mean and what
does that mean so it would be easier for
them to
watch videos like that
oh yeah the australia austria thing that
kind of originated before whole live
because i'm just austrian and people
they always think i'm australian
but i feel like i could probably still
the crying baby yes oh my god that's
necessary the dead baby because i always
explained that i always have to explain
that
[Music]
yes yes yes yes yes
a guide a guide not a [\h__\h] post guy no
an insider guide to kfp
part one
casper
[Music]
11 out of 10 idea thank you
oh
inside the guide would be great right
round run run yeah yeah yeah let's do it
let's do it let's do it how to kfp 101
yeah
lord iceberg yes yes yes yes
there's probably some things that i'm
forgetting so once i run out of ideas i
might ask you guys for ideas
or now that i said it out loud i guess
we can get started on working on it
kyle carrot open your dms please
open your dms please
i gotta
write a script though i kind of want it
to be like a
like uh like a presentation partially
like i want to open it up with like
hello welcome to
kfp insider guide a part one
today i'll explain to you something that
you probably have been wondering about
all along
casper and then and then uh there might
be some voice overs over some silent
clips and then then replay the clips
with some sound and then wish wish
casper uh appearance in in in
fire emblem stream and other times and
talking about how it ate my chocolate
and all that
that's kind of how i'm imagining it
[Music]
10 things you should know
10 things you should know about kfe
yeah
super brain
[Music]
to do it in style of a worker training
video
i'm sure we can kind of get it like that
[Music]
number one friend
what
oh bad advice bad advice okay sorry i'm
chilling i'm chilling too much
need to
it's a great song i'm so addicted jay
swagbuck duncan
thank you for the flush chat style i'm
skipping oh wait oh wait what
[Music]
the flush jets are the later alligator
uh
flush jets for some reason in between
the yakuza super chats what the hell
okay
uh
oh my god
randall's channel dagger shoot that's
also from today for some reason sorry
lightning league girl like her duncan
i will do
[\h__\h] it's already next sunday holy [\h__\h]
i will do a
watch along yes for the first day on my
channel publicly
oh thank you guys
thank
[Music]
you put into all the details really
makes a difference thanks for always
being yourself and being the fun nest
buyer for thank you a fun nest
thank you it's so sweet
tiny delta thank you
uh i don't know i i don't think i can
even enable it yeah i've seen youtube is
um
has already introduced gifting
membership in some uh on some channels
uh it seems like mostly japanese
channels
[Music]
it seems like they're serious about it
and it's gonna be eventually a thing
everywhere
i don't know how exactly it works i've
been wondering if you can choose
who you're giving a membership
or
um
because i thought that was a big worry
for a lot of the japanese viewers
you can disable it
i think in general if you can choose who
you're giving it to
um then it's fine
um but so we also discussed that um even
if you can't choose
we could do a um an extra perk
uh for those
memberships
um that just doesn't really give you
that much access to things
it's random on twitch
oh
what's that so
if it works like twitch you can pick a
paper you can pick
ah you have the choice you can either
give randomly or pick uh-huh
[Music]
like an emote only to yeah for example i
don't know
and then videos would be
extra
i guess
maybe if if need be
if it has to be like that no
[Music]
we'll see
i guess you guys don't know for sure if
it's random or not on youtube
i guess you can only really know if you
try it out giving someone
memberships
gotta investigate
yeah it's 100 random on youtube really
so far it has been random
[Music]
i mean it would be nice to be able to
give memberships to people who can't
afford it you know
but
um
it's a hassle to pick 50 people
well
then
they should make
make it possible to give lower numbers
you can gift one membership to one
specific person but anything five to
twenty is random oh really you can no
okay interesting
you can do specific ones too
hmm
um traditional and reliable membership
is reliable entity
[Music]
well at the moment i don't even have the
option to enable it so now we don't have
to worry about it yet
[Music]
wow
still a testing face i suppose
thank you for the red super chat thanks
for cheering us up today tanja you're
the best oh i just
i'm glad i'm doing that i'm just
streaming doing my thing i'm glad it has
that effect thank you james mcphee mwah
thank you
i hope today you didn't need cheering up
and we're already happy and genki
wish you all the best thank you for your
love and your support
the dire tourist of the lands between
dancing
[Music]
tk nelson shoe dankeshen james mcphee
another red one thank you brief tensor
oh well sometimes when you're excited
about something you just don't need to
breathe
glad you all enjoyed the the pretty good
attention so much
[Music]
pick it up at the counter please
i put it in a nice bag for you
with a nice ribbon on top of it
[Music]
which of those three compliments you
liked the most
you can't cheat on and say all three of
them you have to pick one i'm asking for
a shy friend who wants to compliment you
i think
uh cute
[Music]
someone's saying i'm cute i think i
would be the most happy about
hmm
merry pippins thank you thank you for
catching up thank you
thank you thank you for the pinky
number two cuckoo number one and three
are nice bonuses but it's the pretty
good knowledge
cory no disco queen singing and later
alligator playful said steal my heart
what's that about
that doesn't make
quite sense
does it
number two was uh cool
is that what you mean
[Music]
i'm confused
i don't understand how it
how
how it connects with the rest of the
super chat
how are my
plano disco queen singing and later
alligator play for school
[Music]
huh
are they cool i think they're cute
i'm confused i'm confused but okay
thank you thank you for the pinky
confusion worked successfully mr vegeta
name has changed support has not still
on board for as long as you want to run
the show
archive game today though thank you
cool and cute yes yes i mean
sexy sometimes too subconsciously
can't do anything about that
mrs duncan
miss
are you his
to say
[Music]
do you want me to sing the song
i think i've standard before probably
hmm in the stream miss fist i see what
you're doing there
yes i might have been behind the scenes
behind the curtains yes maybe
[Music]
what song um a certain song from bono an
idol group called bono
[Music]
thank you for the pinky and the red
super chat
so generous thank you
kiara you are like a female hurricane
because i'm always unprepared for how
much you blow me away
shout out to harvard for the kfb seminar
on female hurricanes in pre-chat what
i i need uh
i need a recording of that what happened
what the hell were you talking about
guys
[Music]
context i was telling preach that an
interesting fact about female named
hurricanes they do more damage than male
ones because people tend to not prepare
as hard for them
that's how they're separating them
what
it's so weird
it was in the spirit of international
women's day which is today oh
today's international women's day
we mean
women we man
wow wow girls girls girls i like girls
girls girls girls girls girls girls
girls
[Music]
happy international women's day
i guess indeed
when will they make a beat super day we
shall make a v2 bidet ourselves
can i dedicate a kiss to fluff rubbles
oh
i've seen i've seen
uh them in the chat today
you're so sweet you're so giving
so sweet so nice doug joseph
well for here's a kiss if you're still
here
[Music]
thanks for being here today and watching
the stream hope you enjoyed it
oh uh your employee number
let me think it is
two
three
this two
next up there you are
showing your face again finally after
all these years after all these years of
buying milk and never coming back
[Music]
hope you're happy in college
i hope you're happy
[Music]
it's not like i'm sad or anything
no
not a single tiny bit
[Music]
maybe a little bit
today is my second birthday with you
second birthday
kfp and i had such a great time since
debut for that i want to thank you hope
realize how much you mean to us as for
my personal employee number should be 70
right yes
seven zero though we gotta add a zero i
always have your back pinky promise
thank you happy birthday
your second birthday
oh man it's crazy to thank
some of you guys
have been around
not two years okay but it's your second
time celebrating your birthday here damn
[Music]
thank you for still being here
let's celebrate my second birthday too
this year all right
i'm excited
thank you so much
i wish you all the best stay healthy
a lot of success i wish to you a lot of
happiness
hope all your dreams come true [\h__\h] 70
donkeys
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat the
attention i've just sold my investment
position today
oh i wish to hand you a small cut of the
profit may my next adventure be blessed
by attention for a 10 times
[Music]
i don't understand the last sentence but
nice
nice thank you thank you thank you thank
you yeah thank you for the red super
chat i appreciate it thank you
optimus prime thank you so much
skipping the sneeze chats
trevor g duncan
um
i think i gotta put that into the
translator
google google
[Music]
right
thank you for my best attention thank
you
you're the best thank you for your
support
i appreciate it
thank you hope you enjoyed the stream
today i wish you all the best
take care of yourself thank you for the
support
[Music]
i see some flash uh some flash chats
and skip them again the game recruit
uh
laser busting right so freedom
i've got mine too but
um i don't really i don't really am i'm
not a big fan of dakimakura so just have
it lying around at the moment maybe i'll
hang it up
the one from akira hmm
[Music]
sorry my mandarin pronunciation is [\h__\h]
looking for the top thank you navidad
rocky s
but then again maybe she heard alligator
meat taste like chicken i've actually
had crocodile meat before one time only
many many many years ago
in like some kind of like asian
restaurant with a buffet where they had
they had a lot of different meat um
and you were like able to choose it and
have them grill it
uh
yeah i think i actually tried it and i
mean it was okay
no i didn't eat that ain't a crocodile
not an alligator
close enough though
no no don't don't don't don't don't
don't misinterpret my words no i didn't
say that and i said crocodile you guys
told me alligators are different
it was a crocodile not an alligator so
there's no way it could be pat's family
don't put some words into my mouth that
i did not say
[Music]
i will not take that slander
lightly
[Music]
anyway i probably wouldn't want to eat
them again there's just certain things
that even if they taste okay i don't
want to eat them
that's just because of where i was
raised and what is normal to eat here
yeah
only lasaga
i want
[Music]
actually it's liable shut up
same thing
[Music]
uh
10 out of 10 voice acting as always and
thanks for sharing the experience with
us thank you for watching
it was so cute thank you for joining
today as well
i won't forget this game
yeah my mom also really liked it by the
way she was watching the first stream i
don't know if she was watching this one
too but i know she was watching the
first one
and she um
she told me
that she thought it was so cute so
lovely
yeah yeah i don't think anyone can not
like this game
[Music]
they should translate it to japanese so
that the whole life japan members can
play it
i'm sure they won't like it too
um
[Music]
thank you glad you enjoyed it okay
refreshing time now it's gonna probably
mess it up a little bit because like
there were some
some mixed in with the yakuza super
chats
um
[Music]
thank you today no words you got shy
again huh cause last time last time i
was teasing you about saying six words
and now you're so shy again you say
nothing
thank you
i didn't miss anything i'm still reading
should be fine
project oh thank you thank you
[Music]
yes yes yes yes
guys don't worry a cow carrot i'm not
gonna make you work for free
i i will uh
offer you some of my
hard-earned money
[Music]
i originally
make an exception for you
um
but but you don't know
where that money came from it might have
might have been some
edgy uh not edgy sexy sexy money that
you know
you might not even want to touch
you might not want to get your
fingerprints on that money
pay him with coupons
tomato soup coupons
[Music]
and mozart gundam says camping new
employee training is a great idea lore
evolves so fast here it does i went on
vacation for a month and when i came
back people were calling you kiwawa and
i'm too afraid to ask why
oh
[\h__\h] well there's not a really real
reason it's just like after i guess i
think after streaming for a long time i
guess the name has just evolved on its
own
um
i just suddenly enjoyed calling myself
baby versions of my name
yeah i mean guna could have said it too
but i don't think she was really
the starter
what's she
first it was kiawah then we said started
saying kiwawa because kiawah was not
good enough anymore
i think cause i was calling good agua
maybe that's why she said that kiawah
hmm cause i was always saying gu
also on discord chat i always typed at
her gua
[Music]
maybe that's it
welcome back though i'm so happy to see
you so often again
hope your vacation was fun though yeah
if you needed a break that's that's fine
welcome back thank you
soon
thanks for the sneeze chats kusami
taskaroo arigato hi
hello got stuck uh working at home today
but i was finally able to watch your
life oh so that made things better
wonderful perfect all according to
kaikaku
[Music]
next
year
[Music]
yeah
one day one day i'm sure i'll go to
egypt one day
emotion thank you so
maybe it would be more
um efficient to
pay him directly
because youtube takes a cut and so on
you know
maybe we can like
wire it directly
just kidding
just kidding just kidding just kidding
i'm just joking joking
i'll get him the money in some way
i think i'm done thank you oh wow
i make it sound shifty nothing shifty
about that
nothing shifty about kfp
it's joke
what credit card number
please
need to pay
a clipper to make good video
video
please
also
uh
to book a hotel for trip with wayne
you see
this is
yes
[Music]
no no that's
that's not your clinic card
[Laughter]
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you oh thank you celebrities pizza
also thank you oh my god super toy dog
[Music]
a dog house
dog house what a clipper
oh bunk beds for all my clippers how
about that
you know sleep at the same room
right now thank you for the pinky
say no more okay
i've been shushed
thank you jim tracy duncan
[Music]
we'll end it here guys stop
bunk beds are very efficient i used to
have like um
i think very very very back in the day i
used to have a bunk bed with my brother
but then afterwards i had a bunk bed
with no bed underneath you know one of
those high beds and i had like my
computer underneath when i was still
going to
junior high school
i'm probably even partially before
like during
no actually most of junior high school i
had a normal bed
i think that was mostly
elementary school when i went when i had
that um
[Music]
that high top bed thingy
it was really cool though really uh safe
uh
space saving thank you one wonderful
tickets
it's kind of cozy
[Music]
you always gotta um climb up a ladder to
get on top of the bed
thank you come come back
[Music]
oh my god all that monopoly money oh
[\h__\h] yeah i love that that's what i'm
talking about you get it now
um um
did i miss something
i think now i'm fine
i always sleep in the upper bed
if i had to choose now
[Music]
i think yeah i would probably
probably not for the bunk for the upper
one too
[Music]
thank you
no no uh
no feathers were ripped out in order to
make that money right also i love that
umbrella that you made
play johnny thank you for the pinky oh i
would love some chicken nuggets right
now thank you
thank you very much
muchacho
thank you macho muchacho
thank you
i slept on the low one because it was
bigger oh
if you're lazy then you might want to
sleep on the moon stop it
this is oh my god
wait dakuma you're just paying me so
that i can so that i can pay you one day
right
i mean that come on that one has been
dug my has been paid before i mean some
some contributions were free but but but
but
dakoma has received payment before
barbara rank secretary
for wayne and my wife
oh thank you
recirculate the money
is that what they call money money
laundering
brandon duncan for the pinky set this
money inside for a rainy day
it will be for the rainy week we'll be
there um i think probably for like the
whole week oh god i'm feeling sick
because i'm so hungry jacob's monkey
down the stream silly fellow dancer i'm
gonna go now no more reading
i'm gonna go now okay i'm feeling
sick the game recreates i'm really
feeling sick i need to go eat now bye
bye and in german we still freelancing
i'll see you guys tomorrow
for the
for the vr chat collab i saw the stage
now
looks cute
i'm excited
everything is prepared so far
[Music]
africa saying goodnight everybody
thank you for watching today
[Music]
thank you for watching everybody
do
[Music]
you