[Music]
oh
honey oh I never tweeted about this game
[Music]
it
meting DJ keep
he we
dancing sry so emot
[Music]
ah got no Pandora what's up
how does this go
[Music]
on I will love you till I die that with
rhyme I'm asking you guys I'm alone in
these Callie isn't here
[Applause]
[Music]
yet my mic is low no that's just because
the BDM is
[Music]
loud K building Castle sky thank
you just out
us we can make it if we try just a two
of
us build building Castles in the Sky I
don't know that's probably not the
deal
[Music]
K
hello good day good day good day hello
hello
hello how's it
going
hey oh thank you for the Super Chat what
Escape for the buckets 2 years oh thank
you feels like you've been around longer
than 2
years oh chy monkey
[Music]
I'm feeling okay today last night I went
to like up until the point after the
stream until I went to bed I still had
like tummy
horde um a little bit of Ana in my
stomach I don't know why she's doing
this to me I don't know why she hates me
so much what did I do to her
huh um whoa whoo whoo whoo whoo whoo who
my game looks so the menu the UI UI
looks so big to me today is it my
imagination can I make the UI
smaller I want the UI to be smaller can
I do
that yeah it's huge
[Laughter]
right okay it's not just me
uh is it here g g youi at this one oh oh
[\h__\h] you
two H threee I like it I like this
smaller Vibe I don't have full screen on
so um considering how it's not covering
my whole screen this is kind of small I
guess but it's actually good Cy has
joined the game Callie's also streaming
guys I think I don't know if she started
yet but she's supposed to start oh what
was I saying just
now right before I did that was I
talking about Ana or what talky wony
talky wonkey she flopped right in front
of my feet oh
Kelly did you hear her
guys she's like showing me her
tummy oh she's a baby Kelly you can't
you can't prank me back I know exactly
what you're doing I see you I'm I'm way
more aware of my surroundings than you
are Kelly I don't know if she hears me
actually she's not in the VC yet
I'm putting my foot on her tummy and
she's like tickling me oh sorry tickling
you oh sorry just so you know you you
didn't surprise me at all because I I
cannot be surprised I cannot be pranked
be okay I pranked you okay well it
wasn't necessarily about surprising you
it was about it was about Annoying You
by making myself really big and then
making myself really small and then
making myself really big again and
myself really small yeah I'll move you
is this okay for
you yeah okay that's cool nice very
distant that's okay though I understand
you know you know what I'm doing I know
what you're doing I'm going to do the
same thing actually which means while go
bye-bye by she by the way did you watch
did you ever happen to watch like a clip
of the prank to see what I saw I saw I
saw it on Twitter actually
I saw you I see you I came in like
several times the clips I think lots of
the clips didn't even like put all the
moments in they cut a few even so I came
in and then I waited a while and then I
left and then chat was like oh k k and
it took you it always took you a while
until you
noticed oh yeah sounds about right and
by the time that you noticed that the
chat is saying something I was already
gone and that repeated like several
times oh yeah yeah it was pretty funny
honestly well I kept looking every time
that you showed up I happened to be
looking at
Minecraft wa even I also look at
Minecraft you know in my middle screen
but I I think I would notice like on my
other screens if something's happening
you know if someone joins the room I you
got C too big they're too big there
there's just not enough I don't have
enough eyeball to look at everything all
the time look please understand yo why
is it so big is your UI also big
it's so weird cuz usually the game is
the game screen smart oh it's cuz maybe
it's cuz I made jackbox really big oh go
okay okay H the UI if the Minecraft UI
is big I can tell you how to make it
smaller oh that's okay yeah no I I
figured out how to do it thankfully to
make the UI the UI smaller and it's been
a lifesaver especially when fly
oh oh zombie gone even though I gave him
a [\h__\h] name a that's weird maybe some
an asteroid came from the sky and killed
him or
[Music]
something okay we can find another one
easily if we just don't put torches down
somewhere but that's sad I I used a
freaking name tag on that one was
covered too I mean that's all right
these things
happen they happen rude rude rude rude
or is he like did he like down what
there's a
Golem is he with my
wait a second look at the Golem oh he
okay wait how did I not notice the Golem
before he probably killed the zombie wow
what the heck do we put him in a boat
wait are my villagers there were they
kill they no way there's no way because
there's a fence no way okay that's all
good all good with my
villagers oh that's good news ah the
Golem spawned probably because of my
Villages but wouldn't the zombie have to
be like is it because the zombie was
relatively close to the villagers to my
villagers and then somehow really the
villagers sensed it and then called for
the h interesting Chad says try to fight
him can you leash or boat a a Golem chat
that would be
helpful oh he's kind of small he's much
smaller than I thought he would be
that's a little guy a
he he feels fight him please he's a
small
King short King I mean short
King you can leash him oh okay cool oh K
this could be our first Golem I mean
they will spawn automatically anyway
once the contraption is finished but
nice or he could just literally wait no
let's leave him here because he will
protect us whenever some shitty enemy
spawns Iron Giant yeah let's call him
Iron Giant iron giant should I give a
name we don't have any more name tags I
think actually oh dang it and those are
kind of rare hard to come by right we
had we used to have so many I feel like
but nowadays they're not showing up
anymore dang it's okay it's okay knows I
guess if if it spawns once it will spawn
twice it's okay oh you know what you
know what actually chat says maybe he
killed the zombie yeah yeah yeah yeah I
said that too oh duh I'm sorry I just I
look it's been a long day
have you been a really long wait have
you greeted your viewers yet you can do
that if you want don't don't oh hi
everyone I'm so sorry I um I'm just a
bit I'm a bit scatterbrain today I had a
7-hour recording session was standing
the whole time and yeah and I didn't I
only had like four hours of sleep they
should like hi everyone don't you feel
like asking for like recording while
sitting or you want to stand oh I want
to stand so I can use my diaphragm oh
because I I've heard of some people who
just like sit down while recording ing
because it's more comfortable for them
honestly when I record stuff from home I
sit down too so mhm that's super normal
yeah I would
I
Yeahs di yeah 7 hours long time really
your not a lot of no I did a scream I
did a scream song Today
scream yeah scream song it's pretty
pretty cool but it was definitely a lot
of unravel the world unraveling the
world something like that and then I
recorded two other songs as well but
there were like features and stuff like
that so it was like half a song kind of
oh yeah just bu busy I'm okay though I I
wanted to stream today because I want to
get this iron farm working I just got to
put my nose to the grindstone you know
fre yeah wow and and a skirlington horse
oh my god let's go call I do want to say
um thank you for being so committed to
this I really appreciate it you being
here a lot no problem heck yeah I want
to help even if I'm useless I want to
help be a part of everything here doing
my best you're not useless
girl thank you I'm learning the ropes
little by little you're going to be
employee of the day if you finish that
iron farm oh employee oh cool okay I
want to be employee of the day that
sounds like a high honor yes yeah and
there's a h Stone all right let me watch
I got to watch that tutorial though and
I
know the audio is going to come through
so I need to find a way to not let you
hear that although I don't know maybe it
would be easier for you um instead of
adjusting that tutorial to less Hoppers
finding an actual tutorial that has only
like two Hoppers or so yeah from the
get-go that's like built for that that
might be a good idea I wonder if I can
find one let's see Farm Minecraft
1.15 two
Hoppers yeah I wonder if it comes up
like that I hope so
simp let's
see um it it's got to be a small one low
effort one missing Hoppers the word
Hoppers is missing from all of these
that's okay I'm going to try and make it
work and maybe I can do some more Mining
and get more iron blocks or look up look
up um I iron
xo4 I nxo in one word I x04 and then
like iron farm or so Ian xo4 yeah I A N
sorry I a oh it's okay iron
farm you find him iron farm on day one
okay I think I did
oh let's see okay I just make sure that
he's doing it for 1.15 but chat several
people said say 1.16 to 1.20
a 1.16 onwards huh does he have others
other
ones it does look pretty
simple no Lava needed either no name tag
any zombie will work easy loading
villagers and zombie into Farm
ooh I mean it looks nice it's a 30
minute
tutorial why they why they all got to be
so
long yeah is what it is
see all right I'm looking I'm looking it
should work don't think they've changed
the spawn mechanics in 1.16 okay they
think it
works okay it better be working easier
okay gotcha I'm going to turn music off
really quick so I can listen to his
speech I hope the base is similar
okay if you need to mute me to watch
that don't worry about it you can mute
me oh no it's okay you you're fine
you're
fine no
problem oh yeah chat little
update uh so there there was indeed a
problem with you know overlap not
overlapping with the stream but like
overlapping with preparations of gaa's
birthday stream so we got to figure out
a different
time um I'm trying to get everybody's
the answers soon as possible that we can
maybe do it on the weekend how did you
get out what the hell hopefully we can
do it on the weekend but then if we do
it on the weekend I was thinking um
obviously I'm taking tomorrow off cuz
like I feel
like we won't really have anything
really to do uh until the end so I think
it's fine if we all just like chill
until the last
stream um so yeah yeah that's probably
uh hopefully what's going to happen and
then everybody can you know do some
other streams if they want until that
point like Kell's doing Red Dead
Redemption stuff right red dead I'm
going to do my memb stream my watch long
and I'm going to do the the
soccer stream and stuff so I think we'll
it's maybe good that we all have like a
small break and then we can continue
slaying
the
game
yeah that that would be the ideal plan
at this
point now chat could you do you know the
date and time I guess it's G's usual
streaming time but do you know the date
what's the actual date for G's birthday
stream cuz I don't have her in my
calendar anymore for some
reason and you know
everything
620 so tomorrow okay I mean for me it
will be the day after tomorrow even I
suppose cuz it's going to be like 2:
a.m. in the
night okay okay okay
okay okay okay
okay
okay want to say sorry for being boring
I'm watching this tutorial but I think I
fig the farm will drop enough for you to
craft okay see this dude is yeah he's
definitely like um he's like f he's like
mining mining um let's
see on a sec trench into a three oh man
he's quick that's okay we'll figure it
out he's like he like goes into the
ground so I I feel like we can't go into
the ground so I'm just going to all
right calm that CH my dude hold 3 a.m.
okay okay okay good to know yeah that
makes sense that um that wouldn't work
out and that's fine no problem I thought
I saw a thumbs up but looking back there
was no thumbs up I must have like mix
something up it's okay it
happens let me figure out is it a 3X3
let's see one he's going down three
three
Focus watching
tutorial like a 3X3 in the
there are three beds lined up all right
I think I got it and then there's like
bunch of trap doors okay here's what I'm
going to do in order to kind of mimic
what's going on here um okay might as
well hey hey hey chat you guys are
mesmerizing wow that's nice cuz I feel
like I'm not very mesmerizing right now
I'm going to build something to dig into
oh yep cuz my peanut brain can't handle
things like unless they're exactly as
shown in the
tutorial you fig out
I'm I'm just going to build ground for
me to dig
into I like this yes you learning like
even such difficult things that even I
don't do like building
a I want to try well I mean I made the
haunted house work that one time right
oh that had a hop wait do you mean the H
yeah was like a yeah for Halloween of
last year um we did like a little um
haunted house and then I invited Avent
to come check it out and people did
little contributions and and I followed
a blueprint from most of that until like
maybe the last 10% 15% but it was I
don't know it was it was nice to try to
actually do something mhm you know
instead of being like ah well this looks
too difficult I guess I won't do it you
know mhm it was cool I'm glad you're
evolving I tried I'm
trying I do will be trying so be patient
with me cuz I Bae made a pumpkin yeah
she made a pumpkin and a pumpkin and a
pumpkin yeah there was some cool stuff
going on it was fun but Halloween I want
to try and do more
things I know I can if I if I really try
and put my nose to the
grindstone dang I couldn't wink because
my eyes were put my nose to the
grindstone don't put your nose to the
grindstone that new nose is precious we
want to keep it don't grind it okay yeah
true I don't want to grind it back down
to a stump
that do you like your new nose I do look
look at how so big but it's not like
it's not annoying big it's like just big
enough to make me
happy cute you know good size nose it
gives you more personality than you
already had a wow hey I'm happy was that
a lot big nose big big personality right
yeah big personality oop all right I'm
using other blocks instead of just
probably should put some
energy nose nosy let's go big
nose yeah big nose team congrats on your
nose thank you my nose surgery no
surgery went well that's the actual
surgery that you had the actual surgery
I has no
surgery don't tell anyone it's a
secret we don't want we don't want we
don't want people to
know the nose knows though the nose
knows the nose knows a wait that's a
that's a dad's joke yeah it was Father's
Day recently felt
appropriate is Father's day like
directly 1 month after mother's
day oh kind of like a white day
Valentine's Day yeah is it cuz that's
the feel the feeling I got might be
wrong no
no I felt like one month apart but I
could be extremely
wrong chat's more knowledgeable on
Father's day than I am to be completely
honest Mother's Day is in March that's
pretty much one month apart oh just
about just about a oh I saw did you see
the of course you saw the height tweet
right oh yeah Happy Father's Day k i
happy I saw that did you see my reply
they did you wanted to know why they
didn't do one for Mother's Day what the
hell and you know hey's been kind of
teasing me and
kfp like the way they're like replying
to me and stuff and then kfb is like oh
my God is she getting a hide case is she
getting a hide case in fact I'm not like
so far there's no no like talks about
that at all but they keep on getting
everybody's hopes up and
teasing ask what are you doing ask for
one I don't really I I I don't know I I
don't want to like you're a
gamer I don't want to do something like
that uh
when I I'm not sure like those items I
feel like it's maybe hard
to sell because it's relatively
expensive and big
and not everybody wants to buy a new
case so I'm not very confident in it's
selling so well but it's not really my
decision if they think that I should do
one and they think it would sell well
then they would they would probably hit
me up I guess that makes sense I don't
know when it comes to whether it sells
or not I don't care about that I'm just
kind of like oh I think some dead beats
wanted PC case and also I want a PC case
so all right so it did you originally
did you go to them and you were like hey
I I can we do also one because wait who
was
first let me see first I think it was
wasn't it ba B and the
croner really yeah they were first
pretty sure so you actually spoke up
about it okay okay not hold yeah I was
like I want it and then it turns out
that I think um one of the Hy people I'm
like they're oi like that and they did I
didn't know that I was like wa me
you okay they were more than delighted
to do that they were like yeah you want
you got it I was very happy I don't know
yet how it's decided though but I did
say yeah it would be cool if we had a PC
case for the the dead beats and they're
like all right we'll see if they'll do
it and they said
okay I did that with something else um
so yeah that that does work sometimes
but chat just so you know that's not how
it always works like usually they hit us
up and they're like hey we want to do
this and do you want to and we're like
oh okay yeah or
n okay or
n oh there's a hole okay but if there's
something we specifically want to do
then our management will try to see if
it's possible and if the company in
charge is willing to do it yeah yeah
yeah that's how it goes that's how it
work
I'm making a piece of Modern Art oo
piece of Modern Art uhhuh speaking of
piece ofy kfp you want to see I I I look
take a look yeah but Kelly can you send
me my can you send me my art come get it
come get it okay the the small one I can
like the the most recent one I can go
get oh yeah easy look small yeah okay
it's a box kfp no look at the kfp here
taking is looking that's what you mean
came get off so far is it like an empty
box yeah I haven't started digging down
yet but I'm about to start digging down
I like these like rose patterns on the
Terracotta it's pretty yeah it's cuz I
ran out of cobbly stone m all right now
let's take a little look Stone the
gobbly stone going to take a little look
see all right punch Me Harder says
g o o o K that's Kiara's job not mine
all
right y's job I think I'll do a little
mining he's just really quick so I'm
going to turn this down to like half
speed I'll do a little
mining yeah go for it first I do a
little
sorting
construction like the stuff that's
filling back up here Chad is that like
was that in the hopper or what
[Music]
what's happening 1 2
three your son coobo seems to be
betraying you yeah um that little Brad
that absolute Kaki Calli we need to do
something about her like she sees the
new members and the first thing she says
who's who's my new Mommy right so
because she already has plenty of
mommies I reply to her hey and then
which is very C like actually hey hey
hey like a really manlike and then she
gave me the Brest reply ever she was
like I'm I'm an adult I don't need you
anymore you can't tell me what to do you
know but if you're an adult and you
don't need me anymore then why do you
need any other mommy oh and she did say
like she needs money which implies that
she's not really looking for a mommy
she's looking for a sugar
Mommy I see this is typical child
behavior though from what I know yeah
she's crazy she's
crazy yeah I believe it though that's
that sounds very cobal
likee we need to like whoever can buy
her that pony or that
motorcycle speaking of which I'm
probably going to get her a pony maybe
you can buy her a motorcycle what yeah
we need to we need to divide up
the O scary we need to divide up the
responsibilities here the the
responsibilities or the
thein the spending
money what's the word what's the word
for wagon fart what
wag what's the word for spending money
uh in English yeah not all I mean the
spending the budget the spending oh yeah
I get um expenses yeah that's what it
was but I don't no that kusogaki she has
earned enough money to buy that [\h__\h] on
her
own a I guess that's true enough yeah I
mean you don't really get to choose
though when you have when you have like
a baby child and I don't speak from
experience CU I only have two cats um
but I have a mother and from from
knowing Mama Mory um it's just kind of a
just you're you know what um you can't
uh parenting is a thankless job oh yeah
they do say that they do say that maybe
at least until your child reaches a
certain adult age when it realizes uh
that it's time to thank your mommy than
yeah
exactly and it will happen eventually
just got to grow up a little bit just
wait for it it'll happen the time will
come please wait mommies please don't
lose your minds
yet not yet not yet not yet but that CR
soaky I swear to
God
yeah she is goty what can you do a
difficult one what it's down another
block okay how many more all right so
two more layers all right
this is very
deep FP
please
FP are they in the way I'm sorry he's
just watching he likes me
a a oh we have some ah you were cooking
glass there's nine glass finished I'll
let it
continue
cooking G shove him off
wait let me get the KP that I saw we did
have some glass huh did the uh guide say
you need glass in this case in this one
nope not this one I don't think oh
okay I'm just trying to dig in the
ground KOB loves her mommy though does
she she she she has barely been saying
things to me she's been like not not
giving Mommy any love
you there's ghost in yeah
yeah kids are cruel she doesn't care
about her mommy at
all a it's okay
yaha don't worry about it she hates
me coobo hates me I'm sure she
doesn't she very much loves you
still it's hard to see sometimes that's
all let's see see
surely surely this will be enough I mean
it looks cool how does he keep doing
that kids are so crel down get
[Music]
down your kfp chicken keeps coming over
to talk to me what do you want from me
little guy I have nothing to give you
ask Kiara for treats or
whatever okay KY I got something for
you come
here this one I think so he's going to
try and climb up the stairs
[Music]
again give him proper love and and
affection it's not climbable anymore
that's sad a he's cute he's so
plump for you big boy for
you see stay with
guua I think we got
all right cool that's
one kfb hearing screams of animals in
the neighboring room and are like oh oh
I hope it's not our turn next yubby
yby wait this cow yeah this cow
can this cow can
go you guys also eat wheat right uh-oh I
don't have any torches in
here damn I really need more wheat all
the
time it's okay I got wheat I got wheat
[Music]
but
wait all right guys I've dug
sufficiently into the ground I think
amazing how far you've all come with
this one block awesome work right like
this world is pretty cool I kind of want
to keep this forever I know it's pretty
nice right yeah so nice good stuff good
stuff good times oh no There Goes My
pickaxe all right I'm I'm on
back I'm going to bring a
Whatchamacallit a
torch torch you need
torches yeah that's okay ah there's a
few I have like 20 in this box let me
bring them to you o okay thank you hold
on I got to make a weapon new weapon oh
oh where is she I'm I'm over here by the
chest I know that doesn't help when I
say this world is so small and we still
keep on passing each other there you go
we do thank you more
torches there's probably more
[Music]
somewhere all right um what am I doing
what is what is the wa doing what is the
W
the yeah someone in chat says kobo's in
the rebellious child phase M I feel like
she's in that
forever she's never getting out of it no
no no no true surely
not any more oh wa this one can
[\h__\h]
torches hey why do I only have three
that's oh cuz I'm holding them in my
other hand oh my gosh I'm so Perpetual
rebellious face it's when she says it's
not a pH Mom it's literally not a phase
like she's just forever
rebellious that's just how Gobo is from
the face mom yeah that seems to be the
case
kopan
indeed oh
go I'm almost level 40 damn level 40 is
the the level of 40 is in
demand that means you've been doing a
really good job uh not dying right yeah
I hope I will not die because with this
level I could do some cool stuff in the
enchanting table I think oh for sure m
okay just got to move this way and then
it'll be a three by
three and we've got the basic starting
point the inner structure then we got to
lay the beds down can I put this on the
pickaxe guys that would be good
right so much gold oh I need the trap
doors that's
right it's good right yeah okay let's go
I got something good out of a chest for
my
pickaxe I should make a ladder honestly
oh I'm not making a
ladder let's go you heard apples oh yeah
good apples we have enough golden apples
actually oh yeah that side quest is
finished finished side
quest Golden Apple side
quest okay let's see this person puts
crab doors
there at this point guys if you think
we're doing too much it's just because
now the last stream the end episode will
be a few days later so now we're just
you know we have the excuse of there is
time so why not do more yeah exactly o
this guy's face is this looks kind like
a creeper face okay I'm going to make
ladder uh and then I have beds yeah
ladder it's just really fun to finally
have something to do again in Minecraft
for me
yeah yeah cuz you're you're a pretty big
fan of Minecraft aren't you yeah but
like I I'm not the biggest fan of
building things so my favorite thing
about Minecraft is adventuring and
finding new bomis and stuff but I've
seen them all that we you know can
see um in our server so for me it's like
I'm waiting for the next Minecraft
update so that I can look at new stuff
look at new animals new enemies and
stuff yeah but this opportunity in this
one block Minecraft gives me the chance
to start from scratch again and it's
been really cool like having problems of
iron for example getting iron or getting
even the simplest things that's really
rare that that experience you only have
in the beginning when you play Minecraft
for the first time and right well
actually no not not even then because
iron when you play the game normally
even then even if you don't have an iron
farm it's not such
a huge problem
usually but we had a huge problem of
iron yeah we
did yeah we did and I'm kind of we're
fixing it too late but that's okay no no
no no now now is the best time now is
the best time actually I can put a
ladder here that's what that was
supposed to be for okay lad time stop
lad time lad time
[Music]
still in a dream
sake the ladder it's always the
ladder you should eat oh you're right m
m yummy time I completely forget about
that and then I see that I have the eggs
and then I I remember that Minecraft
doesn't take place in Japan so you can't
just eat the raw egg
oh yeah that's that's I think tourists
are or not even tourists just generally
foreigners who don't know much about
Japan they might be surprised that
there's so much like raw egg in all the
dishes in Japan but super normal yeah
it's pretty normal there and the raw
eggs are super safe there oh yeah and it
makes everything tastes like really
really yummier in my opinion like
Sukiyaki or like I like tamago Kaka
which is like yeah RW egg on H
rice yeah can be good can be good for
Sukiyaki when you like dip stuff into
the raw egg mixture which is not a
mixture it's just a raw egg twir um yeah
I I I like that too but I when I dip it
I try to only get like a small amount of
the egg the meat I don't want it to be
like absolutely dripping with the egg
you know oh yeah there are definitely
some people that like want it to be
drippy for sure mhm not me not me yeah
you don't seem like that kind of person
that would be into that
so um I want to feel like this can go
[Music]
somewhere
okay
BS you got three beds there you go
okay actually what do I do I was making
some actually was going to make some
books but then I was breeding the
cows and then I wanted more
wheat but the wheat is growing
slowly very slowly okay okay that's
fine okay guys look I'm making proog
look I'm making progress dead beats
look w already make the potion no but uh
the books that I'm making I want to make
I'm preparing the books for the the not
the potion maker for the enchanting
table actually yeah the potion make I
saw I saw it like yesterday
somewhere in one of these
chests okay now we got to Contin here it
is see guys it didn't break what's next
brewing stand is so back where should we
put it let's put it somewhere else okay
let's put it
here told
you
P okay so we're going to hollow out
behind that how many minutes are you
into the video
Kelly um four wow four the
FR let's go you can do it
come I flip it down flip it back up
after it's down and then I go two in
flip it down and then flip it up and
then go two
in what is this what is
this and
then random crap
chest that part behind that
okay got
it yeah there are a lot of random crap
chest hanging around sorry I really got
I'm I'm actually trying to like sort a
little bit as well so just to help you
out a little bit thank
you one block one block that fits in
here did I
not oh well I think they can go in here
too the thing with eggs is that we treat
them in America and it destroys a
membrane on the egg that makes them the
way they are oh a
membrane
oh any raw egg can have salmonella but
that doesn't mean all raw eggs will if
you trust the source of your eggs go for
it if not I
wouldn't yeah at least like you don't
have to worry about it at all in Japan
it
seems that's good yeah I'm a raw egg fan
so if you're the type of person who
loves their protein and stuff and chugs
five raw eggs in the
morning then go live in
Japan yeah do that I've met a person
like that and I I was watching them chug
it's it was a very buff person actually
was a um yeah they need their protein it
was actually a f relatively famous
person that you guys might know but I'm
not going to say the name
but uh
they were chugging yeah it was Gaston in
person Gast gon no one eats five billion
eggs like a Stan I know that they were
chugging those eggs in the morning I was
like ew and know it was in a at at an
event so
anyway I was like how how
how can you at least like put salt and
pepper in that raw egg mixture and enjoy
a bit more like that I wonder is that
acceptable I mean yeah I mean at the end
of the day I'd still prefer cooked over
raw came down to it
right it was actually Yago
Yago I don't think Yago chugs raw eggs
in the morning he seems pretty fit but
not like that type of crazy
fit right
this boat really is moving around a lot
F though if it stays here s this there
the boat should be fine if it's right
here see Kelly that the uh oh oh
beautiful
parot Kelly beautiful parrot new color
that we didn't see before Oh red with
yellow and blue but mostly red nice
Red's a good color that's like the most
beautiful typical parrot ever oh but I
was going to say did you see um the
whole life Japan and I guess Ian to
Twitter they changed their profile
pictures uh to the Justice logo which I
don't think they did they ever do that
before I don't think so and so I
literally didn't recognize their their
um account when they were on my timeline
I was like who the [\h__\h] is this oh nice
good job who the [\h__\h] is this
yeah I didn't even notice
that it's like new phone H
this uhoh this seems bad okay it's fine
we'll just rebuild right they they've
had the usual cover logo for
ages so that was oh oh H let's see how
this is going to go hey protect me Golem
protect me
oh oh good job MW I love this Golem he's
just protected me from one of those
flying vexes Skelly what a nice guy he's
such a nice guy he's kind of useful
maybe we shouldn't put him in the F yeah
yeah I think he should stay here cuz the
they will spawn anyway in what you're
building automatically oh yeah
exactly we need more Golems on the
ground body guard and then it just walks
up from here I feel like this is going
to encroach on the storage space but it
is what it is
oh can't be helped
encroach interesting enro on
it oh yeah it means it's going to get up
in it sh uh it's going to it gets in the
way
J useful H useless book useless
book want here
[Music]
hold
on I'm crouched it's good I need to be
crouched no please don't do
that okay
I know I know I can heal the Golem but
right now he still looks very
fine he's doing well don't think he
needs a heal right
now he's very buff he also chugs those
eggs in the
morning yeah and uses antlers in all of
his
decorating did you get that Kiara the
STA what yeah never mind it doesn't
freaking matter he's like from a Disney
movie right stop it wait you don't know
wait huh oh he's from a Disney movie
right
G yeah yeah he is do you know which one
uh I think
um oh yeah the
Beast
n it's just funny to me that it took you
a minute to to remember what he's from
he no no no no that's what I've been
thinking about since the first time we
mentioned
him it's he's just such a a meme I
watched Beauty and the Beast recently
when I was recovering from surgery
so a Disney kick and like a wait which
one the classic one oh yeah yeah yeah
classic of course um I'm just kind of on
a Disney kick where I'm like thinking
about like old Disney movies and stuff
like that and like um also not just not
only that but like also like funny like
Disney like haha funny funny Disney
YouTube videos where people like edit
the characters and make them do funny
things oh there's funny Disney Disney
funny Disney videos yeah YouTube Doo
YouTube do
da yeah you guys know the videos I'm
talking about right it's the good stuff
right hand me your
Vios s them to me I don't think you have
a different different name in
germanone probably I guess so this
doesn't sound no not
sure maybe in yps is pretty good that
brings me back to my school days my kids
would be like look at this funny video I
found on
YouTube and they' play it and be like no
the
teachery teach's going to get mad that's
an inappropriate video
d d
[Music]
d how
manys I wonder let me go ahead and check
oh he's still okay I kept it
playing all
right so dude goes up there I want these
chest I will literally never open the r
chest I've opened the just a million
times and I still don't know what is
where oh my
God are you guys losing your minds over
that cuz I
am I certainly am
steps seven steps I believe it's too
many chests no you're
not you're not
really 4
5 6
good good decent
book going to work great guys it's going
to work
awesome you'll
see I put labels on mine yeah those are
unlabeled would probably help to put
labels but even here I don't look at the
labels who knows if they're still
accurate though if you don't need
to yeah
[Music]
sorting is visually pleasing
really really running out of blocks here
cat this looks new uh we got a new music
disc oh it's new it's
new
wait let's listen to
it pump up them jems pump it up while
you're feet on the floor pump pump it up
pump up JS Pump It Up why your feet on
the floor oh yeah I love it I love that
one get down get down
guua
oo that's
good wait hold on no I should
be it should be correct never
[Music]
mind all
right not remind reminds me of mini
motorways mini motorways yeah yeah it
reminds me of the music that plays
during mini
motorways puts me into a trans it sounds
like several plimp Plum tracks
overlapped oh okay now it's getting
better
[Music]
yeah kill it
I'm about to run out of cobbly stone oh
my Lord all right we got to find another
block what block should we do now
guys oh I'm going to die hello
[Music]
KY Kelly what do you think about
jojoa oh that's a hot opinion thing that
people are talking about
huh oh man my opinion
is I don't have one you don't have
one
no not in particular oh okay okay not
even a top nine JoJo says chat all right
that's
cool cuz I watched a deep dive about her
cuz I had like absolutely no idea who
who she was and uh what she's all about
and then I found out she's from that uh
dance toddler dancing show or what
Dancing Yeah dance mom's Dance Mom's
show I do feel for the people that were
on that show that's a pretty terrible
shitty ass horrible show yeah I do feel
for them the way the kids are being
treated and how biased that teacher lady
[\h__\h] sorry but like Mama Mia the way
she treated those kids and the dance
mom's out crap crap crap crap crap yeah
those are oh no yeah those are those are
children and I get the world is Harsh
and it's good to figure out how to
handle criticism early but um those are
children those are those are little
literal babies that don't their brains
aren't ready for
that there's a way to ease them into it
and that's not it it's done you okay G
yeah what's going are you really okay
yeah
yeah crap sounds like a battle's going
[Music]
on did she
survive
oh you laying eggs again is what says
yeah she's laying eggs again
yeah oh my God
Jesus they're really that painful to lay
eggs my good
goodness take a
break take a break from the
eggling how do you do that birth
breathing is it breathe in twice and
breathe out once or is it breathe in
once and breathe out
twice oh my
God two twice in one long out
[Music]
it's okay it's getting better it's
getting
better thanks for the memberships oh oh
those are the eggs that I just
laid oh my Lord what the
heck thanks thanks live egg laying on
stream my goodness do I need to do I
need to
AG not the first time this
happening
[Music]
huh yeah
yeah what have you never laid an egg on
the stream before
c let me
think
um no I haven't I have not ever done
that before in my life but what's it
like tell me tell me about it what's it
like it hurts
but the relief when it's gone is so so
much bigger than the pain when you have
a choice to not to not do it well why
would I not do it when it when it comes
out it's got to come out you
know okay
but but I mean I don't know is is it is
it something that happens no matter what
even if a chicken like doesn't like do
anything quote unquote you know anything
even if the chicken doesn't like meet a
nice uh a nice rooster for example like
even if the chicken doesn't meet a nice
rooster does the egg still like come
out in all world yes in all world yes if
you say
so all right trust me believe me trust
me bro if you have to get rid of them
you have to get rid of them somehow it's
got to go out oh either way some way
better out than in Shrek always saids
exactly wait how did I only oh never
mind I got more
okay
torial hold this
n yeah H lay not fertilized eggs all the
time says chat some of those American TV
shows are [\h__\h] up is what I was trying
to say I agree definitely are and chat
might actually be surprised that this
once um I don't like when of these
shitty TV
shows are you a big fan of shitty TV
shows us no actually not like on that
level like those are all [\h__\h] like
actual like not not good not good not
good at
all oh everybody just
suffers the moms were suffering too
partially but the moms are just
basically stage Moms living vicariously
through their kids and and getting that
Fame through TV through their kids and
getting it through drama and the TV
producers are [\h__\h] too because they they
script those things and they cut those
things in a way to make the kids or the
the ladies the moms look bad and and H
it's just all a [\h__\h]
show Showbiz is full of evil people can
you believe it I believe it I believe
it absolutely believe it
true Aquarius break
you tell them y waa I'm telling I'm
telling them I'm telling it how it is
waa speaks the truth
always do it for the ratings and that
sucks yeah exactly mhm how about them
ratings well I'm rating it zero out of
10 because it's
[\h__\h] it's not worth like having children
grow up so in such a traumatic way with
such traumatic
experiences agree like imagine like
practicing and dancing your ass off for
like 10 hours per day or so when you're
like I don't know eight years old or so
and then you're actually like really
[\h__\h] good like amazing and and they
still like somehow have it out for you
and Target you and they're like oh
you're [\h__\h] you
suck oh my God it's just so not worth it
it's so sad seeing kids work their ass
up and then get nothing from it besides
yeah especially cuz when you're a kid
it's like you know that's like the time
of dreams you know like you have dreams
that you want to see come true to a
certain extent that kind of training
surely for some girls uh or boys too for
some of them for some kids it might work
you know some of them might get
motivated from that motivated from that
and and will actually get a a kick out
of it but doesn't work on every child
you you have to like adjust the way you
treat and teach a child and train them
depending on their personality and all
that it might not work for everybody
like treating them like [\h__\h] doesn't
work for
everybody yeah I also but I also am uh
of the opinion that the opposite is also
not very good so like everybody gets a
golden star kind of thing um I think
that that should not it should not be
that way unless there's like one kid in
the class that isn't getting an award
and every other person oh uhoh you know
it's like maybe let's who did that agree
though oh my God that donkey is living
dangerously on the edge who did that oh
we should sleep because Phantom is out
oh Phantom yeah sleepy sleep
yeah not everybody needs a gold star
though it builds
character also
that uh the the reason why they had it
filmed in that one Studio one of the
reasons is also [\h__\h] up it's just
because the location the state or so
where it was located in had really
really loose uh children working labor
laws so that they can have them work
longer hours and stuff like that film
longer hours for the show like that's
the simple reason why they filmed it
there so that they can you know have
them work their ass
off I'm going to answer a quick question
um in my chat sorry it it involves a
piece of
merchandise yeah there is a there is a
members only version of my my new album
that's out um someone was asking how
much it is I believe that it is
$31 it's a it's a special cover that's
drawn by stud it so if you want the
physical version grab it it's very cool
pretty yeah it's members only that one
is so hope you guys like how is a
members only how does that work so the
way that they do it is it's like you
access it via a QR code or like Link in
community post it's only for members cuz
yeah descriptions are visible to
everyone they know that but mhm members
only descriptions are visible to
everyone even if you're description of a
video you mean or yeah oh okay okay okay
yeah I thought you met the community
post I was
like no no no no no those are definitely
a me mems only those are okay oh yeah
just wanted to answer
that where do we go next from here oh
person who's telling me how to make this
please Ian
Ian
meach me the ways
we're getting
somewhere no don't don't leave come back
come
back
trench okay and then trap doors
got so ti so TI put two beds over there
three more beds over there okay
three more beds I need three more beds
get
out get out good thing we got sheep get
out mom m there giving birth again no
it's just so much in this chest that I
don't know what oh my God maybe we
should just make random chests to just
throw things into even if we no we will
never find things ever again yeah but
like we don't need them though we don't
need those things
you have the shears
yes gra those from you there you go
thank you step by step step by step even
if it's overwhelming we'll get it step
by
step okay
w got to mine some more what am I
looking for right
now bone blocks blocks iron blocks oh
thanks for the gift memberships that's
kind all kinds of
fans Lea iron yeah
[Music]
yeah basically trying to come wait for
those cows to make more Babble
babos
yeah enough okay we just need a little
more come on grow some WS
go okay let me feed some more of them
wish you could like bone meal on the
animals so that they grow up faster I
know I was literally about to say that
but I thought it's that is
stupid what yeah I was thinking the same
thing bone meal on animals maybe you can
like give them treats or something you
know in an update for some
like that would be kind of sick wa W
okay what is this for new three
beds that's a lot
of meaning cotton candy in
Japanese have you had that um like uh
you know the what myai had that collab
of that uh lamb Shabu shaboo Place yeah
did you ever go to that place before
uh-uh cuz they serve you know they serve
this like plate of raw lamp meat right
and then on top of on it yeah the super
fluffy cotton Cy top it looks so nice it
looks so cute I did see that that look
pretty yum but I didn't get a chance to
try it out I actually I went no no I
liked it I went there with vame sire
banai auki S I think there was one more
person there maybe um and we ate
together uh when it was like Senai
collaboration and we did shabo shaboo
all together and you know they gave us
like a lot of merchandise from what
collaboration to that sounds so fun mhm
the heck cool yeah yeah good times good
times I got to go there at some point
I'll find a way to go there at some
point honestly they already had it like
twice maybe they'll do it again at some
point oh fingers crossed I mean the
collaboration the the lamp with the
cotton candy I think you can have at any
time yay
cool of course they chose wat for that
yeah say have some real Cotton kid
that's what her name means
after you're not hungry yet what the
hell why you not hungry that's just one
okay never mind I messed up all right
all good Chan collaborations chees
yeah
man it's so cool that in Japan stuff
like that is even possible
mhm yeah I'd really love an Ian
Cafe I love an Ian Cafe didn't we
here and there we have those anyway
already in nepon in in
Japan okay maybe not yeah yeah I want
one that I can go to really easily
instead of having to go to that you got
to go during non opening
hours oh yeah of course otherwise that
would be dangerous very very
dangerous over
night see okay
makes a
line that oh no oh
God it's like a
trench difficult looks
difficult yeah I'm just going to have to
expand okay expandi pill expand it's a
serious illness that's a lot of people
in the world are affected by these days
yeah expand dongus
a lot of people are yeah quite common
from what I've heard oh well second time
I heard about it in these past in this
past
week
yeah see maybe it's 9 by
five 9 by five trench I
think so one two four five six 7 8 9
and we have to
expand it's okay we'll make it
work I'm not afraid of anything I'm not
afraid of hard work yeah maybe
definitely
aren yeah hey what's up
guys feeding
time come on eat the breads where you
going why they're hiding from me they're
scared of me what what are you doing
why what they're discussing how they're
best going to assassinate me what's the
best way to assassinate takanasi
stop their plotting stop it I'm giving
you bread and beds in a nice fancy house
what else do you want jobs too like hey
and and and the Golem's protecting you
like this is the
life you going to go
oh my
[Music]
God all these random blocks are
hilarious cuz it's so
disorganized think any of these can be
burned oh I could buy
bookshelves wait no we're not using lava
anyway so it doesn't
matter mag baby make a
baby make a
baby go got
it is there more beds oh do I have to
won't they won't they make a baby if
there's not enough
beds they better remember how much bread
I gave to them yeah be
grateful well that is at least like um
economically smart of them to not make
any more babies if they don't have any
more beds in their
home yeah they can ially
smart a good economic decision makes
sense and I shall make more beds
although I might have to make a second
floor for that house but I don't want to
I don't want to make it too big I think
we don't need to go
crazy yeah we don't need a a Trader for
everything just been until here we check
the tutorial
do will you need beds for
your uh Farm what the iron farm well I
already made them don't worry about it
okay
nice s Ka n uh-huh can we sleep two
three four hold on five yes five gotcha
oh yeah we can go we can sleep let's
sleep after I put down a couple torches
H it's very frightening
mhm
okay all right and we can
sleep guys do you want bgm again should
I put bgm on again Chad like we had
before I've just Oh you mean like yeah
regular yeah we should that'd be nice
I'm going to put something
no sure yes
no actually that's quite a few
nose yeah I don't know what it is that
feel like for this stream people have
been like no bgm please which is really
interesting well then if you need bgm
then I guess it's
it bring your own bgm to work
day is this
normal on the
floor oh they're definitely bugged let
me try to get them up oh they are up M
this version of Minecraft this mod is
very
buggy mhm
oh yes
[Music]
H you remember that I gave you bread
guys right or do you need more again
they
forgot
[\h__\h] okay yeah it looks like we're
going to have to end up leading
villagers over to this you think we can
do that get in the bed easy all right
villager master I feel like you're such
like master of using or utilizing
villagers from what I've seen well well
well I am the creator of
phix
uh yes yes yes esteemed founder the
original uh
F from the
hver and this is
uh
practically uh Phoenix's
Stone uh
numero yeah uh do it nice I don't know
what this is French Italian who who the
[\h__\h] knows one of them it's a
mix
mix we we we we peepee wee we peee ah oh
yeah um
well speaking of like uh different
languages and yeah different languages
so now that the girls have been
Unleashed on Twitter Unleashed yeah we
know about them so do we and we see
their designs fully already I'm
surprised the all of the artists from
Justice already put out the full
reference sheets for them did you see oh
yeah I did it took it took me three
years to
get yeah it seems like they kind of um
decided on all of them putting it out
with like even the same description kind
of um seems to
a thing a pattern for them yeah they
have some sick weapons right mhm yeah I
want to fight him fight him but no we
will we will watch Advent and justice
fight it out and see who
survives and then we can beat up the
Survivor yeah survival of the
fittest ah whole life English is just
Hunger
Games oh yeah it's just Hunger Games in
case you
no I feel like there's no power creep
anymore though what no power creeping
what yeah one's I it means that I feel
like I can beat up the new people you
know without them being like these
miraculous gods that can defy death
right that's what I was worried about is
that we just get more and more powerful
people and then I'm not going to be able
to beat up even my co
yeah yeah yeah want to beat up our K
yeah beat them up beat them up beat them
up Kai should not be able to so easily
beat up Senpai I mean they can I want a
fair fight is the main thing I want fa
want a fair
fight yeah I want a fair fight what's
what you want an advantage Kiara we
already have an advantage I mean I guess
that's true but fair and square is
good I'm a phoenix they can't do nothing
about me all right Kiara if you say so
if you say so wait they they have like
an official description out already too
right wait let me see live English
Justice there was like a press release
right yeah yeah yeah let's see let's see
right we have Elizabeth Rose blood flame
code name the Scarlet Queen ooh um so
far guys uh I've been calling her and I
would like people to pick this up uh
because she has a really long name
you're free to steal it from me I've
been calling her herb
it's Rose blood no it's the first three
letters of her name BB yeah I'm just
been calling her
herb she's uh her April her April her
birthday is in April she's from great
ardia whatever that means uh oh ah some
of the data is like oh wait it says here
uh herb paves the way for the world and
all of its people she does how she paves
away for the world and all of with
people how all right maybe I was wrong
about the power creep yeah I was wrong
not only does she stand at the Forefront
during missions with her physical
prowess but she also captures the hearts
of all around her with a beautiful
singing voice mhm oo she does have a
beautiful singing voice yeah we heard it
she heard it she gave us actually in our
first meeting she gave us a a beautiful
you know how do you say it she saged for
us demo yeah demo she demoed her voice
for us it was it was crazy lovely lovely
so she's highly self- disiplined and a
bit too hard on herself that sounds like
my
description but perhaps due to her
culture's emphasis on politeness and
manners okay we're hinting at something
here she tends to Gull a bit soft on
those around her as a result she spends
her days stressed out with her work
coordinating justice but it seems like
there's nothing uh a nice nap in comfy
bed can't fix okay ooh
relatable yeah have you guys noticed she
has like a a flamy blue flame on her on
her middle
chest that looks really cool FL on the
inside she's flaming you think it's open
like y if I put my finger in there am I
like inside of her where are you
sticking your finger into Kar the the
blue the blue flame chop it Oh you mean
in the flame yeah yeah blue is the
hottest fire in case you didn't know
like really hot burning stars that blow
up he y That's undermining my fire oh
okay again the power creep I was wrong
about
sorry well yeah she looks really cool
she seems to be like the mature of type
out of these four right uh I like the
red and blue combination I think she
will look really really nice next to
narissa yeah red and blue hair is so
cool they look so nice the best color
combo in my opinion I love that yeah
next is gigy murin or wait was it gig or
gigy it's Gigi but I want to call her
gigy for fun yeah I might call her gigy
too G
yeah um it's like how I say Digimon I
say Digimon usually cuz that's how they
say it in German
yeah so yeah so she's the Chaser
apparently I mean she seems fast
yeah um it says born and raised under
the flag of Freedom oh
wait doesn't well that that okay I mean
the the other one was you know in the
polite and M some subtle Clues here
there are definitely Clues there uh geky
murin
is I can't I can't help it it's locked
in gigy Morin is a free spirit to Chaser
and mischievous gramlin while she is
proficient in chasing down targets with
pure intuition she struggles with
memorizing directions uhuh and making
calculated decisions yeah that's what
she looks like she states that she'd
rather not spend much time thinking
because it makes her head hurt
uhuh is it like a pattern like the
smaller uh girls in whole life have like
smaller brains seemingly whoa there but
yeah also I think you're on to something
but I'm definitely an outlier in that
situation cuz by all if if that's true
then I should be small no you're just
using up all your brain cells for your
work and then when you you know do other
things sometimes maybe the brain cells
are already used up for the day thank
you for coping for me I appreciate that
coping on my behalf but I just don't
know if I can agree no I I I agree for
you it's very sweet of you it continues
as uh these quirks are also present in
her everyday life where she tends to
prioritize her instinctual craving for
fun and being silly over anything else
she's often the source of headaches for
those around her causing trouble because
she thought it would be
funny a okay cool I'm interested in
seeing if that will actually transpire
like yeah in reality I want to see I
want to see is she really a a silly
little silly little Gremlin not all
Gremlins are are meme Lords though so
I'm curious a little Lord so far meme
Lord Gremlin or like I don't know
regular old kusogaki Gremlin that isn't
educated on memes I'm curious I want to
know I think she is I think she is I
think she's educated on memes and her
Doodles are so
cute she's a good doodler I think her
design is my favorite out of the bunch
what do you think who's your favorite so
too yeah yeah well my f actually no my
favorite is RA oh that one's really damn
good yeah but I really like her hoodie
and I love the the hair uh color
variation of the light uh Brown and the
dark brown and and and she's so cute
she's so cute the little the little
pigtails are cute and she's orange and
that's
nice
she's I like all of them yeah so the
next one is Cecilia emmer green green
emmer Green
shre immer in German means ever so this
is like Evergreen like evergreen tree
yeah I think that was on purpose so it
says she is an ancient automaton with a
pent for flowers tea and creating music
oh tea another tea person mhm crafted
during ancient times cilia was
originally made to be dedicated to
Eternal servitude o yet in recent times
she began slacking off on her work o
lazily cooking mostly potato potatoes
pot
potatoes potatoes I'm feeling something
I'm sensing something with whatever else
you found in the kitchen she has now all
but abandoned her duties doing the bare
minimum and mostly immersing herself in
various crafty Hobbies with Newfound
interests in life she takes on every new
experience with pure curiosity of a
young girl no oh she seems like the LI
headed no Airhead airheaded yeah and
sweet kind of personality maybe aaton
that like doesn't understand like human
things like IUS from Persona 3 that's my
favorite Persona game and there's a
character that's just like but she's not
a character this is a real person but
still you get what I'm saying yeah yeah
she seems soft and in her design first
of all I love the the dark green that's
going on it's beautiful um and her
design is really beautiful and she has
that um that violin
yeah
beautiful really interesting looking so
far and people are getting kind of crazy
about her limbs uh which is also a nice
feature getting crazy about them what
does that mean what does that entail
getting crazy I think she'll
actually like she's kind of matching
robai oh yeah I get that that idea yeah
she's not fully a robot aat is a little
different yeah but they're kind of
matching doll like
yeah yeah okay so I finally AG green a
new green
member exciting and the next one is a
pink one yeah and I think her brain is
also very Pink as they like to
say uh ra
ra I might up saying it the Japanese way
ra ra what do you can you say it how you
going to say it
yeah p p panta I don't know a difficult
name to say um the artist with the god
eyes Raa panta is endowed with
investigative investigative and
descriptive prowers her means of
information cing are diverse utilizing
not only her agility and social skills
but also various social media platforms
and other dot dot unique methods huh
what does that mean what are they
implying I that means what does it mean
what does that mean I don't know
actually what are they implying I
actually am at a loss I have no is it
the the pink stuff
like like flirtiness or so I don't know
or we find out I don't know the face
Composites composits composits
comp comp Kelly help mug shots that she
draws crime how do you how do you
pronounce it composits composits she
draws based on the information she
gathers are renowned for their accuracy
almost as if she was looking directly at
the criminals she as she draws maybe she
was however these days her gaze is
directed towards finding a new finding
new pizza
joints okay
okay totally not a hint uh and enjoying
the pop culture of the Far
East come
on spicy me B
piz oh we're going to have fun I'm gonna
we're going to have so much
fun yeah so her design is super cute she
has that big tail did you guys see my
tweet at her where I drew um I drew a
good fan art of her asking her if that's
her it's a Well drawn composite drawing
I think she will get that a lot um yeah
composite pink P she is literally a pink
panther she is there's no lie that is
what she is no I really like the way she
looks I like those spiky fluffy hairs I
like those ears I like the big like
chunky tail it's not like super fluffy
right but it's
chunky yeah I read an interesting uh
kind of theory about like the colors
that they have and whatnot in in like
contrast to us so I saw someone make a
point over the fact that like for
example fauna is nature she is of course
nature incarnate and then cilia is like
machine right but they're both green and
then ra is light and I'm Darkness but
we're both
so like they show and uh and Elizabeth
is red and so is so is hakos CH Bales
but ba is chaos and Elizabeth is order
so like there's this kind of like
they're reusing how
light cuz look at her outfit it's white
Oh you mean light and color okay okay
yeah yeah yeah she's got like this
brightness to her yeah but like B is
chaos and then Elizabeth is kind of you
know order right they're both red so
it's like there's no over there's no
real overlap even though the colors are
the same I forget what the what the Gigi
one was I forget what that well she's
orange yellow
or orange I think that what did they say
I forget what it was I forget what it
was I didn't see that I to you I don't
know I think it's cool though I like
that they're using the same colors but
it's not a total overlap
yeah
yeah yeah g is small and K is big I
guess that
workfield I don't think it's a stretch I
don't think it's a stretch at all I
think it's actually smart can you
imagine if there was another dark pink
lady I'd be like a
uh yeah I mean eventually it might
happen because rtic there's not you know
in in hello project the idol company
that I really like um they also give
everybody an image color but they just
have so so so many members not as many
as AK could be but still um like for
example in morning musim they have so
many members Sometimes they come and go
but uh at times where they have like 12
15 members or so they really struggle
with giving out different colors right
and then eventually they had to give
someone like brown and you know those
girls are not really happy about having
Brown is their image color so they call
it like macaron color or so something
cute to make it sound
cuter but that's like the where you end
up at if you give image colors to people
and you try to keep everybody separate
now here in all life we have some
overlap because can't be helped right
can't be helped can't be helped
eventually we're going to hit every
color of the rainbow but at least we can
do like different combinations well so
far we had no Brown yet though no Brown
and all did we have I don't think we
ever had black we've been having white
but no black oh I'm waiting for a black
and white that wait hold on shy is it
black CH IM color is black oh M wait m
is brown I am right oh my God she is
yeah oh let's go yeah TR true true
true her it's like a what do I say she's
so cute I I don't know it's it's hard to
hard to descri I think Brown is cute
brown is cute yeah I think it's very
aesthetically pleasing and like
furniture and
stuff was what was I just saying
uh where's the if we have a black uh who
who did you say Shi shot is black and
white but not she's image color seems to
be purple when looking at the talent
whole life Talent website oh yeah I
guess so huh no black I think we should
get a black I mean then the question is
what penlight color would they use I
think you can just go for white then you
know just like the opposite of it just
give it white I think it's supposed to
be one block deeper oh God black would
be cool would be sick yeah it is one
block deeper oh my God this freaking he
goes so
fast I'm on two times speed and it's so
quick okay it's
fine
whatever whatever
please make a baby please y yeah I need
to let more of them grow so I can make
more babies instead of slaughtering
them um oh man sorry guys again I'm I
think I'm more productive than yesterday
cuz I'm more uh awake but it's still
rough to do so many things at
once taking my time why are these eggs
in here no one will ever know
and you can't like use rabbit hard for
books the same way you can use leather
right even though it looks so similar I
wish you could I wish you
could yeah at least I have cie here from
the start hi that's
good I'm just grinding along trying to
baby's first iron farm
a at least I'm doing something kind of
it it seems like it's
working so well I mean I haven't tested
anything but you know what I mean like
it I'm making it work even though it's a
bit
[Music]
tough okay well I don't have enough
rabbits it seems oh well four rabbit
hide to make leather I'm pretty sure I
saw some rabbit hide I I have two but
you need four I don't think we have
more oh no we do actually we do have
wait is that the the one I just put in
what the hell no no we do have four we
have exactly
four all
right okay cool that's at least
something then that's out of the
way disenchant is a good idea what
disenchant
what cil's birthday is one day after
mine let me look at their birthdays
again
is May 11 which already passed Cecilia
is November 11 which is coming up
still
uh gigy is October 18 which is coming up
and yeah herb is April
25th a good it's a good day right herb
the
herb makes me think of like uh like an
herb you know like
a that
plant what do something Golem do
something what you looking at he's like
you got to protect yourself
woman oh he's doing something now he's
going to die probably this is pretty
rough protect me while I'm getting a
sword
all right I'll spawn a gazillion
more okay uh the the dude is gone now
it's just the
vus nice sweeping Edge good ah don't
don't die
Golem
[Music]
come I want to help
him where did it
go good
job well I have reunion in my head too
these
days yeah yeah I've been using it as the
intro for this these streams
oh yeah the instrumental I've been using
it fix the Golem but okay I guess we can
use
some some iron like one one piece can I
ask a question says chat you can but I
might not answer it CU I'm collabing
with guwa which one hey what's up answer
it don't worry
okay well no it's just somebody said can
I ask a question oh so I'm like all
right ask it oh ask away how do you till
the um the soil ah you need a hole you
need a
hole a ho there's a hole in the in the
tools
chest oh okay I did it
okay all
right hi guys put oneing
in I'm making it an iron farm I
think we'll find out you can do it oh
wait no all the all the hey come back
why is it turning back to dirt stop
that which one's say you could do that
[Music]
stopy give
me need some water oh is that what it is
I need water oh now my hoe's gone okay
and the there's a hoe in the tools chest
oh thanks let me keep watching that
tutorial let's see the torch
proof out a hole to turn the dirt along
one side into
Farmland
okay h
nobody's taking the
job H
okay all right so I need water need
water bucket you know how to do it can
we go get that
water okay get a bucket and go to the
endless water source yeah you taught me
yeah plant seeds in the Tilt ground it
won't break them to become dirt again
but you need water to keep it from going
back when you break the seed freaking
Slackers man
oh wait he just got the job
right we'll just oh yeah okay we we'll
just wait I have the bucket oh it's just
it's a little it's
trapped
oh
hi look I'll show you boat is this the
Bodacious boat come on dud a regular
boat come on
[Music]
dudes I'll be
back's okay take your time no I'm I
meant the the the to the uh
villagers oh okay I'm still with you
don't that's scary
place strange and scary okay you guys
you know what I'll focus on
now the
bookcases one bookcase needs okay three
books six planks how many bookcases do
we want
chat
for what version are we playing on it's
1.15.2 if that really matter
okay
15 and what's what's the uh enchanting
table let me look up a uh recipe
Minecraft enchanting
[Music]
table o obsidian oh and two diamonds and
one book
okay make it for small I think I made it
too small dang it that's fine how do I
take one I will never
know wait two diam [\h__\h] wait one Diamond
two diamonds wait is it like
no mine under it take one there a lot of
me watching tutorials sorry
guys you can use your Emerald Sur B CU
yeah I was thinking so too
yeah I might do that I I'll make a few
myself and then oh I
see it's long ways
okay never mind I did it right was
there no longer nice
rip rip diamonds uh I need
four four
obsidian and one book okay so uh
enchanting table
okay yeah I made
it now we need an area for it that
can uh oh actually I'll build it right
here in the
back let me make my
hole I don't know if I put like we're
going have to get rid that L
here
maybe and around it will be the
bookcases 15 it's like two rows I think
from what I usually
[Music]
see show this now I need to figure out
where they plant how long will the
stream be today not super super long uh
I want to just finish enchanting table
and iron farm thingy probably that'll be
it cuz I want to get some stuffed
done uh IRL after the stream
understandable I also want to sleep you
too right don't you have you're going to
sleep and then you have red
Redemption yeah
oh so 5 hours so 12
hours
while no it might not even go up to 5
hours who
knows okay let me watch this part of the
tutorial again and half speed even
though it feels like it's going at light
speed we'll go with the flow chat go
with the
blow um ah
okay all blocks
placed and then my D starts digging X
doubt okay that's fair oopsie what did I
just oh
yeah um y y y oh wait I got a totem of
dying sick
sick hey no I'm not so mad that uh p o
spawned
yeah have a couple totems of undying
that I was trying to save for the nether
a
couple yeah away from the bed hey yeah
there's like four or something like that
I yeah so the torch is away actually the
torch right here and then ho it oh my
God please don't do it's the opposite
okay I got it guys I got
it it in the
Farmland won save you from the void well
it will save me a death from the Ender
Dragon it's good it's good I will not
fall into the
void I Will
Not Over My Dead
Body
no oh dang it I only had the one
water all right hold on it's okay we can
redo that part later get more water over
my ashes that's right that's how a
phoenix says that thanks for the
memberships
[Music]
and
cows what am I going to do about the
cows maybe I don't need
them is there any villager job that
takes lapies l in exchange for emeralds
cuz we have so many
this ladder needs to
be I forget
where I think right
here okay I did it I did what the game
wanted me to do cleric
really that'll be
cool
yeah yeah
we're making progress we're making
progress everyone clar is the reverse to
give emeralds four L yeah that's what I
mean thank you for gifts that was
nice and the way you're saying it means
that I give them lapies they give me
emeralds that that would be good cuz we
don't need the lopies for
anything okay got it that's how you push
the Golems
okay ah got it
okay the water has to be at the same
height as the farm blocks I needed to
enchant oh okay okay oh well done so
does it need to be up here you mean so
I'll need two more things of water is
that why pickle always was
asking me me is that
why is that what you needed it
for give me give me
he give me give oh she was
enchanting well she do an enchanting
woman flirt 100 doing the
tutorial [\h__\h] I
can't I have like this problem when I'm
like it's like a performance uh
nervousness failure
that's okay I think that's normal also I
know you guys say same level as the farm
the water needs to be same level is the
Farmland but in the tutorial they only
do it once I
think they only do one splash of
water I don't think the water goes all
the way up to joh go away doesn't seem
right
they do one in every corner including
this
corner in this
corner buckets no more the tutorial just
had them
go and PR are we out of
buckets Kelly do you have an empty
bucket or you probably need all your
buckets
or huh do you need all the buckets you
have do you have one that you don't need
no no no I'm I'm good I just did it I
just finished the main part now we have
to do villagers I
think oh okay I'll make one
anyway you can't plant if the water is
blocking the crops oh so I needed a
plant before cuz he didn't put any seeds
in there whoever made the tutorial
didn't put seeds just tilled the
Farmland
oh that's weird was I supposed to put
seeds in there hold on a sec I'll look
maybe the villagers do a
themselves not sure yeah cuz there are
no there are definitely no seeds in
there yeah maybe they need some starter
seeds I'm just going to follow the
tutorial
see oh no this isn't a normal farm this
is an iron farm this is an iron an iron
farm oh are you starting to say it like
me yeah iron iron farm
yeah the W way see the Farmland is
supposed to stop the Iron Golems from
spawning on those spots no seeds are
needed okay gotcha
M I see I see okay understood Minecraft
Geniuses who come up with this stuff
genius cool who's
iron iron is uh is actually um the of
Sauron you say
so you say so they're
related so
relative
see
waa sick head
Cannon it surely sounds like sour on the
way I say it
M
bubble two bubble bubbles hydrated okay
now we get all right now we're getting
to villagers so I might need a little
bit of guidance from Kiara on this one
because I don't you mean you need
free let's find out a DUS villagers
sleep on the beds that you set up on the
surface or at the surface Rock
the beds out from under so that they
will fall into the farm and cover up the
hole when you're done okay so that's
what we do okay would you like to see
kind of what I'm planning to do yeah I
already ran over there saw the saw the
building it looks pretty
colorful yeah so I'll show you it is
going to be Troublesome getting
villagers up here but look let me show
you yeah so we get them to sleep in here
and then we take the the beds away I
guess we got to make them some normal
stairs cuz I don't think they can use
ladders if we make them normal stairs
they might go to the beds on their own
especially now that it's night
okay you guys are making
Railway uh suggestions again but I think
I think we can just you know try it the
yeah the easy way
first give it a shot for me that's the
easy
way okay
stairway make stairway I have 12 stairs
all right here we
go now constructing the stairs
stairs just just kidding
stairs get this out of the way for a
moment and I know this is going to make
some
trouble
um maybe it it's because the trap
door as long as you break all the other
beds so they don't try to half find
them
yeah this may seem complicated but hear
me
out please don't do thate although
currently they all have their own bed
right can you birth some more yeah I'll
make I'll make more should be
possible
okay a if you could oh my Lord
okay that works
right but then we got to wait for them
to grow up too for a moment cuz they're
going to need a little moment to become
adults yeah all right I need to just use
regular blocks first I get it I get
it the regular blocks for
partyle
qule
[Music]
qule all right actually what I'll do I'm
the Matchmaker this is now a Netflix
dating show oh my Lord and I am the
moderator that I great appreciate it
though what
the love
making yeah or you mean something in
your
chat I don't know anymore my brain is
I'm brain dead right now here oh Babble
Babble I don't know what's going on good
morning Babu
babo babo one babo has been made need of
oh two babos okay hopefully we're
running on the bed wait wait it's one 1
2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 9 10 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9
10 damn it it's exactly the same amount
that I have in
beds all right I want more don't worry
oh I hate to use this I know I should
use an ax I don't have an ax
okay all right and
then vill should be this one they looked
untaken
get rid of
this sorry deal with this sorry oh boy
oh my God I thought it was hurting him I
thought it was hurting him never mind no
don't hurt
him y you can't I thought I Wasing
that's why I always switch to like a
different uh non weapon before I touch
them cuz I don't want to hurt them don't
worry idea it's all good jump
all good nothing to worry about here
nothing to see here folks I don't need
to play horror games I can jump scare
myself yeah yeah you can ah um I'm going
to wait do you have beds over there or I
do they're ready okay then I'll close up
the myth house cuz otherwise they might
go
to place instead we don't want that good
idea here's the staircase I made Kiara
that'll lead them to the beds wait
uh What
uh y let me see oh nice from here okay
oh oh beautiful
C I did then they just what they stay up
here or we push them in or they sleep
they sleep on these three beds and then
we destroy the beds and they fall down
oh is there holes there
oh okay interesting the color
combination yeah used random blocks that
were available he's
beautiful never seen an iron farm so
colorful ever
before yeah it's cuz we're low on
materials um we got to let them grow up
though so I'm going to kind
of uh peek at the tutorial see what we
do next after that actual kidnapping
actual torture oh calm down it's not
that big of a deal if only they ate
something besides
bread I kind of want to see The Mating
process I'm curious about I mean not the
not that but I want to see how you do it
I don't need to mate them anymore
actually
um really I just need to transport them
now you could possibly help me okay tell
me what to do boss um let's um okay
let's see if now this might not work
okay we have to open
this
up make it a bit
wider okay okay and now the
sacrifice I hope somebody
will come into my boat please come join
my boat you know you want to take a ride
with t escaping come on baby no little
baby go back to well whatever I don't
care that much about about the child
maybe it will to the bed
eventually you you do you want to take a
ride
potential oh okay is this one that I
like no not not particularly this one
can actually go but oh I can't sit in
the boat
anymore he's taking it over can we push
the boat the child went back in on its
own good good child oh good
baby uh how come it's all stuck it's all
stuck no you can lure them with a job
like a barrel yeah uh that is true but
this one that I caught now already has a
job is that a bad thing I
wonder
well this may end up oh now the stupid
child is in there
now okay okay we're going to we're going
to do a quicky we're going to get rid of
the boat and then quickly place it
again a child had a taste of freedom and
got scared come on come
on who wants to go be tortured forever
afraid of a zombie to make
iron put the boats around the entrance
so no one can escape yeah oh okay Doctor
oh no the double again no no and they're
making love in the
boat and what do you think about this
you guys think oh God they became
one oh God this is horrifying just one
just one just
one no where you going well they will go
back for the beds no worries oh okay um
all right if you say so hey where the
[\h__\h] is
going
hey ah
uh uh wait wait uh yeah there's not a
lot of room to move
sadly I just want one of you guys to sit
please one guy oh okay oh wow two dude
said now not two again not quite
optimal stop stop stop stop stop you
like me back back in wait that's that
hey hey hey hey hey hey does he have a
name he does not have a name currently
he sells iron armor this hurts me so
much oh don't worry we don't need him
it's oh perfect perfect okay let's go
okay off we off we
fly got to make a
turn let's go let's
go y get ready for your life of torture
my man well actually great now with our
method although we could on top of those
stairs we could make an iron card but we
might have to wait for night time we'll
leave him here for a moment how many do
you need again three free we can just
get two and then make them have a baby
actually but we'll try um need have a
baby down in the dark well that I've
made the dark trench spicy
time okay I have another
boat and possibly the child will go in
ch children are okay too I think yeah we
got a child we got a child let's go oh
my
God ah the ethics of this don't worry he
grows up fast they grow up fast these
days
Kelly mean yeah but yeah ah
whatever kidnapping but who knows maybe
that's maybe that's his
father possibly they're back together he
knew with his daddy he probably doesn't
know either who his father is they all
look the same true enough they all share
okay they don't have feelings it's fine
it's fine okay one more mm
m- no the P ideally I would want
him would you like to go on a little
trip it's going to be fun I promise no
no not Tri no you're
valuable oh no you stay right
there this is messed up not going to lie
let's go to iron Paradise come on oh oh
oh oh oh he took some job what the hell
what job did he take what the [\h__\h]
cleric okay cleric's kind of cool I
might want to take someone ah [\h__\h] there
was already someone in there didn't
realize oh he hated that ah
uh-oh that's okay does that ruin it
forever no he's more expensive but it
doesn't matter if we end up transporting
him hey hey oh he's he's running away
from me oh where is he going oh do you
want to go to the iron farm
sir I'm oh oh oh car CA uhoh wait keep
an eye on him keep an eye on him okay
got it oh he got in the same boat as the
child oh okay that's fine that's fine
for now um we can force him out of the
boat and get him into the second boat
yeah sounds good or oh no never mind
might not be necessary because the plan
is now stair it's becoming night time so
uh they will go up themselves there okay
no other available beds right exact
exactly I'm hoping that the other
villagers are coming back to their house
as
well come on so I'm going to keep that
open yeah these two can you please go to
sleep or
what go to sleep
please go
go yeah you're thinking about it push
push push
push okay good good get back in there
they have less options to run what are
you doing why don't you want to sleep I
know you sleep always so early come on
okay
okay want to want to get back
home
push push push push hold on what are you
doing delivering a child pushing a good
yeah there we go okay I there's some
more missing but this is okay um I'm
almost back to you
cie actually that
I'm going to need to make a zombie come
here at some point we'll get to that in
a sec yeah the
villagers and they'll go to the beds I'm
watching them go to the
beds destroy them and then they fall
into my
trench
okay and then and then I'll cover the
hole just really messed up but
okay okay I'm coming to do step two all
right thank you for the help with the
Villagers yeah let's go I hope this
works crossed oh he's going he's going
oh sorry no that's bad well he might no
now he's his priority now is probably
fleeing but come on he's calling down
I'll get away it's okay it's okay he's
going he's going child is also going up
see chat this is easier than having to
make rails way yeah yeah let's go we got
him now hope they really fall rid their
bed fingers crossed the child will
fall yeah fall down dummy job good
job push push yeah yeah push him wooho
oh oh okay he almost died from the fall
but he's alive that would have been bad
good job Kelly y thought thank you we
did that was the last time that they saw
daylight super over for them wa we did
it you did it Callie oh boy oh there's a
little bit of daylight here
huh that's so nice of you just a little
bit oh yeah oh you can go down there
what it's what is it like down there I
want to see I need to I see what I need
to
do we can visit
them
yeah and let's see don't you need a
captive zombie to threat the zombie is
the next part Kelly I think you might be
might be the fifth member of Justice
with how you are imprisoning these
people what can I say I have a great
sense of
Duty somebody said the boat is too far
what is the boat for I don't know how to
keep the how to keep the boat over here
though is the thing not sure what how
where what the boat is the Bo what
captures the zombie cuz I think the
zombie goes down these trap doors and
goes here and then they see
him but I just
don't if we move The
Boat Boat need to be at your side not
near a villager yeah guess cuz if it's
that close it would hurt the Villager I
think right exactly so what we can do is
for example we need to be out of here
and then I guess I'll put the boat yes
so I'll show you sorry I I go behind you
jump over your head okay here I think
it's it's like this
yeah yeah but what if the zombie gets
close to them we can remove the boat for
now turn off the light for spawning them
I think that that's what's the zombie
once it's in the boat it will not move
don't worry oh really okay so we just
have to lure him down here then yeah oh
we can do that I think if we just yeah
make a place with no torches right now
like a dangered Zone and then we he runs
after us anyway so yeah yeah I'm
watching in the video they lure how do
you usually get out of here do you just
mine a
block uh yeah you go up and then you get
rid of it but okay let's see and they
trap him okay first steps he'll go down
the steps into the boat
automatically everything is done right
with your farm it should start in a
moment just be careful in case you get
more than a zombie yeah all right all
right ready
um and then oh wow okay the video is
really long but the creation part really
actually isn't long at all okay I think
shall we remove some torches maybe yeah
but uh where do you want to do it up
there I wonder what would be best I
guess that would be so
close no he he can't climb the stairs
but if we spawn him up here I
guess I guess that could
work if we got rid of the Torches I feel
like he might spawn egg and chest we
still have one
what oh
really oh we might stairs there's an egg
O in the chest really wow we still have
one be perfect usage but which chest the
boat needs to be
sideways so I'll make it I don't know if
that's true but I'm just going to do it
anyway wait the one we had before we
used no bottom chest top
right bottom chest top bottom top right
what
what I just opened
it like that I have a turtle
egg that
one me
out fine turtle
egg oh you thought it was okay you ah
they thought it was a zombie egg that's
okay it's fine we'll spawn him now yeah
yeah yeah spawn hims by removing these
yeah if we get something that isn't a
zombie we're going to have to try and
kill it
mhm with all of our might Chad will it
spawn in our presence
or should get rid of a zomie first
okay let's so that it doesn't fall down
and hurt them no it will not spawn in
our present only 16 blocks away okay we
might have to go and look from maybe a
different uh
rooftop maybe over
there beware of
creepers let's watch from here oh good
idea that should be 16 plus watching
party okay
maybe use fences to stop things from
leaving the roof ooh true he might jump
down once he sees us yeah fence
okay I can make a fence really
quick the villagers won't die if they're
stuck down there will they
uh no they won't die okay cool just
making sure they shouldn't unless
something goes
wrong sure not right
guys no
way there's a fence it's fine what
where
fence fence on the bottom there is but
oh there
[Music]
okay I just don't want to make too many
fence
pie oh oh my God
what the
heck what on
Earth are you
good I kind of saw I was climbing up the
ladder like not seeing anything at the
moment I reached the top there was a big
spider right in my
face my oh jeez hey at least things are
spawning to
waitor spider is dead now we wait for a
zombie
yeah oh yeah I was GNA make a fence but
I'd rather it's
probably the spider did jump down so oh
it did right well the sun's Rising
anyway that's fine oh um uhoh the chat
provides various suggestions such as
using a Zombie egg creating a special
zone for spawning monsters and checking
their chests for a Zombie egg yeah that
is
true Minecraft streamer asked the chat
for help figuring out how to lead a
single zombie without trouble yeah good
AI actually
decent fig
analysis maybe better to create a 24
block Bridge into the void so you can
control the spawn better no no
[Music]
no this is the
most horrific how do I say it's hi
hi just really it's
just the different blocks are really
bothering me even though I'm the UN
responsible I did this to myself but
still into the void is kind of scary I'm
going to build that
way
yeah I'm short a couple
fences this looking pretty weird Cali
not going to lie we'll wait till you see
how it works chat
and then you'll be proud of
me how many blocks
16 1 2 3 4
5 can't
count
24 it's pretty though that's a piece of
modern artwork 1 two three four five 6 7
8 9 10 11
12 it should be here
uh
15 16 17 18 19 20 21 22 23 24 maybe one
more for good
measure okay Cy yeah jump on the carpet
and come over here although I guess it
will take some more time until it's
night time again
we can wait oh and then we can come here
yeah sounds
good wait let's go do the other stuff
then while we wait can you sort the
chest I don't want
to you don't want it anymore nah I've
lost my my touch
no that's okay though I'll do it cuz I
don't want it doesn't mean I
won't does not mean I won't
also wait I guess I should put torches
on our Bridge otherwise it's going to
spawn on the bridge oh yeah idea and I
make it a little bit more oh it's
already pretty
dark are these a
problem I don't want to meddle too much
with Callie's
build sure it's
fine don't you
worry okay
the torches on top of the dirt is it
okay if they're temporarily removed call
I think it should be okay
okay we won't want them there when there
are like BS well I guess it doesn't
really matter they're not in there in
the original build of the for the
tutorial anyway okay you can just get
rid of them okay we just wanted dark for
now oh no no huh oh ah okay I see we can
put that back
oh God you're scaring me so
much there's a pth out there okay I I
need to put some more water back into
your uh
thing okay that's fine no
problem are you good um as long as the
Farmland is
tilled does all have to be tilt all of
it yeah it it prevents them from
spawning uh because I don't want Golems
to
spawn on those areas oh that's the job
he took
off ah he went to the potion
thingy okay he brought some water it was
uh right here so that's
it it doesn't look tilt though does it
only these these blocks on the side look
til yep yep that's there it's only those
that are supposed to be tiled oh okay
then all is good in this tutorial but
I'll double check and make sure it's not
like a double that I missed but I don't
think
so ke you being able to build this kind
of inspires me to also build something
like this
sometime ah why I just follow I'm just
following the tutorial but I wanted to
try and do something where's the lava
this is a non- lava build it's slower
though I think with the iron but that's
okay I don't
care I just want wanted it to work we
don't need like endless amounts of it
God the Villager why is he in the boat
should meant to build underground to
make it work you will have to spawn
proof the spawn proof the area of 713 17
with villager at the center in short it
will be very hard to make it work
reliably understand 7 by 13 by 177 will
have to be spawn proof you
mean you mean light it up or
the it will work it will work we'll make
it
work 17 14 17 the one in the boat used
to be a baby the small hit box let him
get out of the bed area oh my God
otherwise the Golems will spawn out of
the farm ah you have slabs ah hold on
hold on I think I see what you mean but
I the area 7 by 13 X 17 I don't really
understand
that what what what like seven
eh what what does that
mean so we should turn the spawn proof
already true like in that direction it
should be okay where there's only
sky this direction towards our island is
the problem maybe I'll fix it at night
time freaking babies man I swear to God
follow tutorial first and then fix yeah
we'll just make it work once and then
we'll see if the Golem spawning
elsewhere is is a problem for real so
Kelly you understood what they're saying
y i get it that they might just spawn
nearby instead of inside of here here
which is not what we want
yeah make sure they can't spawn on the
yeah I get
it you need to make everywhere around
not a place things are able to spawn
okay but like how far out when you say
17 14
uh yeah that seems yes 177 blocks in in
that direction or something like that
should they be slabs right I feel like
the reason that they did that that way
in the satorial is because of the
location of the villagers being exactly
where it is then this is exactly where
they would spawn but I don't
know yeah it's fine figure it out Center
cover the area with
leaf and remove the beds
nearby oh yeah that beds are gone the
ones maybe they mean the maybe they mean
the myth beds
too oh these guys can't get out they're
trapped anyway so good luck to them if
they want to get out cuz they
can't and cover the stairs with torches
they can only spawn in that
area um
they won't spawn in okay I'm going to
make some carpet
then yeah they don't spawn on carpet
right yeah and slabs but have to be
placed correctly well maybe carpet might
be
easier okay sheepy come
here hello
sheepy nice we already have t of white
wool wait
youing they're like all over the place
Shrek Shrek come on go to your bed wait
let me try to lead him back in now that
we what the Shrek
doing isue
anymore we figuring it out
guys got this oh sorry sorry why are
they trying to leave why are they trying
to
leave come back in it's isn't it night
time the villagers cuz they figured out
what we're doing it's not oh my God come
back in
we're done with our
treasury it's not night time but soon
soon soon soon
yes I'm going to put some carpet
down they want to the they want to use
the Bell they should I use the
Bell oh it's genius that I have the Bell
it's actually that was a good
purchase when you ring the bell they go
inside their house a oh oh come on come
on come on what are you
doing [\h__\h] idiots coordination is
going oh [\h__\h] idiots that's kind of
mean don't you think no he so stupid
come on let's go let's go let should I
have bring it again
huh come on time to go
oh why are you so
stupid did you put a hopper in chest no
this isn't one where any Hoppers are
necessary you have to manually go pick
it up but it's okay because um fixed I I
saw what how it works and it's not it's
not like perfect but it works just just
trust me you'll understand it will work
yeah it's like I said it's it's it's
like a very easy one where it's not
about maximum saving up iron out like
whenever you go grab m iron there will
be Iron there it's just I think there's
a limit it it'll be like a stack like
one stack and you need to go once every
26 minutes or it'll despawn but that's
fine I don't care about it will
despawn yeah just because there's
nothing to collect it the iron that
falls down is the thing you have to go
collect it yourself but every time that
new iron appears it like Stacks up again
and it resets the timer okay it's night
time now do you want to come over to the
platform yes okay one sec we can upgrade
it later I think there's an upgrade
option for upgrade later so it's fine
okay I'm coming but first we got to make
sure we got to make sure that uh the one
villager gets back in his bed cuz the
baby grew up Kiara the baby grew up and
he he slipped through um he got in the
boat he got in the boat oh okay no
problem we can fix that I going to
attempt to fix that a that's funny
you're not leaving
[Laughter]
I might have to open this up is that
okay for you that's fine yeah try that
just replace it afterward ah okay H
there we go okay seems to be here yeah
uhhuh close sorry okay okay and the boat
back right oh I got it I'll place the
boat you can place it it just needs to
be sideways is what they say yeah and
then jump over it
wait you know what you're doing
sideways
Kiara not fair not no what not fair not
fair not fair not fair I glitched
through it and I lost my diamond
Pi
what wait oh God what if the same fate
befalls
me Callie not you
too this is what we get for playing God
I never I should have put the floor
below because that happens a lot somehow
in this mod there's like a problem where
we glitch through often I also died a
few times by that that's all right The
Sword and the
pickaxe I'm sure I wasn't holding
anything too valuable and my paper I was
holding so much paper that I needed and
my lever no [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
more it will be worth it for the iron
it's can I go into creative mode and get
my things back that's not fair [\h__\h]
glitches oh are you allowed to do that
in Creative mod I don't even know how to
go into creative mode how does it work
yes can I at least like the I I don't
know I want my paper bag I think that's
fair oh what do you mean
no who who gives you the right to say
no you don't have the right therefore
you don't have the right I I also think
that that the iron farm will help us now
get more emeralds and then no wait o no
o oh careful Kelly did you fall again
stop I accidentally entered the boat I
didn't want to ENT the boat that boat is
[\h__\h] up what if the zombie glitches
for two we have to make a floor below
all right well it's not an iron farm yet
but you know what it is it's um a death
farm for us soku yep it's it's an
automatic soku
[Music]
I'll make a floor
below because that helped at least for
not
dying oh man here's what I'm going to do
the B of death break this first oh my
God I can't
okay make it make it taller um wait
where's my stone
color yeah that'll work
is my stone cutter in here where's my
stone
cutter with the cows
oh
why all right why see if a zombie spawns
c
c c where did it c ah there ah ah right
because of him
H yeah man that's really [\h__\h] sad we
lost some cool stuff I'm so sad spider
skeleton I don't have any weapons
actually to beat those guys oh yeah me
neither now because I lost
that
okay there something
else and I think one Infinity bow also
[\h__\h] were you holding the Bodacious
bow I don't know if it was the Bodacious
bow but it was one of the two Infinity
Bows Oh my have been the Bodacious bow
dang it that really [\h__\h] sucked I'm
trying to go get some weapon though so
we
can kill them yeah yeah kill them or at
least like protect ourselves from the
others that are you
know in the way that's okay that's all
right it's fine it's fine get a sword or
something that really sucked I'm so mad
it does really
suck well these things I guess we have
to make sacrif spices with them but it
doesn't mean it's
fun that's a that's a setback that
really pisses me off yeah it's not the
funny kind of
setback it's all right we'll make more
bows
andity I'm sure do you want a sword I
can make you
one sure I can go for SW here iron sword
take it take it behind you oh thank you
all right cool kill him with
this um pickax I don't know we need one
maybe
X make sure no creepers creepers are the
number one thing we need to be worried
about
yeah so
true uh
okay o ooh they're already there huh ah
he's a waiting you oh good job
SK nice we got him oh he can climb the
ladder
yeah our battle will be legendary okay
um where are you
there on a bridge just praying for oh
there's a zombie
down he can shoot so far what the [\h__\h]
the heck he's following you try to try
to kill him he's trying to shoot me
right ah o o can
youie sorry the animals are
free come here come on zomb yeah B oh
it's a blood bath here why no zombies
why oh no
um my stuff here oh now there's creepers
we kind of need a bow to get rid of
those
now yeah I have a zombie
though if the skeleton can climb a
ladder can a zombie climb a ladder too
oh you can lead him over the
stairs I think so let me try that but
then if you wouldn't mind helping me
with the creep CU yeah if you go up
there and everything explodes that's
[\h__\h] um no oh no stop stop that stop
that
no come here don't kill my
animals oh God okay chaos chaos chaos
chaos chaos that's I wish we could put
him in a boat and drive him but I feel
he's going to hurt
us here all right he's following me it's
working are there creepers up there
though yeah wait try try to go in a
circle with him for a
moment all right you got it
um uh bow bow bow no bow here okay wait
wait go go keep on going in circles I'm
going to go get a bow right
you got it please don't see me creeper
please oh he sees oh the creeper sees me
okay it's fine he's stuck in there the
creeper can't do anything he's stuck cuz
he's a dummy uh arrows arrows arrows
arrows arrows arrows arrows arrows
arrows I have 12 oh it's okay I I'll
probably I have some okay I got them and
now uh I got to go up from a different
way because otherwise coming up how did
you get up there a stairs that I I built
okay okay I'm I'm here I'm
here all right the creeper right
there easy beat him he fell into that's
well I can get him from here right yeah
surely oh he's still alive okay right I
got to go grab
break
okay yeah break the fence
okay
creeper
die and die you dead uh now they're both
dead okay let's go all right come here
zombie he loves you he's following you
so much he wants to have us an autograph
no go down I got to
close Okay you think he will go down to
the boat so far he doesn't look
interested it's all right you got to go
this way we got to line up the platform
now that we have him
though
yeah okay come this way cuz he still
wants you oh okay I think
oh no
he's no
stoping stop it no oh
okay oh he lives oh oops oh that
works clutch nice absolute
clutch wait why supposed to go though
let me watch the tutorial again I feel
like you should go ni safe yeah yeah
don't know maybe
it's hard for him to move trap doors he
falls in the trap door
okay he falls in the trap door can we
push him somehow a he's going now he's
going now oh oh nice wait now he's yeah
he's going towards our Direction
now I sense him is he in the boat think
he got in the boat let's
check if I think he
did he's St Landing next to the boat
interesting how he didn't get into oh
no okay that was dangerous cuz he was
hurting
oh H the boat moved like into
the into the uh Stone and then he sat in
it and destroyed himself it's okay we
can get another one I just I think the
same thing will happen again though um
we'll make it work we'll make it work
okay I'm just uh I don't want to die by
this boat again but this should work
agree yeah no Dying by boat for any of
sideways yeah I feel like the sideways
is important so that he doesn't hurt the
villagers maybe okay I think that's what
chat was getting at but not totally
sure don't place the boat sideways then
no need to be sideways okay I guess it
was one guy never mind okay it was one
guy well one of all this placement Boats
were so glitchy in this version for real
man you can't attack in the boat okay
um
okay
[\h__\h] no
no okay I have to uh get rid of this
stone for a
moment
probably it's okay do whatever you got
to do H I
trust why does it move around so much
why is it got to do that it's pretty
Annoying It's
buggy that's not a sheep that's a polar
bearn oh that cat Zoom cats have the
Zoomies look at them
fly um I think the trap doors need to be
open not closed the villagers need line
of side well all of
them um
but then what if the villagers run into
when they wake up what if they run into
the
zombie uh
I
yeah he he it seems like once he sits in
a boat he can't attack them so but they
do say close the trap door oh like this
if they walk into him though that could
be okay I I'm too uh dramatic it's fine
no wait ah oh H close uh is it open up
there close uh okay it's fine that's
fine fun it's they can't go up there
come back come back get too bad come
back to bed come back to bed you
[\h__\h] come back to bed oh no okay we
just need a we just needed to be nice
one guy what the trap doors is one guy
the Trap F it's always hard to tell yeah
it is how did it look in the tutorial
did they have it down we should check
again but I believe it was the way that
I left it let me see hold on a sec I'll
check I feel like it was several gu not
one guy yeah there were quite a few okay
so when this person leaves so making the
steps
up
okay and there's that
boat in there trapo is closed on the
tutorial that boat placement is very
specific there too overall the
territorial has the instructions
there the boat does look like it's
sideways but I don't know how they
placed it let me see how they placed it
there's a chance that the trapo is a
little bit too high like one half of a
block or
so
maybe maybe
maybe I was very careful
it's okay I can make some out of these
fall it was open I didn't realize it was
open here what the [\h__\h] wait is this oh
trap do please look at the Trap
do they'll go back inside open they'll
go back
inside the f is on your platform
okay uh that's a different one please
turn around tutorial
man it looks like it's up he left it up
he's gone he left it
open use the B he leave hey one of like
they both left because the the exit was
open the trap door was open oh my gosh
those freaking jerks not uh yeah yeah
the trap door yeah but it's okay uh we
can we still have two so we can birth
one more out of them
okay you know it just takes just two of
us open you and
I I'm going to go get some bread for
them in
advance okay yeah it looks like the trap
door is open
okay well I'm going to trust it
then m m Mama Mia why are these things
not like easier why can't do perfect
oh what are you doing oh what's he do oh
he's stuck there is it a
villager there's currently they're like
in the water or around the water just
don't worry they will go to their
bed okay I'm just going to prep some
bread and then we'll need they get on
another zombie although that place is
not lit up right now so once it gets
night time it's kind of dangerous for
them so we'll have to be fast for them
to get to bed okay and protect them in
case something
spawns no problem this is riveting this
is exciting rting ribbiting ribbit
ribbit ribit ribbit like frog yuua
ribbit okay he's planning his Escape oh
too bad for him it's not going to work
out there's no sha shank come on if I
ring the bell from over there you think
they'll react on the other side chant I
wonder the other side of the world
Splash okay I'm going to ring it see if
they're going to move to Towards the bed
okay probably not right nah they're not
moving they seem like they can't get out
though so I probably need to provide
them with a block or
something uh
oh yeah need oh they're really trying to
get out let me see okay I got some bread
for them that's one thing I'm trying to
put a block down for you how did
you I can't get a block what are you do
this definitely work but you're my clay
guy
ladders shouldn't he be
here how did he get there this game is
so
glit have to stop the water all right uh
I'm going to need a water
bucket get yourself to safety please my
man please the water's preventing them
moving oh this is really hard to break
okay just use my gate oh yeah he was
escaping the zombie but like how did he
get over the fences and stuff come on
move
move where's
bucket I don't know where the bucket
is okay there was a bucket I was holding
a bucket now it's gone bucket I to use
IR we died use iron to make iron
everything's gone IR everything's gone
everything that's
okay still going to make this
work need to collect paper
again carpet on the fence top you can
jump on it yeah but then can others Jump
On It villagers Jump On It
that's chaos but you can recover mhm but
you know what I'll never be able to
recover those pickaxes and
swords I can try to make something
better though come on yes okay yes oh no
what come on up
here I think they're figuring out how to
jump
they can escape
surely use a smithing table to lure them
seems that work they they just want any
kind of job so
yeah carpet stopping them oh my gosh oh
all
right I'll give you a nice path back to
Home by home I mean your
whole they're learning they want their
free
[Music]
too freaking
bad I'm going to light this place up
because it's getting dark yeah um
although one torch though yeah we'll
light it up so that uh the Villager can
get back to bed and then we'll unlight
it again so that we can spawn enemies
AKA
zombies sounds like a plan oh they're
already back in oh no they're there oh
okay okay okay
M they didn't want to go up the the
blocks you placed they were they did for
a second and then they
stopped AR their beds close right below
yeah their beds are down there they're
trying to go there and they can't get in
there oh oh
maybe
maybe the
pathing I think we're stuck no we
could the get rid of them once or M
or okay idea yeah break the wall I I
guess I could no wait wait don't do that
yet how about we we make the block
closer to them wait I guess they can't
really go up
there oh and we need to move the carpet
make it easier for
them how about now come on
you're like nah dude the beds are right
there you
think I could buy another uh uh Bell
although no I guess they're already
wanting to go aren't
they they under their feet knock through
the wall just break the wall okay if
it's really right below yeah do you
think it's okay to for for your build
like you know what you build like maybe
yeah they can we just we got to
try is that where it
is maybe I have no
[Music]
clue
wait oh
oh oh is it is is there a hole
now uh maybe we'll find out I don't see
a hole from the from below yet hold on
hold on oh wait you're there oh oh
hi yeah they can come in here dummies
they can probably go through there we
got to push them into the
hole pushing we can do oh yeah push
where are they now are they done with
you didn't they follow me oh there's one
of them came in oh where's the other one
one of them went to the bed where the
hell is the other
one uhoh no they're both in the bed
they're both yeah I see their heads but
there's one empty bed yeah cuz yeah
that's because one of them just
disappeared but now that's why I made
some bread we can just feed them again
oh wait I want to go for your hole uh oh
I know that sounds weird but I just mean
I want to go through there yeah OD weird
thing so I can throw the bread at them
yeah and then we got to close up the
hole we got to close it you're you're
not in the mood huh okay let's sleep
first but are you sure you're not in a
mood you feed him tomorrow
yeah got to close up this hole it's a
good B bread throwing hole though not
going to lie it is kind of nice but
they'll be able to escape through it hey
I don't think so they can't jump up
these slabs no no no really wa we can
make one block uh we can close one block
but don't let's not close it all up so
we're going to need but we're going to
need to fill it with water eventually
after we have the third villager again I
think is then we can fill it up again
we got to go step by step with fixing
this chaos and we might want to do we
have some
torches no I lost all of no just stay
there apparently it won't spawn as long
as you're
there uh let me go grab some okay that
was really dangerous of me H I'm going
to quickly go below and make
a uh bottom floor so that the disaster
from previously never happens ever again
good
[Music]
idea your version the farm only works if
they have their workstation available
putting it in in the wall behind them
should work their
workstation none of these guys are
assigned to any work
though an escape attempt gone wrong they
never had a prayer
I know I don't think these guys have
assign
workstations okay
a oh how did you how did you get down
here okay building floor below need to
be able to
sleep yeah I see a lot
ofion but that's okay confusing
M did he use boat hacks too
maybe a [\h__\h] boat man sorry I'm like
so mad at that boat and the
glitch you have the right to be angry
I'm also very
upset dang it oh well Golem won't spawn
there oh should I like you should build
with bottom up yeah okay
okay uh dude don't go
there we're so
close we are really close to getting it
done
yeah let too too bad the zombie
destroyed himself though I hope that
doesn't happen
again I was saved him clutch from one
situation but I couldn't save him from
all of the
situations that's
okay
boat hello villager there's another
villager that wants to come up here
oh don't you just come up
then oh you think you can bring him up
there's a bed for you if you
want I don't have any blocks but yeah he
looks he's looking at me like he wants
to come up here does he have a job I
don't know he's just standing if he
looks really plain then he doesn't have
a job if he looks like he's wearing some
fancy clothes then he does have a
job might be my clay guy
come
[Music]
on oh no he I think he's got a bunch of
different items but they're not really
useful items h no no they are useful
because we often we have a lot of clay
and we can uh exchange it for emeralds
one Emerald oh yeah well he's standing
right here for some reason so maybe
should take him away or tell him to go
somewhere else cuz he wants to go he's a
bit confused he used to be with the cows
now he's confused because the zombie the
the enemies were like hunting him
down oh go back down
then go back down as long as oh right
cuz it's two true [\h__\h] one guy again
because it's it's not like enough space
for him to spawn any
[Music]
just in case I'll try to build below any
way whoa what the
[\h__\h] oh wooden
hole
okay and I want
axe
yeah all right we're going to make this
work I'm telling
you oh so much oh
dear which part this
part no he's on the
dirt it's all so
difficult why is so hard
why we can't even really guarantee the
zombie is going to not do the same thing
again but fingers
crossed so all we can do is cross our
fingers and our toes 2.5 LS might be
enough for the Golem but like the half
they he can't spawn on the
half oh my God you
guys this might be tall enough for him
but he can't spawn on the
half
M on the bottom half
nobody actually knows nice deflect yeah
it's
like Bo flip Bo flip Bo
flip you you say something you try to
one guy me and I go Bo flip Bo flip Bo
flip that's I think it was a was it a
scrubs
thing you know the the guy what's his
name Ted actually like in Scrubs uh the
guy uh who's like sweaty the sweaty
lawyer of the hospital uh is really
nervous all the time and he has no no
confidence and stuff and people people
make him especially the hospital CEO he
makes him feel so
insecure and then yeah in order to not
be affected by what his boss says to him
he goes like boing flip Bo flip I think
I vaguely remember that yeah did you
watch scrubs
ever was it was not in the background
because Mama Mory was a fan okay it's a
really good show I've rewatched it like
a million
times yeah
nostalgic right I'll put this
back yeah I think as long as it's where
the uh The Villages and the boat is
that'll be helpful but the rest doesn't
necessarily all have to be covered can
you stand where like even if it's not uh
below even if it's just above them can
you stand where the villagers are
roughly
sure is that here okay okay cool down
k no problem appreciate it yeah
hopefully we can get another one in here
just for
us RI the last season yeah the last
season was
bad oh no hate to hear that m it's okay
we had so many good Seasons you got to
appreciate the good things you can't
always hate on the bad things just
appreciate the good things you
got Wise Wise
Phoenix
words wise
words okay I think that should be good
hey oh wait
you wait where did you come
from how many villagers are down there
right now
no
do or did he lose his job I guess ah is
it the potion guy but he lost his job
okay he's probably going to die down
there although he would be the perfect
candidate to put up there if I make him
some
stairs it's so complicated I'm just
going to burth another
one yeah birth
another this should be fine they can
actually go in there okay I'm coming
back up and I'll help you birth the
third villager are they awake right now
surely they are yeah they're
awake More's
not push him off push him off
no o he's a he's an emergency villager
if we're like really really emergency if
we really need one we could have one
from
there okay we
oh wait I'm going to the bread throwing
Place bread hole oh
my oh
hi I left the bread behind
water
[Music]
BRB yeah so we can close the bread
hole I want to put the water
back yeah
also no they don't need workstations
beds should be enough is what that is
said a lot so we're going to see if that
works if it doesn't work then we'll try
that I think the workstations would just
be helpful to get them to where we want
them to go cuz they usually when they
have no job they just like move towards
the workstation to get a new job we them
we trapped them look there are prisoners
[Music]
going to bre him okay yeah I I only have
16 so this better be enough for you guys
o no no no no don't be so
greedy don't be so greedy why you why
you want what do you want from
me make love to each other take
bread okay okay what's wrong with them
not want do it anymore what's wrong
with small one can escape from where oh
it's okay from this trapo but it's okay
cuz we just we just let him back inside
I
think we we can destroy this platform
and then it'll be fine it's cuz I'm
watching let him back in at night well
I'm out of bread see it's working heart
I saw the hearts okay do it do it do it
do
it doing it
how am I going to escape oh oh
no oh baby child okay baby okay okay uh
can't let him Escape can't let him free
so we'll wait till it's night time and
hopefully he'll be grown up and
okay yeah thank you they were woohoo
woohoo H okay fix the Villager the the
disaster
debacle yeah should I take the
ladder and brow up you
could I can take the ladder
[Music]
and
bu
nice okay we can close it up now doo doo
okay missing some dirt do you have dirt
by chance um curently
no okay I need another dirt
[Music]
block see can the baby still go under
the slabs he wasn't but that's okay
he'll go back it's okay we'll figure
it's it's easy to fix it's an easy
fix and then when it becomes night time
we try to spawn the zombie
again
okay yeah we'll try again we got this
all right I'm going to replace the water
now you're going to take it from the
edges there yes that was where I placed
temporarily oh my
Lord
oh
okay
now that
water now just one more
side on come
on there we go don't fight it you got to
be one with the
water maybe you could use the platform
to spawn the zombies oh no here here's
fine it's Fine's
fine D taboon yeah
maybe
[Music]
probably
okay seems good and then we need to try
the boat again we need to make a boat
but make I have a boat in my inventory
oh
okay oh man the whole Bing thing scares
me okay but now there's a there's a flow
below it's just um so when we fall it's
okay but if we do get a zombie to glitch
through there then it's going to be
difficult to get him up again but yeah
he will just sit down he'll sit his ass
down and he will stay seated yeah what
if we rode the boat sideways and then we
glitched through the floor on purpose to
leave the boat sideways we can do that
now yeah yeah okay let's try that I can
I can try it if you want I need to eat
though I need to eat now oh God I'm
about to die I'm about to die oh don't
worry you don't don't die in Minecraft
from like no food you just stop moving
fast wait you F
this you were living in in danger and
fear this whole
time kind of look have a heart it's okay
I'm good now oh half a heart or half a
hunger half a heart oh well that will
yeah that's dangerous it wasn't
regenerating because I hadn't been
eating yeah yeah okay okay okay
I you die from Hunger difficulty was on
heart oh you can do that like make it
even more hardcore like that
interesting yeah how are the
cows make boat
okay I'm going to try glitching through
the floor oh look who's back wait you're
yeah you're the right one oh thank God
he's
there SM SM
[Music]
cow basically it's a cat
basically I probably should wait for
the the baby oh oh they're all sleeping
nice they're sleeping we need to wait
for the child to grow up I think maybe
yeah
Yep they're sleeping suya soya oh that
means it's uh possibly zombie spawning
time let me go get a bow for creeper uh
killing should we put him in here before
the baby grows up though cuz the baby
can get right now true but so oh wait as
long as there's wool up there I guess
nothing spawns at the moment
anyway yeah
smart okay yeah bab we grow up I wish I
could hit you with some bone meal and
you could grow
up how long do they take to grow up I
wonder I think tomorrow like in
Minecraft tomorrow he will be
grown
nice okay then
umut them thinking time books I need
leather I need
Lea do we really have no no more leather
anywhere
else boat placement is it 15 minutes 44
seconds of the video 15
minutes wait I can buy ah forget about
it forget about it
okay Smite free actually hey I like that
on a sword right Smite smart not the
worst but you're not the one I was
looking
for but I am worried about things
spawning on top of these so I'm just
going to chill here for a little bit and
hopefully baby will be grown
up oh we'll figure it out
same it's for UND it's for zombie and
skeleton only okay yeah I want him to
change his job again then but oh wait
you see what's happening right now there
two of them using
one uh table again for their jobs this
shouldn't be
happening should we sleep for the night
because we don't want anything to spawn
right now
anyway yeah that sounds fine to me
all righty I'm on my way we will
financially recover from this yeah o o
Callie NY did you fall of Me no where
did you fall
where it's my own fault I deserve that
did you car something anything okay I
made a boat that I like though was
that boats are very
replacable there's really kind of
nothing I'm glad that I put other stuff
away though thank goodness for that
can't do that anymore anymore anymore
you can't do that anymore anymore that's
cute I put the important stuff in here
because I was planning on glitching out
anyway it's
fine you will be you will be caught
safely by the under floor I think
yeah sleep F we're sleep I don't know
why I came all the way back up here cuz
the easy way was always available right
here what a silly dummy dumb idiot all
right sleepy time what's the fall
counter for today yeah we fell a few
times our own
home did you board up the doors oh yeah
cuz I didn't want the villagers to go to
that house but you can unboard it now
yeah should be okay there is an arrow in
my hand how' that happen good
[Music]
morning so somewhere
H
well I guess I might just buy it he's
growing up
now find
[Applause]
out
hello no he's still
baby can they please fix this
bug no they won't it's too old too
old who plays
1.5 one block who plays it us STS
please devs yeah look that'll
work think we should make it more exact
though only five versions behind was
probably fixed a new version I really
don't know why we have this old version
but okay
okay oh hello baby no baby go back no no
no baby yeah go back to your
parents go back to them stay in there
with
them what else could I
trade grow
up I kind of just
really but what if wait what will happen
if I lock him in can both of them be
locked
in oh wait while I'm at it give me
another Ming book stop dreaming of going
to the outside world stop it won't
happen oh now he lost his job okay and
then that belongs to him so actually I
need a second
one I actually want to put this here
yeah you're not getting
out yeah same same guys same stay in
there so you grow up I'm like genuinely
Hing along with them
what is outside what is grass touch some
cousa touch some grass and you will
know touch some
cousa think waa think come on baby
child it's time to make get new
pickaxe where boat not
yet not yet I'm going to make it slip
and slide destroy the ladder but why
they can't climb the
ladder corn only chicken here you eat
corn cornfed chicken oo yummy
specifically cornfed chicken I'm a
cornfed
phoenix corn is yum I also like it in
ramen even though it's not like a
traditional thing I it seems to be a
Hokkaido Ramen thing right the Miso
Ramen yeah I think so mhm and I wish
they would combine my like tonu and Mis
Ramen because they have the favorite
things I want in a Ramen just combine
them and then that's the perfect Ramen
for me yeah I really like the butter and
corn yeah in the hul it makes me
remember the the ramen that we ate
together in hok do c it was so yum oh
yeah speaking of that I wanted to ask
you do you have like any plans for
vacations in the next months
oh let me think well I kind of I kind of
did but you know I'm I'm healing slower
than I thought that
I so I don't think a vacation is a good
idea there's some there's some business
that that I have to do this year that I
kind of promised that I would do um is
just yeah it's kind
of busy even though I didn't want it to
be and and yeah I didn't is
okay travel more but I have to I have
to it is what it
is it's fine try not to travel as much
these days I'm tired tired of
traveling I'm done with it I think we'll
end up traveling either way even if it's
not for
vation true enough but yeah I wanted to
go to some places too but the summer is
really so busy don't know if I can might
have to wait until like
Autumn schedule's all packed huh
mhm can't be helped I'll be in Japan for
most of the
summer yeah get some
Mis Mis to Ramen but they have so many
calories yo true which is why we
calories
now same it's okay it's
fine to be honest I have not I've had a
really poor appetite since the surgery
no can not do acrobatics to get out of
please go back now will be able to go
back it's because the beds are so fun to
jump on oh my God and he wants to be an
acrobat when he grows up is he not grown
up
yet no damn it leave him
alone oh I don't know if that's true but
yeah maybe maybe just leave him maybe go
mining or
so he's gone what do you mean he's gone
he's back
o this is a slippery little dude Kiara
slippery little dude yeah he's training
to break out he's gonna free his parents
didn't think that's going to happen
sunny boy mm be working really nicely
over here am curious about it look he's
waiting for me to break free he's like y
I'm going to I'm going to slip through
the
hole no you're not you go
back come on come
on okay oh it's pretty good should be
enough to enchant the
pickaxe nice to see M working so good
yeah and we're going to make the iron
farm work as good
we will we will it takes 20 minutes for
them to grow up
okay we go find something else to
do I'd love to take it
that AB are
nice Marry m marry myth mining myth Mary
mining mining merry my Mary my Merry
myth mining
wasn't quite the previous name but I
like this name
better okay mending pickaxe has been
restored it's not quite the same because
it had efficiency before but we're
getting there maybe this maybe we have
some
efficiency repping Edge for
sword efficiency
W was it efficiency free before perhaps
but this is fine
Mary
Mary okay I had a pickaxes back it never
happened it was never
gone strong pickax is
bad let's mine a bit together for
efficiency together cuz I wouldn't mind
getting
some specific blocks out of this like I
want some bone blocks and
maybe some Emerald
blocks that might be nice yeah oh why
are these animals always walking all
over our stuff well this one just
spawned sorry I want to I just want to
get it out of the way oh wait they
dro the was that a donkey well then if
you dropped me some
Lea sorry cat oh I didn't realize no not
the cat the cat is fine the cat is
fine go please I'm awake I'm awake Kelly
are you okay I'm good I just I want the
child to grow up
now it's like
Cobble it's forever a child even though
it claims to be grown up oh my
god get some sleep no
you're so close I can taste
it one of the meals was tamed by Ena
well I don't think she needs it and it's
not like she's showing up to take care
of it is she oh I mean yeah that is true
so I shall murder it she'll probably not
even remember
it probably not even be looking for it
[Music]
so when it becomes night time hopefully
the baby child will have grown up and
then we'll see if we can make him go to
bed and then we'll begin operation make
the iron
farmw be
sick and then you can go take a
nap and then you can play the Cowboy
game the Cowboy game
yeah
Cowboys is there like is there like
gangster Cowboys because in GTA there's
like you
knowla yeah out Outlaws gangster Cowboys
are outlaws okay I'd say so yeah makes
sense yeah oh yeah it's tons of fun it's
a really awesome story too now we're in
the epilog so if you hate spoilers don't
you're busy red de can wait can wait I
appreciate that guys but but it's okay I
want to
keep you need some coffee or something
I've been drinking Coca-Cola zero today
pass my bed if I drink coffee I won't be
able to sleep after the
stream yeah all right let me see surely
true true
surely it's night time maybe instead of
coffee just like a black tea or green
tea just a little bit of just small
amount of
coffing yeah coffe coffeine coffe coffee
yes he's an adult
now grew up before my eyes he's going to
bed all right placement time yes uh what
you're going to get rid of the
carpet uh yeah let's do it all right I
placed the boat correctly it's you plac
the boat correctly all right let's
[\h__\h] go o luck all
right and now
actually we can leave these open
yeah zombie spawning time and creepers
probably
too it's go time took a while to get
back to this
point did that's
okay you think this is good
enough it uh probably better to get rid
of all the carpet to be honest all of it
yeah we can put it back after
okay all right up it
goes be I'm putting away important
items well this one I want to keep
though for shooting I'll be fine there's
floor underneath I don't know why I
would glitch for the world
now shouldn't happen
there St still in the water you got it
yeah I got him all right let's go it's
go
time go time operation get a zombie with
Takami yeah okay operation takamori get
a zombie just be careful when a skeleton
is shooting at you it's it might you
know shoot you down the edge and send
you into the void again don't want that
we should be really
quick but I got a
so if I see a creeper or anything else
that we don't want I'll shoot him
down okay I'll leave it to you yeah
Operation Zombie take two cut come on
yeah take two cut got to stay away got
to stay
away come on
[Music]
zombieing
okay oh skirlington
now kind of far oh there's a zombie too
okay I'll take down the
gring then we should Place torches as
soon as possible so more okay it's go
don't show up zombie zombie zombie do
you want to lead him again although I
think he's on me but let's see oh yeah
now he's on you ah ah look at Kelly look
at Kelly look at Cy look at Kelly she's
beautiful look at her 2.0 update now he
really likes me right now oh yeah okay
no okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay all right all right all
right all right all right now yeah let's
uh lead him towards the beds and I made
sure that the the boat was properly
placed he might be stuck in the trapo
now that's okay he starts moving
eventually right uh no he should he
can't go back up anyway oh he can't come
on come on cuz it's two blocks high yeah
true
W there really is a method to all this
huh come on now you want to go down
maybe it just gives him a sec it just
takes him a second
push oh no how how am I how am I going
get down get down you
[Music]
bastard get down why are you not hitting
me anyway we friendly now okay we're
chilling get
out we got to put it oh okay we got to
you got to put the block back come here
yep I'm going in a circle where my wood
go my Wood's gone he ate
it we were friendly for a
moment do you have a block you can maybe
place in that there we ah good good good
good do you see his green head is he
staying there or is he he left he went
away
oh H I wonder if he's in The Boat Boat
he is it worked he's stuck in the
boat so wait let me let me see this he's
in the boat they're not attacking each
other oh this should be working Ka geni
op Genie genus
genius as in genius op
yeah sorry sorry I put the carpet
there oh it's
okay now wait huh where where's the
block I just had uh it fell uh oh
actually oh pick it up maybe oh that's
block will thank
you yeah all right let's carpet up the
whole
area
yeah we might be missing one carpet
maybe that's okay go down and get it
let's pray that this
works everybody pray prayers please Jo
hands in prayer oh boy we need your
we need your
help we all got to pray I'm out of
corpet pray pray for
Takami yeah
tamoi you did it though maybe now now
we'll see it will take a while maybe for
a Golem to spawn so it's waiting time to
see if it
works okay a little
bit what you think chat how long would
it take name the tag name tag the we
don't have a name tag right
now yeah they're pretty scared it looks
like maybe they're really frightened
it's only two though isn't it there's
only two villagers what happened to it
there should be the third one in there
are you sure it's only
two are you sure let me see where case
we can birth another one but there only
two where where the [\h__\h] did he go did
he glitch
down let me
check I'm so I'm doing parkour I'm doing
Hardcore Parkour that's the second time
I went down there
Chad that's the second time it it works
guys it works it works here glitch and
go away oh hey there's a dude here m
no there's same dude there's um there's
one dude down here that I think has been
down here for a while now that is
unrelated yeah that's a different
dude it wasn't a baby villager uh he
grew
up he grew
[Music]
up I don't
know come on spawn here
Golem I need to see this with my own
eyes come up but if you destroy the
block uh that's like sitting underneath
the carpet you need to bring a
replacement
block you'll understand when you try to
get back up and you can't you
can't that does look like to oh yeah
beying maybe we should try and lure
another one
just drop him in if he grew near a block
they can suffocate me yeah did you watch
the moment when he grew up yeah he
became a full grown adult and then was
he like taking damage or from something
what was he doing he was just chilling
in his bed H maybe they're just
idiots I mean can Golem spawn with just
two or does it have to be three check
the lad D you think he climbed up or
what
wait wait wait wait
wait we can
[Music]
check he he's not I don't think he's in
there but we can push another one in
there or
try but I I prefer to push an adult one
in there at this point I think so too
just check from the roof yeah uh can we
do you remember where you made the a
wait what it's okay there's in there he
was just probably half in the
wall oh there isn't the third one yeah
what the [\h__\h] he just he just walks
through the wall and goes back and don't
worry about it so funy m mom why how
dare you worry us like
this was silly and even chat is like
what the
[\h__\h] dude found hiding in our walls this
mod is so cool and so
mhm nothing wrong with this
mod it's a known Villager glitch oh okay
he's just like glitching through the
walls and comes back so he it should be
fine it should be fine name the zombie
we don't have a name tag but wait the
the potion people they make they sell
name tags right if I level him up then
maybe I can get a name let's do that cuz
we yeah we definitely don't want the
zombie to
[Music]
despawn yeah but there should be no name
it's in a boat it should be uh it should
be no
need I think it's
fine if there's an existing Golem you
might have to kill
it that doesn't sound right oh there's
currently no Golem I think that sounds
like not
true there can be endless amounts of
Golems set up lava now no this this one
doesn't need lava he dies because he
suffocates with the
water oh yeah yeah yeah yeah C gets C
knows what she's
doing I don't know I don't think we
should kill the Golem nearby that's a
good guy is there one I don't see him
anymore what happened to him he probably
died like at some point from all the
shenanigans well if he does still exist
though do you think that interferes with
it no
I don't think so one spawned below
below oh yeah the place that you buil
underneath all of this don't worry don't
listen to chat it's not it's not going
to spawn there cuz it's bottom slabs
they don't spawn on bottom slabs oh I
see I see
smart think you a
workstation yeah it can't it's it can't
SP no
can't somebody saying Golems don't die
in water but if the tutorial says so it
will die in water it died in this water
for
sure the farm doesn't work in
1 15.2 you're using a 1.16 yeah but we
thought that would be fine we came to
the conclusion that surely that will be
fine because it's just one version
difference they will die to to we'll
kill them one way or another even if I
have to kill them by hand with a bucket
of lava I will fre freaking do
it or if I have to shoot them if they
fall down there you know we can just
shoot them with our own
hands first of all we needed to
spawn another
goem I'm going to find him if he's they
died to Suffocation from the blocks okay
there you go yep it will work
believe see I'm going to go find
him who the Golem the Golem if still I
think there is no more
Golem I wonder what happened to
him I think he
died I saw him walking
around pretty sure that they need
workstations to summon a Golem okay all
right let's say they need a workstation
how would I make that do they have
workstations in the
tutorial no then don't do
it it's
fine well something went wrong somewhere
you need the villagers to have jobs for
this to work
right I know that's a whole bunch of
guys but well I did my best I really did
try to make it work
but they don't they don't yes they
don't I
try oh
[Music]
20 minutes to watch 3 hours to
accomplish barels on the foot of the bed
easy
fix
[Music]
really
be there is an easy fix add three
composters in the wall next to the beds
what's a composter
that's uh the the thing where you get
bone meal out of I think uh wasn't that
let's go take a look see yeah it's also
a job thingy it's for
Farmers oh oh I see
it you need bunch of
slabs it's a workstation for
Farmers oh
I see bunch of slabs okay it's pretty
simple yeah try that then that seems
manageable you can do it Callie you can
do it thank you I'm
trying we get
there we got 48 slabs which means we can
make
composters great
there's some more
Le and another turtle
egg okay now where shall I put them now
because of the zombie situation I want
to try and put this behind them or enter
from behind Maybe
[Music]
okay so the
bed pretty close by I think I remember
oh it's a let's play rather than a
tutorial that's why it's so long not
hold that'll do it he my guys you're
never going to be
free letting you know right now
Freedom will continue to elude
you evil
laugh sure they can't climb up here and
we are so devious and so evil aren't we
that people are so terrified and scared
of
us all right I need to figure out how
many blocks of
here I ladder
Mak get rid of
that no
Freedom
no but I can climb a ladder we know they
can climb ladders
too uh these guys make me nervous the
villagers from what I saw they're not
they don't seem to be able to climb
ladders okay the skeleton however was
able to
H right put these things next to each
other we're going to need to be
quick they definitely can okay maybe
they can
[Music]
what the W current goal what the W
current
goal making
books I have to remind myself
sometimes Chad do you also forget what
the wa current goal or you never even
know to begin
with the books yes books books but in
order to get the books there's many ways
to get to books such as you know trading
it then I would want more emeralds and
then for emeralds I would want I would
want more of the other
things blah blah blah so many things
involved and maybe bread to make more
villagers I don't know why I'm doing
this I know no I'm also making wheat to
feed
the cows as well many purposes and this
as
well
yeah need one to be a blast furnace
because one of the villagers already has
a blast furnace related job
oh yeah he might be locked in I don't
know if he was locked in cuz like if you
never trade with a villager that has a
job um if you don't trade with him and
you get rid of his workstation and give
him something else he will change his
job but if you already traded with him
once he will not want to change his job
anymore you know oh okay what's a blast
furnace called in this game Blast
Furnace but you might not have the
recipe yet and I don't you kind of need
iron for it to iron okay we have
iron spend iron to make
iron need oven
[Music]
of cobbly
stone
yes think the existing one no doesn't
someone need
that um yeah the thing is I don't really
really understand why he still has that
job anyway cuz I I think I only locked
in one of
the guys with that job and it wasn't him
or was it I don't know anymore
M I'm only made one but normally one
workstation per villager they cannot
share workstations but this game has
been kind of glitchy and it's letting
them share jobs
so it's kind of difficult to know yeah
it's it's
bugged so he should lose his job but
sometimes sometimes they lose their job
over time and sometimes they lose their
job just because I
replaced let me actually do that really
quickly before you finish making the
blast
furnace yeah I don't know what the
ree don't worry about it I don't think
we really need it
okay so I replaced it our blast furn
this guy is H my they're not
working he wants his career gone bottom
three smooth Stone oh
[Music]
we need a smooth
Stone maybe if we just offer him a
different job he might take
it that could work but you're going to
have to get to him to talk to him about
it I'll talk to him about I have a
little talk I'll have a little
conversation with him maybe you should
go around the back so you have to deal
with the zombie I don't know oh there's
nothing here don't oh Oh you mean those
it's okay I'm just going to I'm not
actually going to talk but oh there's a
creeper in the water on it's okay it's
okay just as long as we don't get to
wait the zombie is gone how'd that
happen zombie gone uh the zombie gone
but and they turned into uh Farmers not
all there it's hard to see what's
happening here there's a be a
workstation did you like leave something
compost yeah I put compost there there's
a compost that's just unplaced
though yeah I it it got stuck I had to
break it and then it got stuck there
zombies in boats didn't stop despawning
before
[Music]
1.16 okay we need to give my name is it
guys is it the potion guy that I have to
level for a name
tag sorry cie this is so seemingly
endless of a process it's it's okay I
wanted to make it work
somehow I want to go get the composter
now that they're
sleeping fishing
Works
fishing you mean that you mean I can
fish a name tag but not in our pond that
one is too small can try giving him
armor that should stop him possibly yeah
the but I was trying trying to do that
with a different zombie and he just
didn't take any of my
items book guy not potion guy oh okay
okay
okay that's good because I got one
already I know we're working on you
don't despawn in 1.52 if they are
wearing equipment yeah I tried that
before giving one equipment but he just
wouldn't take it he just didn't take it
strange piercing four I'm going to Kill
The Creeper
kill I guess I could buy a few lanterns
to level him
up eggs too eggs too not all zombies can
only some zombies can pick up things and
depends on difficulty some
zombies only some you'll just need to
you need to find the right one what they
don't even look different they just all
like there's a percentage of zombies of
the same type that
okay name tag would be a sure version
sure way to do it so I I'll I'll I'll
try to work on that I think cie if you
want to sleep you're um probably good to
go I can try getting a zombie finish it
tomorrow I can finish it
tomorrow I mean you wanted to I think
you wanted to rest right yeah I will I
will well we'll make we'll make we'll
get it to work now I can definitely try
like getting a zombie to spawn up there
is pretty easy and then luring him in is
pretty easy like that shouldn't be too
much of an
issue but I don't know I'm going to work
on a name tag and leveling my are they
hard to make no depends like we used to
have many just randomly out of the boxes
the treasure chest from
mining so if if just another one shows
up that would be no hor
otherwise you know oh yeah hey to the
yo we'll see if it works the problem
uhoh oh no not the powerful
skeleton oh boy that's bad that's bad
that's bad that's bad that's bad that is
bad it's fine fine oh the curse that
curse is really bad I killed him no oh
no I'm still dying I think yeah you can
drink milk to fix it but it will go away
on its own oh it's cool just keep your
health
up yeah did he drop something super dead
just experience
okay some
XP do you want to help sorting the chest
one more time
okay sort the chest if you don't mind
getting the creeper that is up there
creeper
yeah in the water I already took him
down oh already dang
quick okay thank you for doing that all
right I'll quickly you out this and go
to
sleep it was a tough
day a really really tough day Call's
going to fall asleep someday the tough
days will
end oh maybe not I don't think it will
that's fine though I'm having a good
time
me too sleep I'm not as like brain empty
as I was
yesterday that's good thanks to the
Coca-Cola
maybe oh maybe that'll do the
trick I guess Str Works in there as long
as the it's like decently
organized know like just enough it's
organized
enough oh finally more string
yay oh evanel ah he's back you're
right I was wondering these past days
like H actually
I've been missing
some Fanboy
tweets something's been missing for
sure thirsty fan play tweets oh hello
villager not like we need you now at
this point
welcome thanks villager for nothing
villager
back up
villager he's just going to keep on
swimming keep on swimming keep on
swimming I have the hiccups
why hick
hick oh God it never stops fing we could
use him to replace the one that already
has a drop how are we going to we can
drop them in you can go in from the back
but you should wait till they're all
asleep there is a back entrance
you're there
too um okay I might try to trap
[Music]
him
yeah
well well that's
okay that's okay where did trto go so
scary where it go where it go
where did it
go thanks for the memberships sponge it
up it's
okay feel like there was a trapo here
yay yay
yay but I kind of wanted to get rid of
that so that he can walk
out kind of stuck how about
this oh
hi guys oh
he's he's hitting the
gritty he took he already took a job he
took the farmer job hey
sit why the [\h__\h] won't you sit this is
my last
dump well final dump he might actually
go to the bed on his own again once it
is time awesome if we kill the other one
oh good idea yeah like I said go on the
back and maybe but now we still need
another
zombie maybe it'll work oh he wants to
be farming there's nothing to farm here
sir sir please take a seat take a seat
he doesn't believe
you aren't you already tired from
working
huh nah he's a
workaholic be a good boy and sit
he has seating
resistance it seems oh yeah okay he's
sitting
now yeah I don't know is it really an
issue of the the one guy how what do we
think is the issue why why is his job
having existence a
problem I think that I I'm not sure what
it was about the update but I think that
it's very important that like the job
situation kind of it stopped
Maring after one 1.16 but before that
maybe it did matter so that's the only
reason why we need to have their
workstations next to them that's my
guess okay the though they need to have
access to their own workstation to to
spawn hold though okay okay to spawn
Golems they need to have access
okay oh wait is this what's this hole
M you find the back oh I'm not
sure where are you well there's no
zombie there right now either right so
we can lead him also through although
I'm kind of scared about that now I will
I guess go ahead and
kill this one I'll do it I'll do it I'll
do it
yeah [\h__\h] no oh no
I think it's time for me to go to bed
that's okay that's okay well we we tried
real hard and everything was basically
set up but I'll fix it for you Callie
I'll fix it I'll make it work maybe
maybe oh yeah you are if it's not fixed
by tomorrow no pressure though no
pressure yeah
[Music]
wait I shouldn't I'm actually I
shouldn't we made along the way what
matter
right see you guys tomorrow for cowy
yeah for breeding okay cow be more it
was it was fun having you
around yeah let's play again at least
once before the ending maybe that would
be okay I was thinking probably I won't
show up anymore until the end cuz
there's not
really much to do at this point it's
okay to just
okay that's fine then I'll see you later
I might just show up like off stream to
do something with the iron if we can get
it working sure same here all right well
then I guess I'll see you guys on stream
for the
finale bye
everyone good work Ka be uh uh
construct more more iron yeah yeah yeah
not quite yet though cuz it's not
working but that's okay I'll see you
guys around you too
construct Mor Mor construct construct
make sure that you grab my new album
that's all I'm going to go away now bye
everyone check the link in the
description check the link in the
description oh man I'm going to I'll
play the ads play the ads we love ads
I'll roll them if it's your own ads we
love them a thanks Q I'll see you guys
thank you have a good sleep with the
K sounds good
peace hou we have a
[Music]
problem sleepy sleepy
sleepy sleepy
sleepy I should focus on one
thing what thing do I focus
on um should I F I don't I don't even
feel confident fixing this that like we
have three villagers and then okay but
if it's because of the if it's because
of the freaking work spaces then okay I
get it I get it then books should I
focus on the books first okay let me
feed
more I don't know how exactly I want to
get the books books do I want to make
them on my own I could I have lots of
paper
can we
wait can we
wait need some weat I made it all into
bread okay wild P raid hello dead beats
I will try to continue what cie has
built uh you're welcome to help me with
your brain just don't one guy
me m
[Music]
look at all these shiny books I love how
they're so
shiny I kind of want to ooh o okay okay
cool cool cool
cool could make another one worst
case bone tide
what what the [\h__\h] is Oh
Oh I thought it was an item you telling
me to make leather out of bone tide or
so
M wait I do have a couple of letters
didn't I where did I put them 18 there
we go books books books
books W going to show you how book smart
she is we have 19 books uh we need slabs
right for or was it slabs or
plags for one
bookcase just planks
okay see my brain is working so much
better today but it's still lot to do so
it's still hard
to get my mind focused on one thing that
is
six that's only
six
okay let's see you build it like with
one block space around it right I I
think I know how to do it should we like
make it face this way
perhaps six is like almost half of what
I need 1 2 three if and put I think it's
like like
these does it already feel stronger how
do I know how do I
know
mhm I actually have a a picture behind
my windowed Minecraft that shows me what
it looks like
so l l give
me hey hey wait come come pickle come
pickle come pickle hey hey
hey
hey I always have to like reinsert
myself into her by saying cuz that one
always gets me back into the right kind
of sound you
[Music]
know
hey I can't I can't somehow
wait P
laul 21
[Music]
September oh like a that's different
where does she say
it I'm so I hear I'm so so efficient
[Music]
I'm fine thank you how
about give me give
me oh [\h__\h] it's gone what the hell
actually some of the words I I can do
pretty
well
PE I'm fine thank you
about give me give
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
I still got it yeah there there's some
there's some different is here and there
uh depends like how much I say like if
it's just one word it it it might you
know work out pretty well oh can it not
just stay in there I keep on getting it
back okay let me bring a chest here for
just just this
purpose doing her impression is fun and
it's like pretty much the only
impression I can
do oh wait there's a ly block when did I
get that what the hell
okay more books not lapis that they give
me
uh Hey Hey Ma oh that was good the the
the The Punchy H was good
hey
heyle
hey give me
how is your M impression oh I I never
tried doing one
before I should try more different
Impressions wheat don't go wheat oh oh
oh oh okay okay uh am I ready for this I
guess I am uh okay come come come tell
me that I didn't ask for uh where the
hell did you spawn from oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh oh oh uh follow me don't
hurt the Villager
is this okay I don't have a name tag no
but let's see if he takes an
item how about does he take
bread villagers like bread so maybe he
likes bread too I don't have name tag I
don't have name
tag what would he like to have for him
some gear okay zombie wait wait wait
wait
wait Stay Stay
Stay
uh I'll find him again yeah I don't want
to give him the sword he'll just hit me
harder with
that here the the helmet would protect
him
from all kinds of
dangersous oh
don't really want to eat the bread but
it's all I have in my hand right now
okay where is he is he up there
still damn it oh creeper oh oh oh oh n
oh ah there's too many where did where
did they is it from my
where are they spawning
from could it be ah this this area is
kind of
yit
maybe
ah okay uh zombie what the [\h__\h] why are
you there spawn on on top of dirt blocks
the dirt blocks in the water should we
what if I like put water there
too but it doesn't seem like the ones
that spawn in here they're not able to
get out at least throw items down to
them but what if he doesn't take it
anyway cuz not everybody takes it
right but I want to see where they
spawning from uh here's pretty could be
here too honestly
oh hi second zombie huh how about
this will I just pick it up like
immediately if they're capable of doing
it or do I have to sit him
down yes okay so he doesn't seem to be
the chosen
one maybe I'll Purge him in that case
let me try it with the other zombie over
there stop following me stop following
me try
eggs I guess he'll just hold it right oh
but the good thing is uh he
will the egg chest he will uh not burn
if I give him the helmet so that would
be
nice I kind of looked interested in that
egg for a moment
feels like he ate him just
now no okay I don't think he's the type
of
[Music]
person Hi
chat could he take it like this probably
not he can't leave he probably can't
take it
either Chad don't leave
[Music]
me don't just
leave where's the other zombie there
okay you know what I'm going to kill
that
one mhm to focus on this
one do you want this let's see nope how
low is the percentage of zombies that
can take these things in this version of
Minecraft we'll do better I promise yeah
I hope so it's okay I kind of want to
also try getting name tags I don't mind
trying
that I where's the oh where's the bowl
that I had here maybe trap him first
they have to walk over them I think he
did yo
keep
trying ah no he's in a stupid idiot
sassy
[Music]
Baga why
why okay okay okay oh no no now the
Villager H wait H okay okay look at me
look at me look at
[Music]
me can throw it at him now okay wait
wait wait wait wait wait
wait ah
hi
Doo I don't think he likes
it come
on yeah now he's definitely walking over
it
so it's turning daytime
now no no okay I can get a different
one I'll get you guys
eventually you think it's bugged
dro the golden one confirmed negative
yeah apparently and I trust this
information because this person seemed
to write it straight from a Wiki or so
it's bugged
e they just can't do it fish for name
tag and as far as I know this Pond is
too uh small to get Treasures which I
would say name tag counts as one I'm
just going to I I I'm just going to work
on these people wait so
um uh hi uh oh blast protection no you
got a new job that's nice to
see if I continue working on him or on
the other
one then I can get name tag from them
[Music]
in easy they can't pick up items what
there's so many like butts butts butt
but this butt this
to to every single
thing can you move your model up a bit
for no partic hey this version is too
buggy yeah so let's go with the safest
thing if if the armor [\h__\h] is buggy
let's go with the safest thing which is
a name
tag you won't change your job huh I was
going to get some emeralds and buy some
lanterns from him how early do they get
the name tag is it like the last of
their
levels that would be rough if it's the
last one
made another one oh hi name tag didn't
I'mma get name tags from fishing was it
from fishing really cuz I think it was
from the treasure chest from
mining I think I even saw some of them
personally come out of
that is it from fishing
another
hold maybe it's
[Music]
okay yeah whatever
pretty lanterns for
decoration fix block behind compost CI
forgot to put block back
uh take a
look that looks kind of
nice ooh chicken's getting it more and
more comfy in there
isn't that
nice
hey where the next one wait with the
next one you could try with a dispenser
and a pressure
plate with the next
one what
also wait I wanted to breed
[Music]
them breed them or bring that one
up cuz that one spawned so he didn't
claim a bed or anything yet he just
claimed a workstation and that seems to
be one over there right so which which
block are you saying she didn't
fix throw some bread in I don't
know I guess I
could is he still mad at
me I would want two children though
because his job
sucks what's the block that needs to be
fixed though looks fine to
me 50 memberships oh my God thank you
it's Amelia s that's me Al I gifted the
memberships thank you kiar you're
welcome
kiar percentage of zombies that can pick
up items easy zero Hey normal are we on
easy or on
zero ah easy H
okay wait what what what what is I'm
looking for chat I I looked up and you
also became I you renewed your
membership thank
you a that's so sweet of you to give 50
and then renew
yourself what did cie not finish
uh
uh the zombie in above which means it
want why I don't have to repeat myself
so often we had the zombie in a boat it
seems to have despawned and we found out
that in our version of my Minecraft they
do despawn they only stop despawning at
116 we're
[Music]
at5 I think it's the block up uh What uh
the blocks behind compost she used to
get down
there other side of the composter block
is missing apparently the other side of
it I don't know how
she like behind that I don't know how
she's been doing
that what what she's been doing
there is it like
here should I fill this
up how' she get down there
ho [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
L is there a lther
there what if I could oh scary wait how
am I ever going to oh wait it's okay I
think M mhm mhm mhm
mhm mhm and then I work myself back back
up I'm not going to balance on that
fence that's for crazy
people okay imagine if I ran out of
blocks it's good though it's good
uh
okay hey thanks for telling me about it
fixed
it fixed it this can stay like this for
now so okay sorry let's gather our
thoughts again do I want
to breach make new baby or do I want to
try to get that one up there maybe
breeding is easier oopsie I just don't
want the [\h__\h] baby to
escape I I need to make two babies
because afterwards I need to kill this
dude after they breed the breaded with
the bread after they bread it with the
bread yeah no stop moving no no no no
no I place it after
maybe cuz I'm scared the child will want
to although that would be fine I
guess wall off the uh boat area first
before
breeding why place it after placing
after is fine
right blck off the
area
uh how
about how
about like
I'm
[Music]
hungry I guess just like this
whatever and then I'll just bread them
from somewhere
else just hope that nothing spawns
there to kill
me no idea what the Strat is I don't
know maybe so that the child doesn't run
away I don't
know they spawn on the floating dirt oh
oh yeah then they fall
down okay where do I do it do I do it
maybe here could be
okay won't the water go
through I don't want a flood to
start oh wait this oh
okay but now they're
sleeping God Dam
it I'll be back after a little sleepy
timeit my home is not my home
anymore I recently I just sleep with my
villagers
just might swim out I don't think so I
closed it back back
off quick check on
the um wheat and on
the on the cows for more
lever this is all growing so
slowly not even sure which one's grown
this one's grown
this and
[Music]
this just a little bit to feed the cows
I thought this Farm was pretty damn big
turns out it's not big
enough you really look like you want to
do this work for me but I can't let you
go you're my backup Farmer for whatever
what you trade by the
[Music]
way are you done you're done are you
done
yeah oh these are done seems like they
grow faster when I look at them he's on
vacation it's it's kind of torture like
your vacation you don't have to work but
you're just like forced to sit right in
front of your work it's very
unsatisfying his fingers must be
tingling this is
torture this is just
[Music]
torture uh okay let's feed the
cow really need more cows I shouldn't
have killed so many any of them before
you know really getting a good amount of
them
going okay
baby baby bone baby
bone okay they're all done for now you
get one each or
so now start
growing flashbacks I always wanted a
baby born doll when I was younger I
don't think I ever got
one let's mine a little
bit maybe we'll get something useful who
knows while we're waiting for the cows
and we're waiting for
wait we wait we were waiting for the
night to be over now it is over let me
throw some
bread um
oh don't fall
down bread donation from the heaven
think of me as your God because I am
above you and I'm donating bread through
here
oh
cute cute a
cute
a
a man I hope one day I
can achieve the love find the love the
kind of love that they have but it seems
really rare not in Minecraft in
Minecraft it seems
pretty
constant if only IRL love life was like
Minecraft love
[Laughter]
life okay I should probably wait for
that one to grow up or do you think
they'll make another one is there like a
cool down on baby making probably right
for the same villagers they if they just
birthed one it's probably a cool
down nine mon what do
you 8
minutes what do you mean nine months
cool
down don't lie to me no I mean like in
game but it even in game is like a like
N9 months equals like 9 days or
so but wait they already birthed one
there's no way that is a N9 month once
you preg on a it then it's a 9mon cool
down but they birthed it so the cool
down should be over if we're talking
like
that let's
see I mean there going to pick it up
right oh the baby picked it up is the
baby
hurting no it's just the shadow right oh
there they
cute okay the adult picked it
up I don't think they can even make
another baby that fast I don't think
I've ever seen that before where's the
baby what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] are you
doing
here oh the door door is open I
guess
ah
ah oh you you you you you look at me
look at me no no no no no no no oh
no oh ah maybe I can push him in uh
put him on a leash can
I ye the baby
well he can can he walk up single
blocks eat the
child where's B get a fishing rod that's
not going to work a lead is the best
lead lead you can't lead villagers yeah
don't think you
can right this was 100% my my fault my
oversight
here um although I might keep it open if
I get into to walk through here
somehow bucket the water and move it
with
water
uh fishing rod can pull
what that
sounds weird
uh fishing
rod I don't know
um oh I
think
buckets did Kelly take some buckets and
then lose
them think think wow think H what do we
do what do we do what do we do I don't
want to make any one use a boat good old
boat good old boat
good old boat
indeed we boat him but then what maybe I
use some of these
stairs make him a platform to go through
the hole to the bed what do you think
then I don't need the boat I
think should be good should be good
should be
good no I'll just make him some stairs
he to go up here and then down again
I'll push him
M now you don't you're not planning on
going back there huh let's see actually
oh oh oh okay here here
um oh
what this was going to be another
glitching through the world moment
what will not work just kill it no I
spent so much Bread on this [\h__\h]
[Music]
baby but even if I bring the boat over
there I'll have to release him and he
might just be going back into the
water walk the water first okay yeah if
I just get rid of the
water um but I need to I need to I'm
going to go grab a
bucket make a
bucket
bugget
buget buget bug
it no bugged
iron not much not much
iron this is why the iron farm needs to
start working sooner or
later ra sooner please we we've come so
far we can't like you know give up don't
I need two buckets
[Music]
though cuz there two sources I think one
is here
right well I can always get more water
back
again or I I'll send it down
here where is the other source not
here
okay we bug it
where do I where is not dangerous where
am I not killing
somebody here oh no it's night time y y
y y that that mean that's good because
that means the baby will want to sleep
okay don't hurt the
baby go go go go well what if he jumps
up go to bed go to bed good children go
to bed and then they'll be rewarded by
good bread in the morning okay okay go
go why are you so this is just like IRL
children they just don't want to go to
bed and I can't really push you from
there because of the stupid Block Please
what are you doing what are you doing go
in before monsters spawn come on this is
going to end badly for us although I
don't think they can spawn while I'm
here right we we we we decided that
before okay yeah yeah yeah [\h__\h] you no
no no no no no go go away go
go okay [\h__\h] brat [\h__\h] kids
[Music]
going to block it up for
now I'm going to put the water back
in I wonder if the stairs there our
problem if I keep them for now if it's
okay remove
them well currently I think I can still
[Music]
St come on
chat
hello why is it why is my internet so
shitty these days and please tell me how
do you make it so that torch stays there
I'm pretty sure it was
here I think I placed the water
correctly did I
not wrong corner I placed it both in
this and that one is it too
high oh okay okay okay thank
you I'm learning I'm
learning I'm learning
[Music]
learning uh actually I should get uh no
maybe it's not time for a zombie yet
maybe we wait until we have the one more
villager so I'll sleep again and then
we'll try to birth another
one name tag uh yeah name tag for the
zombie though fish for the name tag
I don't really like fish I don't even
know did I have a did I have a fish
maybe uh fishing
rods
oh uh let
me sort my inventory a little bit
[Music]
fancy sounds going on here speaking
of
[Music]
mhm do you hear it like circus music
we're doing five things at once again
yay
[Music]
we're a bunch of clowns I do feel like a
clown this game is making me feel like a
clown with all its Shenanigans like this
won't work this won't work this won't
work this is glitching this is
bugging Mom if if I'm glad I didn't give
this job to am because she would have
probably lost her mind on it too
CI at least hasn't been through so much
of like Minecraft failures like this yet
in terms of building that she's still
like when things go wrong she just like
thinks that it's it's her fault but no
it's actually the game's fault and
that's even worse
maybe well she's not as as broken yet as
am maybe maybe that's how I think it is
how the cow's doing oh I wanted to feed
the let me let me go back in a moment to
feed the villagers just more cow
making okay I think one was born every
time that you speed drops it seems to
mean that a cow has been born
yeah good good
good get some of the
St good stuff good stuff more beds for
villagers
oh where will I put it can it be just
close by like on top of the
roof cuz there's no space down there but
no wait I can now kill the one that we
don't need and if the other ones grown
up they can breed with each other which
is obviously so wrong but like you know
this is just how this game does things
where the [\h__\h] is this child probably
like somewhere on the
stairs right how did I even get out of
the the blockage I
made's a stupid
[Music]
child a there it
is grow up already well why this one
one's relatively in a safe
position if only these two weren't so
lby duby together it probably jumped
over from the beds and blocks I thought
I thought it made it pretty
[Music]
safe last time I really thought I had a
good aim if I hit the farmer again the
farmer's going to
die but maybe it's the like AOE or so
you think this will be okay like if I
maybe aim a little bit away from
him all
right now the beds won't be the problem
nice
job now we just need the child to grow
up to make a baby with his
[Music]
Dad we love Minecraft we love Minecraft
so much Minecraft then that's [\h__\h] up
logic let's go fishing a bit I
[Music]
guess bro I'm having really a lot of fun
today if only I wasn't so busy I'm
almost considering to play
tomorrow oh can we really okay kfp look
up 1.15 fishing if we can actually get
treasure out of such a low
Pond secret water
message who wrote
this how does this work you guys will
have to teach me
um can you disenchant books at the grind
still can
I Nerf was in 16 oh so you're saying I
can get treasure wait when it's bubbly
wait how does this work
maybe it's if it's like pulling is it
pulling that
now
okay is reeling just one
click this [\h__\h] circus
man okay one right click
oh I got a
fish okay we'll need a few tries to see
if we can actually get treasure I don't
trust it
yet maybe does it need to be wider a
little bit somebody said 3x five or
something like that it it seems to be 3x
five
fish is considered I don't I I I I don't
am wasn't streaming so we can't know for
sure right if she really got name tags
from
fishing I saw name tags in the treasure
chest
[Music]
before you can always ask her I don't
she's
around oh
[Music]
fish wait
I can't I can't pick up the rod right
now
okay one of two may have also come from
random chest but sure not all them
okay reading the patch notes right now
fishing Nerf was indeed okay okay there
really there's so much like stuff that
people are telling me and we're telling
each other but oh oh cool I saw that
line we really need to think about the
version and make sure every information
we're sharing is version
specific yeah oh thanks for all on
someone spamming hearts and
hundreds
ah should I put one of the enchantments
on the fishing rod we have so many
surely one of them will help me with my
fishing Endeavors
right boots is that considered
treasure luck of
[Music]
SE we had like a a book guy who wanted
to sell me luck of sea but we got rid of
him what about looting does looting not
work also is the boots considered
treasure
[Music]
don't think we have it
actually lure
[Music]
helps for I guess luring more of them
in they're junk but if it if if this
wasn't working you'd only get fish okay
boots are treasure okay lur makes it
quicker oh okay let's put l on there
[Music]
L what the [\h__\h] was
lur we have
[Music]
more [\h__\h] I don't think we have there
did we
imagine has it ever rained oh yeah it
rains it rains
often right here
idea I don't know what this will give us
at this point
but I don't want Unbreaking how do I
make it give me something
else what is this break level recent n
what when did I die again to get down to
level five when did that
happen what the
[\h__\h] I guess I think I
remember I fell off the map no no no no
I leveled after that but then I I think
I died again just from simple natural
causes what is a natural cause in this
[Music]
game
hello could get a name tag out of this
could I I feel like there's a chance a
low chance oh is there is there is there
is
[Music]
there no damn it
the chicken let me free the chicken from
this
situation it's a way of freeing
it trust me trust me bro
what's what was the highest level I
needed at the disenchanting level level
anyway
table can
trade bro that scares me that scares
me who was the zombie guy
again Freddy is Max oh okay I'll go a
little bit more more than maybe maybe
maybe claric right near the Bron
[Music]
okay what I built is really kind of
phoenixon
2.0 mini version pocket version of
phoenixon pocket Pock pocket St
[Music]
oh that sounds like an actual
country Phoenix and
[Music]
slums it's not very slummy
here what my chat need
[Music]
refreshment
guys the girls have Twitter now and
there's so much information out there
did it say when the debut dates are cuz
I know but I don't know if you
know I mean it's pretty obvious it's
usually a few days after the after the
Twitter opening yeah okay this weekend
yeah this weekend
which is
uh one of the reasons why I kind of
wanted to keep the weekend
empty I mean somewhat empty didn't want
to do my outfit reveal for example in
this weekend for
sure oh oh the this enchanting table
specifically couldn't go up to 30
huh this makes sense makes
sense The Waiting rooms are set up
already oo a man I'm excited Deb Deb
streams are always excited but they're
going to be a [\h__\h] time for me and
certainly at a shitty time
for some of
them
um so I don't know if I'll watch him
live I
mean I could probably stay up for it
but I feel like if when when does it
start 5:00 a.m. for me yeah I don't want
to I don't want to my sleep schedule
still be shitty at that weekend but if I
actually do that yeah I'll probably be
awake but if I watch it it will make me
so much EX it will make me so excited
that I'll stay up even longer than I
really
wanted where is where's this
[Music]
guy don't tell me he's dead he's been
around for so long he's been chilling
vibing
[Music]
fing guess I'll take L
yeah oh wait oh he gets other stuff too
wait where is luck of the scene
huh yay I've made that's I think the
first time ever in Minecraft for me that
I Enchanted something in no h Maybe not
maybe I did it once before but it really
feels like the first
time
cool yeah L of to see is what I need
yeah but also lur it makes everything a
bit faster apparently in terms of
[Music]
fishing now you need mending mending I
can get actually having a good reason to
buy another mending book
helps me as
well it does feel
faster make this too
deep I wonder what's underneath can I
just I hope it won't like
[Music]
drain let me see one
second are the new girls for our benefit
or for
kadas are you I mean I mean is this a
serious question you're you're just like
joking
right obviously for the general benefit
of the whole live fandom and
[Applause]
Community don't don't don't get pushed
back why don't they they they want me to
drink their milk instead of drinking
this stew don't be so selfish cows all I
want from you
is no more wheat Dam it oh no I do have
wheat all I want from you is a
lever we're getting there we're getting
there the more I get the more it
multiplies the more it multiplies you
know make more get
more multiplier
goes multiplier
goes the more the
more okay what was I doing I wanted to
find where the hell is
the the guy is he like in here or
so could he have drunk in a potion like
the merchants do
[Music]
hey give me oh full
inventory didn't he lose his job did he
no no no no why would he why would he
when he is still oh was he too far away
from
ah ah who could I have an idea H he can
still change his job right this
guy how do I make him change his job I
would have to break the other one huh
can you not just become a potion guy
please just become a potion
guy I want to trade zombie
flesh CL don't drink oh man they're
straight edge like
me W do you want to become potion guy
please become potion
guy what are you going to do if I get
rid of this bat what's what's what's in
your mind H
would you con mind
considering the life of a potion
[Music]
maker no no don't feel like
it think about it think about it time to
breed the villagers
true there's see I'm going back and
forth between so many things did you
trade of him no
hi hi hi
[Music]
spider oh no arrows I think all
right almost 5 hours
well
well wait where's the other guy is he
glitching through the wall or something
like that o o o oh no said wait the
child can't come back the child grew up
but can't come back I suppose what are
you doing
here
um I'll help you
[Music]
just don't do anything
funny take the bread already ahead of
time did I take it
[Music]
back sir good sir good sir at least he
took a job
now m
m i I think I have to break this I have
to okay and now take this
bread take this bread make love be happy
yeah yeah quick quick quick uh uh uh uh
uh uh where's your SL oh I don't have
the slab uh oh okay uh ooh ah ooh ah ooh
ah ooh ooh ah
hi should be
safe should be good don't think they can
go
[Music]
again baby close everything or baby will
escape it's it's close it's close
shouldn't be able to escape I'm going
and monkey
why
why come on if we make this third one
then finally it will be free farmers and
that's what we
wanted that's what I'm working
on it needs to be free
[Music]
Farmers eat that bread get
fat how much more do you want
they love that
[Music]
bagette he's picking it up they both
have plenty of breads make
up plop
[Music]
plop swear to God
unbelievable do it just do it
this [\h__\h]
circus so much to
[Music]
do so much to do
okay
[Music]
uh let me quickly check on you
guys oh that's fast you you're already
ready you're all ready to mate again all
horny horny cows horny horny
[Music]
bastards
fly what the
[Music]
[\h__\h] he's having fun thanks for the
membership
why l mov moo moo
moo moo baby moo I was going to make
more bread
[Music]
actually maybe I'll play Minecraft again
tomorrow depends if I get my [\h__\h] done
if I can get my things
[Music]
done tal please I know I
know I know what you're trying to
[Music]
say no ideally I want to take a day off
yeah
I need to mow my
lawn this time with an actual lawn
mower I was going to buy one these days
but I just couldn't find the time cuz I
also wake up so late
[Music]
okay wait kind of want to use a
composter because with the seeds can't I
make more bone
meal come want to make
one how are we looking on
Naro what are we doing next we're
waiting for the child no we're making
more bread we're making more
bread I'm I'm going to buy an electric
one of course of course because cuz
otherwise I'm going to have to buy gas
and gas is expensive and I don't even
know I don't know it seems just like
more you know I I I like electric
things I like things when they're
electric okay you losty men who will
never get enough of their aphrod
X you're getting a kick out of this
aren't you is are they bucked or what
this is impossible
there's no way that you're going to eat
that much bread and not make
love
oh what what's happening here oh okay
the bread is like they were probably
full on
bread could it be that they bread
inventory is full well now they picked
it up I
think oh finally oh no it's still out
there it's still out there thanks for
the raiding thanks for the raid baby
I dare you to escape you little [\h__\h] I
dare
you okay the bird is bugging
around if this [\h__\h] escapes I'm going
to put a trapo here
now
good although yeah now we would after it
grows up we would want a zombie but now
I'm going to still keep it going to keep
it uh
carpeted so in the meantime while we
wait for it to grow I go some more
fishing ah wait I wanted to see what's
below uh oops that looks like it's
leaking well I can find the link from
below then I see where it
is hi
babies uh wait is it is
it uh oh
I could have just gone from
here it's part of the pool
[Music]
huh it's just part of the
pool no need to do too deep for 1.5 two
deep is patch oh my God okay I was just
going to do it just in case but okay
idiot dolin Dolph John Dolph
[Music]
John I do have things to do but it's
okay I can do them a little later still
it's
[Music]
okay my taxes it's okay I have like
until sometime in July to pay the the
late
[Music]
fee so nice of them to give me such
a long far in the future
deadline you shouldn't have to pay the
late fee at all she did tell me that we
can try to like uh what's the word be
like
AO Wow way of speaking we can be like he
yo but if we don't have a good reason
why I'm late oh fishing a fishing rod if
we don't have a good reason which is
really there is no good reason then they
will just reject it ah dispute yeah we
can dispute it but they'll just reject
it cuz I don't have a good reason why I
was late I was just the reason is I
wasn't reminded I forgot and that
doesn't count that's just not going to
work she said
so would need a better argument than
that said you had to make Minecraft one
block n well I don't know about that
either your honor I was playing
Minecraft yeah I'm just honest it's it's
true it's my fault I forgot
but it would have been nice if my tax
lady would have reminded me if she saw
that I didn't pay like even until the
last day cuz she reminded me like a
month in advance or so to do it and then
I for
Gore of course I'm going to for Gore
once I for Gore I forgo
forever me remembering on my own
something oh that's that's I only I'm
lucky when I remember something that I
already forgot
in terms of work like whole live work
there's so much going on right now with
all the all the concerts planning man
like especially for me cuz I got the
tour as well and I got my uh my own 3D
Live also we got the Ian uh not Ian we
got the Ian concert yeah and we got the
myth uh freedy YouTube anniversary live
and and we got
uh I got some
other a few
appearances lined up
to oh there's just so
[Music]
much no I mean like in other Freddy
lives other people's as a
guest not many and like one or two got
canceled again like not the
one where the whole life got
cancelled and one where my song
participation got canceled I'm not going
to say who
but
uh
yeah like my song participation got
cancelled because not because of
something I was late with but the other
party was late with
[Music]
something which is sad cuz I was really
looking forward to it in both both
occasions so if you see something and
you're like H kada is not there it might
not necessarily be because I was never
going to be there possibly I was going
to be there you'll never know you'll
never know at least you're getting
invited yeah here and there a little bit
I'm always
happy to uh be invited
[Music]
can't believe Ana would do that to you
right Ana she just hates
[Music]
me she just hates me so
much you're reminded to my birthday
o what's the pay
oh thanks for the Super Chat what's the
[Music]
pay oh a
saddle for ignoring her and rust I
ignored her and
rust I
[Music]
did did I I don't remember that
anymore maybe I did
how much do clowns charge hey you little
[\h__\h]
[Music]
oopsie yay perfect match I love that
video that we
[Music]
made I love how aggressive Anya sounds
in
it endless fish and the Pond as you can
[Music]
see they're invisible once you catch
them they stop being
invisible but they're totally there
don't you see the the
bubbles the splashing
here an oxymoron what the hell is that
[Music]
jumbo shrimp
what a
contraction a
contradiction uh
okay
okay 0.8% chance for an in see if I knew
that from start I wouldn't be fishing
like I don't like those odds at
all I don't like
them what the
hell
[Music]
idea trust the process guys trust the
process
[Music]
wait you didn't just become a cleric you
are the one from over there you found
your bed you found your way to the bed
huh oh well all right
then give me name tag wait no he's not
the name tag guy I I know that I just
want some
[Music]
emeralds wait I want to see what you
turning into what the hell let's sleep
through
it yeah he can replenish now too not
that he needed to
but oh I can trade all the [\h__\h] gold
we have but I'm not going to trade all
the [\h__\h] gold just the the you know
some leftover Maybe
[Music]
interesting maybe just a a
few cuz the those will give more exp
well for him when
trading cuz it's new and he she's doing
it should have waited for a discount oh
still no wait I'm not really looking for
anything of particular huh rabbit's for
D oh wait is he double leveling
up was is this
bugged should we do one
more
[Music]
what one more
trade how much gold was it one gold per
Emerald or
five or six no it wasn't one it was
threee I think
threee this is unsatisfying I just want
him to level up one more
time
mhm why he's so close to another level
up
what I want to Max him now
[Music]
wait the where are the C Apples by the
way where are them C apples did she put
them in here oh a she already made them
gold all right all right all right she
already made him gold
[Music]
one
more
no I never maxed one of these before
it's
interesting oh never WS oh is he maxed
now yeah
Master well I might as
well cool thank
you okay if I have more zombie meat I'll
get back to to you sir and um okay now
we level we could continue leveling
him oh laa an idle be discusses her busy
schedule for the year which includes a
birthday ofter fry showcases wait did
you actually did you write this yourself
or did the AI really Rite this and other
appearances meanwhile she faces an issue
of potentially getting arrested for
taxation
no there's no no such danger of tax
evasion uh
no let me actually buy these bookshelves
from
you just a
few do the lantern
yeah the rest I'll I'll do lanterns okay
[Music]
emerals more I have no more what should
I trade what could I trade can
I is there anything else we can like
trade
[Music]
around clay right how much where is the
clay a few
[Music]
clay do we have like clay blocks is that
a
thing don't worry Justice can't get
me coal Coal could also be traded but I
don't know about trading
that I have paper more paper
[Music]
Granite
Stone but the stone is the onetime
melted Stone
[Music]
right honestly that's like an
endless source of emeralds with the
cobblestone generator but
[Music]
like this
right oh
[Music]
man how many per trade 30
something sell water bottles to the
cleric
quick
question water bottle does it only need
glass because I I would was thinking I
could make a couple on my own we do have
a few here
but can I drink the
honey
oh
o free glass H more rotten flash uh I
could make more but I think I just like
pick up most of
it
um
nine
nine it won't break right do I need I
don't
need oh I
do oh I do I do need silk touch I don't
have silk touch anymore do I do we have
a silk touch
enchantment probably not it's okay we
have some glass from when we thought
that we need
glass when we thought that we needed
glass um
bottle good
amount you chose not to get it twice and
we thought you'd never need it
what which what
what thanks what was I
doing
[Music]
oh
no hey I can't see
him oh
[Music]
discount no I well I guess you can't
really discount the one Emerald
things what you going to have after
this is this normal is this [\h__\h]
normal that he gets the same book
[Music]
again how the
[\h__\h] it's more
expensive what the actual [\h__\h] it's rare
why why
why
what I want rare things to happen when
it's good things
whatever I don't really need any more
books from you anyway does he can you
get another book If I level him up
again I'm running out of emeralds here
bro
whatever bye for now
[Music]
m
nice
[Music]
uh I think it's time for some puring oh
maybe one more one more one more go
also
here it's been growing a lot the sugar
cane ah I had I think I had sugar cane
juice in in
Thailand I
think yeah yeah I'm pretty sure I had
like some kind of sh cane
juice was it in Thailand or was it
somewhere else actually I think it was
in
Thailand it was mid for
me but I don't
know it has an interesting flavor really
[Music]
the fresher squee I think that is pretty
fresh yeah it's interesting not
bad but I
know the sugar cane flavor itself is not
my favorite thing needs a bit more like
maybe add like a one more ingredient to
it but yeah it seems to be a very
popular thing in the summer like as a
refreshing
drink in like sea
mhm it need sugar no no no no no I don't
think that's
it I don't think that's necessarily it
[Music]
okay got some more wheat let's feed the
cows
again also ah should we shouldn't we get
going and like trying to get a zombie
zombie happening again I'm so scared of
now [\h__\h] up though I'm so scared
about
[Music]
that I forgot about that too the baby is
ready by now
so y let's do it
[Music]
hi dony
wonky what you are so cute Don't Run
Away Don't Run
Away a she's so
cute she's like Mommy you said you're
not going to stream so long
today oh she's so
cute she's so
puffy she's looks like a
[Music]
bumblebee who looks like a
bumblebee I need to place a boat right
wait I don't have the boat right now
y uh they're not going to spawn that
fast are
they H Bo
[Music]
name tag
first okay yeah yeah okay okay okay then
I have to level the the
dude I have to level the dude are they
only going to have a name tag when they
have like a certain pattern of like you
know book first or whatever you know
what I mean or will they all eventually
have a name tag like I'm not leveling
the wrong person
right mhm
[\h__\h] random should always be there at
max
[Music]
level
um what should I what should I TR maybe
some
paper kind of wanted to make some more
books though wait wait wait wait I'm
doing so many things ah
I was going to perge some cows
now and this stupid alpaka really has
been bothering me whoa what the [\h__\h] was
[Music]
that they so
calm
wow don't don't hurt the Villager
right and don't hurt too many cows also
that'll not be good either you're the
last one I'm going to take down
okay
okay I make a few more books while I'm
here so that you
know slabs I can make two more bookcases
I think right
now mosts um planks
[Music]
free we're already
wait a need to
be kind of enclosed
like
oh oh man oh man oh man
that's still not quite the first row
finished yet not
quite I wonder if I put like a diamond
sword in what what enchant enchantments
I will get you can do two layers oh yeah
that's what I was looking at
anyway but I need to finish the first
layer
first no I want to get the iron from but
I need to oh I would have I would have
said let's trade iron to get the name
tag but I need the thing to work
[Music]
first meal support from the
baby no the
Wy chunky
Wy such a sweet
baby I love you
[Music]
just just so you know if you don't hear
her purring that doesn't mean that she's
not purring she's just away from the
microphone but she purs every time I
look at
[Music]
her I'm petting her on my
lap yeah yeah well you heard her clear
for that time but she's still purring
now
actually oh she Pur all right
emotional support
lasagna
baby okay I'll let you
go I
think that was necessary emotional
support for both of
us seems like she came here cuz she
needed it too
[Music]
let's trade some
paper oh thanks for the Super
Chat what is
happening t t with me and my
cat get up already hello
hello why didn't not getting up maybe
they're bugging
again it's morning get to
work wait uh can I trade paper with him
too oh it's discounted even wait 23 how
much
does do you want 24
okay discount discount oh h i could that
sell the unused books and
quills wait speaking of I got to read
C's
diary be right
back I got to do it like I mean Ena is
not riding
it yeah okay I'm going to sell
enas K is actually riding into it let me
see day two I organize everything I'm
the [\h__\h]
Minecraft day three never let's [\h__\h]
go also sorry about not very smart
snart hey it's okay I don't think you
did anything
wrong and you did you built the the iron
farm we got to give it a proper name too
like
mmm
okay today was lovely day together with
Ki and Friends 25 golden apples were
gathered at long last yay happy day
additionally construction of an iron
farm began and materials were collected
handly
yippee well she forgot to write today
again but she was so tired like I
couldn't even have asked her to do that
um okay wait I want to put Call's
back oh I might I might sell them all
and then they can just write the rest of
of their Diaries in
Discord if anybody feels like doing
it you
[Music]
know can I if I can get iron out of iron
stuff back can I get lever out of Lea
boots back don't sell them sell them not
worth the trade H it's cheap I want to
level him up and the most recent thing
that they want to sell me or buy from me
it will be bringing more exp not worth
it oh come
on right now I don't know which one is
which oh this one's SC
out keep the books I mean I would keep
like Callie's for example cuz she's
actually using it and good as
too Mama Mia
Mama M
[Music]
Mia damn nice
discounts eight
eight so close can you keep that
discount for a while
please see how little this
is how much would this
[Music]
be maybe I can make a book and qu let me
see but then I need lever
[Music]
again generally you make a book right
and then you
make ink and a and a feather see that I
think I can
provide I just want to see how much he
will uh how much exp he gets from it
it might be worth
it you
can maybe you can trade emeralds for
glass and make flas to trade for
emeralds again oh emeralds for glass
glass
for jeez emeralds for glass who was
selling
glass emeralds for
[Music]
glass W that's a lot guys I'm going to
make one or two more of
those
librarian the library librar libr
librarian I don't have a librarian no do
I do ah the book H wait that do that's
yeah okay
maybe uh think what what what what what
what was oh yeah um
[Music]
good
stuff I hope he really has a 100% chance
of getting a name
bag you changing already or oh
yeah now I just
need well a lot of
emeralds okay we wanted his glass is
that worth it four glass is one and a
little bit more than
one is that I hope that's going to be
worth
[Music]
it not worth it's worth ah which
one not worth
[\h__\h] well now I started doing that so
I'm going to continue doing it I
[Music]
guess f [\h__\h] circus music is perfect
cuz that trait just made me feel like a
[Music]
clown let's do the
math you guys do the math not me I get
four glass for one Emerald with four
glass I make a bit more than one glass
bottle I trade eight glass bottles back
to get another
Emerald
please show yourself Math
Genius it's all wor if you cope hard
enough an hour worth but like how much
is an hour
worth okay wait I do I can I guess I can
tell now by seeing I only got two back
and I I think I spent more what am I
going for right now I'm going I have to
make I have to
get 19 well you know what I we have
relatively High chances of getting
Emeral block sometimes out of
mining just got to get lucky you never
know buy glass and sell glass panels big
profits really
I'd rather gacha it on the Block than
think of yeah let's do Block
[Music]
gacha
M mob farm for zombie flesh also true
also good
[Music]
m
can't think brain small
[Music]
I was going to trade the granite too was
it
him yeah let's see how much he needed
actually oh and wasn't I burning some
Stone see this is also stuff I could get
out of the uh the mining that's maybe
you know good
[Music]
stuff chunky wony what only one [\h__\h] all
this time all this
[Music]
time just answering my cat don't mind me
oh can I burn the oak leaves or can I
burn the
bamboo yeah
understandable oh wait NE
WS how much was it for NE WS how many do
I
[Applause]
need ow what about we get a Fletcher
going so I can trade [\h__\h]
sticks so many options okay I can't
complain about the options I'm being
given 22 for the ne W okay ah
oops you guys hear
[Applause]
her yeah good she's cute she's blessing
you with her meow please appreciate
she wants to be heard she has something
to say she's doing a little cat talk
instead of net Ted Talk who's
[Music]
N I love the
sound I'm going to make a Fletcher
I wonder if somebody doesn't have a job
yet I think they're they might all be
currently
employed
maybe what what is the what's the
Fletching table I guess Fletching table
Fletching but I don't know the
recipe ah this one oh two flint okay I
don't have much Flint but two flint I
can and what was it the
planks
[Music]
okay new job idea another
one another one
hopefully somebody will take this job
oh I don't I think everybody has a
job she's rubbing against my that's not
fair that's Foul
Play don't think they can jump like
that no if I can't then they
can't you get the point of my TED
talk if you keep that bone for that long
you'll experience serious price
volatility what are you talking
about what are you talking
[Music]
about
21 I got to go make more bread again
[Music]
wait I have some bread right a little
bit this is never ending guys never
ending eight bread for one
baby if they don't rip me off it might
work the end is never the end is never
the end is never the end
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh thank you for being
for giving me a child making discount it
seems you want more a bit more I can
give you ah there it is
Babble
YooHoo now please take the I mean I
guess as a child you can't yet but
please hurry up and
grow up as fast as you
can damn those bamboo they will they
will come in
handy well there's more there even wa I
need
food grow up or
else 20 minutes what 20 minutes to grow
up oh man that's a
lot I need to at least prepare the name
tag okay
y okay while we wait we could either
mine or we can uh get more zombie
flesh but if if the child grows up and
you know I I can trade my sticks
then it
basically will probably already get us a
name tag
[Music]
two
wheat it's a drop in the sea with how
long this stream has
been yeah 20 minutes won't make much of
a difference
I'll go get
some that was by the way that was a
Minecraft cat that's not my cat or was
it she's still down there next to my
feet so cute she's just so cute
man I don't understand like there's so
many whole life members who have cats
but they don't let uh their cats into
their streaming
room which I think is such a such a
waste of happiness
she's me oh she's looking at me with the
cutest eyes I've ever seen she has such
dog eyes even though she's a
cat no cat on M that's that's not oh
what's with all the creepers holy
[\h__\h] the cat hairs they're they're fine
they're not a big
problem n she lets little man into her
sing room not always she says sometimes
she has to get rid of
him what does she want from
[Music]
me you know
smoothie she's been like these past
wait what the [\h__\h] where's this where
did the
[Music]
spido smovie has been waking me up
usually exactly an hour before my
alarm like uh
consistently for the past days it's so
UNS unsatisfying she will not stop me
meowing but the thing is if it's 1 hour
see I get up I make her food I take the
chance to go to an idol meeting cuz I
kind of feel like I need to anyway and I
go back to bed
and all of this doesn't take long but
now it will take me a while to fall
asleep
again and then okay I fall
asleep but then you know this it's just
like so close to the Finishing Line
organic alarm clock it's so close to the
Finishing Line why why why are you doing
this to me
smoothie I could almost finish my sleep
and now it's like
so being woken up right before I should
wake up and then losing a few more like
20 30 minutes or so because I have to
fall asleep again okay maybe not 30 so
I'm relatively tired still at that point
sometimes it doesn't work though like
yesterday I think I ended up just
staying up like I went back to bed I
tried to sleep again I realized my brain
is too excited too
busy out I'm
Ry so then there's those times you know
where I just can't sleep again because
it was so close to my
alarm oh oh man she's like she's
she's she's baiting me oh
baby okay
okay this is making me feel
pain zombie
[Music]
flesh only
they took some of this other stuff
too I don't think they
do 61 wait might want like a few more
right cuz it's like
is maybe misses you she wants you to
stop
[Music]
please end your stream and pay your
taxes set you alarm 1 hour later as you
usually wanted and she wakes you up then
it's right on time you would think
so you would hope that that works but
probably not then she's just going to
continue waking me up 2 hours before
Oh big brain idea though
she doesn't know but I've noticed one
thing like you know I I will try to like
ignore her and close my eyes and
continue sleeping until she just shuts
the [\h__\h] up
but she will continue meowing endlessly
then H but when I have decided okay [\h__\h]
it I can't sleep anymore and I take my
phone while I'm still in my bed and just
look at my phone for a while with the
intention of getting up
soon just squirreling through my phone
browsing through it she will stop
meowing usually often because she sees I
stopped trying to
sleep
she's
just this cat I swear to God hello
[Music]
hello you guys stuck or something
cat doing cat things that is honestly
orange cat's Behavior but she's not even
orange where are the zombies we need
more zombies being
spawned okay now it's almost 1 hour
after the time I really wanted to end
so okay I I will really after I get the
name tag I will really end it I
swear I won't even like wait for the
zombie to appear yet okay I won't even
go for
that but I'll put the name tag in a
chest so in case cie decides to
stream Minecraft tomorrow you guys can
tell her where the name tag is or I can
tell her but I might even be awake for
it who knows who knows
I'll see what cie will do I might play a
little bit off stream if CI doesn't
stream then if she doesn't stream and
doesn't play I'll just like try to fix
it off stream although it would be good
to have your general input you
know but if she does stream I cannot
guarantee that I will take the deal wait
how do you I'm back to 10 isn't that
what I had
before anyway uh maybe the child has
grown
[Music]
up no it's still not grown
up where is the zombie guy
you h 31 see
[Music]
like you know imagine I would have left
her alone today with all that I don't
think that would have been good feel
like she needed me I feel like she
needed
[Music]
me grow
up could make a book or some a book or
two one one lever per book right
we're getting there we're getting there
enchanting table almost could make it
one level only too still pretty good I
mean for now at least
[Music]
oh you can cut Corners e but will it
still be the right
amount you
know will still have the same effect or
won't it be weaker will it not be weaker
[Music]
this needs to be 15 within
range H then in the end it's the same no
we'll see we'll
see
child if you don't grow up
soon going to force you to get to work
even as a child
[Music]
Corners don't get
detected
huh huh these
[Music]
Corners this one
too Corner got detected
[Music]
pretty sure corn
is yeah otherwise why would everybody
build it like
[Music]
that whatever
uh oops
[Music]
see ah ah ah
thought of one
thing they do have a lot of Bones over
there and I I wanted more bones for bone
meal for more hay for more bread no for
more cow
feeding and villager feeding too maybe
but so many uses for this right and they
questioned I'm a question do we really
even need it yes we do I've been getting
a lot of use out of it
H yes we
[Music]
do yeah my my Minecraft streams have
been consistently like 5 to 6 hours
these days pretty much so what am I
doing today is another one of those days
[Music]
what the hell
no
[Music]
no leave me alone leave me alone leave
me alone
[Music]
bamboo into sticks oh yeah yeah
yeah surely he's a Fletcher by now uh
I think he might be a Fletcher by
[Music]
now just give me one more farming moment
here one more little farming
[Music]
session then if I come back for sure
there's no chance that he's still a
child could get get dizzy from this
honestly sorry if people get dizzy from
the way I play this game with almost
Quake
Pro I like it when it's kind of fish
lens you though because at least that
way I can see more I wish you could just
like get more view without making it
fish lensy that would be better
[Music]
yeah no
space you should really fix those blocks
that have no soil nah whatever it's just
a few a few no hay blocks that's okay
just a
couple or is it is it like some sort of
problem that is created by that
ER and I I don't even know how they
showed up there like I I don't
think I did anything to deserve that
I fixed them a few times and then they
still came
back I don't remember jumping on
[Music]
them okay I can make him grow again with
all that bone meal but I do want to
see about the
child after I feed the cows
[Music]
it's like I'm in a loop
hell it's pretty bad I'm
[Music]
stuck I'm on the grind
yeah ah it's already good amount that I
could Purge the
again just kind of want to wait for them
to grow
up don't really want to hit the children
by accident of course Fletcher
man how the [\h__\h] are you still a
child no no no yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
are you back in does that
work pushing you back worked amazing
how is he still a child that
[\h__\h]
[Music]
unbelievable we had to sneak on soil
back in the day o
that is
no
difficult how how can you mine
efficiently thank God they changed
[Music]
it that takes you back you played
Minecraft so long ago how long is that
ago I'm really a noob when it comes to
Minecraft if you think about it because
I only started playing it 4 years ago a
little bit less than four years
ago where am I see okay that I just
admit was
me was my
fault just
jumped 500 years ago
[Music]
ohos this
you played it with your iPod what just
like who said that was that GDA who said
that too that's crazy I can't believe
you were able to play games on iPod I
never knew that I mean except for maybe
like games like uh snake or whatever
it's called the small snake game where
the snakes eat each other the the pixel
game you know what I
mean is that called snake
games had simpler names back in the day
like
Frogger
snake M was a Nokia kid I don't know if
I was a Nokia kid but I I just was not
an iPod
kit okay
child
wa child must have grown
up it's been 5 days or
so just one more
time what are you riding there dhood
what what are you doing what are you up
to okay I'll give you one promise guys I
will not stream
tomorrow I might play Minecraft but I
[Music]
no I will not I need the
time I need
it for real also considering
how I've been I didn't have a break for
at least a week or more and actually if
you consider that I've been working on
my break days too it's probably weeks
since my last break
tap and uh the weekend I want to stream
on Friday Saturday Sunday ideally
I we'll see about it
though which one this one's the Fletcher
I think finally kept me waiting huh it's
32 3 I'm
[Music]
Son Discount Maybe
oh he's already doing it
okay
huh damn even that's kind of rough I
thought wouldn't be as
much how many do we have now how many do
I need I have 15 was
it how
many um
19 ah so close I have 15 he wants
[Music]
19 uh what else could I
do more zombie is there how fast to the
the wood
grow can make some more sticks out of
actual wood too though oh oh oh it grows
relatively
fast not as tall as I'd like it to
be let's take it we take those
W's make sure to pick it up
W make sure to pick it
up did you finish the enchantment table
set up well I mean it's kind of there
it's not I I would probably add more
books to it off screen tomorrow
M more bookshelves
tomorrow I'm I guess I'm too too once I
add the first row it will like start
taking effect or what I thought it might
already have effect now so I need one
full row at
least don't want you get exhausted and
be sick while your
bed well at least I think by being kind
of food
poisoned for two
days maybe my sick
uh ra ratio or so what was it called not
ratio I fulfilled the what's that
word quoda yeah I fulfilled my quota for
sure
for a
[Music]
while oh no the tree is so
tall I'm too lazy to get up
there another time
[Music]
that won't
work
oops oh she got some bow meal here too
actually got some more logs I'll take
them I'll take them
a few of
them okay okay okay
okay wait plank
planks six
[Music]
okay I got so many
sticks you cannot refuse my trade offer
unless you are out of stock that's that
will also be a problem please don't be
out of stock ever ever
ever it's time for a discount my
friend come on when when do they How do
they how do they decide when to give me
discount actually I might have enough
now
woohoo
yay oh
hallelujah usually after an upgrade oh
okay okay okay uh
you is that from 20 to 19 or is it from
28 to
19 looks like a
[Music]
28 20 Al I thought it was giving me a
pretty generous one okay this name
tag if if that zombie dies the future
zombie I will be so
mad we first before okay in any case if
cie ends up streaming tomorrow and I'm
not there and she's trying to create
zombie let her know to not name it
before it's not in position like not
while like hunting it and leading it I
mean I feel like she would not do that
anyway but while it's still being led it
could still die or like something could
fail once it's seated in position
nobody's getting hurt then it should be
[Music]
named you can tell her yourself yeah
probably cuz I'll beat there probably or
I'll do it on my
own oh
[Music]
H you guys want me to do it too yeah I
know you okay okay I didn't expect you
guys to say do it but okay I didn't
expect
that I'm still kind of worried about the
placement but I I think I
remember how far away it was it wasn't
too difficult and then it wasn't hitting
the villagers so it was kind of
[Music]
fine bro
I have no arrows well she seems like
he's going to stay
there he's
turning hi guys you're still free people
right you know is this is this does this
look okay is this okay or does it have
to be like this I think it has to be
like this right
[Music]
okay
now that looks good
too wait I don't want to push it
away okay that's good that is I think
yes I only did that because I knew I
would be
fine but that really sucks that that
happens ah testing testing sound's
coming a no he's
SP a man there's a roof there you
idiot is that the one that I saw
[Music]
well
okay I will take that and just leave it
at that even though it would have been
nice to get it
[Music]
done and it will hurt
me it will hurt me
[Music]
uh
close the trap doors and remove or remve
the
[Music]
boat well aiming the zombie belongs to
finish iron farm
[Music]
really yeah wait
nothing down there right okay okay okay
[Music]
okay how did I get out before all right
I teleported freaking teleported my way
out of
here okay
[Music]
hey I can't go back up oh there we go in
chest
uh uh at uh iron farm
roof name name when
seated name when seated makes sense
right I think
so okay okay why out why out why no
touching
game W no touching the
game wa stop touching
game no more touch no touching touch not
allowed or else W ban for life from
Minecraft um I I have to eat some kind
of lunch now and then I'll get to my
work that I need to
do too much careful W too much Minecraft
careful W too
much so true so true no tou
[Music]
that's a relevant one thank you guys so
much for hanging out with me today again
while I
am being pretty efficient and however
kind of losing my mind because I'm
playing too
long thank you I had a good time it was
fun careful wa careful wa careful yeah
takoni was strong today again
I'm I'm really really happy that she's
um I mean honestly she might be like
almost like too too dedicated I don't
want her to feel like she has to be here
like every day I don't want her to like
force herself when she already has so
much on her plate but I really
appreciate her um you know
supporting she always supports projects
that I have going on and I feel like I
also always support projects that she
has going on so Takami is very
supportive of each other but you know
everybody's busy doing stuff and uh it's
okay that it was just takam that's fine
too I got so much happiness out of the
other days
too I would explode if I if it was myth
every day full myth I would
explode um but then anyway I
think I think either coming Sunday night
or Monday night or so
we should be able to do
it the
end yeah and ideally until then I just
want to like put this on freeze on
hold
yeah which is a bit
anticlimactic but it's okay it's it has
to be like this
it's got to be like
[Music]
this what do you mean w will'll be able
to rate people now you mean generally or
uh because you know new members are you
implying something there or do you mean
right now just because I'm ending the
stream I've always been able to rate
people I don't do it every day cuz
sometimes I forget and also sometimes
there's not there's some No One
streaming or
but I've already been able to raid
[Music]
people usually it's like you know Ena or
or sometimes FAA kind of starts
streaming when I
[Music]
end no it's not
mandatory yeah but yeah if if there is
and we don't know if there's anybody
closer to my streaming times you know uh
then maybe we can yeah rate each other
more often there but it's not like there
was a a non-existence of raiding both
being raided and raiding until now ID
raids me a lot for example
too yeah
maybe so yeah and sorry guys for not
having time for super chatos a maybe one
of those other days
I need to get my [\h__\h]
done
German what do I eat for
lunch lunch at 10
p.m. stop the clown music
now if call streams Minecraft I might
show up just like you know doing
stuff yeah but she should take a break
too okay
bye-bye love
you Cho ch ch ch ch ch kfp
Lau hope you had
fun I had
fun I felt like everything is a ticking
time bomb
[Music]
W
mama oh there's actually no one
streaming right
[Music]
now well there's really no one streaming
the next stream is like narissa in like
4 hours or
what
wow what that's rare okay well then have
a nice evening
[Music]