[Music]
so
uh
[Music]
hello hello
it is me
oh
i'm feeling a bit shy
you know what
one's sec
hello
i closed the door i wanted to keep it
open for the cats but i decided to close
it i'm too too embarrassed um hello so
for everyone who doesn't know why i'm
embarrassed uh
uh today
kind of uh
last minute spontaneously my my mom is
here with me i live alone but
my mom is here um but she's uh she's
keeping herself busy by um
well before the stream we kind of
cleaned partially together oh my cat's
already meowing
[Music]
ah smoothie doesn't like it when the
door is closed
yeah but now she's gonna continue um
cleaning a bit for the next couple hours
and uh
and
yeah uh she's gonna bring me um some
food later i think um it's okay though
because she knows that i was gonna be
streaming and now
oh it's moving okay okay i'll open the
door it's moving
[Music]
that didn't last very long
mommy visto hello son
no hello
my mom's going to say hello
aloha okay she's she's going out now
okay see you later mommy
okay okay mommy's gonna go out for a
little bit so i i feel uh more
comfortable
yeah yeah it was mommy mommy mommy
yeah we're gonna play l in the ring for
a few hours there there are no there are
no super chat so there will be no super
chat ratings so yeah it will be a
comfortable stream where we're gonna
we're gonna explore a little bit and
then um
later we're gonna try
to kill that dude over there again
but
um you know what i could probably brute
force it and kill him
if i try
a million more times but
yeah at first i have to get used to the
game again like first of all how do how
do i open my
there it is okay
uh how do
how do i see the
ah
when i fight again i forgot
these l and r buttons
okay okay
um i want to get something uh how do i
open the map again
not that way
that
no
no no no
how no
i open the map
what's the map button
okay
i want to go somewhere i don't know
exactly where it is but i saw a video of
a turtle shield you know what i'm
talking about i think i gotta go um all
the way down here and then
i'm not sure i want to get the turtle
shield
[Laughter]
maybe you know what i'm talking about
cat can you not go out that door it's
leaned on i'll help you
you know when cats never know where they
want to go out
yeah turtle shield because that's a good
starter shield
that i've seen that's pretty pretty easy
to get we just got to travel a little
bit
um
you've seen it
it's south yeah uh i think it's like in
an area here and there's like something
where you can zoom jump up uh with like
an air
air flow thingy with your horse
yeah and also like the the the starting
area you guys are talking about you are
you talking about like
this area or
i don't i still don't know
where that was supposed to be
it's the starting area in this area
around the water
yeah yeah
are you saying that's correct for the
starting area or for the turtle shield
yeah that area okay and we'll walk over
here kill a few mobs
and then we'll go find that turtle
shield
uh starter area is even further
what even further
this
further south into the fog
south you mean where we're gonna go for
the turtle shield
okay that's i find that very weird that
the starter area is not where you start
out
that's that i find kind of weird
is shell shock is that the name of the a
welcome back cat oh oh jokers haven't
seen you in a while junkrat has been
hiding because the cleaning action was
so noisy okay i guess we're gonna
teleport to
here
how do i use my horse again guys one
more button did i have one of those on
the right side of the it always popped
up on the right side of the screen
i don't want to push the wrong button
and use a flask
itself is extra sturdy
for the extra starter it's not a hotel
why and down i don't have why
triangle
ah thank you uh was it a bracelet little
finger it was a bracelet yeah okay i
heard that when you're um
when you're when you when you get your
horse
you're invincible while you're summoning
the horse
nah
leah how do i sprint again
jump jump
oh there's some zombies there how do i
unmount
what did i push to mount ah
there we go there we go there we go
let's try to kill some people hold all
four jump for sprinting okay and how do
i
no i knew this would happen
damn it
how did i crouch
oh there we go there we go let's kill
them
i knew i would do that
that they won't even notice me those are
weak [\h__\h]
and i think this was yeah focusing on
them
and how do i do that surprise attack
again
um
ah okay i did it
oh they're shocked
don't run
don't run away
what
those aren't zombies right i didn't just
kill some normal civilians no those are
zombies
they don't i know that when you kill
like a leader of a group sometimes the
other ones don't want to fight and [\h__\h]
i did it again
you're scared of me but i need those exp
i'm sorry guys
so we go back i want those flasks
but then the enemies will be there again
wait what's that cool thing yes cute
uh and fan glass
wait that looks so cool i want that at
home
oh there's a
friend
i'm gonna try to kill him is he strong
oh he turns around
doesn't look like
wow he does look kind of strong
looks like he has a strong weapon
yeah better or not i'm scared
a telescope yeah
mama don't
uh
you gotta go down so when you unmount
you're also invincible did you know that
i can use it oh
oh
now i have my flasks back right yeah
it's been it's been a while
i need to relearn some things i think
but we'll get into the groove i hope
let's go let's go get a proper shield
then i'll feel more confident when i'll
block something maybe
i see they're back of course they're
back but i want to look for it
can i use that oh use bird's eye
telescope you can use the bird's eye
tails cause found in various areas to
get a version of the terrain that oh in
the direction that it's um
[Music]
okay
but of course oh what that's cool
of course i'm not invincible while i'm
looking through it
i could be attacked at any time will i
see myself
where am i
should be somewhere there should be
there
i don't know if i can see the thing
where i'm trying to go to
it's like a tower
this is pretty cool
we can even look up
okay let's kill them a second time
[Music]
oh it would kick me out of the telescope
there's a big one coming
i already turned around
i'm sorry i'm sorry i gotta kill you too
every exp counts you know do i pillage
you no okay the other one another one
we're gonna let him go let him go
was i supposed to touch these
nah
okay
oh would you look at that
yeah
yeah wait
there's someone
wait i just want this thing here
i don't remember another woman i don't
know
anything
[Laughter]
wait i want the ball
i want the ball where did the ball go
this is not how it's supposed to go no
no no no no no no no
that's pretty bad that's pretty bad
[\h__\h] beetle
oh
cool we got some armor can i wear that
this is not how it's supposed to go
and
it's not better than what i have
probably not
oh it is
it's a bit better
it is a bit better
yo it doesn't look as good i look like
one of them
i got the drip yeah
he's still scared maybe we should help
him by killing him then he wouldn't be
scared anymore also what about that guy
damn
[Music]
i don't know
maybe on horse
when he turns around there can we kill
him i also want to get an arrow a bow
and an arrow
more arrows more than one
are we crossing that first right now no
it's a different bridge or is it
yeah okay
charge i don't know i don't know how to
charge
okay
come here come here come here
we just both keep missing
oh yeah
oh nice
oh
[\h__\h]
i should maybe leave the horse
okay okay
he's going down he's going down
okay
one more
xp
oh this mountain well he didn't dismount
me what a loser and raisins i know you
can feed your horse with that right
beast liver damn you dropped some good
stuff laughing
i i took too much damage there
[\h__\h]
okay wait i should equip that
that sounds like a good item but heavy
maybe
[Music]
we can't worry about not really though
it's probably even too strong for me let
me see
heavy load strength 19 is required we
have 18 i think
huh no what
what no
what
huh
ah oh there it is strength 10 19 i need
19 huh
i'm so far away from that
yes the weapons are not really myself
but okay we got a cool weapon maybe one
day we can use it i'm 10.
what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] are those
am i supposed to just are they going to
pass by here
beat him up
no that's probably not happening
nicole
they're not gonna cross the bridge
they're just trolls
i'm gonna go left uh no right
[Music]
right whoa
and i have a chest yeah but there's no
way no way i can fight them um
i can mark right uh mark um
okay can i see that um
no i can't
i want to mark it so that i can a beacon
place the beacon
see the beacon there it is okay um oh
[\h__\h] they're coming
don't attack me
i just want to go somewhere completely
different
why is that dude marked
can i talk of you
what's with him
huh
hillary's remains oh he's dead
let me
i i could do it from the horse okay
a somber snapping stone
what can i get that leaf no
it looks so fancy
uh
uh okay
oh there's a guy looking for me
i'm scared
[Music]
oh one hit
i just want some some meat maybe that
will be helpful what is that animal
supposed to be
like a squirrel kangaroo we've seen it
before
hello well you're no match for me
probably
as strong as your friend huh
oh no much weaker
wait i don't have flasks i gotta be
careful
oh
[Applause]
okay well you're not dropping anything
well that was easy
that was easy
he didn't fight that much
a lot of people
let's go
oh
i see what's going on
oh [\h__\h]
gotta be careful that they don't see us
and i gotta go that way
i think i have to go up
caravan
um
waypoint runes
oh i have not been here before
and get those fruits is there something
here to loot
what is this
the flowers have hp
not a hodor
wait is there like ah
oh i'm poisoned
ew why would you do that
stop that
a glowstone
when i use the glowstone
oh my god
okay well excuse me
but what's happening
what
what is that
what is that what is that what is that
[\h__\h]
was that is that the flower
stewing
did the flower do that
or what no [\h__\h] way that the flower
did that
big flower in the middle
i don't see a big flower in the middle
is it so big ah
it felt that i was hurting its
children
oh perhaps
salmon
touch this summoning pool is now
functional
what about this thing
[Music]
holy lights trying to destroy me
damn
scary i want to find somewhere where i
can heal myself
all right let's go around it coconut
coconut
where am
i i'm kind of going the wrong way
here
this way this way this way
photo shooting oh whoops
not scary
unless there's a lot of them oh no one
is sleeping i don't wake him up i'm not
here to wake you up keep on sleeping
sleeping very important
very important
oh god are they following me they're
still following me
why is everyone so mad at me huh
what did i do to deserve that
oh i'm leading the wolves to the to the
sheeps oh no
i'm sorry
i know don't worry they're not here
anymore i love the way they wrote oh by
the way i supposedly banned the word
rolling i don't know if you guys can
still use it
oh i think the video said the video the
guide video said that i should just run
through here
i think this was the point was it
maybe
i guess i'll run through i'll try oh god
this is dangerous
how do i jump again okay
oh
run
[Music]
so far so good
no no no
no no no oh what is that what is that
skyline shines
no no no why didn't you
my heart just stopped for a moment i
thought i was gonna take a there it is
wait that's not it no it's a different
thing
oh we're way too way too far still
i thought i was gonna die falling down
apparently the word still works okay
whatever
whatever i thought i put it in i did put
it maybe it didn't save properly put it
into the ng words roll and rolling
ah
okay wait
i thought i thought map is safe but no
map is not safe nothing is safe where is
there no no no no
spot for me to chill for a moment and
like to heal
what are those
what are the dubs
i guess i'll just stop
run through here maybe i could kill you
um i'll go wait i have oh god my damage
and i'm i could die like one hit
dangerous
spirit spring jumping i don't know jump
well on the horse back near your spirits
when you ride its current high into into
the air is blair you won't take damage
from jumping in i know
there are churches
all right maybe uh
uh
oh god and this was the thing i needed
to run through can i go
can i go without damage i mean look at
that
korean
where is the nearest ah
i could go back to the church
the church is here
maybe something is here
rush through
just don't get hit that is a good advice
thank you very much
okay
[Music]
myself here
oh
myself
i wanna be
all by
myself
is there nothing here
there should be something here come on
what
the [\h__\h] is that
a crab
it's a crap dance
what about this can i not rest here
sliver of meat i want to rest
there's no place of resting
wait
he's riding fast oh my god
[Music]
grace southeast of the crabs
uh
oops if the crab is here southeast so
somewhere here
behind me
i passed it
uh is there any
indicator south
somewhere
somewhere here
close to the road
okay but there's some people walking
there close to the road
over there
[Music]
look for sparkly
sparkly
oh my mom's home
my mom's home
my mommy's home
walking around it straight south
straight straight out the streets
um
i got chicken nuggets
chicken nuggets
i had i had uh two pieces of cake for
breakfast
uh now i'm gonna have nuggets of course
vegan what else would it be
the best sauce sweet sour
oh
are we good are we good
oh they're following me
really slowly
oh we got some time to eat
go back
he really wants to do something with me
you want my phone number
i'm not gonna give my phone number yeah
go back okay
he understood it
um
oh he wants to nuggets oh
communication is key
why are these old zombies i would fight
them if i had a bit more exp oops
where's that gravy
close to the road close to the road they
say
if you kill them and get a heel coat how
can i do that with such little
but is it the light that i isn't that
the light of where my corpse would be
the one in the
in the directions
don't kill me no family
wait wait
how am i not finding it
did someone just blow a horn oh whoop
oh god my fingers are slippery right now
oh no this one's where the plant is i
don't know what i'm missing
oh
use maps of fashion i don't know but i
thought there was something close by
what about here
is this where the plant
is the wolves
i should maybe just travel because now i
can also get a level i think
oh i can't travel because i'm being
targeted
is that what it is
okay
quick quick church uh oops
[Music]
huh i was going the right way
well i don't know uh
rest
rice and eat a chicken nugget
eat that chicken nugget
um
[Music]
oh wait i can't yet i'm still eh
i'm still missing a lot okay
wait no i'm not missing
1200 i'm missing like 200 okay
hmm
fresh hot warm chicken nuggets
um
she's reaching out for the chicken
nuggets
oh i'm sorry you can't have them i don't
know i don't think it's good for you to
eat this stuff
it's very very processed and [\h__\h]
sorry kitty cat there's a lot of
a lot of spices in here
oh i picked up golden brooms oh
hmm
that's what they were for
kevin is missing from work oh he's sick
he caught the virus
[Music]
they say he might not survive it
he might not survive it so he probably
won't be coming back
don't wait for him don't wait for him
don't worry i only got six nuggets
that's all that kevin was able to give
me
hmm
i mean before sending him home because
he was sick
i went to get some food and then i
thought he was sick or sent him home
that's all there is to it
[Music]
so wait i need to
go into my inventory
and open up um the golden runes views
right
400. yo i got so many golden runes at
the grave
damn i feel bad for
taking
them damn
basically using someone else's
life to get more for myself
now we can level up
i think i'll go for
how much more hp oh
it's quite a lot more
okay we'll go for bigger now
yeah
yeah they won't need it
all right
all right time to go
horsey calm down
now once again we'll go that way what is
that
ah i never couldn't ruin yo
yo
oh wait those are confusing i made the
wrong
thing here um big boy coming
run run run run
another wait they're like everywhere
what the [\h__\h]
and just level up by running around a
little bit
without even fighting anything
uh yeah dexterity i noticed by watching
other people i noticed that
they get a lot
oh you can
you can summon your friends here you get
a lot um
more faster
with
uh
like if you
use a different shield or if you use no
shield or depending on how you
hold your
sword and shield and so on
um
yeah
so i always felt like my robes were
really slow maybe because of that maybe
uh
i need to experiment a little bit with
that where the hell am i going i'm going
this from this side now
is that even possible
yeah what's down here
okay
another golden rune um
i saw in the video
no he was just using it or did he also
get it like in a bow or some oh did he
buy it
not sure i want to get a bow it would
help me a lot i think
we'll do that after the shield maybe
i suppose
okay
okay okay all right all right
we could already do another level up
yeah
already
am i going the right way
where is the marker
anyway
oh what was that again that sign oh it's
not the sign that leads you to a safe
thingy yeah yeah
i found one
uh
that's what you meant with the sparkles
okay for this one i found it that was
not the one that you guys meant though
or did you oh maybe you did
that's not southeast
of the crab
the south
that's west of the crowd
well while we're here
uh i know actually i need to we should
show
there's never one there uh-huh okay and
i will
use more golden rings yo
let's go
get another level up a free level up
wait did i use both no
ah that's not enough for a level up
soon though i know
i think it's
not quite enough i want to be like 1400
or something
yeah a bit more a bit more
he was still like tattoos yeah yeah
i i know i feel gory
but i know
i also heard that when you're when it's
nighttime
the enemies will be um
had to stay
they'll have a harder time
noticing you
what the [\h__\h] are you guys
have a hard time noticing it looks
pretty realistic i like that because the
nighttime makes you harder to see
oh and
you can attack if you have two weapons
you can attack with the left hand as
well
on the horse
i need to farm runes yes yes i'm gonna
dance yes but i want my turtle shield
the question is will i be even using it
once i have it what's going on over
there
hey what's happening
should i join
get some experience this is a bad idea
oh what the [\h__\h]
they're focused on oh my gosh
get out get hurt
what's happening what's happening
i'm helping him right now
oh did i just kill a group basically a
group of
oh they're all dead
what happened
mosh pit
free exp yeah yeah
oh
we can get another level up now
[Laughter]
damn it everyone ended up dead
and i won i'm the only winner in this
fight
i deserve a nugget for that
oh
my mom made some sounds and it startled
me
the last remaining nuggets
oh
man it's nice to have someone bring your
nuggets while you're streaming
um
should collab with cali
see
i don't know if kelly mentioned this on
stream but
um
she was asking around for a
co-op collapse but then
after me mentioning it she realized
most of the other girls
are playing on pc
and me and callie are the only ones in
halloween who are playing on playstation
5.
mm-hmm
we've been hollow ian
we're the only one who can play together
right now
and i don't know i don't think kelly
will get a pc version just for
playing with the others now
but i told callie
that i heard this from um
from neuer standby
uh
no understand by also plays on pc right
now in her streams but she got herself
a ps5 version as well
just for co-op with uh lulu
lui and lami senpai because those two
also play on ps5
and rami are ps5 norwegian is both now
nice
and yeah me and callie ps5 and the rest
of the ian girls are
pc
yeah i just i just chose ps5 because i
have a ps5 and i heard that usually the
pc versions are
at least around release a little bit meh
yeah you guys recommended me ps5 but i'm
surprised so many other people are
getting what is that
is that a grace
why am i finding everything now and i
couldn't find it when i was looking for
it
can only find things when i'm not
actively looking for it huh is that it
this is the one that you guys meant
right
is it unstable
you see really
i sure
how did i not see that
it's easier to see at night though
way easier
now
i was running around here ahead
okay
now
i feel like i can run through that one
part uh even if i take some hits wait i
should get wait wait wait wait wait i
should level up before i do that
okay
yeah yeah
i should do that damn 1 800 by doing
nothing
what are those rainbow stones
serving as a guide
i think i saw it in a tutorial like if
you throw it down
um a cliff and it breaks loudly then you
will die when you jump down but if it
doesn't break you will not take you will
not die is that really what it's for
oh and this kind of i guess is like uh
will tell you
we will help you
it's great to check if you'll die
i don't know if that's really the
purpose it's supposed to be used for but
2 000 yo
i can get one level up
dexterity makes me faster right
so we can go for one dexterity now
right
strength for shield oh we need it for
the shield
oh
yeah that shield probably needs some
strength
the turtle shield
14 for okay well now we gotta
prepare for that okay
all right i didn't quite think about
that until now
okay
oh wait sorry
um do i need anything else
mommy's so loud
a good shield from the soldiers no i
want that turtle shield
i saw i can get it without even fighting
so now i want it
[Music]
faith allows me to use fireballs yeah i
don't know i kind of want to use magic
too because like at least i can fight
from the distance
but there's only so many uh
level ups i can do right now
so
i kind of wanted to find some time to
um
you know
grind a little bit before the stream
oh that really hurt me
it's really hard to get through here
okay okay
can i uh throw it the other way too oh
that person
oh a lot of dead people
am i safe
safe
who are you npc
i did it
hello
is somebody there yes i'm here now bend
your ear for a moment please i'm
listening my name is blind
i've escaped from castle mourn to the
south oh my god the servants there have
rebelled mommy is making noises i can't
be sure what it is
my eyesight's been weak since birth you
see oh but i swear in the castle you
mean the castle allowed was
my good i think margaret secreted me out
the castle but decided himself to stay
he says it's his duty
as commander
uh-huh
always remember to talk to them more
often
the servants are full of wrath
filled with hatred for every one of us a
lessons come for every one of the
companions i escaped with
they haven't spared a soul this is a
sci-fi it's no different at castle
morning please
i implore you where in the map is that
oh you didn't meet him to my father
right after that
my soul wishes that he escaped even if
you want me to save your
bodies
i just want him to be safe
uh yeah but i just i don't have to do
that right away right well okay we'll
accept it for now
then please
take this why not how much exp do these
side quests give i wonder or do they not
give any who remains in the castle if
you please
eventually it might take a couple days
weeks
uh
i can't open the map
not being attacked
let me open the map
i mean you could at least have me open
the map even if i can't teleport come on
i don't even know where i am
why can't i not open the map i don't
even hear battle music grace next to the
bridge
grace
next to that bridge
above or underneath
race
[Music]
mushrooms
okay
now to continue my path although maybe i
should rest
yeah when did i use so many floss oh
i remember
i remember now did you get margie no not
yet but it is our quest today around the
end of the stream
to
do that
get market margin market
whatever you want to call him
so uh
i think mostly i just have to follow the
path from here i have the video open in
case i get lost
i wonder if i
i think i'll be fine
is your inventory i think it's over
there is your inventory
and endless
like does it ever
is it hello
does it ever fill up to the brim oh my
god just just run through
ah
it's not the button i wanted to push
so what's happening
kill it
[Music]
helpful for when i use the bow
oh
the [\h__\h] are you
oh my god
uh
okay
run run run
come on stay away from that guy
oh
hello hello hello hello is he following
me
patch
please follow me hey um
what's the
he's slowly approaching me uh menacingly
oh god
[Music]
this guy dropped something crazy well
he's right here we can i guess try to
fight
where is he
and now he's of course not here
but he walks this area i suppose he's on
patrol
oh man
at least it was really close here oh
wait is that it oh wait that's it up
there
this is it no
well that was fast isn't this where i
wanted to go
i just got to go up there and then as as
i've seen in the video he appears at
night he spawns in it ah
not during daytime i see
that's it
that's how
how easy it is
wow
okay everybody who didn't know you're
welcome
so we have some stuff there there it is
that's it great turtle shell i can't use
it yet but
yes
that is the wonderful shield that's
really opie and the warming stone
yeah jackpot
i suppose normally
are you even supposed to get up here
like that are you supposed to go like
from below i don't know
wait where is the how do i get down
i need to jump down again
where is the are here
this is really safe to do
yes yes yes okay okay
it was that easy
you need a horse for it yeah
that's just the one we already saw right
yeah okay i'll calculate okay that was
really fast i thought it would take a
bit more time
so is this the area the beginner area
that you guys meant
we should get um we should get the map
i don't know where it is
oh
that looks like where
a map would be hiding
but isn't that usually like yeah ah
chloe i was about to say
map
yes
what what what what what's what's going
on
what
from so far away
i see a big boy
oh he's he has a huge bow see here it
comes here oh
is that the castle where the father is
from that lady
oh my hell no
oh hell no
no no no
oh no no no no he's slow
i am
he probably has a different weapon too
he's easy to kill oh no way
i don't believe a word
is that wasn't that up there
do we want to fight him or just pass by
him
oh
keep hitting on the legs avoid arrows
okay well
we can try
[Laughter]
maybe he dropped something nice
should i use um uh wait how do i
oh yeah
what
wait why where's my second i thought i
can use both
what what can i use
equipment
on horseback it doesn't work yeah if i
would work
okay
um
oh god
oh god are we doing this for real
charge forward
let's go
kill ourselves
i am phoenix how are you gonna shoot me
from there
how are you gonna shoot me from there
i died
wait how how far did we get him down
i guess i deserved that for making fun
of him
you guys trolling me when you say i
should just kill him
i don't believe i can kill him can i get
one
one and a half yeah 20 okay okay okay
give it another try oh he's already
already aiming at me
[Music]
why are you you mad bro
you're so angry
hey you can't shoot me you can't shoot
me you know i'm here but you can't catch
me
coming for you
wow
okay
oh wait he has going barely barely
do it do it
do it
i think
how much xp does he give me i mean 1 800
now
what did he drop he dropped nothing
huh it was easy though but he didn't
what's that
uh ambrose
crap
is there grace here because i wanna
maybe here
make sure i don't lose my exp before i
go ah but then he will be um and he'll
be here here again but i could kill him
again
whoa
red jellyfish
what is this
the siege of castlemorn
what do you guys saying at the entrance
inside okay a lone hero fights for his
vengeance only to
i was i was ringing joffrey only to
follow the hand of lord godfrey okay not
jeffrey from game of thrones okay
uh
is there a lot more to fight inside i
guess we're doing a side quest if it's
realistic for me to
to do it
yeah rip man
r.i.p
oh everybody did oh why is what is this
is that like a
dungeon
oh i have to get off my horse
oh
is everybody just dead then it would be
nice because i don't have to fight
anyone
what's grace discovered oh it can't be
that easy
it can't be that easy oh it's an
elevator
okay go
what
is hello
it's not being operated
level up ah
forgot i keep on forgetting such a weird
way that you have to level up manually
but okay
um let's also use this
step on the oh okay
the middle
strength
we're going to be able to carry the
shield soon enough
we're ready
all right but wait when i go outside
will he be
back greeting me
hello
all the way to the top
oh hell hello
oh
oh is that a
hill of bodies
is this really beginner area guys
should i be should i be here
they're like they have a leader i guess
it's like a leader
wow look at all those bodies hanging oh
no
well where is the oh wait is that the
king
is that the king there that they're
about to burn
i'm good
they they look they look they could be
kind of weak they don't have armor
be careful sneak should i sneak you
think they won't notice me
i'm not sure about that
if i had an arrow now i could snipe the
leader
king is at the top you mean at
like hanging there right now about to be
burnt or somewhere else
of confidence
hey
how i'm
probably gonna see me like immediately
oh god
it's gonna be okay oh wait i have oh
yeah yeah i can uh someone here
all right
no problem then let's go
let's [\h__\h] go
oh
i forgot how to fight
let the dogs do the groundwork
i learned
[Music]
what ah
why i went because
um
i wanted to be useful
i don't how long do i have to wait for
that [\h__\h]
there you go
go go
go go well we found a nice uh thing to
do today and that is past time
until we fight mortgage
margin yeah yeah
jumping oh yeah i know it makes it
stronger
all right
um
let's see what the dog's gonna do
no you're not gonna go
okay i'm gonna kill that guy and i'm
gonna walk back a few steps
okay
oh oh you're not dead
right now you are
okay
okay we can do this we can do this and
get my body while i'm at it
easy easy
no no no no
no
no no
right when i die
okay that's exp i'm not never gonna get
back probably
why you gotta be like that
why isn't she healing
me
why are you here
i can't do five million things at once
okay
me give me a moment to assess the
situation
hmm
back to the tub
try number three
this one's gonna be it
wolfie
now my body is at least kinda easy to
get
okay
[Music]
no the boss is still chilling
okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay
oh yeah they're still so vibing i could
attack him from behind thankfully well
now i got the boss's attention
oh
[Music]
wait one two three four
five
um there's a lot
i feel like one joint from behind but a
few others were still busy behind i
don't know if it's worth it trying to
kill everyone
in the back
before
going into the middle
jellyfish nah i think the doggos are
more helpful here because it's like one
versus million people
luring one by one
that doesn't exactly work because once i
attack one of them at least two other
people joined in
in the fight not everyone yes but
um
[Music]
i mean someone i think someone in the
chat said i don't even have to
just run
yeah
no i want i want to kill these people
it's not impossible it's not impossible
it's not
impossible nothing's impossible
oh
how nice that the dogs are not attacking
yet
what is that over there is that the boss
or is that the king
oh oh they're going at him
okay well as long as you don't
start a fight with the oh okay
didn't even get myself killed
oh
what was that
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] oh the dogs okay
well this is [\h__\h] this is [\h__\h] this
is [\h__\h]
i'm gonna die i'm gonna die i'm gonna
100 die
out i was about to heal
what
run to the elevator i don't wanna just
pass this
and stop if i keep on passing by
everything i'm gonna end up like last
time we're gonna
end up at the boss and then we're gonna
be under leveled just like with marjit
it's gonna be the same thing repeating
history
just because everything else was so
scary and we're missing all the exp
hmm
we're not gonna do that again
i know i won't can can i craft the
arranged weapon with what i have i have
a crafting kit
you know
i need recipes for that
i don't think
i have i have um
darts
oh i can i can make darts
what is that fireplug fro enemies to
inflict fire damage hmm
that's
but does this make
five okay i can make two so ten
okay and then i put them i also have a
cookie cook grease
still
pots are nice too
uh
wait how
here
bolts
oh no wait how
no
i don't have to put them down here
uh-huh
how about this
or or place them up here is that not
better
now we have them
like this okay
i don't know how they work
i have never tried using them before
waiting one on time with the darts okay
so for example
and do i have to aim
no
but it also didn't hit
attack wolf's attack
easy
the others didn't notice today good
interesting
interesting now let's try this one
okay come on here come on here
don't go too fast yeah yeah come here
come here
i like this way
it's fine
yeah this is how we're going to do it
this is how we're going to do it
[Music]
come
okay i threw one at him out because oh
yeah yeah not one now i wanted to heal
damn it
uh
i don't want to push anything
accidentally like this okay
the
the cook crease we have both of them
well let's use more bone dyes
yes
turn on hud how
it's turned on now but it always
disappears
i don't know why
okay
you can buy a ball from the merchant
we'll
perhaps do next time
oh
interesting we got the one in the back
we're piling up the enemies here
there's a button to toggle hud oh i
don't know i don't know where let's get
this one
come here
doggo versus dogo
it's a doggy dog world as we all know
okay there's not much left not much left
how about you
last bone dart
and i missed
wonderful
oh that does nice damage
beautiful beautiful beautiful
and the big guy
i want
we're gonna
try to lure that uh other helper
out i suppose
now it's really manageable
okay
well there might be some wolf still
joining the battle but besides that
watch out for the dogs
they didn't really bother joining before
but
okay
i wish we can kill them now
[Music]
no no only cat food was me oh god
oh
[\h__\h] wasted
wasted my uh
cookie
also switch my weapon let's go
oh my dead body don't forget my dead
body
and now only the big boy is left and
that big boy
that one looks stronger though even
though he's sleeping he looks stronger
all right all right all right all right
let's do something
let's do some starter damage with my
last cookery
oh we can would he notice if i go
sneak up shoot him from behind i don't
know
okay
and doggo's help oh you have another
friend
[Music]
no
i worked so hard to get there
[\h__\h]
no home
wait does
when i re when i reload there that means
my items and all that are reset right i
can craft it again right
right
no
eh
but
but i can get my exp and then run
i deserve those things people where am i
gonna run there's another enemy there
like you
and should i go that way where what is
the actual right path
oh god yeah
oh hello
only one
you're not gonna kill me because i need
my body first before i get killed
blur him down you can run for gravity's
what what what what what
was
the right path is forward and then to
the right
what's the big boy at the back
okay
and go down the elevator again
why would i go down the elevator again
to uh to the block
um
[Music]
will they not join me
[Laughter]
okay
i'm scared
okay okay
why are we going this way now
wait i can't even level up like that
bye-bye
bye-bye sorry dogs
sorry
got some extra exp
this is like a horror movie
okay let me rest
i can't level up can i okay a bit bit
more i need a bit more
but uh at least now i
i'm here again
why did i why did i go here why did i
oh no
buy a bow
oh yeah
yeah i guess i could come back anytime
right
now we're gonna
if i fail again we're gonna do that
maybe but for now
let me sneak i don't want the dogs to
attack me although that one that one
that's awake
that was a jump scare
where'd that come from
nick
i mean i understand that they want to
attack me they look like they haven't
eaten for a million years
okay you're fine i can handle you
thank you
so what about this is she not gonna
attack me when i walk by
what's that helmet
oh god i feel like i could backstab him
really nicely in that position he's
sleeping
he's not worth fighting is he although
what is that over there body
is it
not worth it right
okay one right side yes
okay i didn't do that sneak attack for
some reason
okay we need to find that uh king guy
who's apparently still
somewhere in here for our side quest
oh i've heard that you can attack while
you're climbing up and down i don't know
what the buttons were
ah there it is it's just the normal
buttons
yeah yeah
mr i don't know left i didn't i kind of
didn't go on purpose
how did you
that thing drink it
oh my god
you're not that strong
[Music]
every time i drank something he had time
to hit me again
every [\h__\h] time
oh yeah i don't really use my shield
i have to get used to using my
[Music]
my experiences
i'm about as
frustrated about that as you are
take it easy
take it easy okay
i hate it that's so passive aggressive
can you walk a bit faster when i attack
you here he's just gonna
ask your friends for help
can you burn yourself if you stand in
the fire
the game has been pretty realistic so
far so i wouldn't be surprised if you
could
yeah there's new remotes
um unfortunately not the exact same ones
that we had originally
that i surprised you guys with but
original ones oh something's attacking
me
wasn't there another dog attacking me no
okay
okay let me get that item now
i have nothing to lose yeah yeah so cute
new emotes i'm at the maximum now but uh
i'm gonna try to uh smithers don't
figure out if there's any way to
get more emotes
should be impossible in theory
i want more emotes
oh yeah you have to focus on them
oh but i wasn't quite behind him
i guess
i've got the power okay here we are at
least uh when we like just sneaked by
everyone it's pretty easy to
get back here i should drink some [\h__\h]
though
they're gonna immediately attack me
i don't even remember how to use my
shirt was it l1
where is that dude that attacked me
oh how do you
how was that so difficult the first time
unbelievable
[Music]
it really wasn't
hmm
there's two
do they have wings are they like those
flying
what are they called gargoyles
gar garage
and one in the middle
uh wouldn't it be nice to have like
throwing weapons now
we don't have any more left huh
[Music]
i want to
can i like maybe craft anything else
that i can throw
what is
that finger remedy
reveals co-op and hostile sometimes um
i got canned crowns
i don't have beast bones
i can grab this but
from behind for at enemies
to flick the fire damage i guess that's
we could do that one i guess
okay and then equipment
we'll put those there okay i've never
used that one before
but
sounds useful
how far
could i do it
oh
well this one we can make a lot of them
no the other one reacted
i'm gonna die
what's that feather on my [\h__\h] it
uh
how do i even attack you when you're up
in the air
how do i there we go
come here come here come here come here
okay oh i found him
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
flying enemies never had that before oh
jump oh
that's just armor
there's like air between you see that
that's not even real people hanging
there
[Laughter]
okay where is that king
i'm scared i hope my flasks are enough
golden runs
[Laughter]
where is the king
[Music]
do i need to go that way no right there
was no
way to go there okay
okay apple don't fall here i think that
one enemy is down there now
gotta be careful
um i'm scared
something's gonna let me suddenly attack
me again
oh what is this
oh there's an item over there
what if that's worth getting hmm
or is that that's not what is that
shortcut
that's where that dude is
using the tower to the left
do you mean that one or
that one
oh well in any case any enemies left
here no
no enemies
some butterflies
what's down here don't fall
oh
oh grace i can rest here but how do i
get back up if i go down there
is there
is there a ladder
i don't see a ladder
maybe
maybe you gotta go through
don't go don't go it's a one-way yeah
that's so mean
you can't
that is so mean
okay we're going uh this way
what they're shooting
wait they're fighting
they're killing each other they're
killing each other guys oh
but their the enemies are probably gonna
win are these the other
the knights are probably not on my side
either
please i hope no one sees me
i'm not really good at aiming
okay am i supposed to help
vote for enemies yeah
um
they let them do their thing
i'm not gonna get that in speedo if i
don't help right
[Music]
hey sorry uh to disturb um
all right all right all right run around
and run run
oh you killed them good job what did you
whoa whoa whoa whoa i don't know who i'm
fighting anymore
i survived i survived i survived
i [\h__\h] survived
[\h__\h]
that was scary i don't have much to heal
is there like a way to heal myself
sometime soon
without it being a one-way
am i there soon
only have
one left
there's a grace
what where
oh holy grace
go up that's how is the king really oh
my god oh my god oh my god
well then we can go back to the grace
and teleport the hell out of here
don't fall down
king
yo
i have a letter from your daughter
there's a face i've not seen before i'm
a friend i'm edgar
warden at this castle that's order
you're still protecting it huh
but you can see how things have turned
out yeah the menials have all rebelled
they gave me good service also i thought
but it seems it was all an act oh foul
creatures as it said and true enough
they're foul inside and out they look
very valiant
but whatever you come here to do
i'm afraid oh i came for the letter
won't hold much longer
take this
by way of apology
why are you apologizing to me what is
that sacrificial twig
of course i'll give the letter let me
see
from marina yes thank you
i need your dad you can't die here
yet you have to go the castle should
fall
there's commander there's a grace over
there you can teleport out of here sure
the treasured sword of mourn does not
fall oh i get a sword
if you see arena do tell her uh her
father will come for a
once again oh we're going to go back in
order to get our our reward if you see
arena do you think that will come for uh
i hope you don't die
so shall we go back
sword there's so there's a sword here
that i could in theory get on myself
kill him
no
i have to kill the boss go ahead and go
fight the bus
wait what what what we could do is uh
touch the grace
and maybe that leads to the boss at
least
it's wow what is that that's a cool
place
and then we could try to um
when you say the boss are you talking
about the one that was sleeping
i just hope that the other
monsters will not attack us when we're
doing that because it's pretty close
buster the boss room what that's the bus
that's where the bus is
oh that's oh
the in the water
when did i miss the grace where the hell
was it
i'm gonna go up
there's a bus route yes yes
but that's like far away
it looks like it doesn't even have
anything to do with uh those stuff here
okay
ow
punch
when you say it's easier than market
someone said that in the chat
here
why is the bus down there how is that
even a problem for this castle
i'll level up
always have yellow fog gates
i don't see it from here but okay
they're ruined and if i kill that boss
he will be
happy and give me a sword or something
maybe
all right can i even level up
no wait i have some
have some things
yeah that won't be enough fever
will it eight hundred
one thousand five points nope i think
that's not enough
uh huh
that will be a waste if i lose that [\h__\h]
yeah
now i can lose it
game of thrones sword
wait you guys think i can kill that dude
are you sure
are you sure about that
oh
oh what the [\h__\h] is that
uh
[Music]
[Laughter]
kitty
i was basically dead
where we knew when kiana was killed
oh my god
wait that [\h__\h] is so strong
talk
come on i don't have much time please
help me with no how can i help you
you're dead you're a ghost
why am i drinking
help me i have no how how can i open the
door
meow
there's a torch i don't have a torch
not that i know of
now
okay finally
uh i'm gonna use up
my my um bottles until i'm down at the
bus this is not is this the right way
that i'm supposed to go
well
ignore the ghost okay ah man i'm sorry
for the ghost
sorry for him
yeah okay can i get my flasks back when
i'm down there
why are these why are these monsters all
given up
are they intimidated by the boss aura
oh
don't fall down don't fall down
i almost have enough for level up
yes yes okay then i suppose i can also
level up
when i'm there
okay
oh you look strong oh
oh
ah
[Music]
smoothly being smooth
all right
brb
tell tell the mobs that i'm afk
i'll be
back in a moment
another way to uh
yeah
use
i did that a second time
another way to use the afk mode
okay
let me kill them
they want to switch back to two weapons
uh
yeah i guess
yes it um make sense
well i want to learn how to use the
shield i just i just can't
i can't get used to it
yet
okay okay okay can we sneak this time
he's playing with the butterflies
or no he's not that's an illusion oh he
he sensed me
[\h__\h] i wanted to dodge at the right time
no okay this is like that's a warm up
for the bus
to hand your sword i like faster attacks
though
i know it's much stronger
[Music]
but
there's different ways to play this game
right different classes
and all that
can i
find
ah this is above that room
well it doesn't really help me going
here but but what
okay
yeah yeah
um free the sufferings suffering
monsters i'm just helping them
release them from their suffering
i don't know why they're acting like
this
you're free
you're welcome
nice movie again she keeps on coming
into my room
meow asking how i'm feeling so nice of
her
okay
let's try to use the shield sometimes
kiwama let's try
ow
ow it's gonna kill me
why
are we sure that i can kill margie today
exactly what just happened
same thing
yeah my timing was up i know
i know
oh
here's a doc oh was i able to summon
them here i didn't see
i don't think i am able to summon them
here
not that i really need them
i don't see the possibility no
okay body body first things first
how about how am i playing aggressive
[\h__\h] the timing
[Music]
okay
no no no no no no no no let me pick
why am i so bad at this
2400 exp
i can't lose this body
i'm trying to
roll when he swings but his swings are
so slow
so i roll to ellie
by the way my mom she she uh played dark
souls that's the only souls game she
played
she said that
i i asked her if she wants to play
element ring she said it's not really
her type of game
because she doesn't like she prefers
stealth games and you know what if i
have to
choose from
between
i'll probably go for my stealthy game
too
because all the dodging
and all the rolling
with with
these kind of games it's just
too
accurate
too detailed
um
okay hey i'm back again
you won't get rid of me so quickly
what
what i thought when he already notices
you
[Music]
[Applause]
yo
the screams are getting more and more
um
disturbed and
painful
and then and then how am i if i struggle
with that one how am i gonna kill that
one down there huh
[Music]
a free hit combo oh yeah i hate this
three hit combo i hate it
i'll [\h__\h] you
no one got time for you
i'm still trying to kill these you don't
even give that much exp
61.
not even worth it
or is it maybe it is
old fangs
no this is not the margin fight no no
don't you dare fall down here come on
that one is so dangerously placed
i know i expect the moves it's just not
that easy easily done
okay
[\h__\h] i couldn't do my the confidence i
wanted to do
[\h__\h]
just [\h__\h] you
it's one word no two words [\h__\h] you
[Music]
i can't
i hate this
[Music]
i'm just gonna ignore the mobs now
she's gonna ignore her down
just gonna ignore them all
can't be that
okay that's actually not that difficult
to do
why did you get invincible frames there
[Music]
oh
didn't even drop me [\h__\h]
leave me alone where am i supposed to go
where does it continue
we did it we have to go up and then down
yo i don't want to lose my 3000 xp
where is the grace
what's up
there what's up dog
what's up coronet
thank you i finally did it hallelujah
oh it's a chest
oh treasure chest
twin blade talisman
ooh twin blades
i've heard of them
and then down again there's no way to go
up now okay
twin white i teleport back to the grace
eh
why oh too i
should but then and don't i have to pass
this do it again or what's he optional
put it on
i'll go back to the grace
i'm like this in the lake
you can jump down okay well then let's
um teleport
back
behind the castle
level up
there he was optional okay but he gave
us a cool twin blade
so i want to thank him for that
uh level up
strength
again because we need that shield
one more then we can carry that shield
apparently and you guys say equip that
tallest one where is that i don't know
what is that starting like shards
oh
wait wouldn't that be over equipment
right here
equipment yeah
here ah here
oh that that's where you also put this
will be lost on death in place of runes
ah one time only aha
okay but nah not now enhance this final
hit of chain attacks
oh i thought it would make me able to
wear twin blades and to begin with but
no that has nothing to do with that
enhances final hit of chain attacks
i don't know but am i not like really
heavily loaded right now will it help if
i
question is also how am i gonna fight
the boss am i even gonna use my shield
i feel like i'm not gonna
try using the shield so i should maybe
unequip and now i'm not in the red
anymore i'm like much wait no that was
not had nothing to do with that maybe
but med medlo before that i was
what i wanna be i want to weigh less
how how low does it have to be to have a
a quick roll
you can unequip this too though right
not
still says med i just have to be light i
suppose
just not heavy
oh okay
and i mean
i guess that is pretty fast okay
so now we just jump down there
that looks like it
wow
wow it's really here is that safe
yeah
take off the end equip okay
[Music]
no not there okay further along
okay so we go here again
we'll go here oh
[\h__\h]
again
and then maybe from here
so wait to jump down here
oh no maybe from the bridge
i hear boss music
from the bridge okay i suppose here ah
okay
ow
i hear sparkles
uh
oh
up here okay
where's that oh
wait for me
[Music]
ah
tarnished golden sunflower
yeah the beetle
reminds me of those um
what was it golden something something
bunnies or what was it in in breath of
the wild that gave you all that money
the money bunnies
wasn't really is it really bunnies
i'm not gonna chase it
no
uh
here
and then down that hole
raise up
huh
carefully
oh god eh
are there enemies down there
slipping stone
rat spill be careful they're interested
wait wait wait wait i wish i wish i had
something to throw at them
[\h__\h]
um
okay
[Music]
[\h__\h] rats
stupid [\h__\h] rats
i'm panicking it's okay
man why is that [\h__\h] boss so far away
why could it not be in the castle why
are you gonna be so far away
yo oh [\h__\h]
oh oh that's okay
that's okay
up your
oh no i i got rid of it because i wanted
to use two swords
forgot that
my instinct just never uses the stupid
phone
i'm not gonna run after you again
not again
just gonna
just gonna throw yourself off the cliff
leave me behind
no no
not again oh now i can't uh harvest that
body anymore
now
i need to harvest my own body
oh
you want to come out and play oh you
can't oh
well you can okay
those are some fat rats man
what did they eat other rats are the fat
rats
ow wait
wait where's my flask what the [\h__\h]
okay okay okay where is that
grace it is
there it is
finally
finally oh wait i should uh
rest
i know i know elwyn now
no
i know
because
i killed boss
i don't believe
in myself right now but wait there's
even more what are those jellyfish
let me just go straight to the balls
please uh
oh
i don't have to fight this one right i
can just jump down
if they're friendly okay i'm not gonna
bother with this [\h__\h] again
it's the same as before
fine i'm coming jellyfish
[Music]
oh
you're really friendly i should probably
still not touch you because touching
jellyfish dangerous
oh
wow
pretty
[Music]
oh
no no we're gonna do without although
this time it's not a it's not a mage
it's a
he has a lance
hmm but he will just make him stronger
so we're going to do it without without
the friend am i ruined oh
oh my runes
ah [\h__\h]
my runes
i'm gonna get my runes forgot my body
1300 is worth going back to
although if you fight if we die a lot
with the boss i have a feeling we might
lose it anyway
thank you for reminding me
okay oh never mind i wanted to pick up
the item but never mind in my mind in my
mind in my mind never mind oh
your mind
don't need it
plus boss
boss
jumping chase help me
traverse the mist
okay what are we fighting the red haired
guy leonine misbegotten
wait a minute
he's fast he's [\h__\h] fast
oh
you're saying this one is weaker than
margaret though right you said that i
believe i don't believe you
i want to believe it without gonna fill
up some water hey
that's uh
yeah he is okay
i don't even what i even get for killing
him
will the king be free
ah
we're due to summon
[Music]
he's weaker
this boss is
[Music]
more aggressive
you get a cool sword okay
i want the cool sword
oh this will take a while probably guys
this will probably take a while
for me to understand
who
some people say i sure use this dude
if he can stun
it's pretty nice but let's try a few
times without
i guess
oh god um
hmm
runes
but which which
helper should i get the jellyfish fish
or wolf whoops
woofs
wolves are more aggressive too so man we
gotta use aggression versus versus
aggression
[Music]
you don't stand any chance against this
okay just for you just for you i'm gonna
win this fight eventually
just to prove you wrong
all right
what's happening
i'm too good
oh he killed one of my walls
oh i ran into it
but we already
got him down like one fourth
we're not my mom just laughed in the
background i heard that i heard that she
was like
and i said one fourth one fourth is a
lot
yeah are you watching on the tv mommy
no she's cleaning so i think
i i heard that her
giggling
giggling at my suffering
kusa
snickering
i'll prove you all wrong
whoops let's go
[Music]
that one's wasted
i want to be a granted tool
i want to be invincible
[Music]
hey what the [\h__\h] i thought the water
was so really shallow
what
[Laughter]
ah
[Music]
i didn't see that coming i need a mirror
on my back view
my butt need a butt mirror
why it's so shallow here i literally
went into that area like right there oh
ah oh now i see it
i can't can you not swim in this game
that's sad i wish you could learn how to
swim
i mean
okay
i'm so young
all right buddy
well i can deal with you
you're manageable
does he have like a lion face that's why
his name is leonine
yeah easy easy
this is
[Music]
easy oh easy
boy
easy though
oh he killed my friend now it's not so
easy anymore
oh i feel like because his moves are not
so slow i almost feel like they're
easier to dodge
do you understand my logic here what i'm
saying
forget me
yeah
this slow moves throw me off so much
with margin even though it's like i know
even when i fight him 50 times
even then
we got him to what half a bit a bit more
than a bit less
bit he was a bit more below half i think
i didn't look so closely i can't focus
but after the wolves i need to be more
careful obviously um
when the wolves are still alive i need
to be
100 percent
focused
as well
to kill him
my focus is
[Music]
these attacks keep on being disrupted by
us
as fast as him
wait oh the wall's still alive and
oh wait wait wait
wait a minute
[Music]
[Applause]
wait that only took me like below 10
tries
oh
nice
nice is that can i even carry that sword
thank you oh finally something good
happening i feel like i had less trouble
with that enemy than that one
low bump
oh up there
it's the froze
i got the game of thrones sword
wait i don't i'm so
why can't i carry it
a game of front start oh not yet
strength 40 i need quite a few levels
for that oh but like is it because
there's so many swords on the sword
because i don't remember a sword in the
series looking like that but i guess it
looks like the
looks like the throne i want to carry it
but i can at least look at it i can
carry and look it
wow
yeah yeah is that a piece of the throne
of the game of thrones throne
is that what is i mean is that on
purpose you guys think that's on purpose
like a reference
wow
i'm styling
i'm styling how do i uh two-hand the
weapon again oh
yeah
probably yeah
that's so cool
will that boss ever come back like when
you kill a boss once they don't come
back right different from the other mobs
i know he helped to ride the game yeah
and triangle
ro1 okay
wow
what what what where did those blood
splatters come from
oh is that from the fight that this
happened okay
i want to be strong enough to use it
oh
oh oh that's a
parrying
hey
posing
[Laughter]
nice
i already touched the grace um okay but
we can't really use this weapon
i don't i don't quite understand what
they mean with i can't use it properly
but
if they say that then it's probably true
oh wait what
did we always have this one
when did we get this one
is this the knights
uh
sword
the the the the um
the king's sword
or did i from chest
when did i get this one the king gave
the king gave this to me
from the cap
yes oh really but it's also
two
i have 13 strengths this needs 16 uh-huh
uh-huh okay we're still gonna use our
shitty weapons still
huh my dear turtle shield i'll be there
soon
okay
soon tm so what now we gotta go back to
the king
or
or do i go
will the king
say anything but
i can two had that one oh
oh marge next
ah
what i use l1 shut up
oh level up oh yeah
forgot
go back to the king go back to the king
and then his daughter okay
um
strength 14.
well 14 i think the sword needed 14.
uh do i have
any more
experience fingers no
shield
wait that was for the shield
really it was 14.
oh
this one needs 16 okay 16 14
19 15
but
what would you look at that
wait that's that wrong
but how slow am i now though still meant
okay oh wow apparently this is a really
really strong shield
apparently
hey
hey hi you can't touch me no no no no no
okay
[Music]
why is it strong i don't know because
the stats are good
i don't know if i really want to go
immediately for market already um i want
to get some
more exp
is this the the low bulb area that you
guys talked about this this place or
in this area
i can't visit oh yeah forgot
wait which one is the right
one behind the castle
but i thought i couldn't go back up
anymore
man can't go
do i have to go from like the beginning
that area is nearby
okay
oops
i have to go to start
does margaret and the stream well let me
just i planned it for the end i don't
want to just go immediately back to him
we're just going to be frustrated again
i want to do as much as i can before
going there
and yeah
and then now we'll kill morgan even
though there was a time where i got
really close to killing him when he had
like two percent
uh left
still
um i don't want to waste too much time
with retrying him again and again today
i want to
make sure i'm prepared well
i know that area is fine to the west
um
yeah i will go to the daughter of course
okay we gotta sneak again snake snake
snake snake snake snake snake snake
snake snake snakes
use l2 shield
yes
i know that's how you block
small small turtle shield i'm a turtle i
actually i talked a little bit with my
mom about something i was
thinking about doing i have this um you
don't have a tv in my my bedroom
but
i don't
okay okay i don't have a tv in my living
room because i just i always watch tv in
my bedroom
you know
just doesn't seem
it doesn't feel like i need
one
in my living room so but i still have
like this this big
sideboard that where
that could
that could fit
uh
i could fix tv nicely and i was thinking
what else to put up there instead
and i was thinking a little bit that the
aquarium would look so cool up there
and also because it would fit the rest
of my furniture because aquariums tend
to look kind of greenish
with the plants
and the
end of um
and the water and i thought wait there's
gonna be an annoying fight now again
let's see if i've learned from my
mistakes
okay whatever i wanted to use the shield
but i'm too stupid to do it yet um
um yeah uh
and it would be uh
it would be probably cool for
the kids the children
the the kitty cats as well
you know
um but
then i was a bit worried that maybe uh
maybe
an aquarium is a bit too high level to
for me maybe too much work you know oh
now they're all coming
wait drink
non-free
[Music]
wait wait drink that [\h__\h]
what is that attack
okay get them down bastards
where are you
this is so [\h__\h] mad
yeah so
yeah i don't know and then it feels like
a lot of maintenance would be necessary
so i thought how about instead of an
aquarium a terrarium would be nice too
and then my mom told me there's actually
like an in-between thing um
and i could have um turtles and i also
wanted frogs so i thought how about a
frog turtle
rock turtle aquarium terrarium thing
mm-hmm rather than having uh fishies
turtles would be so cute imagine little
baby turtles
little baby turtles and frogs i like
frogs you know i have a special
connection with frogs i gotta fight all
these folklories again
or they they're
fighting actually each other again doing
most of the work for me
ask i'm about it yeah yeah i know i'm
gonna know some stuff about that
surely
how the [\h__\h] do i only have one
left
ah
oh
[Music]
i
hate this
i hate this it's so unnecessary
[Music]
oh stop and
why do i have to go so far
why why why why why why why why why
why why why
[Music]
try to get used to it okay
can't change my habits immediately
next word that's going on the ng list is
shield use your shield
nothing i'm trying to do huh
[Music]
i'll leave you alive if you're nice to
me
i'll be nice to you
you could i could give you those
butterflies
with how skinny you are i feel like even
a butterfly could be good for you
probably has some protein right
bugs are bugs are very healthy
apparently
like a butterfly
could
i thought i wasn't being noticed
i was wrong slimy and satisfying slimy
butterflies are slimy
hello it's you again
i know this area too well by now
[Music]
imagine
some butterflies can be poisoned
that must be like really really rare
though
uh
better to drink
sometimes i [\h__\h] up
so unnecessarily
put out the fire
i know you could do that
oh
okay now the flying beasts
come on come on i'm here
i'm here
let's see if i can
quickly
[Music]
i don't see you
ah
oh oh i'll get up get up
[Music]
oh i hate you guys so much
at once is just not nice
it's just not nice
[Music]
short bow
i got a ball i got a bow
but when i carry it i will be much
heavier now
oh
so how do i equip the bowl
what was that
i got a bowl can i carry it no of course
not i need strength 16 and it would make
me heavy load okay well then for now i
can't even use it
soon one day
but then i don't have to buy it anymore
anyway i didn't get you guys opinion
what do you think about me getting frogs
and uh
frogs and turtles
kinda want more pets but i feel like
getting more cats would just um
oh thank you ask for my cats to be
jealous but i don't think they would be
jealous if i got frogs and turtles
go ahead
you can two hand the ball
yeah i know
i know you have like a sniper mode then
here it says to equip a ball to fire
arrows you can equip two up to two types
of arrows to choose from at once when
wielding a bow with two hands hold l1
for precision aiming use r to adjust
your aim ah one fire error type one r25
arrow type two l1 precision aiming okay
good idea turtles are somewhat high
maintenance really
but they live for so many many years
why are they so high maintenance
oh you automatically turn on the ball so
you can use it huh
oh wait wait wait no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no
uh but but now i'm heavy load now that's
the problem
um
oh they're coming for me wait uh
oh
wait
[Applause]
[Music]
[\h__\h] ball right now
i should never
[\h__\h] that king man [\h__\h] that [\h__\h]
king
no
[\h__\h] that [\h__\h] king what will he give
me when i talk to him tell me please is
it worth it
what will he give me
[\h__\h] i hate the [\h__\h] mouth i hate
everything
and everything
[Music]
well
pick up the seconds right now
walk past them um
i don't know sometimes they don't go for
me we can't can't go
not worth it
nothing nothing gratitude
he's
his gratitude
okay i'll try one more time to run past
him
he really only gives me gratitude
oh my god wait not bolts i need arrows i
don't even have arrows right now
i know i do i put them there okay
aha
how
how to use chocomate
it continues the plot
um
complete the class
why is he going to make it so difficult
to go back to him huh
kill him for x
is he an actual killable npc
we can't do that
we just basically
killed the big boss in order to protect
him why would we kill him it's not even
logical
so
um
what how do you
i still have the sword in my hand what
do you mean i automatically
someone said i can still use the bow
[Music]
oh
oh oh oh
like really
am i two handing it now
damn oh man that's kind of
rough
what
why have arrows why do you act like i
have no arrows
what is this problem oh there everyone's
there what do you mean
you have to put them somewhere else like
here
there's arrows great era it's already
too big
wrong arrows uh huh
okay
well
and then in that case so
stick
i'm gonna try to run past the enemies
this time
oh dogo did you see me
did you see me
[Music]
like you saw me
you definitely saw me
i come faster
craft
and the legendary grades i already have
some i already got some kind of great
sword
i'm i'm happy now don't need any more
great swords
i didn't realize that that was happening
there
is that where
i died
look at them
look at those idiots
nice parry mm-hmm
are they already doing the groundwork
there i feel like when you see them
from far away fighting
they're not actually doing damage yet
right until you like get close enough
so if you or is it or is it not like
that because that's that's how it felt
like to me if i stay far away
then they will just
uh
fight forever basically
is that
because that's how i i'm um
seeing it but i might be wrong i'm gonna
fight this one but the other ones i'm
gonna ignore or try to
[Music]
hello but they're gonna follow me they
even have wings you'll
i don't know if i can really
can i even climb up there
safely looking ah it's not climbing it's
walking all right
[Music]
or i should try to fight these ones but
then ignore those those might be easier
to ignore because they're fighting
they don't follow you forever sprint
through okay we'll try go go
um
go okay okay
oh there's not much left here
there's really not much left
damn
all the action happened without me even
if i wanted to fight them again
all right king it took me about a
million times to get back to you i mean
you're dead
yes keeping the sword from those foreign
creatures which sword you're not gonna
take my game of front sword are you
once i've rescued arena i will spend my
remaining days with her oh you'll go to
erina
thanks to you
i will be reuniting with you hey did i
just get the xp from over there
gentle nature though
i only hope it remains intact xp let's
go thanks dude
all right so goodbye thanks
look at all these feathers he has in his
body it's like minecraft
look at him
he looks like a bird he's becoming a
bird this is a ritual of turning a human
into a bird you see it live here now
oh that poor guy
you can't even reach the bird or
whatever that is
this is riveting
who should we help oh damn nice you
downed him
okay
beautiful
now
now we have the good ending this is the
good ending
a little bit of revenge i would like to
a teleport
i can't use it
why why
why
why why can't i not use it
why why why why why why why why why why
why why why why you can't use it
i want to teleport i can't use it
if i talk to you
thanks to you and devote my remaining am
i
out of combat no
sneak
wait a bit
stand still okay shhh
i'm not in combat game
i'm not in combat
is it because those birds over there are
so mad
i'm mad too
[Music]
really
oh no
i guess i can
run past what was it again
i gotta jump left somewhere oh did you
see me guys
shoot me
shoot me oh you're out of arrows
i'm gonna kill you
where is your friend
where'd your friend go
you stuck or what
he's [\h__\h] stuck
okay where was that i think you gotta go
up here
jump that well
yeah there's no there's a grace here but
i think you're gonna go up first and
then down
here
that's it okay now the arena
who would have thought that getting uh
this turtle shield
would lead us to this beautiful side
quest do i have enough to level up now
mm-hmm
finally irina was
was she here or here no no no she was
here
i think
yeah but we got a really great sword for
the future
once we're able to use it i don't know
that she's not here she's even further
behind
hello to you by the way oh wait you're
one of those
merchants
maybe i can get proper arrows from you
um
so not the great errors normal arrows
huh
wait i'm getting two arrows only for 40.
then i can't i can't use that because
money and exp is the same right
i don't want it now
maybe another time
leveling is uh more important now and
for margin i don't need i don't need
can craft them let's see what do you
need
oh
well
i don't have a recipe for it do i
um
i think arena was here
i don't have
crafting
do i need to buy it at the church
arena
[Music]
santa has it okay
what do we know
do we know
no
[Music]
brina
how could this be
my daughter deserved better no
who fought life
with me
i chose duty over my daughter's safety
and
that is how faith has answered sir
no
she's dead i see that
i'll find them
the foul wretched responsible for this
i'll hunt them down and exterminate
every last one of them
rest assured
arena how do you know who it was
what would have happened if i went to
arena first i guess it wouldn't have
been completed properly because you're
going to go to the king first in order
to continue the quest the foul wretch is
responsible for this or i wonder i
wonder because we could have already got
gone to arena cause we delivered the
letter and he didn't necessarily ask us
to
arena
[Music]
wait what
what just
you guys what did i step on
i'll find them okay
sorry when did i stop
one of them
what did i step on okay where are we
gonna go guys where are we gonna go
should i go here
where are we going
i fell on him what did i do
uh uh i don't want to go the other way
bridge of sacrifice
how
about uh i go um
wait that's the wrong way anyway try to
find caves
margaritas you
invited can i like go up here please
what's the right path here
yeah
even those runes
what a church
i guess you gotta go through here
keep exploring great loot there
i want to fight frank oh i know there's
a dragon reachable
i know
but ha ha
oh that big guy again oh yeah
i guess i could try to fight him too
he has a lot of like little doggos
though
can't imagine him being stronger than
what we already fought
right
shall we try
are you gonna attack me too
fight him loot the wagon
let's fight him first oh
wait what
goggles you take care of him or me oh i
didn't i did not you just stay healthy
enough to kill the others
yeah yeah okay
um
we're gonna fight with the big man
hello
hello he doesn't even react
why
he does not react at all
okay you gotta like activate him he has
a button on his butt
wow
there's a lot of these mobs uh out there
in this world right
i
get him
he's almost dead
he barely did any damage to us at all
easy now i'm not scared of them anymore
not scared of destroying me anymore
because we killed him once
what about you you're not are you happy
that oh you're gonna attack me anyway
that is so mean like i killed that dude
that was like probably the reason why
you were
lost here
this is how you thank me
oh another one
but now we can loot the
wagon
see what's in there
went from here no way that's the wrong
side right
morning star
oh
cool
hey
another interesting weapon
golden runes um
[Music]
these people are literally asking to be
killed
i'll do them the favor
don't kill me
do i get something extra for clearing
the whole group again
yes this is this is what did that just
refill my flasks
i think it did i think it
did okay everything's clean here
did they kill any yeah maybe they did
maybe he'll maybe the the king will
thank me again
for killing the ones who probably killed
his
daughter this is his daughter right now
his wife audio oh did you hear some
crackling sounds i was thinking the same
let me try to fix it
now it could be fixed but
right now i don't hear it anyway
i forgot to loot something here
this margaret did no but we killed
another boss we killed like a lion
lion guy with the game of thrones sword
which was absolutely perfect because i
love game of thrones
i feel like i'm much stronger now than
last time
okay and next where we go next
don't forget to heal oh yeah
oh yeah
sometimes sometimes i just forget time
to upgrade this okay i never did that
before
bananas
huh
no no no no no no no no breakfast
breakfast banana mama wanted me to eat
banana
oh i'm already strong enough thanks to
chicken nuggets
chicken nuggets gave me the power
to believe
i think my wolf just left
uh
try the morning star use the mornings if
you can
[Music]
with the shield i guess it's a
one hand weapon
um
are we safe here
can i use it i can't use it
oh
yeah
we can try it
it's stronger right
not not much uh option here to try it
out with
i feel
a little bit slower
oh my god
i'm gonna get that back
i'm gonna get my body back buddy it has
bleed oh
that's where all the blood was there
oh
i know that if you get someone to bleed
a lot then um it does a lot of damage
that sounds very useful
all right give me my body back body back
while you're back you need my body back
body bag body bag
oh
the boy is back
just passing through don't mind me
what can you do with the ruin fragments
i guess it's just for crafting
bleed is let a bar when
uh
please where you probably need to attack
a lot to stack it
i've heard i've heard so i've heard
lead is a bar buildup that does
percentage damage once more
compared i've heard am i going the right
way
not quite what is your house there i
don't know
bobby first
uh
yeah we'll definitely operate the weapon
before i
go
to market margin
definitely do that
oh by the way guys i'm planning on
starting uh where's my body
i hear oh thank you planning on starting
yakuza
this
this week and the coming week but also
there won't be
um i think i think i won't be doing a
schedule there's grace
i won't be doing a schedule for the
coming week
because um
[Music]
not gonna be streaming much next week
and you know
for for some reasons
that i don't want to stay
i think it's better to not publish a
schedule so you don't
yeah
but but don't worry if the the there
will be some streams and there are gonna
be long streams and there's gonna be vr
with ama yes yes i'm gonna teach her a
dance um i originally wanted to teach
her dreaming choo choo
but
i figured
yeah i'm gonna teach you a different one
because
dreaming to do
the song
can't be monetized so
so
uh i'm gonna teach you oh my god
something that can be monetized are you
like a boss here
okay let's see let's test out
my
morning star
oh
you go fast too like the lion i like
that
oh and it keeps on interrupting him nice
whoa whoa wait i think i got to oh oh i
died but i see it okay wait that was uh
was he bleeding already or did that mean
the bar needed to be full right
the bar needed to be full i suppose
give me my body back
oh wait i should i had so much exp i
should uh
level up again i think i had enough for
a level up again
i understand hope everything is okay
everything's super okay i'm like super
excited actually about something that i
wrote on twitter and you actually
misunderstood me guys you thought i was
excited about the vr thing i am excited
about the vr thing too
um but but but but but
that is
not the only thing and not even the main
thing
jump heavy attacks i will try i will no
try okay okay
uh oops uh
let me level up first and then kill that
dude
he'll explode the blood oh exciting
exciting what should we do now still
strength or maybe another bigger because
now we can carry the
the shield we don't need that much
strength immediately anymore
um
[Music]
whatever it is let's get hyped i'm so
hyped i'm so hyped about it
more chicken nuggets
[Music]
not quite
strength bigger
yeah also one bigger
hmm this will be wait i'm level 19 now
this will be a big difference what level
was i when i first tried margin level
six or something like that
big difference
hopefully
enough to do the trick
can i surprise him
endurance for more green bars
nine ten nine
yeah something like that under ten
ah
can't
oh wait i already got it
oh okay that was a bad timing to do that
wait did i go okay
wait i'm still alive no
the bar confused me
okay okay okay okay okay some mistakes
have been made wait that's my blonde
oh he has bleeding too
wait
that was my blood
oh
oh but but
but i'm inflicting bleeding too right
okay okay
right yeah okay
dodged that nicely good morning sunshine
oh [\h__\h]
oh
i'm gonna roll down man
almost almost
okay
we didn't get him to bleed i think but
that's okay
but how much the xp did you give
not that much
i thought you would give me more oh if
you just do a yay pose oh i did i'm a
girl i'm a good girl character
where am i going right now
okay that's where i wanted to go
[Music]
oh yeah there's not gonna be schedule
but i think i should tell you when the
vr chat cloud is happening on
tuesday um
12 noon time pst
uh my time gmt plus one nine pm
write it down write it down write it
down
might be on ami's schedule what are you
what are you what are you
are you difficult
oh no you're not
out
okay
oh interesting looking enemy though
writing it down okay okay
okay
i guess it's a
what did i say i didn't say
2 p.m cst
i don't know it's a pst
12 p.m
like noontime
there's a there's a floaty thing right
there
wonderful dough
hello
oh that was an easy free hit yo nice
feels good it's good
3 p.m est
yeah we're gonna use the models from the
music video
we got them ready to be used for
vr chat and you can see like movements
much more like body movements
so i really appreciate that
like with the wolfy models because
they're so small it's like really hard
to see
um body movements like exact movements
it's just everything is still
scrunched together
but um amma showed me a little test
yesterday and it looked great
it looked very good
at least for
like you know
[Music]
considering it's vr and not like like a
proper tracking bodysuit just vr
stuff like the belt and the
shoe thing is
margaret must be so afraid margaret yeah
let's call her margaret
[Laughter]
what's over there is there something
interesting there
something must be there
yeah i i know which song i'm gonna teach
it's like an anime song that you all
know
but i
i kind of know the choreography but i
gotta gotta relearn it again i just know
it roughly because i
um
saw the dance a million times
i need to relearn it quickly
to be able to teach other properly
i'm excited she said she's a bit worried
about it um
she doesn't have much experience dancing
but it's done i think she can do it with
my help
i'll try to teach her as best as i can i
mean being in the same room
would obviously be easier
but
this is fine too what are you
examining
oh guidance gatekeeper for those
returning to the roots
what does that mean
[Music]
oh it's not hard to hide in you guy
i i know that dance too but i asked her
and she said she already kind of knows
how to hurt you guys so i said okay i'm
not gonna teach you that one
leads to a dungeon
what's your dungeon
that was i guess so it leads to the tree
kind of
the trees really sus and one of those
like chickens
what are those
oh wait those are trees
oh they look like chickens standing
around the tree
oh thank you thank you i'm glad you like
my um
elden ring play through even them [\h__\h]
at it
thank you
choreography instructor
it's like one of my
few skills that i have dancing so i want
to make use of it and i wanted to use
the vr models because we got them made
i got them made just for the music video
but it would be such a waste to just use
it for the music video and for nothing
else so turtle so cute can i take you
with me to my apartment and put you in
my terrarium huh
are you cute
cute little turtles oh my god i'm really
excited about the thought of getting
turtles now
it's fun to watch someone learn
you mean me with eleanor ring
it will hopefully also be fun for you
guys to see how uh amma learns a dance
that's a dog that's not a dog that's a
turtle
what
you guys are saying that so seriously
what the [\h__\h] is that it looks like wait
i mean no surprise considering the
people working on this game well that
looks like a straight out of ghibli
ghibli sorry german the german-ness
inside of me makes me want to say ghibli
that's like the like house moving castle
are they supposed to touch these things
no
oh [\h__\h] rest
it says souls aha
oh
what are you protecting or eating oh
uh i want to find the
uh grace i haven't seen one in a while
and what else oh
that's not a grace
what are those enemies what the [\h__\h] is
this
what is this enemy
such a weird enemy
pick it up pick it up
bowling ball
warms
can't even catch you from here
okay i'm gonna ignore you guys because
you're weird
boss fight
onyx oh
yeah
it's like onyx
did i
is that church
starting because i
oh [\h__\h] what
did i activate that because i
killed one of those
oh hello
it's moving it's literally moving
it's the moving castle
and these are protecting him
oh there's a big bell down there
can i
is that a boss monster
that's like so big it looks like it's
just terrain not a monster they have no
head
oh it's going back so they're following
him back
why are you separated
ring the bell
it's fascinating i don't think i should
be here
it doesn't attack
no way
no
how much 915 i have to lose okay
it doesn't have a health bar
so it's not really an enemy it is really
more just like terrain
is it going back now
just don't get stepped aha okay
hi meow indeed
wow
i wanna find the
holding race man
but
it's so cute it's like a turtle
everything's a turtle now
oh oh
it's just the fact that i can um get my
wolf's hair
is
very says
my wolf's in my jellyfish
there's a church nearby oh there's uh
there's houses hi
wow
there's a lot of stuff you play grace by
the church which church
is that the church
which bane ruins
tom's void ruins
what is the church
is that tall thing over there at church
up north
uh
right now
i just saw it
oh that house down there
no
race at the houses
go to the house okay
i don't i see it i think i see it
okay
sorry for destroying your fence
hatch
no
we found a grace
[Music]
hello
isolated merchants check
check well cute
there's been an age since i've seen a
customer really
how can i help here at the end of the
earth oh the end of the earth is at the
end of the map
purchase
they do they sometimes have different
stuff
he has a sacrificial twig
no it's walking mouth so lamb the thing
over there
note imparting knowledge in brief right
i kind of want to see what it says but
it's probably just like a
info on
like a lore
buy cookbooks you have cookbooks it
doesn't have [\h__\h]
it has uh the notes though
buy a lantern it's too expensive
it's important info
actually useful
maybe i can sell him something though
uh
okay let's take a look inventory
um
where would it be
to stop the mausoleum stride you'll need
to clean up around its feet first uh-huh
it's a hint and then it sits down
then it will sit down and chill
we need to clean up so i guess
those headless warriors around it
we now have something to do guys
we found something to do
all right we have a new mission
no not them the barnacles
oh that's what was going on
what exactly am i cleaning what is
barnacles what does that even mean
what am i
something didn't go away when i hit
the leg over there
i'll
you guys always say step on me mommy but
you don't want to be stepped on by that
thing
get it
can i attack while jumping
kind of
too slow
[Music]
don't have anything to shoot with
probably this mountain
maybe that one
this mountain would make it easier maybe
let's do the others first
i can't run away as fast without a horse
okay
he steps in the other direction i'll
save save
wow
i'm guessing immediate death if
i get stomped on
clean that stuff clean it all nicely
i think this leg is almost done it just
has one high spot
can i precisely attack like the bottom
for example
hey hey that was an unexpected movement
can you not move your legs so much
please
oh my god oh my what what's happening
wait oh are you telling me that was
enough i didn't have to do it all
it's doing
it's doing a set
ah
it was like if i fix i sits
oh the mobs are disappearing is it
because it sat down
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah
is there a dungeon inside
i'm just uh
reward
it's clean
reminds me a little bit of that super
mario sunshine um quest quest where you
clean the teeth from that monster in the
water where you have to dive
it's just a printer inside excuse me a
printer
oh
nice chandelier
a printer
what it duplicates bustles
what does that
mean remembrance duplication menu with
the remembrance duplication menu you can
duplicate remembrances you previously
cry what does that mean
this includes remembrances from which
you've already drawn on power and
duplication can only be performed once
per month with liam what does that mean
i can't even
get bosses back or pretty print
okay but still cool we got a little
secret
fun
just a printer man
i have to kill a big boss first eh
that was big boss when i killed there to
lean the lion man
[Music]
don't put down my accomplishments like
that
deal boss traps
oh you can duplicate the loot
bar says that you can get weapons spells
oh
okay
so okay mar margaret is supposed to be a
big boss
okay
um what do you guys recommend me to do
right now i don't want to go to
mortgages yet
[Music]
marker
this one
margaret is not a big boss
uh go to church church church church
church church or church which i i still
don't know which one is the church maybe
that tower thing up there
i'll go check it out
no of course that north
that is kind of north
wait they're still here
[Music]
weirdos
okay
the weapon is
a little bit slow so i need to kind of
like
push the button earlier
to anticipate when i'll be reaching the
enemy
uh wait where are you
what did i kill him
oh
lord one straight sword what
sounds cool
why can't you do that that's fancy i
want to learn how to do that
there we go
drop i'm lucky my drop luck
well this doesn't look like this is the
ruins no this is something else
it's not the church that's not george
church wouldn't be protected by these
idiots would it be
i want to fight you
off of my horse okay
all right you sure shield i shield
out
you're using foul tricks i tell you that
yeah
yeah baby
oh
group was cleared and i got some bolts
okay both are for um
not for the ball but for the other wait
what is a church it's beautiful
wow
a ruin of a church oh
we found another church
okay
golden rune all right maybe um how much
do we have after using all my runes
oh i have quite a a lot
yes four of them
uh 1 400
plus
another one
it's deadbeat well you're very valuable
to me
1850. was that enough
how much do we need now 2 600. damn
okay we're far from that
what's this
sacred tear
thank you don't cry so much man don't
cry
you're beautiful you don't need to cry
um what is the sacred theory
and flask upgrade oh can i do that
all right that charge to flush
ah golden seeds
two i have two
oh oh no i don't have two
uh increase amount replenish by flats
how about that
ah
that's what the sacred tier is for
yes
okay oh you increase the amount of all
of them cool
okay so i have still six but they're
stronger now yeah i've noticed that they
don't fill up all of my hp anymore so
important
okay what else can i do ah i want to
upgrade my weapon now
uh do i need to go to the other church
for that because they had like a
smithing table
and i guess after that because already
three and a half hours um i was thinking
like four to five hours gameplay today
after that maybe we go to market
church santa church a round table for
upgrades
oh
church
or son go back to center church with
santa and oh okay
why around him which one is better or is
it the same round table has smith
okay let's go to roundtable
this place right
the table of lost grace
round table hold uh where is this smith
they don't have a map in here
where is this myth
i'm gonna let you upgrade more huh is it
does anyone have a hint
round tables for upgrades past plus
three uh-huh yeah i heard that uh there
you can only do up to plus three
other side here ah you look like the guy
i'm looking for
it's a little kind of cursed but okay
for a new face
no matter
it's all the same true
damn what are you loud your arms
let's get sniffing i thought you were
human until i looked at your feet
and
what's the ashes of war anyway
i feel like the game explained it once
about the chains on your livestream tell
me you've noticed a change
nothing special
i'm a prisoner and these are my chains
oh why are you poisonous oh
i'm dying smithing for you fools
well you're not doing it voluntarily
maybe he's um manipulating our weapon
then special skill uh-huh okay we're
doing strength and armament right i
guess we're gonna
do the morning star
340 is the cost okay
uh so that goes from 118 to 124
another whole dull
should we do the morning star
i'm enjoying using it and the bleeding
could help us if we ever are able to
activate it
okay
morgan stan
another one 141
and now i can't afford more
can i sell oh you're a prisoner oh we
can talk more don't worry too much into
it
well no grudge against you okay my a
prisoner is no fault of yours true
reasonable
i don't mind smithing
despite my differences the weapons get
stronger all the same
given time
technique never fails
besides it helps me forget
the sheer terror of her
oh her
i want to talk more now he doesn't want
to talk anymore
interesting character chill dude yeah
nice dude
um
anything else actually so before i don't
know
what is this
oh
uh i don't know
uh
i don't know
i guess we're done
although maybe i can sell something and
get one more upgrade
what is not uh that valuable how much do
i need
uh
wait how am i
how do i not have enough
items i need items
a snipping stone
stop can i not buy smithing stones
does anyone sell those
uh some merchants sell them not yet
he would have way more business if he
would sell them too dude
think about your business opportunities
you're gonna make so much more money
think about it think about it
there's a mine they're in mines oh you
can kind of farm them oh hello who are
you
nice room
who are you greetings great champion
called by grace are you pretty i am fear
have compelled my stay at the round
table hold on great champion
would you allow me to hold you
hold me flee
perhaps you might share with me hold me
like on your can i get uh he's a makura
tartedness like a doing i put my head on
your lap a champion you you pat my head
i am sure
will bear a bulldozer wait did you not
mean it literally do you think vulgar
perhaps
where i come from
it is a sacred act
oh wait wait do you mean you do me you
did you do mean
not quite literally but differently
oh she means um
18 plus hug
okay
my time is still a great champion
yes yes okay no
18 minus hug
very well 18 minus hug
[Applause]
sensitive jokes
finger maidens and then his 18 plus hug
i get a health debuff
but debuff
is it debuff
what you felt light up inside you what's
the people begins blessing though it is
by the fleeting thing i am afraid come
back to me
should you require another why would i
require a debuff
as often as thank you
well how long does it go to debuff
is it something i activate or is it
happening right now you will have
manager until you use that blessing
it goes away when you use the blessing
why
um i don't understand the meaning of it
defense buff oh healthy above defense is
buffed
oh
you can use it during a battle and it
grants you r resistance to stuns and
stuff but it gives you five percent
health buff debuff until you use the
item
it gives me poise
why you get an item what
um
you give me a buff item but you get hp
to go
talk to her more
i don't want to talk to him more
i am pleased to see you again
would you like me to hold your blessings
what did she give me all these [\h__\h]
fingers
unbelievable
uses fp to temporarily boost poise
wait so right now
oh now i activated it and how do i
deactivate it
yeah just
now it's oh it's gone oh it's gone oh
okay
oh okay okay okay good good good now
let's go back
um
maybe
farm a little bit more speed for one
more level up and then go to margin
is this the exit
no i can just teleport i guess okay
uh
farm exp dogo
i don't want to go to the same place
again i want to go to a new place
i still
didn't um
see everything here but
i get it again and use it before margin
before
is that useful
the merchant in the roundhouse go east
of the map east explore east
okay
dungeon
engineer by church
the church
the latest church or the first church
you mean the dungeon where where i got
jump scared with the
[\h__\h] trolls
yeah i don't i'm not going to use it it
makes you die less really
more flask go north
of ireland bridge
for others church
another church in the south
south
in this area
i didn't see one
or you mean
here
are you staring
yes that dungeon isn't that hard you
mean the first one the like from the by
the first church
sorry a lot of uh the catacombs a lot of
input right now
the really prominent ruin on the north
point of the island
island
this island
prominent ruin we have the tom's wood
ruins what do you mean this one
that's the one thing i didn't see it or
the witch bane ruins or the unnamed one
north of the tree is church
north of that tree
a little big tree first
okay
i'm a bit confused uh not sure if we're
talking about the same thing yes yes
okay
i will go here
and then
oh it's the it's the thing that we made
sit down
can't speak english
is there no witch gonna say hello to me
here no witch at night no
all right we're gonna try to go
here i guess or here i'm not sure where
you can go
uh easier
i did i just put two oh that's confusing
let's not do that
ah over there okay
what is this place though this is so sus
here what if i step in the middle
sure something will happen
up the top of the island north
i just heard a beetle i think
and there's a wolf sun
what
think i'm hearing a beetle
whatever
dangerous place
tomes want ruins no you're not the one
i'm looking for
for circles of boss arenas
sanctuary
stone what's that
where's that
uh
where did it go
i don't know where it went i wanted to
look at it instead of always asking you
guys for the answer
you can check any ruins go ruins
but why do you guys want me to go up all
the way up there is that the church
it looks like the church
oh
oh don't mind me guys
i guess we're both heading for the
church oh ghost ghost
ghost
let me talk to you
get off of your horse
the mausoleum prowls cradling the
soulless demigod uh-huh
they're not already talkative church of
pilgrimage
touch
don't cry don't cry no more
i got your tear baby i'm i'm gonna catch
him
they're too precious
don't cry no more
now we've got the flasks and an
increased amount yes
i know what i'm doing now all right
all right
so we did that we can i guess enter a
ruin
that's a nice jellyfish right
won't hurt me
hi it's okay
iron shield
probably not as good as my turtle shield
though right
but uh i want to go into a ruin that's
not too big though
because
i don't want to spend any longer than 30
minutes in there i think
[Music]
go down the room you sell alien
trailer shield
it'll be right up there aggressive not a
hotel
okay we're gonna go
um
i guess let's go to the toms more room
wings
where is it
get some more xp i hope this one is not
as jump scary as the other one that i
entered before
go go go go go go go
always got the shiny stuff
i always get the shiny stuff
all right ah
that's what because it's ruined that's
why i can get the
mouth
my help now i'm chunky
donkey mama gonna play a little bit
longer okay
a little bit longer oh it's so dark eh
uh
don't you need a
oh no
don't you need um um a torch for that
is there is there a brighter uh ruin
around here
lantern
i don't have the lantern i don't have
money for either
lantern all the ruins are like this huh
the one
with the jump scares was brighter i
could actually see [\h__\h] there
there's no
boss by the
tree which tree
there's a lot of these shiny trees man
i mean this tree
kill him let's kill him
oh that's what yeah that's where that
thing was pointing there
all right that's my next mission we're
gonna kill that boss
i don't know if i am
too cocky now too confident
overconfident
um but i believe
how do we get up there
that box will take a while
i think so
it's pretty hard
[Music]
oh by the way my mom actually she didn't
come for this purpose but she um
uh
when she came here she brought me
some stuff for my balcony to put
oh come on
for my balcony to put um plants in but
not just plants but
like you know like actually she brought
me
some [\h__\h] for oh is that the boss
for
uh raspberries and some other
berries things
yeah for my balcony
so they're actually who's yelling
[Music]
are those people up there
still live
[Music]
[\h__\h] you
[\h__\h] you for doing that [\h__\h] you i'll
not forgive you
okay i'm getting bullied here
no no no not that easy that that [\h__\h]
is [\h__\h] you
oh that dude is almost going to see me
okay
okay now he's coming for me
[Music]
i never tried to fight one of those
bastards
okay you want to fight [\h__\h] [\h__\h] fight
me
fight me
what's this you versus me
i'm winning though
good luck buddy
oh you have your bad friends
not there
horse is down is he dead you're dead yet
no
soon
sent in
who are you charging it
and i'm having a hard time hitting you
there we go
gil with great shield oh oh
oh they're mad
they're mad now these little okay okay
okay okay we avenged those people
up there
that was not the boss that you guys
talked about though i'm pretty sure
many of you guys are so sure that now
i'm gonna take a while
and and it's too difficult for me then i
might not go there maybe i should just
um kill margin
just gonna farm some exp here
boats thanks
how about you
you want a piece of me
i'm good [\h__\h] talking them but i'm not
so good at playing the game
feel better than mine
nah no way
the one i just got stop yelling oh my
god can i help you like put you down
i want to help you great dragonfly
work with cave is a fast good boss for
you merc with cave is that like can you
see that somewhere in my mouth
oh god stop yelling
stop
i don't want to hear you guys suffer i'm
suffering myself enough in this game
[Music]
oh my god
better is relative laundry time
nah
okay
you know what [\h__\h] it
it's margin time
it's my jitter baby
there's a treasure chest in the tower oh
[Music]
[\h__\h]
if i go back now i have to um
damn it
i don't even know where it was here
where was that
ah whatever
it's march of time um but uh let me see
oh i have 1 900
no using that wouldn't be enough to
level up right
and i would probably just lose it
so i'll keep it
keep it
and wait you said you said that that uh
shield is stronger
nah that one isn't stronger elements and
stronger
i mean okay those are stronger but i'm
not strong enough for them
so right now the best i can do is that
and we're gonna
wear our
morning star plus two but i wonder
what about
maybe it's worth getting some arrows
though
how heavy would that make me if i
get my arrow too
oh yeah wait i'm not even no but you
said it's fine both hands automatically
both hands
it's got a billion
i don't think i'll have like enough time
and
oops it to like actually
take it out and then use it i feel like
i'll be too nervous and
clumsy
you won't be using arrows arrows are a
weightless errors aren't worth it okay
okay let's try it let's see let's see we
gotta
warm up again i'm gonna go without the
dude
uh
and
get my friends out
yeah i don't know i'm gonna die a lot
but
good timing
good start
oh [\h__\h] i hate that you're so slow
oh you're so [\h__\h] slow i hate that i
hate that so much
is he fit is he bleeding like i don't
know
no sorry dude sorry sorry sorry about
that
i didn't mean it like that
how's my jellyfish still alive
incredible
it's a great first try well the fact
that i'm still warming up
oh
oh jellyfish dead
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
ken hawkins in germany we say king
hawkins
all right this is not gonna work anymore
but i feel like it was good it was good
i will put my foolish ambitions to rest
after the stream is over
not before that
um but i didn't feel much stronger than
before
i felt much strong oh yeah shield i
forgot about my shield
[Laughter]
you know
when uh when an enemy is that big [\h__\h]
wrong
[\h__\h] it
when an enemy
is that big i feel like like using my
shield
um
he will just crack through it you know
what i mean
i called the wrong prince
we're just playing now because i i got
the wrong um
helpers
just playing around with him now
ow
who is very foolish of me
foolish foolish
foolish humans
what does that skill do again by the way
that my shield was doing someone
explained it in the chat but it went by
so fast i couldn't read
my mom is laughing why are you laughing
my chat goes very fast i can't help it
oh huh
my mom is laughing at my cats
wait one second
no she it was actually not reacting to
my um
to what i said she was reacting to my
cats
yes okay sorry
sorry mommy wanted to show me my cats
ah [\h__\h]
oh
i did not expect that that dodge would
work
oh
okay he's focused on me but he looks
like he's jealous now
no no no no no no no no
no
i'm not gonna waste hours and hours and
hours again on your body today no no not
today
i'll [\h__\h] i wanted to
go to the sign
he was like get out of the [\h__\h] way
wait wait wait wait wait no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no go go go wait please
ah the first one was so good actually
but we'll get there again he's poisoned
at least
[\h__\h]
i lost my focus
wait i'm already at zero flasks [\h__\h] i'm
so [\h__\h] up
yeah yeah just kill me
[Music]
okay maybe the maybe the key is to not
look at the comments
[Music]
i'll get him
sorry i just want my body
okay now we can dog
i knew that would come i knew it i kind
of knew it
[Applause]
um okay
oh
no no no foolish
did i just um
successfully perry i don't know
i am
oh
stop hurting me
okay phase two
i'll never be able to kill him
what happened
oh
i should have just waited i should have
just but i tried to dodge but i should
have just waited because he was poisoned
the poison would have killed him
i feel like i jumped i did jump right
right at him at the moment where he was
also about to attack me i think
i felt good
that did feel good
it was from the front right it was a
frontal attack not from the back
i broke his posture i want to do that
more often
jumping our i didn't do a r2
but maybe i should try more of them
all right i did do a jump attack
definitely
l1 plus r2
what
this is i don't see an
l one ah l one plus r two
wait it's just the same as without l one
what do you mean
l1 plus r2 that's the same as just r2
some
advices i don't quite understand
r2 right after blocking a hit
ah you mean
l1 not plus r2 but then r2
uh
huh
okay i can try that that's not what i
did though i was kind of asking you guys
what did i do to repeat it but
body body body body
body
no
no i do not allow that no no no no buddy
no no
i don't know i'm too slow for that i
know you're going to be fast for that
[\h__\h]
let me do it again
repeat jump attack and heavy hit him
put these foolish ambitions to rest r2
as soon as it hits r2 i am
try again i'm trying
[Music]
thank you for blocking that
uh
ah [\h__\h] wrong button again
stop killing my the previous turn here
was way more focused
on my all on me
and i had the jellyfish alive for much
longer
oh god bad run bad run
really bad run
you killed it
he's not even poisoned is it
uh
but okay let's take this as a run for
experimenting
[\h__\h] i tried
but i guess it's kind of unblockable
that
that huge jump
um
i wanna
have him focus more on me in the first
part of the fight
so that i get the jellyfish for a little
bit longer
but also not get as much damage
is that too much to ask
[Music]
i'm trying to do the thing that you guys
tell me to trust me so you can uh stop
asking me to do it
i died i see that
don't forget to jump attack that's
literally what i'm doing old time yo do
you not see me doing it i literally just
did it one second ago
i did this and then
l2 for strong luck
l2 for a strong look
where's my body
it's too um i was a bit preoccupied dude
okay this is bad bad start really bad
start bad start bad start
[Music]
i did what you did what you told me to
do just now but it doesn't seem to work
when i do it
yes i do know about summoning i don't
want to do it anymore
we tried it a lot last time
and it was not efficient
i'm gonna also stop picking up my body
[Music]
out
god
[Music]
i think
it's okay buddy it's just how a woman's
body works margaret margaret you can't
hide it no longer
i know your true
self it's okay
it's okay buddy
are you poisoned i feel like he's not
poisoned
it's okay margaret
you can't be friends
i
i made too much fun of you i understand
understand this understand
[Music]
i mean we didn't even get that far to be
honest it just felt nice because i
finally got him to bleed
sorry guys for disappointing you again
and again
again and again again and again
mmm but that wasn't
[Music]
no
i know what i just did so i want to try
it again
yo
you eat me any further and i'm flying
off the cliff man you won't want to play
around with me a bit more
[\h__\h] no that was unnecessary that drink
that sip
oh he's mad he's so mad he's like oh she
figured it out
she figured it out
[\h__\h] she figured it out
oh
i see just you and me again hmm
um don't break the healthcare no don't
break don't break
don't don't break don't break don't
break
break under the pressure
[Music]
my foolish ambitions
will never be friends
put these foolish ambitions
to rest
what if i
hmm
try
[Music]
what was it again let me do it again
yeah yeah oh i become turtle
i know this makes my
uh
thing stronger
this is still if i do this is there any
meaning behind me even putting on the
shield
if i hold it two-handed anyway
wouldn't that be faster if i take it off
i take it off
i'm turned up i want to keep it to
become turtle
just for fashion
okay for the drip okay keep it for the
drink
i agree i 100 agree with you guys i'm
glad that we have come to an
understanding for once
oh yeah go away from my body
oh we're going there okay
[Music]
i was about to heal i literally just
pressed the square the moment he hits me
and turtle
i don't really know how much more damage
i'm making because i can't pay attention
to the health bar that much
what
i know about summoning
oh you mean summon the jelly
oh later me get my body
okay okay
you did it oh
oh you didn't
meow jonkers
okay well now i don't have to pick my
body up anymore
because now there's nothing to get back
anymore
okay
he took some
he was so nice to um take some luggage
off of me
okay you go um to jelly
but we have to admit that i'm better at
dodging this guy too
better than before although this attack
will always get me
because i just can't react that fast
literally
almost dead
yeah okay for once i got a
in the right time
okay
but
jellyfish still kicking
yay
still kicking and very much poisoning
the boss thank you
wait red red white white white white do
i wait
no
no no no no
this might be the run
[\h__\h]
but we got to a good point i think
yeah i jinxed it
i might have jinxed it
yeah
i bought the flasks yeah flasks are
still looking okay um jellyfish was
never alive for that long before i think
um
yeah oh no went mostly pretty good
i think okay this time
i'm gonna get too close to you oh oh oh
he wants me
he wants my hot phoenix body
i'm not sharing i'm not sharing with you
get
wait
you have a long reach man big hitbox
yes
i jumped over his blue tails
a lot of flasks still
oh there we go there we go
there we go
that was pretty bad
save the jelly
[Music]
hallelujah
please he's poisoned
wait
i'm gonna style a little bit
and calm down
uh stalling
i pressed actually the wrong button i
think
no no i'm gonna ruin it i'm wearing it
i'm finding it
i'm ruining the perfect run
i crumbled like an apple pie
with ice cream vanilla ice cream
[Laughter]
oh that was so nice i was always aiming
for that bleed
and then it happened then it happened
the incredible unbelievable thing
happened
see that was i was trying to dodge but i
was so nervous i kept on pressing the
wrong thing
i kept on pressing x let's just jump
yeah but the blood is really good it
like immediately
takes so much damage
but i found my
new technique of charging at him
charging at him with a jump and then a
heavy attack which you guys i know
you've been saying all along blah blah
blah
i can never never get that
what do you want to do
what do you want to do he's indecisive
time for jelly to do some damage
going around it huh
even that i pressed like 10 seconds
earlier at least it felt like it
and even that was not enough time
to dodge
in time oh he's a
dangerous place to fight
guys security
you can't
who builds who builds this place who
builds these places
incredible amount of
danger here
lack of security
[Music]
you know that this makes people die
right people die when they fall off a
cliff
just like they die when they're killed
it's just logic okay
hey i am you and me buddy
you and me
i'm turtle
and what you are i will never know
oh my god
okay we're going like for really small
damage all the time right now
but it's better to do that than to be
killed oh
[Applause]
okay
buddy
nice to meet you too sir
uh
i'm a little bit too much of a chicken
in this run to make him bleed i guess
well that's okay
there's times like these
[Music]
yeah i felt it too i felt this could be
the one
but
i feel like i'm curious like i'm getting
i'm getting good i think but
it's not enough it's not enough it's
just never enough
that that was the run that was supposed
to be it
uh
i'm getting good though right i know
oh no i'm getting good oh
i thought it was good to be so
unaggressive in the last turn
what what i'm sorry i didn't see it
coming [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
then the jump back cause i was like yeah
he's gonna hit back
and i lose that opportunity for big
damage
i knew he was gonna hit me right back i
knew it
we're gonna get another chance
we're gonna get another chance i promise
you
free
free flask stone
at this point
i like that
i like that that was a good move man i
was for once
for once i
broke at him
i don't do that much
feels too dangerous
oh
i wanted to roll at him again but i was
stopped
but jellyfish still
so much hp
still so much hp man
oh
one there he goes
[Music]
holy [\h__\h] collateral damage
yay
r1 would be better than r2
i literally stopped using our own you
always say i2 i2 r2 now i do r2 r2 and
you say r1
really
i use r2 too much now i use r2 too much
first i use r1 too much then i use row
too much then i use everything else too
much
now i use r2 too much
you guys are never satisfied with me
no
me
i'm streaming
yes
[Applause]
okay i got it once i'm happy
he sliced my head up just like that
he sliced my head up
there you at once he's down you mean i
should r1 once i
uh-huh when he staggers you mean when
he's basically on the ground
r1 after stagger you mean staggered
means ground
when he's on the ground
uh
i thought you know when i got the chance
gotta do a few more heavy hits okay
i'm gonna do a weak hits all day
i guess we got a lot of time at that
point
i almost had the timing for that almost
oh
it's gonna die
yeah
almost almost killed me buddy no no no i
got my upgraded flasks
you can't scare me no more oh here
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
you know when the
light bulb
what did i do it again am i insane
i'm an assassin
i did it oops i did it
again time to heal time to heal baby
no wait wait oh such a good girl really
really really
um
never
just can't just can't um
i am
i'm cursed
i'm cursed like i
do so well
only until that point
when i'm alone when i'm alone when the
jelly leaves me
when the jello leaves me
you
can't live without you you want best
friends man
painful
[Music]
oh
as if i'm a baseball or something
it's like strength
you're out
i wanna make you bleed honey
yes
yes [\h__\h]
that [\h__\h] baseball hit
ah damn collateral then
[\h__\h]
you're so [\h__\h] why did you die so
early jelly
oh foolish i can't
i can't
[Music]
can you summon jelly again no
no it's impossible
ladies
i'm trying to mix it okay
you guys
i don't know what you want from me
first i do like the tanks then you want
the hard kicks
the heavy ones
what you want from your high chokers i
really don't have the time right now
trunks
i don't know i don't know just kill me
kill me
[Music]
okay maybe some belly pads will help
thank you jonkers
to just you know that table that i
brought from the balcony into my room
for the um
for the
uh hot glue thingy now she's rolling
around on it showing me her belly yeah
yeah
yeah at that belly
that that belly
bent that belly
at
i don't know about that oh
oh sorry i bonked against the microphone
oh that feels good yeah
oh she's aggressively purring
i'm taking that per energy
yeah i'm absorbing it
oh yeah
oh yeah circular circular belly padding
and that's the spot yeah
summon cats no [\h__\h] npcs we're summoning
cats
throwing the kitchen sink that's a good
idea that's a good advice
now don't wait i mean we can give the
summoner
the magician one more try now that we're
like kind of used to
deal with this guy
with only our jelly maybe maybe it will
hmm
now what do you guys think what does the
chat say about summoning uh our old
friend
or a magician
maybe now that i also fight him
differently
maybe it's
worth a shot
[Music]
okay jonker is i'm done petting you you
may leave now thank you for your energy
thank you for letting me dry my sweaty
hands on you
lame we're gonna try at once but i don't
know because it gives him double the
double the amount of hp
and
if we if we think about if rogier does
double
double damage
like if he makes up for that i'm not
quite sure
i feel like he
doesn't quite make up for it
in the beginning i always thought it was
good to go with him because he gives me
more he takes away some of the
um
aggression towards me the aggro
but he also dies like a [\h__\h] fly
immediately
well okay we can
that was kind of stuff there
maybe
maybe with our new technique
and we just get both heated okay
he has more hp than me i wish i had that
much hp man
man he's so aggressive
oh oh that was fast yo
holy [\h__\h] i'm good
wait why did i do that
i saw it coming
that was actually really fast
you're in the way
i don't see [\h__\h]
okay sorcerer is dead but jellyfish
still has so much hp oh my god
okay guys
thank you everybody for watching today
thank you i have four flats literally
nothing can take me down now
[Applause]
okay okay please don't tell me that this
was just a lucky run um and that this is
always like this now alex
stop don't tell me i think so that makes
it seem like it was my fault
that's just how it happens sometimes
it's just how it goes somehow the next
turn next turn next run
man we got him
down so quickly
holy [\h__\h] i don't know
i don't know i guess it's really just
that i
learned a lot and i'm stronger and we
all do much more damage
yeah yeah yeah yeah
that bleeding too damn came out of
nowhere
oh oh hello sorry too disturbed scared
okay
better than germany
drink
because we're doing
more damage that the bleeding gets
activated faster
don't roll down the cliff oh that was
close i was so close man
i almost rolled down the cliff
oh i did it again
okay okay
okay
kind of foolish of me there for one
moment to think that i could get away
with that
she just did it yo
sorcerer yeah
oh i'm changing my mind about you
how are you still laughing
oh
froggy
[Music]
okay
ah
touch
wow
thank you
i mean in the end the turtle shell
only gave us
style points
but still worth it i would say for the
adventure
and we met that cool other um
boss
so
how much xp do i have
nine thousand
did it cap at nine thousand is that
possible because the per number is so
perfect it feels like oh no wait because
we're at zero so he probably gives
exactly 9 000 exp damn
so much
yo i don't even know what to
thank you thank you yes the morning star
amazing the bleeding really comes in
handy wait can i just in order so just
so i cannot confuse things
um
every time when he when we downed him
that was not him wait did he have a
bleed
i'm not confusing things here i'm like
we downed him and did critical damage
that didn't mean that he was bleeding
did he ever bleed
bigger
[Music]
all bigger
how many can i do i can do three right
minimum for you or me oh wait maybe not
we'll see uh
that was stagger i think he bled
he bled sometimes maybe not in the last
run i don't know in the last run we yeah
we put we
broke his posture a lot of times
i guess he didn't bleed
but i feel like i got them to bleed
sometimes
sometimes sometimes
i'm gonna do
bigger
two strength one how about that
level up
i guess you can rescale anyway if you
want to so
uh bleeding is a sudden chunk yeah i
feel like i saw that happening before um
finally man i was uh i was getting uh
frustrated again thinking that maybe
it's never gonna happen
um but it did happen we did it it only
took us uh five hours today to
do a little bit of an adventure and then
come back to the margaret yeah
and uh
how long did i play last time also five
hours so it's 10 hours to get margaret
a little bit ridiculous probably didn't
need to spend that much time on him but
i'm still a beginner in this genre in
this
game
style of games so
many things to learn um
but
yeah having so many
uh
them having someone send me so many
damage deals at once really helped at
the end
i feel like if i would have
done it alone i would i would have still
needed a couple more tries
it's not impossible but um
you did very well thank you only gets
better from now i don't know man
i don't know i feel like uh
yeah
it's probably you know what so
what i'm going to do with alden ring is
i'm going to play it um sometimes and
i'm going to try to do some co-op here
and there but the problem is the only
other ps5 player is kelly within her
live vm
but i did ask uh noida
if she wants to do co-op sometimes
so i think for co-op it's a nice collab
game at the moment for the moment
but not gonna be a weekly
regular series uh just gonna play it
maybe
maybe a few times in the coming weeks
but
like i don't aim for this
i don't aim to play this until the end
because i know it's a big game and i
know that it will just be a lot of
frustration even if it's also rewarding
i feel like a game like this
maybe
maybe at some point i should play it
alone like the next couple streams there
could definitely be more streams but
um i'm not gonna play it until the very
end on stream
but let's see maybe i get really good
at it in the next couple streams and
then
it will be a piece of cake to
finish the game
but yeah i don't know
for now it's not a regular series and we
are going to start yakuza
uh in the coming week supposedly
supposedly um
yeah
thank you guys for coming by today um i
think i have maybe like a tiny amount of
super chats
to read but uh you know i have a guest
today so
oh
do you need to save in this game i
forgot
when i touched this thing it's saved
right
we're gonna go make some food with mommy
and we are going to have dinner and yeah
tomorrow's stream i will
put up soon but no schedules for the
week keep that in mind
and sorry if i was a little bit quiet
today i felt a little bit awkward
um
quiet as in not telling many stories no
saving necessary okay okay but the game
and the ps5 uh was really mad at me when
i turned it on today because they were
like why did you not turn us off
properly both the ps5 and the
and the uh game told me that when i
opened it i was like yo sorry
sorry i feel like really scolded sorry
about that man
okay
yeah yeah oh greetings from mama tony by
the way
oh oh i want to tell you guys one thing
she came today and she saw my omo cat
merch i'm also wearing it now
and of course remember when my mom
turned down
the omo cat merch and i said mommy you
will want it believe me and she said no
and now she comes here and sees my omo
cat merch and guess what now she wants
it
now she wants it gotta i gotta contact
normal cats
tell her mommy wants some of that merch
[Laughter]
yeah i knew it if she saw it in person
she couldn't resist anymore
oh and i tried wearing them the slippers
the birthday slippers today i had them
lying around but i didn't unpack them
yet
um they are so fluffy yo it feels like
you're like
wearing like clouds
it's a little bit difficult to walk in
them i'm gonna be honest
um but at least for me they fit
i'm gonna have them lying around for
guests i think i don't wear slippers
that often
yeah anyway more chitchat soon um i'll
see you guys tomorrow and warren's
portal entrance what
what does that mean
i'm done i'm i'm fine ending the game
here right
it's all good all good
yeah
fluffy very fluffy indeed
thank you guys for watching
and then in german we say
auf wiedersehen good night
thank you everybody there might not be a
tweet
afterwards
maybe not immediately
quit to the main menu let me do that
system
how do you close a game properly so that
it's not mean until
oh wait no maybe maybe we're gonna go
no i don't know how to close the game
i think last time i just kept it open
like this
uh
in system
uh why is it so hidden
10 hours there you go kiara level 22.
bye
[Music]
you