foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
hello
hello oh wait wait
my game's not there wait
what is my game
oh there
ah
yes hello
okay
yes let's introduce ourselves
who's first
from the top
okay okay
karaoke
[Music]
hi hi
I'm mute oh sorry
no problem more is here hi Jessica
happy death Grim Reaper I'm here I need
to do my best for my team ID Sports Fest
well let's go let's go
yeah dude I don't know it's been a long
day
it's me hey I'm Hawaii gin one and I'm
your feet not Lo-Fi but you can't call
me your Brio fee but it's not love I am
[Laughter]
FYI I'm I think probably I'm not the
only uh I'm the only one who doesn't
open stream so you're free to watch from
whichever okay
[Music]
thank you
next time
hi hello everyone my name is
[Music]
okay
um I'm the black kid from whole life ID
third generation
remind yourself about your introduction
I've never done any introduction in my
own stream
oh my God
again
okay
Indonesia generation one I am
part two in these guys I'm actually NPC
right now
honey I can see your forehead yes
be careful with my forehead
yeah
okay okay
[Music]
so I have I have been chosen as the
pretty steam leader this year again
[Music]
a good good day good morning good
evening everybody I am participating in
the soccer match and also in the
badminton with a teaming up with Kaila
moment
[Applause]
[Music]
my name is
[Applause]
okay so before we start I actually have
a little bit of uh
yes before we start so
um
this is this is giving me pressure
pressure
okay so before we start I have something
to announce that
Uma will not be here but but they are a
really diligent member so they already
practiced
um in the afternoon although there is no
stream and also later on uh one hour
from now uh hopefully sooner Senpai will
be able to join
yay
what uh I think Mona here tonight will
help us as the mod for uh several uh
some games nice PC okay and also
NPCs
so I will also explain about the game
first uh for each game
but maybe it will be better if we go
about the teaming first are you guys all
right with that yes
so first
nine members including me and then there
will be elfi Kyla Sona Senpai ganas
Kiara Cali and fona
[Music]
is so many strong people yes so many
people we are strong all of you are
great
you too you're great you're the big team
now
yeah Pink Ladies listening ladies hi
pinks there will be one two three four
five games
five games five games
the first going to be a a catch the
fourth captured before capture the four
thank you uh and from our team it's
going to be uh Kyla me uh fauna and Luna
yay
um foreign
[Music]
to kind of like join
um
here if you want to try it before you
can just join in okay thank you
thank you
and then there will be potato sack race
yeah
so basically it's a race
uh basically you insert like like you
you go inside of the potato sack and
then you jump
so basically it's not it's not the the
normal race it's like race while jumping
you have to jump okay yes and whoever uh
complete the three laps uh within their
member
first is the winner
okay
the team will be me thanks
another
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
thank you
yes
[Applause]
you're playing against the blue the big
the big blue yes so basically it's the
pink team against the blue team
[Music]
because
it's going to be me coyote and Cali
power
[Music]
down again
and then there will be badminton so
badminton will be like we'll have two
rounds basically A and B
[Music]
in badminton a there will be Kyla and
Kiana
and in badminton B there will be eovie
and Sonos
[Music]
and then last there will be soccer yes
soccer is really fun
I love how you're saying soccer and not
football
okay
so okay so basically uh uh uh initially
it will be me but it's going to be
change with Erp so the team for soccer
will be eovi Kaira Kiara Cali koyori and
Luna yes
[Music]
and before before we start playing I
would like for everyone to go here
foreign
[Music]
the colon response of fertility okay
ready ready
I'm looking at the let me look at those
scripts
I will I will read everything first from
the from the top to bottom and then
we'll practice after that okay okay
okay okay so I will I will give example
first
fight fight fight let's go
foreign
[Music]
wow
foreign
[Music]
yeah
so we got it no no problem what does it
mean oh okay okay so basically uh that
one
is like the the best teams
okay like the strongest team ever
whose team
um
[Music]
yes and that Aya is like it's just like
why why yeah yeah
it's like yeah Indonesia
and it's like yeah
let's go okay
[Music]
ready I'm ready
probably uh I wouldn't say it's probably
like most likely
um the MC will tell us to do that before
the game starts later
chill yeah okay if you'd love to
practice I already put the
the example the audio example for that
there so feel free
to me right
kind of kind of you're kind of gone
yes really because
you listen to me
foreign
[Music]
so uh which game do you want to try
first
um
yeah let's go let's go soccer
[Music]
change
yeah
[Music]
oh my God
Instagram
so yeah you can click me you are not
participating in the next game
should we should we
um split how many people a year how many
people here I mean
[Music]
all right
okay
what should I do is roll one
for white okay so if you want to be a
keeper or Stacker I feel like we should
practice what we will really be in the
end okay so basically who wants to be a
keeper because keeper is the only one
position
that is right I I want to try it if it's
okay
I'll practice the the other one
okay I'm just oh roll okay I'm just
gonna be standard too
um
six minutes please
six minutes
right now
um
I have to explain something first is
that okay okay
so there is uh like three items uh if
you are on basic there is like two shoes
green and yellow and if you're the
goalkeeper you will holding this
[Music]
for the goalkeeper
um if you want to get the balls you have
to click it so it's gonna be on hold
so you hold the ball and for the
basic one uh there's like two uh green
and yellow the green is like a regular
cake and the yellow is the long cake
um and there is uh if you are on the uh
some special occasion
that you have to kick to the goal what
is the name
[Music]
it was like a final decisions kind of
thing so make sure the 11 meter shooting
gun
the eliminations the elimination the
final elimination yes
um there is there is like uh
you cannot use this one you can use the
yellow so you have to use the regular
the green one the penalty will be in
where you stand in the corner and then
shoot or no no no not in the corner and
the center in front of the goal in the
center okay ah where they line up so it
is 11. yeah okay yeah they line up and
they try to get a goal until yeah they
can okay okay okay okay
oh that's all uh have fun oh
[Music]
please thank you thank you
okay
let's go you ready
are we ready
[Music]
yes start
whoa okay
I can't be out of breath here in this
game
[Music]
that was a good kick
okay
let's go
try bro okay
as close as possible
I don't know
anything alone don't worry
[Applause]
even think about it
don't go
on YouTube
yeah if you were holding it it's gonna
be like that
okay
it's okay yes
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank you
okay
[Music]
thank you
great time oh there's a great time cool
okay
[Music]
where you can actually discuss with your
teammates oh so okay I will I will be
the back Kiara will be okay
I will I will
um
no man wow a long kick
yes
here is very good at this long kick
apparently
okay
[Music]
just take the ball I think
all right
yes yes
[Music]
no
no oh the fireworks are giving me lag oh
really
open my door BRB
need to pause
nice
nice oh
no
let's go is Carol okay
[Music]
okay should we pause
the game oh it doesn't look like it oh
you want to boss the game reference
yes you always have King a bit for like
a few seconds
apparently there's no Pals in the game
[Music]
yeah I think
opening the door right now so she is at
the moment
yeah okay
[Music]
I'm sorry
Amazon delivery Amazon
this game is only six minutes as
requested by risu
regular game will be on 20 minutes
21.
in Pokemon unite I'm excited
now what are you talking about
natural Talent yeah
you guys want to try this again maybe
goalkeeper
[Music]
be prepared
we got it
oh who is this
[Music]
okay
oh yeah
we got a lot of penalties
okay I can't defend the goal right I
can't
you can you okay
okay really okay
[Music]
I'm gone I just fell for the world oh no
you fell for the world yes
I was flying a second ago
do you switch because it was switched to
ilfe so that she's controlling the goal
and then
okay
[Music]
let's go okay all right good good all
right I'll do this
and I'm gone
and I'm gone oh okay yeah me again oh my
gosh
[Music]
so basically the the second
is it's gold
let's go the spectator mode
yes
[Music]
wow that's very good to be close I used
to have to be up closer to it I can I
can see Cali
ready you're ready yes
that's what we needed
oh
[Music]
okay hold it oh you did it
no go coils
[Music]
bring it easy
come on
let's go
ready ready
can't curve yeah try to curve the ball
okay
[Music]
yeah
nine
I don't think we should be the goalie
I think wait is is eofi
um in the soccer are you in the soccer
game yeah I'm in a soccer game you
should be the goalie I don't want to be
okay yeah that's the only way I can we
can win all of us okay okay guys
once more yes yeah I'll always try for
this time okay
I'll be the keeper team white again
I'll be team red I like red
I think I get a white again okay
wanna try and okay I'm gonna be Striker
I'm a goalkeeper
I'm the best soccer player in all of us
because we suck in Austria we never make
it to championships or anything Striker
Striker okay okay okay okay
yay okay go to keep her who red let's go
keep my who
sure
okay I think I I think I pick it already
I cannot change it
I think you can okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay
[Music]
hold on I'm gonna make sure again okay
for there
okay
let's go
Holly let's go
side through okay wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait where are you
going
yeah leave it to me
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
no
no I'm gonna get it I got it
oh
nice
Kyla's so strong
let's try
what people say oh goodness
all right let me go back let me go back
okay
no no no no no no no no
[Laughter]
no
QBC let's go let's go
come on come on let's go
no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no
okay y'all are aggressive
let's go
[Music]
yeah
nice
that's nice
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay here we go
[Music]
okay okay
oh yeah
okay okay yeah
okay okay
[Music]
okay
nope nope nope oh yeah
let's freaking go wow
you guys are getting stronger oh yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
hello
is
it
wow Emily
rigged
absolutely Rick no no no
yeah okay
oh God oh my God is getting stronger and
stronger okay
oh it's over there I see gotcha all
right all right let's party
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah I wasn't prepared
[Music]
thank you
Get Ready Get Ready Get Ready
[Music]
come on
all right
[Applause]
yeah I touched
yes
[Music]
[Laughter]
but if you want to try it's okay though
hello
we can take take turns what color are we
gonna right let's go
red red okay
[Music]
I think it's gonna be easier if you
press F5
you cannot see the shuttle corn because
can we hit each other
okay ready ready ready let's go
let's go okay uh just make sure that uh
when you want to kick the is it
uh make sure you don't go uh don't look
up because when you look up it's gonna
be sword oh
yeah it's gonna be short it's it's gonna
stuck in your place it's not gonna be on
your open any place okay something more
straight
yeah it just looks strange focus on the
street
[Music]
I know
Linda
over there wow
okay
no I see I see aim for the red
oh I can fly oh my God
let's go I can see from above
[Applause]
if you're not playing the game you can
fly don't worry about that
[Music]
oh I see
oh
I think I understand how long will this
game be letting the actual uh tournament
if you get 10 points
[Music]
[Applause]
wow you guys are strong
I think I think
I think I can trust my team you guys are
really strong on every game okay I'm
sorry this is difficult it's fine it's
fine we can practice more later it's
fine
yeah nice nice
okay
is better because you see the shadow
really I didn't know that she said
though right girls you said F5 for third
person is better it depends it depends
on your preference actually no no okay
I'll try this one um live okay I'm
trying F5 okay
does someone else want to try no you
guys can try it it's fine
foreign
[Music]
man
okay
let's go let's go we're gonna be here oh
let's go okay
turn
it yes
okay nice
one Kayla
it's on Sunday
right it was fun Sunday for me
that's pretty good
Saturday for n a okay
got it okay
okay
nice
oh
hit the ball out oh yeah that's out
okay let's go
we can't do it okay okay
[Music]
ground yeah
wow yeah um if they're shooting over to
your side for the first shot you should
just let it fall down to the ground if
they're gonna if they're not gonna hit
the red
here they already learned
yeah very good okay okay
good job come on let's go
what
no it did it pretty far yeah yeah I felt
like it yeah
so loud
but I don't see the shadow but at least
I see the ball
that's me okay
oh no okay
[Music]
let's go hit it hit it
sounds nice
oh my God
[Music]
I'll be right
just kidding I'll be left it's fine it's
fine just follow whatever yeah just
follow just follow the Batman yes
we'll have one more shot one more shot
oh no one more
bring it on let's go let's go
oh no
oh my God
wow you guys are strong is it out
um
you guys win yeah
we have good badminton players
[Music]
those are
um
[Music]
so everyone can try
we can all try this one it's okay
yeah three and three yes because it's
like three versus three so yes
I'll join white the white okay I went
two versus two is it good though why no
you'll enjoy it now
[Music]
close your eyes
it's okay it will be over before before
you before you realize
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah there's no way that I would be good
at this
it's okay
wait wait
are you are you going the wrong way
Kelly
oops I went the wrong way
[Music]
already in her second round
nah I know I'm not
I'm not wrong you passed me already but
that was okay because if you were slow
what's the best route why am I so slimy
yeah so try it the best fruit
how are you gonna reach the goal so fast
what the termination
[Music]
oh my God okay the bounciness I can see
how yofi gets sick from this yes
I understand yeah emotions sickness
ocean
I'm gonna get sick from this too being
stuck in the bedroom
you get through the berry bushes
there's like no path through them
[Music]
oh
oh you can get through the cobwebs
that's about it
it's kidding I lied
I'm not in sync with my potato sack
relax
you can you can actually just just stand
there waiting for the other team to
finish it
okay
[Music]
flying
oh you're done
if everyone is already gave up just tell
me I can just stop the game yes guys you
don't need to find yourself okay yeah
you don't need to push yourself okay
okay
okay okay
the only one from our team who's here
right now who has to practice this is
yes I'm already finished so okay okay I
believe I believe yes
okay
[Music]
I have to say it's a very cute original
way to replace a normal Marathon relay
yeah
[Music]
let's go let's go let's go back
okay no more okay I need to practice
this one
um
yeah
okay okay
[Music]
my name
is
bye
[Music]
um
she stays up late
thank you
um
okay
[Music]
foreign
everybody goes up there no it doesn't
need to of course
okay yes okay
okay you guys ready
ready I'm ready ready okay three two one
find out your finger Queen
uh you spam right click on right click
the lever
oh this one
okay
[Music]
basically you need to like spam clay the
the lever with a right click
okay
besties unaware
we both didn't know what to do no idea
oh I didn't join the team
um
you wanna practice you haven't joined
yet oh yeah the team I'm going down okay
I'm going down
leave it to me
okay let's go okay macaroni
scanner
the whole architecture is insane I know
who built this okay Magic
Mickey
[Music]
boys
strong arms no more noodle arms strong
arms no more
on my fingers
again again again again
we have to win
let's go let's go
so basically our left side or right side
either fine is okay and also okay
I'll see also tips from me you can
actually play uh the furthest lever so
you don't really need to like stay on
the front lever
okay
so you don't fall off so early I guess
okay okay
foreign
if you want to focus more we can like uh
divide on different level left or right
yeah
okay and everyone hits a different lever
right yeah yeah
Ichiban
foreign
[Music]
here we go
laughs
foreign
okay
what actually I started doing better
when I changed fingers when I changed
fingers yes
yes right yes
my finger is broken you can actually
change
to your main finger
oh man
this time I'm gonna try okay with the
other finger you guys never give up
practice until you make it okay so yeah
basically you can actually uh click with
your
um pointy finger yeah
with your finger yeah I switched Midway
through so that the other one gets a
break but team the current team red
lineup is our homeban lineup our real
lineup so you girls gotta win against
team white go go go go go
okay I'm ready
foreign
[Music]
everything
also you can you can press shift so you
can you you barely move I think so
that'll be nice
hold on hold on hold on uh I messed up
I'm still moving I'm still moving even
holding shift
yeah me too yeah it is kind of kind of
like
but in small steps ah wait hold on
because it ah because I hit shift it
messed me up
it's okay for
eign
[Music]
who did the most pulls each member I
want to see exactly one one versus one
wow we were using if we were using a
game controller it would be a different
situation
can I change the click to like space bar
no I mean I mean you can do it right
okay yeah even you can do it if you want
it okay yeah yeah
I don't know how to do that
okay let's just try without Kayla okay
okay
two versus two okay oh okay one more all
right let's try
no without kailas oh yeah
[Music]
oh yeah
let's go
[Music]
um
heaven
by myself are you kidding me by yourself
I'm gonna stop it okay let's start
again wow
awesome okay you know why were you alone
[Music]
that's another
I mean he one two one versus one it's
okay though I wanna I wanna try white
team okay okay so white and Chihuahua
white okay okay let's go okay that's
good that's good okay
[Music]
you're playing against Kobo you wanna
teach her a lesson right which is so
true
no no no
no no no no no no no no no
[Music]
oh yeah yeah we're gonna be against
Cowboy man I think that yeah he's so
much stronger oh God okay
[Music]
right
let's go with the bus
[Music]
[Applause]
oh it's so close
[Music]
oh my God
the the numbers then it takes so much
longer and now you guys have to hold out
longer
[Music]
as long as you need me to
strange
[Music]
I may not be the fastest quicker but I
have stamina
the finger's gonna have an ABS
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
come on
it's so close
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm starting to kind of lose it
[Laughter]
let's go
yes
why team leading what's happened with
red team red team already
ketchup but but we're still leaning okay
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay
[Music]
yeah yeah
oh my God
[Applause]
I don't know man my finger's giving out
one minute one minute
[Music]
one minute left
syndrome
[Applause]
there's a little
bit on their best right now
trying again 30 seconds
still a good thing for us is it not no I
know
uh 20 seconds yeah things are going well
it's good for you
okay 15 seconds
we tried really hard
rights and dogs
[Applause]
oh
yeah
are you guys ready to fight your life
I'm never doing this again
[Music]
against you
yeah seems like we played them all looks
like it one left one guess oh what's
that one again
[Music]
feel free
I think moey's actually gonna have to
leave now I gotta go to bed okay that
was really fun
good luck to you guys
bye
[Music]
okay
maybe maybe while we're taking break we
can try to um the the yellow first yeah
sorry Senpai is here
[Music]
activities
okay
let's download okay okay
[Music]
okay now
foreign
[Music]
take your knee
is
[Music]
so foreign
foreign
[Music]
this
is
gonna play me
and also there is another thing as you
can see yeah
[Music]
okay okay
heads up here I want to tell you guys
that be careful uh if you're on your
opinion land so as you can see this is
the center of the place
the one that I am sitting right now is
the center place and this is the red uh
the Red Land and this is the white land
if you're white and you're going to Red
be careful uh if you met your opponent
because you if they get you you will go
into jail immediately
okay and it also vice versa with the
others
[Music]
nobody your friend can help you to get
out of the jail okay please explain it
in Japanese okay
my standard
um
[Music]
foreign
Canada
[Music]
um
I do
initiative
[Music]
Mississippi
community
so so
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
so if you pick white you see that a
white Blazer like too up to the sky yeah
yeah you need to go to the red one okay
okay it's red okay yeah if you're red
you need to go try just try to find a
way
um to the white and then if you see your
opponent just punch
easy
yeah all right I'm back in I'm back in
again
[Music]
to go with red
guys
yes you you practice
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
let's go
[Music]
should we go together
yeah okay maybe separate is better
because we have higher chances oh this
is close
do we have HP nope yeah we have the the
red one red bars above your items
oh yeah
oh
[Music]
okay
can't you like remember
if you if you can if you want to
remember you can do it I mean I'm not in
this but can the people who are actually
participating remember
maybe maybe
[Music]
you just gotta remember the pattern and
you win yeah but but there are mobs
right there
past all of them they didn't hit me once
yeah
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
put one door somewhere oh
foreign
[Music]
I do
[Laughter]
anyone's worried but she wants to have a
pink team okay
[Music]
should we practice the badminton again
yeah
we are here right yes yes
oh you
saw Batman yeah
okay we're gonna go to batam let's go
um
your wife is okay
versus three
not two it's only can play base
I mean if you want to play three it's
it's fine too it's candy yeah
okay okay all members
since uh you guys will no longer need to
practice
I think uh you can actually lead this uh
start game and the stop game okay okay
okay
foreign
[Music]
okay
okay should I stay more in the front
than you were in the back yeah
okay
[Music]
let's go let's go we don't expect it
oh
[Music]
oh dang
okay okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
too much power
playing too much power
[Music]
yes
Auto
[Music]
let's go you view minor
okay let's go let's go
wow you guys on fire hell yeah yes let's
go let's go
this is fun I like badminton but it's
easier to uh in Minecraft than it is oh
no
it is
okay okay okay there's no need to sweat
yeah in in Minecraft
[Music]
sweating potential
wow okay okay
[Music]
up
shoot so far
thank you
[Music]
I'm not ready it's fine it's fine it's
Green River
it's not ready though it's okay it's
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank you
we need to run faster yeah okay all
right it's out I think it's Alex yeah
it's out
[Music]
wow
red team and white teams are getting
better on this everybody they are
putting on good match
with two points difference
[Music]
nice it was fun that's fun wanna
practice again oh yeah of course that
was already good much better than before
you're good
[Music]
okay
Kyla I'm up for more practice Yeah okay
maybe I can one versus one yeah
yeah definitely
okay okay
oh wait oh I went back sorry oopsie it's
fine okay
one of the rest of the people doing I
have I have something to finish today so
I'm gonna take my leaves it's okay
tell me
[Music]
oh yeah
Corona
[Music]
foreign
makes the Minecraft screen really really
short for the potato sack game because
she normally feels sick for these kind
of games that's actually really tiny and
it helps it's actually really smart
[Music]
um
can we have play different games at the
same time I think so we can we can we
can yeah
maybe into two different ones sure yeah
maybe yeah yeah sure we're gonna be
talking about different things okay
where should we go training oh training
training okay yeah okay okay um
[Music]
foreign
yes
[Music]
foreign
why not
okay
yes yes
[Music]
go go
go go go go go go
oh
[Music]
okay
thank you
[Music]
foreign
okay
a red okay yours
[Music]
foreign
okay okay okay
[Music]
I'm listening to Lisa's listen and song
download oh
oh yes
okay okay yours
again
foreign
let's go
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
let's go
foreign
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you
I know
um
[Music]
thank you
thank you thank you
[Music]
say bye
now
[Music]
good night
yo
[Music]
OSH
okay
and then we'll continue
yes you know what
let's go to Kyle and Kiara please
I'm so glad that today actually
today is Purdue team practice already
um went very smoothly so I'm very happy
about it and also
um
even though we didn't stream it
and fauna actually really eager to try
to practice so we actually had practice
in the afternoon so I would like to tell
you guys again about that and they
actually did great on the practice and I
also uh told them about
um about the uh cheer song the yellow
so I'm actually really happy about
productivity because
everybody's just very eager and very
sweet so I'm just like
so yeah let's go to Kyla and Kiara place
this is actually teamstick so it is
actually
laughs
okay okay
that's fast how did it go yes we
actually
tried twice and
and when
really great really good really okay
okay we are practicing really great too
yeah yes you guys are really
um
passion passionate
[Applause]
that's so good it's not so close very
good yeah that's very good that's very
good oh you guys you guys will be fine
no one more Kyla okay
I can't believe that you want to stop
this practice you want to go back to
hollow cure don't you yes you want to go
back to home here I can see it
yeah just thinking about hola cure all
the time she's like come on are We
against on the badminton from the three
candy who are who are we
Totowa okay
okay sure sure sure I wonder how good
they are if they're not a practice
stream I need to watch it
did
in the morning
I need to watch the Vlogs yeah I need to
check it too we need to know our
opponent right yeah yeah that will help
out no it's not I don't rely on the auto
yeah
okay so yes Kyle is serving Kiara is
also passing it was very very close
[Music]
oh no this is bad this is bad
Kayla okay
[Music]
it's a big field
I think it's pretty pretty big
okay
oh Kyla is catching up oh we'll see you
ready
I'm getting a feeling for it when it's
out all nice oh you you already uh
mastered yeah we practiced for that yeah
yeah
[Laughter]
okay
nice nice wait what yeah I passed
through it it was too close
okay I like the Smashing sounds
Too Short both team are equally strong
apparently so we'll see which is good
it's good because we're on the same team
yes and it's actually a good thing
yeah okay okay okay okay okay okay I got
it got it
okay
oh this is so close
oh
[Music]
my God I think I don't know
I think it's my mistake for still
hitting it even though I wouldn't yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
okay this is so fun is that Alex no it's
not oh
I'll talk
oh my God okay I'm ready
[Music]
good to look up and make short shots and
that is good because they don't expect
it okay
[Music]
oh
okay hi
[Music]
foreign
this is going to be
very tough
I thought it was more in the front than
it really was okay nice nice
I think
I've been fine I don't know if you want
no practice again I you can't can we
uh for soccer we have two three people
is not enough I guess yeah I mean we can
do oh yeah I think you need like at
least four yeah but you know right you
can dribble the ball so by the time
that's the very important one so you
just can walk and yeah dribble the ball
you don't need short shots yeah you
don't need to just kick kick like that
no you don't need to do that you can
actually hit the ball with your body
yeah yeah you can dribble the ball oh
without clicking uh yes you would have
actually clicking that's why can I try
that yeah sure yeah let's let's go let's
go yeah I didn't know that that's secret
knowledge yeah that's why because if we
kick we lost the ball
okay soccer soccer
I thought that was the only way we can
make it move
I will be the white team
okay me too
okay nice shoes
okay ready all ready yes
bison okay I'm ready okay
we will not have goalkeeper yeah it's
okay that's fine
okay hold on don't kick okay don't kick
it just just walk over it to kick this
first oh okay just okay just walk over
it okay just walk don't kick okay okay
yeah like that yeah yeah
yeah yeah you you just need to like turn
left turn right yeah yes
how is this not go go in
there you go yes so you you need to like
do that I want to try something okay
yeah uh let's let me see how far I need
to go
until you maybe let's say I'm here on
the line and then ah too far wait to go
back
I think that's yeah that's kind of okay
I think if I do a long kick from here is
it gold no no it is the post I think it
hits it
doesn't have to do with like if I'm
looking up or down no not really Landing
no
[Music]
not right
try try try practice the dribble fart
yeah because if you think you lost the
ball
oh there
oh that was a score
apparently what was that
there you go
that's not enough let's go this far
right
you can you can actually go that far
like I ask and and munas be like yeah
you can actually just like go there and
just I guess I've seen that in soccer
before as long as yeah but I think
people doesn't stop you yeah I think the
goalkeeper gonna it's easier for the
goalkeeper to hold
rather we dribble the ball like that
I think the goalkeeper gonna catch the
ball if we got I think I want to finish
I I don't think I'll I'll try the the
dribbling but I want to finish my
dribbling off with a good kick yeah okay
okay yeah practice yes try try try yeah
so
can we have like maybe lisu in the goal
no okay try to stop the ball no or maybe
or maybe I will be the goalkeeper okay
let's stop first okay okay let's stop
first our actual goalkeeper is gonna be
who
try to stop the dribble okay
yes do it okay okay
so the goalkeeper is either elfi or Kyla
I think yeah
yeah I think I think it's better for me
because I think I can dribble quite okay
oh yeah I saw you Yugi you be the uh the
the striker
gonna be the goalkeeper I think okay so
what team should I get
yeah maybe white so you can you can be
in the opposite okay yeah yeah okay
against you
should I be the goalkeeper I'll be the
goalkeeper no no no no no no no you you
need to be the standard so you try to uh
take the ball from Kiara because Kiara
is like trying to practice the dribble
Arena
okay so you're being the stop I'll be
the goalkeeper
wait I will be the goalkeeper for the
white for the whitening do we need a
goalkeeper
oh yeah to try to stop yeah okay you're
both against me now okay yeah yeah okay
yeah yeah what am I am I not a
goalkeeper or am I a goalkeeper
no right I'm a goalkeeper
you can just you can just try to take
the ball but don't hold the ball well
let me finish the ball yeah yeah just
try to stop the dribble
okay
[Music]
again I'll go around here
although okay
I'll be giving okay
oh okay
yeah
but you got it right you got it nice
nice thank you okay
try okay
I was pretty far and I only used a
normal kick yeah at the end
so that still went in nicely I guess the
problem always was that I would hit the
the top of the goal a lot ah yes don't
don't use the long cake yeah just use
the normal cake one yeah my
let's go buy a goalkeeper
[Music]
okay okay okay own goal
at them
Corner
cake but no one
nice thank you lisu no
try to catch up no
no no no
[Laughter]
man it makes me want to play Real Soccer
I never actually play Real Soccer uh
what about in school like no I only
played when I was little and I never
really played anymore
little was little weasu when I was
little little baby no not baby actually
this is like little little
let's go let's go
[Laughter]
back
I think when Lisa smacked it at me I
smacked it back oh yeah
okay
[Laughter]
five seconds oh no
okay break time I will talk to my
teammates and I'll talk to the ball I'll
I'll talk to Esther both goalkeeper do
you have any tips
um balls
balls yes yes
okay thank you Kiana I will do my best
Kiana all right thank you maybe try to
go from the side Kiara okay can I look
at your gloves yes this is my gloves
okay
both have it
yeah look and what we are talking to
each other
we're in a team right now hey I'm also
team white trust me trust me hello
wider I'm the widest person
basic let's resume the game yes
okay here we go
[Laughter]
[Music]
the problem is I have to go around the
ball because I I don't want to shoot it
in the same direction man okay
okay
no idea so no this is no this is
Well normally I would have someone
behind me to back me up right to help me
no no no no no no no no no no no
[Music]
to keep her now
[Laughter]
I was pressing the wrong thing I'm
scrolling elsewhere okay
you don't need to scroll by the way you
can just use like one two three
the hard one running away though
oh
God my fingers are busy being on wasd
okay okay you know you know
Nice Shot back into the middle
not for you Lisa not for you
I think for the goalkeeper it's also
easier to use the F5 the third point of
view oh yeah I'm also doing that
no
[Laughter]
nice nice fun I'm feeling so sweaty and
hot
I don't care okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
oh thank you
Risa are you playing the soccer no right
no I I changed with elv
oh your figure okay okay good you're
good at it
Kiara is feeling the pressure
[Music]
that was close if I would have angled it
a little bit more to the left and I
would have been a girl
oh it's almost out okay
okay
is actually really friends
nice and nicer what are you wanna try
again I want to try anything
um
no no stop it
stop it is me
[Applause]
to Kyla versus Lisa because Kyla you
know we actually did yeah already
[Music]
is fine hey but I want to see it once
how many how the point differences I
want to see it okay
I won't be in my uh top performance
because I already did it but I could try
one
I want to see it okay entertain me you
want them to tell me
okay sure that's a request right there
entertainers it's your job okay I'll
pick your white team oh we we have done
like 1 800 before
it's 1 800. yeah it's like five minutes
ish yeah five minutes and it's like one
on one one I don't want to match
[Music]
why is Kyla not in the tug of war teams
I don't know because I'm not there
she's not picked by the um staff I don't
know why
you would have wanted yeah
it's fine it's fine
I wear that clothes so it's fine the
score is closed yeah
oh my God my my hand feels sore already
now
again okay
I'm
I'm here
am I right on white you're red you're
red yeah red okay
yeah we're we're actually that close law
yeah yeah we're that close so I mean
it's fine
Oh I thought it would be a big
difference but maybe in the late game
maybe yeah when when like one of us
tired too so yeah yeah who gets tired
first
oh my god oh yeah so far it's so pretty
it's pretty much the same
[Music]
I'm sorry I'm already sorry for in
giving you this challenge it's gonna be
five minutes like this but yeah I really
have done this before
sleeping and and she's creating a bigger
and bigger lead
it's only a matter of time until she
pulls the first waiter oh yeah she's up
no she's already right I feel bad for my
mouth
six red and four uh White so
wait what I'm I'm red right I'm red
right oh wait never mind you read okay
sorry no no I don't know I don't know
which color am I yeah you are ready
on the top it's like switched with the
with them actually yeah the place right
the place right yeah the place
producer is still doing very very very
well yeah I mean we got the same spit
like yeah yeah
five minutes match and
got it so yeah basically our difference
is like 20 to 30.
on average yeah on average
one one letter tap is like
um
one point or two points or what I don't
know I don't know actually I think it's
three three points every leper
really I don't think it's one burn
yeah and and I don't really know like
how well they do it like this yeah yeah
I don't know I haven't watched their
practice yet Coco is definitely a speed
clicker I think because she's a Zoomer
she goes fast
away
she's a speeder I'm pretty sure and and
gura yeah is you know a master at Rhythm
games so she clicks everything really
fast and she's like she doesn't just
click everything randomly no she's very
coordinated with where she's clicking at
what timing so she should be pretty fast
I will I will always I will see the
practice of the distance oh I got Kyla
please record me later so you can
prepare myself
because that time when they did the
practice I was doing something else I
was like touching grass outside okay
you're touching grass yeah touching
grass
I need to touch some grass not because I
want to touch the grass
touch grass you know I saw the clip
about
um the uh Hollow cure
um Easter egg where the uh grass
for perfectionists
oh yeah yeah completion is completion
the completion
conclusion is grass so it's like one
gold
yeah one gold yeah I wonder who's that
for wow yeah I mean well
I play Hello cure on Monday or so
because I don't have time
on this uh Minecraft and thank you so
much thank you so much
no don't worry I have this problem this
uh starts for me at six a.m and the
Pokemon tournament I had to be there at
4 00 A.M
I don't know
step or go to sleep super early or go to
sleep super early yes
normally though
yeah also I have I have hold a talk at
10 P.M
will end at midnight that's six hours
before the Minecraft thing I would be
done with holotalk six hours oh so
that's not really enough time for me to
sleep because I need one hour at least
to fall asleep um
[Music]
I didn't think it through I didn't think
it through now I wanted to do a whole
talk on Sunday instead
[Music]
today again I'll take a nap I'll just
take like a free hour nap or so and I'll
be fine
okay looks good all these matches
looking good yes I think I think we are
ready yeah I think I'm good I'll
practice maybe me and Kyla can practice
tomorrow a little bit privately and yeah
yeah you can we can just do it off
stream too it's fine yeah yeah just call
me anytime or even before you know I
have to hold a talk until the actual
Minecraft Holo cup is a bloody cup I
don't know what to call it
um
between those I have like you know some
time probably so we can play the race
sure I can actually uh accompany too so
like whatever so I thank you definitely
make my
um schedule and usually it's gonna be
midnight
if it's midnight I'll I'll leave you to
Kyla I think midnight for me is like
morning time for you girls
yeah yeah
they're doing a great job at organizing
this and I'm I'm really impressed at
everything that has been prepared for
this turn this ID cup so good job thank
you thank you
yeah I'll go read super chats probably
me too
see you later then see you on the next
parties
thank you for having me
[Music]
yeah
ah
we close this
hey
I used tires
[Music]
foreign
what a nice looking hip
all right
[Music]
this time yes I think we are ready I
think you are ready for hollow ID cop
team party let's go there
I actually was very very very very
nervous before this but I'm actually
uh I'm actually really grateful that
everything is definitely everything went
really really really well
shoe
so it was amazing I am able to interact
with a lot of people today I actually
interacted uh
uh off stream as well with a lot of
people so I'm actually really really
really
happy that
I have the chance to be the leader of
partivity
[Music]
so yeah it's it's just so amazing thank
you so much for everybody who arranged
this thank you so much for the staff
thank you so much for Mona because Muna
really put a lot of work in this
although in the um
in the
real match later she will only be and
see but definitely she did a lot more
than than you guys see so everything
really is prepared by Mona so it was
actually really amazing
so yeah Super Chat time
#party win let's go
well the thing is uh this match is a is
a friendly match so we really
want everybody to just enjoy uh weather
whether it's the team member or
or the viewers so we'd love to have this
as a very friendly Sports match
so there there will be no hard feelings
whether
about the winner or the or the loser so
so basically this is a very
place for us to just have fun
and also you guys please watch and have
fun and nothing else aside of having fun
okay okay wing wing wing
[Music]
all right
okay so super chat from tonight from uh
you don't
know
[Music]
let me check again
next from Buddhism
from chunky Oreo thank you super sticker
not the episode
foreign
actually
um
also help behind the scenes so thank you
so much
next from
naming systems
you know I really like being around
Sonic Senpai because she's very sweet
and I don't know it's just she just have
this calming Aura I know that everybody
call her Dai Senpai but she's really
she's she gave this
um and she
uh what is anshine
who's answering
because because I need to talk with
three languages so I my brain is just
like jumbled
um over here and there calming soothing
soothing so she just have this soothing
Aura so I feel really comfortable around
her
this is a
so yeah it's really nice in uh instead
of being nervous I actually feel very
very comfortable so it's really nice
oh
NYX from RK super sticker arigato
from Caroline
congrats thank you actually I wouldn't
be this
um it wouldn't be this well without
elfi's um help because EOP actually
helped me a lot especially for
translating or also for the text
announcement and everything I actually
uh asked eovi a lot so I would really
say thank you so much for eov and also
she really handled well she really she
really takes the queue well whether when
to translate so
yes it's really it's really it's really
amazing to have ufi around so I think I
would I would love to send her uh some
cake
later
thank you Ryobi
speaking secretions
[Music]
mm-hmm
yummy has already already has cake
though but she needs more cake
is there more let me check
from Supreme blood from news
Yeah Boy Lisa look what will be open to
reorder in September it's your chance
how would I okay here's the thing okay
here's the thing if uh back then I think
it's about the big Slowpoke plushie yes
it is about the big Slowpoke plushie so
it's around 50k Yen right and let me huh
let me check on Google
[Music]
uh into
a 50k
it's very expensive
and
I know I know it's around 50k Yen but if
it's going to to be delivered to
Indonesia it's going to be doubled no
actually it's going to be tripled the
price because I saw I saw in uh
encyclopedia the first time people
actually uh sell this it's actually
around uh 14 million rupees because
obviously tax
so it's around
130 ish Yen if I am as in Indonesian
wants to buy that
[Music]
so with taxes it's going to be 14
or more Indonesia a million Indonesian
rupiah so it's about
130 or 140
000 yen
foreign
yes so it's actually
it will take
a really big portion
of
my income so I'd rather have that
allocated to a very meaningful project
instead
so that is very expensive
I think it's going to be like more more
than half of my income actually so it's
it's really it's really that expensive
[Music]
oh yeah
and also I'm cooking something so I
really really savings uh saving my money
to to to the cooking okay so I don't
think I know it's really tempting but I
don't really have the budget for for the
nuigurumi
I am actually really cooking something
right now
so thank you so much for the information
though I'd love to but I don't really
have the spare money for that
so yeah I'd love I'd rather you guys
have whatever I'm cooking at the moment
so
yeah see I'd rather you guys
um help me or fund me for for for the
for the cooking the cooking
for the cooking
she cooking will prisoners eat yes
prisoners actually ate a lot of spoilers
on the previous
um prisoners night so so yeah if if you
really want to support me please support
uh for for whatever I'm cooking at this
moment
thank you
next is
too many spoilers I haven't slept since
then
okay
take your time we're always with you
buddy
next is from social bus from someone
Ito from streamlabs
I'm six cooking funds thank you for the
cooking funds I will surely make the the
cooking very delicious
you guys will definitely eat well
so if you if you really want to know
about the cooking you can actually join
prisoners you can actually join my
membership because I actually gave a lot
of Major Spoilers there uh uh during the
last stream yes definitely if you if you
join prisoners now you can actually see
archives of membership stream so
definitely worth it yes so whatever
whatever you want to find out just join
person
okay so I think that's all guys
we get privilege too yes privilege
there's a lot of there's a lot of uh
spoilers normally in prison so if you
really want to know you can Joyce you
can just join prison
wanna be a winner for once join the
membership now
definitely yes definitely
yeah thank you so much thank you so much
for the one who actually made uh made
the uh yeah yeah as well
it's actually really
um really fun and it's really easy for
the other member to to
pronounce so that's why I picked the uh
I picked this one so thank you so much
for the yellow
it's big thumbs up for your
um
for your participation on helping Timber
TV make the yeah yeah thank you Timber
Timmy for the renew
well we should play Holocaust sometimes
soon I will but not now because I also
want to focus on
on the Galore Hollow ID because we will
have a lot more stuff even after
even after this after the hollow ID cop
so
I really really really really want to
focus on that because not everybody is
Carla okay
and we also we also have a lot of things
going on in the background as well so
yes thumbs up
yes hashtag party win yeah let's go
thank you so much for watching everybody
and please support team for TV so
whatever outcome that we will have uh on
the on the day it's all right I'd love
everybody to have fun and that's all
right that's the most important part
having fun
I don't know I'll see we'll see on the
day okay any any kind of hashtag will be
official on the day okay
so thank you so much everybody thank you
so much for watching ethos
thank you so much
[Music]
so I think we're gonna end the stream
here
thank you
[Music]
all right