do
oh my goodness the door is overflowing
hello hi
how are you
wow
thank you so much everyone for coming to
join me today
my special special day today
um it's my birthday
ah the taco jar is broken let's uh
pretend everything is okay
oh boy oh boy
yay
thank you thank you thank you thank you
it's the taco candy door
[Music]
hello i don't know why but
but i'm i'm like more nervous than i was
for the debut
they read butterflies in my stomach
are you so nervous for some reason
i think it's cause i'm not really
i'm really um
i'm not used to celebrating birthdays
this big
and um i'm just i just
it's just been really really really
really
really overwhelmed by all the support
that you guys have shown me while
preparing for this stream well always
but like even more so just going through
all the messages and
all the art and the music that you guys
you know prepared for for this day as
i was just
[Music]
i had to fix the ceiling a couple of
times
and i might have to again during the
stream but
thank you thank you thank you
honestly can't say thank you enough
[Music]
no it's not even 10 minutes either
it's not even 10 minutes oh
hold on let me let me get it
oh dear my nose is to be more plucked
than usual cause uh
i i woke up today well i took a short
nap
ah i love you guys too i love you too
girl i love you kiara
kelly
okay so i woke up today after a short
nap
and uh my nose was completely plucked
because
allergies i was like oh dear what what a
wonderful day for
my allergies to kick in
so yeah and then
plus the ceiling being leaking it's uh
it's been a it's been an interesting day
yeah um
thank you so much
so so so much
i i even like wrote like a small like
like like
like like points to cover in the opening
but i'm just like whoop
there goes there goes everything i
planned
and empty no thoughts
thank you thank you
i am i wanted to showcase as many fan
art
as possible um i was frantically
trying to like like save everything
into the right folders and make sure
everything was showing
i know i i couldn't showcase all of them
because some of them uh some of them
were
lost in the mountainous tweets and i
really did my best to uh
i really did my best to uh save
and showcase as many as possible but uh
make sure you guys check out
the yeah my art tag and like my birthday
stream tag
and uh check out all the different uh
creative submissions
all the gifts that everyone do for me
as well as um um
some sometimes they um
they gathered uh
in a big big project to display their
work
on the um
times squares billboard i know you can
check out
some of their artworks that was
displayed on it with the hashtag
taco times square i know they also have
a website that kind of explains the
project
um so please go check them out
i was i was really really um happy to
see
the community come together and put
together something so
special for me and uh and
i'm honestly at a loss of words
i sometimes say this but if i had
like i feel like i saved
i saved like the world
in my past that i don't remember that i
deserve such
such a blessed
i don't know how to explain it
uh i don't i really don't deserve
the kindness that you guys give me
um uh yeah
ah okay i'm fine i'm fine i'm fine
yeah it was really really cool i think
some uh
some people already like took uh
videos of it if you guys want to check
it out but if you want to see like the
individual entries they put it all
together
on the website and i think they also uh
the participants also
uploaded onto the twitter um as well
with the hashtag so
please go check them out it's wonderful
yes and um
yeah you know
you know
[Music]
i can't even talk properly
but um yes i forgot
i told you i was i was more nervous than
i was for the tv or the outfit review
stream i don't know what
i don't know why but yes
yeah i'll see i can never say enough
thank you
oh yes
okay i'm fine heavy breathing
yes
anyways um
yes thank you thank you so much thank
you thank you thank you
yeah my brain my brain is not working
right now
and um yeah
i mean it's not working i'm okay i'm
okay
i'm okay
so how how how's everyone doing today
did you guys
did you guys how you could get rest
can you drink
i honestly need to look at my cheat
sheet
what did i prepare for today
oh yeah we need we need karaoke
a little later i'll sing like maybe
three songs
oh yeah
[Music]
i um i had a pretty good good day today
actually
um i woke up
and oh no youtube
youtube youtube
okay don't die on me youtube oh
that scared me for a moment so my saw my
obs flashing red i was like
it's fine it's fine it's fine
underneath uh
bought a cake for me made a little bit
of the cake
it was a fruit fruit cake
what do you call it fruit and like
whipped cream the usual
basic cake but i was uh
really happy
yeah it was very yummy it was very yummy
and um and then
i was uh preparing for this gym
and then yeah
i always say honestly don't know what to
do
i have never panicked so much in my
lifetime
[Music]
it's like a prepared prepared so hard
but i don't know
i know i don't know what to do
[Music]
you said it's okay to come on
thank you
[Music]
in german we say not our financing we
say
uh alex it's a bit
long isn't it you lost me at it
okay okay repeat after me okay alex
alex
what
[Music]
let's
can i sing in german for you yes please
ok
[Music]
so
in german whole sides live and whole
slimes to live and time
is a hulk and then it goes on and on and
on like that i
don't know the rest of it it's okay i'll
just
i'll just like cut that part out of the
fall and just loop it
yeah i just love it i mean i want to be
honest the lyrics should be changing but
that's okay
hey how does it feel to be older
i have butterflies in my stomach and i
feel like i'm um
a puddle of jelly on the floor
yelling on the floor is not so good that
that
that's like you know dropping spaghetti
on the floor
i wouldn't really i mean i would maybe
still try to get like the top layer of
the spaghetti that dropped on the floor
but for jelly i would probably just
throw it away though i think on a scale
of a zero
to uh spaghetti
i think i'm a called lasagna
[Laughter]
yeah you know it's been such a long time
since i last talked to you
uh yeah my lasagna i i i don't
i don't know what kept me from eating my
lasagna
uh when it was still warm but yeah for
some reason i had to warm up my lasagna
um but i was still good it was still it
was very yummy still
[Music]
but i feel a lot better now that's good
it's you just you just have to
give yourself some more time to sleep
you know
cause i don't know did you tell them
that you only slept like two hours on
that day
uh baby i think you left
that fact i was i was just busy
preparing
for uh busy preparing for the streams
yeah
yeah yeah yeah so i feel like it was
totally understandable like if i would
if i would set my
alarm to ring like two hours after i
fell asleep i would probably also be in
such a deep slumber that i wouldn't hear
it you know
usually it would have been fine but i
somehow just you know
only set one alarm out of all the times
i could have only set one
yeah thank you did you mama did your
mama um
like notice the incident oh no i didn't
tell them yet
do they not like watch your streams and
stuff at all not not live i don't think
they probably watch
the archives sometimes when they get
really really really really really bored
when they run out of like netflix shows
too much
there's a lot of nice that's nice of
them
that's cute um wait i i have
one question yes now that you
are one year older is your name now
san nomaya inanes no it's
uh inanes
because nina maya is one ah
now and next year
okay okay okay it's getting very
complicated here
and we need some some people to explain
all of this to everyone else
because not everyone is as big brain as
you know
i think i think i already explained
before
written as kanji the lower stroke is
longer so it's
lower stroke longer stop it's not yeah
there you go flexing your japanese
knowledge you should do that more often
because a lot of people don't know how
good your japanese actually is
it's really good nihongo
jose
[Music]
i mean it because i it's not like you
only speak three words and i'm like oh
my hunger
you say you go to japan as a tourist you
say
ah arigato gozaimasu
[Laughter]
i like doing my grandma voice yeah so
you know i actually uh
i don't wanna like take too much time
but so i actually have something for you
now i wonder if you managed to
not notice what i was doing
you were totally drawing a cucumber
did you look into the stream i did not i
did not i did not
but you you you kind of knew what i was
doing so you just went
okay okay okay i mean did you notice
because of my twitter post
i noticed because there was cucumbers
and your tweet was
inna and you know
my my google
oh well i mean that's kind of good that
it was so obvious that it made you
notice and then not
not come to the stream that was the kind
of the effect that i wanted you not
coming to this video
[Laughter]
i recently uh originally got myself
finally
my new welcome cintiq 22.
it's really great and i did a drawing
stream yesterday the day before
yesterday before
i did the waiting stream on you
and i would like to show you the result
and
right now i'll i'll send it to you in a
private message you can
show it on stream if you want to of
course
just keep in mind this is the first time
that i've drawn in a long time so it's
kind of like
yeah rest resting you need to have more
faith in your art
it's very cute okay so here's the the
cucumber that i've drawn for you i hope
you like it
i was even eating cucumbers
you really should it's you and your new
outfit but with that with the other hat
i kinda
um personally i prefer that head
thank you let me show it off on uh
i didn't show the finished version yet
because i didn't get to finish on stream
[Music]
it was really fun to draw you you have
like a quite like
a simplistic but still very um
um how to say it like it's like so chic
you you have like such a stylish outfit
i don't know you just like it like
you're really cute artsy student
i love it so so cute thank you
it's a cute camera huh yeah you are
a cute combo
and i noticed that dark green really
suits uh like the rest of your outfit
dark green really harmonizes with it
so yeah that's my present to you i
finally i finally got back into art
and i will try to draw more from now on
finally i get to you know pay you back
for all the art you've done for me like
you you remember
the swimsuit art yes
and the one you used in your outfit
reveal right
[Laughter]
that's not showing up the glory of my
beautiful hourglass shaped body that i
normally have
what i mean you were beautifully shaped
like an egg
it was only very fluffy i like
fluffiness okay okay next time i'll make
it fluffy
so yeah oh once again happy birthday no
you're you're such a lovely person it's
great to like
work together with you and and and you
know stream with you
and hang out with you you're so calming
you're the sweetest person ever just you
have having you in our team
just gives it like a you you give up a
soothing soothing aura and we really
need that
so you are a very very important part of
halloween without you there would be no
balance and
you know we love you i'm gonna cry
thank you my feelings are broken for a
while
it's just it's just the rain
let's watch cats sometime soon and and
yeah
get get our cat game oh yes
[Laughter]
better be ready soon
[Music]
actually um said um
i'm not doing like a formal call-in but
if
friends are free they can join us and oh
god
kelly can you hear can you hear me
yes you know
i hope i hope you can hear this
thanks for waking up so early oh my god
good morning wait
no wait i can't hear it is it a recorder
oh no
[Applause]
this chord is blocking your recorder
beautiful recorder again
so i'm on my phone i learned how to play
happy birthday
god damn they don't want it it's okay
i'll use my inner inner uh telepathy to
listen to it
right now here you go
[Music]
[Applause]
is the best i can do for now that's the
best i can do
i'm so mad play it but it's fine we'll
have to
collaborate again on the recorder
someday and i'll play it i'll play it
right for you
a couple months later thank you you're
welcome happy birthday
ina happy birthday thank you kelly
yeah i hope it's a wonderful one
oh good any day for you
what happens it's been a blast wow that
uh
that that taco candy jar is going crazy
yeah it's uh
it's clipped at the top but uh it'll not
yeah
i mean there's something beautiful about
that though i just i got it
yeah like the kind of you know candy
that you get at grandma's size like hey
grandma
can i get a piece of that oh sure go
ahead youngin
yeah it's a very very friendly vibes it
suits your your soothing calm
aura you know the rare cali
yeah yes yeah grandma callie exists too
people underestimate grandma callie but
grandma callie mostly appears in the wee
hours of the morning when my
my voice is cracking um it actually
ended up working out decently well
because i i was working all night on
something anyway
so i had really fallen asleep yet so i'm
gonna fall asleep after this but
it's just really important to me that
that you know uh
how much uh how much you mean to
me and all the other en girls because
um you're our irreplaceable gen mate and
we have so many fun times together
and you work so dang hard and just
everything you do is just
fantastic and you have such a sweet
personality and yeah i just want i just
came here to gush really i just came
here to be your number one fan for like
a couple seconds
oh gosh thank you kelly i could honestly
say the same to you
and yeah
i've been thinking about i've been
thinking about it since you know since
you and
i guess somehow death sensei showed up
for my birthday i was like
no my god i hope ina is okay at the same
time i was thinking man i wish i could
do something cool
like like go to the go to the ancient
ones and be like
be like hey yo like transmit a message
through me to like sp
speak to ina but uh the ancient ones
were like nah not not this time
not this time man we got other stuff to
do so i was just like all right i guess
you know i can't one-up that but i can't
bring the power of my mighty recorder
but i guess uh the ancient ones also
didn't want
uh those frequencies interfering with
you and stream either
plan c baby just uh just
gush i guess about about how
how dope and amazing of a gem mate you
are so
you're the best my dude
yeah yes that's right it's perfect it's
perfect
it ended up working out okay um
but i can't wait to do more to do more
dope stuff together
and uh everything that that you uh have
planned for
for your future um ganbatte
and i support you i'm behind you 100 my
dog
oh thank you kelly i feel like i can go
against the world i'll take over the
world
too yeah i mean
elder a tourer and reaper we really are
kind of unstoppable you know
any any time anytime if we're together
uh we can probably uh slay thousands of
people we not that we want to do that
i'm just saying you know lots of
tentacles
you know i've got my scythe um it's just
it is possible
because for now i guess we can just
because
yes mortals but for now we can just have
fun streaming together
[Music]
yeah yeah heck yeah you enjoy the rest
of your day my dog i'm gonna let
the other girls drop by to say hi to you
but you take it easy
you be good to yourself and i know how
hard you've been working so make sure
you take a nice rest after this
okay that will do thank you kelly
you're welcome ina buh-bye talk to you
later tonight
bye peace peace
yeah i uh i'm so i'm so blessed
with my gen mates so blessed
oh yeah
[Music]
i'm so excited i i hope all of you guys
in chat are excited too for
announcements because we could finally
get something
from inaudible something to spend
money on something to buy
multiple versions of yeah
am i allowed to guess maybe just one
guess yeah one guess
is it blanket no it's not a blanket
you want to be wrapped in your tentacle
what
okay one of them is as comfy as a
blanket actually the other one might
become snuggy
but the big thing the big thing
i think bubba might like it too ah oh
it's a hint
[Laughter]
i can't wait to i don't even know what
it could be a bone
was eating melon earlier is it
watermelon
he likes watermelon okay noted but i
like watermelon
did you eat something tasty today for
your birthday yet i had
i had some soup and then i had some cake
cake what kind of soup um
egg soup oh i like that it's really soft
tasty
mmm nice yeah it is because it's so warm
and
yeah cozy i hope you guys eat more comfy
food
for your birthday after you after the
grand reveal of what i'm gonna get
yes i was gonna oh yeah i wanted to sing
because
kiara also sang in german and cali sang
in dut uh so i was gonna sing happy
birthday
uh in spanish yes
okay
[Music]
oh also i wanted to give you this not
really
a present but maybe
that's to um adjust your cup really easy
thank you i was like
maybe i should ask for help
for next time for next time really tasty
though thank you
oh yeah you know your
your streams are always like like such a
big
inspiration motivation i'm just like she
does so many
creative things i'm just like oh maybe i
can do this too
and then yeah honestly you're
you're amazing amazing thank you
yeah sometimes we'll talk about stuff
like cool different things to do in obs
and i feel like oh she actually used it
it looks really cool
[Music]
yeah and um
yeah thank you
you're welcome hopefully gooda when she
comes on next maybe she'll sing happy
birthday
[Laughter]
you have to beg her for it now
thank you for the idea all right i'll
let you go
bye-bye happy birthday bye
yay
i'm so blessed so so blessed
ah i'm not gonna cry no i'm not gonna
cry
[Music]
thank how do you feel
have your nerves calm down yet uh i
think so
as soon as i heard your you guys voices
i'm just like
oh i'm at peace
that's good lots of celebrating left to
do yeah
yes yes i can't stop looking at your
your candy john i know it's a little it
needs a little work but
no it's excellent it's excellent
packed full to the brim it's perfect in
the scuff department
oh i i know plenty about that yes
should i do what amelia said would that
be all right if i see you happy birthday
yes please can i do it like this
happy
[Music]
thank you happy birthday i saw yeah
i saw the uh the times square the build
did you stand next to the taco bell yeah
i was like it was like one of the first
things i noticed i was like wait is that
taco
absolutely incredible absolutely i think
not i think not
wait you said you had you had birthday
cake with fruit right
yes did it have like strawberries and
melons
the strawberries and it and the
cantaloupe and the honeydew were scooped
out in perfect circles
honeydew honeydew is the best melon i'll
thank you
oh yes that was mine for everyone
it's okay i come here i can hear your
thoughts
you can hear my saliva yeah
it smells
[Music]
the only one i can think of is you and i
say um
[Laughter]
[Music]
is slowly becoming one of my top used
yes actually although i think i'm
starting to use the oya oya in places
i'm not supposed to necessarily and i
feel like i might be making people a bit
confused
it's okay it's okay it shall become a
part of your
uh natural side of
i don't know quotes
oh yeah
[Laughter]
of course anything for you ina we all
love you very
very much and just like kiara said you
if
you bring balance you are such an
important part of the the en team and
and we would not be the same without you
you are the best
so i want to say thank you so much for
all that you do for us
and just all that you do in general
thank you for being you
yeah and i'm proud of you we're all
proud of you
and we all can't wait to see what you
get up to this year
it's the big year yeah we'll have lots
of fun lots of fun
yeah lots of fun exactly you know yes
um all the fun
okay thank you
of course i'm going to keep watching the
birthday stream
thank you and have a wonderful
wonderful day too thank you i'll chat
with you later
okay bye bye
not gonna cry no i'm okay i'm okay i'm
still okay yeah i'm still okay
yay oh my goodness i uh
i think like yesterday day before i was
like
i'm not having like a formal calling
stream
per se but um
if you guys if you guys happen to be
around that'd be
i'd be really happy if you guys could
make a
special appearance and uh
honestly i just say
okay i honestly
couldn't have asked for better gem mates
i say this all the time but
blink blink
i love you guys too
i told myself no the ceiling is gonna
break completely during the stream
and it did
okay i'm okay
ah i'm honestly blessed to be here
okay water
ah
you know next next segment was actually
going to be um
actually going to be karaoke but
my nose is completely plugged down
i don't think i can see
oh boy
i can sing uh
the duck stop where where
where where
okay
ah okay maybe maybe i can manage like
one or two songs
maybe
okay
okay i think i'm gonna go with two songs
i don't think i can manage
i don't think i can manage uh uh
maybe three maybe three but
um uh please excuse me if uh
if my voice is not as
a good as usual
but um
first song i will sing for you guys is
my brain is just empty i can't i can't
ah this is this is the worse than i
thought
but um okay first song i'm gonna sing
i've sang before i sang a couple of
times i think
it's a song with a lot of memories
it's a emmy's song
yes
yeah it's a song that uh got me through
a lot
so oh no go away cheers
so hopefully it's uh
okay
you
[Music]
my
oh
[Music]
um
is
[Music]
my
a
[Music]
my
is
[Music]
[Applause]
um
[Music]
[Applause]
um
[Music]
ah
this all never gets old honestly
[Music]
emmy songs uh helped me through a lot of
hard times
i had dr sina loop for so many years
and uh i hope i can sing it better
sometime but
um yeah thank you
thank you yay
i gotta i got i gotta make sure yago's
goes idle dream is achieved somehow
next song is uh
i think it's a little high for my my
voice but
i'll still do my vest
it's a uh it's a supercell swap
everyone probably heard about it before
but it's
why
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
i
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
know
[Music]
yes
me
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
laughs
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
is
[Music]
me
[Applause]
[Music]
it
so i was just told that the normal pgn
is running with my karaoke
[Music]
um
oh oh dear
don't worry about it it's okay uh at
least i won't
get um it's fine it's fine
okay at least at least i realized before
before the last song
because it would've been very
embarrassing if i did it for the last
song
ah so
um next song
my favorite favorite favorite whole life
song
you guys all know it you can sing along
to it
my favorite now
what
um
[Music]
i
oh
[Music]
um
my
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
is
[Music]
i
foreign
[Music]
yay
still needs a little practice but it had
uh it had my uh
my passion for hollow life songs
thank you thank you okay
ah man
what uh what a rollercoaster ride of
emotions
it really is really is ah thank you
[Music]
um again thank you so much everyone
for supporting me supporting my
teammates
i love how ian all of hollow knives i
love cover
i love i love youtubers i don't know
thank you
ah okay i am calm now
i think i'm back to my normal self no
more no more ceiling speaking
i'm good and my nose is back to
back to whatever normal state it was
it's not plugged anymore
it's all good and so
i think it's time it's time
to announce a few things
you guys ready are you guys ready
okay i'll start off
i have a couple of things to share with
you but i'll put kiara's
are you ready
yeah i i'm actually quite quite quite
quite worried about the uh
the shipping cost of
certain goods but
i hope i hope you guys like it but first
of all i will show you
i will show you i will show you
the arch for the birthday
oh it's covering my face but it's okay
you know my illness birthday celebration
2021 yay
i should have i should have gotten like
a clapping sound effect
but yes
the art as i promised is drawn by me
well at least uh
at least the um oh maybe i can move over
a little bit
oh no i'm clipping into the thing okay
should be fine yeah
hey guys are you guys are you guys ready
to see
see the rest hold on i need to
i need to fix my my screen a little bit
uh
excuse excuse myself
okay okay now i can move over
okay outside you can you can go away now
sorry
okay yay okay next slide next slide next
slide
okay first of three goods
is first of three cuts
it's a taco ground acrylic key holder
what is this you may ask what is this
acrylic key holder
well i drew up a quick picture to
explain how this works
uh let me let me just pull it up
um so everything
except the white bar and me
is transparent so you'll be able to take
selfies
with me with the key holder like this
yes they can take
selfies or you can take pictures of food
so it's a it's a key holder so you can
put on your backpack carry
carry it around everywhere travel the
world
take pictures of your daily life
yeah i always wanted i wanted like a
keychain or like
a like a postcard clear postcard i can
do this
and i was like maybe i can use it for
pretty good so
is that okay what's next
you guys might like this one you guys
will love this one i love this one it's
none other than
the taco decks hoodie
art drawn by none other and
[Music]
you can see it's kind of hard to see in
this uh this picture here
but there's all kinds
of taco that's why i saw taco dex
takutachi x or taco tex
and if you look closely oh my oh my
is that is that a takodachi in its
natural form
yes
now you too can wear inna goods outside
it's you guys yes
and uh there's two sizes large and extra
large so you can get
it's one of those like really comfy
comfy uh
comfy big hoodies you can wear all the
tacos
yes it's very comfy and uh
i even drew a special custom
tag this cooling tag so please don't cut
it off
i know you guys don't like clothing text
but don't cut it off
uh okay okay okay
yeah it's it's like really really soft
and uh yeah maybe
maybe i can ask if yago would wear it or
the sample and take a picture of it
yago clothing model
emma is it possible
okay okay okay jago sample
uh and my sweating okay maybe not
but okay okay
the next one though the next one the
next one is what i'm
mostly worried about
i'm very worried about the shipping for
the next one when i said
i was worried about the shipping
there's a reason it's uh
it's it's it's big literally
it's literally very very big
and um yeah i forgot to mention that i'm
wearing this hoodie in the
birthday art i drew it since it was
going to be the goods too
so yeah anyways okay are you ready for
the
last last goods
it's big i'm telling you it is
big that's why it is called
project kdtd
and kdtd sounds like
it stands for kusot
and it's kind of hard to see
um see it in this picture
but basically basically
let me let me explain this to you
i need to explain
okay this this picture is not to scale
it's just drawn in like it's drawn
in very which i say
very roughly but
very approximately it's a beanbag
cushion it's big
and the reason and the reason the
takorazi
has that face has that face and is
blushing
has his eyes open is because
you'll get sat on
so yep that's
uh
that's the that's why
it's either open it's splashing
originally it was gonna be the usual you
know takarazu face i was like hmm
how do i make this even more special
but if you don't know the context of the
space then it's just
it's just a cute taco you know but
you know if you know the context then
yes so basically
those are the um those are the uh three
cuts
and what's next
yeah i believe the
goods will go on sale on booth and geek
duck as
as per usual uh it will open
i forgot when like
in like an hour and a half hour
hour and a half
eight fifth eight jst
i don't know what time it is soon
like 30 minutes okay around 30 minutes
apparently
yeah it'll be
um on sale in around
30 minutes apparently i think yes
and um
i i did my best my best to
bargain the price of the base price of
the cushion
especially because of how
how big it is and i
really really really worry about the
shipping fee
i really do so um
i'm really sorry
but um yes
i did my best you can get them all as i
said
yes you can get them separately or you
can get it as a set so
yeah we did our best to keep it as cheap
as possible
it's like yeah i was like please please
i worry about the shipping please is it
possible to make it any lower
and yeah so
please take care of beanbag taco
taco that you come in all shapes and
sizes
in beanbags and plushie form that's to
be in the future but
please take good care of project kdtd
[Music]
yes yes
and um two so
there is a something else
i wanted to
get a not really announcement but
um see
since there is no voice pack
in the whole whole if you buy everything
pack
um i also wanted to
distribute you know lack of a better
word
the the art that was used for
the birthday uh announcement
as a wallpaper for everyone
um there's gonna be only three sizes
though no ultra wide sizes this time
sorry i couldn't prepare it in time
but um it'll be available for download
for
30 days i will give you guys a link
afterwards uh you can download it you
can use it
on your desktops and whatnot
it's for personal and non-commercial use
so yeah don't resell it
that's a no-no but um you can use
this new wallpaper just in time for the
summer you know
bright blue skies and white clouds
okay let me actually show you the
fall or huh it's only cropped on the
on the uh preview so
okay is
sit down oh let me
fit the screen there you go this is the
full art
wow blue skies whoa
and uh yeah and then in the birthday i
try to kind of incorporate like all the
uh
all the goods well minus the katakura
but i'm wearing the hoodie i'm taking a
picture
and i'm in my favorite place big bright
blue white skies mm-hmm
so i will be giving you guys a wallpaper
in a bit
i will leave the link i guess on twitter
and my community page and maybe in the
description
box and the link will be good for 30
days
and then it will self-destruct not
really i'll just
be disabled but same thing
and um yeah
that's it for now okay
i'll leave this here and uh
yeah that's uh that's
all wraps it up i think maybe
possibly
[Music]
oh wait
oh wait there's more
there's more i think
i think
uh a lot of people have been asking for
this
for a very long time and i've been
working on it really really really
really hard
the last couple of months along with
some of the most talented talented
people
and i guess
the video will speak for itself
[Applause]
[Music]
what was that
an original song coming soon
we're working very hard to finish it um
it's not quite complete yet but
soon soon gm
what do you guys think of the teaser
uh let me just uh let's see
uh
right here there you go
tada my first
original song violet is coming out
sometime soon i'll also be uploading the
teaser onto my channel as well so you
can
dissect it frame by frame
but um i just wanna
say uh big
big big big thanks to
um stevenson who
wrote the song um luminassan
who wrote the lyrics and worked on the
movie also uh
big special thanks to benikson for the
strings arrangement and big thanks to
me i'm kidding i will be working on the
art for the
art for the uh mv so
um as soon as we have more nice
we will announce it
but for now for now
just a teaser
and uh yeah
maybe i will
leave you guys around here i think i've
said
everything i needed to oh
wait the ancient ones
they're they're telling me something
uh-huh uh-huh ulta
i see i see
okay got it i want to tell you guys a
little story
about one of the goods one of the goods
uh let's let me scroll through
there's a story behind this hoodie
actually and the reason
papa worked so hard
to draw this for me i think i mentioned
it
in like a member stream before but um
the reason this was chosen
was because it was actually
a candidate for my new outfit
it was one of the candidates one of the
many candidates for a new outfit so
it could have been that i could be
wearing this hoodie right now
and uh i got permission from kravos papa
to show you guys
[Music]
this was going to be this possibly could
have been
my other outfit
hmm i could have matched cali wearing
pants
yeah i guess long long pants
carol has shorts shorts are a different
category
but yeah but when i saw the design i was
like
i can't choose how can i choose how can
i possibly choose from all these godly
designs
and i saw this hoodie i was like man i
would totally totally wear that
every single day and then i was like
is it possible if i could possibly get
this as
good one day and
voila we did it
yes thank you so so so so
so much
more
but yes that is why we got the hoodie
that's the goods
yay and now you can also wear it too
too much okay right here
oh yes isn't it so cute
i hope one day um one day
maybe we'll get even
cuter outfits
every time every time i like look back
at all the designs that kurovuchi papa
giving me for the
outfit i'm just like i want all of them
but i know i know it's not it's not
idealistic of me to ask
of karash papa for everything so
i'm just happy that that i can wear
wear this honey i'm so happy
but yes
[Music]
yes i am i am the moving
example of kuroshi papa's art
so i'll do my best and then more people
will look across choppas art
okay okay okay thank you thank you
everyone yay
[Music]
just a little longer for everything to
go on sale
on booth and geek
are they going on sale at the same time
i don't know but please look forward to
it
uh i'm i'm just
i just also want to take a moment to say
big thanks to everyone again um
it's it's been an amazing amazing
time since debut until now we made so
many good memories and so many
fun memories to you know make
in the future so um
i'll continue doing my best
so i can i can show you all the fun
things
all the happy things and
and we can all just you know
enjoy our time together
you know
ceiling is leaking again
thank you just thank you
i want to see so much more but i don't
think i don't think my tear ducts will
last
so yeah
ah i really really really appreciate it
and uh i'll see you guys
the next team in the stream after in the
stream after and then
after let's all
enjoy
all life
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you
please look forward to to
the original song too will be um
after i end the stream the teaser will
be up
on the channel um i don't know if it's
gonna be a premiere or not i forget but
if it's the premiere then the premiere
itself is gonna be longer than the
actual
15 seconds of footage
but yes um
i hope that
i hope that um i know like
individuals it's kind of hard to you
know quote unquote change the world but
i think if i leave
a little bit of a
positive impact on the community than
my job is done and
i think i think i'm on the right track
thanks to you guys
thank you always and
uh i'll see you next stream
yeah yeah next
tomorrow is the birthday but the day
after we'll do a little bit of a chill
chatting stream
talking about laughing at laughing at me
future is gonna feature ina is gonna
laugh at me for
her crying so much but
but we will have a chill chatting stream
but until then thank you so so so
so much i
how many say how many times did i say
thank you because it's never enough
but um thank you
and i will see you guys next time have a
good
rest of the day morning afternoon
evening
uh grab something yummy to eat get some
good rest
and i'll see you back here next stream
until then until then
take care and bye bye
bye
you