[Music]
thinking
go
hello one second let me go call i need
to go call gura and amelia into the room
i need to go call gura and amelia into
the room i was like ha ha
no scuff let me let me go get him real
quick they're here they're here
there they are i knew you guys were here
you were just hiding what were you doing
under the table
um did you drop something they were uh
they were good and you're so small
hey who's satori
[Music]
you have such wide range of motion
oh my goodness
hello can you guys hear us okay
[Music]
hey i tried to kick your reiki
i tried i tried to normalize the volume
as much as possible
as long as you guys hear them over the
background music
that is what is important so everyone
each individually go ahead and say hello
first starting off with gura ah
tell me this i am and i'm excited to
roleplay
yeah excellent
yeah yeah okay now let's see
next up let's go with kiara yes it is
i am i'm the phoenix from her life
english i don't know if you knew
uh i have a past
of playing uh a ttrpg before
uh what yes yes yes
a long time ago with my family with all
of my family
in in a family circle we played the
ttrpg and
dungeons and dragons or something like
that but it's so long ago i barely
remember it
but i think this will be fun
heck yeah i actually didn't know that
kiara
i had no idea i think oh i remember you
said that you had experience but i
didn't know that it was
that it was uh d wow
indeed it was i think yeah dang you
might be better at this than me
no no no no i only played i never i only
played like for a few rounds and
we didn't go on for too long and it was
not me who was the the
the game master oh i see i see
i don't know wow well i hope that you
enjoy playing this game with us today
i mean we're not we're not really
playing too much today we're focusing on
character creation but i hope that you
enjoy the campaign i hope it
hopefully lives up to the hype i'll try
my best
all right next up we got ina ina say
hello
hello i'm uh you know my indanies
uh from paula english yes uh
i'm very excited and nervous at the same
time first time
playing gtrpg actually this was one of
my uh one of my uh
goals and dreams during my debut
so i'm very excited to finally have
video with you guys
yay i'm so glad yeah that makes me
really happy quiet
i it's weird you know because i always
have you turned up to 200
it's just my voice is quiet hello so
sorry everyone else is like at 130
percent
but but yours 200 i don't know i'm not
i'm
not sure what it is i'm not sure either
actually
yeah i turned down the bgm quite a bit
though so hopefully it'll be okay
um ye um just maybe
shout every once in a while
it's okay yeah give us a good what to
get your attention and we'll
we'll all make sure we listen very
closely 300 the taco i can't
discord doesn't give me that power it's
a it's all right
you should leave my voice a little
higher too on my side yeah it's okay
on the quieter side no problem and and
you know what chad
can can prime their listening ears okay
listen up
chet you listen you zone in those ears
into ina
okay do your best gum bots you can do it
come on
and let's see finally we got watson
say howdy watson hello i'm amelia what's
up hello someone detective uh
i'm a little sleepy but uh i'm looking
forward to this yeah i
am i've played a ttrpg very very briefly
before and it was like a
campaign that somebody had made
themselves so uh yeah i kind of suck at
role-playing but i'll try my best
ye no worries sleepy or zippy
are you sleeping or is sipping oh yeah
sleepy
oh okay cuz okay did i say it did i say
it no no i thought sippy because also
you were so so very energetic in the
beginning of your breathing i thought
you were maybe a tiny bit
tiny tiny bit um drinks
[Laughter]
i mean we certainly can bring out the
drankies i mean check out all the stuff
that i've got
is it coffee yeah like coffee tea that
kind of thing
i'm actually going to go ahead i'm going
to go ahead and link
um the artist who did these amazing
background assets and is going to be
continuing to do um going to be
continuing to do all of the background
art for this campaign
uh who actually did uh amelia's
office art yeah go ahead oh
he's really good yeah really really love
um this person's works let me go ahead
and
throw that twitter in the description
all right eg art
and there you go definitely go check out
uh
their stuff go give it a look heck yeah
all right and with that being said um i
guess for the most part
um we got everything kind of set up so i
guess i'll briefly explain
the way that the the setup is for here
uh so we have what's going on there's a
little summary in the upper
uh left-hand corner for people that just
drop in
and i'll be actively updating it
depending on what's going on
in the campaign
yup smart yeah uh and then
and then we have scene where i will be
putting uh
some art related to i guess wherever the
characters are hanging out
that kind of thing so you guys can get
invested in the scene
um and then we have off to
the right uh the roll the roll area
which is where you will be able to see
the dice that we roll right now you guys
can't
um it's fine because it's not super
necessary right now
we're getting some stuff worked out uh
so that so that we can show you that
soon hopefully in time for the first i
guess
tutorial session and definitely the
first main session so please anticipate
that
yeah and that's the basic layout
um by the way you guys may notice that
there's a logo that says dark pack
yeah so we have been very graciously
allowed to
to stream our playing of this game um by
a world of darkness
um they very kindly
thank you so much thank you because they
very kindly were like hey yeah please
play our game
um so really recommend that you check
out uh world of darkness
stuff um i'll be putting some links in
the description um once i get
a little more time uh after i'll throw
them in there for you guys to check out
oh they're here hello
hello world of darkness world of
darkness is high oh man
no it's okay i'm not nervous i'm not
nervous at all this game has very very
close to my heart
um it is it is my first it was my first
tabletop rpg experience
uh under the vigil was my first
ever um and i feel like it's
it's much easier to get others um kind
of invested
in it um it's probably the easiest to
jump into in my opinion
so hopefully we'll all have a lot of fun
together but today
today it's about you ladies it's about
your characters
um
i'm gonna explain to you guys everyone
in chat uh and you guys
everyone watching today what exactly a
tt rpg is because i still feel like
there are some people that don't know so
we'll keep it pretty brief um i know you
know i know what it is
all right because what's the ttrpg it
said
i repeat between friends
[Laughter]
i mean you're not wrong you're
definitely not wrong
sorry i will say that is that is correct
all right
kiara's not wrong um though
it actually actually stands for tabletop
role-playing game you guys knew that
because it's already knew that but that
was a that was a good description kiara
that is technically what this
is um so it's also known as some people
may know it as a pen and paper role
playing game but you know pen and paper
not exactly required
um so basically it's a form of
role-playing game in which the
participants
describe their characters actions
through speech and the participants
determine the actions of their
characters based on their
characterization
and the actions succeed or fail
according to a set
system of rules and guidelines so within
the rules
players have the freedom to improvise
and their choices shape the direction
and outcome of the game
often times they're conducted like a
radio drama
so basically only the spoken component
of the role is acted a lot of
a lot of times you guys will be speaking
as your characters
um without even saying like okay i'm
going to speak as so and so
now i'm going to speak as bob you just
you just speak as them
role play right exactly yeah but we all
will be able to tell the difference
between when you're in character and out
of character
hopefully if we can't hey that's that's
probably part of the fun it's okay
we'll we'll roll with it you know um
and so yeah every system is different
for the most part
um like for example chiara you said that
you've played dnd well world of darkness
is
is quite different i would say for
example one big difference is that we
use
d10s not d20s ah
do you guys know what is that a detail
it's a d10 all right
so a d10 well a d20 you know is a
20-sided die
right oh yeah a d10
is a 10-sided die so d just stands for
dice exactly
okay yeah yeah um so the main
yeah we'll be using d10s for this system
um
and basically rolling those dice will
determine uh your ability to perform an
action um so i'll go ahead and go on to
the next
the next big difference the setting the
setting
the world of darkness so this is
literally coming from the world of
darkness side i'm going to read it to
you guys
okay okay all right i'm going to do a
little
music change there we go
that's not the one i wanted this is the
one i wanted all right here we go
now
get that gm voice going what if
monsters were real
not as abominations lurking in the
shadows but cunning predators hiding in
plain sight
influencing every aspect of our world in
ways we would never dare to imagine
what if you became one of them
what if you didn't i added that in
myself because you guys are going to be
humans however
however enter the world of darkness
in the world of darkness vampires
werewolves and monsters of many
different kinds are all living among us
an entire supernatural world hidden in
plain sight
that is the description from the website
smoke hey i knew someone was gonna say
that
i knew it here goes the chat there they
go
i mean i probably am going to be the
most sus to be honest because i mean as
a gm it is definitely my job to look for
ways to destroy you guys
i'm just kidding just kidding i'm your
friend
i'm on your side don't worry
definitely not going for a full party
wipe it's all good
hey i had to check my coffee really
quick
so basically um hunter the vigil
uh takes place in this world of course
you guys are hunters
what does that mean well let me go into
this little description that i came up
with myself
here we go so
imagine now for a moment you are your
characters all right
only for this second you don't got to do
it the whole time just you know hold on
to it like 30 seconds or so here we go
you were all normal human beings once
just living average lives blissfully
unaware of anything at all the true
nature of the darkness
lying upon the underbelly of each of
your worlds
once things were simple but now they
ain't and that's the biggest thing to
remember in all of this
this big mess of a predicament you found
yourselves in
for example if only you hadn't moved to
that old
rickety house in the corner for a
quarter of the price just to realize the
landlord didn't tell you about the
demons that never left the ancient
burial ground below it
oh no that was familiar
if only you hadn't stumbled into that
club of cute boing boing ons only to
realize the owner is a vampire gangster
and the ladies
well they ain't exactly human either
might be a good thing though it's kind
of hot i was gonna say and
[Laughter]
well say for example again if only
you hadn't been rummaging around in an
old alleyway for scraps of food
only to discover this neighborhood's
night watch is a band of werewolves who
aren't so keen on your kind and what
they've done to their city
things could have been normal but now
they aren't
and it's because you figured out a
little secret
nothing is as it seems monsters walk
i'm not gonna say it again they walk
with us
they walk beside us
they're doobie monsters out there and
now
things will never be the same for you
guys
but you're a lucky bunch you know
because the timing of it all was on your
side
you don't gotta go through this alone it
turns out
three other strangers are right there
with you
each of them encountered something truly
frightening
something supernatural
unable to return back to the doldrums of
that boring
blissfully boring and ignorant life you
search for a new way to exist
to keep up the vigil in the end you
realize that there really was only one
answer
to embrace it that cool with you guys
are you cool with embracing it
i would love to embrace it should we
roll for that
now what kind of embrace
nothing comes after that listen welcome
to your cell pray you earned the
strength to find the key to breaking out
of it
hopefully together the the set this
embrace wow that was fast i mean i mean
hopefully they will maybe they won't
maybe they'll die in the tutorial
session that's cool too hey i'm fine
with that
oh no the uh the is a place
it's a play on words here so it could
sound like prison cell right
but you see there are actually uh three
tiers of organization in hunter society
okay first you've got cells basically
um there's there's the basic human human
human
unit hunter unit
humans a huge unit of hunter society
typically a small group of people who
defend their neighborhood or community
so there may be there may be several
cells for example operating in a city at
one time
so you guys are a small hunter cell
apparently ah right next up
on the next level you've got compacts
yeah exactly
though yeah one whole brain cell between
between the four of you
yeah we're used to it yeah so after
cells are compacts they're basically the
second tier
of organization found in hunter the
vigil so they're
basically organized cells of hunters
dedicated to a common purpose but
still compared to conspiracies they're
pretty much baby town
you know they're they're new unstable
the members fight a lot
they're easy to find and join but you
know
it's still not quite conspiracy exactly
is it worth it exactly you guys may
encounter several
compacts as well as conspiracies along
the way other hunters that are doing
their jobs
right so the conspiracies are the
highest tier of hunter society
and they've got a lot of resources
they're run by very powerful people
and their reach can extend across the
planet so do be careful
hopefully they're friendly um so with
that being said
ladies welcome to myth breakers campaign
that's what we've decided to call it for
now
yeah oh wait i like that i was laughing
because i was thinking mythbusters up
dare we ask for the okay to use
mythbusters i think breakers off to work
busters oh we're singing ghostbusters
[Music]
the myth the myth breakers campaign is
basically this this campaign but overall
the game itself is is hunter myth which
is why you guys can use
hunter myth on twitter to talk about uh
your impressions of the game and what's
going on
that sort of thing we'll put all the
hashtags out there
uh towards the end yeah
so each one of you will encounter a
supernatural being that will open your
eyes to the world of darkness you never
knew existed anyone here seen the matrix
by chance yes yeah yeah
okay here let me explain to you what
happens then so basically there's a dude
that's living like a normal life and
whatever and he gets presented with a
blue pill and a red pill
and he can choose to take the blue pill
and he'll wake up again in his bed
and just keep living his normal life or
he takes the red pill
and spoilers god the matrix has been out
for a long time
takes the red pill and discovers um that
actually all of humanity has been
enslaved by machines
and he's actually living um in a pod
completely naked along with the rest of
humanity
um and was pretty much birthed in there
and uh machines are using humans for
energy
and so he breaks out and joins uh a
force of people trying to stop that
it's all because he took the red pill
right things as they seemed that's where
the meme comes from
exactly yeah don't take the red pepper
oh
i see okay yeah no problems that's
that's basically
you guys have you guys have forcibly
forcibly taken the red pill
uh into monster society world of
darkness society you didn't know that
supernaturals existed until now
and the only way that you can cope is by
keeping up the vigil
what does that mean you'll find out
later but let's let's go ahead and get
into this character creation you guys
sound good okay all right
[Music]
so character creation is really
important we're gonna go
hop over here all right here we are so i
have my example character sheet
character creation is important here
obviously
we are largely focusing on role play
though i will say this one time
just need to give this little disclaimer
to you guys um
we will be using uh the system of course
as it is written
um as as a very helpful guide for us on
our journey however
role play is king in the games that igm
if the characters can come up with
a very clever way to get out of a bad
situation
um even a fail can pass as a success if
they are clever all right very important
nice clever being clever
yeah we're good at that being clever was
never my forte
uh i'm sure it'll be fine you'd be
surprised man
you'd be surprised who could say who
could say what your character will come
up with
all right so i can probably read a
little bit more from the book later but
right now i want to get you guys into
the
into the character creation zone so to
speak
all right so let's go ahead and pull up
your
hunter the vigil sheet you ladies uh got
this all prepared right
yes yes excellent
wonderful so i'll be creating one thing
yeah
i'll be creating a sample character
along with you guys
yeah so okay we're going to first
however
uh go around the room and i just want to
hear
the most basic of basic things that you
guys have planned
for your character you don't have to
have any big plans for them or even a
detailed description
it could be something like washed up
detective um
veterinarian hey why'd you giggle girl
what was that giggle for i got that um
you could be fast food restaurant owner
who's that you callie uh
yeah yeah that's who i was obviously
referring to kiara
you could be um you could be just
a um i don't know a a child
who is really good at drawing okay
you're not a child you know but
sometimes i like you like oh you're so
small
it's the first thing i thought of chad
who's the first you could be
um kiara ah you can
yeah baby kiara that's what i was
referring to i mean kiara is good at
drawing that's what i was talking about
i can legit be baby kiara here's my
oh man here we go here we go this is all
your fault guys this is your fault
don't don't you blame me
[Music]
i'll put it away before people go crazy
no it's okay it's okay we are all in
good fun
lastly i was i was gonna say you could
be you could be
many thousands of years old shark girl
from the ocean but then i realized wait
a minute
you can't humans okay you literally
can't
this is tough for some of us so but you
guys you guys basically get the gist so
let's go around the room
and hear what you guys kind of have
planned if anyone would like to
volunteer to go first
me okay let's see what you got okay
don't everybody
i was just reading the air in the room
for a moment and was like okay
like five seconds of silence
okay so do i just start with uh giving
you my description
oh sure go ahead whatever you have
you'll be happy to hear it
okay listen up everyone so the name is
maybe not final
but um okay
is the young woman who trains and owns
crows and owls i don't know if i
pronounced that correct oh grows in owls
yes we wait for it
uh she grew up in another continent in a
rich family where she had a pet owl
called
um i think maybe my german viewers will
understand
which is her favorite and still follows
her to this day
she also knows how to use guns and
carries two
with herself because her brother is a
hunter
but she herself does not like to fight
very much she mostly does it
to protect herself and her birds she
originally came to this continent to
find
more rare species of birds and you know
train them and own them
since she came from a different
continent however she doesn't speak
uh this language here perfectly and
communication
communication issues arise sometimes
also her clothing style seems foreign
and out of place so she gets a lot of
weird looks
um she's more a quiet type of person who
doesn't trust people easily
she has a habit of forgetting where she
puts things but usually her owl knows
what she's looking for
and brings it to her she also doesn't
understand technical stuff much and
doesn't know how to use her phone except
for taking cute photos of her birds
the end wow
that was so detailed
[Laughter]
but i'm trying to give i mean i'll
definitely work more on it but i'll
i tried to give her already some kind of
hints of personality and hints of
um negative traits like her forgetting
things and her not being
perfectly able to communicate um
stuff like that that will you know that
she will not be overpowered later on
but she also can fight because she uses
guns because you know there are reasons
for
why she uh yeah is is this kind of
person
wow you did
okay
wow that was very detailed you thought
so much about that i can already see
your character
coming to life in the world that i have
planned that is amazing thank you
okay very well done all right who's next
on the chopping block i mean
i mean who's who's next to share with
the class
i'll share it i saw mine okay watson
goblin like conspiracy nut who
uh is here to dismantle
the system as much as they can yeah
a little sleazy you know
that's that's all i have that is perfect
that is
that is the perfect system
oh this is going to be fun i can already
tell we're going to have some good
interactions with watoto
oh yeah more communication uh problems
yes yes
i look forward to your interactions with
the others this is gonna be fun the only
thing
is
turns out that vatoto is not one of the
hunters but is one of the monsters that
we're supposed to use
nobody knew the whole time
[Music]
absolutely perfect watson very good
very good all right who's who's next
hi kanga all right gura let's hear what
you've got
uh planned ideas are a little uh spread
out still
okay um i don't really know exactly what
i want to do but the idea i have is i
want to do a
because i want to i want to role play
this character really well i want to do
a
uh a dark mystery lady
who i have written down here i've been
writing down in my notebook uh
i have like the shadows right so
she either she moves like the shadows or
she stays in the shadows
predominantly wow uh as i was thinking
about her profession and i don't know if
she's either she's either gonna be a
traveling banjo bard
or potentially some type of mercenary of
some sort but i don't really know quite
yet
oh neat that's awesome i mean in the end
if you want if you want uh she can be
both even
yeah yeah we can work out the details
later but that's already a fantastic
start
oh great yeah just just knowing um like
a basic idea can really help you out
when we start assigning skills and that
kind of thing so that's a great start
gura
yay good good good and finally we've got
ina
so i was i was thinking about maybe
having
a not a scientist type character
in reality they're just a very tired
grad student
i love that and uh they're like
scientists and inventor so they can like
make stuff on the fly but
you're kind of i guess they have a
pessimistic
way of looking at life but
and then but they think that uh you know
all the uh
all the monsters and stuff they can't be
as scary
or dark as the confines
of human society that's it
that is really neat actually good
scientist is good to have in our team
yeah we'll be super helpful
so wait so wait wait wait i fight with
guns
you know maybe has some scientist stuff
good on
did you say what you would maybe could
could possibly
use in the fight either your weapons or
anything
you don't have any weapons nothing in
the venue
i don't think about it now though yeah i
mean really long nails
[Laughter]
i already love this character well you
see girl you've got quite a few options
so
for example you could have your
character be very good at punching
things
um yeah there's a whole range
like in the shadow should be like a good
like assassin kind of you know
sneak behind oh yeah
okay i was thinking about having her be
a
career a male person somebody with a
male and they could do something like
some kind of power with
mail like paper paper or something
something i don't know my brand's style
i see
cards something like that oh god
the paper cup is scary
uh i don't know i'm gonna stop talking
this is a big thing no
no no i think it's a great idea it's
always great to have
some starting point and then over time
you'll gradually
kind of be able to i guess um better
better um adjust to the character and
you'll figure out how to play them
perfectly maybe around session
two and a half or so that's how it was
with me so you don't need to figure
everything out
immediately um but as long as you've got
a base and it sounds like you've got a
great starting point
all right so we're going to go ahead and
dive into these
uh character sheets and we'll show each
of your character sheets at the end
so first off let's start with the easy
part
um i say easy part but it may actually
be one of the harder parts
this part right here that says name
player chronicle virtue vice concept
profession compact conspiracy it's the
very top
right okay that's where we're gonna
start
so you guys can leave some things blank
because honestly i feel like this
information
might even be like the harder stuff to
decide upon and you may want to take
your time on it
um but for the sake of example i'm going
to go ahead and name my character chat
what's the name of my character
[Music]
what's the name of my character chet
let's see what they come up with
and player is going to be cali so you
guys can go ahead and write your names
okay right here chad all right chad
your character's name is chad and um
he's a chad there you go
yeah that was surprising i'm not
surprised at all it's it's my chat
um so let's see after that um let's skip
chronicle for now
go to virtue advice
virtue and vice what do you guys think
that stands for
uh your your purity your intentions
your why why is so funny
that
we're going to go with um the
the seven there there are seven main
virtues and vices just to keep it nice
and easy for you guys
if you want it's quick exactly uh seven
is it the seven deadly sins i think so
yeah
so let me go ahead and actually look
them up
to give you grass or sloth exactly
my middle name let me see if i can find
an easy place to just throw to you guys
so here you go
actually
and i'll send it in the main chat
there you go you guys can use this list
to just keep it nice and easy
so we've got for virtues charity faith
fortitude hope justice prudence and
temperance
for vices we have envy glutzny greed
lust pride sloth and wrath
these will be important later on because
your character
can get special bonuses i will explain
later if
they take an action that is related to
either their
virtue or their vice
[Music]
so it's important
interesting okay yeah
so chad uh
not definitely not temperance 100 not
prudence
um let's go with justice
justice no actually let's go with
fortitude fortitude is a good one
uh if you have like a really hard time
coming up
with which one to do because it
basically just means
the will to push through tough things
so i go with prudence yeah
i was gonna ask is prudence is there
like a generally a safe option
and the rest are more uh taking greater
risks
for does that make sense yeah i
definitely
i get what you mean if you look at the
the link that i sent you
in particular um for example looking at
fortitude
um usually possessed by detectives
philosophers scientists priests
true believers etc um you know
other names there are other names there
and then also willpower gained is the
important part
so willpower is going to be uh important
in this game
um i'm not gonna i'm not gonna say how
yet though you guys will you guys will
see in game
but you want it is the thing the
character is able to withstand pressure
to sway from a chosen course
or diverge from long-held ideals so
you see that they're they're leaning
into their their virtue
right so if your action reflects that
if your action shows that you have
fortitude
um for example you withstand something
very difficult
then you will gain willpower i will give
it to you
so if you think that you're going to
play your character in that kind of way
where they'll be in that kind of
situation often withstanding
really tough things like that um then
you want to choose fortitude i would say
i see yeah
i'm going for prudence and pride and no
i'm not going for lost
chat i'm not trying to make uh
i'm trying to make a different character
and even if i was making kiara it
wouldn't be less shut up
oh you guys maybe chad is the true
bottom left hold on hold on a minute
let's see let's see for example i want
chad as a vice uh to have sloth because
a lot of times instead of going out and
doing the mission
chad will stay at home playing pool and
cracking open cold ones with the boys
because chad is in
a fraternity there you go what a useless
dude can you take him out already
you guys will get a chance to i'm sure
but for now chad is here to stay
yeah now next concept
this is also pretty open-ended but first
have you guys kind of decided virtue and
vice you don't need to decide
immediately but
i haven't seen it okay great so for
concept this one's also not
too difficult you basically come up with
it in your own words it's
basically a short description of your
character so
for chad um shitty fraternity boy
yeah you can make it as descriptive or
non-descriptive as you would like
i think there's an actual word for that
which one was it alchemist
yes
is there a limit to this can it be one
long
concept or sure
i mean if you want if you want as much
as you can fit into that small space
go for it
maybe falcon punch is my super attack
all right hold on i'm looking at
something real quick
a profession is the same thing for me i
think
kind of there's a job right
yeah looking ahead sensei
good that's fine for profession i'm just
gonna put no
have you ever like worked the head on
your homework and then like you realize
it's all wrong for you to like
sadly erase everything i had to do that
no no i didn't have to do that
that's the entirety of this stream for
me so far is oh wait
that's okay it it happens i remember i
was the same in the beginning too i did
not know what was going on i remember
the character creation stream for my
original group of friends playing this
game took like five hours but i know
that we won't take that long
it'll be fine all right and i guess
uh for chronicle let's just let's just
put myth breakers
for now oh okay yeah because at least
the way that that me and the homies did
it back in the day is we just put the
name of
our game that we were playing so just do
that because obviously you know
we've got the other details of the
campaign down so just just the name of
our
of our game and compact and conspiracy
you guys haven't decided on a name yet
for your group so just leave it blank
okay
yep so we've got that part done
now we go on to the fun part
yeah so this part is a little more
technical
so i'm gonna i'm gonna explain and i
will re-explain as many times as you
guys need me too
hi sensei all right okay
so we're going to work on attributes
this thing here attributes now
let me explain first the dice rolling in
this game
you guys have d10s right how many d10s
though
do you have do you know do you know how
many dice you're rolling
no exactly you don't because
because we haven't put the dots in yet
we haven't assigned the dots
however many dots you have for a certain
role
will reflect how many dice you roll when
you're performing in action
that's cool so for example say that you
want to do
one of the most central roles in this
game which is a perception check
perception check is basically to look
around you roll to look around and see
what the f word is going on
sanity check yes
a little different but the the the the
sentiment is there
so basically the perception check is
going to be your wits
plus your composure
dots so for example say that you have
this is just for example you have to
resolve
and three composure dots
when i say rule perception you you do
the math
resolve two plus three composure you
roll five d10s
and basically um how many successes you
get
from that role will determine whether
the the action
succeeds or fails kind of thing
we'll go more in depth a bit later but
just so you know what you're doing
like why you are signing dots into
different areas i suppose it's important
that you know that that's how it works
do we have a limited amount of thoughts
that we can fill in
yes oh wait why did i put myself no it
was it was wits in composure you guys
are right sorry about that
um yes you are limited you are limited
so if you go down to the bottom of the
sheet
and read the fine print down here
attributes five four three
what that means is that let's see
for each box you can either have five
four or three dots assigned to the box
for example let's take chad chad
is a chad who is very social so for
presence manipulation and composure
i'm going to put the five here i have
five dots to spend in this particular
area
uh chad is not really the brightest
light bulb in the box
so for intelligence wits and resolve
we're gonna put
three only three dots to assign to chad
there
and when it comes to strength dexterity
and stamina chad can hold his own in a
fight i guess
so we'll go ahead and give him four
or in each uh four for the whole box
so for example strength dexterity and
stamina i have four dots to spend where
am i going to put them
well chad has quite a bit of dexterity
so we'll give him two dots
more in stamina and then two more in
strength but he's just not very
dexterous
so it looks like this
let's say for intelligence wits and
resolve
um chad doesn't have a lot as i said
before not really the brightest light
bulb in the box but he can be a little
witty
so we'll give him two dots in wits and
put one in resolve
that's three dots what is it sorry what
is it
what does um how would you describe
presents uh presents is
let's see that's that's a tough one
you're kind of it'll be more
involved in roles where you are you are
trying to do an action
um that really puts yourself out there
for example a musical performance
you would roll presence plus expression
so you'd want more
dots and presence or perhaps you want to
persuasion it can go either way i think
it might be a manipulation rule if you
want to persuade someone
to think a certain way or do something
but basically yeah charisma
for the most part with presents you're
really putting yourself out there
it's it's chemistry yeah it's similar i
would say
okay can i put all points into one
yeah that's called min maxing watson
um you're you're very focused on a
certain area of your character
um and that's totally fine too have fun
go for it
manipulation yeah sure whichever
whichever one you want
get
[Laughter]
[Music]
how would you describe resolve um let's
see
so resolve is basically your your will
to do something
in a pinch when your chips are down um
inside you still have your resolve
at the end of all of it and wits is
being smiled
wits is in in my personal description of
wits it's being smart in the moment
oh huh just like being more like okay
exactly
one more time sure sorry
that's okay what would you like an
explanation on everything uh
just the splitting the points per box
okay sure so the rule is five four three
um oh okay okay yeah so if you actually
um i don't you girls can't see
my sheet i'm hoping maybe you can pull
up youtube uh so that you can see it
there
um but yeah three four five so there are
three boxes
and so each one is split up um to where
you can put either five dots
four dots or three dots um into each box
so you have to decide what your strength
is going to be so for example your
character
gura um you said you were going to
choose someone kind of mysterious
yeah so maybe she doesn't need to be too
strong in
presence manipulation and composure you
want a little for example manipulation
might be helpful
so maybe in that box you put three
three dots because it's your weaker your
weaker um
role i suppose broken
oh no are you are you using the pdf the
editable pdf thing
yeah dang it ah okay i'll just take a
screenshot later and
color it in okay sounds good
um but then say for example um
if you're going to be doing uh sneaky
things gura
maybe you want to have five um
in the box that has strength dexterity
and stamina
so that you can be very dexterous
or intelligence with resolve you could
do five
as well okay
yeah cuz it's up to you pretty much
um for chad we're gonna go ahead and put
um
let's see um presents
he's he's chad so we're gonna give him
we're gonna max the hell out of chad in
presence
we're going to give him three dots um
in presence and then one in manipulation
and actually no we'll put two in
manipulation because he's got to haze
the newbies
um and composure is just one dot because
you know chad freaks out sometimes so
looks like this yeah
okay okay okay yeah
so if you guys want like a visual idea
of what it looks like
um hopefully hopefully you can see okay
on youtube it's not too pixely or
anything but
basically looks like this
any questions
nope i think it's clear okey-dokey
for me i finished
yay nice
wait wait i one more question what is
resolve what is there
what do we do so resolve is basically
just it's the will
to uh to like take an action and like
kind of stand through difficult things
um
for example this will be a really
helpful stat when
like someone is or like a supernatural
or another person is trying to
manipulate you
or using some kind of special power that
kind of thing i'll have you
do like a resolve check kind of thing
so yeah some resolve
okay thank you yes it will be very
useful
um and yeah i guess
i guess that's about that's about it huh
for the attributes
okay okay now we're gonna go to the next
really fun part which is skills
gonna really start thinking about your
characters here so for skills
again like attributes we have three
sections
okay uh this time they're labeled
mental physical and social
skills okay
okay yeah i feel that
so minus one unskilled yeah we have my
life
and that will be important later by the
way that part
so so for your skills like attributes
remember we had 543 for skills
we have eleven seven four oh
so it's pretty much the same situation
here
for social skills chad is chad so i'm
gonna put 11
in social um
um mental not so great
i'm gonna put four dots in
mental skills and seven in physical
[Music]
so let's see let's right so once you
guys figure that out it'll be
kind of easier to assign the dots but
you should put a bit of thought into it
because this will directly
this is what makes up your roles in the
game
yeah so let's see um
for example chad with them social skills
um chad's expression i think i will
definitely do
many roles that involve expression so
let's go ahead and put maybe i don't
know just for now
we'll put two i'd like him to be
well-rounded
uh two two dots in expression
maybe one in intimidation for times i
want to intimidate
others you know to do like hazing and
whatnot because i'm chad
um persuasion one dot
socialize is gonna be three dots because
you gotta socialize those frat parties
uh streetwise and subterfuge i don't
really need
um dude has like no empathy but i have
so many dots so i might as well
kind of make this guy super powerful and
socialize he'll put
another dot in there maybe one in
subterfuge
probably doesn't know his way around the
streets kind of likes dogs so i'll put
one dot an animal ken
one two three four five six seven eight
nine ten
and then i'll put one more in uh
intimidation
eleven i've used up all the dots
ah i see what does
subterfuge mean it means being real
sneaky
usually doing things like um i know
that's larceny
um being it you're a good liar
real good liar
what would expression be um expression
would be for something like a musical
performance
okay yeah you're expressing yours
or maybe even i like it
or maybe even like trying to get
yourself out of a sticky situation
like when you're when you're having
negotiations with another
with another cell or or that kind of
thing maybe
some supernaturals are in your way and
you're trying to
get yourself out of a bad situation but
not necessarily persuade them you'd use
expression and
what is the there's like a check box to
the left of every
item listed yes what is that so
that is for uh your skill or not your
skills your specialties
so you guys get three okay we'll go into
those next
we'll go into specialties after we've
filled out these here
but yeah a crafts would be something
like
building something or exactly ah
yep roll to craft something like maybe
an explosive
or maybe you're good at making weapons
out of weird stuff
well under the same category mental what
would a
cult be a cult is knowledge of spooky
things
supernaturals
yep and let's see what else do we got
here
um let's see for chad mental this is
gonna be rough um
because for mental you can see it says
minus three unskilled
what that means is that um there is a
minus three dice penalty
uh if you have no dots in that
in that skill
[Music]
okay it's rough
all the others are just minus one
unskilled
oh okay let me give you like a
little
example of what this means for you in
game so let's say you're playing a
grandma
um and grandma just has no dots in
computer whatsoever she's really not
very good with technology
um so let's say we're gonna use we're
gonna use wits for this role just
because she's making a quick internet
search
on where she can get some high quality
thread for her newest knit scarf for her
granddaughter
so she does a wits and computer role
she has two dots and wits in this
situation okay let's say that our
grandma has two dots and wits
but no dots in computer because she is
unskilled
that's a minus three penalty to her role
do you know how many dice grandma has
now
what is two minus three negative one
correct because because
because
she's trying her best because it is
negative one
when grandma rolls to do that check that
internet search check
um she has to roll uh she has to roll
something you can't roll negative one
dice
right so we give grandma one die
it's a pity die all right she has to
roll it
now in this situation um because she
only has one
and because it's below it's zero or
below
maybe just below zero is fine because
that role is below zero
um it's treated differently her result
is treated differently
uh as like a normal role would be so
grandma needs to get a 10 to succeed at
this
if she doesn't get a 10 she fails
don't pressure grandma if she gets a one
here's what happens here's what happens
if grandma gets a one
grandma realizes that she forgot to
reload her shotgun the other day
so she loads up her shotgun while she's
trying to simultaneously search for
this thread for a knit scarf and
accidentally
the gun goes off shoots the computer the
computer explodes into bits
falls out the window hits someone on the
head somebody dies grandma
rolls back on her chair falls over the
banister breaks three ribs
has to go to the hospital and she
doesn't she doesn't get her knit scarf
it's rough for grandma oh my god it's
called a dramatic fail so be sure that
you watch out for those
yeah yeah
yeah grandma doesn't she have a grandson
to help her out what the hell
maybe that's maybe that's the happy end
of the story
let's go with that let's go with that
maybe she'll knit that scarf someday but
because she didn't have any
any skill points in computer it ended
poorly for grandma when she rolled
one on a one d on a wait 1d 10 1 d10
that just hopes she doesn't uh call the
tech support and falls for a scam
you know yeah we gotta warn grandma
about that for grandma
yeah so make sure that this kind of
situation doesn't happen to you guys be
very wary of those dramatic fails
okay yeah so let's see for chad
maybe chad um is like decent at computer
academic's quite good very high gpa so
we'll put two dots for him there
and then um let's see
maybe he knows a little about science i
mean he's take he's taken enough college
courses to have like a basic idea so
there we go four dots in mental skills
for chad
but the good news is that chad's not
going to be doing many of those roles
because surely there's someone else in
his cell that
is better experienced in mental
capabilities
so that's the good news oh well
for physical um chad ran track so we're
gonna give him two dots
in athletics um can he throw a punch
i don't know maybe not
probably like one little punch it's kind
of weak um
let's see larceny chad's stolen
something once or twice in his life
drive i'm sure that he he got his
driver's license maybe
possibly firearms can he use a gun uh
maybe he'll pretend that he can use the
gun but he really can't he's
healthy yeah he has dangerous one two
three four five six
one in stealth and then let's see we'll
go ahead and put one more in athletics
because
chad really did run track was number one
on the track team legs
never missed it the eighth yeah
that's right and so this is what skills
look like for your boy
heck yeah you guys now let's go on to
specialties
you guys get three now when it comes to
basically you choose one of these skills
and you choose something to be
very proficient in and you get a plus
one to your role
um so for example i want one of chad's
specialties to be in athletics and it's
it's uh running away
running away now when chad is in a
situation where he's running away from
something
i'll roll athletics plus let's see
in this situation um i'm gonna make it a
strength in athletics rule
um let's see three plus three is six and
then plus the specialty in athletics is
seven
because chad has a specialty in running
away
now the way that i do it is your
specialty can be in anything
anything some people don't play that way
sometimes
um ah that's a good question
i would say no
at least that's that's not how i played
it back in the day you had to have like
some
some at least one dot in there uh
okay so let's let's go ahead and go with
go with that
that that would be fun difficult
try to think of something um i think
there's a list as well if you'd like to
choose from a list
let me go find it but i like to see you
guys get creative uh but you can also
choose from a list so let me see
so we get one for your category
um it i mean it depends on how how you
want to play it
um at least in the campaign that i was a
part of um
we were allowed to put all of them in
like for example physical
maybe you have a specialty in athletics
brawl and drive
um and no specialty in another area
um that was just that was the way that
we played it i think it's it's more fun
to just let you guys have the freedom to
do what you want in that regard
oh we only get three only three okay
okay here you go here's some
specializations for you guys
and yeah no problem
there there are a lot to look through um
oh my god
find something that seems nice let's see
fast striking grappling
let's see stunt driving maybe chad was a
stunt driver in another life
let's have him be a stunt driver like
monster trucks oh no yeah
he loves monster trucks like car flips
and stuff like that yeah
what is the one that gets us a good good
drift
that drift roll to drift
nice now let's see last um
um i'm gonna put all right socialize
specialization in frat parties
here we go okay
i'm putting gunslinger in firearms
so when chad is rolling to um socialize
at a frat party
i'd have him roll his presents plus his
social eyes so presence is
four dots socialize is four dots that's
eight
plus specialty and frat parties that's
nine d10s i get to rule
that's a big role wait drive is
literally drive i thought it meant like
more of a oh like i i get what you mean
no it is in fact to drive a car for some
people
okay i wonder who will be the driver i'm
the drift master
gotta get that driver
don't my meat is chugging coffee on the
side
oh does that specialty have to be like
in the list you provided or can you just
put like something that you think fits
um i mean different different groups
play it different ways
i want you guys to be as creative as
possible so if you think of something
oddly specific but you think you'll use
it in the game
i'll let you do it unless it's something
like my character has a specialty in
being alive or like specialty and
talking you got to get a little more
specific
is it too too crazy
um to give myself the specialty an
animal can
of of being able to talk to burps no
that's perfectly fine
i'd be okay with that yeah can humans
really talk to birds
i will i can i can well do vampires and
werewolves really exist
on this planet actually don't answer
that they might never mind they're
probably listening to me now they're
very angry
um yeah of course of course you can put
talking to birds
i mean when you say talking though it'll
be less like
in an actual language with words it'll
be more just communicating with them
kind of thing
yeah okay kelly you dare i know i'm
sorry i'm sorry
i'm disrespecting my senpai again i'm
sorry
[Music]
chugs coffee furiously
nice nice no oh it's all gone
live no don't mind me don't let me
don't mind me coffee's all gone it's
probably fine
wide awake wide awake now
[Music]
all right do you guys have any questions
about your skills
do you need a little more time just one
more
sure i'll just be here vibing you guys
take your time
[Music]
oh
let's see let me look up something real
quick looking up something real quick
okay i'm done
excellent
okay
okay got it guys
okay are you guys all ready yes
you need a little more time kiara one's
one 20 seconds
no worries yours man
okay done okay very good
next up uh let's see let's go ahead and
do the easy stuff let's fill in the easy
stuff first
um so before we go to merits let's go to
health all right
so your health is going to be important
in battle
um so and especially for sustaining
damage
um be sure to keep your eye on your
health so
health is going to be your stamina plus
your size
so everyone's size um is is five
unless you are incredibly small or
incredibly big
how big your size is five um like
towering like absolutely giant
above i'd say more than seven feet
okay which is kind of dope to be honest
what
what what what what what what what what
stamina plus
or what was it a stamina plus your size
everyone's size is going to be five
unless you are extremely small then it's
four and if you're extremely big it's
six
okay there's somewhere we write this or
yes
so minus e on the sheet look at where it
says flaws and then under the two lines
it says size
guys thank you you're welcome no problem
so if i have free and stamina and my
size is five then i have eight health
exactly okay
i am the same chad is the same three
four five
and one yeah no wait eight
three one two three four five six
seven eight
we will get more into the health and
damage system once you guys start
uh actually playing in the game
bite-sized pieces bite-sized pieces
my hair how far seems so low wait
yeah i wait what stamina what where is
stamina
stamina is under your attributes where
it says strength
dexterity and stamina how many dots do
you have in stamina
oh geez okay thank you you're welcome
you're welcome no worries
all right now next let's do your
willpower
so your willpower is going to be your
resolve plus your composure
willpower is important because you'll be
able to add extra dice to your pool
if you use one of your willpower dots
very helpful so let's see willpower
resolve plus composure
is two one oh no chad's only got three
willpower well oh well
i'll have two well i know
you can regain willpower thankfully but
oh there are various ways like i put the
stats in the right places
i no i got i got eight health and five
willpower oh that's actually pretty good
wow
very nice
all right now next up
everyone's morality starts at seven
so you can just go ahead and put that
right there you really don't want it to
fall down too far
why not um because if you hit one
you might just one day wake up and
decide it's time to slay your teammates
oh that sounds funny like anxiety points
kind of similar but it's more like what
you're willing to
if you play your do then do you win the
game uh
no i would say i would say you
definitely i mean
you maybe win the game but the others
most certainly didn't
i win the game of life
uh yes you you will win you will
probably i mean it depends on what what
you mean by when i suppose
the definition of winning is
i didn't know kuda had such dark fonts
i can't help it it runs in my blood
genetic i'm sorry it's okay it'll be fun
to see that come to life in the campaign
so i anticipate it
all right now let's see next we got your
speed
so your speed is going to be your
strength plus
dexterity plus five
nice ten
oh wow
is that for every every category yes
exactly
everyone gets one dot and everything
free
for the attributes oh cause you are a
functioning human
it's okay it's okay take your time take
your time
all right let's see speed strength plus
dexterity plus five so for chad it's
three
plus one plus five is nine chad's speed
is nine oh
hey bubba
all right let's see
[Music]
well i'm surprisingly fast yeah
it's okay speed is strength plus
dexterity plus five
this right here
so for chad our friend chad it will be
nine
strings how is why is speed important
um you will see in game it's important
for battle especially and deciding
um how fast you're able to do things
um oh it's like pokemon yeah it's that
attack first right right i'll be able to
show you more how speed works when we
get into like a battle
i think it'll be easier for for you guys
to see there so
anticipate that next up we've got
defense which is the lowest of dexterity
or wits so whatever is lower for you
is what your defense is going to be so
for chad wits is three but dexterity is
one so chad's defense is one won
these are all things that have to do
with like battle i suppose so once we
get into an actual fight i'll be able to
explain
a little easier for you guys in a way
that you can remember we'll play it out
let's see for now armor don't worry
about that
um and let's see next initiative mod
this is really important because when
you roll dice for your initiative mod
it's going to determine the turn
order so
your initiative mod is dexterity plus
composure
for chad oh no chad's initiative mod is
only two
which means chad will roll one d10
plus two so for example
chat let's say that chad rolling his
1d10 gets an eight
eight plus two is ten
so chad's initiative mod is ten
it's ten but let's say another player
rolls a one d10
and they get um a seven but their
initiative mod is five
seven eight nine ten eleven twelve
they're 12
so they go before chad because they have
12 and shad has 10.
okay yep hopefully
uh with the the place that we're going
to use
hopefully we get the okay to use it um
we will have like a list of the turn
order
[Music]
okay yeah quick maths i i was indeed
counting on my fingers
uh as
yeah i was counting on my fingers pull
out the calculator
all right we're gonna we're gonna ignore
um we're gonna ignore armor for now
um and also weapon and equipment you
guys will get that in game so we're
going to ignore that too
um now let's go on to merits
[Music]
oh merits there are a lot of merits uh
i'm gonna go ahead and link them again
for you guys thank y'all
huge list hopefully yes indeed
[Music]
here you go
i'm going to be um quiet and read all of
this now okay
no i mean reading all of it's going to
be tough but you can work
yeah yeah a lot of words um
feel free to to kind of go off and and
do your own thing in in this case um
i'm gonna just be picking some for chad
here for like the chat but i think you
guys
might be able to get the gist just let
me explain first
so um when choosing your merits these
will also add
of course dice to your role uh if you
have the
the appropriate merit um so or they just
do certain things they can also be
reflexive they don't always add
dice to your role um they might just
help you be able to even do something in
the first place
for example ambidextrous under physical
merits
character creation only ignore offhand
penalties so
if you're using your um i guess both of
your hands are dominant
so you could be dual wielding weapons
and you won't take a penalty
to use a weapon in for example your
non-dominant hand because you're
ambidextrous
yeah but you're gonna need to it's gonna
need to be three points
so for merits how many points do you get
let's find out
you get seven points yes that's right
very good
seven points
what what what you get seven points
for merits so you see the list that i
sent you
uh-huh look where it says rating
by each of the merits so ambidextrous
takes three dots
okay so i can add them up until i have
seven points there
exactly okay how about the prerequisites
mean i need to have that in order to get
that married
exactly oh no yeah so let's say for
example
you want to um let's see let's say that
you want to get
um here let me see
what's the good iron stamina round and
pound the ground
are you kidding me
i remember the good old ground and pound
that's good that's good
let's see so for example the the
physical merit
relentless it only costs uh one dot
and what it will do for you is it adds
two to the successes needed against you
in a chase
so say for example you're chasing
someone down and they're rolling to get
away from you
they need two more successes than would
normally be required
because you have that relentless merit
however
in order to get that merit you need to
have two dots in athletics
and three dots in stamina i see
oh man yeah so this is the big brain
part this is going to take a little bit
longer even though
it's less dots than the others you might
want to think a little harder about this
one i'm going to make chad ambidextrous
though
thank you they have a headbutt that's
awesome yeah
or shiv oh my god yeah
and keep in mind in the game with your
exp you'll be able to purchase more
merits
more dots than your skills more dots in
your attributes they all cost different
amounts
we'll get to that later
but you will be able to purchase some
things however some things are character
creation only
for example giant three dots uh plus one
to size but it's character creation only
same with ambidextrous character
creation only so you can't purchase
those later
okay let's see um what else we want for
chad um
maybe chad has some fame
uh nice this is very difficult i don't
know if i can do
this quickly that's okay that's okay
take your time
um i'm gonna give chad striking looks
i'm gonna give him two dots
cause he's chad let's see striking looks
um for striking looks thankfully no
prerequisites your appearance
is noteworthy and memorable add striking
looks to a die bonus to social roles
that benefit from your appearance
and to rolls by other characters to
notice or remember you
[Music]
um questions yes
so i gave myself the specialty
and firearms gunslinger and then here i
see though that in merits
there's also a gunslinger merit i guess
it does
something else it does a lot of things
depending on how many dots i have
but does it make sense to add a
gunslinger to the merit as well
sure if you'd like yeah that there's no
problem with that
let's see gunslinger yeah you have to
have three wits
three firearms i have four
arms ah but do you have a firearms
revolver specialty
i have a firearms gunslinger specialty
oh i see ah but isn't that that that's
it
that's that that that's that though huh
wait firearms gunslinger
i mean i think in this case i'd give it
to you to be honest that's probably fine
again this is this is a this is more of
like um
i'm not going to be a huge stickler for
the rules in this case so i'm fine with
giving that to you
okay because it says gunslinger is like
in the
pistols category of firearms
specialties there's so much text yeah
it's okay
no worries no worries we'll go ahead and
we'll go ahead and roll with it
i mean if that's what you if that's what
you want to spend your merits on and
also note that for gunslinger merit you
can do one dot three dots or
is that six i think it's five i'm just
not looking correctly
they each have different abilities at
different numbers
of dots
yeah okay
[Music]
let's see uh for chad
what else do i want shiv no why would
chad have a shiv
goodness gracious why not yeah why not
why not let's see these are fighting
merits chad's not much for fighting
[Music]
uh oh god
it's okay take your time and and by the
way um after this stream is over
if you want to look over your your
character sheet again
that's fine um i just need i'll need you
to give them to me like within the week
i guess in the finished version so if
you just want it to be a rough draft and
you want to edit it a little bit later
there's no problem
with that ah okay okay yeah so don't
don't worry too much about it
no no pressure no pressure okay
let's see
maybe chad has some resources
once per session you can securely
procure an item or service with it
with an availability that doesn't exceed
your resources rating
including any reasonable number of items
or services visibility is succeeded by
your resources by two dots
so basically i got some i got resources
for days okay cool
we'll use we'll use daddy's resources
here we go
we'll use we'll use debt we'll use daddy
sources
we're only gonna put one though because
you know daddy's not gonna give you all
the resources
son now son
you get one resource dot that's all
okay daddy let's see
[Music]
what's a crack driver oh gosh let me see
what this is
when not taking any when not taking any
non-driving actions add your composure
as a bonus to drive rules oh man
and penalize attempts to disable your
vehicle by your composure with three
dots you can take a reflexive drive
action per turn
reflexive meaning you you do it like
automatically
so let's see like driving fitness yes
exactly super skill behind the wheel
indeed useful
yeah let's see
[Music]
area of expertise raise one specialty
die bonus to plus two
oh that's kind of dope let's see
so specialties give you plus one right
if you have area of expertise um
then in that specialty you can make it
plus two
okay so wait wait i have four dots and
firearms
but since i have a specialty in there as
well i have
actually five yeah it would make it a
plus two if you have area of expertise
in that specialty yes so i have
but with area of expertise you get plus
two
sorry i didn't hear the first part the
plus one is what so
usually all specialties um are plus one
to your dice pool so for example chad's
athletics running away
the running away specialty is only plus
one
to his role but if you have the merit of
area of expertise
it changes that to plus two ah
so i'm gonna do that for him actually
area of expertise it only costs one dot
oh but it needs a resolve
that's a good point yeah thankfully it's
a pretty low requisite
so area of expertise
running away that's his specialty his
big specialty
i'm excited to start playing
are you gonna start drafting girl
no maybe
i am i have some stuff in drive haha
i'm going to be jeff master with me
well because wait under this the special
skills for physical
and drive it says that flying could be
one of the special skills
oh that's kind of dirty actually you
don't have to drive a car
it's necessarily you can just fly if
indeed wait i'll wait
but does does it have to be your special
skill or can drive automatically mean
flying
does that make sense oh
so that one more time i'm sorry i was
completely
one more time so drive has a special
skill on the list that you sent
also called flying right does it have to
be your special skill or can drive
also just automatically mean flying
ah that's a good question um i mean if
you are rolling to like fly a plane or
something like that
then i would have you roll drive and
probably dexterity
as well and if it was a plane you'd be
able to use that flying specialty to add
one dice to your roll
okay and my next question is does it
have to be like a uh uh
a physical object or can you just fly
like i just want to fly so you
oh my god like spread out your wings
that kind of thing yeah
oh you need a vehicle i would say yes i
would say
you need you need something to fly on it
can be a hoverboard
if someone is able to make one for you
but
yeah uh you you can't you unfortunately
can't just spread your wings uh and fly
what if i what if i created my own
device to fly
sure if you had like yeah if you created
a flying device like for example
one of those things where you jump off
the hand glider you jump off the cliff
and you're holding on to
i mean if you made a device yeah you'd
need to make it in in-game
and it might take some time but yeah
sure of course
i can make it for you jet pack yeah i
have
high high crafts oh
yeah nice slide that well though because
i'm technically a mad scientist
yeah it might blow up well be careful
about that there's a risk
okay i'm i'm i'm ready all right now
[Music]
now we're gonna go on to i think this is
is this the last part of the sheet
um it might be so the last part of this
sheet that we're going to be working on
are your flaws
flaws are fun um because you get more
points to use in your merits
if you have flaws
to make your character more well-rounded
here is the list you guys can use
um if you guys in chat would like to
look at this
list um basically any of these lists you
go on to
your your search engine of choice and
you type in world of darkness
flaws and you can access the list
my child listed as a flaw
but i did i did actually i did actually
get um
pdfs for all of you girls i did i did i
went through this
as i purchased them i actually purchased
them so you guys have those at your
disposal as well
uh if you would like to use those as as
a reference point but this is just so
chat has a little reference point as
well
so let's see um for example
addiction can be one to three points oh
man so
basically what flaws are is if your
character has a flaw
you're going to take penalties to your
dice pool if your flaw gets in the way
of your role
okay so for example amnesia
if you're rolling to remember something
rather no that would have to be for
something specific though
um let's see bad liar let's go with that
if you're a bad liar
you're gonna take a penalty to your to
your role to
try and lie but because you have that
flaw
and it says here bad liar one point you
get one uh free point to use in your
merit
so instead of seven you get eight by the
way it doesn't matter
how many points all of these are and uh
we just need two flaws right
um yeah i would say let's just cap it
too to keep it easy
yeah okay okay
i'm still looking for one marriage
that's okay you take your time you take
your time if you guys want to go ahead
and look through the flaws
these will also help you make a nice
well-rounded character
let's see watson are you going to put
short as on your phone
oh gosh what is
um like normal size maybe a little
hunched over yeah
oh i see okay i put a deranged and
dyslexic
wait uh is that like a way how many
points how many flaws do we have just
two
uh yes just just for now i i feel like
let's just cap it at two
um all right here's here's one that i
really like yeah two points
oh yeah two no two flaws oh two flaws
okay yeah
the the points um will i i'd love for
you to write them on the sheet
um but you can see on the the list that
i sent you
um how many points
so let's see i love this one um let's
see
hold on a sec incompetent you are
spectacularly bad you are spectacularly
bad at something
unfortunately you're the only person
around who doesn't understand this fact
so if you pick a single ability you
believe you have the proficiency equal
to three dots in that trait
when in reality you almost always ruin
any effort involving it whenever you try
to use the ability treat the outcome as
if you rolled a botch
so you will always fail edit no matter
what
but hey three points to put into merits
so
with merits you can only pick can you
pick like seven and put one in each or
if sure was like applicable um i mean if
you picked seven merits that all cost
one dot yeah
yeah okay okay yeah
so that's the point value which adds to
the amount of freebie points
during creation process
um but you can only get seven freebie
points from taking flaws
you guys so if you add up all of your
flaws and it comes up to ten
that's a no-no you gotta stop at seven
wait
uh callie i see a lot of mentions of
vampires in this list i thought
we were doing the yeah yeah you can't
you unfortunately
you can't you can't you can't do those
but your flaws the points have to add up
to something or
just it just has to be under 10. um
so basically the the points that you get
to use in your merits from having flaws
it can't go past seven
so let's see for now um i guess just
i feel like the best way to go about it
is to pick flaws that just go with your
character
i guess and uh we'll work out the
details a little bit later
but that should be
okay for now all right
um what is wrong with chad chad is
probably incompetent
um let's see
a girl with a sick roast
[Music]
let's see chad thinks that he is
just absolutely the best when it comes
to matters of the occult
i feel like there's a a perfect
flaw for all of us it's called
incomplete understanding
the whole matter has been explained to
you but you're still not quite sure how
things
in your sect work your imperfect
understanding of the rules and
regulations of your new existence
means that sooner or later you are going
to make a mistake
it's only a matter of time
oh man we're breaking the fourth wall
[Laughter]
it's fine we'll we'll all learn um like
the perfect way to
not really per it'll never be perfect
but we'll we'll all we'll get through
this together
let's see another thing about
incompetence is with chad's incompetence
in the occult
um in order to get the bonus to my merit
points
um from that like if i really want to
get those freebie points
i need to role play it that way so every
time a situation comes up
where the occult needs to be
investigated chad needs to jump into it
chad needs to be like oh man i'm a i'm
an expert at this and
and forces himself into the into the
situation
to do that role and it'll fail um but
that's how you get the freebie points
you got to make a sacrifice um the flaws
need to actually
um like get in your way
ah yeah
let's see low alcohol tolerance wouldn't
that be funny if chad had low alcohol
tolerance
i'm giving myself as a speech impediment
something okay okay go for it go for it
like like
pickle but oh it's it's adam
oh i see so when i'm when i'm playing my
character i always have to
add otta at the end of my sentences and
this is
um the difficulties uh of all die roles
involving verbal communication are
increased by two
yeah that fits the description that i
had with having a few communication
problems
[Music]
oh gosh here they go here they go oh man
all right let's go ahead and give chad i
want to give chad some nightmares
all right uh which is one point
uh incompetence is an awkward three
points um
so with nightmares you experience
horrendous nightmares every time
you sleep and memories of them haunt you
during your waking hours upon awaking
you must make a willpower roll
difficulty seven or lose a die in all
actions for that night so that that can
be difficult for night actions
um and a botched willpower rule which
means you fail the
um even when awake you still believe you
are locked in a nightmare
oh that's scary
right ye all right so let's see i
that i guess i have four extra points
then nice uh but i'm not gonna use those
right now i'm gonna save them just that
we can i guess move along
i'm not gonna put too much stock in
giving merits to chad when we're
probably not gonna use
but yeah so those are flaws um and with
that
there we go this is chad
a fresh hunter no weapons no equipment
but you know his heart's in the right
place we'll do his best
we can add weapons and equipment yeah
yeah throughout the game
um you'll be able to purchase them oh
okay yup you guys will get money by the
way for your jobs
[Music]
usually you'll get paid you can use that
money to get equipment and weapons
question about the profession like at
the top
uh did i have to pick one from the drop
down menu or could i just put something
like whatever i want oh yeah you can do
whatever you want for chat i put no
so i mean you can whatever you whatever
you feel like
okay is there any
any flaw that would be fitting for a
scatter brain like someone who loses
stuff all the time let's see i
can't really find anything let's see
i think there should be there should be
something like that
let me see i just realized there's a
drop down menu i've been drawing
everything in by hand oh
that's fine that's okay i apologize for
my hands
no worries no worries
it's all good um
oh that was really useful i didn't
realize i was doing yeah i was just
doing mine in paint
oh yeah maybe abs not
absent-minded you forget things such as
names addresses the last
time you gained glam ah that's like i
still think that could apply
to anyone not just vampires
[Music]
maybe absent-minded would be good um
let's see in order to remember anything
more than your own name and location of
your
i mean i would say sell in this case you
need to make a wits roll or as last
resort spend
a will power point this flaw may not be
taken with the merit concentration so
you can't cheat it like that
um let's see that could be
good um uh
our our max what did you say that our
max bonus merit points we can get from
flaws was we might set it
seven and i believe it's seven uh yeah
the seven possible freebie points earned
through taking flaws
uh can give a character a total of up to
22 for oh wow that's a lot
let's see oh wow
i'm supposed to add points from the
flaws into the merits
yes to any
yeah i mean or you can just go buy a new
merit if you'd like from the merits
sheet
oh i see
what what what what what what what
i missed that so basically flaws give
you freebie points right that you can
use
that's why i would want to maybe choose
like like a bigger flaw so i can get
more points for marriage
yes exactly but it will it will hurt you
in the game high risk
high reward exactly
maybe i get rid of the speech impediment
there's a lot to decide which is why
it's okay that that we don't completely
figure it out but a rough draft would be
great
all right let's see
i want to go
however you want to play it
let's see
so basically this sheet is done for chad
so i'm gonna make it
go away oh i still haven't named my
character
oh that's okay that that can be one of
the last things that you come up with if
you would like
uh-huh
yeah sure i mean so if you can save the
image and then send it to me
that would be awesome i'll just put it
in the
you know in that place okey dokey
okay so wait there's a page two though
yes exactly and this is something we
don't have to all do today
um because this is stuff that doesn't
require like technical explanation from
me
um but it would it would be nice to kind
of
like figure it out i guess um also you
can choose to just leave some areas
blank if you would like
up to you okay okay okay
still trying to find one more merit that
costs me two points
i have a question about the uh the merit
a roadkill
okay let me go let me go look for that
roadkill uh-huh it says requirement is
aggressive driving but
is that a specialty or
ah yes i would say so okay
no more
ah man this is this is gonna be fun
yes it will be fun aggressive driving
two dots he
oh gosh oh man
what book is this from
well just for the sake of simplicity
yeah let's make it a specialty okay
yep let's just go with that
there is so so much in this game
i i love that i'm like oh yeah this is
the this is one of the
this is one of the easier ones to ease
into but there is so much stuff
there is a lot i'm sure we'll get used
to it but yeah
lots of different that's just for now
even for your boy i'm like man i can't
remember all this so i need all the
sheets up
there are a lot of things
all right i think i'm ready okay
excellent um
this part is pretty self-explanatory so
i'm just gonna write description
chad history he's chad
and things like um endowments we're not
going to worry about right now
equipment uh combat etc we may use later
endowments just not really thinking
about those tactics will be important
for your group later on but not going to
worry about that right now
we're not going to touch tells right now
the main thing that we want to do is
history
description um and just have that be it
for the second page
we may edit it later though as we get
deeper into the game
see i guess i guess chad's sheet is done
[Music]
one that's okay take your time take your
time
if anyone is ready i'll go ahead and
show their sheets on the stream but
we have to do the description and stuff
too right like the
um yeah that would be nice if you're
able to
but it's also something that you can do
off stream so just like a rough
idea is fine okay
just so we can show everyone a general
idea of what your character is like
hey i'm going to break my neck real
quick there we go
sometimes you just got to break your
neck man i tell you what
i can't decide oh my god decisions
decisions
there is a lot to decide for sure
oh it is getting hot in here mine's not
finished but
uh should i send it i haven't really
firmly decided my merits are floss
but okay i mean as long as it's
yeah yeah you can send me just what you
have um
yeah and we'll share there's already the
bonus merits that's what i haven't
really assigned yeah
that's okay i haven't for chad either so
it's it's all good
okay yeah no
[Music]
problem
i think while you guys are finishing up
um i'm gonna go wash my hands cause it's
starting to get hot in here
okay okay all right so i'll be back in
just a moment
but you guys feel free to continue
talking
i'll just be under the table there i go
there she goes there i go
we are talking
but i don't know what languages to
choose
you make up like a gibberish language
that only bad scientists use
latin wait can i talk to animals except
it's only a one-way one-way conversation
back to funguses and scientific samples
what are you putting as like your your
age in the description i don't know what
to put
my toto's age i don't know 400
100 yeah but i'm a human
oh wait this conversation sounds
familiar
are they old and bitter old bitter jaded
[Music]
happy in a sneaky way because they're
always planning something you know
[Music]
this is
you want to wait wait
hey wait i'll come over to you
[Music]
yummy yummy fresh
how long have they been in your hands
for are you sure it's fresh
hey no i i did those are fresh i i
actually
have didn't have them in my hands for a
while now eight months oh okay
i just ordered some fresh ones also who
wants to fight
hmm fight me wait hold on
you got your tent
[Laughter]
hey
how does that look hmm
things that could have been but oh they
are not
like orange with like blue
phoenix tentacles that sounds
like something that would pop up in the
middle of our session
let me put down my website i'm gonna hit
good on her head she already got hit too
often
with me again it's okay
i'm used to it
[Music]
i wonder what kind of adventures await
us
are we like we're in the same compact
right do we work together as a team
against each other i think at the moment
we don't know each other yet but we
carry will help us find uh our way
together and then we act as a group
to catch them all catch all the monsters
huh
[Music]
three turns welcome back
i needed to tell a friend she's back
[Music]
all right i hear you but they say you
muted
oh i was muted in obs there we go sorry
let me let me say everything for
everyone guess who's back back again
cali's back fella frank guess who's bad
guess who's bad guess who's back
we can't continue make sense said i said
something to god
goodness all right let's see
thank you and then we've got enos as
well thank you very much
the first page only for now is fine
right i only have the first page in
photoshop right now yeah yeah the first
page is is fine
as long as we can okay
right now let's see i'm gonna go ahead
and hide this
real quick as i open up
let's see let's start with uh
i'm definitely needing to go back and uh
fix this a bit
no worries and finishing we do that
absolutely do that let's see
i think this is it let's see mystery
dark lady
okay sounds
go ahead good expand
okay all right here's what we got
ladies and gentlemen let's see
all right this is not an example
[Music]
all right let's see what we got here
mystery dark lady i like it
all right we'll get that name a little
bit later so let's see
with breakers virtuous hope vice's wrath
very nice
and courier okay i like it
let's see what we got for attributes i
think i did my math wrong here
accidentally i was like moving stuff
around and i made a whoopsie
oh that's okay all you have to do is
take away one of the red dots
that you have in either the intelligence
wits resolve or the dexterity stamina
strength one ah yeah that's okay that's
that's the only thing you gotta do
um but otherwise looking good and then
manipulation
okay so with manipulation uh presents
composure box
you actually get one more uh because
each of these should already be filled
in so like presents you automatically
get a dot
manipulation you automatically get a dot
you automatically get all the first dots
in each one oh yeah okay so you still
have a little more to spend
thankfully okay
no problem and then let's see what we
got here for skills
crafts it's like pizza correcting
homework huh
no no it's it's fine it's chill it's
it's okay it's just a rough
it's just yeah you really really i don't
i got a type of sweet teacher that we're
all
secretly in love with but we we know
that we can never get with because she's
too old for all of us
yeah yeah something like that okay
gosh let's see mental you got the four
dots in mental great crafts paper
looking good
a little in medicine a little in science
now for physical
we got one two three four five six seven
very good
uh stealth shadow okay so you can stay
in the shadows
yeah kind of thing i see very nice and
then let's see
um for social let's see one two three
four five six seven eight
nine ten eleven very good persuasion
social social maneuver
okay okay i i got that i got that okay
sure um yeah i think i think i'll let
you have that one for the specialty it
could
be a little broad but uh what we'll say
off the list
oh it was no no it's fine if you got it
off the list then it's no problem
um agility or something right yeah yeah
social maneuvers oh okay i see so
like using i guess speech tactics or
social tactics in situations i see
okay yeah that is perfectly good all
right let's see and then
wow persuasion is really high nice uh
some intimidation
socialized one subterfuge three very
good
guys right good job
they're good okay so some of the merits
you've got fighting finesse okay that's
going to be very helpful
fast reflexes okay nice
vestige yes vestige
vestige okay good vestige i don't know
here okay good awesome
and then spin spin dog spin doctor
this is yeah spin doctor i don't know i
really
it's okay there are so many there are so
many freaking merits hold up
i've only memorized like the ones that i
used a lot in games let's see you
all right vestiges you possess vessels
for the for the world's life force which
can be called upon for cursed
strength oh my gosh
wow
can we use that in hunter i wonder oh
this is from mage
oh man i should have
i'm a dummy i don't think we can i don't
know if we can use that
ah okay f
is it so specific oh world's life force
i kind of want you to though
i'm okay with changing it around we can
decide later on
yeah i kind of i kind of want you to
well okay
let's let's put a pin in that because
that might be cool
i don't know yeah we we play we play
this our way
we play this our way it's definitely
hunter but i'm cool with breaking some
rules for the sake of coolness
yeah it would be linked to style points
yeah for style points
and let's see tainted clues inflict an
additional
minus one penalty instead of consuming
any successes nice okay
very good you need high manipulation and
subterfuge for that i think that you've
got it
subterfuge three manipulation whoa yeah
manipulation very high okay good
so you're looking good girl and then
we've got flaws
short temper amnesia perhaps blind okey
dokey
looks good to me cool
all right so we're looking good
big claps all around the table looking
great
yeah we'll we'll work on it um a little
bit later to like i guess uh
buff out the edges but it's looking
great this is a fantastic start
nice all right very well done next
up we're going to go and hit up
ina's sheet all right
let's see mad scientist ina
with the jedu banana
[Laughter]
all right here here is inna's feet
all right so we got the the homie you'll
be
all right come on
got me there you got me there come
on
[Laughter]
you got me there
true
[Laughter]
oh my gosh
oh wow all right no never never be sorry
it's
beautiful what a beautiful soul
you know my union is virtue temperance
vice is sloth very nice
concept is tired grad student slash
inventor
profession mad scientist student let's
take a look at these here attributes
that's the intelligence wits resolve
okay
so for uh intelligence we've got three
points
wits three points resolved two points
strength two dexterity three not exactly
the the strong block
but looking good and then let's see yeah
number number one looks like it's going
to be smarts for you huh
um and then let's see presence
manipulation composure
looking good all right now next we go
into skills
all right what do we got here mancel 11
the whoa
strong strong craft skills craft your
sense
very good computer academics
investigation medicine first aid this
will be helpful
you all will be very thankful for this
future
excellence i love accidents in the lab
yes
indeed all right looking good
next we've got physical um drive
aggressive
three dots hey we gotta get the places
that's right
that's right survival one rep weaponry
two
looks good all right i love the idea of
your character
being like jumping into the front seat
for many of your adventures i can see it
happening high speed chases
i anticipate them and let's see social
for one for animal can expression
persuasion and subterfuge
okay seems good to me see for your
merits
resources area of expertise crafting
encyclopedic knowledge
automotive genius multilingual and
roadkill
very good all right
for multilingual what is what is your
other language uh i haven't decided yet
okay no problem you take your time
ro and roadkill oh man this is gonna be
fun
the ignorant one point insomniac tooth
was very good
looking great inna's character you'll
be all right
okay you got it you got it no problem
you
you'll get used to it oh my gosh
[Music]
how do you do it how do you do it
i just oh man
oh man that that in itself is a special
skill where is where's the puns
man i think there was actually one where
it's like you told the wrong jokes at
the wrong time
oh god i'm just like hmm
mmm so something to pause here in the
future
oh my gosh all right let's see
looking very good ina yeah next up let's
go ahead and
get to kiara okay
okay let's see let me save this real
quick
and let me pull this up okie dokie
open this bad boy
i found it tiara sheet
okay here we go
this is tiara player kiara tiara with
the burbs and the guns
yeah i love it it's a very good mental
image
virtue prudence i think you still need
to change the the top
uh this isn't this is not this is not
yule
right hold on a second uh hold on chiara
thank you very much for letting me know
okay kiara character
sheet virtue is prudence vices pride
concept falconer professional
profession falconer let's see and
looks like you've got the big boy points
in strength accessory stamina
very nice intelligence three wits one
resolve three
strength three dexterity two stamina
three presence three manipulation one
composure two okey dokey
looking good then for mental we've got
four okay academics and then three in
crafts
uh physical okay physical is the big boy
trait here
yeah i'm strong i will protect my
friends
yeah dope firearms
be the shield let's see athletics two
firearms four with gunslinger survival
outdoorsman with two and weaponry three
dots
very nice and let's see social verb
communication yes that's the big one
very good and empathy three okey dokey
wow that is real high
but could be very useful i i hope so
i think so as long as you as long as you
find a way to role play it right then i
think you'll be able to make
very good use out of that
okay let's see merit subduing strikes
loaded for bear
human prey multilingual iron stamina
quick draw danger sense looks pretty
well rounded to me very suitable to my
character
perfect help yeah i think so with the
flaws i wouldn't mind adding more to it
because those are such small flaws but i
need to read more through the the bigger
phones sure sure take your time take
your time
all right new arrival and speech
impediment okay looks good to me
all right very good tiara
[Music]
all around the team oh my gosh
all right my clap's all around this day
oh my gosh oh i'm very excited
okay oh god
sorry oh my stomach already hurts i got
a second
okay let's get wasaso popping off here
is um is the name
watoto supposed to sound kind of similar
to watson
by any chance well like a little it's
like potato and watson
oh i think what gotcha
[Music]
uh hang on let me change this real quick
all right what the why do you say it
like a dad with toto dude
dude
[Laughter]
[Music]
all right oh wait no why would i say
amelia character sheet i'm sorry i got
so excited
i thought you were toe toe for a minute
all right let's look at the homie i love
how it's like typed out but then you
just wrote over it
looking good looking very good what's
out so amelia miss breakers
faith greed investigative goblin-like i
can envision this character already
profession hurts
[Music]
yeah he grows he grows herbs okay
yeah very very helpful
you guys may think now hey listen i
don't know what you guys are thinking
but it seems normal to me
okay now let's go yeah like herbs and
thyme yeah like alchemy or something you
know
yeah stuff together yeah nice very it'll
be very helpful
very helpful um let's see what we got
here
intelligence um so that's gonna be the
lowest i guess intelligence is one
wits three resolve one
let's see i think you can add one more
dot in there actually okay yeah i got
confused because i didn't know i could
have one in each one so i think i mean
sorry about that i forgot that some of
you guys were using the editable sheet
um which didn't have them all already
marked in there so
yeah you guys definitely can um and then
next we got strength dexterity and
stamina and then presence
composure manipulation looks good
looks good we got some we got some
manipulative ones here
why not
why not what
um let's see mental okay looking good
one two three four five
six seven eight nine ten eleven okay wow
pretty high
uh what's the craft alchemy okay okay
a little in computer investigation
medicine occult politics this will be
useful so you don't have to take those
really heavy minus three unskilled
penalties
nice okay and then we've got for
physical two and brawl
larceny pickpocket oh no
oh no no
i'll steal your equipment oh no
you guys gotta watch out for what's up
with toto's slippery fingers
let's see survival luck oh gosh
all right this is going to be fun this
is going to be fun add a little bit of
luck into your dice pool i can i can
respect it
and then let's see social a little
intimidation
i love to imagine what's very
intimidating
oh my gosh don't be fooled by that small
goblin-like appearance it actually uh
plays just thinking about oh my god
oh man and then we've got streetwise one
and subterfuge
one okay good stuff
and then let's see for merits
investigative prodigy
fast reflexes hearty ground pound
it's not just ground pound but that's
the official and the last time
yeah you know what i'm gonna yeah i
think i like it better this way
let's roll with it it's meant to be
it's meant to be okay so here we go i
guess
i guess that's it i guess we got through
all your characters
nice
very good a little bit of a special one
in different like areas and then you
know i thought that was just a little
all-around
you know kind of a wild card you know
yeah yeah
i can imagine that i can see that
happening
i like it i like it all right
so let's see um hold on wonder if we
should do this today
um i wanted to do like a little test rp
but i'm starting to think we really
should wait to get the okay for this
rolling dice but i think that you guys
understand
how the the dice add up um
so for example let's say let's say
um for example uh yule
wants to roll um to
let's see craft something right
um let's see let's say that yo wants to
roll to craft something in the moment
it's kind of like a spur the moment
thing
so you would use um your wits
plus your crafts and then add your
crafter scent specialty
so you have three wits four crafts
uh four for crafts and then one for
crafters since that's
four plus three four five three seven
eight eight dice total
ah yeah your dice pool is gonna be eight
and then you'll roll those dice um and
basically the way that it works is you
want to get successes
um a success on your dice is either an
eight
a nine or a ten oh
and tens you re-roll
so you can get more successes
and basically the amount of successes
that you get will pretty much determine
how
the action is carried out whether you
succeed or not
um so you want to basically increase
your chance of getting successes by
having a heightened dice
pool yeah
and each of you guys will make your
first rolls um
in your either tutorial session or for
some of you who are who are pretty busy
we can just do a lore video which will
be like a shortened version that won't
be live streamed and
we'll just do it together and then i'll
edit it a little bit and you can post it
on your channel
[Music]
yup okay sounds good yeah
that's basically it and then there's
another thing i wanted to show you guys
it's kind of cool
um typically when your characters go
somewhere
um this can happen
now we're in now now check this out
we've gone to the scene
yeah and the actual art inside the scene
box will be like more
i guess a more um like detailed area of
i guess the scene so within the city
maybe it'll be a picture of a bar or
something like that
[Music]
yeah yeah thank you for preparing so
much
yeah no problem guys there's still so
much work to do and
i still gotta brush up on the rules and
stuff but you guys
you guys have been amazing so far with
creating your characters and i can't
wait to see
um how the story unfolds with your with
your ragtag crew of hunters
[Music]
yeah so the last thing the last thing we
got to do you guys
is we have to decide on hashtags so that
um
so that you guys in the audience can
also have uh
some fun with us along the ride
so the main hashtags um we're just gonna
do a
keyboard slam real quick the main
hashtags that we're going to try and uh
choose i guess are i wanted to do one
for let's see well overall for the
overall uh game
it's going to be hunter myth
and then we need to come up with one for
fan art
and then this one's going to be fun you
guys are going to like this
we want to use bgm that you guys create
oh yeah so if you create bgm
you can use the hashtag that we come up
with and maybe we'll play it uh during
the campaign
um with credit to you of course in the
description we'll put the link to the
music that we use
um as long as you guys are are cool uh
with us using your music for that
purpose
needs to be under that understanding
that you know we're going to use it in
our campaign
um then feel free to use that hashtag uh
and yeah
after that uh i thought we'd also have a
hashtag for theories
conspiracy yeah
yeah my favorite i think i'm gonna do
fan art and
fiction as well some of you fantastic
writers as well maybe for our fan i
it can just be myth breakers uh no okay
i mean that might be nice if anybody
else has any ideas
or hollow a myth breaker yeah
um that could be good because we are
hollow myth hollow
mysteries yeah i get it
mysteries oh for the theories yeah
this year yeah oh my god that's that's
great that's a great idea
myth theories i thought
you said mystery but with a lisp
mysteries
i'm not surprised
and the fan art name is miss breakers
are we're starting to find
that one um let's just put it in we're
still kind of thinking about it i think
that
it works if if we can't come up with
like a
a different one myth breakers
yeah um just for art and general fan
content because
choosing a name that has like art in it
isn't exactly accurate just because you
know if people are getting creative with
like fan fiction that kind of thing
um yeah it might just be better
yeah that's true it is art but like if
there's like some kind of
i guess pun or play on words in regards
to drawing maybe we should like
stop somebody said there's like a double
meaning to mysteries because it's like
my theories oh
that's dang smart wow huge braid
brain there are layers for the bgm i saw
water tones
[Laughter]
i kind of love that though to be honest
yeah
it's kind of dope some people are all
encompassing you know
that's true that's true yeah we could
use the
it's good but i guess
bgm myth themes okay like theme music
that's not bad ah miss themes yeah
ah my themes i wonder if there's a lot
of um
stuff in the tag yep i mean okay yeah
let's go check for hunter myth it was
fine there was like one person who
posted
it dj myth sounds like a dj
yeah but i bet i wonder if there is a if
there is like a dj
who's like hey
i wonder
[Music]
oh yeah we need to have i know you guys
are going to want to go wild with those
mimi's so um
how about we we can do we can do meme
breakers
um yeah just go with that that's nice
and easy
gosh that's so edgy but i gosh it fits
it fits somehow
i'll take it oh b b g myth is not bad
either
yeah i wanted to say that yeah maybe
let's go with that
the btm in in capital and the rest in
small but you're
it's not not used so i think it's good
okay let's go with that
i like that yes
good sounds good it looks good to me
all right does this look good for you
guys so looking good
general myth breakers uh for fan content
let's see
fam content fan content okay and then
let's see bgm and then
of course oh myth tapes would be cool
too because mix tape
smith tapes ah that's also pretty good
i think i like that one even better yeah
i kind of like that too
it does sound like mix tape
method nothing for
it's it's free really oh heck yeah
miss tape okay let's go with that
plural maybe oh wait wait miss tape oh
yeah
yeah miss tapes is fully free
wait what is what is so yummy nothing
don't worry about it we're moving on
we're moving on out of this type moving
on
we're moving on all right so we've got
hunter myth for general
myth breakers for fan content myth tape
for bgm and mysterious for fan theories
and meme breakers
for memes go just
just because everything else is um uh
plural can we make myth tape also plural
oh that's also a good idea thank you
let's go ahead and do that
[Music]
okay okay okay if
this this was a mistake thank you chad
that was funny that was amazing
i can't all of you are enough enough
oh my gosh all right so here are the
hatchimals
yeah you guys went nuts these are some
good hashtags i will say
[Music]
all right heck yeah bunch by spots we
yes can't wait to see what you guys come
up with and please
anticipate uh our first tutorial session
i don't know like what order we're going
to go in
um but basically the way it's going to
work is that next month
um everyone will basically each
once per week um have uploaded or
streamed
a tutorial stream or a lore video in
regards to their characters i'm gonna
help make them
don't worry you guys i'm i'm 100 gonna
help you guys with all that
stuff um and yeah so you guys can check
them out once a week
and then the following month um of july
is when we start playing the game
um yeah so for the first season there
will be five sessions each time they
will be on a different person's channel
and we will be playing once every other
week
yes yeah so please anticipate that
a lot of work thank you callie thank you
yeah no thank you guys
thank you guys i feel like through this
uh this is also a great um way for us to
bond and we've already bonded so much
but if we're doing this weekly
you know being creative together having
fun together telling stories together
it's going to be a great bonding
experience yeah
deep exercise yeah definitely
yes i'm looking forward to it too and
it's more of a chance to talk to you
guys
you know
by the way did you did you mention that
you you
you see it as an as a possibility that
later on others could join this
yeah i mean i'd really like uh to bring
someone new
in every season but there's also like uh
the situation where maybe you guys get
kind of busy
um and can't play all the time or maybe
you just aren't really like into the
game
very much which is totally fine no big
deal because like these kinds of games
aren't for everyone
if that's the case um then we'll we'll
come up with a dope exit for your
character and then
maybe invite um another member from from
holopro to come hang out
yeah so please anticipate the future is
looking very fun
we're gonna go back to our fireplace
room oh cozy cozy
yeah heck yeah so um
do you guys have any announcements
before we say bye bye
no yes okay announcement oh
okay uh i'll be having a charity stream
for uh an animal shelter like a sort of
animal charity organization on june 5th
and yeah it'll have like a bunch of
goals and stuff you know when we reach
certain amounts and so pretty much this
is like a
test run so you know in the future we
could uh do other charity or like
fundraiser streams yeah
[Music]
heck yeah thank you for for opening up
that possibility for us
watson
[Music]
can't wait to tune in i'm very excited
thank you heck yeah i will definitely be
tuning in so you guys tune in too okay
everyone in chat
expect you to be there i think you
promised yeah
heck yeah and what a kiara kiara you had
an announcement too right
yeah too uh on saturday uh
we are changing up like whole talk until
now had a fixed time but whole talk
uh time is changing please check out
the schedule because this time is a
special episode 10th episode and the
guest will be
you might already know
yes yes a very special episode we
probably like up until now whole talk
was more about you know
we talking about the guests finding out
more things about the guests but since
the guest this time is
either we will um talk a lot about like
the dev like stuff about the company you
can ask a lot of questions i'll be
recruiting questions soon so if you have
like more in-depth question
in-depth questions about the company uh
please uh think about
your questions and send them to me soon
i'll be tweeting it out and
so that is the whole talk 10th episode
and then on sunday
uh i am doing my one hopefully 1 million
subscribers
uh endurance 12 hour stream microphone
let's go
it's finally time um so i i'm preparing
a lot of different
content that we will suffer through
in 12 hours of streaming on sunday i
think
anyone can catch up hours at least some
point of time
good luck if i can do it yes
you can do it i am cheering for you
despite the fact that you are trying to
beat my record
i respectfully i'm i'm supporting you
when i first had the record and then you
broke it with your endurance thing and i
was you know sometimes i've been
streaming so long
uh where i was getting close to beating
the record but i was like i don't want
this stream to be the one it has to be a
special stream
so there we go
that's it for me can't wait to see
heck yeah thank you gura do you have
anything
no not today okie dokie how about you
inna
ah not i don't think so
okie dokie okay yeah i think the only
thing i have to announce is that i'm
posting a new song
it's going to be yeah you guys heard it
i sent it to you guys
[Applause]
um but i hope you guys like it it's a
cover song and it'll be out on may 31st
jst late at night so hopefully it'll be
an okay time for everyone
tune into the premiere heck yeah it's a
song i wanted to cover for a long time
so i hope you guys like it
yeah i like it already
thank you so much you guys and thank you
everyone who came to tune in to the
character creation stream
i get to go sleep yeah
[Music]
i think some of you guys are heading to
bed too yeah i was actually i was gonna
stream after
this but uh i didn't really sleep last
night either so i
i think i'll just take a nap instead so
you guys i don't know if anybody's
streaming after this but i think you
guys will be pretty uh
cat will be alone oh so sad no no
anticipate the next one i suppose yeah
yeah yes
me and me and kelly are on vata and
senpai's channel tomorrow with
senpai free four-person collab mm-hmm
very exciting
can't wait to play a game yeah yeah oh
my chicken horse oh my gosh
exciting stuff can't wait hope you guys
hope you guys tune in if you have some
free time
all right well thank you so much
everyone for coming to to cheer us on
uh as we made these characters super
chats will be read at a different time
um just for people that are coming now
who want to watch the stream over again
um you guys can do that in a minute but
we need to go say goodbye um first so
anyway
thank you guys so much for coming and it
was very funny
[Music]
eventually eventually i want to come up
with like a cool way to like say goodbye
and end these streams like a
like a yo clap like kind of thing
um but we'll do that later we'll do that
later for now i think we can just say
bye bye
so yeah thank you guys so much for
tuning in and we'll see you again soon
during our next adventure
yeah bye guys peace
[Music]
you