[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
not with that language that language is
not okay it is the first time ever that
this family supposedly is getting
together
[Music]
at family time
family time
sounds like not happy no it's not that
I'm not happy it's just
not drinking tea when it's hot let's not
it's not her feel you know like she has
no family
I know where you're going with this and
I'm sorry about the adoption thing yes
I'm sorry we will have to discuss a lot
of things today maybe make things clear
about who who gets to take care of cool
boys oh yeah you can do it
yeah
come by I'll continue to take care of
you finally I'm the detached father can
I bring my dog
you duck you duck yeah duck yes
yeah I have already found out uh a
reason why she's most likely not any of
our daughters
why is that because
she says she's a dog person but we're
both cat people I like dogs but I do
like cats batters yeah I mean there is
that that's true and she she literally
put her middle finger in the face of
tutu you didn't see it huh
what did you do to my dad that's almost
like this
yeah because she loves you
unconditionally what the hell she loves
you unconditionally and that's what you
do to my tutu yeah right she was so nice
to her wow I was supposed to listen
because I really disrespected
child child where's the tutu I will
apologize
I don't think I don't think dude who
knows what you're saying doody speaks
English and sometimes yeah
yeah cocoa has been screaming at tutu
yeah and where's ghosts calm down you're
scared of the couple because always run
away from me
oh no she likes you she really does you
just gotta get to know her a little bit
you know but she's she's very sweet she
is a princess just like you yeah
that's very different oh but you know
it's not only the first time that we're
here together but actually I feel like
more special than that is the fact that
you two are meeting for the first time
yeah right now
what do you mean very small you're small
look at you yeah look at this oh you are
what are you talking about you're tiny
in every way
my
look at my legs it's like maybe it's
small a little
your face is small your head is small
your your size is small your your butt
and everything is small brain is huge
huge big brain yeah
what was your reaction when you when you
hug your dad very awesome
yes I'm aware they're real it's it's
very different very very very different
push me back push
well yeah there was like a big gap
between us and I was like come closer
and I was like wait now I see why that
can't happen
okay well yeah we have we're very
different looking I was looking forward
to that like to that picture and the
size difference he's very very striking
yeah look at me I Tower over everyone
what can I say
my birds okay but it's
just like Mommy and Daddy have to talk
about something okay we're not you know
Uncle Mommy and Uncle have to talk about
it
I'm still dead
um the distance is it like family
problem yes Kelly what took you so long
to upload yours your reference sheet all
right not my fault
not my fault it's just Mama never wanted
to upload it
I mean maybe she did but like she just
kind of didn't think about it so yeah I
mean I just got it recently and I'm like
Oh yay I think I can post it on Twitter
now but just checking from creators you
know how many like cosplayers and
artists out there must have like a
freaking breakdown because they
cosplayed you or they drew you and the
hood it's a hood and that's a shoulder
bag
only the adults can say those words
I'm an adult
you are our adult child okay Maryland
all right guys this stream is rated M
for Mature um I don't know now I've got
a new merchandise idea you know I kind
of want to sell that hoodie it looks
really cool but you're just so late with
it
um
[Laughter]
share my character sheet really yeah I
haven't oh well but I have you so some
people do it early some people do it
when they're like I didn't win my 3D was
uh
first revealed I think I was like do you
want to show it I'm like oh yeah
so I think people if you ask your artist
she can probably I just thought to ask
about it until now because I didn't want
to be disrespectful
and I think it's
in case you feel about that well it's
nice to have a reference you oh and then
I don't know if you saw there's another
thing
um your your heels are very tall yeah
and your ankles are therefore positioned
very up high and now people more and
more are lining us up you know and
pointing out that indeed it is me who is
the taller one well hold on do your
sneakers not have heels on the back okay
well then let's let's look at it let's
look at it this way who are we to say
that the canonical height does not
include heels or does include heels
maybe it doesn't that's what I always
thought that it doesn't include the
heels the Canon eye Glide so really I'm
something like 169 with the heels with
the heels apparently no apparently this
move the heels because Ina's height also
is mostly who told you that
fact who told you I've been told by who
by the gods all right well then never
mind it's so so we're back to square one
but also I've been doing very very uh
eagerly comparing uh everybody's sizes
when we're all in the idol outfit
because there everybody wears the same
shoes
true and I've been getting very deep
into it and it's very Oh eye opening you
know very eye-opening because iris is
the tallest yeah I don't understand that
she's like a giant she was supposed to
be smaller than me I don't get it yeah
and she is smaller than me but when she
puts on the idol outfit it's like she
grows into a giant yeah
in the conclusion
yes that's really wear our high heels
yes to look taller than you yes
oh that's right Google remember what are
you wearing now what shoes are you
wearing now barefoot no they're no
you're not I am
you're wearing heels with this outfit
and then what's your height then well
see now I'm taller it's like where you
position me all right keep going up let
me see what you have on your feet all
right
[Music]
heels heels heels but there's not even
like this there's no official hide for
these outfits only for a default outfit
so I don't know
something's fishy
that's all yours you see that little
Lindor bag right there
[Applause]
[Music]
you should be more prepared for your
child
but land is so good yum yum yum yum I
have something for everybody oh gifts
only something really small because I
wanted to bring something small from
okay it's just a convenience store
gotcha I try to get three different
things but turns out I got two of the
same and one different so I guess wow me
and Kelly are sharing
okay what's this can I open it
[Music]
that seems like the perfect thing for
you I have a gift as well
I can't guarantee you that you'll like
it or use it a lot I like it I saw this
on the internet and I thought that you
know you'd like it so
it's okay I will describe it's a it's a
black uh bag so far that is made out of
um what's this material it's velvet
velvet materials and inside I feel
some like like small things yeah okay
yeah I will open it
what's in there
oh look at that they're game dies
with the ring
oh [\h__\h] look at the ring yeah
yeah so if you want to play any more
table tops I thought you could use those
because
and they got a nice like um translucent
color yeah yeah they're really pretty so
yeah
thank you that's so cool yeah you're
welcome well they're all different sizes
maybe I can free the Rings from their
containers
yeah if you never play any more tabletop
games did you watch Lord of the Rings
ever
I watched The Hobbit I like The Hobbit
in theaters but a lot of drinks is
better than your Hobbit really like
everybody says so people actually Lord
of the Rings fans are actually like kind
of disappointed by The Hobbit movie I'm
not me but most others don't
everybody
I think these are d10s this is what are
the 20s I think they're d10s no they're
20s they're 20s so if you ever play DND
again they're not all the same shape
though oh yeah oh they're a bunch of
different ones okay there's like D20 d10
there's a normal Square shaped one
that's so cool
like that you say die right in plural
yeah I rejected that died
what's the plural of dices a dice
wonders nice [\h__\h] it yeah what two what
noise is dice yeah okay what's two dices
yes
clearly clearly it's two against one in
this house so I mean you guys are right
you guys are right
where is mommy from
uh
I remember you were not sure where's my
room you should remember it starts with
a g where is it starts with a g damn one
Germany I mean look look at this is what
German people look like no mommy's from
oh
[Music]
what's the capital of Australia the
capital
of Australia New York
are you for real New York is the capital
of America I don't even
I don't even know I have disowning you
[Music]
oh it's okay yeah it's okay because um I
I have to apologize too
I was bringing Kobo I picked her up and
I was bringing her to uh Kelly's place
and uh
she was getting mad at me though because
I was trying to remember from my head
where Cali lives and I was walking and I
was like okay now we go here and then um
several times I dragged her around the
block basically because I was wrong and
and coma was looking at me she was
squatting down on the ground and just
like looking evil I recorded I didn't
forget mommy getting lost no oh that's
such a childlike thing to do recording
your own parent getting lost well I got
her here after all safely
mission accomplished it's all fine don't
worry see now we're now we're here look
at the tower behind me isn't it cool
it's a sick place
high tree yeah Sky Tree the Sky Tree
yeah
everywhere I want to know it's so tall
and when I got up my my ears a bit hurt
because the pressure and it's so fast
it's so cool and I went to the the on
the in the Sky Tree there's like a glass
floor you can see through down and it's
so cool and then near the Sky Tree
there's a uh asakusa
I went to the temple and it's so cool I
I bought a I bought a what is it like um
I don't know why but it's like a for
Lucky oh well
the fortune
what you didn't get only put
it Fortune well fortunately it's when
you look at like a steak normally
there's a box of sticks and you pull one
out it has a number I really wanted
but I don't know how like next time I'll
show you I've been a shrine Maiden
before for you yeah
well yeah and and actually often it was
a big Shrine so often foreigners would
come too so I was speaking English to
them and explain everything to them in
English but yeah I spoke Japanese with
my colleagues it was really cool but um
what you you went to uh not only to
Tokyo right we went outside too I went
to Kyoto oh Kyoto what is this
it's beautiful but it's boring for me I
can't believe it but my parents enjoyed
a lot because so many uh a good
sceneries there yeah yeah but I want to
go shopping yeah I was saying like she's
such a Zoomer because she cannot
appreciate a beautiful scenery like I
appreciate it still
for shame
five minutes enough she'll grow up and
understand later on yeah how beautiful
Kyoto is much more enjoyable than
although you know I love to go to
college I was just gonna say you seem
like a Harajuku fan qo not anymore but I
used to go there like all the time did I
lose the magic is the magic gone it's
just lasting the amount of people and I
guess the style of clothes I kind of
grew out of it a lot mostly but I used
to go there all the time and and now I
think through an optical illusion you
guys can't see but copper is dressed in
Foley
it's very very let me show you my drip
yeah
before but when I saw her running over
to me I was like what the [\h__\h] is that
some random house
[Music]
that was cool I'm like what
I feel like like if you're extremely
small and cute you can wear anything
from anything anything
yesterday I was uh wearing this I have a
story
yeah I was wearing this
it's more hot yeah you're right this one
like today you're kind of dark and then
yesterday you were kind of bright yeah
so because yesterday I I met with my
mama
um
so I just want to dress up cutely you
know and then
um uh when I when I go to the uh when I
meet up with with um
that's the other mom
and uh oh wait I met her too before I
think I met her before again with all
the whole moms Kiara huh I think with
Iran
I think so I think so or yeah I met a
lot of moms
nice surprise like just just
short moment
collecting all the moms as always
surprised when I when I go into the
train uh there's uh how to say oh this
one
a grandpa be careful
I think I think he's a kind person yeah
it looks okay because intimidating
no it's okay he looks sweet he asked you
if he could sit next to you yeah because
uh
because like normally they just sit down
they don't ask me yeah yeah I I don't
know yeah I don't know but he asked me
like excuse me can I sit here so I think
and then he he talked to me a bit like
where do you come from I'm from
Indonesia you looks pretty I love it
stop talking to strangers like what the
[\h__\h] bro what the [\h__\h] okay this is the
more I'm hearing from this it smells
like something that happened in America
that would be a red flag
no we're talking to strangers
why why isn't that scary it's kind of
weird to be taught it was in a train but
but a lot of people uh in the train yeah
but oh that doesn't happen to the
stranger and the trained in Japan like
out of nowhere that's
um the seat that on the empty is only uh
next to me like that's fine okay that's
fine I guess that he would sit there
yeah
and then and then I
uh like oh when I'm going to uh uh take
off from the train
uh you can follow you right no no no but
but he if he's a coincidence that uh he
doesn't like wanna take off too like
like that and then I said like that like
oh I'm I'm going to eat this station too
and then and then
um
so sweet because because uh well just
yeah like he asked me like where you
wanna go and then I I told him what I
want to go here uh uh and I'm looking
for the station right and he he showed
me the weight you told him where are you
going
[Music]
his mom Behavior
Mamma Mia okay son just be careful next
time
but he's not following me let's go to
other ways you're doing me a big concern
right now
Bobo what if that was a fan
[Music]
it must be because you're so cute look
at that that's all he's not following me
or what okay and then I met with my mama
and uh with my manager too yeah she's
accompanying me okay and also for uh
being a translator okay and then after
that uh I'm going back to my home right
and then uh on the train uh with my
manager they start with my manager when
I was he there again
look at that person uh uh she she looks
like uh she watched anime and then I
joke with my manager like oh yeah maybe
maybe she knows me right like that oh
yeah and then when I take off uh from
the Train
she run
to me
she went to me and then she asked me
like uh do you speak English or Japanese
and then I don't know right because I
thought I thought he is lost maybe she's
gonna ask for she's Japanese or
Foreigner yes she's a Japanese so so I
was thinking like uh noises of uh asking
for train route because because he's a
Japanese and then I I just my manager
mermaids are like that so I so my
manager uh talk with with her and then
uh she said uh okay I love your I love
your vision can I take a picture of you
and post it to Instagram like that and
my manager uh just decline it
immediately like oh
sorry but but she looks
good and then oh and then uh I was just
uh smiling and then oh good boy and she
she ran back into the train okay well
you know what you just experienced I
when I used to wear like more Harajuku
style fashion and all that uh is it
normal yeah it didn't happen quite often
because like there's a lot of like
fashion bloggers and so on and they will
ask you can I take a picture of you and
then they take a few pictures and then
you go
um yeah but it's just kind of crazy that
all of this is happening to you in like
a train situation why I actually think
it's pretty normal I mean people people
always want foreign pictures sometimes
but there's not always but there's
always like maybe somebody in the
vicinity like I remember I was shooting
a music video that never came out by the
way it never came out so don't don't
look don't look you'll find it but um I
was actually in Hong Kong a long time
ago and they took a picture of me
they're like hey you look cool they
thought I was like some kind of famous
person I'm like no no
just because I'm dressed like this no no
no no no no but yeah they wanted
pictures in Japan they want actually
theirs this one time when I was in
Harajuku and I was just walking down the
street and this guy with a camera jumps
out in front of me the sotaku man jumps
out in front of me with his camera takes
a picture and says and runs away he just
ran away though it's not nice normally
like in Harajuku and um
is where these people will be to like
look for a fashionable fashionable
people not just and they will ask you
for a show not they just they don't just
that dude just jumped that's crazy
yeah that stuck with me as a bad memory
in Japan absolutely okay yes for the
future since you're very talkative when
people talk to you apparently
um if somebody if you walk around like
Shibu or something or Shinjuku and some
dude asks you
say no no no you say no no no no no no
why not because
your friends it's a pickup line in Japan
it literally means you want to go get
like some dinner like you want to go you
want to go to the kitchen together like
why not
because now I don't know
because what if I'm hungry and don't
bring any money go with monitron or with
friends call up on the bus call me let
me know I'll go to a cafe we're going to
dinner afterwards anyway you don't need
to find some random dude off of the
street so get you to get there you got
lots of friends all around you and
people who like you already very much
yeah but of course also you're an adult
I know you can take care of yourself but
you know just looking out for you if you
if you need a friend to hang out with in
Japan you don't need to to try and find
strangers to hang with I'll hang out
with you
I'm looking for a Japanese boyfriend
I
[Music]
think it would be easy for you to get a
Japanese boyfriend but let's let's um
let's focus on on our career first okay
[Music]
and if you want a boyfriend you first
bring them to us and we chat you check
them out because there's many many many
people who maybe just don't want to get
serious you know okay cool but what
about the dude in your music video you
have a boy right what happened what
happened
but you were so happy yeah but he's from
Indonesia I don't have any from Japan
yeah all you need one from every country
in the world yeah oh
that makes sense right when you travel
you don't want to be alone it's
convenient to have someone where you go
no no no no no
[Music]
if you want okay
from every country
okay well you don't let us know where
the countries are you don't even know
where any country is okay what can a
boyfriend do for you that we as friends
can't do for you girls hold hands in
Japan if you want to walk around and
hold hands you know we can hold hands
and Cali Cali will probably pay for it I
can buy you yeah I can buy you dinner
from like from like from like you know
the boyfriend will benefit you and then
like like uh
I'll say that right now
but I want that income and boys
[Music]
I can do a 12 year old boy actually
maybe
Chan yeah
I love you
yeah I can kind of do like a boy thing
let's be together forever
thanks come on man you're breaking my
heart no it's good she's just such a
oh yeah
[Music]
life is long and full of experiences so
don't don't you worry for now though for
now just enjoy it but you you you guys
don't know when you will die
I do oh wait yeah we are ready
yeah
and mommy is a phoenix
is I'm just a normal human being I'm
just a racial man oh wait if I die can
you resurrect me that's not really how
Phoenix's work I don't think they can
resurrect themselves
okay okay but but death can resurrect
the death itself or you can just decide
not to rape her or yeah I can't decide
not to kill you you're right that's
about it I can't do necromancy
necromancy is against my beliefs
actually my beliefs and yet you play a
necromancer in Diablo don't tell my
parents man don't tell Dustin
yeah yeah guys you say Phoenix down but
that's already up in church I already
used all my Phoenix down oh so you can't
do it again I mean I'm trying to grow
some more but it's difficult take some
time what does Phoenix down look like
like my ear feathers pretty why don't
you just use those well because I've
kept these are actually
um they're fake so around I already used
a couple and then I I picked them off my
ears and and then I didn't have them and
then I I bought some off of Amazon
what the [\h__\h] oh Kiara
Phoenix the the Phoenix in Final Fantasy
16 looks just like you I heard there's a
phoenix I wanna play
[Applause]
request perms just oh yeah yeah yeah
it's just like you know I'm like you
know right now
so I can't really play it yet but when I
get back I will no you'll love it it's
great did you watch the
[Music]
Trek the cigarettes yeah
I know I'm trying to but you remember
right
right really there's in the second one
there's a phoenix I don't remember
hearing about a phoenix
oh I still have to watch with my with my
deadbeats I promise them I promise them
I would that was just actually last week
my members watch along
nice it was so fun
Phoenix everywhere nice
where do rain shamans ever show up in
movies
yeah can you make it stop raining do you
have the power to take the humidity away
from the hair the air uh
you only make it rain right
yeah but
no I can't I can move I can move the
clouds oh no
please move the clouds every day in my
life there are too many so many clouds
can you make your rain in here
I'm here no I'm done please don't scare
my cats
because if it's raining now
we cannot go outside later of course we
can brain doesn't work are you scared of
rain has arranged them don't stop us
from going anywhere no the the parties
and but there's a bottle here in Japan
in Japan did you know because people
it's still so clean right Japan is such
a clean country yeah right so when it
rains there's people outside who always
like clean the grounds they push the
water away from the ground so that
there's no bottles yeah I'm comparing to
my country sorry
what I never even noticed that I push
the puddles away yeah you don't notice
things that you don't see no more you
know yeah you know dang I'm sure as hell
don't do that in America that's for sure
wow we're all from different places huh
that's crazy what was what was it your
first time in Japan really really first
time at night it's it's like my second
time uh using plan
what I can't even imagine that is it
scary for you
uh it feels like when when it's a flying
take take off it's very uh uh jingling
like
oh I see
yes new and interesting I don't know
I've been flying since I was a baby
Reaper so I don't really know what it's
like to get on an airplane the first
time but it also hurts my my ears yeah
yeah that'll happen you have to yawn a
lot yeah you gotta pop the the bubbles
in your ears yeah what about you Kiara
do you travel a lot as a kid
what what ages kid uh I mean
let's say zero plus four and how long
until four maybe not So Much by airplane
but I remember being like in an airplane
already very very very young yeah yeah
because you know we travel a lot in
Europe too
yeah we like travel get ready to travel
even more Kobo because you're an
international star now yeah you're gonna
be in Japan a lot more I know it yeah
I've been to uh to uh
I went to the whole life Studio oh yeah
no it's nice it's so nice it's so like
we can also we can recording
um there and also can swimming there too
it's so nice I want to live in Japan I
hope you can make use of it for a free
DW someday yeah we're waiting amen but
first is
um
I can't wait I can't wait I'm so hyped
about that
I haven't signed the wall yet in the new
studio yeah me too I was like the third
person in there and I still didn't sign
the wall you know the first time saw the
studio I didn't see them personally the
only way I saw it is for that press
video ah yeah I didn't even see
you so no no I had to find out through a
press video on YouTube
I'm going there I'm going there this
week so yay I'll sign the wall too yeah
you should record a cover there or
something like that real quick I cannot
I'm not allowed to there's no such time
or place but it's just a recording booth
that's different than the 3D
[Music]
hopefully that changes in the next year
so they get more yeah it's just really
busy right now but I want to do 3D
streams from there I want to do like
proper 3D ring fit and stuff like that
man what you mean Moco be not good
enough for you it's fine it's fine and
I'm still gonna use it to beat ring fit
because I'm gonna be I'm gonna be the
first to beat ring fit in whole life
[Music]
and others get ready I want to say that
I've never seen the ending over with it
people kind of just kind of they just
kind of stop after getting like a little
workout yeah I mean that's what it's for
yeah true enough
[Music]
I'm waiting for my 3D to play that
because I think it's more interesting
I want to see
[Music]
we can be together in 3D yeah that would
be so cute yeah I want this right now
but 3D then then oh my God Kelly has to
carry bookable on her back oh okay can
you do it do it it's very strong
plus you are so small yeah
I'm only like 36 kilograms oh wow all
right God are you okay
are you okay oh my God you can lift her
with a finger oh my Lord wow that's
crazy you know I saw the the wheel that
you have right yeah
you guys probably know she has this huge
cat wheel right and and I said it was
cobal size cobal could literally yeah
she could run in there she could crawl
really fast
[Music]
it's a tiny small baby I could throw you
so easily I could pick you up and throw
you please don't tell me I kind of want
to though really do you see that over
there do you see those dumbbells yeah
that's a 10 kilogram dumbbell do you
lift that yeah I just bought myself my
first time
but they're two kilograms and I'm
already struggling with the turkey logo
oh no
that's not a dumbbell that's my ab
roller oh it looks like what is dumbbell
they're underneath the table the little
TV table chairs my step my step machine
out of the way
excellent you know when we were on the
way to you I was carrying some some back
with some stuff inside and after a while
it got too heavy for me so I was like
cool carry this for me instead to the
daughter she said so cute
great question we can settle that now
see there's some two kilograms dumbbells
are you good you should help your
daughter you need help hold on
oh my God I can lift it for a moment
probably
oh oh she's struggling
she lifted it okay it's very very
struggling okay I'll try it too
Kelly [\h__\h]
it's hard to lift Cali is showing Callie
is doing it as if it looks like it looks
really easy when she does it that
daddies leave only with one hand come on
okay I'm trying to lift it over my head
you are strong holy [\h__\h]
oh my God that's so happy
that's wrong respect what is that for
squats
yes and then you just kind of all the
way down to the bottom
back up oh that's that's why your butt
is like you know [\h__\h]
yeah she's squatting
I want to shape my butt too you want to
shave your butt yes
free no okay four times that a little
bit less than four times that is
bookable
damn yeah well that is crazy three times
that if you if you got three of those
yeah and then you put my five kilograms
oh yeah two kilograms
that's crazy wow nice workout ladies
nice workouts
I'm
sorry I have to do a lot of my own
workouts in my house these days just
because it's too hot to go outside
that's cool I want to see your muscle oh
it's not that big it's like very
standard
[Music]
me
wait wait again no Kyary you have a you
have a really good yours is almost
actually no yours is better than mine
let's [\h__\h]
God
let's hear that guys I mean for a really
small small little girl they're all
right
no Kiara I'm really confused how are you
having trouble with the 10 kilogram with
those big muscles yeah I know I can't
carry [\h__\h] for real I can't I couldn't
even carry that they're so toned my my
arm was like in pain after a while from
carrying this really but your muscles
are they maybe super toned from like
your idol days or something like that I
mean but tone doesn't mean that there's
muscles right is it I mean I don't know
the shape is like they're they're hard I
mean this is a nice shape I'm really
trying to like yeah I'm confused
I don't really want bulging muscles
though so I try to be really careful
with like how much I lift like I try to
just do it as a cardio exercise like my
heart rate gets going but like I don't
tone the muscles too much because I
don't want I don't want to be like a
bodybuilder or anything like that
the bodybuilder is cool like uh don't
you want uh like a six pack seven pack
on your tummy I mean eight packs I'm
good I'm good I just want strong size my
thighs are very strong
watermelon with your face so that's why
I do the squats so much the the thighs
they're very very muscular
yes you were here for two weeks right
almost what did you eat
me too I'm so curious
oh she's looking
um funny what are you eating Indonesian
food here no no no no no no no no no
convenience store
well
I love ramen so I think I almost eat
ramen everyday
there's so many I don't know there's so
many
many uh I like I feel like I want to try
uh many many Ramen store what's your
favorite restaurant flavor because
I went to I went to that place
[Music]
[Laughter]
very spicy Ramen is it a chain
is it a chain a Ramen place or just one
does it have more one one one one only
one there's no way we would know I think
there's many places where spicy Ramen
spicy so I ordered the the spiciest
Ramen there whoa
because because uh
[Music]
um my Indonesian tongue yeah we use the
spicy food yeah yeah we used to spicy
food right the spicy in Japan is not
spicy for me oh at all
kind of like do you like uh Curry you
should go to a kokuchi Ramen and get the
most
spicy one of Oreo apparently it's really
spicy really really really spicy okay
okay and my manager she loves spicy food
so she can give you good recommendations
next time you come to Japan if you want
to eat spicy food
I've eaten everything else she gave me
but not this
so this is your first time gonna try
this yeah oh that looks faster though
let's go
I was gonna uh give you give you level
three really yeah but you know what I'll
take a picture and I'll upload it on
sorry I didn't bring anything because
it's too sudden no it's okay
we're meeting because I wrote to call
the last night and to Cali also last
night it's very specific
um
[Music]
I'm not eating that why that's surely
very spicy right I can smell the spices
yeah that's spicy oh really totally fine
so so I have I have another story yeah
so I met to uh uh
with my manager oh yeah that's our
managers yeah and then uh I also give
him this
and uh did he like it just ate this this
small like it's really Fitness I posted
it on Twitter now guys yeah like only
this one and he's tried it
and he
he like and get coffee a lot it's that
bad I don't know but it's good yeah just
right just right that's right
I'm no coward I'm no cows
together okay together okay okay
one two three
oh
holy [\h__\h] yeah it's spicy wait
[Music]
no drink challenge no no really you want
to kill your mom oh I'm trying I'm
trying to not get it on my tongue
Indonesians are on a different freaking
level
God damn
swallows and oh my God
don't cry I can feel my metabolism
speeding up
but I will not eat more than that
it's actually pretty good that's killing
my friend pretty good right yeah I like
them they taste like um actual glass
noodles that you like slurp oh
it's like all the spiciness is in the
fruit once you swallow it it's not so
much on the tongue right yeah yeah
[Music]
that is really hot
In fairness I think water might make it
works but oh no no it was fun
it was fun
it's buying warm water
how about tea
I like these oh yeah yeah yeah it's a
what is it I I don't know I forgot the
name
oh I know there's nuts
I'll take a picture of that too it's
sweet it's weird
is it like sticking together like a
cereal bar yeah oh yeah yeah it's yummy
yummy
that was really hot and those chips are
really hot can we is your carpet okay to
show
yeah okay okay no problem
what what oh what uh [\h__\h] you in German
uh
I I don't even like saying it because I
I feel only like I can swear in English
and in German because it's my own
language I feel like very bad too
sophisticated for it no no I just I feel
bad yeah I don't like to say it but it's
not educational I I want to learn uh
okay it's
um
[Music]
yep yep wagon farted
that means nothing it's not it's not
what it means for like the car to stop
or something or the bus to stop wagon
means uh like a car or so yeah a
fountain Fountain means five and means
Drive yeah
you're talking about like something
nasty
[Music]
that's the what's that the milk yeah
ghost cats ghost cat ghost cat ghost cat
oh wrinkles cat ghost come here ghost
cat oh this is interesting he's very shy
yeah I prefer this snack yeah of course
you do it's like it's like those puffy
Reese puffs
with a Rice Krispie Treat but less sugar
nice
[Music]
I like the glass chips that are spicy
but it definitely yeah yeah yeah yeah it
smells very different from what it
tastes like
it's yummy it's good it's good good
stuff my lips are burning
my lips are burning but my metabolism is
so fast you try too hard to impress Kobo
no I didn't I really like the chips
you know what I'll eat another one
maybe each or well a full stack at once
you're done recording your EP anymore
noodles
it's like I'm eating glass shards with
spicy sauce
oh man wow
Indonesian snacks yeah yeah Luna came in
clutch she's gonna bring me some more
apparently
[Music]
oh nice I need the best of your back she
said she'd bring me more
came here
me Iris and Luna had a pizza party
watching um what was it oh hola Fest
yeah
after it was done
[Music]
it was fun
I haven't seen her in a while yeah and
she's so cool have you met Mona because
I think I do members there's no one who
hasn't met each other right we all know
each other yeah yeah yeah we met each
other that's the good thing about living
all in one country and we're all
scattered all over everyone moved to
Japan already come on I'm lonely it's
just me and Iris
[Music]
did you know the instrumental song are
you guys using
[Music]
I don't know
but still I'm sorry but then we need
permission for on our classroom right if
it's on kind of fun it's okay because
then we have the instrumentals for
another cup stream as long as we have
the instrumentals and as long as it's
not um
sorry about that
[Laughter]
um
you didn't go to Disneyland did you I
haven't because
yeah I'm I'm bringing my family oh you
have you want to bring your family oh
yeah oh no no because I agree with my
family because they
are they're not into that stuff but
Indonesia has no Disneyland right no you
should go here next time yeah yeah go to
Disneyland
cool
yeah Disney's super fun here but you
know get ready for lines go on a not
busy day I mean it's so expensive the
ticket for me yeah and then and because
I still I still promised me one free
ticket to Disneyland so I was waiting
for that day I still promise
um
he promised me uh and also Universal
Studios yeah don't get your hopes up for
the Nintendo World though because yeah
chances are you won't get in we want it
we won so badly run I still no don't
tell him to run he made a promise
you have so many John this is so cute so
cute yeah
that's so cute yeah I love that people
but being treated well this time when
when I when I met Puma uh he played the
ramen
so back to the topic I wanted to know
what else did you eat besides Ramen
did you eat sushi yes
I really loved it
yeah I I always ordered that uh whenever
I go to sushi places did you eat any
like donburi kind of you know the rice
balls with you know whatever
I don't want rice
I found Indonesia also uses rice a lot
that's why I'm getting bored of fries
Japan is the land of rice so I mean did
you eat yakisoba not yet well it's
noodle right yeah noodle no I'm not cold
normally butter fried you she didn't do
you didn't go Jackie Nico yet and this
is two weeks so uh
we gotta go somewhere
yeah yeah yeah let's see we'll see I'm
still thinking about where we need to go
yeah
there's good places
somewhere good trust me the only thing
she cannot eat is vegetables why yeah
you're like
she can't eat vegetables either really
she just doesn't eat
I don't know what she seems like the
kind of person who would properly eat
her vegetables though no right but like
we were at dinner and she's just like
I'm like yeah let's get some veggies I
think what are we doing yakimiku as well
I think it was Yakiniku and I was like
let's get some veggies she's like okay
you can have them I was like huh she's
like yeah I won't eat it I'm like I
can't but to be honest when I go to
Yakiniku I also don't I don't want to
order too many vegetables either because
I want to enjoy as much meat as I can a
little salad on the side yeah salad's
good eat your salad no protein too much
it's good it's just I don't understand
how there are some girls especially like
my sister for example never eats any
vegetables she just eats just the most
the most unhealthy food Fried Chicken
all the time fast food all the time and
she's in such good shape she's so thin I
don't understand it's genetics
she got she got the skinny side because
I have yeah for two different ones you
know what that's fine because I like
working out
um
I like I like working out and running
she also does not have some other things
that I have so yeah this is how it goes
it sounds like me too
it's not a skilly soup
skill is you
come on
where are the Capitals I hear them
running around yeah they're causing
Mischief they're about to get real
mischievous we need to get out of there
before they get really mischievous
because they will run across the
keyboard back and forth as much as they
like but have they not calmed down at
all no we even took ghost cat's balls
he's still the same oh
and even tutu you know she got she got
her her tummy
oh it's nice it wasn't I I told you
about right when my cats had that but
she also like you know oh um so tutu's
too small for like a cone or anything
like that so they had to give her a
special dress I call it her princess
dress she did not like it when you
picked her apple she's still sleeping no
actually she was wide awake but she's a
mistress
[Laughter]
princess dress did it work yeah well no
actually she still tried to lick the
stitches I don't know yeah she very much
was able to like she would like sit like
this leg spread and like try and get
under the dress and she did it a couple
of times
I had to take her back to get the dress
put back on but
now they cannot make babies they cannot
sometimes I think to myself it would be
cute if they had yeah it was fake
sometimes
but they're both females so it's not
gonna work out anyway yeah I mean you
also got to be ready for the
responsibility
[Music]
no he's he's a he's a bad boy he has two
alternate sides
um I call one of them ghost cat which is
like the sweet side and then Ando which
is the bad side the reason for that is
because I called the two of them ghost
cat Abdul tutu ghost cat and tutu so you
have a free cast yeah so I decided to
call him and though when he's when he's
acting up
and those
those are very human
the human name
but yeah those are my cats Coco do you
have cats dogs tell me about your dog my
dog is cute it's a corgi
[Music]
okay I can get with that you know the
Corgi I'm very hyperactive
cute and very
stupid oh I mean yeah those exist I I
tell you hyperactive in I'm really
really happy more hyperactive than you I
don't believe that yeah
I don't know like really hyperactive
really they're hyper that's cool that's
exactly what I prefer cats because dogs
are just generally so no that's no cats
are lazy ah that is true tutu was lazing
it up over there yeah that's why I like
them because I feel like I wouldn't be
able to give like a really excited doggy
like the love it deserves when it comes
up to me to like want pets and like
kisses and whatnot I can't give that
back because I'd be like ah I'm tired or
like I want to be alone Etc so I'm just
I'm just better with cats I think but I
still think dogs are super cute other
people's dogs are cute
of course I was actually thinking in the
future I wouldn't get a dog and I was
thinking either or Corgi or a Samoyed
dog
fluffy
yeah they're really big I actually
prefer bigger dolls yeah
I'm not doing it right away anyway but
I'm thinking if I got a dog it'll be one
of those two but probably a corgi
because Corgi less worked in samoyance
too much fur
let me show you the dog I want oh wow
here it's not a cute dog you guys are
like oh these are the cute dogs that I
want Etc
no Chad probably already knows Chihuahua
[Music]
come on
do you want the snoot dog what the [\h__\h]
oh oh oh interesting
he's got the long nose wow
you look Majestic this is cool I just
think it's a cool it's scary
yeah you think this is a scary dog
oh he doesn't want to hurt you it's so
weird because like the the side profile
of the whole body looks so like wow
interesting and then if you look at the
face it's just a very funny look at him
look at him yeah he's got a long nose
here
all the other pictures it didn't look so
crazy
it looks like a little rat
I love this dog so much oh look at look
at the little tongue look at how happy
he is look at his little lips it's
freaking me out I love this dog so much
it looks like I can got hit by by their
nose oh yeah like stuff like they had
like a regular nose and then like
something came down from above and like
went push nose extensions
I've never seen big dog in Japan
they definitely exist I'm sure it is
very rare maybe on the countryside and
so on but can I you you saw you didn't
burn you saw how small all the houses
and apartments are in Japan so there's
no space normally for big dogs yeah it
was even hard for me to be allowed to
have cats in here
[Music]
a lot yeah usually did you know most
apartments in houses in Tokyo or like in
cities or actually probably even outside
don't allow pets you know no she's so
stupid most places don't allow pets you
have to actually buy a house or get the
okay isn't that right tutu
so many people don't have pets which is
very sad because so many people want
pets and that's why there's so many cat
cafes and other pets coming oh yeah
did you go to a cat cafe yeah I bet
you'd like it and that they also have
Dog Cafe in Harajuku yeah yeah yeah I've
seen it and also they have old water
[Music]
otters are a little smelly though they
really stink but they're cute they are
cute my Penguins what about weasels
what is weasels
[Music]
yeah favorite that's what I mean I think
oh yeah I think you know weasel I think
it's illegal
ferrets
yeah it's so cute this is a weasel you
definitely can't own this
yes here's the difference there's
weasels yes
like it yeah much larger in size
apparently I thought it would be the
other way around
we have aren't ferrets weasels no
they're they're not they're just related
oh look how cute the weasel I think
weasels are cuter though
[Music]
they have cuter faces that's a little
weasel why don't you put a weasel uh
because they'll kill you
don't bite the [\h__\h] out of here well if
you're as small as Kobo yeah
right they're little cutie Cutie Pies
they're weasels and I used to want to
ferret and then I went to a pet store
and like played with the ferrets there
and they bit the hell out of me and I
was like never mind they're very mean
yeah
ugly
nice
yeah real nice scars looks cool yeah I
guess yeah I went to the pet ferret and
the ferret rejected me so look at how
cute they can look
very hard to take care of they also
smell very bad but people love them
cats and dogs
do you know um what my favorite animal
is cat no
cats are number two well yeah because I
can't own the first two that I'm that I
love first of all fox fox I love foxes
can't own a fox then there's the
ringtail lemur
oh
we have them in Indonesia it looks like
it looks like they're gonna move it move
it yeah yeah
this is my favorite animal is it exotic
exotic anymore yes you can't own this as
a pet you'll get thrown in jail but look
at this funny guy look at his big eyes I
understand why you like him yes yes yeah
look at the frigate and the nose we need
a limber Beach
spoiler next June wow
please make it happen you go you make
dreams come true give me a lemur give me
a lemur
[Music]
I think it's the snout
snout is kind of fox-like and then they
have like a long tail but I mean I think
that's it well Japanese people and they
use this
Dawn when I was young
thinking Japanese people use kits on the
meat
markets in the dawn but they don't they
don't they don't couple they don't it's
just called kids
why would they use such meat no how
could you but it's just tofu right right
exactly no ghost cat you're not gonna
move my mouse
he's like he's like it's time to get on
the keyboard yes
[Music]
I said it wrong that's why it didn't
look how do you say it Kiara
okay but it turns out it's actually not
German oh what is that what is that it's
like you know this is German no it's
actually man I know it's German because
it sounds like German yeah it's also
Giver it's just King German so what
language is it nothing it's just made us
yeah it's this meme where Koba actually
showed it to me the first time it's like
a guy who's like talking to cats while
filming it and he calls them in every
language like means
and they never look and then he says and
then they look and then he says what
does he say after that
[Music]
um
we recorded that Meme for a YouTube
short oh that's so cute yeah I love that
I want to see it on the girl that's cute
hey ghost cat wagon farted
no I didn't I didn't learn it from
Duolingo I looked it up after because I
was like I want to use this I want to
actually say words
they're only looking because you're
scaring them
it's literally a cat toy yo guys get out
of her purse
um that's that's cats are playing with
my back yeah my back inside my back
there's nothing in my bag
[Music]
come on
it's okay
I want to start dominance
oh my god oh
the kids are getting little tree
I want a more tree because they deserve
to be treated right now so I'm not
deserved to
or do you want to catch treaty do you do
we feed her cat treats okay she wants to
try
I mean maybe it's different yeah
Indonesian cat cat food and maybe
Japanese cat food is more hygiene or
maybe it can be eaten by human you know
well I mean I think anywhere you could
eat cat food and dog food but I mean why
would you choose to do it over eating
human food
Okay Google taste testing
[Music]
it smells good
they're toothbrushing trees oh God she's
eating it with a straight face what do
we think about the tree how are you
keeping a straight face Google it's so
sticky I almost threw up from it does it
smell like fish it smelled yeah like
fishy and weird give us your honest
opinions doing a thinking thing what's
your honest opinion of the cat treat
that you just consumed oh the aftertaste
is
uh mama
[Laughter]
what does it taste like is it fish is it
chicken plastic oh
well the cats go crazy yeah edible
plastic with fish yeah yeah so these
treats are actually supposed to like
brush the cat's teeth it works as like a
breath freshener for them oh I don't see
how that would freshen up it's hard to
believe but you know it's it works you
know their breath will just be rancid
before I give them those treats and then
it's like you want something to drink
I have mineral water okay you're not
gonna wash down the the taste of the
treat from your mouth
wow damn I respect seriously
so chill she doesn't
look yeah it's not
bad was so mysterious
that's right why don't you eat
cat treats
[Music]
I can't read
I eat the same piece of cat treat that
you gave me am I your favorite parent
can I be your favorite parent all right
time to eat the cat treat here I go
you're ready
[Music]
yes oh God the b word let's go please I
swear
[Music]
together Bye Mom
put that tree together
[Music]
unbelievable they both left me to eat
cat treats
they're eating it together eating extra
oh Cali
not looking as happy as cool not good
but like no I mean I'm not throwing up
so I mean
well Kiara
[Music]
cat treats for days
you are the reason why your parents are
not doing so well
oh and I get in trouble for saying Kobo
you're adopted what
wow that's harsh that is Harsh here so
one more left to see who gets it
[Music]
what
just I just threw another piece of the
treat over there they'll find it they're
very good Hunters which is going to come
in handy when the Cockroaches start
coming out
uh I don't want that I don't want that
in Japan
Japan well we're gonna eat some yummy
food soon so dinner dinner
I hope it's not cat food
well little do you know I'm actually
taking you to the pet store I'm gonna
serve a full course meal of cat jerky
not not jerky made of cats jerky made
for cats
I'm gonna undo what has been what has
gone wrong here today I'm gonna undo it
sooner or later don't worry how how do
you intend to do that I will break it
out to a freaking pony ride no you won't
yes I will no you won't no you won't I'm
gonna no you won't I'm gonna give her a
violin on the guitar and everything
[Music]
oh no we'll see if we'll see what
happens oh gosh it's hard being a parent
isn't it
it's okay Mommy we're um it's just your
uncle there well yeah but there is a dad
at the end of that Uncle so I think
this is how it goes ladies I'm sad
we're gonna go to cat cover and eat cat
food let's go yeah yeah ask ask the
people working at the Cat Cafe say we
don't want the regular menu we want the
cat food we're Auntie mainstream mom
those are my tax those are my tax papers
maybe next time we pull up together we
can have a therapist to help us with
this oh nice idea yeah that sounds good
could use one of those yeah I wonder how
that would go
[Music]
she's my little princess
yeah she's really affectionate right now
I think it's that it's that time of the
the month where the cat gets really the
girl cat gets very affectionate oh man
they're always affection oh really do
you notice a difference yeah really yeah
sometimes she's just very aloof won't
let me pick her up and whatnot and then
other times she's just rolling on the
ground rolling all over the bed purring
so loud
bye God they're so cute they're much
bigger now that you'd see them as as
they are now right now I feel like
um ghost cat definitely grew
but tutu looks pretty much the same to
me yeah she's just a small cat yeah I
think she's just tiny I thought three
months would change it more Lucas
still not outgrown I would say by far
not yet the fact that ghost cat's gonna
get bigger is scaring me because he's
kind of fat yeah he's not fat he's got a
little bit of fat hanging down
that's the the something something pouch
oh I have a special pouch okay yeah I I
also didn't know until much longer my
one of my cats is the same chunky monkey
they have some cats not every cat have
like genetically that what's it called
[Music]
that sounds like some Cthulhu it makes
your belly head
it's kind of cute though no I wanna I
wanna pet the primordial pouch now ah
it's apparently an armor for their guts
it's survival pouch really is that what
it's used for originally it protects
your vulnerable tummy
baby that's so cute well I will always
keep ghost cat safe so he doesn't need
to use that at all I love I love the pet
that Flappy belly from chunky monkey so
it's good cute cats it's a good pouch
wow that's so sweet good chunk well I'm
hungry so yeah let's go eat
yeah shall we get ready to take off I
think we should yes is it is it far no
no no no no I won't say how far it is
but it's not far my feet
no no we travel by taxi and we travel by
taxes
[Music]
nice also buy milks milk oh you want
milk don't buy milk alone
all right well thanks for coming to my
house you guys for a cool thank you for
being
awesome
I wasn't gonna say no to you guys come
on now yeah thank you
thank you yeah nice that was fun well
everybody else a quick announcement for
what I guess we'll all do in the next
coming days tomorrow I'm playing Final
Fantasy 16 for a very long time how
about you guys oh actually uh I will can
I use this opportunity not from
something from me but uh just today a
couple hours ago nine seven hours ago
eight hours ago uh we announced that
we're we have a little a whole low life
myth of uh English uh listening
book thingy yeah with a CD and you know
some people were like I don't know about
that it's Japanese or so no no it's not
Japanese it's English and even if you
already know English it's basically like
a like a voice pack yeah right I mean
the English is pretty Advanced I would
say actually even because some of the
lines we recorded I was like whoa they
got a really good listener to like you
know get this but still JP Bros don't
worry I think you'll enjoy it but if you
guys just want to hear us go on like a
little Adventure grab the textbook yeah
because normally we our voice packs are
usually solo but this is basically a
huge collab voice pack it's really long
so many lines
it has a story line and everything
um but just so you guys know you can get
it of Amazon uh but the digital version
apparently does not come with the audio
Yeah so you should get it with the book
because the book is so cute too
cute drawings you guys will love it yeah
so check it out it was tweeted on the
Japanese home left with us so far and
maybe we asked them to do it online
we'll see and I retweeted it if you want
to find it and that's that's one thing
yeah and then of course on in a couple
days how many days is it left we have
our big concert yeah I just did the
countdown video yeah you're supposed to
dance today so how many days was it
[Music]
you guys please watch us too we're so
excited for it was there anything else
that we should maybe because I feel like
there's so much going on
to something else that we we forgot
those pagato uh check the link in the
description for my brand new EP it's a
it's a rock Rocky P rock with some rap
EP I worked really hard on it I just
finished recording it and I'm really
really proud of it
um also I have a really big announcement
coming up on July 3rd oh my God I'll
give a hint about that announcement on
July 1st oh so anyway I just look
forward to it it's a really big deal
vacation
[Music]
your family
um
yeah enjoy but uh but it's just we're
not really used to walk
there is a lot of walking you gotta do
yeah yeah yeah your side's in you gotta
Vlog yeah you gotta wear the right shoes
you're wearing the wrong shoes today
[Music]
it's just for today okay okay it was
cute shoes though now she's wearing my
death Sensei slippers yeah it's so
comfortable I love it I'm happy I think
I must do I have this kind of merch yeah
you should learn
yeah so cute
well thanks for hanging out with us
today you guys
um we'll see you all in the future with
all the amazing things we're doing
there's a lot going on so look forward
to it things are about to get even more
exciting so yeah look forward to all the
stuff we're doing we're about to get
down yeah
bye everybody bye everybody
[Music]
foreign
don't
[Music]
thank you