who yeah
I Don't Wanna Stop it yet playing my
Channel Boy as soon as I saw you I know
oh yeah now you got me down
uh yeah now now if it ain't you baby
then I'm done yeah yeah oh girl you know
mm-hmm
[Music]
but I don't know baby you're captivating
me
pretty
love hate all the same if you know play
the game imma looked up up inside no I
can't fight the feeling and I won't try
love hey all the same if you look fine
again
[Music]
I'm still looking don't ever let
yourself fall in you got it cause Love's
just like a toxin the weight pain is so
common your problem I can't solve it I'm
just not full in love know that it's
more than a crush so you can't save me
I'm in too deep and I love the rush yeah
it's good
[Music]
right
laughs
oh where am I where's my mommy
who is she
oh God
oh Mommy I love her
anymore
[Music]
this is my pretty side
well this is
the game we play Love hatred send me
Trey
[Music]
all right who turned the lights off