[Music]
This program is brought to you by our sponsors.
[Laughter]
[Music]
As usual, I would like to explain this program a little bit.  This
is an interview talk show aimed at English-speaking countries.The purpose is to let people overseas learn more about Japanese talent while also focusing on herbal medicine.The
host, Takanashi,
is brought to you by Chara.This
is the 28th time.  Yay, bye bye and
all requests Today's guest is
Tokoyami
[Music] Welcome Can you
hear me? Everyone, I heard you can hear Toa-senpai's voice. I'm
glad.
First of all, please introduce yourself as if you were a winner.
[Music]
Actually, this is our second collaboration. Yay,
that's right.  So I'm not a little nervous,
but really, it was our first collaboration before and that
off-collaboration, so I was
already excited, so that day I
wasn't nervous either. He's
kind.
Tokoyami
andapiter
andre
after
senpai.  Well, today we're
going to explore a lot of things, so I'd
be happy if you could tell me more about it.No, no, I don't want to.I'm sure you'll
tell me a lot of things today.Yes
, then, what kind of
activities have you been doing lately?
These days, I've been singing as usual.
Activities and the rest
are FPS games. Well, I
was streaming it a while ago, right? I'm so
confused that I'm going to streamer you.
PostureNone Are you
ready for tomorrow morning with a game?
No, I'm not ready at all. There's an APEX
event tomorrow.  But, do you
have a name for it?
[Music]
Yeah, I'm going to do it,
right?
Streaming OK, everyone, please
come and support me.
Thank you for being so kind, no, no, I'm
sure you're nervous. I've done this many times already.
How often do things like this
come out? It
depends on the event,
but UUM is planning this, and
it's probably once every six months or so,
especially this
festival.  That's right, that's right, that's right. I
see. I'm growing a team. You told me earlier. Before the broadcast, you'll randomly
join a team. I'm so
excited.
Good luck. Good Rakuten in English.
Is there a good phrase for "It hurts," but in Japanese?
Good.  If it's a rack, I'm
not saying "Good luck," but I'm
hoping for a good result.
[Laughs]
That's definitely OK, then let's move on to the next question.
Okay, where is this?
Towa-senpai is Hololive.  How did you find it in the first place,
and what caused you to become gray again?
No, but the door is Hololive.
After all, at that time, I was from that or settlement,
but
when I was in the human world, that
thing called vtubers was becoming popular, so
that's it.  I don't have any friends in the human world,
so I thought I'd like some friends,
and I also like dancing, so
when I got used to 3D, I
realized how beautiful Hololive was.  The sky was
rising and everything was beautiful, but
the 3D of Hololive at that time
was very attractive,
and I thought I wanted to dance in that 3D, and I
wanted to make friends, so I accepted Hololive.
Ok Google, let's
dance, right?
[Music]
So let's do it
What, what, what, what, let
's do it I
'm waiting I wonder when that day will come I
wonder when it will come My heart is
pounding So let's move on to the next question
[Music]
Now  Until now, I couldn't say it because of the language barrier,
but have you ever been able to say it when you're overseas? Even though it's a
language barrier, I mean, there
's Passion English, so
there's Place English, so I've already
said I LOVE YOU. I've always loved you
so much.  This is all I have.
[Music]
Thank you for finding me.
I'll tell you OK.
Thank you for finding assing.
[Music]
So
please do your best to express your feelings in personal English.
Um
[Music]
don'tspeakjapanese
speakjapanese
you don't
say you can know
Yes yeah yeah yeah yeah Understand
Toran Cage
Senkyu Just to
clarify, I
don't know Japanese for the door, but it's
just Japanese.  Thank you for trying to understand me. I
'm OK with that. It
seems to be getting across. I've
decided to enroll in English. That's
amazing. Thank you very much.
In addition to those Japanese and English, my senior is also studying a little Korean. The more I study
Korean, the more I study.  It's not like I play
that game, but it's a light game, and I have a lot to do with Korean people, and I
can only report simple locations.I see,
but I've heard that
with things like APEX, Towa-senpai has traveled to many different
countries.  It's like I'm picking up a few words. I
can't have a conversation, but it's
like just a little communication. If I look into it, it's
saying something all the time. Right in
front of me, right in front of me. Yeah, that's
right.
[Music] That's
how I like it.  It's wide,
but what you're trying to pick up is, ``This is it.
'' It's not a word that can be used in real life, right? It's like that, isn't it? I don't really use it that much.
Among the words that APEX uses,
are there any words that can be used outside? Can
be used outside, too.  It's all about things.Even
if it's not Korean anymore, there
may be only the word for FPS in English.This
won't help.I'Mthe
I'MDeadTOURThe last thing you need is the last one.I
hope you don't have to say that.Directions
etc.  I wonder if it's possible. No,
but I don't know. Suppose I
'm outside Japan, and someone from overseas asks me
how I can
get to Shibuya, I can tell them. No, I'm talking about if it's
already close.
Light
side
[Music] It's
straight forward.
[Laughs]
Well, I wonder if it
gets across. I'm
giving you Google Maps on my Prius smartphone. It
's Google Maps.
[Laughs]
[Music]
Yes
Is this Toa-senpai's favorite stream? Games, karaoke, chats,
collaborations, etc.
However,
people have joined the collaboration front because they wanted to make friends,
so it's interesting to chat with people about game collaborations
like this,
and when it comes to large-scale collaboration
projects,
everyone joins us.  I'm
having fun. I
really like watching them
. I
love the Yuruhoro series, so much so that I can definitely invite them
. That's good, please invite me. Yes, it's
lame, but
even if it's lame, it's okay. That's why it's
ok.
Well, it's a follow cart from 2 years ago.
Conversation  But
even though I tried really hard, I
Got My Your. When I
say that I got Mario Kart, it's
easy to say that
Mario Kart is unfair, so it
's like I just encountered something unfair,
right?
Everything was fine.  Even if you do it all at once, it
feels like you're seriously kidding when all four people are trying to throw things at you at the same time.You feel like you shouldn't be kidding around.What's
interesting about coming up with loose plans at times like this is that it's loose and loose.It's like you
can't always collaborate.  I don't think it's necessary because I think it would be fun to hang out
with people I don't often collaborate with and
form a team, so it's
not necessary.
[Music]
I'm looking forward to the next night.  But
here,
there's a cutout here, it's not related,
but it's not related to Mario Kart or something like that,
but there's
only the same face, so it's
so written
[Music]
Cute, cute,
kids.  Even though it was so cute back then, you
said you wanted something. What did you
say you wanted? Glugaga's
panda BlueGO is the one from earlier. I
want this with teary eyes.
Let's just say I want the lantern of the soul.  Kana
[Music] A
family on a journey It
's hard to move, right?
Hey,
what's that?
[Music] What's that
? I'll
be surprised. Let's go, let's go. Come for a
walk, come for a walk.
Move 2,500, and from today on, you
'll listen to what I say.  Sometimes my friends died in battle.
[Music] It
's too slow.
[Music]
Here, the
trial shop.
[Music] Is
n't this enough?
Isn't it okay to just add snot?
This is so bad.  Isn't this the one? Is
there a difference? It's a runny
nose. Isn't it okay to wear it? It's
cute. I
want the lantern of the soul.
Thank you very much.
[Music]
When I tried to carry it,
nothing happened to me. It was
crying.  The octopus was a crybaby. It
took a long time to get to the nearest one.
[Music] I like
it.
[Music] It's
really
cute.
Okay. Nice
delivery. I feel
sorry for the panda, because it's been cut out so many times, and this and that.  I'm thinking, this is
true, I
'm pouring out that kind of love, it's
okay, it's only love. Did
you get that? Oooh,
it came. You
gave me a present. That's nice.
But it's nice.
[Music] It
's an exchange. I'm
so happy.  I recently
went to pick it up myself. You can find it pretty much anywhere. I
don't mean "everywhere," but it's called "camp"
in Japanese. "A
camp of terrible people."
What does that
mean in Japanese? I have a feeling.
Well, if you go to her place, you'll find
detectives everywhere with
that thing in them.  Is it necessary? Let's
go back.
Okay, here.
Now, let's go back to normal questions.
This clipping shows that Towa-senpai's broadcast is generally
like this. I
think I got it across. It's
bad. It's difficult. It's kind to animals, isn't it? That one
time.  Even after the panda died, he did
his best and brought a new one with him.I
think it's amazing that he didn't give up and kept going.Okay, I
won't give up.Okay,
next is about FPS.What made you
interested in FPS games and got into it?  I mean, it's my
first time, so when I first went to school, I really
played a lot of Nintendo games like 3DS and DNS3DS, but
even though I was able to save money from that part-time job, I did
n't have a computer where I could use the internet and play games.
PUBG was popular at the time, so I started playing AUPG.
Yeah, my
friend, my
friend on the Internet, asked me to play it with him, so I
bought it with the money I had saved from my part-time job, and then I played FPS for the first time.
[Music] I
won, I won.  Well,
there's going to be something like Champion, number one. It felt so good, and that's how it
felt when I bought it.
My senior got pretty good at it pretty quickly, so I bought it because I was
n't good at it at all, and it was my
first time making friends.  Yeah, I'm already a beginner, and I
don't really do face-to-face battles with other
players, but I'm really happy when I see someone else win, and I wonder
if they bought it because someone else was good at it.  It's
like I died. Are you
kind? I was lucky.
Ok, I'll just translate it here for now.  Well,
how long does it take?
Well, it depends on the person, but I've
played a lot of doors, but I'm still not very good at it. I'd really like to
go to the APEX chinament and
win. There
are other factors involved, for example.
Reports,
covers, how to cover, etc.
Since the results are out, you're the one. I
think you should admit it. I
have one more question about winnings fpson.
Well,
just tomorrow,
there will be a tournament.  So,
how do you prepare when you go to an APEX match
?
[Music]
But tomorrow is a pretty casual
tournament. It's more like an event than a tournament, so
yeah, I won't be doing anything special tomorrow,
but yeah, it's like a
practice period.  When I have a competition like the actual one, I'll
go for a massage before the competition,
take a bath, and make myself
clean.If I really
want to relax, I'll relax my
body once before that.I'll be nervous,
so I'll relax.I see,
but that's it.  What I
wanted to ask was, ``How long
do you
practice?'' I still have to practice
[Music]
What do you mean by practice? It's like
that tournament. But when it's a tournament, it's definitely 3 hours a day.
There's something like that Scream, that practice tournament, so it
's not like three to six hours,
it's like a month or whatever, but it
's like a week.
OkOkGoogle
[Music]
[Music] That's
amazing. I'm
sneezing.
[Music] This
may have been the first time I put Bless You inside my house. It's
nice because I was always told
that. You know, when I lived in Japan, even if I sneezed, in Japan, people just kind of ignored me, didn't I?  I
thought it was a bit lonely,
so I
can count on my hands the number of Japanese people who would say "Brassy" to me, so I
feel like they would say "A-chan" to me.I
found out about this kind-hearted Vtuber after she became a
real listener from overseas.  I
felt like I learned about it thanks to the listeners.
It's a word that can be used in real life. It's
true,
but wait a minute.
But when you're overseas,
say something to a stranger next to you at a store, for example.
[Music]
Yeah, well, I think kind people would say that. Hmm,
basically speaking, it's good.
[Music] I wonder
what's going on inside me at that time, and I'm
thinking about other things, and I
notice when I'm distracted.  I might not say it when I don't have it,
but it depends on the situation.
But by the way, in German, I say ``
Wait a minute, it's difficult,
suddenly it's difficult.''
[Music]
This means ``good'', so
stay healthy.  That
's true, but I'm
sure you'll lose weight soon. If you
remember that, I'll be happy.
Yes, please take care of yourself, but it's true that
in the world of Japanese sales houses, you might not be told anything, but
in the broadcast, people
say that sneezing will help you.  No,
that's because it's just the internet,
but yeah, it helps. I'm
happy. I'm not happy.
[Laughs] I don't have a
runny nose, it
's
okay. It's okay.
Well, I
sometimes collaborate with e-sports streamers, but
what do I like about e-sports? Well, the fact that you
get better at it if you practice a lot
[Music]
But I think Mario Kart is also an e-sports,
right?  Well, it's not just FPS.
E-sports is certainly
something like Street Fighter, and
E-sports is
more like a competition for games,
so it's not just sports, it
's E-sports.  What does it stand for?
Good sports are,
erm, sports. I'm an engineer who thinks that's the case. I
write this out of love, but the reason why it became so good is probably not.
Electronic sports.
Electronic?
Games played on computers,
computers, other PS4s, etc.  That's fine,
but anyway, I
like games, the Internet, and electronic sports.It doesn't matter what I like,
but I like regular sports as well.Maybe I just
like fighting.I
try my best and fight.  Is it
more fun to have a rival whiskey in a game where you try your best? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I might like it a lot,
but the more I like cooperation, the more I
like cooperation. Sisters
your birthday
[Music]
ICEjustthe
By the way, if
Towa-senpai had
n't been a vtuber, Hololive
would have become a sports professional, or something like that.
In a realistic way, I
can no longer manage my time and my life.I see, I hope things go
well, but if they don't, I won't be able to live my life, so I
guess I don't do it because I'm scared.
Okay, it's fun.
Hololive. I see. It's
thanks to Toa-senpai that Hololive's Mario Kart Cup has been held so many times.
But how do you
put it together? And are there any other
projects like this you'd like to do?
How do you put it together? What do you mean by "how do you put it together?"  I
think there's a lot of preparation involved, so I
think people are thinking, ``I have to do something like this,'' but I don't know
what's important about it.But
Mario Kart is already a normal thing.Assembling it is
easy.It's usually the first thing I do every day.
Mario Kart
doesn't have a lot of lag, but it's
not like I can't do it because of the lag.
When I'm doing things in Japan or overseas,  When I do it with the ID of the ID, it's because I
can do that, so I definitely
want to do it with all the kids from that house and the ID.And there's
no need for words, Mario
Kart, it
's an individual skill, so that's why I want to do it
alone.  Because it's a game to be played, the Mario
Kart tournament is held by all of us at
JPenid.We
first ask the management about the date and time when we can do it, and
then we decide on what day and time it will be held about a month, two months, a month and a
half in advance.  I
started recruiting people, and
then I thought about it more and more.Once I found someone, I
thought it would be expensive to make blocks that looked good, and even the illustrations would be great.My senior thought, ``Wow, I'd be happy if things got a little exciting.''  I'm
watching it, and it's getting more exciting every time I
see it, and I feel like E-chan and the
management are helping out in some way.Nowadays, I
'm asking them to order illustrations and things like that,
but
basically it's just the flow of the script.  The
door is doing all the contacting everyone. Ah, I see the
script. Ok Google [Music] Do you want to plan a game? [Music] I'm going somewhere else. I saw God Field a little bit the other day, but what kind of game is
that?  It's
really a game like rock, paper, scissors, rock, paper, scissors, etc.
Water is said to be strong against fire cards.Water
is strong against fire.It's the same thing.When a
card is played, you block it with water.I
thought it was some kind of trading game.  It looked like that. It
must have been a really easy game. It
made me want to create an Anpanman project that anyone could play.
" He said, "It's
Godfield, the orange cat. I
like orange lasagna."  Cat
Garfilt It's a
famous cat. Let's look it up, but it's not Garzelda,
it's Garfield." He said,
"
Who bought it? Yesterday, my
senior, and
of course Pai,
were also there. When I
asked him about something like that, he said, ``Is it Garfield?''  It's easier if I don't participate when I'm making something.
Well, I
could have participated, but the
number of people would
be a little half-hearted, so when I
watched it, I was sure that
it was your
and I
see. Ok, okay, let's
move on to the next question.
[Music] This
is Rakuten.
What made you interested in Herbal Volume Reduction
Senpai? And I'll show you a photo.
Feminine power. This is
beautiful, isn'tit?
[Music]
Cute. You probably
have a lot of experiences when you go out once or something.  I
had some free time with the experience, so I thought I'd give it a try, and
then I found it
interesting,
so I thought maybe I should try it at home, too.Wait,
this is it.I
think you told me about it the last time we collaborated.I
heard about this, but, but, but.  It would be
nice if you could tell me how to hold it all together. I see. That's a dangerous experience. That's great. When should I make it for a present or something? No, it's when I have free time. If I wanted to make it now, I'd have some materials that I already had.
Maybe there's no more oil left, but I'm also in. Oh,
oil, oil, oil, yeah, it's
all that watery stuff.
What kind of oil is that?
Save that flower.
But it's a real flower.
Yes, it's a real flower. It's a
different, real dried flower that I thought was fake.
I see,
andresqueense
[Music]
and
todayspresents
[Music] I see,
that's cute girl power,
ISS.
[Laughs] I'm
sure you mentioned that you have similar hobbies to Shigure Ame-chan, which I talked about last time. That's
great. Someday, Ame-chan will be back again.  If you come to Japan,
how about collaborating with the two of us like that
?
Well, I'd like to do that. I'd like to ask Ame to tell me about
that Terrarism. He showed me a photo of it. It was
so
beautiful, right? Ice cream.
Justthe
Andred
showed me the photo.  I'm pretty sure it was
during Yakiniku
Yakiniku
indeeduction
OK, cute, cute I want to make it too
Please tell me, teacher, let's do it Let's do it, let's do it,
let's do it, let's do it, let's do it, let's do it, let's do it.  [
Music]
So, I like hot or cold weather. Eh,
stapler
is the main one, which one do I prefer?
New Jersey may be rare, but I
feel like everyone sells it for dinner. It's like
Loderst. Eh, I
like both, but there's something I often eat.
Which one is Twitter or Instagram?  I like Twitter OK
Apple or orange juice Climbing a
mountain or running a marathon Climb a
Mountain Are you strong?
[Music]
Computers or game consoles?
Ah, I like both, but how long will PCs
last? Putting pineapple on pizza.
[Music]
Tea?  Coffee?
But I was worried about drinking coins.
Lately I've been liking it a little bit. Especially
coffee, or rather cafes.
[Music] I see. I see.
Is latte popular on the beach? Or is it
common in famous big cities?
Beach
Yes. I don't wear clothes when I sleep.  Or should I
put on some clothes? No, I'll
wear some clothes, right? I'm going to take a bath. There
were a lot of people, so I'm going to go. I'll go to my
favorite event.
[Music]
Which do you like at Seven FamilyMart Lawson?
[Music] Which do you
prefer, Lawson's desserts?
Or the phone?  I love the
phone I see.
Should I
give or receive a gift? Is it okay to receive one? It's
true that we're only one station
away. Should we walk or take the train? Train,
train.
What is your blood type? A
secret.
So, the color of your pants is
[Music]
Pink.
Paint. That's not a secret.  Why? My
blood type is a secret, but the color of my pants
is a color.By the way, the color of my pants is a lie.I'm
saying it was a lie.I was
lied to,
so I guess that's what happened.Light
pink
is a lie pink.It
's a lie pink.Okay
, everyone, stop here for a moment.  Let's get it
and go see it. We've
moved.
[Music] It's
a little long, but please enjoy it. This
nostalgic
thing.
This time, I'm going to imitate something again.
Is it okay? I
feel like this is the only one.  You're
just
not releasing this anyway.
Not this one. It's
definitely going to be released. [Laughter] [Music] [Music] What are you releasing? [Laughter] You're already talking, okay? It
's
broken. It's broken, so it's
okay.  She moves once and
cries
[Laughter]
[Music] I'm
getting all kinds of information.
Maybe it's coming from my heart
[Music]
Let me understand by saying yes No, I've tried my best. I'm serious about this.  I did my
best, but if you didn't understand this and that, it would have
been a mistake on my part.It was discussion time, so yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I thought it was an air purifier, but when you said glitter, I thought it was amazing.But
[music]
It's broken.  I thought there was a way to express this.
[Laughs]
There's a chance that I'll probably take this one off.
[Music] I don't want it to
sparkle, but let's put it on. It's already sparkling, so let's
go.
[Music]
Air purifier
Well,
Dad.  What do you think?
[Music]
Yeah, what kind of Gion was that at the end? I
thought it would be a good idea to show some kind of difference, so I thought I'd take the dirty stuff out of mathematics and
bring out the clean stuff.
So, something like that.  I thought
something was going on, but I
fell asleep. It's
amazing.
That senior was so good at it, but it's
amazing how great seniors can do it
too. They worked really hard, and Subaru-chan and Tomio-
chan can understand that.
It was
really amazing, wasn't it? It's really difficult. Even in my house, I can't do that
. I probably don't know what kind of sound I should make.
When I was asked to look at the sounds of small things, I
just said the sounds,
but it's a little too difficult. What other
words should I use?  It's
been two years already, so I do
n't remember.
[Music]
[Applause]
How is that difficult?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, but it
's amazing Towa-senpai's imitation. Is Toa-senpai good at imitating?
Satoshi is good at it, but Satoshi is not good at it. He's not good at it.
Write something random.
I'm talking about a few people, all of them,
all of them, and Shinji's this and that, Arashi, this
, this suspicious comment, this is dead, he
's not moving, he's a dead boxer.
There is no, so you do
n't have to dig too deeply into impersonation.Okay, let's
go next time.When did you get back?
Okay, then let's
go back to the normal questions in the second half.The
song is loved by many people, but
where is the song?  First of all, I'd like to hear
if you learned anything.I have
n't really learned anything about singing.I've never
taken singing lessons before.The other day, I went for the first time.What's going on?  Tayo also told me that I was good at it, that it was
beautiful,
but that I should
stop doing it because I was giving it my all.I
see.Well, that happened once or so.It would
be interesting to ask the teacher's opinion about things like that.  I was
like, ``Oh yeah, I see.
''
Well, I've had quite
a few people ask me, ``
What kind of music do you like to listen to in your private life?''
[Music] What kind of
music do you often listen to in your private life?
It's a Disney song.That
's a lie.Someone
said to me, do you listen to rock or metal?
I listen to rock, but I really like Disney, so
for example, I always listen to songs from The Little Mermaid or
Disney songs from movies.I do
n't
question
and
like I
see, recently something new called Retronomy has
come out. I
saw and heard that Daniel from New Jeans, a popular K-Pop song, sang a Korean version. It was being
played a lot.  Hey, it's
cute, I like
it, I think I said something like, ``
Movie
and I see, ok,
ok, I
hope this is enough for everyone.'' Unfortunately, it's more
Disney-like than rock metal.
Sorry, I'm sorry, but
it's Disney again.
Next time.
[Music] It
seems like all the seniors fall in love with their seniors every time they meet, but why do you
think they
can be so popular?
Tell me, I do
n't know. I don't know, I'm not that popular.
[Music] I'm
jealous
of how popular they are.
When the children of their families come to Japan and have fun, we
do things like hospitality,
for example,
in cash.  I
thought you'd really cheered me up by saying something like, ``I'll pay for everything.'' I
want to go see a movie, so please reserve a seat. Like, that's
helpful.
Something like that.
Something like that. I'll buy you something to drink if you're thirsty.
Something like that.  It's
only when the members come that we
don't give it to the Japanese members.Japanese
members of hospitality sometimes treat us to food or are
treated to food.It's
like, ``This time I'll serve it, okay? Then next time I'll serve it.''  There have been times when he's
bought me things like that,
like Subaru-chan, he's so
kind, and we were
talking about face washes, like creams, and he said he had something to recommend, and I said I
recommend this shop.  Subaru-chan asked me what it was and
went to the store and said he would
give me a present, even though it was
n't my
birthday or anything, and Subaru-chan bought it for me on the spot.It
was really kind of him.  Things like
doors and other souvenirs that I often
buy when I go somewhere, and
when I buy a lot of things myself, I
hear people say they're going to eat this, etc. I see,
that's
true.  I wonder if Towa-senpai's kind image is
being conveyed,
but from the gentle piano perspective, I think the
reason why Towa-senpai is so popular is because he's so
easy to get along with.Even
though we've never talked, I
thought he must be like that.Ah, I see.Yes, that's
right.  Haha, there's something about the normal
problem of not falling in love with someone just because they're cute. Thank you.
Who is that?
[Music]
Also, she's really friendly, so I
was happy when she made my hands all squishy. That's how it was.
Tiara's hands were so squishy.  Well, it's
not very smooth.But I
don't wear my nails, so I do
n't think it's that beautiful.It
's beautiful, so I touched something because it was beautiful.That's why
things like that have already happened to me.I wonder
what Toa-senpai is doing.Now that I have Please, I'm
overseas.  I wonder what the popular words are.Japanese
[Music]
[Music] It's a
strange word, but it has a meaning
Charisma, yes, Charis Ok
I'M
[Music]
translatestandby
say
JapaneseHospitalityWhatis
Japanesehouse
the
likedraining
[Music]
[Music] [
Music]  ] There
are many reasons why seniors are loved. Thank you very much for the translation. Because there are many reasons, I have
to do a lot of translation as well.
That's right, that's
right. I'm
sorry for keeping you waiting. Thank you very much.
Yes, I'm loved, so I
'm CMT, but what do you think about being called that
?
IhatethisHeat, you must
be a real angel
[Music] It's
really
true, but I've been called TNT for some
reason. Lately, I've been having a hard time reacting to it. Yes, yes,
once.  It's
starting to get tiresome
to say, ``It's not TMT once,'' and I've been told too many times that I feel like I'm like Akita.
[Music] Are you
joining because you don't care anymore?
How many years has it been?
3  I'm a little old, but I'm getting tired of that.
I don't think I can help it.
Maybe people who watch Toa-senpai often
understand this, but
people who don't watch it that much may only know that,
so I'll
forgive them.  Please.
[Music]
[Music] I
wonder if TNT was a success.Also, Chanmari also appeared, and Towa-senpai might
as well.I don't like being called cute.No, I don't like being called cute.  I don't hate it, but I
'm having trouble with the backlash. I'm
embarrassed. That
might be the case. I see, OK
Google. So, I'll
keep calling you cute.
Well, OK,
Google.
[Music] Have
you had any difficulties since joining Hololive
? Even so, you've
been able to continue your activities.
Is there a reason?
Ah, Kudo. I guess it's because of the
stereotypes and ideas around me that I couldn't do
what I wanted to do.
When I joined Hololive, I realized that it was Hololive after all, and
what Hololive doesn't have right now.  I
really wanted to play FPS.I was asked that question
at the time of the audition.At
that time, I really
liked FPS, and
there weren't any people playing FPS.There weren't any
people playing FPS either.It's a
title, but it's
like a real competition with a practice period.
So I did something like that, and I
said something like, ``I want to be seen by people who like FPS,'' and then I said, ``Okay, I'll just go for an audition.''
When I was auditioning for that door, I
didn't call myself an idol, but
somewhere along the way, I became an idol, and now I'm
starting to call myself a talent rather than an idol.  Ah, yes, that's true,
but it seems like idols are
no longer allowed to interact with men,
and it must have been quite difficult for them to not be able to easily achieve their
goal of participating in a competition.
At that point, I was thinking,
um, I was afraid of what other people would think if I got involved with a man, and I
was afraid of
trying new things.I
can understand why it must have been difficult for me to be in an environment where I was afraid of trying new things.
[Music]
[Music]  [
Music]
[Music]
But
still, I'm doing it now, so
how did you get that strength?
Ah, but in the end, I
want to participate in the tournament that my friend played.
Well, since I entered, it's what I wanted to do in the first place.  "We
're a company that can do what we want." So I started
thinking about it.He
told me he'd support me, so I
thought I had to push him, so I
convinced my manager, and then I realized that I
shouldn't compromise on what I wanted to do.  So, I
had to do what I wanted to do, and in the end, it was all about the effort that I put into it.I
showed my efforts and won championships,
and the fans followed me, and I
still have fans who support me to this day.  I
think that's the reason why we've been able to continue our activities. We've
achieved results again.
Thanks to that, we're doing
the WINGS
and
this
[Music]
COMETRUE
and
This
like
and
the
[Music]
I'm glad, I'm glad I am.  In the end, I'm glad it went the way I wanted it to. That's
right. I'm glad that the company is
heading in that direction now. I'm
glad I kept going. I'm
also glad that things changed.  I'm
glad that the environment is still in place.
Lately,
it's been a good space, Spring
and the
time now,
andPro
SS, the path
created by the saved Ya.
Spy Wayne. That's right, Hawaii-senpai. Yes, it
's a little early, though.  Let's move on to sports and end
with nexpressionthis
OK
[Music]
For seniors, Hololive means
Hololive,
friends,
family,
something important and
necessary.
[Music] I
think it's great. I
think it's great.
Thank you very much.  I think
so. Thank you very much for your support. I
would also like to ask for publicity. Ah, I'm sorry for the publicity,
but I've been working hard on singing and playing games,
but I'm also working hard on singing, and I'm also working
on an original song called Private.  I
'm posting it as an original song, so I
hope you'll listen to it. Please
listen to it a lot.
[Music]
Listen to it anywhere.
Unfortunately, this is the end, but I hope you
enjoy listening to it.  sease
singing I've
posted it below this video,
so I
hope everyone has learned
a little bit about my senior.
[Music]
You're a bit shy, are
n't you? Maybe I'm not very good at being embarrassed. I'm
sorry. I talked so much that I was embarrassed. It's
okay,
it's okay. [Music]
Music]
Thank you for watching today.
Lastly,
could you please say hello with me?
OK, let me know. Well, this one also has a
German word in it, which
is weathing.
[Music]
[Applause]
Please let me know what you think of today
on Twitter using the hashtag Holtalk. I'll
go see it, so thank you.
Seeyounexttimebye
[Music]
byOtsu