[Music]
so
do
[Music]
oh
huh
so
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] is that
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
what
don't don't mind me not moving right now
um but what the [\h__\h] elgato what is this
[Applause]
so
uh
stupid switch
[Music]
itself off and i have to get up every
[\h__\h] time
one second um
i it's kind of weird right now because
um
wait a second
i'm just traveling
i'm struggling
i
you know what i'm saying you guys see
that but you know what i'm seeing
this
this is the screen that i'm seeing
i'll fix my face
[Laughter]
i'll fix my face in a moment but
um
why
in the you see in the background
in the background uh there's what i'm
supposed to see
i've never seen this screen before in my
elgato
game capture card software
oh i'll just restart
i'll just restart naka naganga
uh
come on come on i don't do anything
oh now it's back to normal okay time to
fix my face the reason why i'm not
moving right now is because
um
i have
my my life batteries are at 11
but let's see i'm i'm on i'm being
charged my body is being charged so
maybe
maybe that's enough oh sure
eh
what i always always charge but i had it
in the kitchen that's why it
burnt itself out like a phoenix does and
but now um shut the wait
oh yeah you're not doing what i'm
telling you to
do hey hey hey
rough start but we're we're getting
there guys
hello
why
now
yes i am moving
oh sure
rough start but i am in other ways very
well very rare well prepared
don't
don't worry
okay
so the other way is i'm well prepared is
i have
i have that magical tea
i already tried a bit but it tastes like
[\h__\h]
normal grass that i picked outside
in the park
i have a magical teeth but wait i need
to film myself a new cup but i'm
gonna gotta put a sieve there because
because of raisins
uh
hello the magical thing yeah the magical
tea that my
the
throat doctor prescribes to me
okay let's see how it goes
yo
beautiful
going through the sieve
okay we made ourselves
a cup
of
grass tea
new year's hairdo is the goat oh
i don't know what the goat means but i'm
guessing you it means it's awesome thank
you
yes i love my twin tails the other thing
that i have prepared is
[\h__\h] my cookies
uh
now they're good they're good they're
good
they're fine they're not burnt oh i
thought they would have been burned by
now i should have put them out like
seven minutes ago but there they still
look perfectly fine but i really wanted
to say what i prepared was lots of
cookies and then i was reminded
i put the last batch in like 20 minutes
before the stream and i was like i i
will easily remember this because that
will remind me that at the start of the
stream exactly at the start of the
stream i have to take out the cookies
now i was occupied with other things
that was a close one
abu nakata
i
is even if they would have been burnt
it's fine i still have a lot of other
cookies and i
if
upon uh no contra
what's the phrase upon contrary belief
is that the phrase
i am not eating millions of cookies per
day now i only ate like
two maybe yesterday two yeah two
one
i ate today for breakfast
contrary to popular belief that's it
that's it
contrary to popular belief
yeah uh so i still have one more cookie
from my first batch but they were really
really big and today i made the rest and
uh
i made them smaller
now now the whole
dough is used up
big cookie yeah i have i have one here
with me and some more fresh ones i put
in a in a cookie
box jar thingy
um they actually fit
no cookie pizza this time exactly rmt
and bff still getting some i hope so i
want to give them some but
i don't know when i can see both of them
i don't know
um
but in a cooking job
and in a cookie yeah yeah it's not
really supposed to be a cookie
box i need to buy a separate proper
cookie jar cookie thingy because um
uh yeah that the one i put it in now is
where the cat food was supposed to be
a container for a separate container for
caffeine but don't worry i washed it
i put it in the in the dishwasher
i need now that i know how to make
cookies i need a cookie jar thing box
thing
just like a mom would
it's funny because now you know how we
talked about you open up a cookie thingy
you think there's cookies inside but
it's just sewing supplies now imagine a
cat trying i mean obviously they don't
have thumb so they wouldn't even be able
to open it up but let's just say let's
just humor me for a second let's say the
cats would know the kibbles are in that
box so they tried to open it looking for
kibbles and then it's just human [\h__\h]
cookies not what they're looking for
baboozle
bum boozle
anyway
uh
look new hairstyle it looks so good and
i finally get the orange option there's
finally orange hair
what is this sound oh it's in-game sound
and orange hair and this hairstyle looks
pretty good too
i mean it's a man bun but it actually
looks cute
we kawaii hear the game oh well i mean
it's not really
much sounds but yes no distortion there
was a [\h__\h] distortion [\h__\h]
no
damn
uh are you are you good
what the [\h__\h] was that
[Laughter]
girl buns grill buns
it is cute isn't it coming up
um
so oops i want to sleep until daytime
[\h__\h]
uh today [\h__\h] i didn't
today
uh
the plan is but you still don't hear it
oh that's interesting
ah now how how about i mean
it's really
quiet anyway
how about and now you definitely hear
something
right yeah now it's too loud okay
um
today
look at me looking
then we're supposedly going to uh finish
this game
um
or at least finish the story
supposedly i've heard that there's a
chance that i would be able to do it
pretty high chance
so yeah oh can i drink my tea is that
too hot
that just tastes so boring it tastes
like nothing besides grass look at this
who who would drink this tea
just for
the sake of drinking tea i wonder
because it's not like
it's not like it has any special taste
to it it feels like you went outside and
you decide i'm so hungry i'm gonna eat
the grass now but that would probably be
more satisfying because you're doing it
out of pure hunger but who would drink
this tea man who
it's uh it was called marshmallow plant
tea i think
uh
no
[Music]
before the stream i played a little bit
uh
you know what i'll kill you
i played a little bit oh my god
a little bit too
okay i'll play on obs today
i still get that weird elgato screen i
played a little bit
uh off screen
and
[Music]
oh but not that much uh this time
um didn't have that much time
[Music]
yeah
it's a bit loud okay overkill
jesus
um
yeah
i wonder
when you guys say i could finish the
game today did you guys mean
only if i focused on the story or also
if i do some side stuff as well
i've been also trying to
um gather some materials because i
noticed i kind of
stopped gathering
a lot of materials
unconsciously stop stop consciously
still kind of loud okay
can tangent show finish today that is
the question
yeah um
the goal is not to finish like
everything completely just the story and
i i think there's then after that quite
some
post game for stuff like finishing
finishing the pokedex
i'm not sure if that is part of the end
of the story or if that is separate do
you guys know
okay no we're not going shiny hunt
if it comes on its own then i'm very
happy
if it doesn't then [\h__\h] you
i'm fine with being the only one without
the shiny
um
you only need to complete decks for our
kills
so not
story
post game is pokedex you can come okay
okay that's what i wanted to know
um
still someone hinted at me that
the
there is a fight
um that's as
tough as the one we had against since
uh against cynthia
um
or about herself
as i'm a bit worried
about that
but we'll see how it goes
and someone told me on twitter
um
yeah
well we finally can't be as tough as the
cynthia fight
slightly tougher
[Music]
oh
my definitely tougher than what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
but i already had
okay i only really maybe i only really
had that many issues with the cynthia
fight back then because
i just didn't have the right pokemon to
tackle
hers with
maybe if i
maybe if i prepare the right pokemon
then
we'll we'll have less problems less
issues
that's like post game oh okay hallelujah
well then
thank god
um okay then oops oh yeah let's go start
the story i was doing some side quest
stuff and i went to this [\h__\h]
reminisce island a million times and i
swear
there is no
moving tree there
ever
no matter when i go there
and i'm so mad
i'm so mad this stupid [\h__\h] side
quest is wasting my time
it's quite rare what the hell man
ah
you're not planning to play i already
answered this question
um i am
i'm going to finish the story today
and perhaps
uh do another
stream uh
if there is enough content
to do
another stream
post game which it looks like it is so
this is this might not be the final
stream this might be the second to final
stream but this is the story finish
today yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yes
pokemon
yeah
okay
so
it's not going to be an endurance stream
because i think we're going to be fine
we don't really have to endure much
in order to finish the story i think
especially if that
legendary fight is after the story
finished then that's something we'll
have to
worry about
after
in the next stream
yeah the credit bro i suppose whatever
we'll see how far we get
[Music]
whatever you guys are confusing me
everything is confusing me when you
don't know how the game ends and how
it's just hard to tell uh you know
what
we have to go to command though that's
where we left off last time left off
listen um
let's talk
let's talk also i'm hungry must eat
cookie
must eat cookies soon
damn hungary
[Music]
each of the pokemon nobles became
frenzied and now each of them has been
quelled
we still have no explanation for why
this calamity but fellas but i'm glad to
see it put to an end
and to fake peace would be restored to
history by the hand of our mysterious
rafeborn
helper when tomorrow dawns it will dawn
on a world restored to normalcy
at long last we will be able to return
to our normal lives
you think so
go nourish yourself at the wallflower
and allow yourself some potato mochi
don't forget the survey corpse work is
not over it does not end until our
peripheral people
can't live here anyway without fearing
the pokemon around us
[Music]
hello potato monster guy
thanks for this nice sizeable helping of
potato mochi benny old
chump
oh if there's anything else that you'd
recommend by all means bring it out
[Music]
wait different food
is there gonna be different food
now that ever looks well too we can
survey all of our history
i certainly have my reservations as to
whether avalon needed crawling but if it
means bringing home to everyone then i
suppose we did the right thing
[Music]
i hate to think what kind of habit the
frenzied nobles would have wrecked
reeked if kiawa never came to us you
would have all died guys
probably cause y'all are useless
still even with all the noblesquells the
rift doesn't seem to be closing huh
although wait if the rift went this look
at his face
if the rift were to disappear would that
mean chia won't be stuck here
i guess so
well our little team is certainly very
practiced at investigating things by now
we'll look into the matter and find a
solution i have no doubt
and even if we don't we always have a
home here in juba like village kiawah
now then tomorrow is soon upon us and it
will be another hot day at work for the
survey corps don't forget what we've got
our sights on nothing less than a
completed pokedex
view around that pokedex is as good as
complete hey how about i just tag along
and just
if you would actually help sure
oh so strange come on now ray don't sell
yourself short you're a full-fledged
member of the survey groups too
well sure i guess i am in any case time
for a hearty meal and heavy sleep wait
so what about the other food eh
yeah
yeah we don't care about being in this
world there's something i tweeted a uh
tweeted out by like retweeting this this
piece of artwork fan art that someone
drew
bakum i thought it would be kaboom but
it's bakum
of the protagonist sitting
alone and sad in in her room
in this room actually looking very sad
uh like she is very homesick did you
guys see that fan art
it looked very very emotional and it
made me think
um
it would be
nice the protagonist actually really had
some
feelings like that
but it seems like we really don't give a
[\h__\h] about it
let's see what happened baku
what the [\h__\h]
did we make it worse
this doesn't look good
oh
[Music]
hey i'm just sure doing what they told
me to do and trying to help
some sort of dreadful energy seems to be
boring from the rift in space time
now the entire sky is going red oh see
i have word from the commander
you're to report to his office at once
you little [\h__\h]
i'm in trouble
the way the sky has changed is ominous
very ominous indeed
what's this about commander
you did call us here to discuss the
quorum of all the novel nobles didn't
you
that can wait there is a more pressing
concern there
must be a twist
the first strike of that strange
lightning the one that drove cleaver
into a frenzy it struck the night that
killed are you
what are you trying to say
oh
it always seems natural to think that
the two events might link just
i didn't i didn't do anything
i didn't do anything
[Music]
yummy yummy
you've done all i ordered yeah yeah
but that does not ask any question of
who you really are well i don't [\h__\h]
know
you came from the rift as the delighting
you connected to those frenzies are you
not
did you think to gain our dress by
quelling the friends as you yourself
brought about no
no
and haven't gained our trust what then
what is it you really have to hear no
way wait no what the [\h__\h] man
[Applause]
[Music]
maybe i should
turn into um
turn evil and then just [\h__\h] burn
them all down because like i worked so
hard for them this is how they repay me
how they treat me still after all this
time
i will [\h__\h] smash them with my chunky
pokemon
unbelievable
there's not much denying on me
he died
eh hold on commander there's nothing to
suggest kiawah has wronged us
[Music]
exactly
besides you do you really think she's
got the sort of fearsome power it would
take to make this happen
let me ask you in turn can you prove
beyond the doubt that she is free from
guilt
ha that logic is so stupid
it's like
for example it's like saying someone
stole something from a store
just because it's not in the store
anymore
but they don't they cannot prove that
they did not still steal it but you can
also not prove that they did steal it if
you looked for their bag and you can't
find anything
but if they don't have anything with
them wouldn't it be the most
uh logical thing to say that you have
the wrong person
because you don't have proof of her
having anything you also don't have the
proof of her
not having anything
no if you do kind of have the proof of
hair not having anything cause she
doesn't have anything
so
the fact that i do not
uh have anything that proves that i am
guilty doesn't that
isn't that proof that i'm
that i didn't do anything
you mean
you know you would lose
this person the stranger appeared out of
a rift in space time
who here can guarantee she is who she
says
who here can guarantee she's to be
trusted
objected
thank you
come on let's be reasonable what is key
i was supposed to do then
exactly
what
youtuber
youtuberino
youtube chan
oh
we gucci okay
i was just saying exactly
she will be given the chance to
investigate this latest disaster but not
as a member of the galaxy team she
remains a suspect unless she can clear
her name clear my name from what [\h__\h]
[Applause]
[Music]
you know what the way he
acts like now right now makes me think
he is the evil one
because that's kind of ridiculous
that's that's not any more you know the
whole thing of being a little bit wary
of strangers
that's kind of crossing that
point and his reasoning is ridiculous
maybe he's actually you know what he
might be the evil one hmm
he says now
um
and giving me such a weird ultimate
ultimatum that is like impossible to
prove
to like clear my name from nothing
yeah
says
there are those in our village who
cannot trust this stranger like you who
fell from the sky
i think by now everyone trusts me except
you
and so i must ask you to leave you are
no longer welcome in the galaxy team
consider yourself banished from this
village until you can explain why these
calamities keep falling out good people
well at least i got my hair done before
that
yeah
no until you've restored our world to
its rightful state and proven your
innocence beyond doubt
damn
is that clear it's silly so and selene
yes sir
[Music]
how can you act so heartless don't you
believe in clower
you see the face of adamant right now
it looks to me like that
um
i don't know where that meme originally
is from but it reminds me of that face
actually i think i saw some fan art of
myself today with that face
um
do you know what i mean
i need to find it
like no not really
it is kind of a smug face but
it's like a meme face
wait wait let me quickly try to find it
in my arts of ashes hashtag i saw some
art i saw something
just today
wait oh there's so much new cute art oh
what is that
cute
that's not it but that's cute from
raccoon crush
that's cute
[Music]
this smolder um maybe
okay
i didn't check the art hashtag today yet
oh wait is it this no that's not it
it was some mimi art
meme meme art
[Music]
the rock
hey wait what the [\h__\h] did i see dawn
oh i can't find it anymore
the rock eyebrow you tag me on twitter
thank you
let's see
this is important right now
no that's not what i mean no no the one
that you tagged me and that's
that's not what i mean
maybe i have it in my likes
[Laughter]
scroll skulls close close close close
close close close close close stop
scroll scroll scroll scroll scroll
scroll scroll squirrels
can't find it
i can't find it but i need to prove a
point
[Music]
okay i give up
like i think i give up
i'll find it after the stream i think
[Music]
cute that's also not it but
maybe i should just stream like this
today
[Music]
this is me
okay
that's not what i mean then check out
korean
and cookie monster yay
cute akuma
and cookie monster
i will do what i must as the commander
of the galaxy expedition team
wait but now it makes sense because i
was always thinking
that
like wasn't the galaxy team evil in
diamond pearl why are they the good ones
here oh i suppose well over time
eventually things turn out in some ways
and now
[Music]
that's how
am i am i going the wrong way
am i understanding that's correctly
oh that was galactic
oh yeah oh but i mean i'm it's very
similar i suppose they changed the name
a little bit over the how many years
have passed
i think i understand
[Music]
um but i have not forgotten your deeds
nor the unusual skill you have displayed
that is why i have chosen to let you
walk out of your free rabbit and clap
you in chains
i want to find you right here right now
yeah it makes sense galaxy becomes team
galactic
[Music]
you to be expelled from the village what
seriously
[Music]
why does she not have eyebrows
when she has her eyes closed it looks so
funny without
eyebrows orders are orders
no
let's go
uh but what about all the side quests
that that i accepted it
what about my ex how long will i be
expelled what about my access to all of
these shops scary indeed scary
look at my sad face
oh [\h__\h] you
[Music]
uh
i don't wanna go
[Music]
shame
we can take it from here man
it looks nice
[Music]
understood
however the decision was mine to accept
a stranger as a member of the survey
corps
[Music]
it is only right that i should
personally escort her from the village
and to the fearless camp
i'll come too
because i will
as well naturally
oh
[Music]
then i will walk you all down is bound
for the fit lads camp safe travels i
guess
damn what the [\h__\h] is going on here
thank you for renewing your membership
[Music]
maybe we'll find a different words
would be cool
if we find another one that's so big
nope apparently not
eh
i can't believe the boss would do this
you quelled all the nobles frenzies
under his own orders
quite right moreover even if you do
happen to fall from the sky that
apparently gives you the power to turn
it red
this is utterly intolerable and i might
add absolutely absolutely
unscientific
as a man of science i must fight such
illogical thinking tooth and nail
you must not
look so weird
[Music]
you will only cause chiama more pain if
you are driven out as well for defending
her
blimey
bloody hell
however there are others who might offer
help you've been an aide to both the
diamond clan and the pearl clan oh wait
who's talking uh
of course perhaps adamant or irena might
take you in
no i'm afraid they both already returned
to their respective settlements
i bet you could at least start by
finding leon at the grand tree arena not
sure where it might be
if
you want the diamond con
uh wait i want the poor clan
don't die alone out there that's an
order is she good
if if the other dudes if kamado is evil
and i wonder if she's also evil she
seems still like kind of
um neutral
i will ensure you all have all you need
to complete the survey the commander has
tasked you with they're just using me
man
if i might offer my advice in this life
you will meet with both admiration and
abuse from others
how others choose to view you is a
choice only they can make you can
not make it for them
all that surely matters is that you hold
firm to your own values
what of the dream about first sharing
with you on prelude beach to complete
the pokedex
that dream simply won't come true
without you
[Music]
well what about going shopping for
clothes and then going to my hair
appointments i also need to get my nails
done man
the pedicure would be nice
what the hell
you doing
what did i do to deserve this
oh you
you what in the world did you do
look at the size of that rift
the lightning starts pouring from it all
the pokemon in history could be thrown
into a frenzy
entire clan is in a panic now
i should have known that the only thing
that could come from that rift was a
disaster
i need help this is the one with iridal
right
oh well that's not exactly something i
can do
well
okay
it's not that i wouldn't like to help
you but i it would put irina in a
difficult position no she loves me
i truly do wish that i could repay you
for calling cleveland's frenzy as you
did you must know that but there's
nothing i own can do for you
worded mai might be able to help you
though she's a caring woman after all
you almost likely find my at the warren
bridge i believe it's a very significant
significant place for her
oh i thought i thought i have to kind of
like choose sides here
i'm certain that somewhere in the
vastness of history there is a place for
you as well but isn't my gonna turn me
down as well probably in that case
[Music]
i need to
i need to take a bite
this one this one looks like it doesn't
have so much chocolate in it
[Music]
that's why i kept it for less
use more chocolate
[Music]
with nutella
oh no
[Music]
mmm
still still very good though um
[Music]
my mine is over there
i guess i'll go from here
what
these people don't seem to care much
about that sky
um
[Applause]
over there
okay
maybe i can fly a little bit
[Music]
i'm like a bird
i don't know where my heart is
i don't know where my home is i think
the lyrics are wrong but i'm like a bird
i'll leave my way
i don't know where my home is
[Music]
[Applause]
hello my cutie pie
what a frightful sky
such a disturbing sight would be enough
to put anyone ill at ease
don't know what brat is about do you
no i really don't know
[\h__\h] on you
i suppose it was too much to expect that
you could already have an answer to all
this thank you it is too much to expect
i heard from ali that what happened you
can return you can't return to that
village of yours can you
but i'm afraid diamond clan cannot be
the ones to save you why not
why is everyone leaving me in stick now
as the germans would say
[Music]
the diamond clan could end up at war
with the galaxy team if things went
badly i think you would regret that as
much as anyone
the great word here took a liking to you
i want to offer my support but forgive
me i cannot help you with this
and what
do not abandon hope time solves all
things
crony is the key autumn
and besides you seem to have a challenge
for making your own way in the world i
have no doubt you'll continue to find a
path to work
i have to say though like story wise
this game is really good i think like
better than the others i said this
before i think but
this twist as well well made and the
dram dramaticness of it also
well done well done i feel very sad and
i feel for the protagonist and i'm like
i'm like personally mad
i feel insulted
normally
pokemon stories are always like such
baby stories sorry but
um
but this is good stuff
i mean
still not as dramatic as many many other
more mature games but for what it is for
for
the audience if this is supposed to
please
it's actually probably too mature for
that children audience but
i like it
[Music]
i might have played black and white when
i was younger but i don't remember
[Music]
ah
you cute boy
what is it you're trying to cheer me up
nothing can cheer me up man
don't you
what i'm just gonna be adopted by
pokemon now
become as pokemon
[Music]
no yeah i'm exiled what the [\h__\h]
yeah
you
the one guy who doesn't belong to anyone
strange events seem to follow you
wherever you go don't they
um
i suppose so
i found you at last kiawah
i need someone who will take me in
i've been looking all over for you you
know
what would i do if i were to lose one of
my favorite customers not that i ever
buy anything from you but
don't worry i've already heard what
happened a good merchant knows well the
importance of staying abreast boobies of
all the latest news
it seems you can quiet the pinch
quite the pinch destiny
saw this now
[Music]
no place for you among the diamond clan
or the pearl clan to say nothing of how
poorly the galaxy team has treated you
but not to worry
there are still corners of the history
region where we can stash you away in
secret
i know a spot that will be the perfect
hideaway leave it all up to me
good guy good man be nice to me
here we are oh have i been here before
i know i know it's no palace but you
know what i was saying about beggars and
choosers
well it's fine i like these tents
they're really those tents they look
what you would use uh they look like
what you would use for glamping oh this
is a different place
ancient retreat
nice flowers
huh
who the [\h__\h] is that another new
character
another new character
sure keem your work to come pester me
again even beneath a bleeding sky you
never change
oh it's a pleasure mistress kogita
but i'm afraid i'm not here today to
learn more of jesus myths and legends
oh she's pretty
the white hair makes me think she's old
but she doesn't look that old
hmm
[Music]
i like her design even though her hat
is kind of
blurry
and a mistress thank you
just kogita
no no no mysteries thank you just kokita
and this is
why kiyowa is the woman of the hour
she's the one who quelled the frenzy of
all the pokemon nobles believe it or not
ah the poor ratchet speak off lost in
time and space
dear me lost one
it seems i'll be able to fulfill my duty
at long last thanks to you she's so
she's so mysterious
being like alone here in the middle of
nowhere
drinking tea
dressed in black with a fancy hat
who's your last one
indeed i am to guide you lost one for
the task of preventing great disaster
falls to you
the rift in space time must be mended
lest time and space themselves be thrown
out of balance
[Music]
but come you may enter my dear hideaway
there's much to be told
[Music]
she speaks
weirdly
what wow
she has an actual proper bed
um
you know
me lady uh uh
um
i've been trying to i haven't i haven't
gotten a good night's sleep for like
months now because of the those futons
i'm not used to them but you seem to
have a a problem
may i um uh i mean i'm not saying you
have to sleep anywhere else of course
it just looks like there's enough space
for both of us
[Music]
if you would be so kind you know i think
i could help you better if
if
if i could get a good night's sleep for
once please uh i i i i i i i just need a
pr proper bed
yeah
yeah what i'm sleeping on the floor no
no
i don't wanna my back is like dead i
need to sleep on the bed
a space-time rift is said to be a portal
to innumerable other dimensions
in one such realm far and further still
from ours dwells almighty sinner
[Music]
they expands from antiquity and to
eternity and he expands to all sides
above and below
time traces the path we treat from here
and now into oh she only has black
dresses look at that on the left side
it's like she goes to a funeral every
day
now into the future
while space yawns all encompassingly
surrounding us in every direction
you see don't you the two together time
and space comprise all creation the
universe
i don't know
much about what she's talking about
she speaks so fancily
i sleep on a bed of fluffy chickens
okay i'll take that
[Music]
nod and smile
how can one claim that either is greater
than the other as those two clans do
you really can't
um
perhaps the truth is clearer to wanderer
to anyone such as you one who has known
other ages
now listen
last one here is what you must do
history holds three lakes of great
importance
like ah
those ones with the big rocks in the
middle
in the middle yes yes i've seen them
like verity lake valley and lake are
ice
add each dwells of pokemon set to embody
one aspect of the mind
complete the trials each will set you
and bear their gifts to the shrouded
ruins
[Music]
there you may receive the red chain with
it perhaps you can bind the world
together
behind the world you say you mean it
won't close the rift
kindly spare me your doubts young man
i know the old words and what they bid
us do how true they are isn't mine to
know
what the [\h__\h] is she saying
and regardless of their truth i am bound
to pass them on
how callous of my ancestors to leave
their legends to their children without
a thought for the hardship it would
cause them
but here we are
you know your duty and you'll do it
won't you
yes of course
because you're finishing it today
there is no ability in knowing what must
be done and seeing to it
my my magical mysterious phone is
beeping i can see the locations of the
free legs oh i know where they are
without you marking them thank you
though
miss mistress caldi took out a lovely
workbench here and if you need materials
i'll be glad to help i'm always happy to
do business with you
thank you
i wonder about the pastures
oh that's a problem isn't it what shall
we do about that wait
don't tell me i can't use it for the
time being
huh
what was that cry have we now lost
pokemon as well as a lost job don't see
to it please
how could i uh oh that was her how could
i refuse you ma'am
off we go kiawah
please tell me i can use them because uh
see i have cypher level 14 with me for a
sidequest
useless pokemon
hopefully you're gonna teleport them to
me right
all right hello hello it's an upper
where did you get a board from
got a letter thank you you're gonna help
me thank you thank you
thank you thank you okay
uh you'll be able to use our base camps
oh a very fit every confidence in your
ability as an adept service corps member
to bring this bizarre situation under
control properly someone hmm
duncan
good job just from the letter then
yeah
it's the lens opera
[Music]
now dan's the way to visit for the free
lakes it doesn't sound like an easy task
that's for sure it sure wouldn't would
be wonderful to have a kind soul who
might help us out
such a consummate guild merchant
i've actually reassured my people for
now the wardens are keeping a close eye
on their nobles too seems all quiet for
the moment and so here we are
but still we'll never get away with
openly hating you
if we wanted to undermine the
commander's direct orders relations
would grow strained
long story short we want to help out but
without drawing attention so it'll be
just one of us
you know the answer guys
that is
could it possibly be
oh so hard to choose
it's not like by coincidence the game
that i played was um pokemon pearl
and coincidentally the cute girl belongs
to the pearl game
so i think it's meant to be
[Applause]
of course you'll choose me and of course
we all know we all understand i was the
one who got you what you needed when you
first set out to quell cleaver you and i
made us bombs together there are so many
other reasons so many more other reasons
than that but
yes i choose you
just what i would expect of yukiawa you
made the right choice you won't regret
it
thank you
so then the left overleader will
left over think again can't we trust me
enough to leave the tough job up to me
alone i'll be keeping an eye on the
commander so i can let you all know if
anything happens
of course of course and the lucky chosen
one comes with us to the lakes we can
fill you in on the details as we go
well the first task will be to decide
which of the history region
reaches three great lakes to visit first
but yes we should get moving i'd rather
we walk this road together
but if the commander were to get a win
of it it would only make things worse
i'll meet you at the at whichever lake
we choose okay
okay
all right eureta you and kyowa well you
two do what needs doing
the trial of lake verity the trial of
lake valor and the trowel of lake acuity
ah you wanted me to pick anime well you
should have thought ahead that i would
obviously pick the cute girl
that's on you not on me sounds like a
new
[Music]
problem oh
it's a cute little place here
yeah oh then oh yeah i wanted to change
my
little pokemon
um
we're switching out
uh oh wait no not real i mean i guess i
couldn't release but no no
uh wait where is that pokemon that i
need uh ah it was uh it was
look my the way i caught this fluffy
bird cute
and palin palin
when this one
cute hot zoro is so pretty
where is my girl
where is she
where is she where's smoove
ah here she
back into the team where you belong to
rafa becomes your flying mount ew
switch in the shiny ponies no why why
don't wanna
you don't wanna
okay time to go
i guess
the more of all female routes for the
cute girl pokemon
[Music]
i see
where will you be heading i'll guess
we'll go here
yes yes yes gardevoir oh
that is indeed kind of cute
not really my taste but
[Music]
uh we need to go to lake parity which is
over here maybe we can
fly
at least for
some part of this
[Applause]
cap
[Music]
a pokemon that speaks to me you know
oh hello
[Music]
yummy
oh they're all so aggressive
what i do want to see
[Music]
oh
oh [\h__\h] hold up
i wanted
wait i never caught an ah
i don't think i ever caught a wormer
down before
[Music]
please let me catch you immediately
here's the police
yeah okay and now we can run
although 43
not much of a problem but i've preferred
to go
but they're killing me
oi
okay well
okay well now
i have nothing that's so perfect
then even more reason to run
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
chuck
i have arrived
hello
they say this lake actually used to be a
volcano um then it erupted leaving a
huge crater that filled with water and
still lake verity was born
what do i do here oh a messprint
it is protected by a pokemon called
messpert it was when mesper took a
flight that people first learned it the
joys and sores of living or that's how
the old tales go anyway
my phone
oh that does remind me of your name now
that you say it
oh man don't mention your name
what
okay
i know my phone can do something like
that
um
okay
why does it look different man
all right
oops maybe he'll um
[Music]
okay
no problem i'm young welcome to the
stream
we're finishing pokemon today at least
the story at least one part
[Music]
the air feels somehow tense in here
yo you're slimy as [\h__\h] you
the menacing pokemon stands before me
you were disgusting
what do i find that one with hmm
hmm
i suppose that's poison
oh
it's an alpha right um
[Music]
he's just standing there menacing me i
don't want to hurt his feelings it's
actually kind of cute
[Music]
steel
dragon oh glassine would work too
oh wait try to catch him okay
wait are we going to fight her
i guess we can try
crashing right away does that
work it i don't think it does
yes
[Music]
okay i hope glasian was a good choice
any second there's some cat hair on my
[Music]
top of my cookie
hey chad
hey
hmm
no
but okay if they wouldn't have attacked
first we might have had a chance
[Music]
am i supposed to um defeat or to kill
them
either
wait i said defeat or kill is both the
same but you know what i mean
either of either of them
[Music]
well i didn't catch one of those before
so i want to catch him
i hope i don't play with the fire truck
maybe if i do androids guys
really
um
wasn't it critical cuz like what the
[\h__\h] yeah it was a [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
all right
obviously game crashed
whoopsie
i did save um
damn
that's not what i wanted to happen
now this time
we don't go in
with glasses
no good
[Music]
but
can we not attack first
yeah
[Music]
would it be helpful to have this one for
that really difficult fight that you
guys mentioned
oh damn
i go strong one
okay
yeah it would
maybe i should use it in the final fight
dragonfield
yes
dorsil
[Music]
we've never used bruce before let me try
uh-huh
[Music]
wait smooth is still dead what
what pokemon do i have that um
he won't one hit
he won't kill that easily maybe
maybe maybe it'll be spikes
ah i revived him opposite huh
and it looks right huh
yeah i want to paralyze it and then
catch
[Music]
okay let's do this let's do this
did it not get paralyzed
uh
[Music]
okay
come on please make it easy for me
oh no don't kill me now
either
oh
[Music]
oh wait wait it was
[Applause]
um
cookie give me power
chocolate chip cookie i need your power
[Music]
no no no the game could crash
oh no
[Music]
um
some more damage or throw again let's
throw again
now should i
oh wait i couldn't attach twice so
[Music]
some more damage won't kill it good good
good good
now i broke
now i'm from
i can't catch it can i
oh oh come on
oh damn the game crashed
what a [\h__\h] annoying pokemon that is
it keeps on crashing my game
what it's like bugged
what game freak
please uh
please i'm trying to play this game here
come on game freak
i'll go
my eyes are so strong
why is it so strong
might actually really want to put that
into my team
maybe if it's really that useful
holy sees
potion
super potion
up super pushy
[Music]
sorry i just feel like crafting right
now
save again
could have killed it pretty easy yeah
yeah yeah i'm just trying to catch it
man i might have been able to kill it if
if i would have focused on that but i
want to catch it
i tried to paralyze but i guess it
missed because it was obscured in that
moment so it starts out being obscured
or did i miss it using the skill that
makes it obscured
it just stands there menacingly
uh
let's okay let's start we will be sparks
and hope it doesn't want to kill me
shelter it was shelter okay
[Music]
sounds like grass wait it's my move oh
because i'm so fast i thought it was
always gujarat first because of raisins
oh
these sparks is fast so that's why even
though it's so donkey but you're still
so fast
chunky fast rat
should i
if i do strong style for fun the wave
it has a higher chance of paralyzing but
if
it's not obscured right now and accuracy
is 90 i mean it should be enough right
[Music]
there we go
okay so during shelter i suppose we also
can't catch it so let's try to do some
damage
while i'm with uh in here but no one
it's not even worth attacking
because everything is not effective
oh [\h__\h] i should have healed smooth
so let's uh switch to
mummy
oh i can i can try to catch now
ah
but with no damage we would be have to
be quite lucky i'll give it a try
kelp has no effect on catching okay i'll
kill kill king
so beat me though
okay maybe you'll just kill me that's
fine too or not okay
the paralyzation goes on until the end
though right
i'm going to try to do some
damage
oh yeah then i missed i missed
hi hi hi
it boys off oh [\h__\h]
four to four five oh dear okay
ah okay
uh
is this do be a pain in the ass i don't
wanna kill you but i don't think this
will kill you
last time it also didn't kill you
do some good damage
why is that so oh cause it was so um
it has stats
stats
this even with a crate i feel like we're
fine
next i'm gonna throw a ball
okay okay
getting pumped
hopefully still paralyzed yes okay
[\h__\h]
uh
um
i'm sorry guys
i wanted to do some more damage
let's try
[Music]
uh do i have anything else that i can
put a status effect on it um with
i'm not sure what baby doll eyes did
again
i'm gonna put any other status effect
maybe a burn with flamethrower
spam well i have to put in another
pokemon
but
revive daichi
[Music]
why do you suck so bad
oh
so much you are insane
what if i oh yeah
oh but i don't want to kill it oh that
might kill it do you think it might kill
it i think i might kill it
can i do like an agile
pokeball throw
you won't kill it it won't you it might
some people say it
use a heavy ball
i think an ultra ball has more effect in
this case
i had to burn my killer every time i
just throw another ball
ultra ball
[Music]
come on
please i might call you a little [\h__\h]
if you join the team it does not want to
be called little [\h__\h]
oh no it's open
holy [\h__\h] macaroni man
oh my god
why is that why is the catch
right so [\h__\h]
low
what's going on is this supposed to be
like this did you guys have troubles
catching it too
don't kill me no
boy
revival fly too
good idea
oh
that means um i can't attack but
paralyzed paralyzed won't work either
right so okay i'll frodo i throw
did a good job
please be kind to me
[Music]
yummy
wow
it's done again
oh no
feels like the game is crashing soon
[Music]
can it be double up skirt like even more
you wasted two moves scudra you could
have wiped my [\h__\h] team
you're wasted
i think i'll throw a ball
see what happens
throw that ball
oh
you hatched cute
how often does it want to do this stupid
shitty move
wait did it run out of pp on all its
other skills or what's happening
i don't know if i want a stupid pokemon
like this in my people
what why is he walking away from me
because i bumped into it
oh that's funny
let's bully this [\h__\h] pokemon
bully bully bully bully
go away go away kind of
cut it
sorry um
get into the [\h__\h] ball
i'm so mad
i know after all we've been through i
don't want to just kill it
okay okay okay shelter again oh
yeah does it not have anything effective
against crystal green
[Music]
what if it runs out of vp for shelter as
well
what what does a pokemon do when it has
no ppu for anything
oh then it might use dragon pulse until
it is rather out of the pp but dragon
pulse doesn't work if will you struggle
ah
oh she's okay
um
before that happens but wait so it
probably still has dragon pulls no
and if you're bringing ob sparks it
might try to kill
it with dragon balls
but
what if we do a quick attack
i don't think it will kill it
it does like nothing
it does like nothing you're gonna do
another shelter you couldn't do it who's
gonna do another shelter
[Music]
okay we're red now we're red now
we're red now
so this is what i wanted
what are you doing
[Applause]
you look so stupid now good dress this
is what you wanted is this what you
wanted to look like here also i'm
wasting all my [\h__\h] ultra bones on
you i don't wanna i'm gonna use a great
ball
i have i have something to inflict the
status of that but not on kusaki not on
the current pokemon
oh
it starts to use some dragon balls
okay it's out of obscure and move points
oh you're so stupid what if i'm gonna
run out of ultra balls come on
wait now now let's run out of
dragonfalls i could switch to
oh boy
i'll switch to my boy
wait it's still using ground poles
how many p does dragon balls have
i don't want it to come into the fight
and then be one-hitted by dragon pulse
10 20 10 15.
that 10 is even if it's just 10 it still
probably has a bunch
[Music]
it's too risky
i think people think
that a heavy ball works on alpha pokemon
better because heavy makes you think oh
alpha is big so alpha is heavy but
that's not what the heavy ball does
heavy ballers it works as far as i know
works better if you're um sneaking on to
pokemon
it's not called heavy because
it works better on heavy pokemon but
it's called heavy because
the ball is so heavy
am i finally understanding more than the
chat
that's why i almost never use the heavy
balls because i i don't ever get so
close to the pokemon anyways
i am correct get that
finally i'm not even happy because i
wasted so many ultra balls
[Music]
what a [\h__\h]
that one's called
you little [\h__\h] oh man
okay i'm pouring in some more tea by the
way
stupid stupid gujarat
why are you so stupid
um
that was
so unnecessary thanks for the pinky
though
yeah
it's curious but when i watched you in
your pokemon battle i was face palming
because of this ridiculous ridiculous
outcome
i feel as if there's no obstacle besides
the game crashing that can't be overcome
if people in pokemon work together
now let's see about the pokemon of the
lake
i found a mysterious presence
oh
good it's a legendary right or no it's
not there's a different type too right
not legendary but um
what is that
mythical or
was that again
[Music]
mr mythical ah
i'm gonna fight too
[Music]
um
you're
you're right
[Music]
hmm
i can only imagine how it must feel to
speak directly with a pokemon my dad
[\h__\h] eardrums blasted
wait is this a quiz was that the right
answer
are there wrong answers
[Music]
we live in a [\h__\h] society
that's what i felt
which this one comes the closest to
[Laughter]
that
[Music]
thank god i don't have to fight
wow
[Music]
prove that you have completed the trial
set by mesprit the being of emotion that
lives in lake verity this item is needed
to forge the red chain but only the
first answer matt the other ones were
like whatever
[Music]
i should have made into a quiz
what a weirdo
i know that pokemon spoke of you yet the
words did not reach my ears i guess the
frequency was too high
it's mysterious but i suppose when
dealing with someone who fell from the
sky it's only natural to encounter
mystery
next on to lake valor and lake akuiti
it's not like i need another cookie
i do kind of need another cookie but
cookie is too far in the cookie jar
[Music]
i cannot reach
maybe maybe a little bit later
[Music]
safe oh
wait am i fighting him now
you can scare me with being so
impatient about saving
no okay
looks like that worked out well kiowa
i must say you know an awful lot about
history volo i suppose a merchant like
you sees all sorts of things in their
travels
that's right i'm just
you could say it's because i'm a
merchant but mostly i'm just naturally
filled with curiosity i want to know
exactly what happened in the past that
led us to this particular present
or more accurately i suppose i wanted to
know where i came from and where i'm
headed i wanted to know my path so to
speak
same goes for me our clan settled at the
very spot where our four bears
four
bears
once they held long mighty sinnoh that's
a fascinating word
but i i have still never seen almighty
sinner for myself
wait waiting matters to ponder for sure
but we have an um important guest before
us
four bears
many are bears
do you want to return to mrs kogita's
home
[Music]
do i
or do i save before going there and here
i think we want to go back right we want
to go back we want to go back i do okay
okay
very very i'd like to see what you think
of your progress no i don't really care
just let me continue
i need more ultra balls though what the
[\h__\h]
i hope we don't feel
like uh we need to like i don't we hope
i hope we don't feel obligated to catch
the other ones because ultra balls i am
out of them
ah miss pritz plume so the legends told
it true then the red chain must be real
as well
i beg your pardon kogita ma'am
well one of these pokemon that represent
the mind have to do this wretching and
why exactly should it find the world
i can find them in other places yeah i
guess though yeah yeah
buy more
does he have ultra bells
it your doves doubt suggests a keen
intellect i see you're not your clan's
leader for nothing
without the mind where to re where
where the the word the word to widen and
the very world to end would we even know
it
deep [\h__\h]
one might even say the world time space
all creation exists only because our
minds are there to perceive it
oh
is that a tin foil hat that i'm seeing
perhaps the red chain's purpose is to
let one see creation as it truly is
[Laughter]
oh
so does the mind create the world but
isn't it the other way around or is it
oh sheesh
she's confused
con used confusion on erida confusion
was successful
such ardent leaves my child teaching us
about the world in their own
incomprehensible ways
they urge us to think more for ourselves
on the nature of almighty sinner and on
the nature of the world in which we
dwell
you're absolutely right maps and legends
are such a fascinating
such fascinating thing to say
spoiler alert after myth after hope
after council you know what comes next
whole live english legends
because that's the that's
you know how we discuss like what can
possibly top
council now
who are basically gods i'm not sure if a
legend would really top god but it
wouldn't be quite on the
quite on the same level now or close
close enough
wouldn't that be cool though well live
english legends you could do a lot with
that like it's pretty that sounds so
vague i feel like you could do like
anything with that
hollow illuminati
live heroes oh
superhero wait that would be cute too a
superhero themed generation that would
be so cute
oh
that would be so cute wait i can totally
see it everyone loved their own theme
color like almost like a sentai like
common writer or so and and with capes
yeah
they all have cute capes and maybe some
cute masks
heroes and villains oh that would be
cute to mix them together have like free
heroes two villains or three
villains two heroes oh oh oh oh oh wait
i wanna
i want it to be true i want it to be
true
oh that would be so cute yeah they could
be like gogo power rangers
and sheen
ah
yeah people in the beginning thought
that maybe because of my belt that i
have a another form that i can transform
into and then in my debut i was like
yes let me
transform chicken
[Laughter]
cringe
no sorry to disappoint i i cannot
transform but who knows maybe in the
future someone else will transform
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
i need to write to yago after this
directly
a sentai fans are van boos yet you're
still here in your bucket
thank you
because i know like a few like santa and
fans
talk with that to the fans in the
beginning they were like oh she's gonna
be my oshie because i'm sure she's into
tokusatsu
uh and i was like oh
man
they're not gonna like me because i
don't know [\h__\h] about tokusatsuk
but you're still here yay
yay thank you
i'm one of those sendai fans i still
have hope well i mean
i i
i have some kind of
low-key connection to tokusatsu
but not because i like it but
it's a difficult complicated
situation
i have some kind of connection gel
it's complicated
[Laughter]
it's just
complicated
in any case we all all we have to do is
complete two more trials and we will get
the red chain
yeah
how nonchalant you sound how confident
of successes to which you contribute no
thing
whoa
oh
yes
that's what i like to hear
this is it roast him roast to npcs for
not doing anything
you talk along only for the chance to go
grab a bargain at more ancient ruins
that's all you do
useless
yes
well if you at least sell me some ultra
balls i'll i might change my mind
nope
do i have to buy more from him in order
to get him to sell me ultra balls
or what what do you want from me
um
bring some burn heels not that he has
any burn wait i've never even seen a
burn heel in this game
wait what would heal a burn
side quest oh i haven't done it yet
is it the one for the main shop i was
working on that one but i couldn't
finish it in time
you burn heel for oh my hand
ah raspberry
right yeah
oh
oh the berries oh
oh well um
wait let me save
um i hope
i hope that was [\h__\h] worth it for you
all those little triples i feel like i
feel like it's not gonna be really
originally said by this guy this it
means something similar to the whole you
can only prove your own existence
thinking what's going on
[Music]
wait where where was that recently where
i think therefore i am
[Music]
somewhere probably in my netflix shows
somewhere that came up recently uh
well now i'm so
philosophical phoenix now no now i'm so
so curious what that was but that
reminded me of damn it
i know it's a famous quote but it came
up somewhere in something that i was
watching
now i want to know what that was damn it
i think you're fine
okay okay okay we'll go to the next one
let's go
cutie pie where will you be heading
none of your business
is
[Music]
me
where do
[Music]
not like
i mostly just when it comes to k-pop
groups i mostly just listen to the music
i don't really pay attention to the
personalities that much uh but generally
i kind of if i had to say someone then i
would say yoona
thanks for the membership welcome
face
you're nice cute like she's my type
like
from the looks like
but also like
her behavior she's cute
cute
i want to look like luna so cute
you know what i'm looking for
separately for side quests
i was looking for you
yeah yeah
it's cute seriously all that matters no
but as i said
if you were to ask me which one
then this would be my choice not but i
don't know
much about their personalities because i
really just listened to the music as i
said hi big stone snake
[Music]
just let me pass please
no
no no no where is that lake
where's that lake
there it is
here yeah okay
[Applause]
so
what's it's got what's it gonna be this
time hmm
which one
am i which alpha pokemon am i gonna be
meeting this time
arena you here
hello
let me show you my phone again hmm is
that to have been formed by volcanic
eruption same thing
though there are also other theories and
let's say it was carved out in the midst
of a
sneeze
an explosion sneeze
pokemon itself when nazel took flight
thank you
the will to do what it what he's doing
was born in people's hearts or that is
what legend would have us believe
[Music]
make hole in wall um
thank you
that phone maybe the phone is what made
that hole in this guy if it can make
this hole too
what did you just say here we go i
wasn't listening
well i think we're fine we're healed we
saved and we're not gonna
get stuck in
in trying to catch the pokemon oh yeah
no one here
what an eerie space why would there be
columns inside a cave anyway
oh what the [\h__\h] is that
i wanna at least try to catch it because
i feel like i'll have a hard time
catching it anywhere else is that is
that a pokemon that usually you have to
catch in the water because i'm really
bad at catching pokemon in the water
poison dark
oh a quill
over cool that's the name what the [\h__\h]
that's a weird name
got any fighting at all
you ever for clothes from the sea
no man crawfish involved
oh
okay
i have with my balls my pokeballs i
barely have any
i have two
[Music]
magika
we're gonna try
i might try a little bit um
with all my balls
go iron hunting time to farm
ah
i'll try if i run out then i'll refresh
and what's that graphic
what
and and fishing me
and go get some materials
cause we are living in the material
started off with the wrong pokemon oh
but we might be able to get a power in
wait was it iron i don't know doc dark
uh dark
it's not water dark poison
um
i kinda wanna try to
do some damage at the same time is that
risky
well we can try twice
we can do one thunderbolt hope that
paralyzes if it doesn't then we do the
other one
let's see
no paralyzation
[Music]
okay well then
okay there we go there we go
at least we did some damage
[Music]
okay
now
next up
um
i don't have anything super effective
wow
[\h__\h]
what is super effective against this one
i know
what
[Music]
damn
okay that's okay but thank you for the
membership comes on me what what do
what should i definitely not throw in
here
[Music]
okay what this commenter
why why do i want to use that i'm going
when you're done
but it would make me stronger huh
hmm
okay you know what i don't mind trying
giving that a try
i can do a bit more damage and maybe
i'll stay alive longer who knows
paralyzed
and now let's do
a strong ice cream
i hope it stays paralyzed for a while
whoa that's a nice animation though
i was too strong
ah whatever i don't have many balls
anyway
it's
[Music]
oh well oh well whatever that's okay
we don't want to waste too much time i
can always try to catch it off stream
[Music]
it's a really really old maid cafe song
wait and it gave us the ball
what is service but then you didn't even
have to prepare it by ourselves
you meant to try to hit as hell for them
then
try to hit
you making it sound like it's really
difficult
really
is there a pattern
does it move every time i throw no okay
i have to throw them behind
oh is it going to turn with me
wait let's find out the pattern it goes
from the middle to here
is there a pattern
oh
wait
let me continue trying are you already
giving up on me
i seem to hear a voice inside my head
[Music]
wait should i give up
don't give up keep trying to
don't give up never gonna give you up
i'm never gonna let you down never run
around around and what if i stand under
you
oh then
[Music]
let me think
um
what if i i wanna i'm gonna like fake
bro
i'm gonna be like
and then ah
nothing in my hand
[Music]
where are you where are you [\h__\h]
well that's ridiculous though
what
oh
[Music]
why did that go through
why did that go through you sound like
how do you do this
[Music]
not giving up
give up you struggle in vain when you
yet press on i'm not full
what happens if i say i'm done
[Music]
what
game over
what happened
when
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh was it just
what
did it stop dodging
was it not my skill
[Music]
did you see the graphics are kind of
weird here sometimes
it was like some weird squiggly lines
around my body and around the
pokemon as well
testing my willpower okay so it's just
about going on and on continuing
continuing even though it's impossible
again do you see that what the hell
um
it's the water maybe um
that looks exhausting but only one more
to go now nah that was fine
that was fine
[Music]
all righty
i assume all went well kiawah
[Music]
still i must wonder why don't they just
give us the right red chain why are all
this running about because we need to be
worthy duh it would be too boring
otherwise
perhaps they mean to test whether
whoever seeks
[Music]
yes
exactly what i said
perhaps you're right who knows what
would happen if it fell into the wrong
hands after all
she always says what i'm saying
our brain cells we share one
though on the other hand what use with
those wrong hands affluent
who can say for sure maybe the red train
has some other use besides mending the
world
we finish it that is sandwiches
um
jinx thinks again
the red chains aren't as mysterious as
this entire predicament weigh in but if
we continue visiting the lakes we'll get
closer to an answer
so shall we return to mr squiggly this
home let's go
yes wonderful
okay yeah more insights more deep stuff
please
keep on talking to me mrs cognita
time for some wisdom guys cognita of the
of the tea what is your wisdom
so that's ourselves fang i send some
warmth to it
i do ah i do have to wonder if anyone
else has ever completed the trials of
this lake pokemon
indeed yet we may want to add just a
dash more speed things in jubilee
village are intense
this makes me think i'm in the fire
emblem game
what makes you say so
it seems the pokemon's been glimpsed on
the other side of the rift
one of those ginkgo guild merchants
informed me that commander kamado has
raised the force not to survey the
pokemon but to subdue it
should the need arise
one of those ginkgo guild merchants you
make it sound as if you're not one of
them
now if if a pokemon truly were to appear
from beyond the rift what would become
of everyone i wonder
don't let history's great vastness stop
you
let's go to get the final item we need
where's my wisdom
that's the spirit i'll come watch this
historic moment unfold too
oh you'll join
what is that all you really do
let's go kogita it was not cognita it
was kokita
remember once you've sought the third
lake and found what's needed for the red
chain make for the shrouded ruins
good job good job good job
i guess we'll go on our way to the last
lake we'll go try to get some
um materials what i need again for ultra
tumble stones iron chunks okay okay okay
just iron a lot of iron
okay
yeah
you guys also have such a shortage of
of uh
with like pokeballs and materials for
pokeballs
because i definitely do
is it just me so saigon
is
[Music]
all right
here we have some stuff down
[Music]
guys that reminds me before this stream
um
today i was watching uh some videos
oh
i was watching some olympic
videos oh
alpha thingy
um of like you know austria winning
an amazing feel
ah made me feel so proud and
excited to see that normally i don't
care about sports but i think when it
comes to the olympics
i feel like
that's it that's like
one of the few times when even people
who don't care about sports
uh
actually
finally do care a little bit right
and um
yeah austria it's not over yet right how
long is it going in those olympics
austria
uh
has been winning
quite some skiing sports
[Music]
sunday
sunday the last day
um
you go up there is there something up
here
oh mountains
[Music]
wow
also doing well yeah i mean when it
comes to
you know ski jumping for example it's
just our strong suit you know
but
then
youtube started recommending me some
other
stuff
[Music]
not austria winning and ski sports but
all kinds of people
in important competitions having
accidents and stuff
dusk stone
[Music]
need to make space for that
um
i watched the the holy trilogy
of bobsledding number was it called pop
starting what was it again
um
you know the one where where uh you know
the sledding competition where
they go like zoom they speed through
this tunnel on the slant where they lie
on their stomach on top of it
that's from mystery vision murkrow oh
bobsley bobsley yeah yeah
and
uh so there's like a trilogy of
accidents
that happens during important
important very important
um competitions
[Music]
uh
one of them was
so this this
person starts
bob slaying
and
in the first few seconds
oh
in the [\h__\h] tunnel that they're
sliding in
is a [\h__\h] broom
it's
unbelievable someone just left a broom
wasn't that even a limp i know probably
not olympics but something else that was
really big like a world cup or something
yeah a broom
the broom clip yeah and then there was
another one where you know how how
there's like
fans who um
lean over
the defense
uh and and look at the competition like
pretty from pretty close up
you only see it for a split second
because they slave they slide through in
such a high speed
yeah maybe that's why they
thought oh oh it's not so dangerous but
then there was someone who dropped a
[\h__\h]
fan a fan dropped the fence
into the tunnel
tunnel yeah into the tunnel and and uh
that
kind of
slowed down
the speed of the sleigh
of another person
that was number two
and then there was one more where
the
um
the athlete
that one was really sad
because i think
for the other cases they can ask for
uh doing it again they can ask to redo
it
because it's not their fault that that
happened
oh my god
but the third one was
so athlete starts running to speed up
their sleigh and then you jump on it
normally and land on it with your tummy
but in this case she missed her sleigh
like she kind of stepped on it wrong and
then
uh she
she slipped and the sleigh goes on about
there
yeah and you i think she wasn't even
able to redo it and that was terrible i
really felt for that one
damn yeah
look it up you can look up the the
trilogy
um what was it now box lane
uh
accidents or something like that there
was
some
video that put all of those together
uh
yeah very unfortunate it's [\h__\h] rough
because you're trying so hard
and then ah that one [\h__\h] mistake
i need a full pokedex entry for a
sidequest sadquest
of those pokemon
that one mistake
oops
where's my membership
maybe maybe
because um
because of the
whole
membership
memberships being taken away normally
they should have been reactivated for
everyone
but i heard that there's a slight slight
slight tiny chance that something
fails there and you're reactivating it
automatically and you might lose your
membership
um
but you're welcome to join again
some memberships
yeah i didn't hear of anything in within
kfp
but i heard it's a possibility
aya if your renewal was during the gap
which is kind of stupid unfortunately
i gotta double check well i see your
membership don't worry
no i want to [\h__\h] catch you
without going into a battle
please no
okay
let's catch this one first
and then oh another one oh god i kept on
getting accident recommendations then of
winter sports and stuff
another one that i watched oh my god
another one that i watched was a male
skier
um
doing the slalom
you know that one
and then he got one of those
when you call them those poles those
blasts i think they're out of plastic
they go so fast so it actually hurts
when it hits you
and he got
what exactly happened
he hit the flagpole and it kind of
went into
in between his legs
that that looked painful
that looks
he looks like he was in a lot of pain
and yes i'm laughing
and then there was then there was
another one
and there was another one that one this
one i really really
felt
terrible for
because that was career and some of
these accidents could end your career
this one ended his career there was a
french
a french athlete and he was also
doing
a slalom skiing competition
down the mountain
and it was really fast and he was doing
so well and it was like
around the end of the slope
um
uh
i think the snow was pretty bad because
at the same competition six other
uh skiers crashed but for this guy
oh my god he like
around the very end
um [\h__\h]
no
around the very end he kind of somehow
slipped or something but
um
he he then
kind of crashed and he dislocated both
of his knees
uh
and it was really [\h__\h] bad you saw in
the video
how his knees
kind of like moved in a
really weird direction in a way that
knees really shouldn't be moving
it was
terrible
oh that was so painful to watch i don't
know why i watched it because even the
video video description said that that
would happen
yeah
but i don't know and then i looked up
like who apparently
he did manage to somehow heal and after
you know therapy for a long time he
tried again but then he had another
accident
which completely
ended his
career forever
but that first accident holy [\h__\h]
damn
made me feel so sorry for him
makes me so sad
oh man
and then i spiraled into ice skating how
a lot of ice skaters have accidents
because their bones are so weak
and their backs there's like so much
pressure on the backs
oh my god i went into this whole rabbit
hole
of
winter sports and how it [\h__\h] up their
lives man
oh man
yeah it's so dangerous all these winter
sports are so dangerous
[Music]
thanks for rejoining
welcome back
why you know
[Music]
a lot of risk involved in sports yeah i
suppose well of course uh non-winter
sports can be very dangerous too
of course of course but i feel like
winter sports
especially
have a ten tendency to be incredibly
dangerous
um
pouring some more tea i have actually
almost nothing left nope nothing left
only a half
half a cup left
looking dangerous
hmm
[Music]
video of a man who got his hip split
up no stop shut up oh shut up don't even
talk to me
i really i really cannot stand
watching people
have accidents and be in pain
well i hear a sleeping one
somewhere
yeah
we're sleeping
we called it gliegar oh
and why did you even watch it i don't
know
i got killer yes
i got curious i couldn't help it
what is that green light
oh then like the the onsen onsen
oh it looks so stinky are these pokemon
just extra stinky
minaxina
[Music]
[\h__\h]
yeah
nice one nice ones
and you just gotta stay in good job now
we're gonna catch this one
yeah right on his back
can we catch the monkey
yes we can catch the monkey
oh
oh oh oh fbs kiwawa
going crazy
oh no you know you're a small target
gotta get a little bit closer
yeah
headshot
oh we cleared the onset now we have it
all for us you and me kfb
oh that feels good
oh that's hot that's nice
i'm better at estimating those those air
balls those wing balls now yeah i used
to be pretty bad at it too you got to
figure it out
and then it's not so difficult anymore
yeah it's not so deep
yeah onsen aren't really supposed to be
so deep i need that one oh
oh
oh level up for slippery isle i need
that raspberry for side quest
i need also this mushroom for recycles
but i don't need this one so get rid of
that
okay we should go to a chest hmm
also
we can do some
oh
we're back at 10.
we're gonna do some of those one
a few more would be good
hmm
a few more are you guys fine with me
finding a few more materials use the xp
ah true
okay
a few
more materials would be nice
[Music]
hello
more dear
excuse me while i'm grinding
oh alpha
what was it again
no not right now
got no time for you now
like the audio is being a little bit
crackly
at the moment
a little bit
space-time distortion is for me
yes
[\h__\h]
i thought it was a terrain
oh yeah
it's an avalanche i don't want that i
thought yeah it looks oh wow that's an
alpha crazy boy
oh
um that pokemon doesn't really look like
it likes any berries but
maybe it likes the crunchy stuff
yeah yeah
oh boy
[Music]
not bad
not bad at all
[Music]
papaya
have a book avalon is an interesting
looking pokemon
oh there's another one
they remind me of a
of a bug of a
ah what's the name
i'll give you some more salt if you want
yeah
get into my pokedex
oh
finding that these are sometimes hints
to me as to what's effective
it says it says you need to defeat it
with fighting types for a test so to me
that means okay
fighting is effective to you good to
know
i really still have a lot of issues even
figuring out but just by looking at them
what what what elements they are
oh
good job on surviving
wow
oh grass i snub it
all
right oh oh yeah right i wanted to check
out the space time distortions over
there then i guess it's a good reason
for me to
once return
uh to some
camp and clean up my inventory and then
go to the space-time thingy distortion
thingy
uh
i feel like there might be a lot of
extremely strong pokemon in there that i
won't be able to handle but let's see
let's just take a look oh where did i
get that one and the dusk stone yo
[Music]
those berries and that [\h__\h] and this one
i need for of course this one will put
away
okay i'll kill again and that one will
so
lots of rare items oh yeah yeah yeah i
think i've oh i think i've only ever
been in the space-time distortion
in the
nah in the first and then the second
um
area
oops yeah
put the stardust no i'm gonna sell it
wait i want to sell
[Music]
do some shopping
so
i just start this
yes
and that's it that's all i want to sell
okay
but this organization it hurts oh
you have ocd huh
if you save stars you can sell it for
more what
okay it's still there
um
things only ever get interesting once
that second face starts right so
second phase we're still good
didn't happen yet
uh crap
by the way yesterday i ate that
pizza that i was talking about
and i'll go from here
i ate that pizza my favorite frozen
pizza that now has a new recipe
there it is
ah there it is
i have to say
it's not bad but i prefer the old recipe
so i'm kind of disappointed
it visually looks more pleasing now
but
the taste is
a bit disappointing
yeah
unfortunately
that's a shame yeah especially because i
cuz they're probably not gonna go back
to the old recipe aren't they oh hello
[Music]
i'm just i'm just here to look at some
interesting pokemon and pick up some
items
electric right what is that
yeah it's the red one what
oh level 16.
steel bug
this is not this is not the history form
right this was the actual original final
evolution of that pokemon that we fought
before
right fire's super effective
well for now we'll kill the eevee
[Music]
that
why are you not doing anything to touch
your
uh
nothing effective against pikachu
[Music]
i will switch my pokemon
i will switch to
tell me what to switch to the game thank
you super effective fire
okay
waiting leaf blade rule ko you think so
i'm gonna catch them
i'm gonna catch it
usually you need a metal coat to get
scissors oh
that's that's something i don't think i
have found yet so
it sounds useful oh i don't want to do
too much damage what if i do it agility
well it won't kill it
it shouldn't kill it it should not kill
it
[Music]
oh
oh well
oh wow
oh
sometimes i really underestimate my
power
oh man
game crashed nice okay
we'll find more maybe even if not i'm
not i'm not that mad about it
no not interested thank you
you guys battle everything you find in
here i usually just keep on running
until i find something new a new pokemon
that i haven't
we're not a noob okay
oh what do we have
i'll puppy catch oh oh hello
oh wait uh we're on pokemon but okay we
found that singles
[Music]
and we will attack it
with a little bit of an ice cream i
guess until you kill me we found another
[Music]
i will not attack with a fire attack
don't worry i'll attack with hex
do at least some damage until we go to
this point good
and now we try to cancel
come on
come on come on come on come on come on
please
yay we got it
i got it
good job
level two
sixty
sometimes you've seen it just ice cream
stop following me weird big hairy
stalker what is this
i always get noticed usually when it
comes
no
oh i did catch it
[Music]
oh oh you already saw me okay but i did
catch the other one
right two nine two
right two
i think i'll save once
it's done service you
nanny with a beard b
[Music]
we did catch one right it looked like
it didn't get caught but i think we did
by the way
um
[Music]
how about that poor smooth poor poor
pretty smooth baby are there ever like
better revival items later
like i'm already in late game so why
don't i have them yet
distortions don't sit yeah no no they're
called pokemon do i think
i mean if i come back yeah the
distortion may be gone but the pokemon
that i call it i don't want to just
i mean i guess that saves all the lights
too oh
hello not interested
[Music]
it's not interesting just here to steal
some items oh
good
[Laughter]
fellas oh
hello hello no i'm not interested is
that all you got give me like an
eeveelution please
i want an evolution of an eevee
[Music]
if i quietly go back there i could maybe
throw a pokeball at one of them nope it
never works
they keep on despawning and respawning
something rare
well that's not the case
[Music]
a shiny would be nice too
oh no it's gone
okay
fine
i don't have so much time anyway
what what were we doing i think now we
have
maybe
a good amount of
balls to tackle
the next lake
[Music]
some folks will only become available in
space-time verbs in post game and you do
need to catch everybody when you're
posting for information
oh yeah
yeah but the ones that i had there i
already had uh caught somewhere else so
i was not interested
mm-hmm this way you spawn huh
[Music]
do you like a cherry berry
it did not quite notice me yet
we get another chance
i think damage i i i heard that i heard
that's pretty cute like please say is
don't attack you if you took some damage
before wait only if your character
yourself
took some damage or if pokemon
within your group
took some damage
i'll throw another one
and i'll go with a
heavy bone
perfect perfect perfect
sorry that must have hurt a little bit
[Music]
don't be a pain in the butt
it really likes berries though
that's good oh no it's looking right at
me
oh
that heavy bowls will be heavy though
what is the matter with you
okay monkey
one can have banana for you
good banana
yummy fresh banana freshly picked from
the tree just like oh
she wants the banana too
[Music]
you help us no oh
okay this one really does not want well
maybe we can fight or are you just gonna
go away
[Music]
fighting loves joining his double edge
okay
i hate it when they just are like yo i'm
out of here i hate it
thanks for nothing
oh but i don't think i ever caught um
wait is that the same pokemon
or is that the prevolution
i'm getting confused
i have some honey
chansey okay it is a different one i
thought so i don't think i ever caught a
chance before didn't i
hallelujah first one
[Music]
oh
okay i think i'm done farming now
i'm done i'm done i'm done
let's see how many
we will have total
17.
okay but i don't want to waste them all
again on one [\h__\h] stupid pokemon
[Music]
where where are we going
ah over there that's far away let's go
to the pearl settlement
never done something oh wait um
i am being approached
thank you
what's good to the main quest i don't i
know sneeze layer can climb i don't know
i don't like using sneeze that much
though because i wish it would switch
back to the other mount that i'm using
after it's done climbing
the switch is what annoys me
so
kind of weird i know but
it annoys me so i don't like using it oh
hello
[Music]
it's so slow too
like when it's just walking
i guess i will
decent
i have a preference yes same okay good
stinky onsen again yeah
uh
not another huge fan of lundstein but
awesome would be nice also i was
thinking today
even though i just came back from a
skiing vacation
i was i was uh feeling a little bit of
the breeze outside and the breeze made
me feel for a moment as if i was at a
beach i don't know why
it's not even warm outside but that made
me feel like i'm i'm on the beach
and and now i really want a beach
vacation
hey to come beach vacation with me
oh
all of them speech theme
nice
[Music]
it's a family well then i will adopt all
of them except that one
boobs on the beach yeah
phoenix and
phoenix and peafowl gonna get roasted
on the beach
let's go to the beach beach
i want to know what what tasks i have to
do
don't notice me
defeated
ghost top move
ugh
[Music]
i'll kill you
oh wait i should have done ghost i'm so
stupid okay that works too
no beats in australia you know what i
kind of just want to move
to a [\h__\h] beach paradise already
i want to live somewhere where
you can
uh
always go to the beach that would be so
nice
but i'm thinking that's probably better
to do after
you know
one day one day
when i when i feel like
now is the time to
[Music]
settle down and chill
on either a beach or living on a lake
that's my goal
oops
um
[Music]
no no
no not break-ins no
i prefer lake
i want to go to a country where there's
always somewhere
i know if you live there
and you're like oh i want to know what
it's like to live in a country with who
which has more than one season but but
but but for someone who was
raised in a country before season so i
kind of don't want to
win a summer-only country
[Music]
come to brazil i've been to brazil both
in winter and summer and winter was very
warm as well indeed yeah i mean maybe
not swimming weather but still very warm
yeah
okay guys i'm going to take a little
break for a an idol meeting will take
about two minutes and maybe i'll pick up
another cookie and pet a cat that i meet
along the way
cookie
whoa
i'll be back very soon please wait for
me and then we'll continue i drank too
much tea i need to
exactly
[Music]
so
uh
[Music]
oh my god
oh my god why is this one better
why is the one from my second batch
better
it's much crunchier too oh my god
oh the i think
i like it when it's a mix of crunchy and
chewy
but um this one is smaller it has more
crunch area
but it kind of tastes better
not only because of the texture
is that just because i had it in the
fridge for two days
oh man
order cookies you should make cookies
you get so much more out of it
and it's so much cheaper i think i
actually don't know how much i spent for
the ingredients but i think it's
probably cheaper
[Music]
down
you guys want the cookies
you should need to do more cookie
research yeah
[Applause]
more cookies
oh
i'm so proud of them
stand mixers oh yeah the mixer
i mean i suppose you could do it with
your
my mom would probably just do it with
her hands
um
i don't know if a mixer is really
necessary
um but once you have a mixer you can do
so many things with it so many
[Music]
he's talking so much yeah
my mom
[Music]
hand mixer works too
damn it's really good um
some pets
[Music]
hmm
so now i have some cat hairs on my hands
again
what does that message say i cannot
read yet
i'm so proud of those cookies i want to
share them with my friends
oh mom i especially want to share it
with rmt because she's the one who
originally tasted those hotel cookies
with me
and there's a connection you know
there's a history
ah
it says
something like that
i wish i could give you some but i can
give you the recipe
the recipe is uh if you if you google
double tree or hilton
cookie recipe
you'll find it that way
mine is volume he's hoping to
he's munching already because he's
asking me to put a cookie in his mouth
he's not talking he's already
preemptively munching the air because he
wants a cookie
[Music]
well you won't get it
hmm
[Music]
sorry i'm just eating cookies all stream
long
[Music]
okay
half of the cookie is gone
sea water
nobody knows why
wait what do you mean why is it why is
why is it a questionable thing
it could be a fluke of geography or
perhaps it's connected to a pokemon
uh-huh
like i'll ask how do you pronounce this
one akuti a sweetie is protected by the
pokemon ooxie
from ooxia took flight the knowledge to
solve problems was born in people's
minds that's what the stories say anyway
equity
okay
my iphone
make a hole go
what if she pointed the phone into the
sky instead of to the wall
you think it could maybe make another
hole in the sky we should try it
we have to experiment
a cute
okay
[Music]
look
a tool that can make caves simply appear
from nowhere it's quite a handy one to
have
handy is a funny pun if you speak german
because i told you handy is what we like
to say to the phone
i wonder what wait's inside
it's probably another alpha pokemon that
i'll accidentally kill even though i
don't want to
i imagine there may be a pokemon in
there yeah
um
yeah two whole zio is like plus plus
plus and a plus is a minus
so yeah two holes will if one gets me
excel one two gets me pardoned yes yes
that's the logic no honestly that's not
even i didn't even think that far but we
could try that
i sense a chill in the air what is this
[Music]
ghost disco
wow wow wow oh is that the evolution of
the one the cute one that i
caught oh
it doesn't look cute anymore
[Music]
[Laughter]
wow that is quite the evolution though
it goes from that small baby to
this [\h__\h] it's like it turns into a
werewolf
why
it's pretty scary but what normal normal
ghost what was it
yeah it was normal ghost right because
we said that was [\h__\h] strong as hell
well
if we can get this one
[Music]
if we use it then there might be no
reason to use the other one that we
caught because this one is already
evolved there's already alpha so what
the hell
okay i will try to catch it
they look like that because dora died
and they hate people
is that laurel lit
oh what
what no no no no dark normal ghosts no
more ghosts no more ghosts right yeah
um
what's
dark was the only thing it was weak to
the right okay
you don't want to kill it but
got to be careful here i should have
started this
with my guide to again
paralyzed oh well
oh well well well
super frail oh
immune to normal fighting and girls
but let's see how much damage my dark
attack does i do have a no wait i do
have a dark attack but it's not an
attack attack
nasty
plot wait oh none of this really works
okay
testing good
wow that's wait that pokemon is weak as
[\h__\h]
if a non effect is not effective
it's also [\h__\h] strong okay
so it's strong and weak at the same time
what
low defense high of damn
what do you mean glass cannon
what is that
glass what's glass can is that
i never heard it being used like that
before
basically ah
that's that's what you oh
yeah i've heard it in that use before a
lot of times now i get what you mean
oh
do you think it would be helpful to have
this one in that final
yabai fight
hmm
[Music]
do you think that will kill it
accident
depending on what finally above our yoga
yes absolutely i love using mine
pretty good
i want apparel that will kill it oh wow
it's so weak
[Music]
this
way come on come on
it's got the power right now we can
throw a ball nice one
okay ultra ball please don't be as
painful as the other one yes
please
please please yeah
hallelujah
first try
oh why can't the other ones have been so
easy but that makes up for the amount of
balls we wasted on the others
yay
i might put it in my team because it's
really strong but also every week
i might put it into a fight and then it
gets one hit and we're like why did i
why did i even bother ringing bringing
it with me
and i regret it for the end of my
gameplay
game
playthrough
rng balancing itself
lots of tap resist but still we did so
much damage to
with not even effective attacks man
the painful fox is a pokemon set to be
filled with malice we were told stories
about it as children hmm
we used to be so cute was it mistreated
when it was so small and cute
what the [\h__\h] banks will always get
me
three immunities
yeah
the worst way
poor baby
then we must give it some love
[Music]
time for um
sorry
[Music]
you're gonna ask me what they all have
in common
ah how many are there
[Applause]
[Music]
well i don't rip
ah each one one bit okay i find all it
oh
can you repeat
oh you're telling me thank you
six zero one three one
wait
a columbia six eyes
what if i fail
hormone yet all all at once ah
that's what you mean
well now i already know the answer oh
well
[Music]
oh like this oh i thought you would give
me choices
with choices it would have been kind of
easy because if you know at least one of
them then but just by knowing the order
um it would work
i forgot six zero one three
one
i forgot was it this
yes okay
[Music]
okay
i got ooxia's claw
by the way the tea
[Music]
right now it didn't do wonders i'll tell
you that because my throat hurts a
little bit
it's not like it's doing any wonders but
i can i think before i eat super chats
um i'm gonna
try that
fruit candy
that i got from the doctor
prescribed
because that one apparently really
is amazing
oopsies club proof that you have
completed a trial set um
i mean supposedly maybe it helps more if
i drink it
for like a whole month every day i don't
know
amazing you cleared all the free trials
of the lakes you really i wonder
tell that to [\h__\h] kamado
tell him
[Music]
soda tell them
okay
[Music]
oh it's fine it's not done
and just a little bit
pick what i stand by also is taking a
few days off because of her throat
everybody right now has road issues man
this winter is hitting hard i think
because for me i think it's also
partially the winter
um
[Music]
no i don't think it was this bad last
year
this year everyone is like
seeing their limits
of their voices
of their vocal cords
oh god
oh by the way
apparently my tweet translation was a
little bit yeah bye but i didn't say
anything about it just the translation
being weird that's just how you say it
you like my my video that i always use
it's actually a video you gotta turn on
the sound it's not a gif for gif or give
the video
but i like using that
here's some rainbow energy from a
unicorn from a kiwawa a waffle kiwawa
sitting on a unicorn
i sent that to all the holo members who
are sick as a twitter reply recently
and there's a lot of
meanings
that that could have but the one that i
mean is that
yeah it's like my throat got
messed up
[Music]
my throat has been
you know
if i say it like that then you can
totally misunderstand
the way that google mistranslated it but
you know you know you know
yes
that yeah i told i told
i wrote to pick what i sent by yeah
i also have that problem a lot of us are
having it i wish you all the best please
take care you know what in some way i
think
i think it's good um because
finally decoration is kind of forced to
take
uh
a little bit of a break she said oh it's
maximum three days
but when is the last time that she took
three days in a row off i think
never
after her vacation
after her debut
i don't think she ever
took three days in a row off
[Music]
she took about three days one time last
year
oh but yeah it's very rare like three
days from the japanese
mindset from the japanese point of view
three days is a whole [\h__\h] vacation
uh three days for them is like two weeks
for us
i feel so worried and and sorry about
yeah
they don't they don't take enough days
off
especially piqua who is like
she's on the [\h__\h] grind and i i get
it like she she probably honestly she
really
enjoys continuously streaming every
[\h__\h] day but i want her to take some
time off
[Music]
yeah you don't become the third most
watched female streamer worldwide
without background yes but i feel like
now
she can
like she grinded enough
to
take a few days off every once in a
while
it's not like she's suddenly gonna be
unpopular afterwards not pick or no no i
think there is
that's it's not so easy anymore for her
to
um
you know
be [\h__\h] by the evil the algae rhythm
or by the
fans no no no they love her we love her
she has a really
really loyal loving
fan community
i wonder if she pressures herself to not
take a break but i hope she doesn't i
hope she just doesn't take a break
because she's enjoying it so much not
because she feels like she can't but
anyway that's just me worrying about
whole life japan members
who just work way too much
she wants her daily login bonus
yeah
it seems like it
is
simple
they also worry about you don't worry
about me i just came back from a
vacation and i'm already thinking about
my next
i have like
so many locations planned for this year
don't you worry about me because i
combine it with like getting content as
well so don't worry don't worry
i'm already excited about my next beach
vacation
i'm gonna go now and also i i wanna go
um
i want to go to the sauna and to pools
more often
i did that a little bit
we're only tangenting right now sorry
i did that a little bit um i think it
was
before her life
before i've i got myself like a
a card uh
like a like a
membership but like a a card that you
can use in
in many many um pools
like
public indoor pools in the city
um
to
motivate myself to get some swimming
exercise and help my my shoulder and my
back because i already had problems back
then of course
um
no not a punch card but you it's very
expensive but it's worth it when you if
you go swimming a lot
so i got myself that card and then i
went to
uh like every freaking pool that we have
in the city
um
no but it was a year a year pass
for a whole year
i think i think it was a year or half a
year not sure i think i think
okay i forgot but either one of those
i should get that again
but but they only
uh
they only
that card was only i think for like
the public ones and i think they didn't
even have a sauna
um
i figured going to the sauna more often
would be pretty healthy for me as well
so
sometimes they come with the
what's it called in infrared cabinet and
i think those are good too
[Music]
i should get one of those could use some
swimming hell yeah hell yeah
yeah if you
i think it's a good motivation for
anyone who's like short on money but
needs to work out like if you get a gym
membership don't i maybe it doesn't work
on everyone probably but
buy a gym membership and then you're
like
[\h__\h] broke so now that they bought it
i have to use it
get up early and work on fixing your
sleep schedule
big swig are you implying that my sleep
schedule is fixing
hey the past few
days ever since my vacation i've been
doing pretty fun i mean
i stayed up a little bit late tonight
maybe
i can fix it any time it's not that bad
yet it's not that bad yet and i i i
actually i actually i keep on waking up
pretty early
before my alarm because because because
so yeah i'm like um yeah very used to
waking up early now
chef
shut up you know nothing
i am an early bird now
um
[Music]
stop doubting me
mods ban everyone who says yes
yes or x
ban them
go on the rampage if you need
band every exit in the chat
[Music]
okay
you know what
no chat
there is no chat
i'm just um
playing a game alone
since we'll finish the free like trials
if i remember
[Music]
so quiet don't know what could await us
there but i'm always excited to explore
some ancient ruins
[Music]
if only they would apologize
then it would be loud again
[Music]
all right so free a little [\h__\h] there
they are i'm sorry quinoa we're sorry
oh
i'm sorry oh he's a good chicken who's a
good chicken
who's a good chicken
[Music]
oh never excuse me i am some people are
still
oh
[Music]
okay i cannot
bring it back then
shrouded ruins oh
it looks like unga bunga drawings
never doubted you buzz i know you
wouldn't end
oh
some of you are sweet some of the others
are little shits
thank you for renewing your membership
oh no i'm not seeing anything anyway
because i'm not look there's no chat
there is no chat
no no no no
no no no
missed is a very good
obscuring things it's long been said to
blur boundaries
what do you mean this was
there was missed in front of this before
and now it's gone because i
or was it always clear huh
excuse me
okay well chat if taking away the chat
is not
enough of a lesson to you then i will
take away myself
no i want no chat this is just
a silent playthrough of pokemon now
yeah that's that's where you break ryan
yeah
please forgive us
no you want your icing back once your
back goes to the back you want your sit
back off your back is that what you're
saying
oh oh
okay well
this won't stop my unyielding well dead
that sounds like you're still against me
so i will time you out
i'm sorry i'm sorry
okay i'm sorry i'm sorry we want oh i'll
see you back i'll sit back i'll see you
back you want your aussie back i'll see
you back i'll be back
you want yours you're back once you're
back oh
sorry oh
oh
oh who wants there oh she back off your
back oh is your back who wants their oh
she back oh she back what's your back
okay ah
well well well it can't be helped can it
you get a handbag
only your hand
unless you say
we love kiwawa
say it
ah
oh there it is there's the chat
there it is
i saw i saw that we left i saw
iron vader i saw that one janma in
between all the kimonos so i'm timing
you out
you think i wouldn't see that
well if
there everyone has to
be on the same
[Laughter]
okay i come back
that i'm uh
okay now let's [\h__\h] focus guys let's
[\h__\h] focus
if we do somehow bring together the
world of humans the world of pokemon and
the world of myth
then maybe we need a setting such as
this
hello
i'm home
so i hope you're gonna stay in good
thinking now
i love kyoza too but what does that have
to do with anything
hold on
hey
that being said what are we meant to do
now
seems i've made it in time
you arrived just when we assembled all
three gifts did you somehow see your
progress across the distance dividing us
um
rita i don't know why you would assume
that that's kind of creepy i would just
say she
i don't know
just just
she was just bored and sick of waiting
and saw us uh an hour ago so she assumed
we were done already
oh mama
i had the aid of a rather remarkable
pokemon if you really wish to know huh
could you mean that pokemon that flips
about the history region
ah but never mind that now what about
the red chain how are we to forge it
good question
i would hardly know
we speak of a divine
instrument once said to be capable of
binding the very world
do you really imagine it can be forged
by mortal hands
and what are we to do search the entire
vastness of history for the answer
hmm
they're gonna help us so thank god it's
is it exquisite
the pokemon of the lakes welcome back
welcome back welcome back nice to see
you again
[Music]
i really suck at that by the way
i received the red chain
[Music]
so it was true the fact our people have
passed down for all these generations
has been kept
at last i can set this burden aside
you've succeeded once again kiawah
yet things do not seem to be going so
well for the rest of this world
what ha what have you heard now
i've had some news for my fellow
merchants in the ginkgo guild it seems
that the commander is going to forgo
for
forgot
oh
oh wait that's a word for go oh
for
girl waiting
for our investigation to finish
he plans to
uh climb mount corner himself
sounds like midlife crisis to me
has he lost his senses he plans to get
close to the rift to study it himself
well he doesn't yet know that aokia has
managed to get the red chain now does he
that's true there's no way he could we
need to tell him about the chain and
about everything kiawah has achieved
before he sets out
we'll go
aha uh-huh
four forego
skip or not to partake of oh
hey
is he like really [\h__\h] sad that i'm
gone but here i am
uh excuse me coming through
wait kiawah it's you i can't believe i
just let you pass right by
oh he was depressing espresso
thank goodness you're still alive
i'm honestly more surprised that you're
still alive but okay
i mean of course you are i knew you'd be
all right
wait one second i'll go let the captain
and the professor know you're back
oh okay
oh he lost his aussie just like you guys
remember remember that don't forget
about it because you might do it again
if you're cheeky
oh my dear kiwala i really missed how
you voiced me with this beautiful accent
i don't ever want to lose you again
thank you fire trap for the message
that's right my man
that's right
racer i know you've been worried about
kiawah but you really don't sound
english at all
[Music]
uh um
what you're trying to say that i'm fake
or what no this is my perfect english
accent discrimination i say
and besides weren't you the one who
couldn't get a wink of sleep from all
you're worrying over our friend
you know you didn't have to tell her
that
just ignore him kiawah
anyway where's captain celine wasn't she
coming with you professor
she's very on the amount of work i'm
afraid wait to join her in the service
office it seems her hands are more than
full now that commander camado is gone
he's gone yeah
i leave this town now
well he sat out for my corner with the
security corps in town he really wants
to know what's all that about about a
quarter night senpai to kill dogo
he's determined to handle this old space
time rape business himself including
dealing with the pokemon that's been
spotted on the other side
and since i'm such a fine fellow i took
over watching the gate for the security
corps folks
well we aren't go anywhere out here
let's add inside and report you can't
put
isn't my accent beautiful
i know i know i know
it just comes naturally
it's just the talent that i have
so you managed not to die just as i
ordered well done
drunk gordon ramsay does it sound like
that nice
[Music]
oh
wait [\h__\h] i should not have said that
maybe
wasn't that a secret oh [\h__\h]
no duh your own pasties earned you any
help you may have received
before moving forward i must ask
you let's just rat her out
[Laughter]
nicely
i assume that you are are here again
because you've managed to learn
something of use
i have this beautiful red chain for you
milady
um i think i i i made it so to impress
you like
you know diamonds are a girl's best
friend i thought you could wear it and
then you'll be nicer to me
no
that's not why i made it
go on
[Music]
i explained the wrenching
that looks gorgeous
yes
i will put that on immediately
thank you
commander camado is no longer here in
jabula village
the security corps had been scouting the
area near the space-time rift and they
reported sightings of something on the
other side of it something that
resembled a pokemon
the commander made this decision to take
the security corps in the mountain so as
to prepare to fend off any possible
threat
they were to make for the temple at the
peak
the bias may be tough but it still seems
like a bad idea to do something so risky
without kiawah's help
as the captain of the survey corpse i
hereby order you to proceed as follows
kiawah
take that red chain to mount cordon it
make your way to the peak and put an end
or to all of this you're officially
reinstated at your former rank
back to normal
it was fairly easy actually
[Music]
are you sure captain the boss isn't
around to prove that [\h__\h] him
she's in charge now
if he didn't wish me to decide things in
this place then he should not have left
me in charge here
then i'll go where's wow
we're all these two we're all in this
together we members of the circle plus
go on yeah
naturally no one suggested you should
not now stop singing high school musical
and get to work
sorry guys apparently i'm tired i i
shouldn't be but apparently i am
my
my mouth is saying i'm tired
my brain is saying not so much what you
have a quest for me
something to matter lucario
[Music]
oh he's got a nice hairstyle
i'm right
and you won't
he's
kind of cool
oh okay yukiya nice to meet you
he's cool and he has a cool pokemon
hmm
riley's and
you know this guy
why do you guys know everyone why is
everyone an ancestor
even this simple nbc
what is it speak
no one understands that speak human
language
if you're waiting to battle
sure okay request 88
he wants me
help you inside the cave oh
i don't remember why you guys remember
all these people
[Music]
character that's your boy
incredible
[Music]
i don't pay attention to the story but i
don't remember all of these
characters and and immediately connect
them to characters that look slightly
different like some of them look
familiar to me too it's not like i don't
feel like uh any one of these reminds me
of someone but excuse me excuse me for
not remembering every [\h__\h] npc in
every game
sorry but that made me mad
cause you don't need to do this journey
oh yeah yes i do
well yes i do
god
oh
calm down quinoa come down come down
come on oh good all is good all is good
i just don't have a photographic memory
okay
stop flexing your photographic memory on
me
and your
pokemon
nerdiness
i like pokemon too but
i just don't remember
everything be cool if i did but
i don't that's what you guys are here
for now
so you guys
tell me oh this is cool because that's a
reference to this and that and this is
cool because that's a reference it isn't
that
um
i appreciate
you guys telling me about that i just
can't i just can't know it all by myself
okay
oh
now that that's clear
ah
i think i have everything for that one
side quest rolls again something with
raspberries
um
[Music]
here
hopple berry raspberry hearty grains
three two one blueberry raspberry hearty
creams hopefully raspberry
purple berry
raspberry
[Music]
and hearty grains
oops
[Music]
there was this subquest
uh
fluaro
he's over there okay
while i'm at it while i'm here
yes that's the one that gives gives me
new new wears
very very good
[Music]
the shop guy
yeah
wait that was not it
the one that gives you new words are the
fetch quest for the uh uh uh uh is that
the one with the mushroom
i'm trying to get those ingredients on
the side as well
this was for evie yeah right yeah yeah
yeah
he's evie
right he was making a treat for easy
hometown muffin
a big treat made from berries and other
ingredients which is often eaten in
regions such as gala
[Music]
interesting i guess the taste is fine
but it's just not the same as the
muffins from my hometown i remember them
being more moist and having this nice
delicate flavor to them sorry to waste
your time after all the trouble you went
for to gather the ingredients for us
but i'm afraid these mediocre muffins
won't be enough to get mean it
i'm sure it will like it
ah see it does
like it it's satisfied
what did they eat at all
uh uh oh me me
you want another i don't think that's
wise too many snacks will give you a
bellyache
i want more beach
there we go she's happy everybody's
happy
jubilee muffins
[Music]
oh
recipe
yeah
all right we got a new recipe for
for the muffins
school
after the cookie ark i will be making
muffins
the muffin ark from cookie monster to
the muffin man
i will become the muffin man what was
the other one
springing mushroom sweet food
suit food fruit i don't think i have
that yet the soup food fruit the other
things i do
[Music]
do you know the muffin man do you know
the muffin man
do you know the lovely man
died
i think the one for the shop is the pop
rod
oh should i do it should i do it now
[Music]
the paparazzi yeah yeah that might have
been it
uh total weight we can do it quickly
they're easy to
um
acquire this one
might tell you where's yum yum yum
oops oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay
pop poppy
pop-tarts
please don't start selling pop-tarts
there
i don't want it
speaking of oh am i gonna be forced to
go to the main quest
did you find the commander i know
the commander is already at mount corona
already how could a grown man like
commander come on they'll be so reckless
first expelling yukiyawa now this i
think he is a stern talking too
as the leader of the pearl clan loyal to
a mighty sinner who reigns over all
space i can go anywhere investigate that
i please and now i am going to stop the
commander
oh
who is the reckless one
everyone's pissed man
and you got
run out of the village right but you
still tried to find a way to help us out
of course
that's right chiara worked hard to get
that red chain to help everybody
to write a fine drop [\h__\h] at two the
survey corpse is always hard at work for
the sake of everyone here in the village
as well as for the sake of relations
with pokemon
she looks cute
thanks here texas
ah
what
max survived what was waiting for this
can you give me more than one
where did you get that from
why multiple
seats i want more of that
your orders are free
one make for the summit camp they only
always ask for stuff they never she
never gives stuff that child gave me
something about the others
yeah i don't have access to them yet but
maybe with the with the shop
uh
check your recipe store
what there's a
recipe store
buy recipes
i forgot i think i used that once in the
beginning
make for the summit camp and from there
the temple of sinnoh
two use the red chain to resolve this
mess
and free return here alive
i'll think about that
i don't know if i want to return anymore
no they forced me to go
again but i can go back i think
oh
[Music]
okay i'll check it out if i'm able to go
back
i've heard the latest so you've been
accepted back into the galaxy team have
you
i suppose congratulations are in order
here some max motions thank you
looks like the big moment is upon us at
last but no doubt it will be fine after
all you worked so hard to earn that
right chain
[Music]
both adam and erica have headed to the
peak as well
my good friend kiawa i wish you a great
fortune in the battles to come
i would truly regret losing one of our
most beloved are you like implying that
i might die
[Music]
it seems kamado intends to use the
summit camp as a base of operations for
this undertaking
he's like writing me a hug
as for me i think i will set up a shop
closer to the temple itself
volo
volo believe in me
believe in me
oh
who do we have here
things certainly seem to have gotten at
the end no not like that
well if anything goes wrong the great
melee will be here for more support at
least
something like that
moral support from you
no thank you uh
the pop pods
was
not here was on the other
on another
[Music]
call 20 pokemon oh did i not get to
report yet oh
it's a different place
mommy money
[Music]
new rank
soon
and we'll return to the village
we're gonna go to the main quest soon i
just want that recipe and the pop tarts
uh but yeah what i wanted to say
was uh
i just want to
mention
um
now maybe better not to say anything at
all um
[Music]
but you guys might be waiting for it
and wait a second oh my god
25 000 is that the only way you can get
it that's
expensive
cortisone
i know tiny hi hi ho ho
yeah
[Music]
holy [\h__\h] a full heal maybe not so much
necessary
okay the other ones
wow can i make one what does it need ah
oh
the king's leaves oh
oops
i need revives
[Music]
and dad
okay
i guess you're not getting whatever
ready before and you will but it will
have to wait um
[Music]
uh
start please turn those fragments to
moon
those fragments the ones that have been
picking up in the
time distortion
[Music]
needs starfish recipe
a stardust
wait huh
how much was it
start piece
okay
oh red shirts blue shirts green shirts
one bag of stars
damn
ah
[Music]
hmm i kind of ignored this guy most of
the time
i thought he would give me like some
extra recipes every once in a while by
by giving me a side quest or something
but no i just
gives it to me like that
how nice of him
[Music]
he has he has pop what i didn't see
it
he does
and wait he has a suit food root
i need that too how many did i need
just the weight how many do i need of
all of that
[Music]
for that i need three pop
pods
and i need
[Music]
one
the mushroom i have but i'm gonna buy
one anyway
[Music]
one and
three
okay
let's give
that one
back first i is it in there
yeah
you neglected him too
i would have probably neglected him for
much longer
if it weren't for you guys
reminding me about his existence
thank you
uh holy [\h__\h] wait there's a lot of a lot
of new questions
evie's evolutions
uh-huh
chime chill
damn so many cyclists
pastel
pro gunk
batman we have putty so
that will stretch just to use of this
hot cd smooth
snow what
wait is that about the aluna
no it's not a shiny right it's a
low level picks
fellow from aluna has several rupees but
he calls them kale
[Music]
i don't think i need it now
okay wait i want to give back
was it down there
[Music]
down here
sure your eyebrows
look so scary
[Laughter]
why is everyone here having
weird eyebrows do you have weird hours
the other lady has no eyebrows at all
hit no mooji
[Music]
jeez did he just say he sheesh
did he just say sheesh
wait you've got potpons would you let me
have some please just freeze
and um them i'll set up with some new
wares
let's go
what where's what where's what what what
what what will be
[Music]
avalanche
okay i'm not now
well someone has barely endured excuse
me
[Music]
excuse me
i was born like this not like i can't do
something about it my nose is fine i
have a nose
look at you go to stock
show me
[Music]
don't tell me it's a max revive
oh wow he's gonna let me give him some
more again
[Music]
let me speak to tal hoola again crunchy
salt
huh
i have a lot of crunchy salt 15 out of
three
okay okay
oh but let's see what he has now what's
what's new
not sure what is new here
but okay
crunchy salt crunchy salt
the great balls are new
oh maybe ultra balls is next door
oh that would be very good for me
worth it
wait
[Music]
i was confused for a minute because the
i didn't mark the quest so i thought he
he's not related to it after all but he
must be he must be
mix that powder
report back to troy about your progress
i'm on my way
should i get this hairstyle
one day for new outfits this hairstyle
with a man bun
what do you think
and a little bit of a cut because it's
pretty short
i think i would look cute with that
okay
is that a hint no no not at all
literally just came to me now that idea
and
you stole his treasure
nothing to worry about
even more wears
oh
[Music]
ah no ultra balls but
uh
oh well okay
that would be too easy i guess
wait we didn't give back the other thing
yet right that i want to give back
uh
this one
[Music]
ultra bombs are next
you unlock new balls by getting stars oh
okay
when i rank up um
i'm close to a rank up
here you go
the ingredients that you asked for sir
[Music]
swamp snack when eaten the scariest
snack temporarily swaps the pokemon's
offensive stats
[Music]
i won't use that sounds interesting but
not for me took to it like offended to
water
[Music]
oh i like the stamp sound feels
so satisfying and now we go back to the
main quest
i will do more side squat side quests
off stream i actually want to keep them
for off stream so i have something to do
okay
mount coat on it um
summit
always summit but i'll go to mountains
okay
[Music]
all right let's see
oh
oh we're supposed to go there okay
so
summit camp
sorry
don't kill me
all right i quickly want to attack that
[Music]
what's hiding underneath
what
a nose pass
interesting i don't think i've ever met
this pokemon before on my travels
oh
don't kill me
that's the nose that i was looking for
huh
uh a normal pokeball we'll do it
[Music]
oh and now i thought he dropped the nose
oh come on
numbers heavy's nice two birds one stone
oh surplus
[Music]
feel
this wheel i think he's feeling we just
rolled off toward went this way
oh his feel rolled off the mountain
oh cute
but no time for that
uh we are going
up here
let's try to fly a little bit will that
help us
excuse me
passing through
i'll climb
oh come get it don't worry
[Applause]
[Music]
stop here
we can wait
[Music]
i actually haven't watched that uh anime
still
yeah
i
i uh
i knew about all the hype
i i was around but it was super hyped
but whoa what is that stinkiness here
like in the onsen
[Music]
what is that
why is it so stinking
me
neither it was it was so popular though
it must have been popular for a reason
mountain swamp
time space stink
stinky
overrated hmm
if you think so
people have people have their opinions
have we been in here before
wait we need to heal a self-edge
okay
[Music]
why do i hear some
slight music that sounds like a radio
who is this
before i was kamado up here
are you the mozzie guy
oh hope so why the cooking
sorry about having to shout at the
shutter the wall flower i'd much rather
be there now serving up some freshly
grilled potato mochi but that task
monster come on it was gone and left me
to oversee our food supply he always
finds a way to put even those old bones
to work
while i'm handling that i suppose i'll
handle you as well time we got
rid of you once in world why do you hate
me what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
fine i'll kill you
i'll stab you in your heart he always
seemed a little bit
like a [\h__\h]
i'm sorry but
he seems like a
discriminating person to me
you know what
sweat sweats
[Music]
snake
are you serious
gotcha oh my mom
i'll make myself plain as kamado's right
hand
it's one of you his right hand i'm just
because you make his food
i'm charged with executing all the
gritty deeds kamadu can't do one do
himself
i could do some jokes here but i'm gonna
leave it to you guys
i gave him my word i'd get rid of any
fools that might dream of getting in the
way of his plans
and besides it's not just kamado who
longs to live in a new home free of fear
and strife
his dream is mine now too
oh
i've seen my smoke bombs before
what
white ninja
when i heard you managed to crown those
nobles one after another oh did it ever
make my blood run hot and my heart pound
it's [\h__\h] creepy
at last at last
one final opponent worthy of my great
ninja techniques that have been left to
mulder all these long years
creeps me out [\h__\h] creeps me out
galaxy team's benny challenged me to a
family he turns out to be more than just
making potato mochi
wally's ancestor
rival from
wally
oh
[Music]
i don't remember the name but
look at him posing over
there uh
oh we have the right pokemon out let's
give him one hit come on come on come on
come on come on come on i'm counting on
you so fat i'm counting on you it's hard
[Music]
okay
oh
did you break your hips old dude huh
did you throw out your hips
[Music]
he's like oh
i'm totally doing a ninja pose i don't
need help getting up no no not at all
yeah he's holding the pose just because
he can't move wait you [\h__\h] avoided
it
[\h__\h]
you won't avoid it no man
i like that pokemon though i like the
design of it
sneeze line
both combat
no that's okay
why is it so
looking so weird though
uh flying
yeah we'll go for
[Music]
hypnosis that was good
yes
beautiful
[Music]
oh
let's hit it real hard
we're not having any mercy yet we're not
playing
it's still alive
it's still alive because it's stats were
raised for psychic how much oh [\h__\h]
okay that's fine that's fine um
we'll just um
we'll handle that just fine
i don't know what comes next
so that's also problem but anyway
i want to attack with
aqua tail
and crunch
[Music]
there we go what's next so give up
oh
i'm alive i'm alive i'm alive i'm alive
i'm alive i'm alive
[Music]
but i don't know what's the most
strong against delayed here because all
are just effective
why do we still have focused energy what
the [\h__\h]
[Music]
wow
that is quite a lot of damage for just
being effective
but we survived we did not survive but
that's okay
damn strong i only have two pokemon left
yo but this is the last one that he has
so
we're fine
um
oh super effective fairy oh oh oh oh oh
oh
is that so
not that we really need anything super
effective anymore but here he goes
down
should i help you
i i i might be
kind enough to give you a hand to
get back on you on your tippy toes
only if you say sorry
seems my ninja techniques will soon be
consigned to history
you are history
very good young one very good indeed
it's only a foolish ninja who tries to
keep after target they know they cannot
beat
and to be honest i don't hate you might
actually like you after a fashion
fashion huh
at least with a skill you show in battle
you don't admire me for how many potato
mochi i eat
i feel like
he should just like me by the fact that
i enjoy what he cooks like i would i
would always be happy if someone enjoys
what i cook i feel like that's like
a real compliment and makes you really
happy if someone even if they don't say
it out loud if they just munch months
months once once on your food and
they're like
oh good stuff
i feel like any cook would be really
really happy genuinely happy about that
unless you're gordon ramsay and
i don't give a [\h__\h] about anyone
stupid gordon ramsay
but listen well kiama pokemon are truly
terrifying
pokemon
no no no
i will try your cooking well my cooking
isn't anything special but i'm trying
i'm trying i can make a few things
yeah
i'm still very um
very very
basic but
yeah i've been learning new things such
as making cookies
kamado and i saw our hometown burned to
the ground by madden pokemon running
amok
we lost plenty of friends and comrades
that day
okay that's understandable that that
makes you kind of like fear or even
dislike pokemon
that's why kamado came here to history
to try to build a new home where people
could live free from fear
but to achieve something i need to yeah
i'm sorry
that's really great you sometimes have
to take extreme actions
if
hypothetical as it may be a pokemon
thanks gordon ramsay sorry you're nice
you want a nice one
a pokemon where to appear from within
that space-time rift
come on don't might lose hold of his
reason
save kamado from himself by force if you
must oh
if you want me to stop him anyway then
why did you stop me first
i'm yawning a lot it's not late it's
half past 8 p.m but i think in this room
sometimes i just lack oxygen
do that and i'll stop you full of
mortals i'm so sick of your potato
margin no thank you
not doing it for you
so sick of it did you heal my pokemon
you did okay thank god because i would
have had to use a lot of revives
that's got it
thanks for healing
was that a threat yeah he's gonna stuff
down all this potato matcha just to make
me choke he's probably gonna mix some
poison into it
that [\h__\h] snake
okay i'm excited we're gonna fight
kamado now i feel like i'm gonna get
[\h__\h]
this is not the hard one that you guys
talked about though right you said that
comes after and i think that's against
uh volo if i understood correctly
i help my choice of pokemon okay
[Music]
good luck thank you
oh
ultra balls
yeah
all right
they probably asked me if i'm ready to
go up
you better take that red chain up to the
top of the mountain
that pokemon threatening to descend on
the peak any moment now i think it may
be almighty sinner
but all this has to be stopped and
you're the only one who can do it
almighty say no seems to be nearly here
but still the commander obstructs us
[Music]
finally they'll see their god
with their own eyes oh my god get your
autograph books out now
okay
i feel like first of all
he had a useless move sliver she had a
useless move
focus energy i want to get something
else uh we don't have a flying attack
right now and he has hurricane but it's
[Music]
that's not
outrage
85 that's a little bit better
going on the rampage becomes fixated
when when when the pokemon is fixed are
you gonna move does it get stronger
every time they use it
i wanna replace focus energy
[Music]
oh yes okay
we're definitely getting rid of focus
energy
but
it would be nice to have a flying attack
on him too or an or the ice attack you
know what
instead of twista you know
something useful
ice or
but this is
pretty bad
75.
replace twist those eyes and it would be
at least more coverage
[Music]
i think it's good to have more coverage
i know smoove already has eyes but at
least it's coverage
ice beam
okay
so confirm that we don't have to use it
but you know
maybe maybe smooth dies and the only
thing that saves me is an ice attack and
then we have slither who's still alive
you know
there might be a moment like that um
who else could use fixing
sock do you have anything good
85.90
100 double edge oh
life risking tackling which the user
rushes to turn this off damn uh-huh
a tackle a really strong tackle
i'm kind of regretting getting kusagaki
it just looks cute but it's kind of
not really that strong
call mine
okay
maybe this one instead of swift for
a situation
where we're really really desperate
uh oh play rough is that good a5
instead of fairy wind
oh yeah yeah
okay
who's here
[Music]
best moves are treated most and we
should have gone to the tutor we'll go
like before
the real
worst fight in this game
okay chance moves up smooth moves of
smooth smooths
uh also has double edge and
ew nothing else okay
let's check so fetch
everything new fire blast
may leave the target for
is that worth it
playing for a better
okay then the rest doesn't look really
good either okay
and we didn't look at mummy i think
don't expect anything new but um
leave store 110.90
you store him instead of leave blade how
about that use the whips up the storm of
leaves around the target the recoil from
this move lowers the user's defensive
stats
oh brave bird
brave bird
instead of ariel ace
okay
maybe
blade over sword
leaf blade
is better than
what sword
huh
leaflet is the blade is better than leaf
storm ah okay so just change that
okay i think we're done
[Music]
okay
i feel like we're still gonna have
problems what pokemon should i send out
first does he always send out the the
same pokemon first you guys wanna you
guys wanna hey maybe tell me give me a
hint which pokemon first would be good
[Music]
no
no you're not gonna tell me you'll be
gone too
[Music]
secret
don't remember okay
now you're always excited to tell me
these things
write your glasses
oh
are you here to stop him or help him
and he's wearing an armor
[Music]
someone died
you're good
i've heard that this red chain of yours
will bind the world i assume that to
bind the world means to hold the world
together keeping it as it meant to be
a welcome idea but can i truly put my
faith in such tales
[Music]
well
if you won't trust anything i offer
anyway then why did you tell me to go on
this mission anyway like to begin with
commander please be reasonable i
understand that you're bound to protect
your people as commander of the galaxy
expedition team but i have the same duty
toward my clan but down in kiawah like
this you're not just wrong you're full
perhaps you're right but if i were to
simply please my faith in this girl and
that faith were to be betrayed then how
could i possibly face my people
you may think you're the only one to
desperate the only one desperate to
protect the people of jubilee life but
you're not kiawah is putting her life on
the line as well oh
huh
fine enough
let fate decide what happens next
whichever of us is stronger will prevail
face me with your pokemon chiama today
we battle in earnest
it's about [\h__\h] time
yeah
[Music]
challenge mary done
for pokemon okay
oh
wait does he have all the mounts
[Music]
is
not all of them though though though
right because there's more than four
but this physics
ah okay no that's not a mount it would
be cute if it was damn
sunk
ground pounds another chunk
uh oh [\h__\h]
i have something effective farting
hallelujah
what's this i want to look in your
monster sir
excuse me
[Music]
it is flowing in wet in the wind the
mustache my friend
is flowing in the winds
the monsters is flowing in the wind
i was so strong because he looks very
defensive that snorlax
ah
[Music]
oh
wow
that is problematic
that is
problematic that is problematic
that is a problem [\h__\h]
i wanna i need to revive mommy
i won't be able to get him down
otherwise
[Music]
oh
i will revive
wherever max will have yes
[Music]
it's
a question so if this uh affects
christopher's order if someone else
switches in
do they
continue with the order that kusuki
created
[Music]
i've never really looked at that how'd
that work
oh okay
[Music]
how did that do so much damage
because it lowered the defense
whoa
whoa that must have lowered it by a lot
though
yes
[Music]
good job
although you're in danger here
males are lower targets you know what
why not use this
and i'm gonna go strong because it
didn't affect them
thingy anyone okay so
offensive little words
and i'm dying but that's okay
that's why triple r is amazing now
damaged by the recoil oh
grass and fighting super effective so
it's it it was worth it to revive women
after all
welcome back my boy
um
finish it off with the leaf blade i
would say
it could
beautiful
cleavable
fluffable clear table i don't know how
to say your name
oh
super factor
psychic two times you little [\h__\h]
[Music]
damn
but oh no
the only one with something super
effective
[Music]
so what else
we have three choices i mean we can also
revise both sparks
[Music]
should we try to attack or should we
just revive obese spots
[Music]
you can throw some flames you think
oh
sometimes
[Music]
let's
i will try
[Music]
it's not going to kill but it's going to
do good damage yeah yeah yeah oh we'll
stay oh mark's perfect okay you wasted
the move you wasted a moment
because i'm gonna raise my sets another
time
[Music]
and then go strong and it's my kill
maybe maybe maybe maybe maybe oh sheesh
let's see what that does
it doesn't stack
wait that doesn't why does that not
stack i don't know what stacks and what
doesn't
but i bought something
something's definitely stacked i mean
it's not sure what it does oh well
okay
it was a good spot maybe
uh whoa well what killer anyway
somewhere one way or the other just for
safety i'm giving myself the chance to
attack again well okay we're good we're
good
wait you have one more no
[Music]
any pokemon that threatens our life here
must be eliminated
[Music]
thank you
do i fight sinnoh do i catch sinnoh
you're truly a force to be reckoned with
but sir i could not defeat your mustache
this is what japanese people call doge
it is a very very very dramatic way of
apologizing in japan i did this
like sometimes just out of joe like
jokingly
uh in japan
when i was with friends or with teachers
and so on and they would be like yo
chiara yeah get up get back up get that
don't do that
yeah they don't um
they take this one quite seriously
wow
very very dramatic
appall apology this is
ah i did it in the excellent school yeah
yeah yeah but a good christmas scholar
for that one most people didn't really
understand what i was doing
yeah only if you do something
insanely bad like i don't know kill
somebody's
um brother or so i don't know and you go
to the family and say i'm so sorry i
didn't it was an
accident yeah
or
or when you're in the yakuza
and you say to the to the shareholders
you say
makotoni
gozaimasu
um
[Applause]
[Music]
i've decided i concede
wait i take your place now but i
apologize sincerely for doubting you
commander
i know i have no risk to ask it of you
any longer but please use that strength
of yours for the sake of the galaxy
expedition team you never had the right
to ask me anything though
no for the sake of the celestica people
and all the pokemon living in history
i look cute
don't you worry commander we've got the
right chain
okay
well if we manage to
do that then i'm not scared of what's to
come
and i will
save okay
am i gonna try to catch sinnoh
if yes then i might need more balls
my money is fading away
i will be fine we'll be fine
[Music]
probably
what do you find remember at the end of
pokemon uh a little pearl
uh i i
first try uh caught the legendary so
[Music]
i think we're good
interesting
is that cleaver
and uh
that one is my mount
that's my other mount on the left side
is all the mounts and on the right side
is all the lures cool
cool
[Music]
it's a statue of the one pokemon that
was said to have been loyal to the
ancient hero oh wait does it say the
same thing
yeah
in here
oh okay they're loyal to the ancient
hero really
wait what mount is dad
that looks like the nightmare before
christmas uh like some something from
there
huh what mouth is that
i thought left side was only mounts
but that's wait that gives me ocd
does that only give me ocd because
there's just one side that needs to be
switched
cause that's the mount again on the left
side the the boob
and that's the lord again
but that's the lord and that's the mount
and that's a lord here
that's a lord
[Music]
and that's amount and that's amount
and that's amount
wait what what why why why why why why
why why
why why why
why why what
that really bothers me
[Music]
attention to detail please
what's the reason why did they do that
okay canceling your pre-order
come on now's the time use the retching
wait what what is this
there's a voice in my head is is just
telling you that you love me irida and
that we too should run away and marry
yo in your heart yes it's speaking to
you your love for me
you hope that red chain tried to catch
me then wait you are the legendary ear
[Laughter]
is single
i'll catch you irida
do you hear what you're saying
almighty sinnoh i think all my
descendants may be speaking to me no you
are cinnamon
i'll catch you
it's telling me
you hold the red chain
try to catch me then for the fight to
come
take these
balls
i
didn't need to buy anything afterward
[Music]
say no
wait i wanted to take a screenshot and
push the wrong button
[Music]
oh stomp
wow
[Music]
oh
wow i don't know i won't even be
uploading those because there's a
spoilers but this looks really cool
whoa the red ring
when you take photos that you're never
gonna use anyway i'm never gonna look at
it again anyway either he broke it
washed on that
i went so hard on them you just break it
[Music]
oh
we can paralyze it let's go
please please please please please
please please
it might have been good after all
but let's do some damage as well
it wasn't
one hit hockey i wouldn't
[Music]
there are no quick balls in this game
just want a dragon blood
i doubt it
oh we could also do dragon
i want to kill it
fairy would kill it
oh well
not a lot of pokemon to use so
let's play around we'll probably easily
catch it anyway did it just turn its
back to me
why my oh my
your coward
this is not gonna kill it if it was
dragon itself i know dragon is effective
against dragons how many times
outrage will kill too
[Music]
or crunch
low as it targets the sensors
[Music]
but it would take ages with ice cream
and crunch
[Music]
but it's fine well maybe not anymore now
no it's probably
[Music]
go back to the beast box
because i'm scared that the carol is
paralyzes will go away
let's do this
the music is becoming kind of like
emotional like positive
cinematic
[Music]
dramatic thing
one more [\h__\h] i wanted to throw the ball
i know i know
[Music]
that was um calculated because you guys
may have thought that i'm bad at math
but i'm actually a pro
i like i like that small pokemon against
that huge boy
looks cool
[Music]
kick
well it wasn't red i didn't have the
status effect so that was to be expected
yay is this what is this the
the where the post credits uh the the
first credits start soon
we say more
she caught it right she called almighty
center yes so therefore i am god too
become as god now treat me like one
pray to me
get on your knees
the red chain's been shattered but
we've still got the pokemon of the lakes
to thank for getting this far
right the red chain was so useless eh
i totally did it without the red chain
it was so useless
was that just useless was was a waste of
time
i calmed it down for for like a moment
at least a little bit
it weakened him ah okay okay i
understand
oh well donkey i want my girl
masterfully handled yeah i was watching
the whole time as you battled and caught
your way to a simply stunning victory
literally on the prize of the super
cooks and now i am god it's all because
she had me to show her the ropes when
she first got here
oh
kinky
i didn't see anything
no scene like that was that in the
in the dlc
is that pre-order scene
ah i can hear my descender
no it's it's called palkia
mighty pokey are speaking to me in my
mind
one question
did i get parking on because i chose
irida
or did it recognize that i have
a pearl on my switch
and that's what i know it's because of
it okay okay
cool
space time grows chaotic
the power fails
the frenzied one
it comes now to fight
that is why i am here
you're telling me there's another one
but the rat chains smash the bits
no way even kiawah kutaka will never
pokemon as strong as that last one now
huh
i'm good
another one right away
here oh
is it the other one diagonal
oh oh looks like it
[Music]
what's up
cool cool cool i like the cut scenes
um can you guys
get on with the sampling that necklace
hello uh get that hot glue gun
steel dragon huh
[\h__\h]
all of you we must vacate no we're gonna
fight now
uh forget the fancy talk book it come on
no eh boring let me fight
we'll fight
before this almighty sinnoh decides it
wants to fight us the other one
but commander that's my god
i can't just leave it here
you're dance
when
you won't be any use to anybody if you
die a bit
what you're waiting what you waiting
what you waiting what you waiting for
no no coward
i wanna fight
uh
yeah
it's my night
nah no no reason to retreat though
did you did you pick up the pieces of
the chain guys you had one job
are you telling me i should have done
that
i thought that legendary
i'm not gonna picking up i'm gonna have
time picking up those uh
pieces of the chain
[Applause]
red chain broken man
such dreadful power is certainly beyond
our current capabilities to survey such
a creature i'm amazed you even managed
to stay on your feet before it your what
well i'm god and did you notice the
energy pouring out of the rift it seems
likely that a buildup of the same energy
was what caused the strange lightning
not thrown another pokemon into their
friendships
so our two clans truly were following
different almighty signal but both were
real no more reason to fight now
what a shocking turn of events
that sounds ironic you say nothing of
the shock of hearing the commander speak
so differently
i must apologize from the bottom of my
kokoro
to the both of you as fellow leaders
you saw the truth that i could not you
never abandoned your trust in kiawah
and to you kiawa
i acted on the ill considered
presumptions and drove you from the
galaxy expedition team forcing you to
face great hardship alone
and despite all that you still stroved
to save all of history
finally the respect that i deserve
thank you
congratulations you're both wrong
[Music]
kamado working at the friars oh he would
look good in my uniform and not my
uniform but can't be uniform please not
in my uniform no no no
well it's not like we could just sit
back and ignore the space-time rift
and we understood commander that you had
reasons to act as you did you really you
were all like [\h__\h] he's crazy
commander might i suggest we return to
the matter at hand
with left wings and quite a stage up at
the temple
that's the stuff mr professor you'd
rather face what's in front of us and
dwell in the past
just would i expect from a real
scientist
artist no no no no no no before you
waste your time on drawing dad better
draw me
okay maybe maybe me and kamado's uniform
rather than him in my uniform
no we don't need that we don't need
kamado in my uniform no
don't waste your time with that
no please not
outfit swapped
hi smokey
hi
who's it tired baby
welcome baby
oh i would love to see me in irida's
outfit if someone would draw that i
could use that as a final thumbnail for
the next pokemon stream because this
does not seem to be the final one
it's moving
you're welcome to sit on this chair
this one
no
think you can think about it
a dependable attitude indeed yes let us
move on no need to speak any further
about my rash actors not to mention my
loss of composure
because i don't want to talk anymore
because my throat hurts
it seems like having a
little good influence
it's only natural piano is strong enough
to defeat even this new opponent
single-handedly
yeah whoa whoa slow down did you forget
that the red scene broke
i'll be all right armed with the
knowledge mighty of halkia imparted to
me
palpia the pokemon talk to you
yes it told me its name but that's not
all it also told me this
the stone of creation's beginning
a chain of red
the vessel of humankind's invention
unite he's free and
wait can you repeat this [\h__\h]
and call the chaos now disturbing the
flow of time
[Music]
one more time please
it's a tree man
it's trying to get our intentions like
hey hey hey listen hey listen
and then mighty punky must go with us
back to the temple it said
well that chain of red is in pieces no
but if little bits will do one gap with
those thank you hallelujah someone was
doing something smart
in the background
on the verso of humankind's one shot i
dare say that might refer to pokeball
in very fancy words
it's got to be but what about the stone
of creation's beginning let me let me
think let me think
my phone i don't know no
what could it be
stone
stone of creations beginning
um
leon might have some oh am i not
supposed to know like immediately
hmm i will not get it okay the other one
was kind of easy the vessel
he's knowledgeable about stones and
minerals he even goes digging for ore
sometimes
i'm not supposed to okay i felt stupid a
little bit just now
i thought so the word only and will be a
fine resource to consult
what are your thoughts professor
lavinton do you have any idea what the
stone could be
[Music]
oh upon my work her apps i don't
y'all want my girl could you let me
those flights you received yeah i was
thinking like what the hell to do with
those the ones that rollers that have
messages and grape
yes yes
i look so cute i look so cute
[Music]
a heart just as i remember it here in
the back on the earth plate it says when
the universe was created its shorts
became this plate i think this might be
a hint to what we need
how do you mean
wouldn't you say
we must search for stone or rather or i
suppose that shares the same material
properties as he's placed in fact i
believe that young liam might know just
where to find such a thing as he said
he'd been investigating it out of all of
ujj
now then you mention it that vola roll
of fellows come around the diamond
settlement asking about those plates
before too
this seems like a lead we're following
exercise again let's begin our search
for the stone of the creations beginning
although the name is rather mouthful in
your sight i propose we'll call it
original
yes
we don't maybe ask for your contact once
more
of course i'm calling to the summit camp
once more at once oh he'll come here
thank god i thought i had to search him
okay oh mary
a white hat as long as anyone could
reasonably expect but my invitation just
never came
so i decided to honor you all with an
unsolicited visit to be glad and rejoice
hooray rejoice can't be rejoiced
now adam and i see all these other nouns
have their little task be getting on
them but what are the great melody
what's my role in all days
i mean later melee show shred of respect
would you
fine whatever just hurry up and give me
a job great leader adamant and make it a
good one
i want a job your job to support the
others
all the other warriors are busy looking
after the nobles and keeping the people
of our clans from panicking take a hit
oh
[\h__\h] fight but with boys
oh other men oh oh oh you silly silly
foolish boy don't you understand
anything everyone has work they are
suited to and work they are not
you know
i could do her nails like look at those
they're so
ripped disgusting ew
before i forget it seems you weren't
italian uses after all galaxy team grunt
well done
gorgeous think this is a reward for your
adorable effort
this is my way of encouraging the little
people and you are so little
this little [\h__\h]
[Music]
is
i wonder how they
how his dialogue is in in japanese
i brought leon
there he is
yeesh then ugly hat since it's as poorly
as this important rule does i don't like
this at all i should be the one
consulted for my wisdom
he saw his orange and stones like a
precious resource since i was the first
to realize that fact it's only natural
that i should be the first consultant
if you have a problem with it perhaps
you like to take it up with cleaver and
battle with that bumbling ball of you
[Music]
excuse me yeah that bumbling ball is
more than capable of zapping both you
and an ugly bug of yours all the way
back to your stupidly oversized tree
shall we prove it to you right now
oh my god
that is so not fetch
[Laughter]
wow give it a rest and play nights with
the pearl clan folks for once with your
bigger friends or stay careful steak
but other man
everyone back home is all went up
because the pro clan got to speak to
almighty say no
or whatever do you want them to hog all
the glowing
wire then leon if you would
ignore
he's got a small baby pickaxe on his
back so cute
by the way speaking of pickaxes i
watched good uh playing minecraft vr a
little bit yesterday i want to try that
too i wanted to do
something with vr i was actually
thinking
of um playing
um
more vr games first of all
or more like any at all
and the other thing was
yo minecraft vr is like hardcore
minecraft in in another way the other
thing was is i wanted to
um
do a stream where
i
do like two
push-ups or so for every swear word i
say
and it would work really good if it's a
vr
because then you can actually see me do
the push-ups
what do you think
and we could combine that that would be
[\h__\h] exhausting minecraft vr
already so frustrating to figure out
everything and and move to anywhere
wait using elytra in minecraft vr oh oh
is it
oh my god
how would that
how would that work [\h__\h] that that
sounds like something
you would get
really sick at all i wanted to when i
was watching good at playing i was
thinking
i wanna
um there's this there's this roller
coaster on the japanese server i want to
try that with vr minecraft i want to go
there
and and then ride that roller coaster
but already you guys know i don't like
roller coasters so
there is there's this one roller coaster
it's not it's not that
crazy it's more i think it's more meant
to be um
mean
like for transportation i'm not sure
the hats are not really cool yeah i
think that's the one i mean
not the pickle coaster i don't know
there was one that i used before
what where
what
we can try all of them
[Music]
i love how come out and made you scared
on the roller coaster in the music video
yeah but it's still not quite accurate
because i had my eyes open in the music
video i usually would close my eyes
and then
really like
like i would my body would turn into
like the fetus pose i would really like
crumble
together i would turn into like like a
snail you know what i mean
i would look down
and um like almost sink
through the for the chair for the seat
and just not look i would try to just
not exist
like for and in the beginning of the
roller coaster i usually i'm i have my
eyes open and i'm like
you know checking out what's going on
but then there's always a certain point
where i'm like nope nope nope i'm out of
here and then i yeah become become baby
and try to
act as if i am
i'm not there
[Laughter]
are you silent at first i scream so loud
and so so
desperately that i lose my voice
and and like the ability to scream at
all
and then i just i just roll up into
fetus
and close my eyes and suffer in silence
it is um
quite the experience to be on a roller
coaster next to me because i i go from
suddenly
dead silent until the end of the roller
coaster
yeah
it's like oh wha what happened you
stopped screaming you're enjoying it now
nope she's not enjoying it
but i still it's not like i'm so
so
scared of it that i won't go on roller
coasters i i like to give it a try
and
some of them
some of them are okay
the baby ones are okay by
my taller tolerability
my level of tolerance
is pretty low
[Laughter]
when it comes to roller coasters
and if i if i'm with someone um i mean i
would never go alone to
a roller coaster but i would usually ask
um you know does this one have a loop
and if it has a loop
i'm usually not going on it
i
i cannot
knowingly go on a roller coaster
knowing that
i will at some point
do a 360.
that is a big note for me
[Music]
i've experienced it before though
because i didn't know that it would have
a loop
in in one um
one
roller coaster in disneyland
had one loop
and okay i got through it just fine
but i i don't knowingly want to go back
not even on the same one even though
even though i survived it before i
wouldn't want to go back
it wasn't even that bad but
i just don't want to go through it again
anyway back to the story certainly
[Music]
yeah never been on the road because it
has a loop
oh have you ever been to disneyland no
i tell you gravity will hold you in i
don't believe it yo golden umi you and
me tin foil hat let's go
love roller coasters i get scared before
getting on them but love it while riding
them
for me it's the other way around i'm
excited to get on them
pretty much but then once i sit in them
i'm like why why am i here why am i here
why am i here why am i here
why
the letter set out at once will make for
the prem prime evil primeval gretel
okay head to the place where you can
obtain origin ore
uh-huh
[Applause]
[Music]
you know what that looks like that
actually looks like um
[\h__\h] who's following me
it looks like from toy story oh it is
you
oh
i wanted to try catch it wait a second
doesn't that look like one of those and
one of the ones yeah mr potato head yeah
yeah that's what it looks like to me
that was kind of funny pokemon
funny
this is funny
why didn't it look funny to you
[Applause]
[Music]
don't lose your nose buddy
73 wait can i even i think i can catch
73 pokemon
but maybe we should attack first sounds
like fun let's do it
i stole some damage okay i gotta show
your face is this my face what do you
mean
what do you mean
robo pass
wait is the offensive stats got a
defense offense right yeah yeah
the defense good
damn oh okay but oh we might have killed
oh critical it might have killed by
accident if i didn't do that
why is this pokemon look so funny that
mustache
this makes it look like a joke
catching
i know i can capture them without
fighting i've done that many times
but i thought this way it might be a bit
easier
[Music]
woman is no longer pumped up oh
no no pumpy pumpkins
[Music]
we'll catch him
we'll get great balls
well i do have a lot
come on you better singing
please
okay
[Music]
good job good job
i got a big big nose face
[Music]
wake up from your slumber
your special attack
how much does that really influence like
how much stronger does that really make
me like percentage-wise i would like to
know that
who wants this
go fetch
thank you
you want this you want it okay
you can has
you can also have oh [\h__\h]
you guys also do this
by accident
that is a lot
damn
okay
um
oh and revive
would be a good idea
[Music]
what is this
shiny or
what a curious cave i feel some
extraordinary power here as if the world
itself was created in this very place
what do you think leon
he's got little ribbons on the backside
of his booties
taking into consideration my knowledge
of words my skilled minding and the
strength of my sligo's moves
[Music]
you think you'd better leave any
extraction work up to us wouldn't you
stay
do what you want the ones you need to do
homemade physical otaku
are you saying that was bad that i did
it or that was good that i didn't
because i did it by accident though
we're going to have to ask you to stop
right there cool
haven't seen you guys in a while
what's your problem now did you guys see
this guy you realize that we're trying
to fix that do you guys just want to die
or what
oh come on who's there we don't have any
time to waste with
you know huh
clover we haven't seen you since you
walked out on the clan where have you
been all this time
oh
ex-lovers
i don't have to tell you nothing
look you can carry on digging out that
treasure you're after and then you'll
give it to us
i don't know why you even look surprised
it's not as if you were hard to follow
well we think maybe as precious as the
treasure but this isn't about how
valuable it is we needed to restore this
awful sky to normal
that ernest goody two shows act of yours
is what made me leave the pearl oh she's
originally from the pearl clan
enough i don't care why any of you ran
off to play bandit but i won't let you
get in leon's way there are three of you
in three of us let's go kia will you
take charm
finally fairness
unbelievable
i bring good luck to my sisters wherever
i go and in luck to anyone who crosses
our paths i'm the eldest and i'll be
your unlucky charm especially in this
the battle of a lifetime
let's see how many pokemon she brings in
well i guess you don't need more than
two when usually
you always go free against one
and everybody has two pokemon
then in total you have a full team
which is totally fair too right sending
all out
out on your pokemon
all at once three people versus one
trainer
sounds fair to me
super effective but he's still alive
guys how much longer question not
because i'm sick of it but just because
i
feel um
kind of
[Music]
low on
health
you guys know not much longer quite a
bit maybe another hour
30 minutes okay
guys
such a beautiful smile
um i'm gonna have you kill me if it must
be
but i'm not gonna leave the
battlegrounds now
[Music]
is
i might not be so
fully energetic anymore
uh yes no i will probably not read super
chat after all
tomorrow is monopoly right
i gotta
figure out
test out everything make sure it works
too
um
for no pulling
will be on my channel
hope everything goes well from a
notebook gotta make the thumbnail
as well
but
it's gonna be fine monopoly is pretty
late oh but wow i actually have a
recording tomorrow before
before monopoly i think um
looking forward to it yes it will be
good
it will be fun
yeah this isn't even that long yet but
um yeah i'm not doing so well today
kind of my my stamina is already used up
for some reason
come on clover why not come back to the
diamond clan you want her back now oh
are you in love
times are changing we're changing and we
could really use someone as strong as
you are
are you jumping i've got no interest in
living back in that place with all its
stupid rules
look we'll let you keep your treasure
this time but you'd better do something
about that scott that's all we're trying
to do these [\h__\h] idiots
[Music]
you're as strong as ever kiama maybe you
really can do something about that
monstrous creature at the top of the
mountain but even if you do the next
time we meet you won't escape without a
beating remember that
yeah me to beat my butt
oh no she's gonna beat my butt
honestly those three what did they even
call me for exactly exactly
i'll hear everyone's pokemon thank you
[Music]
the coin that i remember never hesitated
to help someone in need even if she
growled as she did so i suspect they may
have been worried about us perhaps even
wanting to help oh
oh you sure
you sure then they should have just said
so what a pain they are hiding behind
all that attitude
sunday man
what a cutie is that the pokemon before
the one i caught today the gooey one
i was able to extract some of that
origin oil or whatever it is you want to
call it i suppose it had better go with
yuki however
it's so cute
oh
hawaii
come on
roomba slug
oh looks fancy
an aura of mysterious powers spoken of
in ancient myths and said to contain the
power of almighty sinnoh itself
oh surprisingly
oh
boom
no you simply fail to recognize my skill
you have to be praising my hard work
honestly
i know i could count on you mian no
wonder cleaver recognizes you as a
worthy warden
tt
she knows how to handle him this small
silgaki
let's hurry back to mr professor and
show him what we got the leviton's got
some judgment plus no much to spare
despite his silly streak
she's so cute
[Music]
[Applause]
wait that image on the top left it's
like just his nose now it's not his nose
anymore
[Music]
it looked funny
can i investigate you know
is this a is that a pokemon that looks
like a house though
it's kind of like a pokemon like uh
bones of a pokemon fossil pokemon can
you like summon it later or
back theodon and rampardos you guys know
anything don't you
[Music]
all right here
back to the professor
[Music]
find them and just
ah maybe i already did and i forgot the
name
i don't know did i
and
it sounded like a while in case i'm not
healed i was too lazy to check
and
we'll see what we can craft
before
ah
oh
i can craft one star piece
and
and now you're supposed to sell the star
pieces for lots of money
that's i'm supposed to sell them right
there it is how
much five thousand
yes okay
very very good
this one
[Music]
okay
uh
yo
look at the fancy stuff i got and i eat
rest of cooking
now oh
wow
[Music]
everything might sound a bit exactly my
world
back to the live village
yeah
[Music]
hmm
the red tail
is fixed um even pieces i think we'll
find it's still pretty good on purpose
we're jolly lucky we had the foresight
to pick up all these broken bits back at
the temple
i think that was to be expected
you're up next camera time for whatever
we're calling that stone
the fragments of the red chain collected
at the great personal risk by the
diamond clan then the stone of creations
beginning which we all learned of thanks
to the pearl clan
and now it is time for the galaxy team
to play its part and turn these items
into proper vessel
right my boy
you're one of our team's greatest crafts
people could i ask you to do the honest
i stole it right
and finally see what i'm truly capable
of
if only that was about you being a good
pokemon trainer but what is it about you
assembling a chain
yeah maybe your destiny does not lie in
becoming a pokemon trainer maybe you
finally realize okay
assembling a [\h__\h] chain
is that supposed to impress me
[Music]
come on mr professor i wish that hurried
up and uh
i'm starting to suspect all your
prattling about the value of time is a
cover for your own impatience
guys
the word
time and cover
in one
sentence
don't you think that this is hinting at
croning
[Music]
i think it is i think it is
and then there was also the word suspect
which means
that crony will be
performing suspect as a surprise guest
in a whole live furred fest just kidding
this is a joke this is a joke this is a
joke
[Music]
suspect is a song by the way from her
life an original song
[Music]
my tinfoil hat is becoming bigger and
bigger
crony is dialga no
no no
[Music]
diagonal is gonna twerk
[Laughter]
[Music]
you're making a
pokeball
and the message converted to our good
clown leader canberra believed and that
should allow you to catch the pokemon
that has appeared at the temple of ceno
ah so we get both legendaries
oh
and yet
my fingers are sinking into
it not even holding it properly it looks
cool though
a singular and irreplicable pokeball
that can be used to catch the frantic
pokemon raging at the temple of sinnoh
all right
all the way let me think wouldn't we be
able to make more out of those
[Music]
we used
we used the ore
we can get more of that there was still
some there
no can we not make more
can we really not make more
don't we have the means for it
no more chain can we not ask the little
three cool pokemon for some more chain
or maybe we can go up to the mountain
because he didn't he said he didn't pick
up every piece so there might still be
more pieces
we just gotta look closely
maybe with a metal detector
they're
logically thinking there should be more
pieces up there
if someone distracts the
uh diagonal
then someone else can pick up more and
we can make them never masturbal
what for i don't know but you know just
trying to
not be part of your system
i'm gonna take that pokeball the master
ball and i'm gonna throw it on the
ground
i'm not part of your system
faster ball one time only
[\h__\h] now
man
[Music]
okay anyway
to think the fate of ali so you could
rest in something so tiny
is your dressing room catching a pokemon
and one of those one of these things
brings the two of you close together
what what please i hear something that
voice is speaking in my mind again oh my
god
again
you mean pogba
yes it appears that mighty pokey is
willing to lend its own strength to us
in this battle
now that's what i like to hear
the pyro clan's almighty signal well i
guess i should just call it palkia it's
one fierce pokemon
so should i put it in my team
um
i don't think we
need
uh
i have to okay
everything's right now okay one take the
origin bowl and hurry back to the temple
of cinna together with pogba
i need to okay
ah
okay
who do we kick out
um um for a parking in front of you or
will she kneel will she kneel is that
how we get her to kneel
oh yeah oh yeah
what do i see there i can't talk to you
now i need to go to these places
[Music]
we shall put this one in two maybe
soto ark
there it is pacquiao
water ah makes sense that we put this
one because it's very much like canada's
okay
palkia has earth power aqua tail hydro
pump spatial rend
should we just keep all those
and then maybe
but if i
if i put in zoroark looking at the skill
set it would mean that i have to get rid
of so fetch
who also has fire skills though
i don't really want to switch that right
now
don't feel ready for that commitment
oh but gutra steel dragon oh but now we
have palkio who is also dragon
damn
oh well i was also
i also have to show that burme to
someone
um so anyway
we have panchayat with us
check its moves
how chaos moves
change the moves
which one should i change
oh power gem oh rock move yeah we don't
need to
we don't need two water moves
all right here's ancient power too sixty
hundred
eighty hundred so i would say power gem
i drew for power jam
oh yeah that's really uh low accuracy
okay agreed
okay
beautiful
paul kia
um i wanna
do the
um
the burmese quest quickly wanna give it
back
i think they were somewhere over here
these peeps they wanted to see one more
burmese
um which one this one
[Music]
there you go the last one
hydro pump is better than alcohol too
[Music]
did i do something not so smart
take hydro pump over aqua too
okay
really
blah blah
ah complete i don't know do i have a
completed pokedex entry
[Music]
do i
think i do
live
ah it's fine there's worse quests like
the one where you have to keep on going
to that ramados island
and there's never a moving tree
never
oh he has the new quest what do you want
maybe it's something i have
done
never never you well
oh he's mad
what did you do to make him mad what do
i have to give him this time to make him
happy
sand radishes
ah um oh
i think i have them
i'm gonna have some
i don't exactly have friends
[Music]
we'll do this quickly then as well
sorry i'm already low energy
oh but by the way you guys want to hear
something exciting only kfp
must have this knowledge only for kfp
[Music]
i've been talking about working on an
original song right
yeah
um
i got the
uh
the instrumental is now finally finished
and i got them though
we got a guide melody for the vocals now
so next step is writing the lyrics
i'm gonna ask someone
uh
for english lyrics so don't worry it
will be an english song
um
it won't be kelly it won't be cali
but someone very talented so
[Music]
yeah
yes
normally when i create songs i do most
of it behind the scenes and you guys
only know
about it
um
when it's out but this time i've been
working on it for
so long that i guess
i don't mind sharing some stuff with you
guys
um
yeah
my second my second english song it will
be
i said that i wanted to be in 3d
the music video
but
i'm actually not so sure anymore
if i should do it in 3d
um because i'm thinking
i'm thinking if i do it in 3d
uh
then
i think it will have to be in my
in my default outfit and i think that
default outfit doesn't
fit the song
so
i'm thinking now maybe not
not worth it maybe wait to use that on
something more
fitting
hmm original song yay
new outfit for the song i don't even
know like if that is even a thing
[Music]
that's possible because i feel like if
it's possible then why
don't all of the whole alive all the
other live girls get themselves
new outfits
so quickly for music videos and any time
like
for whatever
whenever they feel like it i mean
sometimes they have new 3d outfits for
solo concerts
but
because it's expensive yeah probably but
i honestly i haven't really looked into
that
yet so i don't really know if it's even
in in the realm of possibility
um
yeah i'll have to investigate further
but
i don't know
i think it's fine even if it's not a 3d
music video i'll think about it i don't
think about it that way i could probably
at least
put it out
earlier
although i'm not sure i'm not sure
i'm not sure
well well well
i still have some time
since i didn't even i don't even have
the lyrics yet so there's still some
time to think about it
i'll trust your judgment thank you thank
you
this guy looks like a radish
now do we get more stuff in your shop
again
um
i can't believe there's so many issues
with you
are they finally ending their
eternal fight oh no
oh he's running away never mind
second guessed it or not quite
you don't even have to get along
personally it's just business man give
him the wares y'all you'll probably
profit from it too
new wares yet and then
they have vodka huh
what's new
is this new
not sure what's new
[Music]
wait what
i think i've misused this um
this item before
in the previous pokemon play through
how was this one used again ultra balls
on you
is that still
not a horde
is this a
is this a revive
i thought it was a revive but then it
isn't or something like that
i didn't misuse this one did i miss you
as a diff something else
because everyone was like face palming i
remember that i think it was during the
cynthia fight i missed you something and
everyone was like
i just
slapped my forehead
i got confused exactly by that i'm still
confused by it
i know this is a full revive i know that
we we need a lot of those
for
the eventual not symphyia fight
i'll buy some more
wait why did i buy so many when i can
just make them myself
damn it whatever
i don't have so many ingredients anyway
i think
[Music]
okay quick let's finish the story let's
go
let's go let's go oh kyle carrot i have
a video from you in my tab trying to
remind me to watch an ami video also i
watched that other video that you made
and the new one the new kiwa video that
was really funny
that was funny
i liked it
very very good yeah approved kiwawa
approved
um
[Music]
i'm eating self-made cookies
i i made a stream on baking them you
should watch the archive um
[Music]
stop
i want to try the cookies the recipe is
public selling welcome to try it
yourself
[Music]
and here you are last one ready to face
your fate a top mount coordinator that's
all it's going to be [\h__\h] easy
i don't even have to do any damage i'll
just throw them wait
the the ball cannot fail right
so
i guess
so what's what's the big deal
what is the big deal
no
here ken
hurton
he arkin
to my words young ones
time cannot be severed from space nor
space from time
naruhodo
[Music]
the being you will encounter at the
temple of sinnoh is the alga ruler of
all time
if it is allowed to run wild time itself
will twist and bend here in history and
eventually the very world may be broken
but you have the aid of its counterpart
palacio the rule of space and therein
lies hope
balance will be brought to time and
space
and the world can once again be as it
should
now take palkia at your side and make
for the temple of sinhal once more
excuse me it's time for shopping oh i
feel you girl once you're in here you
got to go shopping to have some good
clothes in that shop and some good
hairstyles but i like your hairstyle and
your current hairstyle and your current
clothes so
i don't think you really need it
well i'll hardly have time for shopping
if the world ends will i
young man
[Music]
i have no energy left
no it's not ymca on my channel lids
[Music]
[Applause]
uh
[Music]
[Laughter]
that's where i was supposed to go okay
jessica
we're not gonna fight now aren't we no
no no no no no no you guys said it would
be after
and then we're not gonna fight now we're
not gonna fight now
i know you can buy very sundries at the
base camp but i thought it might be
helpful to you if i set up here closely
okay thank
i want to have front row seats if
there's a chance to see into the world
of myth legend
and you also want to have front proceeds
when the world ends right i feel like
it's pretty pretty good to see that up
close
i'll probably be creeping even closer to
the action once the battle actually
begins oh oh oh oh he's a sucker for
action
you won't have to worry about me i'm
perfectly capable of taking care of
myself
oh yeah
it will be the big reveal later on that
would have been bootlegged me if it
wasn't for the chat that he actually
ends up being a [\h__\h] strong fighter
and gonna
almost kill me probably
besides i know all too well the strength
of you and your pokemon i've got no
doubt you'll have this whole thing tied
up in a neat bow before i could possibly
be in any danger
okay bye-bye
which pokemons would like for a win it
doesn't matter because we're not even
gonna fight
um
[Music]
am i confusing things and i'm gonna the
difficult battle is with that
white-haired lady
anyway doesn't matter for so long i
thought that i had to eliminate any
outside element that might threaten the
people of gibraltar village whether that
meant banishing you or seeking to
destroy the pokemon of the temple i felt
it was my only path but you've shown me
that i was wrong to think in such a way
are you ready for this challenge recruit
you know this vast space your place has
found you
what in the world does that mean
thank you
it's a
program saying
it reminds us that occasions we must
rise to our also stages where we may
prove ourselves where we might shine our
brightest
well basically you're saying not to feel
nervous
in some situations anyone
i can't move my mouth anymore
we'll support you in whatever we wear
yeah i will protect his who and her
people
he's female protect diamond space for
pokemon
let's go thank you
i'm good i'm just a bit exhausted
i'm good though thank you
it's just these games i have to read so
much
wow
wrong ball wrong ball girl bro check it
out
[Music]
what
um
i don't get the logic here i mean okay
palkia protected me now but why did we
not just throw the
basketball immediately
okay for a cool cutscene maybe for the
sake of a cool cutscene
oh
wow
it is a cool cutscene
yeah yeah that was a good screenshot
here
i know i know a little moment
wait
oh no
[Music]
i like the music
that came out of nowhere i did not
expect this to happen
look at time to
like broke my [\h__\h]
okay
i mean i'm already pretty low health but
still very manageable
if i just
learn
the patterns
[Music]
poker battle
[Laughter]
let me do it again
from the beginning
okay okay i'm gonna get like this i
check out that
it's the pattern on it i need to get to
know the parents
it caught me and by surprise the whole
battle
but
yeah it makes sense because we've been
doing this all along
[Music]
i thought that
did dodge
[Music]
nice ribbon that we got going here
oh [\h__\h] i didn't see that
pokemon trainer return to monkey
i'm doing so good
[Music]
i shouldn't have run that way
my my fault
[Music]
not the first time that we see that [\h__\h]
what [\h__\h] what's happening oh god the a
dodger in the right
[Music]
oh you little [\h__\h]
well that's hard to figure out you're
kidding me
[Music]
oh that's like the arcanine one where
when he's loading up i have to throw oh
i just don't get that hint
on my own
okay this is fun let's do it again
[Music]
okay
let's go
no damage ran i'll show you
[Music]
no damage
a marathon
[Music]
well i just focus on escaping them
during these moments
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
anyway
[Music]
i'm not sure how strong this is
here's a target along with
the space around it
oh that that sounds like a really cool
attack but um
[Music]
maybe another time where it's super
effective on an enemy not just them
okay strong distance
[Music]
he won his
ah
it's pretty bad it's pretty bad it's
pretty bad
but it's our turn
uh
it's our turn
put attack twice once
if that doesn't do the trick anyone
oh no those attacking ones normally
would have worked too
[Music]
[Laughter]
what are you doing don't die on me
[Music]
um
okay
nice yeah
okay but back to the bathroom
[Music]
do it again do it again do it oh
pretty dangerous and my nose is hitting
my nose and my nose is hitchy
what are you doing what are you doing
[Music]
oh
from the beginning again or do we get
one one checkpoint
one checkpoint yeah the meteor came way
too fast i thought so too
yeah that's maybe second phase meteor
second phase meteor
one one checkpoint one one if i lose
again i'll do from the beginning
uh
yes
please
[Music]
he's like i don't know warning me or
something and
uh
yeah okay
dodged it but it's kind of we should
different than before
um
[Music]
oh
what's next
[Music]
sweaty spaghetti hands right now
oh
[Music]
make it so that i can focus on that
that's dude
do two things at once
okay so how do we do this because like
um i can't one hit him
[Music]
so he will kill me next turn
right this doesn't help
i just fell doesn't know
same
why are you guys saying this one just
because you want to see it but
in theory it can't be stronger
because it's just effective but it has
power 90 which is just just 10 more
but it's cool though that's why you
wanted to cool friction ah
hydrogen chance of water
okay we can give it a drawing see how
much it does
critical please yeah
[Music]
why did i trust you
back
[Music]
history repeats itself
okay just wait this way just fine i just
have to keep on reviving healthier
i guess one more time
wait wait that might not be enough
[Music]
i killed it
[Applause]
[Music]
ah true oh it was a stab move oh i
didn't realize that go go go
whoa
ah
one more millisecond later would've been
cool that's the right ball kiwama that's
it not not the great ball not the ultra
bone this is the one
[Applause]
little little fireworks
[Music]
she did a cute face she smiled with her
teeth i don't think i ever saw her teeth
before
oh this guy is right to normal
yay
[Music]
oh
she
she caught it
she really did it didn't she
my eyes aren't lying right she actually
went and called it
wait you guys realize we made that
special ball right
yeah good show little catch you
contained that through something in the
origin wall
absolutely astounding is that what he
won't work
finally
just what i'd expect of my privacy your
priority
yes
[Music]
so even the commander sheds a tear now
and then there before that see that day
yes what a sight to have witness
[Music]
angry
angry kamado noises
ouch well gives commander not sure i
deserved a sumo from
at least it seems this is no dream
huh
there's enough all of you
[Music]
we've faced a calamity unlike any we
have known but we were able to cover it
by overcoming by working as one this
calls for a celebration a festival for
us all
grammar euclides this will be the
greatest celebration history has ever
seen they go weak on them on the
mute soundtrack but they go strong on
the sound effects
and with weak i mean they
generally have quiet moments mostly not
that the soundtrack itself is weak but
just that it's mostly quiet
celebrate with the diamond clan
the two clans together huh
[Music]
well since it turns out we were both
following a true almighty sinnoh of our
own i guess the times when we'd fight
over whose was wrong or write our
ancient history now
i'm sure our ancestors would be shocked
to see us agree
but this may well be the best path
toward protecting the space we all
let us celebrate with the day dawn's a
new day for all those who live in the
eastern region
wait kamado wasn't evil after
i was like so sure that he was evil
oh that's it that's that's maybe it is
that or we see a party
there it is pokemon legends i see us iqs
[Music]
i know i know
the next everything that comes after
that will be in another episode i think
that that's where we wanted to get to
today
the
fake story finale
ah
okay so i guess i'll not share my
thoughts my ending thoughts yet because
this is not the end
this is the final and the next one will
be the fine final
the fine final
that was
a good good exciting end
not a real ant burn
once again another challenging lord
fight
and pretty
out of nowhere for me personally i
didn't expect it so that was
good i guess
but yeah so far you guys know i really
like the game
so much that i play it off screen quite
a lot
uh
that is
not something i usually find time for
but for this one i sacrificed some
netflix time
the music is cute right now
[Music]
cute cute
like do you think the what what is left
over will fit in one part
i need to know to plan
uh the future
yeah
well i guess i need to prepare by
catching
some pokemon off screen i guess
there's a lot of pro skins don't think
so
it's gonna take three hours
to catch all pokemon no no
if i do that off screen then we will be
well prepared i suppose
but do i even have access to all pokemon
now
[Music]
all that there is left
okay
okay okay okay okay well
we might know how many hours left did
that like was that written somewhere
maybe on the first page
how many i have left
how will i know what what i'm looking
for still if i have trouble
finding like two more pokemon how will i
know what i'm looking for
how do you guys know what you're looking
for
i can't just trade you everything you
don't have if i really have y'all buy
problems finding one specific pokemon
then maybe but it shouldn't be that
difficult it is
the pokedex has a filter ah it spoils me
on what's still left oh
[Music]
thank you for adventuring of us oh
oh it's a party
wait i want to look at it longer than i
took a screenshot
and our girl was savvy was flying at the
top uh in the sky cute
my iphone is beeping
oh is it gonna tell me that i need to
fill up my [\h__\h] pokedex that it's not
over yet
bamboozle
wait it didn't look
well
there are jokes on you switch i'm a
streamer i can take a screenshot from my
stream and i can go to the archive and
just look at it and press pause and then
look at it from then
did they do that because they don't want
that picture to be
like online on social media
in order to not spoil people
maybe
but that's that picture itself is
much less of a spoiler i think than
all the screenshots i took
before
that oh
hmm weird
good morning once again
prepare weld and make for the temple of
cinna once more should i do that on
stream i'm not sure
[Music]
is that
is that where they just tell me to
finish my pokedex
not sure where to end
i should
[Music]
leave that for nicer but can i do
everything else
[Music]
without continuing that main part main
story
end here by the phone okay i'll kill you
again
morning kiawah
you came out of your room so i'm going
to talk to you now for the space time
rift is gone you think this is the end
of the
playthrough
no
sorry kia i know you named this episode
the finale but it is not
but wait there's more
in any case there's one book we can't
close yet the pokedex
that was your original mission so we
gotta finish that
and to get back to our official survey
corps duty of completing it
we're going to meet in the survey corps
office to discuss how we'll tackle the
work that's left
see you there chiama
[Music]
man
uh the grind never ends guys
i don't even get a vacation i'm like a
japanese homo life streamer
i want to go to the beach
i want to go swimming
[Music]
okay
okay so i'll go to the beach to catch
pokemon
yeah well well well
okay
um probably next episode next week
and uh
super chatos
uh
i think let me let me check my
schedule
so tomorrow is more no polly
can't read after that holo talk can't
really read after that then we have
members only and oh
[\h__\h]
and then unlike have kyogre looks like
i'll be doing a super chat reading
stream
after all of that
because
it will pile up
anyway
what time is the members only oh i
currently have it planned uh
sorry i just wasn't able to fit the time
on the schedule
but i have it at 8pm
gmt plus one
[Music]
there's still a chance that it might
slightly change by one or two hours
not two hours maybe one hour earlier one
hour later
but it should be around that time
[Music]
yeah sorry guys uh
i think it it's already late too i
should get dinner
i think it's probably better if i don't
read it now even if it stacks up a
little bit
unfortunate but
um
i think i think it's better
[Music]
yeah probably on sunday
after the undercut cutter okay
or
on monday or so
yeah
food very stupid chat later
yeah also i have to
oh no wait
wait what wait a second and i'm getting
i'm confused
ah never mind no it's not the recording
that i have tomorrow that was next week
i forgot but you know what i'm gonna
call um
i made an appointment with dana so that
we would um
find time to discuss
our plans so we're gonna be doing that
tomorrow i just looked at my schedule i
mixed something up i me and arena
scheduled a phone call
so that we don't miss each other and
it's better to do it via voice call and
not
text message everything
oh she talked about it
oh yeah and since we're talking about
reyna
i finally managed to get everyone
all the holoburps to agree to a time it
was very difficult we kept on having to
say okay i guess next week how about
this date next week and then i don't
know yet
okay well that that week is already too
late so how about this week this day
this week
yeah um unfortunately
since
we have
[Music]
all kinds of time zones in horotoni
mummy will be suffering
it's gonna be a really shitty time for
her but she said she'll she'll wake up
for it um
she's happy to wake up for it thank you
mommy
my girl
good girl really good girl
she seemed fine with it but i feel like
she might not stream it because
it seems kind of difficult in her
situation um
yeah yeah yeah yeah so um that will
happen
next week finally the first full
hoteli
er kona bowl
but it will be on all channels because
it's a game that will play on all
channels
except maybe for mummy you know
[Music]
finally
finally finally finally
i always wanted to just get everyone
together
um and now finally it will work
out yeah yeah
i'm always working on something in the
background to put something together
[Music]
yeah i'll be making
everyone's
thumbnails too
i um
my passion is graphic design after all
[Music]
you mean grown up
crony is not a holo verb just as a joke
a little bit maybe but
no she really doesn't even play around
with that hollow bird persona like like
subato does subato is also not really
improved but subaru has
accepted and really
made something out of that
duck persona
yeah
and no crony not really if she suddenly
starts saying she's a crow
cruel crowd then we can talk about it
but
no also we're already too many anyway
it's a pain in the ass getting everyone
together
like this already i would prefer if we
would just stay a small group this is
not small anymore anyway
crony is the helicopter yeah not
everything that flies is a bird guys a
helicopter i know it looks like a bird
to other birds like a very mechanical
bird but guys it's not a bird it's it's
a helicopter
it does not be the same thing as a bird
no no no no no no
it goes blah but those are not wings no
and those uh
feet are not the same feet that you have
no no
no helicopters are not birds no
i know they fly but
planes are also not birds no
no no
there's a lot of things that fly but
they don't they they are not birds
[Music]
what
what [\h__\h] what
i know chickens i know it can be
confusing when you see something in the
sky i know you think it's oh big
dangerous bird made out of metal oh
no
it's okay i'm here to teach you that
yeah well
anyway
and tomorrow monopoly on my channel with
a gouda and uh fauna and inna
so i'll see you guys there thank you for
watching today had fun playing pokemon
again we'll we'll try to catch as many
as possible off screen
maybe
if i don't have enough time then
next pokemon stream might be in two
weeks time if i need more time to do the
catching
but it will be soon nonetheless the
follow-up
[Music]
inna makeup
i
i watched
uh her comment about playing harder for
boyfriend
in order to understand burps better and
then maybe um make up with me
in the monopoly stream
see i already know her plans so
i might give her a hard time or maybe
not because uh i want someone to be
titty with while gouda and fauna are
probably gonna be titty although
monopoly
monopoly does not really leave much
opportunity for tt does it if you if you
play it correctly
by the way i checked steam
and it has really really
bad ratings
it makes me worry but i watched i
watched
a video of the gameplay and it seems
fine why does monopoly have so
such bad ratings on steam monopoly plus
by the way specifically
maybe it's the salty people who lost
against their friends
[Music]
i thought it was fun it looked bad it
looked fine to me
[Music]
i hope the online connection is fine too
one question did anyone ever play
monopoly plus online
on steam
because
as far as i know parsec is not needed to
play it on steam online
but correct me if i'm wrong if anyone
knows
i think it should just be normally
possible
[Music]
i hope so too
oh yeah yeah
oh yeah if it was only with perception
but she played nintendo switch
it crashes quite frequently if on the
steam version
online version lags and crashes
oh
no please no
horrible things about online
maybe i should get
the switch version there after all
because to play online on the switch
monopoly
everyone just needs a
membership but i think everyone has that
in en anyway
gotta ask them if they didn't buy it
already
i hope the switch connection is better
but i
think aki senpai was using the switch
version to play with her viewers and
it seems fine otherwise she wouldn't do
it a hundred times over and over again
and they all played mario kart
[Music]
hello everyone
is there anyone
already bought the game
i hear the
connection
stability is pretty bad so
if you haven't
bought
it yet we might want to get the switch
version instant
nintendo membersh membership
subscription
necessary for
refund or you can refund it
never did that before in steam
antennas would be necessary for online
play
actually the funny works
on streaming to
mind one
[Music]
uh
i i
as far as i know whole life english
most of the girls
get the games necessary
[Music]
less than one day in advance
might be good
we might we might be good i might
haven't gotten it yet
[Music]
refund on steam very easy
well i didn't buy it yet i was gonna get
it
after this stream
[Music]
well then thank you guys for that uh
advice
uh i think we're gonna
play the switch once that then
which is
basically the same game just with
hopefully better collection
wait let's just realize
it's actually somebody's birthday right
and we're playing monopoly the game that
she loves so much
on her birthday
at least in our time zone it would still
be her birthday
i can't get on nice
[Music]
nice thank you
that's probably gonna be better
[Music]
happy birthday everybody wish augustana
play happy birthday
yeah
do it do it do it she i saw she was
doing doing a countdown stream
uh
but i don't know if she's still
streaming
okay okay i will i will go now then
thank everybody for watching
um
[Music]
i'm sorry that
i'm leaving already
uh
i uh
i
uh
oh yeah right it was kind of weird if
she would still be streaming that's like
it feels like one hour ago but
six six always six hours ago
[Music]
hashtag
already i don't know i feel like i
should be reading super chat to feel a
little bit bad about it because the next
streams i won't be able to do it either
but oh you know me i always i always
catch up you know me
i always catch up
[Music]
thank you guys for watching i love you
guys
and
and i missed you
i was kind of even thinking about doing
a gorilla stream a really weird one
probably better than it's good that i
didn't do it probably because i had this
weird idea
um
maybe i'll do it eventually after uh
but
i almost did a gorilla yesterday
so sorry
[Music]
i like you guys
i appreciate the time here you know
[Music]
oh thank you
thank you
for the pinky
[Music]
um
please release us from our ship oh you
want me to go
okay
[Music]
thank you guys
oh stream
ends ah that was a good
[Music]
new request okay i'm on my way
oh
[Music]
me
quack quack
[Music]
um
i thought it was burgers but it was bug
awards blues
where's my burger
[Music]
where's the burger harvest
oh
wait
okay
where's the food
hmm
[Music]
i'm never gonna finish this quest never
this one neither
i never did this one
[Music]
20 unreported tests
where is rebellion
[Music]
i wish there was a search function
okay
[Music]
anyway
41 hours
[Music]
how many pokemon
how many are there
um
[Music]
no
you mean
in
oh okay
242 okay okay whoo
[Music]
no yeah i'll go cuddle my cat now i
don't come with my cats i'm going come
on
oh i didn't realize i was still
streaming oopsie
bye
[Music]
thank you
thanks everybody for the support and
wish you a lovely day
yeah
have a lovely day
eat some good food
make some cookies make some cookies
good cookies
[Music]
wow
hey
[Music]