he
[Music]
w
hello
Hi I hi chat sorry wait I don't know if
I'm ready yet
ah uh
what's everybody else doing on their
stream are they
ready are they did they switch off their
thing that's ready okay
okay oh
wait playing a trailer
uh
[Music]
okay give our W
to so
started
okay
uh hello
all right I have my in-game Minecraft
muted because I'm not sure I'm supposed
to be playing it already hold on sorry
the bgm is so loud there we go how's
[Music]
that
test good stash is back you'll see
why it'll all make sense I think oh wait
um oh I hit my head oh my head hurts oh
my head hole is leaking liquid oh wait
um oh the
ow
hello where am
I who are you
people H am I
dead what
the I think I I think I'm I think I'm
dead is this are we in limbo
what's happening who are these
people why are there little bugs over
their
[Music]
head it's Heaven
oh wait hold on I'm I'm getting messages
in my brain oh oh God why am I thinking
out loud this is just like one of those
comic books this is just like one of
those shows I used to watch where where
they they got teleported to a new world
I got to get get out of
[Music]
here it's impossible I'm trapped I hope
people can't hear me they can't hear me
right you guys can't hear
me who are you they can't hear me yet
okay good wait
um do I unmute now I don't know if
everybody's ready I don't know what
they're doing I think I might I think
I'm feeling really hungry oh I woke up
in this in this room and I don't know my
name and I don't know these people but
I'm seeing messages in my head and my
brain and they won't stop they're
showing like little funny pictures now
they won't
[Music]
stop and I'm really hungry my tummy
hurts
uh anyways
wow this is a big room that we're in
maybe we're being lined up for like
Slaughter or
something I can't tell if we're dead can
somebody pinch
me yeah we should punch people to make
sure we're not dreaming
true I don't know it didn't do anything
it just like went right through
her wait I should maybe I should
introduce myself can I I I can't hear
anybody oh no my ears are not
working wow who's this beautiful
lady I'm all
[Music]
struck I know okay okay
um what time is it okay I think it's
okay to unmute
right WR these funny little messages
these funny little people in my
[Music]
head
um um wait what is the button
again who are you
people huh
hello hello where am I where are
we's oh you guys can
talk I mean yeah oh my God my
hands what happened to my hands they're
so blocky
where's why is it why is it so strange I
don't know why my body looks like this
it's so Square everybody's so cute you
are really am I square like that
too yeah everyone look squ oh my
God what happened I think I hit my head
what happened who are all of you hello
yeah I that's what I want to know I
think you who are you people
hello my head boy are you a boy your
head I hit I just hit my
head
C I'm very durable damage very durable
stand the corner oh there's a person in
the corner from
I wonder if you can H people here hey
hey you
what do you know
me no I don't think so wait hold on you
smell kind
of wait hold on my brain feels
foggy I don't have a button I can't
remember anything
D do you live on a pineapple
under hey what the
heck all right hold on hold
on hold then I'm trying to fix
oh my brain I lost
uh
um back hello I'm back in the hi
hello so
cute oh my God am IAD am we're back
hello I I guess we're back yeah we made
it jum was
hello hey don't fight with me sorry I
just wanted to touch you had something
back there I thought they had something
stuck on your back I attack okay she's
violent is this a battle
royale very Qui
remembering
things there's something
attack corner I sit here
and this
is the last 24 hours as well I don't
remember
wow yeah we a name tag that's CRA in the
middle of the woods you look like you
look fine I'm not
talking all I think I'll I'll stand over
here and watch
people hello yes you me before but could
I have my
corner quter oh
Corner okay you can have it
back why why would I do that
well don't attack me then step
[Music]
back losing it she's already losing it
we've only been here for a few minutes
I'm going to lose my
mind we got to find a way out of here
[Music]
Wasing
about so hry
wonder if I can take a
[Music]
bite my right ear I've seen you
somewhere before you don't what she's
going to leave
myner look at
you supposed to be a cute girl
right got to get out of here your color
I don't know there's a lot of
voices I see little funny messages in my
brain aot of
respons Trapped we're
traed maybe the walls will slowly start
closing in to make a very fast decision
and then we'll all be cuddled together
out we'll have to cuddle for
per she's already losing it she's
already lost
it I wonder what color will all bleed
when we're all swished against the
insides of these
walls enigmatic
recollection wait you know how to read
you know how to read I
do something tells me it's good to be
able to know how to
yeah I'm really
hungry
[Music]
me what does it
say
echo
of for
Goen mamory
wait I think I know how to
read press sneak the
no what is a sneak
key who am I the world oh wait maybe I
should turn my bgm off something epic I
need epic
bgm
shift oh there we go and more than
anything
uh the people I hold most
dear faced with
Oblivion I feel
empty
relieved relived
where are we I want to look around but I
can't perhaps
[Music]
this
uh I don't
know key ah oops
so much I don't know and yet you I've
never turned off sticky keys whatever uh
that is uh and
yet that bright light it calls to me
that the Moon is that the
moon ah
oh hello oh
cool Jonathan Jonathan I just
saw yes I think so I fast oh we got
through it reading it was in my oh
they're even FAS thinking I hell I hope
there's food over
here
someone is this a hole oh my God don't
turn around oh it's not a hole it's not
a
hole jump
jump it's moving guys you see that it's
[Music]
moving lius C
Castle
hello these a couple of Fall Guys hey
you there what are you doing here you
have the look of Outsiders about you
me wait could it
be quick send word to his majesty it's
me I I'm the chosen one right that's how
the story is always go uh the heroes
have arrived at the
sanctuary right
away uh
oh it's a big
[Music]
bean the guards who brought you here
have informed me that you remember not
but your own
names oh wait it's like a
bunny uh a side effect oh this must all
come as a surprise to you but here here
can well to us I who summoned you
here you see an unprecedented Calamity
now threatens our world summoned who
who what do you
mean it has sewn the Earth with
corruption and drives us from our homes
the blinded land now gives rise to
creatures of Shadows known as
stains the kingdom of libell and
surroundings are now the only safe place
left to us
Li
T but should the Calamity be left
unchecked is only a matter of time
before it consumes the entire
world oh my
God bed with this Prospect I scoured the
ancient deex for a way to combat the
Calamity and therein I found one the
ritual of hero
summoning so wait
what you who hail from another world
have been summoned here by me to become
saviors of aestel am I saying it
right hey we have a
mustache I wonder if that's why I have a
mustache cuz
like uh maybe they summon the mustache
on me only you have the power to save
our world and so I ask Will
you what who's that
your
majesty what is it a great host of
stains has broken through our defensive
rine no we are rushing to mount to
defense but the situation is D Your
Majesty we must get you somewhere
safe
what oh hello who are these
strangers there is great power within
you will you be able use it to save us
save the world I got I got
a oh would you like some bread too what
is this
bread it for me I want
[Music]
bread
a ruby
oh my
[Music]
sworden
you The King The King The King is most
mistaken if he think that
I of this where are we
thank I
think I'm so sorry I'm Str danger Str
danger why are you attacking me fight to
the
death facial hair
[Applause]
orange you do yellow
hey looks like
[Music]
you that's more like dog
behavior his television screen this
looks like you thank you for Lending
your a big book
[Music]
too there
she so
[Music]
overwhelming wow this must
be where are
we are
those am I saying that right forget it
not great is it called thetic
pronunciation weren't you listening to
them they were talking sounded
important all I heard was the stuff in
my head oh yeah yeah so
loud the stains are coming the
stains didn't you weren't you listen L
stains on our clothes or
something hello they just gave us a big
that the stains are coming they can't
fight out that's why we're here but all
I heard was your a
hero I thought we're going to have like
big banquet like you know to welcome the
heroes oh we got is this bread oh no I'm
sure you're s you can have some of mine
maybe okay give me all your I'm going to
Sol the
world oh I regret that you must face
such danger so soon after your
arrival do his majesty God explain to
you our King faces an
unprecedented nice lady I talking I
adopted
her
me us why does this this using so many
difficult words even the can
be simple
words too late to save
[Music]
this stop hurting them world's they
brought us here to kill us to defend our
King it's your duty not my I sure wish I
knew what they were saying but I don't
know this world's language I got to get
out of here defeat the stains I'll
defeat you all
right wait where are we going oh defeat
on me laundry
for I don't want to fight I'm a
pacifist I think I don't
remember the
[Music]
[Applause]
beam
lasers I think I might die maybe we have
to kill my fall over wait I have a
wife I'm back oh I guess you can't die
in this world no h H like I'm back we
made it I'm okay is this real you been
reincarnated no I think this is all
simulation wa he got even
bigger
ow hey we must kill the the stain
King that was a big St King we already
fighting wa this is the final boss are
we going to be heroes
this what kind of pound was
that the
ground must be a solution to this
everyone's dying this is just like my E6
went to low what is that
about where is he God we got to look out
for each other you
[Music]
is he
dying I think we
won Neel before the
hero shout Revelation hold your weapon
and left
click
Revelation revelation
[Music]
is that
working what
[Music]
Revelation re
re
[Music]
Revelation no guys we got to say like a
spell right
Revol
rol
[Music]
rol see I told
you I did it we beat the game we exited
the simulation
[Music]
all right I guess we
won I'm the hero now where are my
spoils where's my
herum I must write to the rulers of
liban and demand
compensation EAS the game yes where is
the
princess we never agreed on any terms
but I had terms
okay okay
uh
so
um we
um yeah I was reborn into another world
but bugged out looks like we have to
wait for 5 minutes before we can
continue this the
server kind of title is
this how's it
[Music]
hanging uh I have something on my face
yeah I don't know what happened I was
summoned as a
hero the hero of hero
of
uhan am I saying it right
hold on I need to let me let me think
really hard I'm going to think really
hard I'm going to play music hold on for
memory for
memory there we
go okay
bye I have psychic powers I must have
psychic powers they were so strong
that uh I ended the
simulation we ended the
simulation with all of the heroes
combined
strength our yelling of
Revelation
uh they wanted a different
hero maybe I got swapped out that's true
maybe they instead of summoning me they
sent me
back and now they already have like
another hero what the
heck I can't be your hero
baby I can wash away the pain what is
this song I've never even heard music
before I think somehow the words seem so
familiar eai
like when they send you
back chat is my internet down hello I'm
just kidding that was a message in
[Music]
chat so
um like a few more minutes to kill hold
on wait I'm receiving a a telepathic
message from from the king of Lian
he said Heroes need not worry your
Revelation Was Heard across the
land you must wait in the waiting room
of limbo for three consecutive more
minutes and we will bring you back to
the land our summoning connection was
not very strong we have gathered the
best Maes in the country to
to combine their powers together to
reconnect the
heroes resummon the
[Music]
heroes then I got to check this virtual
message in my brain it's like um I don't
know it's hard to describe
but you know I got like this
uh I don't know I don't even know how to
describe it it's like I look around and
I just have like a little toolbar that's
at the bottom of my vision and like
little messages that's like over here
like on this side
and I got like another like little
window that popped up um there's like
some messages that have like
readed red
little
thingies
yeah good thing I have all of these
little messages to help me and keep me
company maybe that's my secret
power I have like a an all knowing
little message box I guess you call like
a little chat box
uhuh tell me chat
box when do we get a a cool outfit in in
in in our in
our hero
world I need I need an
upgrade I'm too
powerful so maybe if we if we lock the
powers away 3 five business day
I don't have that much
[Music]
time grind more
levels the beach episode we're going to
go to the
[Music]
beach shoot I didn't sign up for the
fast shipping
[Music]
no hello little
detective am I am I a detective
I like the sound of
[Music]
that okay what do you guys think my best
weapon would be I think there's like a
few different weapons we can use in uh
the hero
world uh there's a sword I don't know if
there's guns there might be a gun and
then there's maybe
bow magnifying glass
oh you know what I saw some people
holding like staffs and Wands so maybe
we could
[Music]
magic a
crossbow that sounds cool that sounds
cool hold on I got to fix something
really
quick I
might okay there we go hi
okay it's
been it's been 7 minutes here on my
little timer that you guys can't
see uh I wonder if it's ready yet
probably
not oh
well so um what you guys doing
o over there in that funny little chat
chat
box you guys are chattering
[Music]
away drinking some sod
pop the soda it's not good for
you not good for
[Music]
you French homework oh
nice uh
I
uh oh you just had a burrito I wonder if
there's burritos in
liban by the way how do you guys think
it's pronounced
like
le
le I don't know
uh have you guys seen the other Heroes
do you think the other heroes are
back
Li
liit what is it again
[Music]
ah okay it looks like I'm getting a
message okay
[Music]
sorry I got a message from the King it
was so funny we have
returned the darkness my
room oh
truly it's not this place
again
sword eat
us but she's eating she's eating bread I
don't think she eats humans herous
around people I like bread you like
bread oh okay me too
I can't really hear you I would keep my
eyes on the yellow one the yellow one
seems to have
appetite eating bread dir really
hungry we could be a bread
Club I only have four left wait can we
touch
tips red
tips
swords oh
what' you do you stole my
sword
you you
safe it was
the it was the god I
didn't I got an idea let me out of this
box break out of
here the all
powerful somebody jump in the hole they
won't let us out of these walls man
hello beautiful together to es the voes
in
my we did it we've
[Music]
escaped disable this keyboard
shortcut and ease of access keyboard
settings yes let's disable this I should
have done this a long time ago use
sticky keys wait allow the shortcut key
to start sticky keys
[Music]
No I'm going to win this is a
race oh I should have I wasn't
okay wow I sure would
I made it oh oh are we going for the
light again oh you wel I feel like I
jumped of you guys before I feel like
this is stja
Vu are like maybe we're stuck in some
sort of loop I can walk on this hole
that's
crazy give me
a does that
mean I'm going to explore these lands
and claim them for my own I'm going to
start my own
country you're going to what I'm going
to start my own country Blas what you're
goingon to take over the kingdom that we
were
inie of don't don't tell the king
that oh okay so you're not I I I misread
reev I I misread it as Revolution I
thought we were going to overthrow the
king you're going to overthrow the king
yeah I'm going to tell everyone of your
Deeds no stop tell everyone of your
plans you're you're first on my hit list
I'm going to assassinate you remember
these words can you explain what's going
on we names what do you mean you can't
kill me unless you know my name I see it
right above your head that's not my name
I don't see my name above my head no
what's your name I'm not going to tell
you wait but then you can't tell me what
do you mean you see you must tra names
and then you can kill me
I promise all right you tell me your
name first then okay my name is Jonathan
g spell with G okay that's pretty close
to my name too oh what's your name John
Watson down
wat I will
not it seems that our names are very
similar wait but how's your name spelled
o n a t h o s isn't that
Jonathan it's Jonathan are you
sure you're lying to me quite certain I
would not lie to
you your
name um j
y hello so soon
[Music]
hold on guys I'm hacking the simulation
SK
SK I think there's like a cool down oh
we did
it John John
Watson hello what I told the king of
your of your plan no you didn't you I
didn't but I was thinking about it I
forgot your name you sound like a crazy
person so I don't think he took any of
it seriously we're back to the that's
what he told me that's
what I'm not crazy I told her hardness
was going I should be hearing at this
point where is Royal everyone wait I
know what happens there's going to be
you know what happens yeah there's know
how do you
know I remember feel like I've been here
before there was a right here am I crazy
yeah no I remember too are in an endless
loop probably want to follow her how do
we break it I don't know maybe we need
to kill someone maybe everyone yeah
someone oh yeah let's kill anyone will
do you shall do you purple like why do
you smell like chicken don't please that
gu I offer bread and
why are you like the
[Music]
sty that all you my
enemies oh
[Music]
youting no one
willever you want
massage well goodbye Le
you guys are outside of the castle Yeah
yeah I don't know how she knew that I
needed that endless
loop have to do it right this
time that's a nice Technique we need
your help hero thank you I thought maybe
I hear the voice a
hero we're looking for
Heroes
okay did you say that what a big hat you
have thank you my my dad gave it to me
you know you kind of remind me of a
different mushroom of a different world
you don't
say white the mushroom huh you sound
just like them Heroes you must defeat
the stains or my family oh be
God don't worry they're too
powerful thank you please save us
Heroes why you got a zipper in your back
shut
up hey
don't touch me hair is
yellow I will report you to the king the
king is you have hair you're unlike the
other your what your great great great
Grandad no he's my
friend what are you going to do send me
to The Gallows if I if I have a tattle
on you tell the captain captain I'm
calling him right now hold on Captain
can't hear you from all the way down
here be here
any serves me correctly
here before location with that big
forehead you what is this wait what do
you think the whale you're some type of
sea animal aren't you
like no proof
fungus
fungus smells like it I was about to say
smells
pretty walking about there's anost a
foot right you are rubius it seems you
we need your help
hero oh no the voice the dialogue is
reset stay around too
long will you help
us please save my
family hero help us
hero I mean I don't know who I am you
are my my father are you you hello you
look awfully out of water to be honest
daughter you're not the first person to
say that do you have any idea
why oh wait I need to my to your voice
as
well please listen please listen hero
more it is life for death I think you
hit your head pretty
hard
Heroes
enfe the St
will perhaps she has a g side of her as
well oh anyway Time to Kill the Boss
don't know what that
was two arms my green watch
everybody
protect
okay let's go guys jumping is my
specialty after all hey there's some
Heroes over here just la in around
you're not even doing
anything hit the tummy hit the
tummy
really sh hurt my new friends oh boy oh
how cute there's a little dog don't lose
your
motivation bread instead of Swords what
if he's just really hungry oh go I'll
save you from this evil dog is it a goat
I think it's a
goat yeah I can see why you might feel
bad thank you are we
winning hey stop
that watch
out maybe we have to on the head head
shot I'm L sh chop chop chop chop this
Loop then oh
no oh no she's
dead you die what we going to
[Music]
do can join the battle
I we won I
think did we
win ah this part
again
re Revelation Revelation Revelation
Revelation
[Music]
Revelation you guys need to say in the
chat too that's the only way to
work oh this one revelation
[Music]
oh the stain host has been
routed what does that mean I don't speak
the language of Li
stonia I fought bravely kind Heroes I
pray you are not injured I'm okay I just
just a few scratches that's
nothing that Mighty armored one must be
their leader the stained King
fascinating Most Fascinating so we
already does that mean I'm a hero we can
already have the hero
parade well I see why they call you
Heroes we'd be in right pickle without
your help we sustain minimal damage
thanks to your Valor our kingdom is in
your debt thank you I must hasten to
inform His Majesty of our Victory will
you accompany
me this this is it this is where I get
my her room and my rewards all the gold
and jewels wait no where's the
king the king's been
kidnapped I heard the news oh the king
is hiding cuz he's
scared I heard the news though we called
upon you suddenly uh what interests me
most however is the strange power you
manifested during the battle with which
you were able to defeat the stains that
power May well be the key to saving our
world from Annihilation according to the
heroes the power came to them like a
forgotten memory when they spoke the
word
reel but once they used it to wrote
wrote the stain host it seems that power
vanished Without a Trace well that's
bloody brilliant isn't it so what are we
supposed to do with the next time the
stains attack uh revelation we must
uncover the secrets of this phenomenon
if we are to Prevail against the
calamity El my the Calamity many
questions remain but one thing is
certain the kingdom of liy still stands
today thanks to you here here so Heroes
I ask you once more will you lend us
your strength and save Liv sty from
ruin yes yes the heroes
nodded marvelous on behalf of all Li
stands I thank
you H we are blessed to have your Aid
kind
Heroes allow me to introduce the four
Great guilds which are responsible for
ensuring the Kingdom's peace and
prosperity I think
everybody's okay Celesta this is the
blue one the Haven for the Curious where
knowledge and creativity are valued
above all Celesta I think this is is
this the green one the home for Glory
Seekers with ambition and vision where
the closest allies become fiercest
Rivals oh the yellow the Amber coin and
where's my reward sanctum of healing uh
the spirit of empathy and devotion Drive
seruan cup
speak of the righteous soil where great
threats are faced with even greater
courage the Jade sword one of these
guilds will become our home your home
during your time
here I'm going to be
selected Beyond this door lies the room
of Truth there and you will the will of
the ancestor shall decide your guilt
fear not introspection is a vital step
on the road to Enlightenment excels here
as I always say ever higher time to roll
the dice been seeing some of you lock
down at the Amber coin Guild Hall let us
save the world together the room of
Truth awaits go forth with
Valor
[Music]
yo the room of Truth okay hold on let
me let's pause this step on the platform
and receive the will of the
ancestor hello
[Music]
ancestor oh amidst the Raging currents
of the heart seek the peaceful Cerulean
flow I'm green does that mean I'm on the
Green Team Jade
so speak to your Guild
Master good Master where it is we're
back we're back
we're back did you guys see my awesome
cape look how cool
waa so
epic I look like a hero
right all right let's turn the bgm back
on uh hold on let me find something
really quick oh I hear
somebody oh excuse me
you got to speak to the Guild
Master yeah I remember you your voice
sounds
familiar blue your are pink
[Music]
IE I heard you
talking
hello hi yes I'm Elizabeth and you are
enemy I don't know my name wait what an
enemy what's your
name I guess I I got to pick a name hold
on let me ask the voices in my head
what's a good name voices voices name
what's what's a good name guys you got
to make friends and stuff so a call
name are you also part of the Jade sword
Jade SW oh that's
me and you are
wa I see I see all right I got a name
what's your name John Watson you call me
Watson joh
Watson John yeah I see John Watson
earlier name what's your guys wait are
all of you oh yeah I met you both of you
that's a big knife oh it's not a knife
it's called a scythe a like a farmer
uh farmer no I think Reaper so yeah
farmer but farmer of souls maybe spy
sweaty hey I'm not sweaty jeez cut it
out boy well you guys have really long
fingernails yeah you're right you going
to clip
those oh wow okay I see so they weapons
all I have is a
glass wa hey how'd you do
strong oh it w't use again I guess my
magic is only come
play that was a big
sounding I think that was my
weapon Jonathan
uh this is your weapon yeah it's a
bubble blower or something who are you
going to hurt with that a bubble blower
I can smack people in the
head
hey myself nice die that was a test he
what I'm a Reaper so I'm strong
too
a you have really name is no my name is
Mory kipy but you can call me cie that's
what the the bone people in in my chat
say the Kia people yeah that's what they
say stay back
though
okay is your big sword do anything talk
to
them over imagine it
do can I can you show off I want to
[Music]
see
nice I'm glad I have you guys on my team
you're so
powerful I imagine you are also powerful
Jonathan if you are part of the J sword
yeah maybe I think I have to level up a
little
bit you can challenge your friends to
walk DS here at the arena I don't want
to fight yet we'll be working
[Music]
with that
couldest our this is the headquarters of
our Guild sword and I am the
master though you have barely set foot
in our world you agreed to lend your Aid
to the fence of Li
lionia first thing I do when I become
king is we're renaming the country need
sword oh we have wait why you guys
saying except why you but your sword is
red
map map yes that's kind of weird why
would they put you in you will be
working with us to repel the stain save
this world first you ought to familiar
surprise yourself with this Kingdom and
how and learn how to accept and perform
quests I guess if it was GRE you find a
quest
board that look at that look at me you
look nice
I know I'm muted I'm reading this this
is our home reading the lore we live
together now go to the quest board live
together with people we don't know
Elizabeth yes we live together yay wait
where's our beds yeah do we have like a
a place to rest maybe think oh it
doesn't go
anywhere not that door that's
uh I talked to VI he said we had to find
he said yeah we got to find a quest oh
this looks like an arena maybe we're
going to fight to the
death wait let's use our map let's use
our brain create a
group Quest Master ah yes I'm using the
map I'm going towards the quest
Master sorry we're trying to look for
the quest I have the map here we could
go this way oh you do yeah lead the way
all right let's go wait I didn't get
everybody else's
names speak to your gu Elizabeth oh
Elizabeth you are you bow
bow I don't want to my own I don't
know it don't like it it makes me
upset worry puy I shall protect you
think we're Wai for never the GU mate
behind I will not leave you alone
oh you only but a few steps away I only
a few steps away I want to be by your
side
okay okay from here on out I will
promise you I will remain by your side
thank
you let's wait for the
reaper yes did you find the quest board
this way find the quest board I don't
know Quest Master down here no
all right we're almost
there whoa this town is huge oh
hey there's other people
here oh you guys come from like a
different yeah we're from the green
Guild Intruders
intr Intruders
[Music]
intr they're nice look at this look at
this oh my God your sword is way bigger
than mine I know I mean it's
not IM I I don't think I was supposed to
fight your's like a baby sword about how
you use it of course excuse me
[Music]
but she doesn't have a going on I've
never felt special in my entire life
[Music]
little you must be one of the
heroes now
sure that
sounds understand your
main
hope I must go back to and speak to the
Guild Master okay we'll wait for you
heree do you where do you check the
quest
[Music]
did she get that
creature to Quest
Master
complete where is
the a mighty Ste
thece I can I your
[Music]
horse I have a
too holy we're so fast
whoa Speedy the map we can go I'm
zooming oh
[Music]
[Applause]
sorry it wasn't me it was
her you join us you as we are guil think
we're on the same Quest join us wait
what quest did you guys
do
atal needed at the SMY okay materials
accepted for another worldly hero hey
guys we move a lot faster on the
horse only one on the
board
at and mys
running you can help us trade or invite
the party I shall invite you to the
party
everyone is invited to my
party is there a way we can fix our
group chat because it would be a lot
less chaotic if we oh yeah there's
groups there's groups I don't I think
apart
from do we start a voice chat group it
says you're in my party oh yeah we can
start a voice chat group that's a good
idea oh there she is oh my God okay okay
okay okay okay okay still
I shall free you I
will mayhaps instead of typing accept
you click on accept is my humble
opinion Goodbye Oh press T and then
hover over accept and press
it you joined my
party
welcome I must charge my spell
device thank you
Revelation Revelation Revelation let me
invite the red
one is it this way I guess we can take
our
horses I want a I want
a I shall be
back how about making a
group a voice chat group voice CH
group I think it was I think it's
oh is my voice cool it happen how' you
get that egg I don't know he a voice
born from an egg yes I have one
[Music]
too oh my
goshow to get talk to
the a great questiony the I guess we
just wait how does one
find and then so open your chat and then
you click
accept nice idea let us ride oh
M let's
go we'll wait for everyone
B bow bow as they say oh she changed
color now
oh that was cute a color changing
Ste memories of riding a horse me and
she already have the same problem but
she got I don't know if it's okay to
ride
over
how there can we take
this can we take these trees I I don't
think so I don't I don't I don't think
so maybe maybe we can go a little bit
like
hello I was
muted you heard
nothing I'll wait for them
here hello cute
[Music]
goggles wait what what am I doing
materials
[Music]
needed
wait completed speak to blacksmith
francess collect 10 oak logs and speak
to blackm
Okay hey guys the blacksmith's right
here
over here pleas don't want it sorry you
guys disappeared you went so fast you
you got to talk to this guy in here oh
yeah here this this little
fella hello little guy I may look scary
but I'm sh you saw the quest the start
and oak logs Oak log
okay
okay we got 100 coins just for to little
guy can I talk to you again and get some
more coins talk cool we have coins wow
easiest cash I ever
made Rich I'm sorry s do not worry about
the horse that just appeared in your
face what's this what's this what's
what's
this what' you findle spell
book I use my wa what does that do you
cannot use the enchantment table you
brought the thank you so
much wa outside this place is getting
busy hello excuse
[Music]
me let's I think me and Jonathan are
going to be good friends then yay all
right shall we go I think the gate is
that way right it says we have to go to
the actually I'm not sure where we go
what go to another location
yes yes
oh oh oh we're outside now no I don't
want to go to another
location ene en
ene was this correct oh
gosh
ow wish we could catch them capture them
in little balls or something and keep
them in mycket
I like that nice I'm sure I like the way
they they
cry
iing oh is this Oak we shall the land of
stain we shall rid the land of the
trees I wonder if we each need 10 wood I
think
STS yeah get get some
EXP I'll get a tree that's farther
away that way everybody can grab a
tree wait how many do I have
now oh I got I got drops from the
monster stay
ah step back I have a magnifying
[Music]
glass and it didn't even do that much
damage I got to level up my
spells what the range on that is
crazy
okay here we
go does it freeze them I don't think my
I don't know hold on let me hover over
it
maybe I keep pressing the wrong thing oh
I got 11 okay eye of
wisdom I don't know oh the trees respawn
oh hey I'll save you oh
thanks a sword meter filling up press it
once I'm cool down hold
on yay where' everybody else go feel
like I knew how this worked once upon a
time and then I
forgot
hey right I have I have 11 wood I'm
ready am I going to level up
hey there's a lot of them
oh watch out yay got eight coins hey if
if we beat the enemies we get coins oh
nice nice yeah we could grind and buy
maybe some new supplies or something
yeah or like some armor or something
like that yeah yeah let's see how much
how much wood do you guys have I have 11
I think we just need
10 oh
okay I'm going to explore these lands
I see because the tree grows back so
fast it hurts me really
yeah that's interesting all right let's
see how much I have 13s so I'm done
get yeah I'm finished I got know how
many oh if you press e you can
check you can check your inventory have
n oh you need here I have one more you
can
have thank you he's not dead
go wait there oh I don't think I can
drop stuff never
mind what the heck
very
a they are strong
too I'm trying to time it
but die foul Beast
Abominations yeah get them like a little
I really could use some food
I give you oh we have to trade oh
here I got the gr back there's so
many use the sword
while
yes side is still stronger I
feel I'm sorry F destroy them all at
once oh no nice we work well together
nice job though
all right I have enough wood you guys I
have 10 I have
10 all right let's turn in our
[Music]
Quest oh and go
yes all right
okay it's over here this
one wait who is the the
map ah this
way hello waa cool
swords is this the smiy
yeah I can't get through the
door oh you're not wait you brought the
ls yeah oh you want if you bring the raw
materials to you can make all sorts of
tools
completed wack pick at the smiy and
speak to blacki
princess oh I have some logs left
complete the side quest and then speak
to the oh whoopsies I'm sorry about the
horse why won't you let me talk to stone
tools Pur
should your master you bring the raw
materials to him can make all s of tools
and items for
you you can craft logs into planks and
planks into sticks from your inventory
planks ah
a sticks seem
useful was
like a
stick somehow I know the recipe a
pickaxe a wooden
shovel yay I got
one oh but you needed certain things
like 20 coins three Oak planks and two
sticks um wait what am I doing oh oh oh
maybe I can make the sticks myself now
what ah so we can't craft at a crafting
table we got to craft it here craft them
from inventory yeah he's the new
workbench
true so wait is that it complete the
side quest and
speak all right green if if you guys did
it we
can over 10 oak logs there's a bunch of
trees not far outside the town that you
can chop outside wait outside okay let's
try going outside
outside of town okay I think really oh
that might work too but you can also do
it in your
inventory yeah make planks first and
then sticks oh yeah you press planks
then
sticks I made a pickaxe made a plank and
a shovel two two logs makes plank yeah I
four planks two planks makes a
stick wow so they wanted us to make the
yeah you got to make it in your
inventory and then give him the
materials does he want the planks and
stick and stick you can make sticks in
your inventory by using two planks yeah
just stack them on top of each other
like one on top one on the
bottom I don't think I can fight again
until I have something to eat let me
read these funny messages in my brain
def something yeah we lost our memories
we don't know how to craft tools thank
you for the gifts wow gifts
I they're very excited making sticks she
has a cloak on look she
they
puy I wish the cloaks were like
different colors that way we can kind of
tell who's on what team yeah I am a
member of Jade sword after all so I'm
going to put this here what do you
want inventory is very full you got to
get the pickaxe and then you talk to
this guy he wants the
pickaxe I gave the pickaxe pix that
one's very SM I made it nice gave it to
me like that oh I purchased it you can
talk to this guy do it we can be
friends why do
I craft the wooden pickaxe did I buy it
I bought one I SP qu the bought
it oh no I didn't want to spend my money
it's okay I also bought one I thought I
was making
it I don't think it's a scam a scam what
you got scam actually use it I'm
confused maybe we can make one do you
have a pickaxe in your inventory I have
a pickaxe but when I talk to this this
fellow here yeah does not speak to me I
think
uh we can go talk to the quest Master
buy things fair and
square buy like normal humans yes humans
buy things with
money I think we can
our Quest or do I don't
know wait do you guys think wait we have
to go do Cobblestone now I thought we
completed the quest now we go to I'm
going to go back oh oh yeah to get the
coins
huh I'm going to the quest Master I'll
go check the quest
master and then if not we do
[Music]
Cobblestone oh oops how do I make a
pickax you can't make one you have to
buy one bring the Mater
can I mean mine was made immediately do
you have the required materials C wood
and
pickaxe completed wait what where's the
master if it's completed we can go to
the quest Master yeah where's the master
especially if you need coins wait do I
have to do something with them everybody
have their
pickaxe okay I'm so confused second
how do I drop them oh you have to
trade oh yeah make sure that you trade
with the the uh the person charge okay
trade I think we have to buy from him we
have to trade too yeah it's both you
trade your coin you have so typically if
you think about it every time you buy
something at the store you are
conducting a
train to theol
why oh you must do I think okay good I
don't
know I have low confidence all right
we'll check with the quest Master but
maybe we need to do another Quest I'm
not sure okay okay shall we
GOI wait am I going oh here it is Quest
board hello Quest Master we did your
quest looks like the perfect job for
best of luck off you okay I think we
also need to collect Cobblestone
now I don't know if I finished
oh know I think I think it's okay oh God
damn it there are more
quests oh there was Cobblestone we had
to get too yeah I think this is like the
next part of the quest so that's why we
need that's why we need the picka I only
pickaxe to get cobblestone that makes
sense come on let's go gather
Cobblestone this John Watson character
is definitely uh the smart one in really
me she
do I do have the glass of Wis you're not
done it's okay it's
okay you have the pickaxe right to go
we're going to go get cobblestone let's
go not yet what happened it's okay you
have a
pickax maybe they have some
bread it's part of the quest it's part
of the quest right I have traded oh
hello hi hello I'm not too what is cob
I'm supposed to get cobblestone yeah
let's go get cobblestone
[Music]
puppies puppies have
you puppy
Panic
M follow me
m pablin d is a special
material oh
well I hope that they can make their
pickaxes I think they already have them
right yeah so it's time to go get
cobblestone I think I think so d yeah W
went that way are you okay now fuzzy one
I think so I don't know though brandish
your pickaxe and let us see yeah let's
see your
pickaxe now swing it from side to side
side side to side pickaxe pickaxe oh no
that's that's an
axe huh that is an axe it's a different
weapon of mass destruction what that is
an axe it is a different weapon TR with
you
okay accept my trade
request all right take this it's quite
foul is quite foul I don't really
likeing about that but you're
not oh okay you have one is it in your
inventory I had one but then it didn't
work one
second there you go my trade work out I
haven't finished the quest yet that's
okay we got to get cobblestone to finish
the quest follow me follow me I don't I
Scarlet
wand Scarlet wand they'll figure it out
they'll figure it out say Scarlet it
makes my ears perk oh true is that part
of your name red
one I don't know maybe it was a nickname
cuz it says e blood
flame above your head but you aren't my
friend blood
flame riding their horses upon me oh I
wish they would see us hey but watch
where you're going these days no
manners whereing
[Applause]
youre something something defer you must
that one of those legendary horse girls
we're doing they
don't hey I'm just saying I've heard of
your kind
before I will defend myself
you must come over to the Jade sword
area exactly they gone that's all right
you know people talk a big game not
ready to defend
themselves yeah some people can can talk
a lot of s word but they can't actually
take it night
time I'm ready to mine whenever you guys
are to we got to wait for I'm sorry oh
that's okay did does fuaa have enough
materials by chance to make open the
trade oh yeah Quest
master master quest
Master where did she go just right uh
let's see right click when you talk to
the quest or the blacksmith
person the
Smithy yeah you just right clicky
blacksmith and you right click and then
you talk to this little guy where is he
oh where' go
well please submit guys the quest isn't
done yet you have to go get cobblestone
yeah if you have a pickaxe I think it's
fine we'll just go get
cobblestone I have I have the oak logs
the
what oak logs the stu oh so with the oak
logs then you make Oak
planks I have PL okay thank goodness
will you buy it from him
well yeah I bought the oak pickaxe now
you some talk my master you should be
able to make you stone tools give it a
try
yeah come talk to him okay come talk to
him Cobblestone and sticks okay I will
talk to them the blacksmith's
Apprentice oh I see okay now I can talk
to him I see now makes sense from now on
when you find new
materials more
now it's completed my master will make
you put some cool
stuff okay I already got the stuff I
don't want to talk to him though right
as
we okay wonder what would suit you best
bring cobone next probably find Somey
around you must use your Oak
planks did you buy did you buy it I I
bought a
would the if you bought one then you
have to mine the cobblestone
to the complete gain 50 exp speak to my
Apprentice I see figured it
out nice thank you bone
people people why was I supposed to talk
to the blacksmith then to buy the
pickaxe more
pickax okay why can't I just use this on
the let's see your pickax let me see
that thing
that's not a pickaxe it's a horse are we
going to go somewhere you can hardly
tell the D unless the horse's name is
we're not leaving until we see your
pickaxe oh there it is St until you show
us your pickaxe young lady all right
we're ready let's go get
cobblestone
okay the places are so
fast
okay oh here's cobblestone
this hey easy enough is this we got to
Beware of the enemies though because I
haven't had a meal in a long time
okay I'll get off I'll protect you seems
like it is working oh that stuff can't
be broken
what away with me oh it's turning into a
seems you can't continue to mine
it it sounds like it's going to blow up
they up on me it does doesn't it
iten
me I'll help I'll
help get get away get away get
away okay nice work now I'll use my
pickaxe okay ooh lots and lots of cobbly
stone how much cobbly Stone do we need
uh probably 10 once
again what the
heck we are efficient
the stain is
[Music]
our all right I do not like it when it
cries
gosh the sounds that makes her
[Laughter]
[Music]
sad war cry Jonathan it is but it's war
cry think of it that way it is trying to
attack
usad it's war cry
I got all the C I think we need more
food soon oh I got it see I knew that
rabbit was evil
robbit theone now oh nice you guys have
Cobblestone
okay oh nice all right let's go turn in
our Quest
Str know I will stay
alive came to
mind maybe it maybe a song that you
heard a long time ago oh yes it would
make good song lyrics I
agree okay all right we're going
back back we
go wait for me oh no it went away no
waiting
okay shoot bab what did he say probably
still fighting he said I could upgrade
but I can't really like
fighting maybe I don't have enough
sticks oh do you have yeah do you have
you cob Stone if you talk to my master
now should be able to make you tools
give it a try that's all we need thanks
for okay do you have
sticks I got
itable wait what do I do what do I want
I want a better
100 points oh but I have 100 points let
me know if you need any St but I can
only
get just in case I can't use I have rest
inace I'm going to go out and make a
phone call three I'll be standing right
there all right coming with you really
strong I see I purchased something oh no
my coins okay well I guess I do need a
sword that wasn't very nice probably
want a pickaxe too huh what stone
pickaxe I don't know what to do with my
wood anymore but I'm sure that I'll I'll
probably break it some stone pickaxe AC
okay that was a strange
crack we did it we did it well where's
every hold on let's check where
everybody else is at TH far we have
known each other you have always seemed
cool or looked
cool did you guys turn in your quest
yeah no not the quest oh we have to go
to the quest board still oh okay nice
you got you talk to The Apprentice right
yeah we did okay cool then I guess let's
go let's go I'm sorry wa
chaos yes
yes okay Quest done I feel pretty good
about her how fast we've been going our
CI are in dead you've gone to finish the
quest the grave duty of fighting the
Calamity but I hope you will stop by the
time and lend your help to the com f
[Music]
time find shop selling Adventure here's
a bit of coin to get started item shop
there's a bit of a coin to get you
started 500 coin we're
rich the shopkeeper I can retire now on
this on this pension yeah we don't even
have to keep doing this anymore another
Quest
no cute is there another Quest we have
the shopkeeper roach armor next be the
shopkeeper okay true maybe we should do
that first oh okay wait where's
elizabth my shopkeepers this way red
one oh there she
is wait wrong red one I only
have you turn your
quest oh yes okay I I yes nice you got
another another Quest yeah kind
of the shop
keep oh this
guy
okay
hello oh my hero thank you for saving
this town in all of our
Lives welcome to my humble little shop I
have all sorts of items here just so
might help with your adventure While
others are just nice to have
all you have to do is talk with me and
everything for free wait what oh can't
give everything for free make sure you
have enough coin okay just stop by if
you ever need anything or if you just
want to keep me company oh and there's
one more thing I like to tell you about
I'm sure fighting stains all day will be
hard on both your body and your heart
when you feel wary remember to take care
of yourself have a break and do
something fun you could try visiting the
guild Halls of four great guilds for
instance each of them has an activity
you can particip any of the customers
are regulars at the arena for instance
when you're tired from adventuring or
simply looking for a little diversion
maybe give some of these activities a
try take your mind off your quest now
and then I'll do good for you if
you the children are attending to them
and I'm sure they be overjoyed to me a
real hero
completed okay go will you return to us
it
is J Watson she wants to kill the king I
don't know you what sh
my cover's blown uh oh what were you
doing nothing
sneaky do you have any
bread nope I'm all out why I want I'll
go to the shop time to buy something I'm
hungry that
mising I'm going to die if I don't eat
something do there's some crazy beggar
on the street I am gues will not kill
the king Guild mates help me leave my
friends alone crazy Beggars like
spouting conspiracy theories and like
now we have to speak to the in
the no I don't
Havey stay away from my gu
member excuse
me excuse me excuse me give a conb
around your neck excuse me you don't
talk to a GU member like that your
talking to my hey these are our streets
just having a friendly exchange this is
our
territory King we are the J sword and we
are loyal yeah we are loyal we're
empathetic we EMP hamster and your
mother smells
of excuse me I my to
be i' never known you guys are
disturbing the piece you know that oh
I'm so sorry don't listen to whatever
they
had you're
crazy hey hey hey this chick's crazy
don't cry don't cry want to kill the
king no can can you tell me more about
this plan to kill the I don't know she
made that up I don't I don't know why
I'm kind of
interested we can't we shouldn't talk
about this here they're listening
oh got to meet up in
secret there's behind you I can't talk
about this right
now use
fac too risky too risky there's too many
people
around all right I have
food um our next Quest is to go to the
gardens which a little
the livonian
child don't talk to us don't talk to us
I
will don't talk I can't K you I can't
hear
you excuse me the air is very what gu
are you guys from what Guild are you
guys from
maybe you are
killer okay thanks now I can report you
guys I'm going to report you
guys hey hey that's not a good
idea that's not you never catch up with
me that's not even that's not even the
right place you
running I know where I'm going I'm going
to see the
king I actually don't know where they
Guild all is oh God are they behind me I
escaped
I'm just going to tell them I want to go
see the king if I see them
okay this is
nice
shoot this is not the gardens huh it
looks like a garden though oh wait it is
the
gardens y little child don't you want to
meet me a hero an
idol goly no want her Ro boy this must
be my lucky
day H right well this here is the
gardens you're free to come and use him
whatever you like pretty pretty Aces is
it my job is to keep an ey on him scare
away birds and stuff you don't like
gardening you can also try building
there's an empty lot just past here
where your Heroes can build whatever you
like oh an empty lot for us in it you
and your guild mates can work together
to make a right spiffy place to
stay stop by anytime if want to do some
building or
gardening oh say can I tell you secrets
you know there's a place in town called
the pit the pit mom says us kids aren't
allowed to go but I hear you can play a
really fun game there you're Heroes so I
bet you'll they'll let you in maybe you
can go check it out and tell me what
it's like anyway I hope to see you
again my wait so there's a place we can
build a house I got to tell I got to
tell my my my my my my my
guildmates is this it
this looks like a perfect place to put a
railroad a subway system around the
whole city hold on how big is this place
anyways I'm going to go back I'm going
to go back to see what everybody's doing
but oh
shoot can't get up here
huh
aha I made it to the top
almost oh this is a perfect snipe
spot I'm on the
wall oh I think the horse doesn't like
stairs that makes sense then I want to
see how big this is it like a country or
is it like a city or just a
town you guys think there's fall damage
on my horse
oh I have so much
bread what's this little heart
thing I want to try to jump on top of
the
buildings oh
water this is big this is a pretty big
area I wonder who built all
this the leonian
NPC talk text Q3 oh my God
adorable you make me feel like we could
actually push those stains back it's cuz
I'm so powerful they can sense my aura
my hero
Aura all right hold on I'm going to go
back to where everybody else is but I
just want to see what's over here
whoa what is this maybe this is a
summoning Circle they summoned Us
[Music]
in oh there's people
here on the
guard I keep doing that I will protect
this place for the people for the king
the king is
here where's the king
oh
[Music]
King oh
King die die die die die die die die die
die die die die die die die die
Oblivion
shoot all right I'll be back I'll be
back when I level up I'll take over this
Kingdom all right let's go back let's
see what everybody's up to
oh look at the sunset so pretty wait
what is
this all right I'm on my way back this
is the way
back oh this must be where they sacrific
[Music]
lonians all right this is the main road
so we shouldn't be too far far from
where everybody is I'm pretty sure my
gut is saying we're going to turn left
right this
way everybody must have gone to the
gardens the next place
I feel like I'll meet a fair Maiden
here going thr the bushes I thought we
were making a salad yeah Mak so sad K
does it really okay wa where's the salad
berries quickly psh what the
heck hey did someone take my berries I
don't get any berries I they're from my
salad salad I got some scavengers yummy
yummy I want infinite m I like not a
salad hey the salad's good for you
Violet on
the maybe this isn't a great idea all
attacking at the same time but it does
seem kind of
fun maybe it needs to not be a sword you
me like a
pickaxe maybe my
S this is definitely a harvesting ah yes
there is
a much food out here too
sustenance taking a bath this is the
public bath
house uh I'm not sure about that I'm
pretty sure it
is but you look like you're
flying yeah Jonathan you're flying I'm
taking a
bath I'm so clean that I must
sending is this how you take BFFs in
your realm yeah isn't this normal
I mean it's different feel so clean now
you should try it try
[Music]
it jump jump get them
all H oh we're cleansed yes I feel
Mighty refreshed yay that was quite
dangerous was it
this fruit
yes not fruit oh
melon oh this one doesn't actually grow
back oh it
does is this where we Farm can we Farm
here I don't know I mean I'm you know as
we are you know part of the the Jade
sword and we we protect those in need I
think we should uh you know
we we should get our take our sustenance
and yeah I think we have a plot of land
where we can grow stuff but I'm not sure
where it is where did everybody else
go they
left ow
ow oh everybody went to the pit shall we
go to the pit
yeah I I shall uh
okay I have enough Jonathan Jonathan
there is Jonathan Jonathan Jonathan I
might
die do that
Jonathan all the horse is faster come
on I won't die from just some berries
I'm a
hero uh the pit pit door man
hey ah this is kind of where I was
earlier oh we're going to make a a left
up here wait sorry I passed
it here we
are this GPS is
slow together and coins here we are see
told you it was useful didn't I you'll
thank me for it when you're
adventuring oh it' be a lot easier if
you had some extra coin is all I'm
saying wishes to speak to us oh don't hi
here it again yes come down here to the
pit and play around or
two you ever see some poor walking out
of here penil don't worry about it is
this are they asking us to do something
shady I don't know like roll the dice
maybe we're going to do like underground
fights FL the
town I don't know Guild Master wishes to
speak with you please meet him at the
Jade sword
Guild that's where we're from right
yeah we know where to go
then yeah we're going to the Jade sword
area
okay I'll follow you guys yeah oh oh
looks are you sure the sharks can drown
though that seems confusing
drown wait what
oh okay Elizabeth you said you'd say by
my side forever though maybe she's just
a bit of a loner I can kind of
relate but you guys I like hanging out
with you guys I don't know where I'm
going are you sure you do follow me
okay what kind of Guild does take care
of each other we got to look
where did they
go good to know all right I'll follow
the
map don't want this stay by my side oh
okay I think I'm going the right way
wait this way
sorry we're going back home yeah it's
this way
okay really beautiful time Town though
yeah honestly not the worst place to
wash up isai yeah oh wait is it up
here oh I think it's down here that's a
funny word
isai I don't believe by the way I think
you're cool John Watson you you're cool
too man I'm blushing oh gosh I got to
look away
they I hope you familiarized yourself
with the T I did I did we learned a lot
about
adventuring we all lament what has
befalling the lands outside our
kingdom the Calamity and the stains it
has borne have turned most of the world
into a wasteland you must be shaken to
suddenly find yourselves in another
world but I pray you will be able to Aid
us in our fight our first priority is
finding a way for you to regain your
powers of Revelation do not include
sticky keys to that end I have just
received word from one of our Scouts
regarding possible lead
investigating the
Calamity our comrades CH on mysterious
ancient
ruin
hello
missing right here Scouts from our Guild
are already stationed at the ruins for
further
investigation I asked that you might
join join them there and lend your A for
Bor cool exit the Town Gate headed the
planes and speak to hastas of the J
sword so that's the next Quest yeah
shaken suddenly find yourself another
wood yes yes I am
shaken okay power of
[Music]
Revelation yeah probably more Coco and I
need to head off here oh you guys are
going away on a different Journey huh a
little bit of a different Journey but
we'll be back soon okay we'll see you
again well let's adventure together when
you guys come back shall
[Music]
we well take care fun getting to know
you both today let's do our best with
Jade sword e Jade
swording
trespasser bye away with
you to be here byebye this isn't public
property now you're the one that was
allowed to be here staining the name of
John Watson yeah your
secret public space yeah back
off tell me where your leader is he's
right over here tell me we don't have a
leader on our team he's right here we're
all leaders team oh thank you oh Jah
Watson even though you wish to kill the
king huh the king um I'm trying to save
the king I have to kill him to save him
wait John Watson huh what you need to
kill kill the king no I said I need to
save him how will you save him by
freeing him from this person one second
I must hang up my phone call real quick
be right back team I I got to go hold on
sorry
goodbye they'll never catch me where's
the other guild
Halls why don't she find her so easily
there must also be like part of this
Arena no or maybe they have different H
she's not behind me oh she's right
behind
me I can't a Shaker
no
shoot I I lose this
chick but I have an idea I have an i
Bob and weave bob and
weave for me no why can't you why can't
I outrun
you a peace you'll never catch me what
are you going to do jump off what are
you try what you what you you'll never
catch me shoot no don't jump I am full
of empathy you would fill me with
sadness if you
jumped listen and the king the king is
evil trust
me trust you I saw a stain I saw a stain
on his
pants on his pants what did it look like
it it was like pretty big and I think it
I think he's
corrupted where was the State located
it's like you know like on the back side
oh why looking there I think maybe he
got touched by stain and like corrupted
and oh my I'm on a secret
mission but I know I know the Queen the
queen is on my team she said that she
met eyes with the King and they fell in
love it's all a lie it's part of his Ru
a lie yeah he's trying to seduce
her okay I will trust you yeah you were
telling my secret to everybody I'm sorry
I'm sorry everybody knows my secret
mission I'm sorry now I'm never going to
be able to kill King because you my
goodness my
mission I will I will make I will make
it right I will tell everyone that it
was just a joke I was it was just a Gest
help me you got to help me kill the king
okay how you got to find the king and
you got to try to kill
him okay how should we
communicate uh I'll find you you'll find
me yeah I'll give you updates then okay
okay Carry On we cannot be seen together
we can't be seen together good
luck Mission successful who are these
guys they cute little hats oh this is
the other guild
huh he look at his cute
beard spee
100 all right I think
come it's night time I think I might you
know head to bed and we will continue
this oh I was going to say goodbye to my
guild mate but hey who's who's back
there I guess it was just the
wind I was going to say good night to uh
Callie my Reaper Guild
mate but I don't know where
went that's
okay all right this was a pretty good
successful stream right guys it's a
first successful stream I guess we'll
keep playing um I know everybody else
wants to like meet up and I think
there's like I heard about Dungeons or
something we could
do
[Music]
so yeah I can call her with the radio
really I don't know how to use it I I
think there was maybe
um a little sheet that I could have read
like a little instruction manual but uh
I'm not quite
sure right click to
use right
click click on it and then wait all
right
bye-bye click on it and
then CLS are cool right right the top
bar this
[Music]
oh that doesn't sound very nice oh hello
oh is that you John Watson yes I'm just
going to call you Watson hi I'm in the
construction area kind of carving out my
own area for me oh nice okay I'll try to
find you okay just want to see where you
are oh yeah okay
byebye okay well let's go to the
construction area and then I'll say
bye
uh let's see I think it's by the gardens
right prank call okay let's do prank
call that's a good
idea who's hello I'm getting a phone
call one second guys hello hello is this
um a
shark maybe it depends what do you have
to sell me uh sell no no no we're not
selling anything I'm with the
liian uh charity and we are looking for
donations for the uh
liian um sewer
population I
see guys the livonian charity donation
is calling me should I give them any
money we'll we'll take a small donation
of 200
gold your your support means everything
I'm sorry my mom and daddy said I can't
I can't give you anything I'm sorry
who's your mom mom mom they told me to
tell you to call The Blue Team The Blue
Team aren't you blue the Cerulean cup
says they have lots of
money and they're nice all right and
charitable I'm going to call back um
when you have more gold okay they also
said that your team is is Shelly
hey they said that not us W this is the
Scarlet one team who's who's in charge
of your
guild seruan cup all right you're
getting ready up I'm reporting you
goodbye hey let's make another phone
call oh wait
shoot already in a call dang it I wanted
to get an update on the
king
okay and let's
see right let's go to construction area
first before I get distracted
[Music]
uh how do we get
there I want to say we take a left
here and the garden is this
way so wait it said it was beyond the
garden so
where Where is the
oh is this it this looks like a good
area to build
no here we go somebody started building
here maybe she want to go gather more
materials oh hello are you going to go
on an
adventure yes mayhaps when we gather our
party members too oh do you do you think
that you maybe have some room for more
party members we we have four oh hello
hello I don't think there's a limit to
how many people can join our party I
think you can only have five people can
enter a dungeon of five five yeah five I
see so they've already got their full
party party of four so you two must
fight each other to the death no no no
it's okay I'm going to bed it's it's
Siesta time oh it's time for John Watson
Siesta yeah yes well take care John
Watson it was nice meeting you today
yeah it's nice meeting you guys okay
goodbye paths cross again
goodbye she's on the phone ah horse
hello don't kick me
off all right I leave my quest to my new
minion all right yeah I'll probably end
it here wait let me see I have a lot of
Kings a lot of red notifications
here
ah okay hold on I got to try using this
magical toome what is this
[Music]
give up on the current dungeon kick
disband only party leaders can disband
okay then
leave
yes
okay so now we know we got to leave the
party
before um before leaving the game
all right CH I'll do what you
want
hello yes
hello m m oh
hi I'm saying good night to my guild
members good night farewell Maiden I'm
on leave me learn I'm on the phone oh
I'm on the mobile oh okay goodbye
Jonathan goodbye well thank you you too
good
luck thank you thank you for for for
your your your your your your your
greatness and your heroicness and such
you you you too you are pogi oh oh you
you
too byebye
oh well
I got a a
little
wow guys
[Music]
jealous all right I need to um come up
with a plan to kill the
king to kill the
king I wonder if I make
TNT and then I blow up the
castle what do you guys think
that'd be good right it might it might
have some
effect might have some effect let's try
yeah
okay for now
[Music]
um I guess people are doing Dungeons and
stuff but uh I had to wake up really
early to get something done today so
had a long day okay and know it's kind
of a short stream but thank you guys for
uh populating my little chat
box
Revelation thank you thank you okay
thank you so much for the gifts and
stuff yeah we're going to have a member
stream
tomorrow and I don't know if more people
playing Minecraft tomorrow maybe I'll
join so yeah see you tomorrow yeah yeah
I'll see you guys tomorrow for member
stream all right oh this cape is so warm
I feel hot and
sweaty okay good night thank you guys
for watching I hope you have uh we're
going to go raid into somebody else
who's going to go into dungeons dungeons
you guys are going to get
spoiled okay but maybe tomorrow I'll
also join a different party in go
dungeoning especially when for M get
back they'll need a you know a party
member to go to the dungeons with so
that' be
good thank you for the stream thank you
for watching okay I'll see you guys
bye-bye bye-bye
[Music]
farewell die gor
oh I was going to H up but it's not
coming out okay bye