[Music]
you
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
hmm
[Music]
[Applause]
wait i think that's the wrong chat that
i put in there
i'ma just chat here hell no why are you
doing there this chat is a livestream
this is the wrong chat you idiots
go to the real chat idiots there you go
now we got the real chat
okay
it's been such a long time guys i'm
[Music]
thank you i'm back
hello oh wait is there even oh wait wait
wait
wait you guys hear the wait do you guys
hear the bgm
i actually don't i wonder why why don't
i hear any pcm
oh yeah oh yeah wait
i'll fix it probably uh
how how are you guys
how are ya
[Music]
you guys hear that and i don't hear it
i know why i know why
how about this
[Music]
how about that i
yeah but i can't the weird thing
oh yeah oh yeah
wait what about
[Music]
um
oh no during the sauna i don't know
i don't know what it's been a while
since i've
streamed on my pc everything should be
fine normally but
i'll hear stuff why why
[Music]
oh wait this is
this is not minecraft god damn it update
updating the logo every time this is
definitely not my thing
okay okay that's something i can fix
easily that's
that's easy enough
oh where's my animal crossing logo come
on
[Music]
animal crossing logo must have saved it
somewhere
nope nope can't find it no uh
i have a fire emblem logo what about
that would we want to use the fire
emblem logo
ah whatever we don't need a logo today
we don't need it
but still i would i would like to at
least have some audio
[Music]
thank you for the recipe what's up guys
did you guys like
save your money to send me red now
because i wasn't streaming for a few
days is that what it is
[Music]
oh maybe here no
don't
i want to hear some audio
you know actually i know i know what the
problem is
the game audio somehow for some reason
goes through my second monitor i heard
it
so i turned the the audio that came out
of my second monitor i turned it off
but but
it shouldn't go through that in the
first place it has to go from my mixer
what the hell i'm so confused
why is it not going for my plug and
unplug
plug and unplug what wait let me let me
reopen
one second one second
you know sometimes that also does the
trick when i just uh
open close this
elgato game control it was like acting
weird i want a new game and what a new
capture card
this is old as hell anyway the game
disappeared don't worry
coming back soon don't worry hello
everyone by the way welcome welcome
welcome i'm trying to i'm trying to fix
something here
i'm trying trying to fix it
[Music]
someone write that down okay if we memo
i gotta sing that in an unarchived
stream sometime
soon oh that's that's really um
nostalgic
what's that it's a free free member girl
group
close the button why is my switch not
turning on anymore
[Music]
turn it on
what's going on
[Music]
of course things have to go bad
why is it not
why come on why is it not
[Music]
wait let me restart this stupid
program again
you you
task manager help me please lord help me
close close it close and now it's now
you close uh-huh yeah i thought so i
thought you're closed now
of course now that i opened the task
manager you you're secretly
you're secretly closed huh
my windows is japanese so it gives me
japanese error messages
okay i need i need
i need task manager after i'll open open
the task manager
open it where is it
okay where the is it let me close
it
okay okay
[Music]
it doesn't show in my task manager
though it says it's open when i try to
open it again but when i
there it is
[Music]
okay i need a new game capture card this
stuff is
but honestly
from our trip right i brought my switch
but cali brought her gaming capture card
so some people thought i brought this my
game capture card and my switch
and that's why it didn't work but that's
not true actually her game capture card
is like works differently than mine
which is kind of the reason why we
couldn't stream on the switch
and i feel like if i would have brought
mine it would have worked because we
needed to
to use like a another tv monitor the
hotel's tv monitor
to stream switch but the tv monitor
didn't recognize
uh uh our switch anyway so here we go
again
come on
come on oh there we go okay
okay now it's not showing me the game
again thank god
but wait do i hear audio no i don't
wait but that's okay what if i open this
now
worst case i'll just not play with audio
but oh one nice thing about
animal crossing is the cute audio and i
really don't hear
it okay whatever i'm turning i'm turning
the music in my
monitor on again i think i'll just turn
it
quietly so you guys don't hear much of
higher i hear
higher i don't hear anything though
well i guess because i changed it here
huh
wait you guys don't hear it now either
do you wait you don't hear it either
okay i know why because
and now i hear it
okay i another idea advanced audio
properties
i'm gonna i'm gonna listen to the audio
through obs monitor and up
okay i hear it it's probably a bit
delayed but
okay
[Music]
now let's go
sorry guys about the scuff i mean i
didn't really fix it
but thank you i didn't exactly fix it
but
this is probably i'm just going to play
for obs now i'm going to play and listen
for obs
hell yeah hell yeah uh
wow what a chill stream this is going to
be chill
this is going to be chill i have just
come back for my
vacation of cali
and i'm sure you guys want to hear
stories but i'm going to
most of what i want to tell you guys for
tomorrow
because there's so much to tell but i
took lots of photos
so that i can show you guys tomorrow
like like a picture book
we're gonna look for the photos together
with kelly and explaining you
every little detail so i'm gonna hold
back today
and not talk too much about what we
actually did well maybe i might sell
some small things though
we will see ah but yeah i actually i
came back like a few hours ago
but i prepared some stuff for tomorrow
because tomorrow's stream is quite early
and this this stream is going to be
uh like like like until i have to go to
sleep
so i had to do it kind of before the
stream but i'm not finished
or any anyway and then and then and then
i then i realized oh my god for i
it seems like i have oh my god seems
like i have lost
my my usual like um block
converter thingy that i use for my
uh nintendo switch because my nintendo
switch is from europe
and when i use it in japan i need that
black converter anyway it seems like
i've
together with my hair iron i think i've
left it in our hotel
because my hair is also from europe and
also needs that so yeah anyway
i left that there i think so i realized
oh my god wait
i can only stream
yeah the hair one is okay
i was more angry about the plug
converter and actually i'm also mad
about the hair iron
i guess i need to buy a new one and
[Music]
yeah so so i rushed uh to the
to the shop to get a new plug converter
because
the switch has to be docked and charged
in order to
uh capture it via a game capture card
yeah
so yeah i did all that before the stream
even though i just wanted to come back
home
and then set up my stream and then just
chill until the stream starts but
i i've been up and i mean i even made a
new remote guys
did you guys see that what is it
what is it
yes guys i've already made a campsite
and we have a visitor we have with my
first visitor oh my god
[Music]
i don't know
so i quickly whipped that up i want to
do more
hmm i was kind of procrastinating when i
was doing that because i was supposed to
prepare my streams my takamoni streams
for tomorrow
there's so much to do
[Music]
i wonder who's visiting our campsite
but i need enough i need to build
another house right
hey hello guys
so many things have changed is this too
loud
but maybe so many things have changed
guys since the last time
that i have streamed but actually since
the last time i've started animal
crossing i've done
one members only animal crossing stream
i know it's too quiet now okay
i know
i cleaned up my freaking island i
cleaned it all up
and i uh built some new houses and i got
a lot of new villagers so i have uh
with me i think we're six people now and
i built the campsite
and i also built the the clothing shop
although i never entered it
up until now and the museum is finished
and
oh everything's like really really
getting uh
yeah hi cat i haven't seen you what oh
hi
you ever have a hard time putting your
foot down about something i
mean like like being like don't
give me that
you it's like is that that is that
what you're talking about
is it is that that's how i i interpret
it
if someone won't listen to what you're
saying you got to have the right
reactions ready oh yeah i barely have
any reactions teach me
no oh i can do that
disagreement you hit it with the
disagreement hell yeah
thank you wait
cat's telling me to no emote isn't that
funny because
cat cat is literally nightmare cali and
callie always says no
yeah that's perfect mood
oh well so by the way i made some cute
outfits
do you want to look at my cute outfits
yes you do
look at them and how do i do it again
uh uh no okay now we got
outfit number two
oh isn't it cute i showed that one in
the screenshot on twitter
i like this one because it has sparkly
eyes and i like the hat and i like the
the
the kimono that has like the sleeves up
um
oh yeah the pacifier is cute too so yeah
then we have uh obviously
uh lore and lore outfits not many people
know this
because i i only said this one time
but i have been actually a shrine maiden
before
i obviously have to have this outfit yes
you guys don't even know this
ridiculous ridiculous if you don't know
that then
what kind of chicken even are you
unbelievable and now we have this cute
one because someone gave it to me i
think
oh i just i ran out of shoes and stuff
so i just randomly can find something
i don't know this still needs some work
and then i don't know i still wanted to
use this t-shirt because the t-shirt is
cute
but i don't have enough clothes look at
me being
ugly i need more clothes guys more
cuticles
[Music]
okay now who who in the chat
watched the last animal crossing members
only stream
and who didn't because
if you haven't seen it then you will see
a lot of new things
me me me me me me wait are those me i
have
like i have wait all those members in
the house
yeah okay so but everyone act surprised
okay everything i show you
that i have shown in the members only
stream is now a big surprise okay
okay you have never seen anything this
is all new to you okay
let's go my name is i cleaned up okay
look at these artists i think these are
just i didn't show in the memory stream
that i i finished my archway
look one two three four five six
uh one more fits like in here
okay you're singing you should be
wrapping though oh wait i just realized
there's a
this hedge is wrong oh well i'll fix it
eventually
yeah it's not cool like having all kinds
of arches here
cool right whoa what are you doing
wait well moment
i thought you guys were actually
surprised when i kissed you enough
oh you're actually wait is that but i
feel like i didn't show that in the
members only stream
[Music]
i don't thought you guys were actually
surprised about that
it got me bamboozled even though i told
you guys myself
yeah and then i i started putting some
stuff here i don't know if you guys saw
it
oh you see we have a bridge okay that's
definitely new we have a bridge
one bridge here and
i cleaned up all this looks no more
items here
just some random stuff here and there
but that's okay
oh a last item
who loves that i will burn it i
will burn it you'll never get it back
yeah bridge and i think i made another
one
well i just thought that shadow was a
fish
stupid wait i think i made uh another
bridge
[Music]
oh you guys wait wait wait you guys
haven't seen her before this is one of
my new villagers super cute super
girly girl
it's been a while yeah i was worried
that i might have offended you or
something
no actually i didn't turn on my switch
for a while sorry like i
haven't i haven't been playing every day
actually
anyway nice to see you again oh thank
you again talk to me
yes
[Music]
what's up snacky it's so cute drop
something oh yeah let's ask her
maybe what is it uh well this one is
this yours
please say yes don't send me around
first try
[Music]
what is it though tell me
it's kind of lame and also kind of sexy
oh my god we got to take a look
full body tights wait i gotta change out
of my
no no wait no
how do you do it again
[Music]
that's ugly that's ugly that's not the
sexy type
i'm 96. i hear
i hear a balloon but i don't have a
slingshot damn it okay whatever
okay well i guess i'll run around with
this for a while this is ugly this is
ugly
ew it's okay we gotta we gotta get some
new clothes because i'm looking ugly
[Music]
i know
first time in here let's see what they
got do they have that what's
outside in the window i don't i it looks
like a kamen rider
uh oh yeah oh yeah
welcome to the evil sisters where we
sell fashions made lovely
lovingly by clown thank you for the
membership
all right it's a great spot fine okay
thanks for picking this fantastic
location for us we've decided to put
down roots here in australia and keep
selling our clothes and accessories
yeah i love the rabbit head i want to
get the rabbit hat
and here let me give you wait wait now i
can get the kiara outfit some people
make piano outfits i want to get the
kill
[Music]
i think i took a screenshot before my
phone of the coat
let me give you a quick tour of our shop
okay so when you first walk in you'll
find our recommended items right there
front and center
we change these up every single day you
know to keep things fresh
and over the left you'll find americans
they're dressed up in whatever seasonal
office we're into
we change them up from time to time
rather than daily oh
ah okay so we hope you'll be inspired
you're still going to love that oh i
can't do it yet
damn it really the prank range outfit
looks cool
it reminds me of the time when um before
my debut when only my twitter and my
design was revealed
where people were like um they said that
i look like
uh like a like um um uh
like a like a like a you know
that i look like um and
yeah sentai sentai
inspired character or something like
that
or kamen rider yeah something like that
yeah and then i got i got a bunch of
people
following me because they were excited
because they're yeah like tokusatsu fans
and sentai fans and everyone was like oh
my god your bell
please tell me you can you can transform
oh my god what's your final form and
then
i was like well
because they were they were so excited
they thought that that
i'm like a super taco that's a fan and
i never was i never had the courage to
say this up until now but
i am not a tokusatsu fan
i have no interest in kamen rider or
sentai
whatsoever
i'm sorry for disappointing you
i'm unsubscribed sorry you know people
come in with these
like like hopes and dreams
thinking that i'm their dream youtuber
turns out i'm not
[Applause]
so ever since then sometimes i've been
getting questions like when i opened my
marshmallows or something or
just randomly people sometimes ask me
like
hey kiana what's your favorite tokusatsu
series or whatever and i'm like
i have no idea i don't know
anything about that stuff i can't even
answer the question
the expectations are too high
top down out of my betrayal i'm so sorry
just say power rangers oh no
so yeah that outfit maybe i should wear
it to
make my my my tokusatsu fans happy
give them a little something
ah
[Music]
i'm so sorry it sounds even funnier in
japanese man i got the
i got the i got the punchline right in
japanese
oh thank you for the red super oh you're
probably very disappointed in me i'm
very sorry
[Music]
well matt i'm so sorry for disappointing
everyone now anyway let's continue
i always felt so guilty about this
finally finally i was able to speak the
truth about this
finally finally i can be honest
[Music]
[Applause]
wait i think they look cute yeah those
are super cute
wait let's go i need more shoes
you're still here in my eyes can't even
without transformation thank you
thank you i mean the thing is the
problem is not that i cannot
transform i can't transform if my papa
would allow me
um ta-da
papa me do you wanna
who knows what i will turn into i i will
i will say no more but i can transform
the question is just
what does kiara transform into
imagine yeah imagine 3d debut stream of
kiana
and then i'm like oh my god i'm going to
transform it i love your blazer that's
so cute
so yeah imagine 3d debbie stream and
then
me i'm piano by the way me saying like
i'm going to transform now
and then all you see is flop like an egg
i just turned into an egg
oh dear
that's
no no this one is acceptable but the
pink one
no too much oh dear no no
wait that that one is okay i might even
get that one
ah oh noble zap suits that's
tap up absolute but they don't have
orange what the hell
oh lane denied this guitar i guess this
gets the closest to me
does that look like me guys why don't
they have a good hat oh there you go
that looks like me
hi my
oh they got those sneakers they got them
sneakers
oh yeah i got some blue sneakers that
looks exactly
[Music]
oh dear lord well um i guess i'm gonna
buy those
no i don't wanna wear it though
[Music]
okay now now the real stuff i want this
yeah i want oh wait wait oh this is why
can i
only like buy wait i got no money
oh they it definitely come i'll be right
back i'll be right back
let me get some money i got it in the
bank i wish you could have a credit card
in this game
they need to add a credit card function
right yeah that's still got the script
housing
[Music]
i want my money to be available anytime
oh yeah see i upgraded my my thingy too
this is upgraded now
what is it
[Music]
you should get a credit card in real
life first of all actually
i really want to actually
today i loki had a chance because like
we were like at the airport and uh
a lady wanted to give us like like what
a lady wanted
us to like you know make a credit card
where you can like get miles and stuff
but i was like i don't know i really
want one and it seems easy because she
said that it doesn't cost much i don't i
don't know how to make a credit card
no no it's not not a scam she was like
legit like really legit
black black
[Music]
you don't need it i want it because
there's so much like generally i don't
need it yeah but many times when i don't
want to like reserve
uh a flight or a hotel then often some
websites
only accept credit card not only for
that but like all other purchases too
sometimes so i really need one
but yeah so but the thing is i don't
really know how to make a credit card
and the lady said it will be uh free in
the first year
and now you don't have to pay anything
usually
right but it seemed really easy but i
didn't do it anyway because i was like
okay well i i should
i'm leaving this country and maybe i
should
like apply for one in my own country i
guess yeah
does that make sense i don't know like
is that does that make sense
it doesn't doesn't make any difference
in which country i apply for one
like i i i have a i had the right visa
to make one
that was not the issue does that make
sense okay well i'll finally get one
maybe next month or so i hope and then
then i'll splurge the hell out of it
but we need a house also why am i
running around like this
looking ugly as hell i need some money
give me money
money abd what does that
stand for again automatic
automatic
[Music]
oh really is that it
automatically machine no we're talking
about abd not atm
goddammit are you even listening are you
even listening
okay how much should we get uh oh god oh
god
how about two
no how about 50
000.
okay get that all by yourself and no one
helped
exactly exactly
so can i make a new house though
or is he gonna like wait until that uh
dude
asks for a house because he wants to
move in like i'm gonna build it now
[Music]
get that tenth person to
want to move in gotta do the campsite
first yeah i figured okay okay okay
okay no problem okay
but wait i first want to go back to shop
for some cloves
okay and and then i'll show you guys who
my villagers are because
obviously that's a big surprise no one
knows yet
oh drinking tea or hot chocolate or what
is that
where did you get that from could also
be soup
what is it
i don't give a about the happy home
academy who gives a about that
sorry about honestly honestly who cares
about them
[Music]
looks like a bottle of curry looks like
soup looks really yummy
[Music]
good our relatives oh yeah maybe it's
like glass armed or something like that
pink version of goodall okay
i'm back give me everything i want this
i want
why can i not buy both please tell me
what what's the logic behind this
that's so stupid what is that suit for
stand up color
mama ah hit plus the purchase directly
girl
what
does it kick me out of the chain
well that's just stupid also did i did i
just buy them the white t-shirt or
also the the blazer
okay because i had that selection but
then i did like this
ah i guess it only bought the blazer
right okay
then it only went in
white shirt did really oh
okay you know what i'm just gonna get
this one done
and then this one yeah
that looks stupid with all my hair
inside that little stupids
well okay i'm getting it anyway and i
want some some cute glasses
oh that's okay that's kind of cute no
nah ew some orange sneakers
sneakers no i want those yeah i want
those
[Music]
everyday tattoos looks looks just like
my
actual skin
[Music]
do you have any cuter socks dude
the boots are cute too what do you guys
think
i need some pants i guess i gotta look
like a businesswoman
no no um that fits
okay yes
did i think i think i already
blocked out blazer honestly i think i
already bought it because of the
previous purchase
but oh wow whatever adorable thumbnail
thank you
a ruthless business woman yeah right i
look like a ruthless
businesswoman
[Music]
oh my god i look so cute
pickle pickle pickle exactly
[Music]
okay so and one of these houses was from
uh
gate what was the name again gay
uh gabe gate
kaylee okay
and check this out oh you can check oh
spoiler okay everyone surprise surprise
my other new villager
is this one oddie very popular one
i think she's very popular
[Music]
oh you're not the only one i think my
viewers also really miss you i'm so
popular lot
she missed me a lot oh i already
already um bonded a little bit with her
when she first moved in
so i'm very happy with her we missed you
mama i missed you guys too
[Music]
it's so weird like i wanted to stream
for you
i know i know some of you were like oh
thank god they weren't able to stream
because they
we are glad that they like can like just
not not stream and just have a vacation
but honestly one hour per day is really
not a big deal
and i wanted to i didn't want to fall
behind that's why i really really wanted
to stream and when it didn't work out
when the q a didn't work out i was
really like disappointed
which is why i whipped up that little
video instantly
uh yeah i really wanted to
stream so it's been a few days and it
felt like really wrong
not to stream for those couple of days
i am very happy that i didn't fall
behind
i was actually relieved yeah i was
relieved thank you guys for the support
everyone
everyone who shared uh the little video
and so on
um what oh my gosh fine i should have
read the instructions whatever uh what
what's up
she's so angry chill oh what's up
what are you doing give me your recipe
making a
[Music]
you already know yes i know who do you
think i am
i even built like a restaurant in
another
i mean yes
i was yeah so sad you already knew i was
all set to blow your mind
since we know let's share the recipe for
everyone else i've already got another
recipe to share with everyone else now i
got two
oh damning i hope someone takes them off
of my hands boob house
obviously i know how to make a boob
house they're gonna
her room looks cute unlike the the
furniture she used
if i wouldn't know how to make a
birdhouse how would you guys survive
right so this should then be the house
of the crocodile sun
yeah but gail is out right now so we can
check it out okay
um okay so yeah
uh that's my two new uh villages
and we got the clothing shop nice too
nice progress
oh you're doing yoga now
[Music]
or like weight training we oh yeah oh
yeah do you even lift bro
oh yeah she's lifting but we look kind
of similar now i'm also super pink now
us okay fit gail hell yeah
and then uh did you guys you guys did
see that that one i showed
did i at this villager no way
[Music]
this villager i i didn't show on my on
my public stream
but i showed on twitter right
i did show that villager on my twitter
and i was like i don't want him but then
i changed my mind and now i'm really
happy that he's there
so let's say hello
[Music]
oh
everyone's so surprised to talk to me
yeah you finally talked to me i keep
meaning to say hi but you always seem so
busy
i'm sorry we gotta hang out and get deep
into snacks sometime
yeah i'm sorry i was on the vacation
with callie you know
no let me give you a recipe what's up uh
who do you want this
that sound was cute what are you giving
me i got some stuff
benedict our brother yes you it's you
guys brother
i can't give him the recipes does he
also already
let me give you the recipes okay wait
sorry
i have to give you something though i
have to give you something because
otherwise this is just sad
being like i got something for you and
then being like oh never mind
how about what should we give him like a
a fish
or a rose
or wheats or one of these things
why should we give him fruit why
he can get those out about on his own
anytime or
orange rose weed snack
let's give him this
orange
[Music]
wait since when did you say ooh all the
time i feel like that i never heard that
before
anyway bye bye at first i didn't like
his look
quite much wait wait wait guys wait
we should wait can you give villagers a
present only once per day
you should give him the t-shirt because
that's the reason why i don't like him
it's because of the t-shirt
i want to give him the kfp t-shirt yes
damn it next time guys remind me to give
him the kfp t-shirt soon
how's it going dude is good
do you want this can i give you the
recipe
hi everyone knows those freaking recipes
well you also get a rose
they probably smell better than i do wow
you just yourself
i'm going to usually eat the flower
style but i'll make an exception for
these fingertips
[Music]
oh was kind of more excited about that
but okay
finally okay okay now let's check out
who is here at
our tent show
[Music]
we're
up until now i've been quite busy with
my villagers so let's see what we got
close your eyes close your eyes
[Music]
dude
oh
so
can i
[Music]
i don't like him
can i just use my mouth tickets and get
someone from an
island or do i have to get that tense
guy because it's the first one that
visits me in a tent
on the campsite give him a chance no
it looks boring
you can ignore him ryan i can ignore him
you need to check out it
you have to get him
really
you gotta take the first camper on the
[Music]
island
i don't have to eh which one is it
first camper or the restaurant moving
that's what i fought
oh my god
[Music]
i don't wanna it takes so much time to
like get rid of uh
a villager right it's good
i thought of a simple way to train my
fingers but writing letters and by
writing layers i can correspond with you
and while giving
my digits a workout at the same time my
hands are going to be incredibly
muscular
oh i got fan mail guys
cute
i'll get rid of him eventually when i
can
i don't want him he looks boring i mean
he might grow on me like the
like the chicken did but
he's happy wait when when now what does
he have to say about that
what does he have to say about that
let's let's ask let's ask the tanuki
what he got to say
[Music]
no
no no no i don't have to yeah but that
sounded like
let's let's try to go to
to to an island
let's see let's see if we have a
villager on an island
reset your island and get a new camper
what you want me to reset my whole game
again
that's just crazy if you want progress
you have to do it i'll go just up like a
public obligatory really oh yeah hey
updated my house i i i did some stuff
so yeah a big surprise big surprise
uh there has never been a animal
crossing member stream so no one no one
knows what this looks like this is
totally new
he got to this haul
i got a pet i got a doggy dog he looks
real because there's a pet bat right
next to him
[Music]
bum
let's look at my kitchen so addictive
addictive look at that i'm trying to
make this kitchen look
kind of like like um like a fast food
booth like american style
thingy i need if anyone does anyone have
another one of those yellow couches
if yes please bring it to me
does anyone have one of those i want
more
i love the rare open side is it looking
pretty cute and cute right
also this is the table and chair saddles
looking really cute yep i have the whole
side
wow there's so many who have it i do
like
oh so many of you do give it to me
i want to have an american diner here oh
yeah it's not like you see how i have
cake here
is there also like burger or something
like that that you can put on the table
i wonder mmm burger oh
i want a burger right now
well can i turn on though i wonder if i
can turn on them
why is it done
[Music]
okay next room
bathroom
look my bathroom this is why i missed
you i missed you too
look this is my bathroom dump
look at that oh my god it's so dramatic
it is so
aesthetic and so dark and so so
rich so fancy
it's always raining and thundering in
it's just it's just automatically it was
just i was just chilling you know
i was chilling and then we have my
bedroom
i need more stuff for my bedroom i need
more
but now that we're here we can set uh
that wait
do we already have the clothes that we
purchased
or do they come tomorrow
do we already have it because she didn't
put it into my inventory
wait i want to set the one that i'm
wearing right now
yeah oh hell yeah that's a
that's an amazing outfit
okay see i have a shirt that says money
also i like this shirt but i don't have
any uh this dress it's so simple and so
cute but i don't have any fitting
shoes you guys are gonna bring me more
shoes i want more shoes
anyway they didn't have the clothes
today that they
um wait don't wait i did i did wait i'm
getting confused i did
use the money shirt no i use it when i
sleep
look this is my random room i don't know
what i'm going to do with this yet but
i got this super cute working diy bench
it's so cute i didn't know that there's
like
such cute benches where you can work out
it's so cute
come on
i got the moon too i don't know i'm
probably gonna
like get rid of it eventually because
like i
it doesn't it doesn't fit but yeah
also we can have make some music here
[Music]
beautiful
that means listen up it's what you want
me coming in tonight for ya
i can't get the song out of my head
recently
i don't know why which reminds me guys
i read actually i did go through the
marshmallows again today because now i
had time so before the stream i actually
went for the marshmallows that you guys
sent me even though my manager
already sorted them out for me and sent
them over to me but i did go for them
and um i saw this like two
two questions asked me if
or like asked kelly if wait why am i
naked by the way
asked tally if
if she sampled me in her new song
and since it was two questions i got
really curious
and i i listened to the song and
apparently in the first five seconds
and i heard it too i heard it too
and now listen i can hear kelly in my in
the back of my head
in the first five seconds of her new
song
it sounds like me in the background
saying can't get a key
right i never noticed stuff until now
but you guys told me
yeah blue sky wallpaper thank you for
that
in the ending as well it's also in the
beginning though i didn't listen to the
uh if it's in the ending too but um
honestly i don't know i don't know even
to me it sounds like me
so i'm not sure maybe it is me maybe not
we gotta we gotta ask
callie oh i have the basement now wait i
don't think i put anything in the
basement yet
oh yeah oh basement is a virgin
now it's time to make this into the
usual room right
so what do i have uh what useful do i
have
and i okay we need we need we need it to
look
horrible scary
um yes perfect
i think i got that actually from by
myself from uh that lady that sells
uh wallpapers and and floors
i got this one and i was like this is
absolutely perfect this is exactly what
i want oh yeah and then this
this is the usual
it's so perfect because you wouldn't
even want to get out of yourself
you'll get here if you do some or
if you write some stupid comments
or if you send empty red super chats
you're ending up in here
got it okay what else can we put here
unfortunately i have no legal lego is
there a lego in the game
what's here what do i have that's
terrifying
oh what the
this is only close uh nothing
i don't have anything that's terrifying
i need more terrifying items for the
usual room
is that is it plasma ball terrifying
probably not
the ring maybe the ring is terrifying in
some way oh wait this yes yes
i got that yeah i wanted to put that in
here it's an unfinished puzzle guys
you know about the puzzle of the one
million pieces in the usual room but one
piece is missing
there god
some stupid comments you too you are
also going into the usual room
i don't have so many cells i have one
two three four
five six seven eight nine
10 11 12 13 14
15. i only have 15.
the puzzle is unfinished not the
unfinished puzzle
huh so
are you guys ready to behave now will
you behave
no one wants to go in here hey i don't
think you guys want to go in here
this is horrible oh my god actually
makes a different sound when you walk
into the lavas
i don't know what to say with this red
super chat okay well that sounds honest
enough i will i will
give you the chance and and the benefit
of the doubt and you're allowed to stay
outside of the usual room i can't even
walk over the puzzle that's funny
even though it's so flat
oh my god ah that hurts me
wait no i'm gonna have phoenix lava
i will just itches a little bit
now let's just zoom
i love that oh my god you see like even
that animation
of like like a little like lava
thingies cool
i like this this is beautiful what a
beautiful unusual you guys are welcome
to give me more
um terrifying items that will keep
people
uh good enough that they they
they don't challenge this and don't come
into here
what i can't even speak english anymore
i can't speak english
okay that's my that's my update on my
how my house looks recently okay well
last time we do we can clean up
um although there is one question guys
how long will i stream today because
i gotta say for some reason maybe it's
because i didn't stream for a few days
my voice feels
my throat hurts a little bit
[Music]
hey four hours eight hours five hours
i know you guys look at this magical oh
my god that's so cool oh look at this
oh my god but i won't use it because i
i already have a cute bed
i want the plants though end it now when
spring
it's already been an hour well that's
crazy i'm gonna go for a little bit
longer
let's see how much content animal
crossing gives us today
thank you
i don't know what to do with that but i
i want the
the the hats too the magic hat
but i also want to sell you some stuff
floor uncomfortable
room it resists irresistible round road
fight the power
[Music]
wait why is the room irresistible why
but the floor is uncomfortable why why
why
just don't come here just don't go there
it's not good for you you don't want to
be there believe me
trust me trust me
oh okay uh
desert towering when when where did i
get that
i didn't
keep it
okay so
i need to use your room why
you guys are just specialistic that's so
weird but but you guys
you guys should be more like taking care
of yourselves
in the usual room you can't do
trust me it's better outside
okay we got the hat guys awesome do we
want that
i actually actually mean kelly slept in
i guess not exactly that we slept on the
floor on the mattress
in our in our second hotel and it was
kind of like a hoot on but not exactly
it was a very fancy place so and i know
it sounds weird when i say on the
mattress on the floor but it was very
fancy very beautiful
um
does it make it a futon even if we're
sleeping on the
proper matches this is not it was a
thick mattress
i wonder if that is still a futon
because if that is considered a futon
thank you i do i do enjoy sleeping
on the mattress on the floor that's
pretty pretty comfortable actually
[Music]
let's see uh oh
that looks cute but not exactly what i
want
oh wait that's why do i have that in my
inventory why did i
why did i buy that i never bought that
what the hell
did didn't villager give that oh wait no
wait wait where did i get that from
does someone know what's that
tall garden rock
that's lame what is that thank you for
[Music]
watching
selling that i'm selling it
and told me i gotta get rid of that
stick
pull away cause it's annoying i keep on
like using it
[Music]
and selling the helmet by the way and
selling
this one okay
[Music]
all right what else can we do guys
what else can we i guess
i wanted to try flying to another island
and seeing if i can find the villager
there
but do i really have to get that tent
guy
do i really have to get your gold
[Music]
can i really yes
but will do i still have to talk to him
or was that
one time talk enough
was that enough and is it if i go to an
island now
will there even is there even a chance
to get
a villager
[Music]
or is there not gonna be anyone because
i'm still like in the beginning of the
game
i need to talk to him i think he's still
upset
yeah she's just kind of lame to be
honest yeah that's what i found
oh it's my first time perhaps inviting
yada no
i don't want him
[Music]
impression yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
no please no
i'm the vip manager beats
good time
[Music]
wait is his is his thing that he speaks
a bunch of languages
because he spoke italian before
and now he speaks german what's going on
is that what he does he uses like all
kinds of uh different
greetings visible confusion
[Music]
is he like a european goat he's a
classic european
yeah i need to understand
[Music]
oh my god that's funny but i
i don't think that's what he's trying to
do i don't think he's trying to do a pun
jagot speaks german
[Music]
okay well i guess we have him for a
while but he'll get kicked out
eventually he got replaced
[Music]
i don't like him i mean i like how he
speaks a bunch of languages that's fun
who wants that who wants that scooty
scooty wants to talk to me wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait
scooty give him a chance i already gave
benedict a chance and that's okay
benedict is cool
does he did he want to talk to me
oh hey he wants to leave
do i have to like help them i guess i
was being stubborn and the competitor
and me just didn't want to back down i
got a gift to make a mad spot well even
a big tough guy like me can't get nearby
oh
[Music]
i hope i'm not taking advantage of your
generosity no way
i'll i'll give it to her and say it's
for me
[Music]
yes i'm on my way what does it do
should i open it i can open it
when i open it it's probably gonna be
mine right
oh my god is that is it like if i open
it
then it's mine and then
mission is failed
no i'm not open i want to give it to her
but i'm curious what is
what's inside don't you dare didn't
you could never do that to school it
wasn't i said it's curious what's inside
yes i am obsessed with your place but
yeah i got something for you
take it what do you say
[Music]
why is no one giving me presents
she
[Music]
oh wait is he in love with you oh
oh
i can see that i can see how he would be
in love with her she's really cute she's
like the new villager
and on the island who looks really cute
really fancy and fashionable
um the member stream bus wait are you
saying that are you saying that
because i said i want presents too are
you referencing to
me receiving a ton of presents from
my viewers or anyone that's true i guess
that is i guess true
but i mean like
that's not what i mean
[Music]
i already got every single fruit on my
island duh
that's useless look at it i have
everything that i want
to need okay let's go aggressive fishing
no no no no no
come on come on
aggressive fishing is not very good i
can't recommend it
[Music]
i cannot recommend it i gotta fish
normally
i'm sure that will work out
[Music]
so guys what did you miss most while i
was gone
about me what did you miss most about me
being gone
tell me
everything that's a stupid answer
that's that's not an answer give
me a little bit more effort
your voice okay that's something tangent
that's also a good answer
your smile oh your energy your humor
your eyes your bloody hair oh
my sanity you missed your sanity oh you
got it back now
your company jrpg suffering streams
i can't get this face
okay bottom left energy
why not see what this one is
they have to miss that that's a cute
answer 10 out of 10 answers
10 out of 10.
an olive flounder he had that one before
apparently
too bad wait wait a second do i have my
swimsuit with me
no there's one time that i want to go
into the water i don't have it
actually today's stream really might not
be that long because i gotta get up
early tomorrow again for the next stream
kind of sad because it's been a while
but also there's
generally not so much to do
uh in one animal crossing stream anyway
i mean i could i could get started on
like decorating and
the whole island and making like like
ground patterns and stuff
but i'm not prepared for that i don't i
i i'm not i don't want to do that just
yet
oh god
i can't yeah i
[Music]
it's like my my voice is my voice is not
er
my voice hasn't been used much in the
past
few days so
much i'm just a bit tired thank you for
the rest of my shot oh
you're like donating for the people
again that's so sweet of you
could you please donate for
like a better fishing rod because i'm
too stupid to get
that stupid oh maybe now come on
why did i pull it back why did i
after
[Music]
do i already have that butterfly i think
yes
there's barely any butterflies that i
that are flying around
in the winter yeah i had that one before
[Music]
close your eyes really no i can totally
do it normally i don't know what's uh
wrong with me during this stream i'm
just like focused on other things i can
totally do it though
i can't i can't fish i can't fish
that's no problem look i'll show you
i really miss your stream since become
routine to spend some time with you and
everyone
thank you i'm so happy to hear that
thank you i miss you guys so it's
definitely become a routine for me as
well
although i mean it's definitely also
good to not stream if
not that stream for a few days it had it
had its um
its benefits too i definitely had some
kind of like
um detox i guess
yeah like a social media detox not
exactly i mean i was obviously
i was obviously still a lot on on
twitter and stuff
anyway it's just okay because otherwise
i wouldn't be able to calm down
i need to check on social media because
otherwise i'm just so worried about
what's like
what's what's happening you know what am
i missing
give me that big fish come on come on
anything are you watching this
for the shitty adventures only shoot the
fish i've already gotten all those
fishies
they're all useless i already have all
of those
give me something new is there
anything anything that i didn't get yet
in this season that i could get because
i feel like no
you'll get a better one next time i
believe in you gianna i don't believe in
it though
i don't
um kiana can i bring you items ah today
today i'm not taking visitors maybe
i i wanna i wanna oh i wanna do a
stream where i'm like actually
dedicating
the stream to visiting islands or like
having people visit me
i wanna like plan it beforehand
what is it i'm so hungry dog
i'm so hungry guys i need to eat my
bento
i bought i bought a tadekatsu
bento bento bento
hare
i don't think you do it's like rice with
katsu
on it and with taro's tare sauce
um
the thank you for the red super chat by
the way
thank you very kind of you i'll i will
try
probably to read super chats this theme
i hope so
100 dollars of cave stuff because i like
this bird can't make the moon
oh thank you stocks oh yes
get those get those stocks best decision
of your life i promise you oh also thank
you for all right super chat yeah
how'd you finally back i like to i like
to give you my heart as a present
your heart that's so sweet but then
you'll die
[Music]
don't don't give your heart to me give
me your love your love is enough for me
you don't get how you don't have to give
me your heart
thank you though
[Music]
okay so i invited you stupid goat
now tell me what's next
[Music]
unfortunately he wants to live here
yes i take it i take it thank you
[Music]
thank you so sweet what
flirt
thank you i love you too but don't get
me wrong i love all of you
so don't get the wrong idea i love all
of you but i love you too
i love you thank you for the support
amazing
okay but do i also have to pay money for
that stupid home
[Music]
okay yeah okay good i think i don't have
to spend money on this one
for once but once i don't have to pay
for it
unbelievable
[Music]
thank you friend that sounds like
something callie would say
why you changed your name though you
changed it back to tacoma shipper well
finally
finally i guess the usual room really
worked on you huh
it did its job it's magic
[Music]
uh you know where the unpopular uh
villagers go
i know where the unpopular villagers go
they go up here
[Music]
your free education yes he finally got
that re-education thank you for the red
super jack
thank you thank you so much
[Music]
you see you guys really had an urge to
super chat
because i was gone it wasn't even gone
for that long but you guys are trying to
pay your your
your uh your uh income right
now your income i can't your salary
you're paying me your salary thank you
guys
perfect
a perfect example of a perfect employee
i must say
what you never read super chat welcome
back my queen kindly
bring the broken i'm sponsoring them
with the super chats glory to the kp
yo big ups to the broke gang
thank you guys so much for the support
wait no that's not the right spot
why can't it i need it to be like same
position as the one below i
was also getting so hungry oh my god
yes thank you for the red super chat
thank you for your support you guys are
amazing
how how do i even deserve all this oh my
god
okay uh maybe actually it should have
maybe been one
one more back but oh my whatever this
will do
this will do okay so he can live up
there
and i will just never make a bridge and
i will never make
an elevation thingy to go up there
[Music]
ah one of the kfp buddies oh
hey link benedict has a crush on you
i guess you gotta come back eventually
and bring me some more presents
on that uh occasion
get your presents ready wherever that
link
guy was benedict has a thing for you
would you like to go on a date with
benedict
you cannot say no we don't want to see
benedict cry
hey listen why did you guys write as if
you were
are you guys are you guys role-playing
as cali today
why why
oh wait no hey that's something that
kelly says but it's also something that
navi says i guess so oh wait
hey listen it's a very big difference
from hey listen
oh my god callie
is like an aggressive
like a really aggressive nappy
hey she does say that a lot
she does say it a lot doesn't she
[Music]
that's funny oh my god let's sell all
these stupid fish
and uh let's check out the
oh the fossils
don't make it yeah it's like hey listen
don't make it weird exactly exactly
she always does it hey listen and then
she then she uh swallows
some some uh stuff in her mouth
i'm just trying to say but that's not
much booker of english what's
up what's uh saliva and she swallows us
i just hey listen i'm just saying i'm
just saying this is how she usually does
it
just stop making it quick
i'm just trying to impress the jelly
okay
how do you pronounce it though
she goes yeah yeah that's the same thing
with gulping it's the same thing as
swallowing your saliva note saliva
saliva ah ah saliva
[Music]
i'm so hungry yeah she's like
okay but how does she
how does she do that she's like hey
now listen
and then what what what was again don't
make it weird
now listen
don't make it weird now birdie
don't get it twisted oh yes you don't
say that a lot too
do not get it twisted
oh my god she got those phrases that she
always says wait
do i also have
do i also have some phrases that you
guys would use if you would impersonate
how would you guys impersonate me
tell me now tell me now in the chat try
to try to impersonate me
do it
eh
yo guys impersonations suck
that's all you can do that's all you can
come up with
you're not doing me justice
not maybe there's just maybe i just
don't have
phrases like that that i use all the
time i mean except kkk but that's just
my
greeting in the beginning
eh i feel like i i do
like i probably do no iron and biome
well that's just words that's just like
single words that i pronounce weirdly
but is there no
to the usual room hmm
[Music]
don't send empty recipes yeah that
that's something that's something yes
yes yes yes
yes yes
speaking in japanese southern german
language
[Music]
bottom left noises but that just sucks
you gotta give me like concrete
traces
concrete wait
it doesn't make sense in english because
in german
we say concrete and
wait what do you say that in english
yeah it's not only the the the flooring
the concrete flooring right okay okay
okay okay for a moment i was like what
the hell what the hell am i saying
wait what
you cute ow i got some stuff for you
what do you think about these things
more than one hmm
but you know what lovers it's kind of
rude that i'm giving and giving and
giving and giving and you're taking and
taking and taking and taking
when will you finally give something to
me
will you ever give me something back for
my efforts
no right i'm starting to doubt
your honor as an
owl
you're a blabbers is a freaking scammer
we all love scammers just ask
we all love blabbers because just
blabbers looks so cute but
we are all getting like betrayed by him
he's scabbing us
he's just doing his job huh
he's just making donations and donations
and donations
he's not doing he's not filling up his
stupid museum
by himself at all it's just all me
you're all useless useless hey i don't
say that that often
cutely talking sudden you gotta be more
concrete
that's just like
that sucks yeah aren't you hungry you
should eat something or you'll get
occur what what
[Music]
i pay back i have
thank you trevor
okay i will forgive blabbers because you
paid for him
but you gotta tell him that this is not
okay
it shouldn't be other house paying it
should be blabbers paying
but for real though ah
that sounds like something i do say
sometimes
also thank you for the red super chat d
love also your hiker sucks i i i didn't
say that that often i just say that
sometimes when you
when your haiku actually sucks but what
that's not my fault what can i do if
your haiku sucks
huh what can i do about that
[Music]
this stream is chill isn't it
it's pretty damn chill here
oh my god
oh the red super just keep on coming
thank you nancy keyboard
that sucks do i say that a lot but
that's just two words i want like
longer phrases oh you guys are how do
you say
mispronounce this word oh neck crack
what was i talking about
sapphire kitten
that's the 10th attention that's me
that's literally me that's the tenna
everybody give
give it up for that by kitten give give
sapphire kitten and ten out of ten come
on
oh damn
i thank you for the membership but this
is okay
you have me
oh yeah i cracked my neck a lot kelly
does that too though by the way
i think it's very funny while we were on
vacation
we both would like so often
crack our necks like she would crack oh
and then then i would be like
i feel like we connected with our neck
cracks
i felt so connected what are you eating
now wait
you're eating a sandwich you're always
eating eat something
wait that makes sense because you say
hey snacking or something like that
let's just keep running and doing
another snack yeah okay that makes sense
lay it on me oh
lay it on me lay it on me
lay your sandwich on me do it
do it lay
yes and i don't give a about your
[Music]
laid on goats just laid on me wait
how does that says it's not the lyrics i
think but still
okay well guys i don't know what else to
do today on this island
what do you have in your hand now you
also have a snack
what's in your hands
why do i have to do all the digging
decorate your home
i already did i need more items for the
usual room
i'm glad i was able to fix things thank
you thanks to you
[Music]
in this topic i feel bad like when i was
uh outside before the stream getting
that converter plug
i i you know this is kind of weird like
i'm kind of paranoid
um but i would say that there is that
it makes sense to be paranoid because in
japan whole life is very popular right
so i sometimes feel like people are
maybe looking at me because they
maybe think they know who i am
so yeah so i was in this shopping mall
and i was out just vlogging and this and
this guy really tried
to quickly catch up to me and
and i just felt like he was following me
but he he probably wasn't he's pro he
probably probably wasn't following me
because quickly like i would okay let's
say this is the dude
and not that not the stalker dude but by
the never dude so i
i was walking and walking and walking
and i looked behind to see if that other
dude
was still following me and then i i kind
of um step
stepped on on the foot of the guy in
front of me who had nothing to do with
it
so i i turned around and i'm like oh my
god i'm so sorry i hope this thing
wasn't the same
and he looks at me like super angry and
looks like he's like
in such huge pain like he has never ever
experienced before like he's just
he just fell into some lava or something
and he looks at me like
like super angry and says
he's like ah whatever it's and i'm like
okay i'm so
i'm so sorry that i kept on moving i was
like i was really trying to really be
really really nice like
i i really don't wanna didn't want to
step on him but i was trying to look
if i was being stalked or something i'm
so sorry he was so mad
but i honestly have to say it looks like
he was like overreacting just because he
was mad that some girl stepped on his
[Music]
foot
oh come on no way it didn't hurt that
much he was acting as if like
i don't know someone like took an axe
and like
smashed it into his knee or something
lucky dude lucky guy
i would have said thanks oh man he was
like being really dramatic but and he
didn't accept my apology and he was like
off
i'm sorry i fell i felt really bad about
that
honestly because he didn't i would have
felt better if he would have been like
oh oh there's over this uh
he was in pain he could have like said
it a little bit differently
so i need a slingshot hey wait how do i
open that
yep need a slingshot quickly
quick
what is that it's a weird looking
slingshot
i wish i was his foot
where's the present where's the present
where's the present guys where is it
i don't hear it anymore did i miss it
[Music]
ah they do spawn if you go inside the
house ah
okay oh well i got a slingshot for next
time then
okay guys i i think
i think i'll leave it here and i'll read
super chat because um
yeah i want to get this uh
over with because my voice hurts and i'm
really hungry
well how much how many super chats do we
have to read though
i have to read from the minecraft stream
too right
it could i feel like that yeah i feel
like that might
take a little while
that that might take too long
because i gotta sleep for the next
stream
but i don't want to leave you guys so
soon because i haven't talked to you
guys for
so long i want some one-on-one time with
you
okay i'm not gonna read super chats but
i'm gonna give you like some one-on-one
time is that okay
tacoma collapse because we have two
collabs uh
back to back in a row and after
like at the uh the second one and once
we're done with the main part then i'll
just uh
say goodbye to cali and i'll continue
reading the super chats
tomorrow okay okay okay
so yeah let's go over here
i think that's the wrong chat too right
just like in the beginning
damn it let me just let me switch to
this this one
here we go what color are your panties
but in japanese
hey i only say that in honor talk
i don't say that just out of nowhere
wait there's no bgm right that's awkward
let's turn on some bgm moves
yeah sorry that today was kind of short
uh
i think i still need to kind of get back
into
you know the whole thing
[Music]
now don't worry about it you'll be back
to form soon and now thank you guys
it's okay take your time thank you don't
stress about it plus it was fun thank
you
i asked myself if casper the room party
i honestly i want it too
also you're mentioning some really yummy
food again
from from really some really yummy
australian food damn
guys you wanna you you wanna know when
when small
knowledge about the trip that's kind of
cute but i'll give you
i'll give you one little thing because
most of the things i will talk about
tomorrow the trip all the trip knowledge
will be discussed tomorrow uh but i'll
give you one thing
i you guys know how i buy this german
chocolate in japan
because i'm just so so so so so so picky
when it comes to chocolate i always want
to eat you know my australian
or my german chocolate from europe and
there's some shops that sell that in
japan
so anyway i brought my my my german i
brought a rita spot
maybe you guys know that was the small
and it was not not small they also have
them in big i guess but it's um
chocolate and i brought um a bunch of
those
on my trip because i was like ah i might
i might want to eat some good chocolate
somewhere during this trip so i'm
bringing this along
so we arrived in our hotel and
i i opened my suitcase and i put out my
stuff and i put it where it belongs and
then i
get the chocolate and i put it uh like
next to my bed
so that i can you know see it and and
it's like ready whenever i need it
now there were like 10 pieces in there
and so callie asks me
if that was like she sees it and she's
like is that from the hotel and i say no
no no
i brought chocolate you know because i
need my german chocolate and then i
waited a few seconds and she's like oh
okay
and i waited and i waited in a few
seconds and then i realized wait a
second
that sounded like she wants some so i
offer him like cali count you can have
one if you want
and she's like oh thank you she got
really excited
and she he really seemed like she wanted
one
so she eats one and and she's like oh my
god this is so good and i'm like yeah
yeah i'm glad you like it because it's
like from germany it's my like i really
recommend in this one like
i'm glad you like my my my chocolate i'm
so proud of it
so yeah she ate it and then she actually
she went for another one later
okay so that that's for that first day
right you you would think that it ends
there but basically
for this whole trip i think it was like
four days
or five days every day she ate my
chocolate
and i haven't eaten a single one which
is totally fine because i just wasn't
craving anything
but every day she would at some point
ask me oh
kiara can i can i have one of your
chocolates again and i'm like oh yeah
sure
go ahead like in the morning in the
evening in the middle of the day
like today today in the morning we woke
up and we skipped
breakfast because we we wanted to sleep
like a tiny bit longer
so we skipped breakfast and then we got
up later and then and then
our you know we didn't eat anything but
she asked me again
kiana can i have one of your chocolates
again
and i'm like hell he has to go ahead
she got really hooked on my chocolate
yeah she did
and she really likes my german
chocolates
i'm so glad she appreciates them
liked it really and then i told her
where to get it
and then today actually when we were on
our way to
um to our airport uh
we found the store where uh it sells
those chocolates it's actually called
plaza and they have it all over japan
and and we went in there and i showed
her some more german chocolates
and she bought she bought some lint
chocolate
she's really into it
[Music]
is too happy about this this tiny little
story
already makes her so happy
for some reason i had no craving for
chocolate which is really
rare but yeah i'm glad she ate it
[Music]
has
um
there's one more that that they sell
there that i also really can
recommend um sorry
sorry i i i blocked the microphone
[Music]
it
let me tell my japanese viewers what to
get
no regrets oh wait just save it
a cup and got an earworm from the
bubblegum track
milk is good so yeah but at the moment
they don't have milka
in that store unfortunately very sad
they had it for a while but now they got
rid of it again they keep on
changing uh the stuff that they have
i don't call it okay it's tonight
one show one second
maybe this one
save image there we go okay now this
should work
tada oh deka it's so big this one is so
good
forgotten
japanese bros this one is so good it's
so yummy
i love it like every time when i'm at
that store
they they sell these as like single ones
so every time i'm there i'll like grab
all of them that they have in stock
because it's just like a single one so i
and they don't have that money anyway
so grab all of them and just buy all of
them
say if you go to that store and you
don't see any of these it might be
because i have just
raided the store and bought all of them
yeah the milk one is especially good
this one they have it without the milk
as well but the milk one is even better
yes
um
any other story that i have for you guys
that i want to tell you now
no i tell you everything tomorrow
tell you everything tomorrow
tomorrow first stream that i uh the
first one i already reserved thank you
for the red super chat
[Music]
the first one i already reserved uh is
the one where we answered the
marshmallow questions that you guys sent
me
us actually we'll answer them together
it's not an off collab yeah it's not
unfortunately uh i wanted to
i wanted to do the takamori day but i
figured that it would be difficult to
like
if we do it through like the whole
japanese day
then well it's good for our time zone
but it's not good for you guys that's
why i ended up not doing the takamori
day like 3d
free streams on one day uh we decided to
do uh the shrek movie watch long
sometime uh
soon next week because i felt like if we
started 12 japanese standard time
now that's good for america but after
like two streams
it will be so late for other time zones
that you guys would have to pull an
all-nighter
and i didn't want you guys to have to do
that i wanted everyone to see like every
of those streams
so yeah that's how it turned out
[Music]
yes yes yes very considerate yeah
of course you guys gotta be able to come
to your shifts after all
tomorrow that's those two streams and
then i will prepare
after that after those two streams i
have to prepare for the stream on sunday
because i'm making chocolate on sunday
i'm making a valentine's day chocolate
because it's kind of like a tradition
thing in
japan the girls make chocolate eh
like on their own for their crush
so i'm making that yeah i'll actually be
using a camera
so you you guys can see like you know
how ha tama does her cooking streams
i'll i'll try my best to um show you
guys what i'm actually doing
i don't i don't think there will be much
action because i'm just making chocolate
but i mean who knows i'll probably
up anyway
because i never did that before i
actually never did that before
[Music]
yo
um
[Music]
i'll get my stuff all in front of my um
a pc and hopefully i can do everything
in on my pc i might i might have to run
down a few times to put like
stuff into the fridge and but yeah
generally it will happen
at my pc
but i'll basically use you
i'm not gonna make it from zero from
scratch obviously i'll use i'll use
like uh chocolate that you um can work
with
to make something else out of it and
then i'll make i'm not sure what to make
actually
i could make like pralines with some
some cute decorations
or i could make muffins or so but i
don't know
or like cookies i could make chocolate
cookies maybe
i haven't decided yet
[Music]
i've been thinking because kelly likes
the german chocolate so much
if i can somehow use the
german chocolate but it's not like
actually souls to be
used for like making something out of it
but maybe i can use it anyway
i want to use the german chocolate
because obviously i'm making the
chocolate for
italian obviously
[Music]
chocolate
gotta make chocolate that kelly likes
yeah yeah yeah
one of the things that i i was really
surprised with
during this trip one one of the things i
found out about her and
we will talk more about this tomorrow
but i know
[Music]
it
she said she's for real she's a queen
symbol now what is that it's someone who
who likes food very much who appreciates
food very much who likes to eat food
a lot she just appreciates food so much
and all kinds of food metta cuisine
she's a foodie yeah she is
that was so new to me i didn't i didn't
know that until this trip because like
she was
she's a huge foodie yeah and she's
really passionate about food that she
has eaten in the past
oh man i can't stop myself okay last
before before i get too much into these
stories last last little thing
and then we'll stop it there and we
gotta we gotta keep those stories for
tomorrow
she's so passionate about food that
she's eaten in the past like when we
arrived
when we arrived at the place where we
were which i'm gonna tell you guys
tomorrow
she she was like yeah please please
please today
today we gotta go to this place we're
gonna there's this one place where it
was like two years ago
and and this this soup curry was so so
so good i really gotta go there again i
really wanna want the soup korean
she was so passionate about it she was
she really wanted this soup curry
that she ate like two years ago
she really wanted it and that was not
the only thing like
the next day the next the next day i'm
like kelly i want to go read ramen and
she said oh yes yes there's this one
place where
i was like two years ago this really
good rallying place let's go there
she kept introducing me to these places
where she was like a million years ago
because she has like this good memory of
those places and she's
she's like she was like really proud of
them she was like those are those are
the this is the best ramen place in in
in the city and this is the best soup
curry place in this city
you gotta you gotta you gotta go there
with me back in the day you know
back in the day back in the day this is
where i went
so i want to share it with you
it was really good the food that uh she
introduced me to was really really good
yeah
yeah yeah it was very nice it was a
really
really nice trip with her more details
tomorrow don't miss it
okay thank you captain jelly for another
red super chat give kelly the new kfp
two-ton chicken bucket with 11 herbs of
spices uh
and our new spicy reaper dipping sauce
i'm sure wait are you like um putting
like
uh other viewers names into that isn't
that like someone's name
it's sponsored by sample katie
flickering light bulb and i love kiara
ah
you like donating so many super chats
that's so sweet
thank you wow
wow wow so generous thank you so much
that's kisses for us katie mumma
flickering light bulb puma
and i love kiara thank you guys
congratulations on being sponsored
i got i got so much oh my god oh my god
face oh guys i can't wait to tell you
about
the near-death experience
it's so funny because i love the reply
when you guys said aren't you always
near
in the near death experience when you're
next to cali that was so funny
but no it's not like that i actually i
actually had an accident
accident but i'll tell you about that
tomorrow
are you okay now yeah but it hurts still
it still hurts after uh how many days
has it been three days
has been like three days but it still
hurts
yeah yeah spoilers
[Music]
that was uh actually i really thought i
was gonna die
it could it could have gone much worse i
could have broken something
could have broken my leg or something
it still hurts yeah but it's getting
better it hurts
i think less than yesterday yeah yeah
in the beginning it it even hurt when i
was like
when when the the spot was being touched
by my sweater or something
i'm a phoenix you always wanted to break
a bone it's not so funny now huh
yeah i did say this before didn't i
you have a good memory memory i did say
before that i always wanted to like
break something because i
never in my whole life i've never broke
something
and i just want to break something for
once and have you know
a cast that people can write on i really
want it
and i was getting so close to it today
and not today
the other day um
honestly that situation was so crazy
that was so insane
that was so crazy can't wait to tell you
guys
i have broken my wrists not any sort of
i'm not you all say it's not
fun but it's not worth it yet i let me
laugh yeah
i want to break something too
it's pretty nice to like
have people worry about you
[Laughter]
although callie was very worried about
me
she was like she actually saw me
yeah yeah she saw me during that
accident
yeah yeah funny i'll tell you more
tomorrow
i can't stop talking about this stuff i
need to i need to i need to stop myself
and you're saying where the muscle is
it's it's not it's not like that i would
i mean obviously i probably wouldn't
enjoy it when it happens but i want the
experience in my life to
at least one time although i want to
break some bones preferably i would like
to break my shoulder because it's
broken anyway and i just want to
get it replaced
topic
oh
[Music]
that's a joint on the bone well
well how about we we ripped a joint out
of there and just put it put a bone in
there maybe it will work better
maybe i wouldn't be in so much pain if
it was a freaking bone another
joint
now honestly my shoulder is so freaking
broken
for years now
yeah the daddy issues oh yeah oh my god
ah okay uh
i'm having fun talking to you guys but
we're gonna end it here so that i'm
ready tomorrow
and um and
we'll have a solo stream again soon on
sunday
there's three collabs coming up and then
one solo
okay the the solo is also very important
because i got a big announcement on
sunday to make
sunday but probably saturday for some of
you for me it's sunday for stuff for you
guys
maybe saturday
night
[Music]
i'm glad to be back though ah i'm so
happy to be back guys
not streaming was nice too but i missed
you guys
ah so nice to see you all happy and
energetic in the comments
very today you and me are so teddy
i missed you mama i missed you too glad
you thought you enjoyed your trip thank
you yeah
it was great it was uh something i've
always wanted to do and
there were some first-time experiences
and um
some really precious memories so
yeah i'm really i'm really glad that i
was able to have that experience of cali
it was a very special trip it was
definitely not just some basic little
trip
it was a it was a very special trip
um
thank you for the membership thank you
welcome
it was so special
we did so many special things in that
short amount of time
my imagination is just running wild
tomorrow and actually not tomorrow like
for me it's today already
in like 11 hours you will get the whole
ah no
in 11 hours is marshmallow in like 13
hours you will get the whole story
okay okay i really gotta go now it's
hard to say goodbye
ah thank you guys for the support though
and thank you so much for waiting for me
and so sorry for the scuff i really
wanted to stream during the
during the vacation i'm so sorry about
that
i even i even brought that i even bought
that little
pink microphone and i i brought my
switch over and all that
i really wanted to stream but yeah
you stream but you stream yeah i did but
like only once and that was super
scuffed i couldn't even stream after we
figured out the solution to our
cardboard disease i wanted
i wanted to move for you guys oh well
um
yeah it's time for some more netflix
time for some more netflix oh you guys
you know one last thing
cause i keep on talking i just don't
want to leave but and
the shrek movie thingy right we only
wanted to watch one originally
but we decided to watch two in a row
next week it will be a marathon
tangent free
we're gonna watch two track movies in a
row
originally we wanted to watch one in in
well while we were in the hotel because
just
you know the time the time yeah it will
be no no it will be an off collab yes
i will i will either visit her or she
will visit me
hmm guys nice guys
nice guys members only everyone who's
not a member close your ears
everyone who's not a member close your
ears
members you know the thing
that i thought i wanted to give her no
don't say it you know the thing i wanted
to give it to her
in person during the the
marshmallow stream right i wanted to do
that
but then we couldn't do it so i was like
i had it i had prepared you know i had
it i was hiding it
i was gonna give it to her but then we
couldn't do the stream so
it didn't work out and then i was i put
it i put it back into my suitcase
because i i was like i want to give it
to her during this trip but i also want
to get her
a reaction for you for you guys i went i
wanted her i wanted to be
on tape you know i wanted to be forever
so
so i i didn't give to her i still didn't
give it
i haven't ready but i still didn't give
it to her so
i'll probably give it to her during the
shrek stream because i still want it to
be like when i meet her on stream
you know no
[Music]
but like it's not it's not even that
special but still
i don't know i just wanted to be on
stream but
i kind of also wanted it to be on my
channel the shrek thing will probably be
on her channel
difficult maybe i should wait until we
do the the takamori
but that's too long that's such a long
time to go but it would be
it would be very fitting because that
takamai karaoke is going to be very like
emotional
and and you know it will be about our
our love and our connection
and our bonds if i give it to her then
it would be very fitting right can i put
my ears back on now
no can i unblock my ears mama no
good timing wait until then okay okay
okay okay
okay now you can turn on your ears
now you can turn them on again yes this
is can it broken listen now yes it is
can i now open my ears yes it is
yes this is
ears back on what happened laughing
lovingly
[Music]
i love you guys i love you
i love the non-members as much as i love
the memories thank you guys
thanks broken thanks you thanks you
thank you broke gang for hanging out
thanks thanks for closing your eyes er
your ears out
thank you for the membership thank you
okay let's go
let's freaking go okay you guys ready
you guys ready to say goodbye to mama
it's time to say goodbye again to mamma
mina
so quick so quick
thank you for the membership you guys
this is why you gotta you gotta cherish
every day every moment every hour every
second
i'm gonna cherish it because it just
disappears so quickly
[Music]
foreign
okay
all right this is ridiculous i i really
miss you guys but this is ridiculous i
gotta say goodbye okay
and in german we stay i'll be dozen
i'll eat my dinner and then sleep
bye bye i'll feed this and see you in
the takamori q a tomorrow
thank you for watching everyone
thank you for coming to my stream at
this
late or early hour
it was nice seeing you again i love you
all thanks for all the support
[Music]
i started
best year of time that that's true yeah
yeah
i'm sorry for not reading the super
chats i'll you know you know me i'll
catch up
very soon and i'll read them very
carefully
thank you all so much me your support
means a lot to me
thank you thank you thank you
bye-bye i keep on i keep on like trying
to make this stream longer and longer
and longer bye-bye i hope you had fun
[Music]
you