Nov. K.
Note: Those
who
[song]
help, just don't know how to sing and their eyes will become tight.
Oh, I know. But I love you very much. I probably will tell you that I love you.
Ah, your child comes home to play Thai and has your grandmother's number.
Come Sita, the goodbye I met eases the
bird's [ __ ], this shocked resident is
also teasing, sadhana house yo, her ears look that way she has.
Dee knew Kanakarn since she didn't come to the officials.
There, I will see you in love. Now I'm broken.   Jai
came to Do Remi and looked at Korat. She didn't give her to Mata.
Kiss,
got Ebola, eyes with different powers, different people.
[Song]
You're okay. I met you just now, but it's Jejo kido that
he got hit by Jai
Danlo.  This block has a small amount of CU, but it will hit the bird.   It's
up to your eyes, it's your heart again. You'll
say I love you.
This one, just look and see, but this little one loves.   If
you like it, you'll
get it. [Song] You'll get a different look. I love you. Haha.   Well, now I'm
crying, I'm sorry to hear that we found Order.
Where is Lek Bird?
She's a chicken but a
child.
You're just us. You have a name that can only be seen by a face.
It's cute and sweet. Okay.
Okay, you're even here, based on
[song]
Dhoni,
this little guy will collect this money by himself,
Doraemon,
timer, timer from the turn
[song]