[Music]
love
K wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait
I um wasn't sure if blue was going to
finish any
assets and then she did but only 30
minutes before the
stream and so before that I was like oh
what am I going to do if she's not going
to put anything up so I just combined
some old assets and and I feel like I
kind of like my look
today so
I think today maybe I'm just going to do
what I put
together look at my eyes doesn't that
look pretty
cool and the hat fits
well just
today
ooh looks like like some sick colored
contacts
Triforce eyes I wonder surely there will
be a
Triforce in this game as well right okay
well I already had a blue screen of
death today so I'm hoping to not get one
today I feel like we might be okay
maybe we'll see those eyes real they're
so
real like when I when I just blink I
don't think it's that noticeable that
they don't close with the eyes but if I
you know go like
this then you see but if I you know if
you don't focus on it also I have
Coca-Cola vanilla I thought I probably
will be
tired so
found Coca-Cola vanilla but what I
really want is
cherry cherry Dr Pepper but this is
okay I haven't had vanilla Coca-Cola in
a while hey hey hey come back come back
why did you disappear hey hey
huh hey Hey listen hey
Hey
Hey Hey
listen going to I'm going to bring it
back whether it likes it or
not wait wait there it
is it's just because I didn't press
a it went into sleepy mode no go away go
away Luigi I'm playing different green
person
game but is it even his game anymore no
link
no finally Justice is being served after
all these years of
[Music]
[Laughter]
misogynism
yeah for justice yeah yeah
can't believe the misogynism man anyway
um I think I'm going to play with this
big uh small
screen
um ah this game has some hilarious
cheese SL skips you can do once you get
some items won't say what exactly but
know that creativity is oh yeah I can
imagine but I would hope that it's not
too too
[Music]
extreme well whether whether you use it
or not in the end is your choice
but
well
whoow the
burpees wait where did the logo go where
did I save the logo
to I'm I'm looking for the logo
I want to put it on the bottom
left and anyway this will be uh full
full playr of the game of course I
always play through the Zelda
games um we're going to play twice this
week I
think it's going to be
fun shut
up and where the hell did I save
that [\h__\h] it I will download the file
again
[Music]
again yeah you don't want spoilers well
play along with me play faster I'm not
going to get that far anyway am I I
don't know uh probably I don't know here
look we have a wa
logo let's
go wa logo and W Zelda art isn't it
amazing where are so prepared for this
playthrough just even the assets that
I'm not using now because I like my
lenses and my hat fitting so well on
this I wish I could I wish I knew how to
change all the blues to Green in this
outfit I wanted to figure that do you
want to do you guys want to go on a
journey of figuring
out how that how that works in obious
change one color in obs
[Music]
eh I don't know it seems Seems
complicated wait Lut
filter
filters oh wait I did
some
H but I'm not
[Music]
sure what does what does what does this
do oh God oh God I'm scared what does
this do oh oh
cool I downloaded these filters at some
point I remember
now
but oh that's pretty cool
too but that's not what I want I want
H that's black and
white that's
grayscale that's the OG
[Music]
H like I can probably get yeah
go oh that looks not as terrifying over
there
I I think I know what I could
do if
I copy
[Music]
paste
myself put myself under
myself can I fill myself with a
color can I fill myself
with h I guess that oh that would work
and then because I filtered out the blue
if I oh but I well because the copy
paste
oh it will apply it to
both not sure how to make it so that it
applies it only to one
yeah this is this is character creative
okay I want to be more
[Music]
Green
Oh The Mask yeah I'm I'm I know I know
like like loky explains
[Music]
something but that's so complicated
I'mma do it for me
okay I I'll I'll maybe try for the next
stream
or
nah I don't know too complicated
unless what did she say
I found the color Channel
masks how's this
work whoa what
what what have I
become
h ah whatever I give
up I give up I give
up did I
say shadow Wawa Mosaic Cho there's so
many versions of myself that I could
become but the original is still the
best
right no if only actually my casual
outfit the highlights in that one I
think are more green than blue these
ones are really
blue in this
outfit anyway shut up
music we're going to go play the game
Meep new down again I can't I honestly
can't believe how fast it arrived now
since the first announcement like what
the hell it feels like there was barely
any any warning time mental preparation
time but
okay I am all
in with my back pain and my neck
pain as high as it ever could be but
let's go let's have some fun let's
distract ourselves yippee I'm locked
in intro
incoming right oh there it
is wait wait I can't hear
it
[Music]
wait I'll make it so that you guys can
at least hear it so
far I can't hear it yet
yeah
yeah good that you hear
it I can imagine it's just
like it's crackling oh
[Music]
great
um I'll fix it
probably so now the crackling should be
gone I assume I don't hear it but I
think it's
gone is it gone
[Music]
no come
on let me listen that's the first time
I'm using the game capture card with my
new mixer
it's not letting me
listen Hey listen Hey
[Music]
listen well you know usually if I just
restart the game capture
window it will often do the trick I'm
starting the game capture
window 2
seconds open it
again it's not a loose connection I hear
it now see it was just I know I can
troubleshoot better than you
[Music]
guys but thanks for at least thinking it
might be something more complicated than
just restarting the program but
I think I know my PC better at this
point than you
guys let me lower this a little
bit
ooh the soundtrack sounds nice and ooh
the weapons look so cool they're going
to take all of that away from us wait am
I link right
now it where is this in the timeline why
am I wearing
blue why am I wearing blue
why is he
Blue Blue Link why too quiet H
okay I want
explanation why is link okay it's just
his hoodie but still like normally he
would wear green this is wrong he's fake
he's a faker oh he's from um that's
another game where there's like
different colored
[Music]
links [\h__\h]
it four Swords or four seasons yeah both
of them
right ah it's so cute I like that it's
back to the
ooh ah ah ah
seems like we have endless
amount I like that it's back to this
style I like both the breath of the wild
style and this
[Music]
style ooh PE PE PE okay we jump over
there oh pretty smooth I like
it like jumping to walking and walking
to Jumping is so
smooth can't aim oh no
but I ow I have Full Hearts Let's Go Sur
will ow no I don't
wait that was a
bomb
nice accidental bumb worked pretty
well platforming parkour
par I'm surprised I'm the only one
[Music]
come here guys ah
[\h__\h] all right let's try this again why
am I doing
this I'm surprised I'm the only one
playing this today on release
day I was like waiting for this guys
I've had it in the back of my mind and
in the front of my mind for a while
now I guess the other girls just haven't
thought about it I'm sure there's going
to be some other girls playing this
right
Target oh there's a
Target z l I'm nice that's what I needed
[Music]
before
surely well if not then not I don't care
then I'll have the
Monopoly Dancing in the Moonlight
everybody
no no no all right lock on so locked in
Ash okay well if he flies then that
makes sense that my arrow doesn't follow
him a a it you should have whoa speed
should have quickly change what where
did that heart go did I suck it
[Music]
up I'm the Zelda cute girl appre I'm a
general Zelda games
appreciator really I feel like they are
great stream games and and I just really
enjoyed
them yeah and I know people say this is
not these are not RPG games but I kind
of want to mix them into that
category and I want to say it's like one
of the best streaming RPG gam RPG games
for
[Music]
streaming they added me into moreal
Kombat I saw something like that that's
not really
me but thanks for thinking of
[Music]
me does that even work on their
armor come here come here let me explode
you woo let's
[Music]
go wonder if there's any way to walk
faster Shield to oh yeah I don't know
he's holding it but I don't know how to
uh ah there there we go e wasn't that
focus on an enemy I'm confused did I
always have it out when I was focusing
on the
enemy it's both okay I wish it
wasn't there's nothing on z r so
far oh
Zelda oh she's wearing quite the classic
outfit m
[Music]
M do you hear my voice differently
now ah o it's kind of it feels loud uh
but yeah all right cool um
uh uh uh so oh I've never used a voice
changer on the new mixer
before
so it's you again
again what a pig ever the Troublesome
one only this time your presence serves
me now I'll land you
both he took off the Blue Cave looks
cute all right boss fight immediately
nice sure okay game
so you're probably expecting me to
already have some experience in this
game oh but he's
weak or experience in Zelda games in
general this is not really beginner
friendly oh oh wait do you want me to to
to shoot it back wait let's I want to
try I want to try ow you didn't do what
I thought you were going to do okay come
on ow what that doesn't do what I
thought it will do okay
whatever and maybe with a
shield no that just blocks
it I try again oh hey oh that does kind
of work maybe I was too late
[Music]
ow
okay I'm not good at
this I don't think I should be trying
this really uh go a [\h__\h]
[Music]
can we just fight normally buddy I don't
want to play
tennis oh okay two times only is
enough
[Music]
ah
tennis there's Mario Tennis and then
there's link
tennis oh okay this time it was threee
times
[Music]
Bonk Bonk Bonk bnk ow oh one last hit is
all that he
needed what's the pre-story why is she
in that stone are we going to travel
back in time to find out
or what's the thing what's going on game
complete first
try comment on be the game yippe
he
runs like [\h__\h]
told a for a moment I felt like his the
way he runs feel so familiar I something
something about that triggers me and
then I realized it's told it's
told
link you
failed really he shot one arrow and
called it a day
really h
wait that reminds me of Jojo SI was
dance
[Laughter]
move now she uses two fists she's mad
she's
mad she made
it
yippee what was
that I'm a lady I'm a princess why does
nobody lay out their jackets over this
hole so I can walk over it like it's a
puddle no I will not walk into it are
you
stupid oh the cape I we're going to wear
it a that would be cute but what if I do
go inside oh okay I
can't I got the swordz man's
cloaks too many SES this is the hooded
cloak that The Swordsman in Green Drop
we know his name don't try to be so
mysterious again we know it by now it's
almost completely cover your face if you
wore it well that sounds great cuz
apparently for some reason we want to
hide our identity don't
we art so cute right I like it
too whoa no no no
no we got to work on that reaction time
girl oh oh oh I I thought it was a cut
scene
I didn't think I had control okay tell
me how many people who already started
playing this game failed that in the
first try because they didn't realize
they were reacting they were
controlling wait can I run faster it's
getting
close you fought that too
right wait I'm reading comments I'm
reading comments wait wait wait wait
wait wait
I want to read
[Music]
comments oh my God my my mic Peaks so
crazy let me turn
on is
this test
test I think that's
better okay we have seen this the
scenery in the back in the
[Music]
trailers better
right
oh wow cute I mean it looks kind of
repetitive with the trees all looking
the same pretty much and the stones too
and the grass
too okay all the [\h__\h]
trees looks so repetitive
um but it looks
cute honestly the world looks a little
bit empty right
now but it's just this this area that's
just this area
[Music]
right sorry Nintendo was choking me
because they were they didn't like what
I've been saying just now sorry I like
the trees I like the trees especially
those wide trees have been
like stretched
sideways okay so what they picked me
up thanks for finding
me already doing a better job than link
by by picking me up and transporting me
safely thanks for nothing
link princess selda you're safe what a
relief who's talking a her you're not
injured are
you we were sick with worry a whole week
is a long time to be
missing I thought you'd been stol away
like all the others a soldier search for
you every
day princess playing with me playing
with
me I'm so so glad you're back but now
one of those icky Rifts opened up here
too yeah princess now that we've arrived
please allow me to welcome you back as
well may I suggest you probably speak
with the King your father probably I'm
sure he'll be deeply relieved to hear
that you for turn safe and
sound okay wow I'm home yippe T Let's
ignore the guy who just tried to save me
and die died by falling into the black
hole I don't care about him at all I
don't have any connection with him at
all hello
bird I'm not
mentally
uh affected by what I have seen at all
the birds they look like chicks cuz
they're yellow
[Music]
pretty this is pretty pretty so far nice
Fountain I don't know if it's my game
capture
card but the it's like the FPS are
low actually might look does it look
better on
OBS oh was that laggy for you cuz it was
laggy for
me is that trying to compare
[Music]
was that laggy for
you I think it looks better on OBS I
don't
know wait I think it looks better on OBS
it's maybe the software this Elgato
softer just
sucks it's hard to tell anyway a messed
up house what where
oh what I see nothing wrong with it
princess Ela it's so good to see you
safe I'm sure everyone in the castle
will be relieved too oh please mind your
Foo footing near the rift it just
appeared but it isn't growing at least
uh you know how it is with Rifts when
they show up people get stolen away oh
they're already like quite familiar with
it everyone in town is accounted for but
please do be mindful demure perhaps we
should be
demure oh look at her
cute ever since you were couldna the
weekly go I've been incapable of getting
even a wink of sleep but now that you're
back I I bet I'll be sleeping like a
baby toight welcome back princess she's
cute I will be demure and mindful the
princess that everybody hopes and dreams
for oh
cute that's some huge ass bananas oh my
God mutated
bananas okay we'll talk to all these
people eventually probably
so there's a lot of dogs around I really
don't like
them I don't like them why is it not
cats what the
hell replace my first order now I'm back
is the princess my first order will be
replace all dogs of
[Music]
cats whoa I'm glowing like a torch holy
get out of that light it's so hot
imagine how hot I watched this video
about um there there the exactly two uh
buildings in the world I think one in
Las Vegas uh that have this like Ray of
death that could kill you and like it
melts cars occasionally and stuff you
know because of the the architecture
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah Sunray of death
look yeah the other one in London yeah
exactly
exactly like one is a hotel in Las Vegas
and then there's just some I think a
company building in
London yeah and they built it like that
and even after the first one already
showed these problems it's the same
architect he went on to build the second
one the same way with no care about the
ray of
death that could in Fury kill someone
H but I feel like if it's that hot like
if you're lying at the pool where this
Ray occurs the hotel pool if you're
lying there and sleeping cuz that would
be probably necessary for you to die
there wouldn't you wake up because of
the heat I wake up at night all the time
when I feel too hot I don't think you
would
die would you wake up before you
die I don't know but yeah
so this why why this is this must be a
really hot
spot hello Princess Zelda please forgive
me for not being there for you in your
time of need as your loyal servant I
should have been able to find you I
promise I'll do better in the
[Music]
future but don't worry even link has
failed so at least you're still here and
you didn't get sucked up by the black
hole unlike link useless just this
little green
ELF so good to have you back Princess
Zelda I'm sure the king will be over the
moon when he sees your
face I agree this looks pretty bird it's
a Choco
[Music]
B destroy my own property cuz I'm so
mad useless link there's no money coming
out of it
oh he
gets he gets freaked out by it I like
the
reaction all right cleaned up a little
bit oh it is that play any
[Music]
chance sorry I I'm still like from when
I choked on the Coca-Cola I still have I
still have it like stuck
[Music]
wait a
second look at
[Music]
him who he's like w holy
Enlightenment I've seen the light of
takanashi
Kiara the Phoenix the tal no and only
Idol it's her she's real she's
real can't believe it she has descended
Upon Our unworthy
selves oh my
[Music]
God there's a lot of uh death Rays
coming into this building you guys need
to fix
that sweet child such a relief to see
you safe welcome home princess I love
doing Grandma
[Music]
voices oh yeah I'm Al
Ki I'm in wa's game
file yeah that's
you I must say your loyal impa felt so
flustered that I could not save you
myself I've I've I've realized a new
thing old people often make s's into
sisses right because of their teeth so I
feel that will add to the to the
vibe my triers eyes are sick
right on top of your kidnapping Rift
have been appearing all over it's it's a
source of much
fear nice
touch touch touch touch touch touch
I'm certain your return will be a great
comfort to the people during these
troubling
times in reminds me of Sophie from house
Moving Castle oh
yeah I guess so yeah she looks really
cute here in this game I like her
earrings or should I call them
earballs you've always been quite
Spirited
Away though I didn't didn't expect you
to make it back on your own she's such a
[Laughter]
jokester well I'm so overcome with
emotion that I've spoken out of
turn off you go now the king awaits
you in the meantime I'll draw a nice hot
bath for you to enjoy when you're ready
I feel like I'm never going to get that
bath am I
you'll be probably dead or all of this
will be sucked in by the time I leave
the
[Music]
chamber welcome M are you ready to the
Run room the king is raining inside okay
well what about this
room what I can really go
[Music]
there now things are back to normal
Spirits are lifted again thank
goodness I to come home I've kept a
close eye on your room while you were
going
that's my
room I have a cat oh
superia Zelda she gets it she just gets
it wow that's a huge plant I feel like I
can jump on the leaves and go to the sky
with that it's so
cute should I destroy my own pots maybe
there's money in these
[Music]
no her voice is
cute should we have a little horse see
they cute we have a little couch looks
really nice and it's fitting it's why is
the couch bigger than my
bed why is the bed so
tiny what if I want to cuddle with link
daddy how old is
she is there any like lore on how old
Zelda usually
is to keep me
demure and mindful
[Music]
she's always 17 I mean cuddling should
be okay with 17 right Daddy come
on maybe it's my cat's
bad maybe this whole room is my cat's
room I mean with this much
money say it again say it
[Music]
again one more time
so
too oh I can rest yeah before I go to
the
king she looks like she looks like um
that princess that needs a kiss to wake
[Music]
up
yeah Sleeping
Beauty oh no no actually yeah I'm
thinking of actually she looks more like
Aurora to me wait is that the same
person I don't
know wait when I rest and then I get up
I can run around on the bed
nice I don't know nice a cute room okay
sorry I'm wasting time oh there's a
portrait of
me
beautiful it's right above the mirror so
that every time I put on my makeup I
have a guide on what I'm supposed to
look like cuz otherwise I'm going to
look so different friend right okay so
the other rooms are closed huh that's
nice that I could take a look into my
room before it gets sucked
[Music]
up okay yeah can't go there can't go
there okay okay okay didn't you go to
the side impa why are you standing here
now
okay looking forward to that bath I'll
never
get
oo Santa Claus
[Music]
wait who's stand on the
right princess I'm sorry I left your
back oh princess wait is that Minister
left is that a girl or a boy what an
absolute joy to see you safe and well
despite that Joy I feel ashamed that we
were unable to find you oh right and
left h
[Music]
cute on behalf of Miss Minister left and
me please accept our apologies
princess turn right Minister
left I appreciate your sentimental but
let's not Dull these joyous moments with
our regrets regretti spaghetti no more
tell them my dear daughter you did well
to return to us come closer so I may
look upon you
don't trust him he's
[\h__\h] oh I'm so relieved you're
healthy and whole and well whole and
well maybe I should cut you up make you
not whole anymore and then and then
Grill you like a steak make you well in
a different sense a bit of
pretend so tell us Zelda what happened
to
[Music]
you a swordsman and green saved you from
a fell Beast quite a
tail I'm still cie yeah what of course I
never never never have been anybody
else no I'm I'm wa I'm wa I'm
wa I'm W don't worry I'm w
[Music]
yeah Link and Zelda don't seem to know
each other yet what the hell but after
after defeating the monster The
Swordsman was taken by a rift it's him
we have to thank for saving your
life so he was pulled into a rift
another one stolen
away indeed I hope he's safe Sten away a
tidy phrase for terrible fate being
taken by a rift but that's what happens
to noobs I guess wouldn't happen to
me an unsettling
phenomenon Our Fair H has continually
been plagued with these Rifts and
disappearances as you know rift's been
appearing for a long time claiming our
young ones Only the Young Ones indeed so
many children have been stolen away
we've remained Vigilant only young ones
only
[Music]
children so what if an older person
person steps into one of the
Rifts nothing happens or
what or has it just I guess they're not
that stupid and it just appears exactly
under young ones all the
time let the story cook no
no but despite our best efforts we've
never been able to prevent the Rifts
from
appearing ultimately those who've
experienced losses have been left to
contend with their
grief now I've been receiving reports
about people disappearing from people
not
children which one from every corner of
I and it isn't just a okay children not
anymore adults are appearing too
disappearing
too what could be wasn't such an
uptake for now we should also work on
finding the swordsman in the green tunic
and fa
why why if you don't really know him how
is that so important to
[Music]
you
what because he saved Z well I don't
know does that really matter I saved
myself h
[Music]
your
majesty oh wait that's someone else
oh what is it
soldier soja boy up in this oh watch me
me
Superman that's what he
said crack D allil you crack D allil
watch me go watch me you
look imagine him just coming in and he's
like what is it Soldier and he goes like
y watch me crank it watch me
go Superman at
oh sorry that's so funny to
me sorry for the musical performance
just now I was kind of excited um the
Rifts they're causing serious
trouble oh
pleas Soldier what are the
details oh of course your majesty
uh what a nose he looks like a Minecraft
Soul uh uh not Soldier um
person
villager oh those are so cute oh oh not
cute
[Music]
anymore ooh
sorry the
Coca-Cola firstly youed word that
someone from s sou s San s Village was
swallowed up by a rift and then we also
received news from dark monsters
attacking people in iru
field that is troubling news
indeed thank you for your report Soldier
tell the rest of your Battalion to
prepare for he looks like one of the
dwarves of rings of power anyway just
because he's small and yeah he's got a
beard okay
cute yes your
majesty rings of power rings of power uh
General
Minister
s Minister left continue your
investigations into the rift phenomenon
I am expecting you to find a way to save
any and all who have vanished into the
Rifts you can count to me
[Music]
S General right I leave the monsters to
you prepare your troops and head into
battle on my honor
sir this crisis must be dealt with
continue looking into the Rifts and
locate those who've been
lost oh see I told you I told you I told
you I told you told you I'm never going
to get my
bath yeah no not the king no Save the
King a
[\h__\h] ah
[\h__\h] It's got eyes oh oh [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] daddy oh
[\h__\h] uh can't can't fool me no no no no
no
Gorge oh
no it's like AI is taking over in their
brains wh why why do they get to look
normal again and the others usually
don't look her up immediately no no look
up the
princess you can't listen to him you
can't my daughter created the rift you
see behind me we can leaves its horrible
power unchecked now he would never
that's not realistic he would never like
what the hell no he wouldn't react like
that disturbing though it may be General
R and Minister left to Bo witness as
well don't you know this the all around
around them
bro well don't stand there lock her up
lock her
up yeah you all right your M Majesty
what the hell okay let's go well at
least I I saw my room once at least good
that I went
there
bro
H well that
sucks bad ending of
Game why did we look up the princess
what could the king be
thinking you haven't heard apparently
she's the the one who created the rift
in the front room H oh what there's no
way so then she might also be
responsible for all the other
Rifts
yeah yeah they'll just keep popping up
so as long as she's
around do you really believe it huh I
don't think so there'll be more Rifts
even while I'm in here let me out
there's even word the king plans on
putting her to Deaths to save the
kingdom what the [\h__\h]
no I just can't believe the princess
would be the cause of these thank you
the one sound mind
[Music]
here incredible how this bed is the same
size as my bed in my room
oh
M
hello
oh
oh he comes back
yeah that's the right place yep yep yep
yep whoa what is that weird
thing
[Music]
H
H you can see
me my name's
tree that blue monster
he caught me too I've been watching you
since
then I followed you here to this
Castle oh yeah I should ask what's your
[Music]
name Zelda not link I got
it Zelda your life is in danger if you
stay here
the person who put you here is the King
right he told someone to hurry and
prepare for your
execution once I heard that I figured
I'd better tell you the king and the
other two got pulled into the rift the
pr that came out seemed
[Music]
weird that's what I'm saying oh you
notice they seemed work too you think
they're
Impostors Among Us with an odd
[Music]
word anyway it's still dangerous for you
to stay
here I think if we could save the people
who've been taken into Rifts we could
reveal the
truth but none of those people will be
able to get out on their own
we have to save them together
Zelda but first let me save you let's
get you out of
here I like this uh
mixer's way of changing the
voice you can't get through the
bars nope must suck
Get
Wrecked um okay well let's
see let me
[Music]
help oh no comment on that okay
looks what does that look like
guys give me a funny
comparison surely looks like something
funny I stick well more than
that a giant Twizzler
MH a back
scrun not a chicken leg no spaghetti
scoop DNA yeah yeah
VI what for yeah yeah yeah
yeah gigg St toilet brush yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah mik Le oh
yeah
okaya I've made something to help you
[Music]
the train
Rod
cute it's a mysterious Rod the same
color as me tree it's warm to the touch
cuz I just pulled it out of my
ass I can create echo of things in this
world not wisdom because then I would
have to play the credits you know so I
say EO of
things I'm not sure what will be most
useful to you but I'm sure this will
come in
handy go up to something that's
shimmering then press set
R fourth wall
breaking pressed are you
sa I learned the table
Echo
cool good job that's how you learn
things anything you've learned can be
with
Y all right like this
wowo look at that perfect
job what you created is called an echo
no it's a
table press set R when you're near an
echo to erase it if you want to raise
all of your Echo hold set R what okay ah
I see things learned using de R can be
echoed with Y the number of things you
can Echo depends on how much of trees
power is
available H Echoes can be erased using z
r to erase all Echoes press and hold z r
okay so quickly and then okay let's do
let's do this I guess I'm going to build
like stairs no wait never mind oh over
here there's like a oh the other Z zel
Zelda the other cell is open so
if I put a table here and can jump on
that I maybe one more
okay ah oh that worked okay wow so good
Zelda Legend of
Zelda now we can escape let's go let's
go let's
go w yippe we don't think anybody will
notice what if I purposefully go over
there all
right game
over how did you manage to get out what
the hell well whatever you're here under
King's order so please stay put don't
cause any trouble please he says please
he's still so kind and
nice all right I'll just do it
again but what if no never
mind I was going to like maybe try build
like a bridge over
them can I would be funny I wonder if
they react if I'm like on top of
something oh
no okay they they they know this pretty
early now whatever let's move
on oh sneaky sneak let's
go
a no problem I don't mind this but the
rats are going to maybe also be an
issue so I should probably try to get up
on this level
immediately
hey
stairs bring it
back
okay oh why are oh those are glowy
because I can get them okay learn
they're higher than the table I
assume sneaky NY NY NY NY NY NY saky
sneaking like I'm snake you learned the
wooden box
echle okay so how do I choose between
them uh holding down the right button
and then select
okay aha
oh I see I see okay so we want to put a
box oh wait I'm to I can lift it but I
can't get up on it oopsie oh god oh no
no no
no wait
no go back to where you came
from yeah just a box just a box
wait how did we switch it again uh no
what was the button again uh ah right
and then
here well I
guess probably don't need anything there
um and once I'm on top of the box I
guess I'm out of their sight too right
what okay you can jump on my table
no where you bringing me to the cell no
okay no more selda
please H do I still have I still have
the wooden box
now hold
no I'm not there ignore me so he did
notice me up there
interesting maybe if I would just be
walking slowly maybe then he wouldn't
[Music]
notice what if I cut off their PS with a
box does that work
oh the
shenanigans oh the oh wait
wait is that how you're supposed to do
it I thought I was supposed to go up on
the second level and walk around make my
way around that but maybe you could have
done it that way too but I like this way
they're
stuck until I remove it but by then I'll
be gone already
that's
funny that's so
funny oh so the other day I broke a p to
test the fury and general right came
running I'm sure he gave you an earful
about it actually no I thre the Pod kind
of far and he ran to where he heard it
break
huh freaking Mouse
brain General R is a simple man oh my
God so
dumb well I never needed to do anything
here apparently cuz I can just walk
by ah there's some BTS
here ah I can learn
them
nice wait so the tree refills its energy
when I get rid of uh things I made right
where is the energy I don't see
it I don't see
it will you show it to me now when I do
ah or just have to look at you oh wait
ah the the
tail is it the tail no the tail shows
how many items I can create free and
then I guess it's gloess shows
maybe anyway
[Music]
oh
[\h__\h] easy what what's with the m still
are they supposed
to make things more difficult for me
wait I didn't hear
it my heart was a little bit donky dony
there oo wait that's a the statue thingy
not statue of liberty statue of life or
so what's that little [\h__\h] Pony
there give me
something can't talk to it oh yeah hi La
statue hi hi La hi Leah hi Leah
basically Statue of Liberty of
Hyrule princess oh well now we can take
you to your bath I guess well that's
great I'm sure so glad you're safe
you're not hurt are you you
sneaky I can't even imagine what his
majesty is
thinking claiming that you created the
rift it's Preposterous am I the only one
here left with a logical way of
thinking what the king General and
Minister are all Impostors are we
playing a big Among Us game here is
there Zelda collaboration incoming how
exciting and your friend tree made you a
tree Rod was it what a ridiculous name
uh anyway I
see Zelda can make use of the Rod's
[Music]
power oh you can't see
it she can't see
it it's all in my
head TR no I call it
tree then it's more funny that it's
called tree Rod you know literally just
picked it off of a
train
[Music]
no it's
tree rhymes with
fee just like I said fee mhm where might
tree be now oh you hear all on your own
no no look at this thing right in front
of
you look at
me
hello a I think you're the only one who
can see me
zeldo oh it's a
lemon interesting uh the world is trly a
mysterious place but I believe you well
come what way I will always support you
princess no no matter what Mysteries
unfold we better not dally D the phony
King is speaking of executing you like
what the actual [\h__\h] right we need to
leave and quickly you'll stand out in
your current attire so I've brought
something for you to change
into oh what is that blue fabric
sticking out from your pocket
there w ah I see it's the cloak The
Swordsman was wearing the size seems
workable it will do a fine job of
shrouding you quickly now before we
spotted
oh come
on is she changing her whole attire not
just putting on the
cape oh yeah I guess she
did but she kept on her crown why not
take off the crown it would be less
likely to be found out oh
well as long as we have it we can like
sell it for money
later you got a disguise it's light and
flowy and conceals your identity nicely
it smells like a a musty dresser
what spin spin to win around quickly by
pressing
R yeah oh you should be able to head
along now without worry why would I spin
the princess is missing and the princess
is missing find
her
no don't tell me you're not recognizing
me no way it seems we have company leave
this to
me walking through my tree Rod my tree
yeah oh lady emper who's that over there
are you for real are you for real like
guards that work in the balance should
be able to recognize my face especially
when I'm still wearing the [\h__\h] Crown
come
on okay sure sure it's dark in here
right no it's actually not I'm like
standing kind of in a lit up
[Music]
area if it is you must stand aside this
instant stand aside h no I don't believe
I'll be doing that see oh oh
[\h__\h]
woo let's go okay Grandma she still got
it here princess take this with you
turns out she's more useful than link
probably but she's retired so she can't
help me you receed the log first a tree
rod and now a tree log whoa
we're
becoming a tree
worker um what's the word for
that not a druid
no well it definitely wouldn't be
Carpenter because Carpenters is my
carpets yeah it would be a lumberjack
exactly this log was given to you by
impa there's a folded map inside oh wow
pretty
beig make your way to the house marked
with the light tell them in perent you
they'll surely help
you I wonder what's
there is it aligned the same way always
with like highroll Maps like are are the
same places always in the same area kind
of more or less like at least in the
same like South North Etc
not
always okay
sometimes this way oh this way ahead
you'll find a shortcut that leads out of
the castle use it to make your
Escape her and now princess we'll see
each other
later
and the Mysterious Rifts main quest oh
okay cool you I only have three hearts
did I have those Hearts before I can
learn how to make a
tree for what decorative shrub
EO I can walk over them
too I see that's pretty
high
e Echo that Echo this is an echo so I
can say here is the echo in Italian by
saying ech
Echo Italian I want to put it right in
front of
me there you go there we
go w w
wind oh forgot how to jump for a
moment
okay I triggered your Amazon
EO sorry
I'm sorry
beds H why are these
beds here in such a
suspicious Arrangement well I shall
learn
it how many can I learn
again or is there no Max I thought there
was a
Max huh
beds are broken I I I would assume so
but will this fall down okay oh it
breaks even okay ah but I if I put it
like on yeah mhm yeah okay basically
stairs is there something down there
though something
fun no maybe not actually no
wait there is oh [\h__\h] I should have done
that differently
ah damn
[Music]
it ah damn
it wait I want to figure out like maybe
there's something up there because
there's a
door and I feel like you know it's a
secret room or
so maybe I'll be rewarded because like
look up there there's like no path to it
but it's so suspicious because the beds
are lowkey leading to
it well
now
rest wait I I
could I don't know
maybe but free is maximum
so um can I remove that one down there
from here
damn it a damn it no that's not what I
wanted to do
yeah wait
um what if I what if I put actually a
box
[Music]
here I mean maybe not not a big
difference but what if we just get up
there again
first that's the priority
maybe no damn
[Music]
it what have I
done
ah did I break an existing bed bed
somehow did I break an existing bed if I
reenter the room it will fix itself but
let me let me let me uh you know try TR
this
again no why are you there here no
that's
fine okay so if I just put the bed
here okay uh get rid of that if I I'm I
am still very much in the belief that
there's something there what if the I
think the plants they can fall down a
little bit ah damn
it I have to build a base you think it's
just a
window do you think it's not worth it wa
wait a second if we go out oh
[Laughter]
spinning is
fun overthinking at his best and the
funny thing is I've already been I've
already stepped outside
once oh and I didn't
realize but it was fun trying to do
things you know we have to we probably
have to do a lot of this kind of stuff
uh from now on
so I don't know if that's where you
would want to go
[Music]
first or if I should have explored the
other path first if that was even
possible there's an oxygen meter really
you can't hold on to
that
girl ooh what is that a
boulder looks like a pumpkin shaped
Boulder Boulder Echo okay how do I oh I
oh well this stuff will not fall onto me
right okay
good we're
diving
nice um
uh not
a so the boxes float that's good to
know thank you for the membership
gift
than oh do we want to break one of these
maybe with a boulder or like push it
down with a boulder
oh
cool isn't that
[Music]
fun that's pretty fun so far pretty cute
cute cute
cute I like the water
texture ooh it's kind of iffy weird here
stinky stinky no no careful
Zelda another
Rift Rifts have appeared occasionally
for a very long time oh really Ming them
our job so you're not doing your job
right
now except my power alone isn't enough
to take care of a large Rift like this
one let's get away from it for
now this is what happens when you
procrastinate your Mount Your Hill of
work will become a mountain of work and
then you can't handle it anymore cuz
it's just too
much uh-oh what what what are you
kidding me I'm not my my brain is so too
slow for all of this can it go over my
ah are you kidding me oh what am I
supposed to go down and swim oh yeah
probably cuz that's too
fast okay I thought I had to like build
a bridge really
quickly bro ah what she's she's not
doing so well did we
die no okay then that was a fast way out
oh wake up hey hey wake
up tell you wake good let's
go yippee a little Stone let's learn
that too no for real how many can I
learn H was there no limit there has to
be a limit
there has to
be no limit
[Music]
really
o
oh okay can even dive there in that
point of view nice why are these boxes
there can I go up there is there
something interesting there I want to
figure out once again I want to see
something that probably doesn't even
exist Al don't like look at
that I must
investigate I must
no go go back this probably not worth my
time
right um
[Music]
yeah
no wait
wait
um no okay I don't know I'm too stupid
for this oh you're excited to see me
play the game thank you me too me too
let's play together side by side guys is
there anybody playing with me right
now oh what's that fruit down
there where are
[Music]
we maybe that map thing need that person
gave you can help us figure it
[Music]
out you're playing no one you're having
fun watching that's nice too I am I'm
just a little ahead that's good you got
to stay ahead of me so that I don't
spoil you I just got the game but I will
have to wait until after work okay I
won't get too far probably with how much
I'm procrastinating so don't worry about
it you're in no rush that's good I
passed you how did I pass you you had
plenty of
time press minus to open the map your
current location is indicated with
[Music]
Dela whoa how' we get from there to
there sheesh
ah and we get like these Square uh map
pieces I see I
see or ah I guess oh no no mind they're
not always Square they're like these
little puzzle
pieces I don't know it doesn't tell me
yet what these things are but this is
gudo I
suppose I was
wondering is this the the that that farm
maybe and this could be like maybe the
that one village where impa lives
this looks more jungly like that place
what was it called in breath of the
wild oh this this actually wait is that
water then that's the the fish
people ah this is the the stone
[Music]
people wait this is also Stone
people maybe I don't know but I'm
excited to figure it all out and
find what this world has to offer Pony
it's a
pony from Risa
games I noticed you I it noticed you
Zelda can you fight
[Music]
monsters hell yeah I can oh oh wait
never mind I can't wait uh can
I can I
uh wait here's some beds sleep you
little
[\h__\h] uh maybe I can drop a boulder on it
wait no it just spawns on the ground uh
throw the rock oh that's so boring I
can't
fight ah man oh oh I can learn this oh
they can fight for me right they can
fight for me I think all Echo
did you learn to Echo that monster
defeating new monsters leaves a shimmer
which allows you to learn about them
like you just
did Monsters learned with z r can be
echoed with Y you can direct your Echo
to attack specific targets by using
targets with a by using Target with ZL
but
honestly I hope we get to like I don't
know I've seen in the videos that she
makes uh like in the trailers that she
makes things fight for her but I wish I
hope there will be way to fight by
myself too or will there never be do I
always have to let things fight for
me I do want to be able to fight on my
own too wait how do I direct it can you
follow
[Music]
me I
ah oh okay now they're attack
okay I got to spawn it like closer to
where I need it then apparently there
[Music]
is oh yeah summoning a bomb for example
I
guess and there they F hey what the
hell go
go it's got to start its um attack thing
before the other
one oh oh [\h__\h] oh to yeah all right why
not it's a Pokemon battle
Yeah it actually
is uh-oh oh oh okay ah because
oh why did you
fail come
on
M oopsie that's not what I wanted oh but
it got rid of the grass interesting
[Music]
I wish I could at least do something
with the turn with the
spin
ooh right we can swim here there's a
blue
blue I forgot the word I'm forgetting
many words
now
ropey nice blue was what five
fish let me eat
you okay but you led me to another rupe
thank
[Music]
you yeah swimming off the bat I feel
like maybe they knew that if like after
breath of the wild if they make it
impossible for players to swim again oh
it
floats the fandom will be disg grunt
because you're taking away something you
gave them
[Music]
already
nice but is there any point in doing
this Wawa no probably
[Music]
not can I hold on to
this there's a chest chest ch just a
treasure chest
[Music]
though
no no wait
I'm no no not
there
yeah
wait there we go uh oh no it's going to
disappear though okay you can
disappear no no no no
no no I want it to go sideways though
what if I wanted to place it in front of
me but like
sideways
ah from here then
okay and then like this oh man it's so
complicated
[Music]
yeah well it makes everything into a
puzzle I guess that's fun I guess that's
nice 20
rupees can we get much
higher so high probably not okay and
then we want to go over these
thingies I can probably just go up
here summon my doll and
attack he won't see what's coming for
him
ah sh oopsie um I keep on forgetting how
to spin and now we swim spin swim so
much to
do this is out now yeah like what people
people are people are not having this on
their radar for some reason heart
container stream heart
container let's go a piece of heart oh
collect four and your maximum number of
Hearts will
increase our first heart
container let's
go wa I want to get the
money oh I I felt
[Music]
that can you skill oh I I guess I could
damn okay let me do it over there out of
the water that's they I didn't think
about it I need to get used to this
still uh wait how how does wait no um
um oh what how how do we do this
again
oh ow
what oh they're not glow a so okay I
can't do it
okay now now I hurt myself for nothing
[Music]
okay they will glow if it
works damn it the direction is kind of
difficult to get
[Music]
right oh bridge is gone no
problem I am a bridge
maker I can do it better than any other
real Bridge maker ow [\h__\h] I'm going to
die am I not supposed to enter there can
I can
I oh it does kill and now I can learn
right I have to die first sorry sorry
sorry sorry see urch and
Echo we have to die first forgot about
that we're
learning we're learning
everything I guess is that the only path
to go through here
[Music]
mysterious who put those ladders there
ah wait I forgot right I was I was
thinking of how to use my bow but right
I'm not link anymore I don't have a bow
[Music]
um keep that thing ready
ouch no I'm going to die
no oh hey I did it let's go but I need
Hearts oh wait I can learn this one too
oh this one can
fly ooh the keys Echo keys to
[Music]
cheese I'm still so clumsy a heart
container
oh oh my God R the Boulder work no then
the spiky thing will work right
no if I I have to drop it maybe wait I
have to drop it maybe it
needs some
momentum right wait can I climb up there
oh okay I was like ah I got to build my
way up here never mind so maybe see
urchin hey but don't hurt me let's go
get rid of it
first
hey
wow I'm learning you got a piece of
heart yippee and now we climb back
up nice went
bouldering um okay so does this thing
attack quite well let's see will it win
this Pokmon battle it will win no don't
get hit stupid
well I do have to I guess if this is a
Pokemon battle I have to I do have to
take in account the turn based battle
[Music]
system now you're thinking with
Echo honestly this will probably become
a phrase just with portal just like with
P
[Music]
portal now you're thinking with Echo
it's really just makes
sense I feel like the bed will be used
even um in the end game unless they give
you like actual
stairs but I can see people still using
the bed in the end
game W 50 rupees that does make me
really
happy
H this is so like it only matters for me
but I was looking up flights um today to
plan my like to have an idea of how much
I will have to pay for my next trip to
Japan and you know I've been telling you
guys before that um in Austria we only
have direct flights in summer after ever
ever after after Ever After
Corona um but uh I've noticed something
when I was looking up flights apparently
Ana all nipon Airways the Japanese
airline has resumed I guess they did
this
before um direct flights and they're not
just in summer they started in August
and now like every 3
days there's a flight direct flight
going from Japan to Austria
again Ana yeah they're a little bit
expensive like I could fly to cheaper if
I take
connections but I looked at the
connections for the next trip when I
have to go to Japan and the connections
are so [\h__\h] like the flight there might
be okay but the flight back I have to
like change twice and then it adds up to
like 20 hours uh no more like 24 hours
like the the the shortest amount of
travel time I saw was 24 hours or so I
was like [\h__\h]
no so yeah but I'm glad to see direct
flights again in like winter time
that'll be very very
[Music]
useful I'm B
jelly I haven't seen your name pop up in
a while thanks for the
[Music]
membership all the flat attendants are
so unrealistically pretty you mean the
Ana flat attendants I mean honestly like
the flight attendants in general are
always so
pretty okay there are some airlines that
really have
more like how to say societ we live in
the society and you know the standards
for being pretty the society tells you
what's pretty and what's
not um but yeah I feel there are some
more well-kept uh
[Music]
ladies in certain airlines than compared
to others private jet fund nah
never we do in fact live in a society
you destroyed the man's crops I was I
don't know I'm sorry I was Tangen thing
and it just led me to do that I'm
sorry welcome to sou Village it's
usually nice and quiet here but now
things are
terrible if only link we're here who's
link who's link H who is it h i don't
[Music]
know yeah business class would make me
happy link is a young fellow from this
Village he is better with a sort than
anyone he helps us with lots of problems
monsters weeds you name
it yeah link usually has a lot of fun
destroying grass wherever he goes so I'm
sure he's helpful with ging
too don't get yourself a lawnmower just
get yourself a link but he's gone off on
a journey right when we need him how
curious link wears a cloak like
yours oh link I hope you're all right oh
he's really loved here
wow what happened a rift appeared nor
for fear and it grew so fast that one of
wait shouldn't I get like a like a like
a
um a light bulb above my head the moment
he said oh this guy is on an adventure
he wears a cape like
yours Zelda ding ding ding ding it's
time to think it's time to use your
brains yeah even an exclamation mark
would be
fine maybe she understood but she's just
thinking to
herself Zelda is mute now too oh dear
she was mute before but now she takes
this is the curse of being the
protagonist in these games you just
can't speak
anymore Mama
Mia she knew how to speak
before CR so faster one of us got caught
inside what's worse we can't even run to
hyru Castle for help the rift is
blocking the way
there well that's a problem let me look
into your
house without your permission
[Music]
M
cute is that supposed to be a knife
because it looks like a
spatula look at that I can learn that
all to eat
it can I eat
it I don't have to eat
Hearts this is way more tasty than
eating a raw Hearts like freaking
Daenerys if I can eat that I would be I
can't eat it [\h__\h] I have to continue
eating raw
Hearts to prove
myself to the to the
people and a ceremony it's freaking bait
looks good though what did I learn that
for but maybe to bait but actually maybe
you really mean it's bait as in I can
bait some animals with it or
so wait wait a second did I did I see
something
there no oh
[Music]
never
mind I can eliminate hunger in My
Kingdom well yeah now definitely hunger
is no more thing no more a worry to be
had who are you hi I wa up one of my
neighbors there must be something we can
do besides
pacing wait you have a freaking
trampoline oh that's crazy
[Music]
I will steal your idea for
it I wonder surely there were Medieval
trampolines
right oh it must have been such a fun
time when they first came up with that
[Music]
idea oh wow so many
beds cute honey pots oh my God they look
like the they look like honey pots cute
oh the wooden sword is so cute oh this
is like for children
huh soup looks good too hi Grandma we're
pretty upset around here one of us
villagers has Rec in a rift and we can't
escape e the forest nearby is crawling
with
monsters don't worry I'll take care of
everything I'm the new hero now you
don't need freaking link
anymore yeah we need the pool might get
his hand stuck don't let the bears go
[Music]
nearby this is so wholesome
already why can't I learn the
axe give me the axe I want to cut
up
everybody make everything bloody oh it's
a
shop cute is that
honey a Flor nectar H when used in a
drink it boosts the effect wait you have
a heart piece never mind how much 100
please 80 I would have given you 100
what a
deal let's
[Music]
go is that our third one or our fourth
one our third I guess what's this heart
juice red Pion oh do I need a do I need
a a container
will he tell me oh well one rupe shorts
well give me a discount I probably need
a bottle right he would tell no bottle
needed whoa give me Ruby please one
rupee one rupee one
rupee one rupe
[Music]
please hello please one
rupe pleas grass are so
[Music]
greedy all
right oh I should jump into the well
intrusive thoughts be
like oh thank you for the Super Chat
that's blue though I needed just one
green
one
yeah oh let's go wa when I drink it will
I REM with an empty bottle or will it
just disappear I
wonder it's expensive but okay it heals
a lot too might want to save
it
who there's Treasures here I'm sure
there's money in there in the treasure
[Music]
chest
what grapes I have them in front of me
too but in
green I I forgot to put them into the
fridge yesterday but should be good they
can survive a day out of the fridge
[Music]
right I can rest here too this will be
my new
home yeah I for I forgot I can use the
bed to heal wait I was going to say yeah
I know I can heal on beds but I forgot
that I can summon them and then sleep on
them need to think with Echo
five jars of floral nectar can be used
to recover Hearts but is more effective
when mixed into a drink what kind of
drink
[Music]
interesting very
interesting the rift nearby is huge and
it's terrifying being so close to our
village it could be in SN Forest too a
strange old man lives there I hope he's
okay didn't we just come from that
[Music]
Forest what I can learn the
sign what
for just to make a
fence huh okay the force is over
there
[Music]
oh make it sound and read it oh will it
always tell me the direction or so that
would be
interesting have a look at
this safe point or what a teleportation
Point
wayo Cann now warp here using the map
[Music]
amazing these are way points we use
these a lot Rifts can appear all over
the place so we use these to travel
quickly around the world once you
interact with you can travel to at
anytime I'm sure they'll be
helpful oh yeah after activating a
waypoint you can jump to that location
using the
map nice if only I could copy paste
those
too okay let me try to make a sign
then uh
sorry the writing is yeah okay cool
you could probably use it as a shield
but only once Oh you mean okay but I
can't hold it I can only place it in
front of
me but okay I'll keep it in mind I'll
trying make another why
[Music]
does it change the
writing warning this sign is made out of
wood which is
flammable ah maybe I want to burn stuff
up this way that way okay there we go
that's now it's telling me the
directions thank you that's so
helpful sometimes a good lie down in a
bed is all you need to feel better thank
you for reminding me okay I should I
wonder how many different signs there
are they should come in handy hopefully
every once in a
[Music]
while who's writing on these signs it's
it's my brain writing out the things
that I should be
thinking oopsie I'm sensing lots of
creatures in this area I think the place
marked with delight is a the
heck when life gives you lemons such as
tree
then make juice out of
it but don't do it right away do it at
the end when you don't need your your
tree lemon
anymore otherwise you might regret
it Treasure Chest yeah yay yay okay wait
uh we need an
enemy can we
sort them by type okay but the enemies
are at the
[Music]
end
attack yeah nice good
[Music]
job strong going to build a strong Army
H Apple Electro apples this atem can be
used to recover Hearts but it's more
effective a okay okay okay I see so
there's a lot of different fruits I'm
guessing you mix the fruits to make
different kind of P
potions what if I dive here is there
something
[Music]
there oh no it's dying cuz it's
following me into the water no
suicidal bats why are you so
stupid what is this sussy
place wants me to go up there maybe by
making some stairs but is that what I
want to do first ah there's so many
things so many
[Music]
directions I do kind of have to go
up but what about
here watch that for mon is hiding in the
grass well not not in this one
can you use the bat to fly I would
assume
not wait trampoline how how high can I
jump
again amazing now I don't have to make
freaking stairs just just for this kind
of height anymore oh there's a chest
here okay nice nice nice
nice I don't need hints from The
Notebook yet I'm fine hi birdie
[Music]
trampoline very
nice happy birthday Mr Game
Boy
congratulations thank you for the Super
Chat
ooh don't be nice why won't you why
won't you just be nice
next one too can you attack the next one
no
stupid you guys need to react
faster so far I've
only only found money in these grasses
but not
enemies can I attack this thing wait
damn it attack uhoh
uhoh you don't want to attack it come on
such a
loser burnt
alive o it's
strong okay there we go it only took
like two
attacks cute it does look like a little
candle IGN need all Echo okay now we can
set things on fire
interesting I wonder if there will be
all kinds of um
ooh
elements ooh oh will it
spread
ow my head is on
fire I
it attack attack it is definitely
spreading yep it y it
um yeah I think you can probably come
back now are they all
dead not that we really needed to burn
everything
down start a fire
[Music]
today quite the
useful Echo but need to be careful with
it can bite you in your ass oh wait wait
can I
hm oh wait that's not it says I can lift
it but I feel like I'm just going to
burn
myself I if it fits it
[Music]
it a that's so
cute it just places itself in there when
you summon it close
enough that is so cute heart
container a bottle for fairies all right
let's
go so I guess you don't get to keep the
bottle if you are done drinking your
potion oh okay maybe actually you do but
you can only use it for filling it up
with potions again who
knows okay I guess we just leave the way
we came
[Music]
in I think
so nice little mini dungeon yeah yeah
yeah indeed indeed very good so far oh
snake danger
noodle we will use our fire on that one
right
[Music]
away come on use fire use Sparks stream
Sparks y
[Music]
ah danger noodle oh I went into the
fire oh my God it's it's following
me okay I learned danger
noodle it looks funny it's called
rope I feel like I saw that somewhere
that's
funny uh I shall
sleep if nobody disturbs
me ah you have to wait for it
okay come
on your rope it's a rattle rope it's a
danger
rope
[Music]
okay
nice really cute and Charming so far I
mean it will be hard at some point when
you have so many but I guess you can get
rid of some I wonder can
you in the notebook you can probably I
would
assume yeah just to like
sort can you
not like if there's some that are just
like annoying to have in here cuz you
like they're the same for like how are
these two different for example
H I know you can sort but what if I just
you know they're like they're already
ready we just begun the game and they're
already too
many a favorites bar would be nice yeah
just have my favorites
out danger noodle
go good job good job one more yo it's a
fast attacker ooh Speedy boy yeah bite
bite
bite good job he didn't attack a single
time maybe he didn't see the danger
noodle because he was so low below his
height
fairy um do I just get the option to
catch it when when I'm close to it guys
tell me if you
[Music]
know rope is strong walk into
it as long as I have an empty bottle it
it FX it up or
[Music]
what that' be crazy heart
container do I have to walk around it is
it like
a down right and then up what wait what
do you call these
again it's doing a funny what a funny
bunny
oh get wrecked
ow this time I hurt
[Music]
myself how much
more there we go yeah I'm
I'm is it in the same family as bunnies
I
Wonder has bunny ears at least in this
game
[Music]
um I guess I got to attack it maybe we
fire I
guess go
[Music]
straight
closer
no oh the armor
D
go
ah bo bo boing oh it's so Dy do you
going to are you going to just start
again no oh you're cute you're
cute they're in their own category I
[Music]
see oh no don't attack me I'm friends
now I can control you don't pick a f
with me I'm
scared ooh do I have to make a stair
here I feel like I should be able to
jump over there
do I have to press up I guess yeah okay
ooh learning how to climb for pro
professional climbers you got four
pieces of fire
yay look at that guys our first extra
hard
yippe nice let's go catch a fairy
apparently you just have to walk into
it let's see if that's true well it
better not run away fly
away oh
wow so
automatic it's
systematic I saw a really weird car
today um and I looked it up later on to
like find the right model um but I saw
an really old tiny loud car that looked
like like it was from like 40 years ago
but it's not one of the cute kind of
classic oldtimers
no I mean it's kind of cute it's called
an Amika a m i
CA and
specifically uh what was I don't know
anymore but it's one of the tiny
[Music]
ones I'm a car imagine her driving
around in one of those cars oh that
would be so funny
M I'm
am yeah it looked really
funny it's so tiny and it was so loud
and I've never seen such a tiny car
[Music]
before yeah from
hyai but like really freaking tiny and
old and it made these loud noises
[Laughter]
like um where are we going oh okay we
got to go there ah but it's cut off
[Music]
huh damn that's where we needed to go
no was this where we were supposed to go
looks like the rift is blocking the
door Zelda my role is to mend Rifts I
have lots of friends who do the same we
all work together fixing our
Rifts but recently we're not doing our
job normally my friends fix them quickly
so it's weird that this is still here
how about you fix
it I wonder if something happened to
them how about you stop wondering and
just [\h__\h] fix
[Music]
it why doesn't it do
something what huh no like why don't you
fix it if this is where we need to go
you're going to fix it right that would
be logical like we we arrived at the
spot where we have to go
to it's not accessible because of a rift
the most logical thing to do would be to
fix
it Zelda will you investigate with me no
I'm guessing my friends are in the rift
and if we find them we can me this Rift
easily oh you want to go inside
huh
no let's have this way we'll need to
find an entry
point uh okay well I mean I would
understand the explanation that this is
too big for this one tree to fix it
alone but it has yet to bring up that
argument
so beautiful
butterfly I like a butterfly oh why is a
chunk of meat there oh you so you do
like the meat don't
you H well I could bait you guys but I
can also just kill all of you
know oh
[\h__\h] my color works it's like
pinball oh damn it no that
way chaos that no go roll roll roll roll
yeah good job good
job oh he's on the fence about something
oh I can like block it
back
no oh [\h__\h] no why did you go
there oh well okay bye stupid
[Music]
it's nice that they aggro it once it
hits them that's good even before it
hits them as long as it's close I guess
ah come on come on Roll
yeah they see me
rolling they
[Music]
hating
uh damn it I know
[Music]
got to be
creative you still need to kill the
other one that fell
off I have
to BR come back up then
o wait I will not come down and stoop to
your level but I think I can ow fight
from here here wait wait wa I was going
to send something down um how about
danger
noodle
[Music]
um go I can't see
it oh I seem that works or or he just
walked off screen and that did the trick
[Music]
too maybe walking off screen is enough
Okay jump back up
[Music]
ah
uh make another
thing
make this
thing and here we go what is it
inside grapes okay 10 grapes but still
like what the hell freaking grapes is
what you offering to
me
[Music]
lame let's go grapes woohoo woo woo woo
woo
no s millas are quite
funny oh
teleportation
nice
[Music]
ooh but there's also a rift here e oh is
there a point to
enter can we not enter from
anywhere I knew it I can sense my
friends in
there you know what this reminds me
[Music]
of what what did you call that like in
in the other Zelda game where we entered
the dark the darkness and then we had we
always had that challenge
to not not in t no no no no in uh
Skyward
[Music]
Sword yeah the the silent
real let's hope it will be
[Music]
different
H yeah let's go in I think we'll have to
go in there and help them then we can do
deal of this Rift properly we can save
them if we work together
telda so what do you
say can I get a hell
yeah wow all right we can get in there
now it's save my
friend hell
yeah what stream died nah did
it we hell yeah too
hard
hello just for a second are we okay W
this is
cool hey is this what would actually be
there I don't know it seems
pretty messed
up this is the still world everything
you see floating around in here was
sucked in for a
rift anything that ends up here will
begin to break apart and eventually
vanish completely oh
no me and my friends have the ability to
restore things that have ended up in
Rift
still speaking of I my friends deeper in
here let's go
zaa okay no
problemo that's pretty
cool
um let's put a
bed over there should we sleep in a
tooth a dangerous place to sleep on
but we like it dangerous don't
we oh is it going to create some random
enemy if it sees us hello no it doesn't
react to me oh oh oh my God it's like a
no okay that didn't uh damage me but the
moment it hits me it creates the enemies
I see how it
is well Fight Fire with Fire attack my
evil little bats my bat
minions I am bat woman now come on why
don't you perceive this enemy
please how do I I don't I don't really
understand how to make it attack what I
wanted to attack is there a
way bad aim kind of off mhm should I
step on these trays or should I build my
own I'll build my
own
however will my whole
construction
fail if I make more than three let's
continue from
here there we go that's probably smart
hey yo there's an old lady she she looks
like I don't know just somehow is
terrifying
[Music]
use your fans as a bridge chicken Bridge
well if only I had chickens to summon
yet if
only when people get pulled into Rifts
they kind of petrify and can't move
anymore and if they stay that way
they'll eventually fade
away but that won't happen to you Z
you're
special okay are you not going to like
help for out or
something what what are you here for
tree what can you
do I know we can fix we can't currently
fix this whole Rift but like do
something about this lady
n what's wrong with
tree
apple nice
okay do you see an enemy over
there go for it okay now the focus
worked I see
[Music]
pre previously it
worked no damn it uh here go for that
one okay the moment I focus on the enemy
it looks at it uh-oh you're going to get
killed
yeah no don't get caught come on attack
it oh my God oh my God these bats
suck when it comes down to it oh my God
for real maybe two is better oh there we
go it's just about timing
really Dodge attack come on oh my God
these dump
beds
um please at least it's distracting it I
guess oh there we go
[Music]
okay we place obviously we
place a
boulder uh hello I guess it doesn't want
to be a boulder what about this there we
go and then we go back o riddle
solved oh
[Music]
why why this
music should I be
concerned I'm just going to bring out
the moblins go go go go you can do it I
believe in you
attack there we go hey what about this
one for your spare yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah oh he can attack
from a distance lovely now come over
here can you come over
here why you jumps on the boxes no you
got to come okay brain cell uh not very
efficient ah now it's now it destroyed
the box at least come on throw the
spare this would be so much faster if I
could be fighting if I could just take
his spare off of
[Music]
him well it works thanks thanks dude for
helping
out he tried his best
no was pretty
good wait I want to see where that leads
is there a map of the oh there
is this kind of seems like an extra P so
I'm going to go
there use
rock you can't make me I'll use whatever
I think is right
[Music]
you guys too stupid are you guys too far
away there we
go no come on shoot it he keeps on
getting interrupted like his shooting
river
ah no I want so I want to get above you
damn it
a send an armadilla armadillo down why
are you stuck here go
[Music]
down damn
it
snake Dam it soke
really oh snake so
aggressive we get him eventually ah okay
there we
[Music]
go baby noodle
man oh 50 rupees I guess that's worth it
we're F of pain let me sleep a little
bit while I'm relatively safe down
here and eat a grape IRL
[Music]
double danger noodle I'm a
genius we love tailes off references
over here at
kfp this is a
scam there are seats in here
it's that
seedless it's a
lie
okay see I knew that was a like extra
path to take not the main path it's just
the RPG senses are
tingling can't tell me this is not an
RPG game when my RPG senses are ting
Ling we could ignore this
guy wait left or right well now I'm not
sure let's
see yeah that feels like an extra P oh y
y oh I don't lose Health
amazing how about
trampoline get it
[Music]
see I knew I could do
it
bounce don't don't no no no no no no no
no I don't want to I don't want to go
away go away go away go away I don't get
exp from you guys after all oh hey
another
one wait isn't
that yeah yeah yeah yeah it's the
left hey I remember this one from the
castle I can restore
you can restore her back to no and we
just ignore the one we walked
by
bro if we meant this Rift oh oh that's
what you mean
oh never mind you mean you can restore
her once we restore the whole Rift okay
okay but she didn't make that comment
about the the other lady I feel bad for
her oh it's on the
tree hey yo what this little
dungeon yeah wasn't important
enough oh this seems like a dungeon if
there's a waypoint
there this is why you were trapped not
too long
ago we're getting closer to my friends
they're farther in but we're getting
there Sor ruins
is it a dungeon yes dungeon oh typical
Zelda dungeon
[Music]
ooh sou
ruins it only two floors or is there
[Music]
more oh
oh Naro don't
do you want me
to
build
eh that's a long bridge I'll have to
build are you for real or just over
either around the void or over the
[Music]
boulder I think I'll do over the
boulder uh it will fall apart though no
wait don't just don't
[Music]
Don't Damn
it
um damn it I don't
know damn it
[Music]
well there
okay now I don't need this table
anymore okay but now the boulder will be
gone a Le there's a lever in this
room
what what are you talking
about no there's
not I'm overthinking it
what
I don't know check the rock
[Music]
oh you they they
are uh punishing me for thinking with
Echoes shouldn't I be thinking with
[Music]
Echo perfectly respectable effort thank
you should have just asked the rock to
move right
uhm are you kidding me
tree you want to move this
thing you kidding me
[Music]
right are you kidding
me
what
oh okay I did see that in the video
mhm it's like in breath of the Wild
okay and we just leave it there
okay
wow definitely an
interesting
function to make more riddles out of
but I was just trying to think with with
[Music]
Echo sorry I was eating chocolate
may I eat one more I only have one more
you had like the ultra
[Music]
hand you also thought you had to go over
right it's normal to think that
[Music]
way perfectly
normal wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait I can't bring this Boulder out of
this like form right
no okay only like side oh wait never
mind if I jump it jumps
too
H cuz I feel like this is my my RPG
senses are telling me this is
um oh wait never mind I don't know which
Pap would be
first but you can kind of miss this part
if you're not smart enough so I feel
like maybe this is
[Music]
extra
see I'm so proud of
[Music]
myself
oh that's exactly like Ultra
[Music]
hand I Can't Believe It's Not Butter
you use the bed to get
there well yeah you definitely can but
with that Gap there I think they want
you to learn that you can move the
boulder in all kinds of ways
huh busted beds
yeah why can't I go down here ah just to
go back up that's just to go back up
never mind okay m m
oh it's float oh it's on the ladder
huh fine with
me fine with oh no oh wait what the
strings ah I can jump from I didn't even
like perceive them
ah I can probably learn how to make a
spider Echo
wait let's send the armor Dow towards it
that should
work a oh no oh they're
pretty
harmless they barely defend themsel they
actually don't defend themselves at all
so if I
summon a
stranda in a place like this oh that's
what I thought it would do that's
amazing it always make me a way up to
the
ceiling how far can we
go can we get much
higher OMG that's that's
insane it may not be useful for fighting
at all but I'm fine with that oh the
dungeon
map that's
crazy sideways I guess not yeah maybe
there'll be other things in the future
that make us a sideways
path what could that be
H I wonder how spider works in the
Overworld maybe it's useless in the
Overworld which is fine honestly having
such a big help in a dungeon is already
op but okay so if I put it here I don't
think it can grab like maybe the the
ceiling has to be visible no never
[Music]
mind
op forget about making Bridges ever
again huh crazy right
Boston what ceiling spider does not need
ceiling [\h__\h]
ceilings uh wait can the spider thing be
fought with a danger
noodle no H St it attacks first
definitely it keeps on cutting off the
the fighting sequence
huh same thing can happen to me and I
never get to attack them the rhythm is
important it's like a rhythm
game
[Music]
H elevator
okay what was H yeah
would you guys always summon more
monsters oh hey we remember we remember
this part I guess I could always summon
more
monsters I don't know I don't it just
doesn't feel right to me oh this one
looks strong oh dear H what's our best
bet come come go go go attack first yeah
another one yeah another one yeah you
can do no no no now it's dead you should
be why don't you have the egg
roll thank
you dark knut Echo dark knut the [\h__\h]
did these mobs always have that name so
far or are they first
appearance
mobs yeah they always had this name oh
my God I never heard it before wait
which is the real
path is there a path there probably
not oh maybe there is ah no there's not
[Music]
okay since Link to the Past
H you have a snake called rope has a
snake in Zelda ever been called rope
before
okay I see we need
fire we need to turn on
every everything in here oh how do I get
there wait a second
[Music]
um okay the fire stays
on
wait oh I already forgot about this
what about this one no this one not okay
makes
sense
armadillo nice wow you get to combine so
many things and switch around I I was
honestly worried that that would get
annoying it might still get annoying at
some
point
[Music]
but so thought it's quite
fun the first useful Zelda besides
pirate Zelda excuse me what about Super
Smash Brothers Zelda that transforms
into
Zelda Chic which I don't know if that is
ever thing in the main game probably
not oh this already the the boss
fight we didn't find the
still oh ocar of time I did play Ocarina
of Time but I was like
five and it like mostly my brother
playing I used to always watch my
brother play games and then I tried a
little bit but I was always too scared
or something why is only this one have a
shield cuz maybe only this one I can
[Music]
control that was
easy yeah I was always like I wanted to
play more but there were always things
like I was not smart enough yet and I
didn't understand games so well yet I
didn't have like this the sense that I
have now this RPG sense and all all that
kind of
stuff and I was scared of evil monsters
you know how I how I told you about
Diablo like I played it when I was young
but I never got past the first the very
first
[Music]
boss one day okarina play for oh very
very like very likely when I just run
out of something to play and when when
there's no Zelda game on the
horizon you know definitely it's up
there but uh it's not like something
that I feel like I need to rush
because you know there's other
things ah damn
it go go go go go go go go before it
sees
you so
dumb honestly so so dumb these bats have
one
IQ there you
go all they can do is flap FL FL FL FL
FL
FL Mama
Mia what is this for is this for
returning oh hello there sir um um would
you like to have a conversation about
our Lord and
savior Lightning
[Music]
McQueen absolutely same Rhythm so they
die together no problem for me I can
summon endless amounts of these dudes oh
yeah you got the first hit why why is
the Agro still on me bro you're so
[Music]
dumb linking make Link Link Link
heart another heart oh boss fight
perhaps with these generous
[Music]
pots ah the chest is in the map I knew
there was something right there but I
thought it's maybe like I didn't look at
the map I thought it like goes around
here and then you jump down from the
ledge there
um okay
uh wait how does the speeda ACT
here I was going to waste my time making
[\h__\h] stairs let's
go
[Music]
who amazing amazing so useful holy
macaroni good that I tried because I
kind of doubted that it would
work watch it you forgot the spider
there I would have
too I doubted that it would
work okay let's switch to something that
can
attack o oh we're
right y it
it is that the person who fought the
blue monster don't tell we have to fight
Link I
[\h__\h] l
no evil
link I'm a
ballerina okay God I have to oh God he's
slow he's not very not a very bright
mind oh he takes up free
[Music]
Echo is is is it even doing
damage no it seems like it um okay okay
have to like crush him instead
could always use uh stanula but
um ah he jumped
[Music]
up no no I could try to cut him off
again wait wait um
[Music]
uh it do all of my mobs not do any
damage on
him I'll
try
[\h__\h] got to overwhelm
him okay um ropes come
on ah ah stop chill okay I think we got
it oh there we go there we
[Music]
go s
SS more Saks spaghetti making the pasta
making the link hates pasta
he hat bu
away do you have a problem with
gluten is that what it
[Music]
is
ah I think we're doing damage right guys
are we are we are we
do how about
this P pin ball come on come on hit him
hit him hit him no also he broke one of
the pots I don't know if I like that
uh-oh n he blocked
it you think I hit him okay I would hope
so oh they're too expensive shoot shoot
shoot shoot shoot Sho yeah ah he blocked
it okay look at me then he probably
let's let's bait him over here if he
looks at me he probably won't block it
ow oh there we go I I I accept the
sacrifice yum
y link come over here
[Music]
link oh but he's n he's oh he did no no
he did block it a look at me look at me
look at me there you
[Music]
go I think I heard it
it a
[\h__\h] yeah good job good
job really slow strategy but it it works
hey look at me look at me look at me
look at me look at me look at me look at
me don't hurt my pig don't hurt my
pig no okay let
[Music]
me ah no o he's aggressive don't steal
my
[Music]
heart hi hi hi hi Cy Cy Cy Cy
oh proo passes him from behind oh wait
what I thought it was over ah no my
heart no
no he's always guarding now he's always
guarding now hey I'm here I'm here look
at
me link why why why why do you hate me
so
much link I'm here I'm here hi hi hi hi
hi hi a [\h__\h] a [\h__\h] wait maybe maybe
there's something
better could be good if he looks at me
look at
me you B what he's going to kill me link
you love me don't you
remember you blocked it what
ow no no no no I only have two pots left
like I can do this right but I only have
so many
pots snake and moblin gets him pretty
good
okay think about like combining it like
this I
attack guys oh
no
[Music]
no come on spare spare yeah yeah the the
snake can be the bait I don't
care Sho a finally as long as they look
in the uh and a different direction was
better come on come on come on let's go
around it's quite
something no no look look at the Snake
look at okay well if that's fine ah now
I had two snakes y be
by
[Music]
[Applause]
accident okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay is this ridiculous guys
am I doing bad oh good job
snake
wa oh no yo yo yo snake getting some
good hits in this really feels like a
Pokemon battle in a
way my spare guy is really dumb
[Music]
why is he so dumb
no what was that a let's
[Music]
go nibble his ears come on he he likes
it it takes so long
though wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait oh Bight bite him in his ass bite
his own snake snake versus snake come
on
no my's
bucked that's just
cheating he was malfunctioning a little
bit at the end there that was funny he
only needed one more hit so we can
accept that ooh do I get to use that
that looks
like that looks like like one of those
like things that you cover up images of
hot hot spicy
pictures and you try to hide like she is
probably wearing clothes you know but
you hide exactly those parts to make it
look
naughty look that s sensor
that was intense yeah it really
was he looked like the guy who helped
you before but this one wanted to hurt
you what is laugh baby don't hurt me
don't hurt me no
more what is laugh baby don't hurt me
more he was weird like the imposters
back at the castle Yeah we get it now we
get
it looks like he left something
behind may I make use of it wait let me
get the plts
first
okay that was quite challenging for
maybe I just did it really badly but I I
feel like I tried everything I could and
I was thinking with Echo but was quite
challenging you got a mysterious sword
it's the weapon The Swordsman in the
green tunic had I don't think link ever
had a sword like this before looks
nice it's rough
yeah you learned how to summon more than
one big
Improvement well I was trying to summon
more than one but most of them were you
know know either you could summon more
than one because it already costs too
much but then I I didn't realize that I
should combine maybe one with two costs
and one with one cost math
sogy link is engraved on
[Music]
it I feel powerful energy coming from
that sword even more powerful than the
large
Rifts yeah that sword has a special kind
of power
[Music]
race sword
oops wait Ian rickle says when you raise
your sword like that you probably should
shout Revelation but I got some energy
you feel a mysterious might growing with
in you wait did did the sword
disappear do I still have it yeah
okay why did I get that energy now
what wait what ah wait I wasn't raising
the sword I was Raising tree
Revelation whoa what what I'm a hybrid
now
[Music]
what what what the hell
you look strong like the guy who wears
green what the hell raise his sword with
up to enter sword Fighter for what any
time defend with your Shield by pressing
and holding that L High than usual hold
down wi to charge your
sword
what all the time runs
out
hey so I do get to like find a little
bit Yi so I return and then when can I
do it again the energy GS in the upper
left corner of the screen will decrease
you'll automatically exit the certify
the form after the energy garge is
depleted you can also exit this form by
pressing up you can refill your energy
garge by gathering the energy
oh it might be super rare
huh yeah I saw the timer but I was too
[Music]
excited wait a
second
[Music]
speed
op oh
[Music]
what is that cute what a heart
pin this hair pin has a distinctive
heart design it makes heart to a cute
a well I shall wear it seems to be for
noobs but I don't care I will wear it
well we haven't really looked at the
inventory
properly
not okay I'm wearing it is it apparent
in my looks no
[Music]
cute energy is found inside Rifts
aha did I like run into it randomly the
one time where IED it
or I didn't see how it like
happened isn't this
there's still more to this dungeon
huh incredible oh my God I thought it
was over oh got a little bit of that
energy oh here too it comes towards me
nice ooh boss
door all right all
right nice okay so I guess we got to go
[Music]
left hey y'all wait
uh I can't transform so danger noodle go
attack ah good job dang a it's
overwhelmingly
[Music]
strong yeah I've been getting Super
Mario
Vibes with this planed enemy and the
door looked to me also like out of Super
[Music]
Mario oh
okay can we jump through the this weird
pattern
no or are they just too dumb for
it no okay I have to get through
it oh okay I can still fight
[Music]
you wait my bat went through I think it
glitched through though I don't think
it's allowed to go through
[Music]
there how' you do
that wait there's another are they just
endlessly spawning
[Music]
there is that allowed is that
allowed who but it dies
[Music]
fast no come here why is it flying away
you were supposed to come towards
me well uh it's okay um I'm going to do
this one first anyway um
[Music]
you do the job up there you can do it
alone
right good job who's a good noodle
you okay wait what the hell why give me
give me that give me
that what about the dark nut can you do
something about this
nut sword what sword I don't have a
sword
wait because I I can't tele I can't
transform yet as long as my bar is
not uh loaded up
right
wait hey I thought I had to fill it up
to the
max
huh oh it does it just extend how uh say
how long I can be in the
form oh this whole time I thought I had
to load it all the way up
[Music]
n wait left or right where should I go
left I'm guessing I couldn't have webbed
up but maybe I could have you know
sometimes we underestimate the little
speeder okay in this
case ah
baby
[Music]
H can
I make something over there uh I
can no I don't want the chest but I
mean no no no I want to no I want to
undo this ah H that's not what I wanted
wait if I
jump uh no wait there we
go wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
release it one more time then get it on
the
trampoline and release when it's up no
it broke it
no okay
um I did not think it would break I
thought it would jump
up huh
[Music]
ah I'm so dumb I'm so dumb
I but I figured it out this took me a
[Music]
while like I was making while this must
be here for a reason right it's not just
like a viewing platform
[Music]
okay okay but we still didn't get like
a uh a key the key would be nice don't
you
think a never mind we can go here didn't
realize we don't need a key just
yet we'll get a key from this
[Music]
one that's ter
terrifying oh I feel bad okay that will
be a
key you can just rip it off its
stem
damn all there's the key
kiaha I have a funny funny word for you
guys
kfp kfp
what is the key to your heart key
[Music]
waah oh my God isn't that
cute oh these ones I can't
move
why but this one I can move
okay oh wait ow wait
[Music]
what am I
yeah smart what a Smart
[Music]
Cookie I don't
know if I was if my way of thinking
was making
sense but because when I captured it
here
it wouldn't go much further back I don't
know so I captured it
here and then Ste further smart so smart
how do I get up to that door though
maybe wait speeda for
what speeda sorry for forgetting about
you it's just you're so op I can't
believe it oh okay well the door is
closed maybe another time
are you Ina in
k i I am quite a pun Master on my own
[Applause]
[Music]
too does it go up and down
too feel like it could
[Music]
this one goes up and down
maybe oh yeah
Zelda there's one more thing you can do
when using bind after binding yourself
to something with X try holding R while
holding R your movements will follow
what you about I
know I I
know
bro looks like a chicken face
[Applause]
but wait
what what's but what about making a path
for me
though wait I'm just going to use my
spider why the hell wait are they
assuming I'm using the
spider
maybe Hold Up Oh you mean I can like
kind of hold on to it
wait
R okay I get it all right all
[Music]
right what
spider
[Music]
move what happened with
you why' you have why did you need so
much time to think about that
one you good you feeling
sick oh no ceiling H
[Music]
oh come on Snatch onto
that no you're going to block my
way uh wait
uh uh but well it ends there no
wait no go
there the timing is
off maybe From
Below uhuh
no
ah
ah I'm stupid for the too stupid to do
this one
[Music]
I'm
thinking can I reach no damn
[Music]
it ah
s do I want to connect to it from Below
[Music]
a I don't know I don't know I'm
confused how did I get up
[Music]
before did that did that always stay
there
oh thank you ah yay let's go
oh it's going to cut off
no sorry brain Energy may have been
depleted at this point of
time I'll just go onto this platform now
and then we continue to
think yeah yeah that's what I was hoping
for but it just didn't overlap
previously I feel
[Music]
like uh yeah okay ky gy ky gy it was a
close call cuz I went back for some
[Music]
reason okay there's another
one and oh no no go down go down go down
I'm not
done go down go down sounds like dangle
dangle
dangle does the spider help me
here yes it does I don't know how else
you're supposed to get up
[Music]
there oh oops sorry I'm getting confus
with the controls
now go away spider
sorry I'm confused what am I doing just
open really 20
rupees actually I have a lot of money
now didn't think I would have this much
money already rich
wah I'll invite you all for some
burgers how about that ooh the master
key is there
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay how
about can I jump while I'm controlling
it
oopsie yeah I
can oh wait there we go easy wow that
was
fast some riddles I solve faster some
slower but we always get there in the
end guys is there no compass in this
game because the map I don't think it
normally was supposed to tell you
without a compass where all the chests
and everything is but it did tell me so
I'm guessing they combined those two
things which is
fine I prefer that I appreciate that
are we I forgot guys I I I lost track
are we still in the
rift or are we out of the rift right
now yeah we are okay I got stuck on that
puzzle for no way well we get stuck on
different things right the other thing
you know I was being stupid about
platforms and and the the path up ways
took me a while to realize that
previously
nobody's
here but I definitely sensed my friends
in this spot
earlier what if they're evil too
now oh hands once again wait there's
more than just
hands what
that a that's a
face it's like one of those Ian REO
enemies
why do I compare everything with Ian REO
now
huh my friends they in that creature
I've got to get them out of there come
on we can do
this
okay uh wait a second can I control his
hands I tried I tried even was too slow
or it just doesn't work maybe I'm scared
[Music]
what do we
do for now let's see if my mobs do any
[Music]
damage I don't know did
it oh it
does oh let's go just need my aim to be
good ah it kind of just stopped there
but there we go oh easy what what now oh
wait uh I forgot how to uh here there
you
go did it suddenly fill up my energy
completely okay I'm aill let's do this
oh I'm aill let's
go go go go go nice armor Dillo nice one
armor Dillo
oh go go go go go no get down get down
get down get
[Music]
down get down get down get
down I feel like there's a better way
besides armor deos but I don't
care and now now he now he doesn't come
down
[Music]
anymore yeah I could get the bat but the
bat sucks I need to be faster here and
the aim needs to be good ah oh there we
go that's what I was waiting for that's
what
I there we go the [\h__\h] angle the
[\h__\h] angle the freaking angle
man my armadillo keeps on rolling
carelessly so
Carefree honestly I could try to
stay Zelda Link
it's still giving me energy
too can I hit you okay wait
no yeah I'm waiting for that I'm waiting
for
that oh there we
go you need to jump up on him and then
still jump
again did you guys do it that way
too I don't know if that's
oh you would go about it
normally yeah you can use bad
still but I brute forced it
somehow cool right yay I feel cool now
yay you did it with the grab oh can you
oh like when he's down there with his
hands down can you like pull it out like
how we pulled the plant out of its stem
maybe definitely you can probably do
that well there's so
many Zelda these are my friends we set
them free they're filled with energy and
ready to get to work so now we can
finally fix the ri here using our Echo
ability we can restore the entire area
that was swallowed up by the rift watch
this yay so
cute they look like those ice cream
balls the tiny balls you
know the Water Ice cream tiny balls I
used to love that something about them
being balls was just so
good Dipping Dots yeah Dipping
Dots
International seems to be an
international
thing
W first Rift closed in 3 hours probably
kind of slow
but we were chilling oh that's where we
need to go you forgot a tree ha
[Music]
stupid I wouldn't say they're
clothes the granny is back give me my
friends shared some of their power with
me
[Music]
y I feel like I can do even more
now oh yeah also they told me something
while we were fixing the
rift they said that big rock monster
showed up and captured them so then they
weren't able to fix the rift because
they were trapped inside the
[Music]
monster and one other thing there are
crystals that show up when we fix Rifts
they're neat so I'll give them to you
[Music]
Zelda what is this unusual crystals
unusual for
sure ah
H what it loads it up one time or did it
make it longer
[Music]
looks like be moo what what's
that I'm all finished up here so we can
head out now if you're
ready on need your Crystal 5 what did
that do did it just load it up once or
did it do anything besides loading it up
thanks for the pinky 3:00 a.m. all time
yeah I started a little bit
earlier you know secretly I wanted to
sleep more and and uh start later in
order to sleep
more but I thought you know I like to
start my long RPG streams earlier so
that we can play longer and also you
know every once in a while
having sea
viewers start a stream at a reasonable
time I'm sure you guys appreciate
it hard
container we're up to
five let's
go that was yeah that was good boss
fight like the link fight was good and
this boss fight was good the link fight
was quite a struggle though link fight
was more difficult for me
[Music]
the RI that was here is gone now which
means we can reach the place you were
trying to go to earlier if we keep this
up we'll be able to fix all the Rifts
and we'll be able to save your father
yeah yeah
y save my father but while we're fixing
the Rifts don't you think they'll be
making more at the same time or are they
stopping for
us that would be
convenient you there a moment of your
time are
you oh they gave you such
a voice for some reason I will not stand
for that I'm Le minister of hyu pardon
the intuition but could you tell me
where ah she doesn't recognize me I
thought you forgot me
ah oh Prin is Zelda oh I'm embarrassed
to admit I didn't recognize you in that
cloak oh why are you wearing that oh she
has probably no memory of kicking me
out cuz you're a
[\h__\h] I'm sorry no we failed to save you
from the Beast and now you're out here
facing so much danger I failed as your
dad's consultant [\h__\h] yeah you did yeah
you
did no was her to me was her I must
confess I'm surprised to hear of your
abilities and your friend tree
accompanied you this whole time yeah
yeah thank you so much
tree you can see me who could miss you
you're floating right there and AR why
could impa not see it
[Music]
okay they're like either one of them is
evil or like just has something to
hide or this is like an after effect of
having been in the in that state once I
don't know
H yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah
weird interesting I guess we'll find
out oh because the echo's fixed her yeah
maybe so after you're in a rift and it
gets closed up maybe you have this
ability to see
it oh so lady inite could see how OD
there we
go all aside I'm worried about his
majesty and the general we'll need to
make a plan there's much to consider but
for now let's head to the location lady
Ina told you about oh I'm getting ahead
of myself would you mind showing me your
map if I recall
correctly yeah that's the place that's
where lady impa's brother lives makes
sense she'd send you there lady
brother did we meet her brother in other
Zelda games before you lead the way
let's
go should I not check what's up there it
was just a the dungeon I guess entrance
ah follow me come
on
sorry is he
[Music]
single not that I can remember no you
don't h
interesting first time
lore we're so blue
together right in here
[Music]
princess
H well this already makes think of the
Shaka yaka girl or whatever from breath
of the
wild cuz of the music and he seems to be
yeah crafting they're like
P
Pur how did I say her name in the back
in the
[Music]
day check
it check it
wait was
Pura at all related to impa I don't
remember is this eat oh God please
no her sister okay so maybe they you
know just didn't feel like putting Pura
into the game again and thought okay
let's make it into this brother instead
he's a funny ha
hairstyle half bald and cute twin Tails
going
up H hello sir pardon us but my name is
Le lady impa is my colleague
and I'm a very busy man I'll
TR oh I apologize for the unannounced
visit but please will only be a
moment no no no no I'm about to leave
come back later if you could just hear
us out I said no I've got to go save
[Applause]
link
blueberry I like
how he looks funny uh his jiggling beard
is
cute hang on there that's Link's look so
why do you have it did you see him
well a what
oh tell me everything tell me about the
Rifts and anything you know about the
[Music]
swordman I understand the situation now
thanks for explanation
princess H we finally got through
him C all right this has been bugging me
ever since you barged in here what is
that Floy thing oh he can say it
n M oh you're telling me H maybe the
more energy I don't know what the hell
you're telling me we're the only ones
who can see you that's
OD indeed such a fascinating and might I
add adorable
creature yeah sure but like the matter
at hand what is it that you and I have
in common we've both ended up oh Alo he
did come out of a rift okay and lift to
tell the tale it seems the Rifts change
people somehow m oh yeah I guess I
should introduce myself though the
name's blueberry I older brother older
brother and the swordman who save you
link I made his weapon the sword of
Might oh tell me more about it Mr L why
did you make him a sword why not he's a
warrior princess remember that big nasty
blue fell who captured you the sword was
for taking him out see I spent my time
researching H's history and its Rifts
fores now Rifts have appeared and
sometimes folks have ended up in them
those un fortunate enough to be pulled
into a RI vanished Without a Trace after
which Town's folk would say they'd been
stolen away anyhow link made its mission
to fight the monsters that come crowling
out of the rits he also tried to prevent
vks from going missing and I've been
helping as I'm able to which is why I
made him a sword one that's effective
against the rift monsters oh
specifically
those the sword of my Princess Zelda
willing is of everyone I hope would be
of use to
link so link was helping out with the
Rift as
well hearing all these stories about
this mysterious link Zelda must be
falling in love with him already even in
his absence it's like he's just
AFK playing a game AFK The Game of
Love everybody's his
wingman sorry I moved around and that
caused some harm it seems
oh
no are you chilling
now please
chill plent H plenty of monsters come
out of the rich but that blue one was
particularly powerful I've got to hunt
it if we take him out it'll fix the
whole people disappearing business
princess you share that link managed to
take the blue guy out you shared that
link mhm and yet the rips keep coming
clearly we're missing something the
first is gone but links are back what we
need is more
information I may have something useful
thank you oh my God for 42 months let's
go when I was taken by The Ripped in
hyal Castle I felt like I was flown
somewhere far away yeah yeah she was
completely in a different
place the rift I was pulled into was a
Tyro Castle but Princess Zelda found me
in a rift in the forest how did I end up
over there
rfts don't follow the same rule as your
world things conect differently inside
of them my friends had mentioned
something about oversized Rifts in other
areas we might end up finding the king
and other missing people in far off
Rifts so maybe link is somewhere else
[Music]
then he
link hey
Fela sorry
[Music]
things you know I'm going to fly up high
to look for some of the other big
[Music]
Rifts I think I found
some there's no saying where Zelda's SP
and the others might be but at that spot
some big Rifts we can go explore it
[Music]
I've marked them on your map what
happened with my voice I've marked them
on your map
[Music]
Zelda if we fix the Rifts we may be able
to save your father and the others so
let's get to
Rift for the
tree uh princess sta I must insist that
you refrain from going to any more Rifts
it's F to dangerous well who else will
do it yeah yeah luberry supports it
there's that for her to decide Minister
I mean she's the only one capable of
vending the Rifts obviously during this
time of crisis in hyu we all have to
play our parts princess Z
included you make a San Point Mr luberry
but princess I urge you to go and be
suicidal by going into the Rifts and you
know risk your life I urge you to do
that you're the only one who can do it
usually it would be link but now it's
you Mr you stay here and help me
investigate the Rifts we will play
support for the princess oh of course
investigations are my
specialty princess the RS marked my tree
are located in the guda desert and the
jabul waters please let me know if you
require further information all right
princess I'll leave it to you to find
the king General right and
Link there may be some other people
along the way oh I almost forgot the
sword that you've got there I'm pretty
sure I can make it even more power than
it is I'll have to do more research on
so talk to me later if you're
interested jaul Waters might be love it
what what do you like about them so
much does he live around here all alone
is there no
Village for people like
[Music]
him cute
cute I want to
read can I really
read the crystal I uneed at the rift
side what I'm now calling a might
Crystal has strange power the monsters
that sprang from it from the Rifts
seemed repelled by it if I can get
enough of it I feel certain it would be
powerful against the rift
monsters he's a Hermit
yeah the Lord
[Music]
is it those crystals you picked up early
yeah I think
so talk to the big blue boiler upstairs
to up oh okay I will talk to the boiler
yes after many late nights of research
I've developed a technology that can
refine the crystals from there I'll be
able to create a weapon from the
crystals as well as enhance that weapon
so now I'm pondering pondering wait
pondering P what
what Tim Allen awakes inside of
me P I don't think they
were I think what they no because it's
the shape of a ring they called it ring
and then pond lingu
maybe I don't know I don't think I don't
think did they just use the English word
like why though what what what would
would what would be the the reason to
use that
word I need to look into
this oh named after the Brazilian PW the
qua
bread okay but that doesn't sound like
Ponder ring at
all a maybe a pwn Pawn maybe Pawn is
like maybe weird pronunciation of pan
Which is bread or or I don't
[Music]
know maybe if you
translate h p no uh po
Theo maybe it will translate to
something that makes more sense like
that does
somebody know Portuguese and can
translate that
is that just cheese
bread
H okay we're thinking too much about it
let's stop pondering on
that I was near attacked by a monster in
the forest when a young man named link
rescued me folks and stuff in Village
told tell me that link was among a group
of kids who were stolen
away what these kids made it back
somehow though remarkable all the kids
who were taken by the rift have lost
something for link he lost the
[Music]
there's an explanation for why he can't
speak in this
[Music]
case what I don't think there ever was
an explanation
before yeah and it's Canon that he can't
speak it's not just like you know they
were lazy to or just didn't want to
bother with it you know make it a
thing oh my God but that doesn't
necessarily mean that this is the reason
why he can't speak in other games of
course because like there were no Rifts
in other games unless this is this would
have to be the very first Zelda game or
or wherever he if he was able to speak
in older games you know it would be
placed whever you know he lost his like
he started being mute but I think he was
mute since the beginning
right B the wild gave a reason for that
specific link too what was it was he
just try I don't remember what the
reason was
there I'm over pondering it's not the
same yeah yeah right it's not the same I
know
that
so there's always different things going
on and different
links it was shyness and stress okay
okay okay which is well yeah okay this I
like this reason
more I like it
more like
link because of being so shy and so
stressed he seemed pretty chill most of
the time honestly and if he was so shy
why would he be wearing those female
guito clothes eh
eh I don't think he would feel too
comfortable with that
honestly he had
to kind a Brute Force I don't know like
wear female clothes that are more cover
up I don't
know if you're that shy would you really
want to expose your tummy like that link
I wouldn't want to I'm not even that shy
and I'm I'm I'm very very shy about
exposing my
tummy it's the desert well yeah but you
know in hot areas people cover up more
somehow apparently that keeps them
colder I will never really
understand
that I will not wear long
sleeves when it's hot because yeah
blocking the sun I don't know it doesn't
feel it just feels hotter to
me this just feels hter to
me it's like the
shade no because it's also covering me
and making me hotter
doesn't work on me I'm a
phoenix can only be hot I can only be
hot yeah trapping my own hotness can
make me explode in my
case oh yeah I'm sure it keeps my skin
safe and I I don't I wouldn't get a a
sunburn which is
great wait now let me look a little bit
for my Discord manions for a moment I'm
nervous
[Music]
H
order
[Music]
uhuh
wa not do
[Music]
okay anyway finky lost the ability to
speak despite all he has been through he
fights to keep others safe his bravery
has moved me
deeply then it hit me this young man he
hit me no would be the best person to
UST this sword of Might to I do believe
I can support him in his efforts
tomorrow well it's not like he could
have said
no to receiving the sword huh the sword
of might I interested to link pxs [\h__\h]
against those Rift
Monsters uh as I
hoped but it doesn't seem to be enough
with the blue monster who we believe is
creating the
Rifts he can still shake his head I
guess
so it is a fearsome monster indeed I
suspect the sword is not yet powerful
enough to defeat him however I should be
able to further enhance the sword so I
must gather more might crystals Link
stopped stopped by on his way from home
uh from his travels to home he likes the
hood I gave him the other day while he
cannot speak his feelings come through
as clear as day I've decided to make a
new weapon I must do what I can to
continue to help link a it's like he
kind of adopted him Link stopped by he's
off to defeat that blue monster once and
for all it's like his child keeps on
coming
back was kind of cute
he seemed to be in a huge rush but I
couldn't figure out why the sord of
Might has been forged as best as I am
able I gave him uh some of the other
weapons too like the arrows yet I can
help but worry please stay safe and
return to us link
H very
insightful okay let's what is it not
this machine I guess I got to talk to
you
[Music]
can you
yeah yeah do something make it stronger
[Music]
please see that machine in the corner I
designed it to enhance the sword yeah
looking at the sword seems like it's
lost some of its power oh
no okay let's
enhance sorry I need to stop doing all
these voices now throat hord
wait I didn't
realize I didn't realize the Australian
Super Chat where's a danger
noodle wait you're from Australia and
you're danger noodle so
fitting check the machine in L's house
to enhance your weapons using M
[Music]
crystals K be snck snck snck snck
nice
snake uh oh my energy you mean the bar
like it will be
longer but we only have five so we
should do the
energy and now we should save for sword
in the
future oo it's going to
explod or
not energy gosh is now level two
oh quite a bit longer
nice let's grow it together with our
hearts
[Music]
bar it's already longer than it it's
bothering
me all right very cool oh oopsie that's
not the exit very cool person very cool
lore very cool insightful
things that we have learned
[Music]
here should we go to the left I guess it
feels closer so we probably would want
to go oh yeah um the thing also the
glowy thing is also over there on the
left let's go YY I wonder if I can
summon the horse or or some kind of
Mount
I do remember seeing horses in the
[Music]
trailer pretty sure I saw
one while Wasing the armor oh thank you
I'm glad you like it I haven't used the
armor outfit in a while I feel like I
would normally prefer to use it for more
serious kind of um
RPGs y this is more the cutesy type of
RPG so maybe visually not the best
[Music]
fit but it
works but next time I I will use the
blue
acids okay are you guys happy that the
rift over there is
gone oh your life is back home
yippe just like is that what's in style
now no I am
link hello there traveler mind if I bend
your ear things have been a mess lately
what I fixed the rift tell me about
something happy so I go on a little walk
and what do I find a giant plant that
flies but wouldn't you know near those
caves deep in the forest I lose sight of
the thing wait did he tell us the same
thing
before and now we have a quest okay that
must have been the first time then
how do
[Music]
I that must have been a side quest how
uh where
[Music]
to ah there it is an elderly man from
saon Village is hoping to cheer up his
wife of a flying plant he last saw it
near some caves deep in I want to do
this but where is
it
uh huh
near some caves deep in S I guess we
have to find it
ourselves the forest is like which
part I don't know I'll go
here no the yellow dot is just the other
region that they um marked remember they
marked two regions of big Rifts and you
know this is the main quest how do I
understand this better than you guys huh
huh are you not paying
attention I'm supposed to be stupid
[Music]
guys okay we need to find a cave here
and a flying plant nearby how come I
haven't seen that
before maybe it was covered by the rift
before but is this still considered the
self en
Forest leave me alone
[Music]
did it say in
oopsie near some cave not in a
[Music]
cave you're smart and elegant thank
you that's a
fairy flying fairy not flying plant
that's where we just came out
of near some
[Music]
caves there's a cave or something like
that there
and that's did we go there
before that's where the dungeon
is follow the blue do
but the blue dot is where we got the
quest
Doo I feel like we just have to find it
on our
own near some
cave
oh did I skip a wayo you think
so well anyway
[Music]
cave cave
cave what about in this what about in
this new region but that's not the
forest
anymore but look at that I saw that in
the trailer wanted Princess Zelda side
to send wor the king of Hyrule no can we
burn
it I got to burn
it no we
can't come on set it on
[Music]
fire anybody who did this side quest
already yeah the tales off game wanted
posters were similar and also goofy
looking
still downloading the game there was a
double torch cave I thought i' been in
that
[Music]
before but I'll try to find it again it
was somewhere on the right side but oh I
got to go up I
guess can I climb up
here
no danger noodle has it out for me
[Music]
you have you
have you do what's your problem with
[Music]
me but it shouldn't it should be near oh
well maybe it will let's
see what was that learn the the the the
the
Torches
H braier
[Music]
Echo have I not been in here before this
looks
familiar oh never mind ah that okay
that's a flying plant is that near
another inside okay all
right is it spiky it looks spiky what do
what should we do
ow
ow oh no
[Music]
no hurts it hurts
stop no
help do
something burn it can
I it's on fire oh let's go what I can
learn this one will it come out so big
as as I first encountered it
that' be
crazy yeah it's pretty big is it the
same
size I don't know if we should really
give that to the lady what if it's like
showing its spikes and then kills his
wife I don't know about that
man I think I was supposed to fight it
here and not run back to the
exit but you can't tell me what to do
all right then can I teleport while I'm
inside that monster made the link up
what you got the monster before did you
get the quest before too ooh Z
red Z thank you
[Music]
wait so wait do I just present it to him
or do I just spawn it in
here I think she likes it oh she
scared I've been told that my husband
kept calling to me when I was trapped in
the rift oh she's the one that we just
walked
past Hello everybody welcome we're uh we
have just begun the new Zelda game today
it's been quite nice so far so a little
bit of spoiler I guess but we're not
like extremely far in the
game feel free to
[Music]
stay I have been too scared to approach
it that's made me fall in love with him
all over again I'd be embarrassed to
tell him that
[Music]
meat it's done cooking stop cooking it
anymore otherwise people will get so mad
at you for overcooking steak they lose
their minds over it you can't do any
more than medium
rare Legend Of Z no Legend of Ki
here can't you read
okay uh yeah uh well let me show you
hi
what it do a plant I saw you took the
time to go find it for me well thanks
traveler I should go grab my wife I she
want to take a look at
that what
what this things are not plant at all
it's a mon yeah that's why I said maybe
not a good idea but okay be careful of
it spikes but don't worry I have it
under control I think
[Music]
help I really had no idea what I was
dealing with I'm sorry you went out of
your way to bring it to
me what it did kind of teer her up
though I
think don't worry honey you went to all
the trouble just to make me oh oh she's
coming from the inside is she coming out
where is she where's she coming
from what
[Music]
that's not your wife is that your
mommy did you hear all
that well your voice does car you know
there was no need to do all that for my
sake I'm perfectly happy as long as I
have my darling husband with
me what was he doing it for someone
else's wife I'm I'm
confused oh shs you've always been good
at making me blush once things settle
down all there what do you say the two
of us do some
traveling is that his mom I'm confus I
should have like more consciously read
the text
maybe is it is eh
[Music]
what explain to me
chat is is the is the one in The house's
daughter
[Music]
huh that was his
daughter thanks for bringing me what I
asked for here's something for
you okay side quests are worth it I
thought I don't know I didn't even think
about what I would receive but I
wouldn't expect anything like
this oh so okay those things they charge
me up in the moment but also you know I
get to use them later to
enhance
enhance I've got all the time in the
[Music]
world yeah that's way better than rupes
let's
go hey complete nice stamp I feel so
stamped we didn't look inside here did
we oh no we did but now they're in here
together cute
cute now they're thinking about where to
go very
sweet I'm guessing that was the only
Quest
here all right what's the best
way to get up there I'm assuming I have
to go around
here so I shall do
that you didn't look in the house in the
upper left corner oh
oops should I is it worth
it wait is there no warping point on the
village don't freak out but you have a
Triforce in your
eyes I'm wearing colored contact lenses
[Music]
today am I just too blind to see the
statue I don't see one
[Music]
guys oh my God I had to go in
here no I want to make a nice fire okay
look his
that
a but that's like the only thing that's
hints towards him I mean the owl could
be a Ocarina of Time
reference but besides
that they should have put more hints in
here just one
[Music]
hat h
but
cute Link's house yeah
cute so we saw we saw Zelda's room we
saw Link's
room nice you got a a cute little cozy
house
there feel like that would be a nice
place to
live but I wonder was he born and raised
there too or did he just kind of end up
there I need more
[Music]
lore all right this area is
new these enemies are
new oh
no go dja
noodles yeah attack attack
well that's not fair oh no my danger
noodles are so committed they jumped
into the water because they wanted to
help me but no wait the plant flies
maybe don't don't don't let it hurt you
come on come on no go go go
yeah wow let's
go can float over the water wait no I
want to learn this
[Music]
you wanted a swim but you died don't you
regret the
spaghetti should I send an octo rock or
one of these pea hats again I feel like
I want one of
those go for it and then the next one I
don't get hit oh yeah we're on the r
baby we're on the roll ha cleared the
whole area
[Music]
can I jump on top of it maybe
not wait we should got that Treasure
Chest up
[Music]
there let's go get
it yep how do we get
[Music]
it do we have to make a weird
construction again
[Music]
um is that enough it
is what rock salt it's rock
salt these clumps of salt crystallized
open a long time you can't use them in
the current form
seems like we'll be cooking a
[Music]
lot Hi boss hello did you just arrive
welcome to the stream we are playing a
new Dela
game yeah we've already been to the
first dungeon and cleared the first
dungeon that was quite interesting we
have made
some
interesting encounters with
link ooh a new Crow I hate these kind of
crows I feel like they had these crows
in
um what was it uh the other one we
played the other cute
[Music]
one
W absolutely killing it yeah Link's
Awakening oh oh they got absolutely
killed too oh
no come on a few more hits there we
go link Awakening didn't they have these
kind of crows there Maybe
not maybe I'm imagining
[Music]
it I think we have reached the gudal
desert
[Music]
ooh what the hell this music is straight
out of Super Mario 64
okay without the flute without the
flute oh my
God
the that's straight out of Super Mario
64 don't you hear
that oh my God wait I can I have four
now I can summon two at the same time
this the same instrument yeah and the
first two courts are the
same oh my crows are killing
it oh my God they they spread money
[Music]
everywhere kind of chaotic right
now but why not
oh no no no don't hurt
it
ow
Dam come on do
something
yeah dear God am I in heaven
why why what
happened clutch heart get it was I down
to one heart I feel like I heard the
sound for a moment but I wasn't
sure why is the stone up
there why is that stone
there I must get it down it
seems
K you're right it could be
wait I can reach damn
[Music]
it
no
no one two oh
[Music]
damn
it huh wait a second
[Music]
no
no can I control the crow I feel like
the game would have told me by now that
I can control my own animals like that
but can
you can you attack It Go For It Go For
It Go for it buddy go for it Go For It
come on go
[Music]
here I'm sure there's like something
there I need to find
out I can't let this stand come on La
think
think with
[Music]
Echo
ah
ah just took me 5 years to think of
[Music]
that I can't believe
it oh works
too wait I I can I can still only summon
three things right never mind I can
summon four things I was thinking that
something would disappear if I
sumon well whatever well I you know I
have to think with Echo but I also have
to think with link that I can now you
know use him to jump
higher if I must you know it's good to
keep that in mind as
well Mama
Mia at least I also realized that I can
use
four four things
now that alone looks like a Pokemon down
there
[Music]
okay I'm guessing I will
sink
no okay that's cool gdo
desert well what kind of dessert is
it is it like with strawberries or is it
with chocolate
[Music]
I'm sure there's a rift we can get into
somewhere around here but this desert
seems really big I wonder where we
should start looking I guess for now we
could check around the area with the
biggest
Rift a rift in the gudo desert let's go
let's go let's gudo
hey what do we want to what do we want
to attack you with
snakes ow
no
way no no come back
no no it's going to endlessy follow it
come on come
[Music]
on sick of you I'm sick of you
Shenanigans
jalap ooh g r cooking what I still
haven't cooked a single thing when are
we going to learn about that a
echo okay now I'm sure they can fight
each other better than any other oh God
come on turn
around uh-huh well mine survived oh look
at
that sax acent I don't know if it sounds
similar to Australia I would say if
anything the Bayern accent sounds more
like the Austria Austria
[Music]
accent this place is so big let me look
at the
map
interesting I really want some kind of
Mount but as we know as I know from
breath of the wild a horse would not
help me in the desert anyway
[Music]
go to the ranch you think they'll give
me a
horse wait which Ranch we haven't seen a
ranch yet have
[Music]
we yeah good job job good job snake
taking on the big boy wao you too all on
you got the ribon right huh hey y that's
a sad face a monster Stone these strange
stones form inside the bodies of
monsters oh isn't that like that when
like um
like uh when your bladder gets
Stones looks like that if it's inside of
them what kidney stones is that what
what you call
it I think in German we say like bladder
stones
don't tell me if I'm wrong
what what are these
[Music]
what it's a fish a fake fish it's a
shark it's fake I'm sure that's just
like it's wearing clothes wait it looks
like it's wearing a cape get out of
there you little [\h__\h] have challenged
me now get out of there
ah no
[Music]
what the hell are
you okay maybe it's not wearing a cape
but it looks funny it looks like it's
wearing one of those wrestling masks or
so peee
[Music]
Stone I I've gotten used to the bgm so
that it doesn't make me think of Super
Mario 64 anymore but I will stand by my
observation
[Music]
let me
in could I force my way up there
or but maybe there's no
point miss the Fast
Travel is it on my map oh wait why don't
I just go there Mama Mia Mama Mia I went
all the way around it several times
H the monsters just keep coming I'm
completely worn
out I hear you but if we keep at it then
that big rift should start
shrinking we can do this we'll get rid
of that Rift and take back G rud of
section I believe in you but wait I came
here should I talk to you
yeah my point tells me to go here
they got different kinds of birds up
there it looks different here cuz it's
hot is it bald on its head because it
looks so shiny up
[Music]
there Southern French jump scare does it
scare you do French people scare
you what's why um wait let me
I think maybe that that is just like a
random
PIN I don't
know where where is
the
[Music]
statue thank you thank you very mucho
there's a I'll get there probably later
anyway maybe it's a side quest or
so at the
entrance
H well well well
why does the porn tell
me to go here when they have no reaction
to
me the crow collects the money
what while it's following
me oh hey another marker
and I think this is where where we
really want to go
[Music]
to a little shop huh oo melon the honey
to it's not every day I see another
Highland in the G desert if you're
wondering about that tent z a gudo
researching something oh in I'm sure she
could use a hand if you felt inclined
might I take your mind off all the Rifts
but I thought you were going to sell me
[Music]
something
what oh my God what are he called
again
D no
way wait attack where's my Crow my Crow
is
gone oh don't worry about
it is so freaked out fish why are you so
stupid are feish just inherently stupid
oh my God there we
[Music]
go um how dumb are they what why did you
go up
Mama
Mia stupid as hell what suon the second
one this one's a bit smarter it
[Music]
seems are these both mine now
okay than I haven't seen you in a while
I don't think there were any digles in
breath of the wild and Tas the kingdom
hey there I'm a business SC oh welcome
to my brand of the smoovie shop
smie there was really no there
weren't H most people say no no kodok I
wouldn't count
them they were C by then eh do they
trans uh what
trans form I forgot the word
K are evolved di excuse me doesn't this
look like the absolute final evolved
perfect form of any kind of life form
like better than the human form there is
no way no way that CS are above in the
evolution of This Magnificent demure
mindful
being sorry got a little bit excited
this is
pink this is a place where you can craft
your own freezing taste for bling
smoothies the process is simple you pick
two ingredients and I blend them
together so come on now let's get to it
ready to make a smoothie hell yeah I got
some stuff oh you not going to I don't
have
recipes
oo oh resistance to cult a similar to
for the wild
okay h no recipes is it too risky to
make something well I mean surely floral
nectar with apple I don't know if it's
worth it mixing a grape in
there wait no I don't want resistance
never mind I'll I'll make this mix
movie oh you want money from me
ripoff I'm bringing the ingredients and
you're charging me just to use your
stupid mixer
peace some there some that mix it all up
with a Chey pant all righty I'm not
going to say that because you you're not
allowed to know the secret you're
smovie oh that is adorable the straw I
haven't had or like seen a straw like
that in a
while cute
let's make everything else that I could
possibly make oh you added the recipe
great now that I already found it out by
myself my siblings and I are new to this
smovie game and to keep hold over the
market we're opening branches all over
hyru but that's been so much work we
haven't had time to come up with new
smoothie
Concepts so what would you say a joint
venture you make recipes and we have a
little business sign M come up with 10
recipes out of ing from your travels and
we should be in glitch shape oh and then
do I get some percentage some royalties
sounds great yeah thanks for the help
we're throwing a reward before you go my
sings are running smooy shops in other
places too we're all sending ingredients
from our local regions to the main shop
back home if you run into any of my
sings give it my best
okay recipes please all righty 10 you
say I don't think I can make make 10
right away but he I wonder if you're
supposed to mix the floral nectar even
with like butter or rock salt or if I
should wait for something better to mix
it
with oh wait
no
yeah I'm not putting in two Flor
electors right now right no no no no
okay let's make the resistance to cold
smoothie for later surely will need it
at some
[Music]
point what should they call their
business has something like kfp um but
with deu and with
smoothie de's smoothie shop DSS or deos
smoothie Venture
dsv something like
[Music]
that
what does it need a
grape
too but is there any way for me to learn
recipes somewhere like secretly written
somewhere like on a wall or so for
example well now I don't want to make
anything else
meow a cute
baby oh my God you scare me those
glasses oh I can learn new beds why
would I learn new beds are they
bigger old
bed e they look same it just looks
better can I
replace please tell me it replaces
it no it's more I maybe it heals
faster doesn't it
oopsie cuz it's so ah yeah okay makes
sense makes sense
y guda soldiers and dances used to rest
here but now it's to's based for mango
research mango toas trust to trust that
Chief s will figure out what to do about
the Rifts here in the desert so she's
keeping her focus on plant research
knowing it will benefit everyone's
future yeah researching mangoes what the
hell it looks like a waa fever knite
poster ah please speak with me directly
if you'd like to try mango Rush it's a
game oh hello there Wonder welcome to
the tough mango plant lab here at the
lab we research effective cultivation
and preparation for potential food
crisis my current field of studies
focused on tough mangoes after much
research I've successfully developed
tough mango seeds that grow at rapid
rate sharing the results of my work
should help countless people in the
future there's just one little problem
this mangle plant Rivers as quickly as
it grows so I'm unable to harvest fast
enough I can't compile data if I can't
Harvest properly at this R I'll run out
of funding for my project in response
I've begun en listing Fox to help with a
little game of manga rush you can easily
harvest the mangos with a bit of force
like from a
spin here there's a participation fee up
front but I've got a gift for you if you
harvest a lot of them would you like to
give it a
[Music]
try she's one of those screaming people
that don't realize her voice is too
loud H I'll need 10 Rupees for your
participation fee is that okay uh great
head downstairs to the field and wait
for
me this just looks like a underground
farm in
Minecraft mangoes can be harvested with
a bit of force but too much and they'll
burn
up H okay are you telling me don't turn
into link cuz she did talk about spins I
can spin as Zelda and I can spin as link
but link spin has a
sword I'd like for you to have short
more mangoes if you do should I is this
just normal Zelda spins I
wonder no wonder they don't grow no
sunlight pretty sure mangos come from
trees oh this is different kind of
mango oh I hope it's the normal Zelda
spin oh are they going to randomly there
we
oh
okay do they only grow when I got rid of
some others or will they eventually if I
were just to stand somewhere oh God yeah
okay they're popping up uh as as they
want
now this fun oh it was going to
disappear there don't
disappear can't have you do that the
music is fun too I you got to go to
which ones came first yum no no no no y
oh we got
45 do we get something do we get a hard
container if you get 50 or do I already
get it
Exquisite Divine you've shocked me I
didn't think anyone would be capable of
harvesting that
many here you are please take this tough
mango reviews fans for some smoothies
perhaps I have a feeling you get a hard
container at
50 exra dangerous
seats vibran SE I had them Sha but I'll
make an exception for you if you want to
see them next time come haris whenever
you like I'll be there ready for you
it's like a heart
mode
yeah yes
ooh vibran SE should we first try to get
50 on the standard or should we maybe
H 50 going to be a little bit
difficult I'll try
[Music]
I wonder if the order is always the same
then you can kind of learn it after a
few tries what where to run
first all right oh
[Music]
God yeah it's the same
order already anticipating them
oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] oh they all came at the same time
no no no
[Music]
no I I did it oh wasn't too bad second
try oh well done I didn't expect you to
harass all of them oh thank you for such
a valuable data I've got a large amount
for you to take with you too more
mangoes but no hard container okay then
it has to be in a hard
[Music]
mode now that's how you mini game yeah
baby spinning makes me go faster oh
really oh [\h__\h] no no sorry
yeah then I should be spinning more but
didn't wasn't there something about I
think maybe she warned me because maybe
if you spin too much you'll get dizzy or
so is that a
thing they say Sprout sharp porn but I'm
sure you'll have no trouble
harvesting can I still turn like spin
into them
she says she's sure I'll have no trouble
really maybe as long as you don't walk
into it and then spin maybe as long as
you spin into it you know what I
mean you spin for traveling because it's
so much faster okay so I guess you don't
get dizzy
[Music]
oh maybe they get thns after a while if
you give them too much
time cuz right
oh ow oh wait I don't need to harvest
that okay now I now I know what's up
ah oh dear
ow no
ah I have to
be how do I quickly get up there do I
become link
quickly uh I wa I can't
[Music]
much I can't summon that fast okay
well she doesn't give me [\h__\h] bruh okay
uh trampoline might be
better although bad
has oh yeah I can set it up when I have
some time
beforehand while there's not too many
spawns
yet okay
okay I forgot how to place
things is it
why it's why must be one
oh that's
fine maybe even more would be good
for more oh oh oh okay I see well the
trampolines get
destroyed if something grows
there got to hope that it doesn't grow
where y already
[Music]
a
close almost had
50 BR okay but they didn't get destroyed
in the locations they were so the
locations were
okay wait did I choose standard or
vibrant no [\h__\h]
H did I
accidentally
[\h__\h] all
[Music]
right I already know where they
grow let's get used to always spinning
[Music]
this too easy
now ah it's too
easy but the
the spiky ones are definitely difficult
cold well we get more mangoes yippee hi
okay I
need I need to finish the vibrant
challenge I don't think this will be the
run but I'll I'll
try okay let's place
them where I had one here
I don't know if that will get destroyed
I'll Place another one
here no no why did no it okay uh maybe
maybe it won't spawn there again in the
future spin
win nice
[Music]
I got ready for
those oh we're at the end we're at the
oh I'm doing it I'm doing it I'm doing
it I'm doing
it that's fun that feels so good to get
it right
W let's go what do I get I get a golden
fan yeah the one that was on the wall
she took it
[Music]
off it's pretty what does it do
just holding this glimmering fan made
with golden feathers makes you feel
glamorous okay great what what not only
that but you harvested everything you
incredibly skilled well then I was able
to gather extremely valuable data thanks
to you here's a bon
escap okay that's fine too I thought we
might get a heart container but that's
[Music]
fine yeah I'm surprised that was the run
I was speaking of V Fergy too g
l a
m oh a r o u s flying first class up in
the sky drinking
champagne living my life in the first
past Lane but I don't care about the
Glamorous O The Flossy flossy and the
Glamorous the Glamorous glam
all the
Glamorous
the and then the the
R I need to sing that song in my next
K spelling is
hard g l a m a r o u s
yeah wait how many mangos eight h
oh what there's more okay that's why you
get the heart container
huh you have St the flame that burns in
my we research Soul this is nowhere near
the true potential of T mangoes I'm
going to develop something even more
amazing it may take a little time though
come Harvest whenever you like okay so
another time you're going to
have what burning
[Music]
mangoes
H why thank you for the membership gift
of course they have gutas in this game
they got to have gutas in every Zelda
game okay but I guess not they don't
have them in every game
huh but in most of
[Music]
them well well well facette doesn't know
and she's the chief's a so where are
they oh just muttering to myself sorry
about that I'm kalian Oasis guard
guarding the Oasis is my priority um but
I've been Ted with another mission
recently I take it you're not from here
are you in which case you might be able
to help me in your travels have you ever
seen tiles that can fly through the air
yeah I think so in in the dungeon if
that's what you mean or maybe not maybe
you need mean something else according
to my boss's research ancient gudo used
them to chase off unwelcome guests I've
been scou the desert in search of these
tiles but so far nothing maybe you'll
have better luck though if you find one
could you bring it to me what a tile
flying tile okay well well maybe we'll
find it on the
way so wait you're not going to sell me
anything H
okay all right all right all right let's
move
on oh
they remind me of Wind Waker I do I do
think we saw them in one of the like
gameplay
trailers what do I want to find them
with speed
snakes who sent them
flying oh I'm sure that was fun for
them come back come on come on hey no
[Music]
can you shoot at the he I never saw the
treasure
chest damn
it they don't shoot oh actually you hit
that one nice oh nice
[Music]
yo what about
no aim do whoo wo W wo whoo wo nice nice
come on one more
hit oh here we go one more
hit what the
[Music]
hell where is that
[\h__\h] sometimes you got to do what you
got to do come back come
back no no I'm running out way
there we
[Music]
go if you want the job done right do it
yourself I suppose is the
motto okay you guys can stop
now what I got to open that you would
think
the the dick would get angry this item
can be used to recover Hearts but it's
more effective when mixed into a drink
oh like a strong
recovery like better than the one I
already made
before interesting
[Music]
no that a flying TI what wa wa
where no that's just a
fish there was a check
[Music]
oh
oh so is it a landing post for a bird
person no
way wait
no oh who is this clown looks like
[\h__\h] Animal Crossing dude you're
stamp guy are we having a stamp rally
you look like you're from Animal
Crossing I thought we were meeting one
of those bird people
[Music]
again I've love stamp since I was a tiny
T now I iroll been
stamping but you curious about this
stand this is a stamp stand a stand for
stamping stamps aren't stamps great the
plunk when you press on down to leave a
stamp behind PL tacular from start to
finish that's why I love a stamp rally
traveling for stamps collecting them all
sounds fun right well I've created a
stamp rally with stamp stands all over I
roll ready to Rally I bet you're rally
rally rally
excited I
[Music]
guess yeah you are yippy okay here's
your stamp cards okay stamp cards are
pretty cool if you get something at the
end of it and if they're not too hard to
fill what would happen if you said no he
would
[Music]
cry I thought it was going to be tingles
he's got tingles
Vibes this time kind is uh for stab R
beginners it was Handmade by the stab
guy and it looks like it oh hey don't
roast him I know you're going to have
fun because I had fun making
it now going stamping like you've never
stamped before
is that supposed to be
you great work what a
sty look for a stand like this all over
the world and get every stamp but hey
there aren't any stands on the water or
in buildings and they're not in caves
either that would be way too dangerous
for my taste also I can't fly in like
that you know I'll give you a reward if
you fill up that card with stamps push
yourself to find
them should I stamp him with a B ER
coming from the sky H okay all together
now ready St St no go stamp really I
didn't see that one coming you going to
stay here for
now want to know my story oh God glad to
share I'm the understand I love s i show
the St release on and everyone will know
the F of pluging a
St and that's the end of St oh that was
short w
Angry Pig new version of angry
pig
whoa
[Music]
who get him get him get
him who he dropped some
item his
s
to mon thing demon Fang double demon
Fang get the fish get the fish get the
fish yeah
[Music]
ahk come on why does the snake always
have to suffer there we
go oh man I must be a genius oh look at
that it's an enemy
camp let's use the torch
Nando
wa can it go up a level or does it stay
down there I think it
stays yeah you're in a good
position oh don't get hurt by the
boomerang here's another
bird attack of the
birds wait I can control them can I lead
them to the bird
[Music]
wa I'm energetic today really I'm glad
you think so it's a fun game I it makes
me energetic gives me
energy here I'm holding him hostage for
you guys amazing life hack guys B was
never an
option van vanilla Coke HS a little bit
a little
bit keeps me awake at
least seven warm
Peppers oh this is sinky sand for sure
and we
don't wait the same thing happened to
link it's not fair but let's
attack ha well at least we set him ah he
got himself stuck
again he got himself stuck again let's
make it short
[Music]
where are we where am I who am I
who
a I
[Music]
see
uh I made it but I'm not sure if I
really should try to get here
[Music]
well I'm getting closer to the rift
that's good but I feel like there should
be something here and I'm just not
seeing
it oh yeah I'm having a lot of fun with
the game we've been oh we've been
playing for 5 hours now
huh I wonder when I should stop and I
did say I wanted to maybe do a Super
Chat reading next week a Super Chat
reading stream but I should still read
some super chats today
right and then what do we have
tomorrow tomorrow
was ah the Team Fortress right
oh oh wait that was
here team fores yeah I do not want to
end too late today because I do still
want to record some hand motion with my
gloves because Kana ubu asked me
to re re-record my hands at
least apparently
the studio data wasn't perfect after
all oh [\h__\h] hey it wasn't like that
before ah it's a fight or is it one of
those worms and sand worms oh no what do
I do what do I do what do I do what's
the best one maybe this
one go get him go get him maybe I should
become link but I don't have enough
energy to be
link what the
hell maybe I can ah maybe I can control
it
though oh oh oh oh oh
oh and
now are you kidding me oh attack how am
I supposed
to what okay I pulled it out but then
what should I place my
octopuses don't don't sink oh no it's
sinking actually the octopuses might be
pretty good
[Music]
it pull pull pull pull pull and now and
now I don't know what
H oh okay it's doing something it got
two hits
in this is pretty a
bit oh
okay okay come on ah it's too far yeah B
oh one more one more one more
[Music]
hit just place them in better ah it's
pretty far though that's not good N I
want him to come over
here ideally
[Music]
but the the octopuses they're quite nice
they're like shooting Towers I can have
quite a bunch of them oh
[\h__\h] get him get him get him get him get
him and sh sh sh sh ch ch ch ch ch ch ch
ch come on yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah
ah yeah tackle turrets oh you get
destroyed sorry about that all right
actually that one might be too far let's
put that one
there oh he's sink there sinking ah [\h__\h]
I forgot ah no I missed my
timing
[Music]
h i
see get over here get over here oh no
mainly got some
hits yeah yeah yeah one more oh we're
done but it just leaves that's not
satisying
F what no I ended the fight
somehow I didn't walk that far come
on no don't tell me it reset itself
Health that's just that sucks it took
too long I'm trying my best
here okay I got some new things figured
out I have my Army ow
my hearts are not looking so good should
I actually
heal uh I do have
um do have the drinks but they heal so
much maybe I'll just eat a
mango for
[Music]
now what that wasn't the time though
that was I guess the distance I think it
was the distance not the
time because that was the Lally just 10
seconds hey you got to be really careful
with where you're
walking oh the heart where did the heart
go
bro it frows
[Music]
pots are you kidding me are you kidding
me
am I supposed to do this fight at this
point of
Time how does that not end the fight I'm
so far oh but good good job good job
that's that's a good amount of damage I
think careful
[Music]
ah damn
it he's on top of
it
I get him no get him no
get oh I'm going to die wait let's eat
something
[Music]
sh sh sh sh sh sh sh my your s sh my
your
s I'm many more octopuses have to die
for this monster
[Music]
y
y ah what how is this spr so
strong am I not supposed to be doing
this so early
[Music]
on come on
my monsters are just that weak but it
kind of works it's a good
stretch I think it's a good
Strat I'm expected to do this post
dungeon but I can win it right I can I
can win it I think I can win
[Music]
it would be op yes let's go
sh
let this is like some serious boss fight
men
huh do I get an ability to walk in the
snow because like snow in the
sand after the dungeon because he keeps
on shooting Healing Hearts uh out of
pots but like they're unreachable for
me
no no I worked so hard on
that
whatever I'm going to do it after the
dungeon but that was so close
[\h__\h] what is
this a little
spers you
cute don't get bullied by that tiny
oneeyed spider you win just because you
have more eyes than
it automatic
win yeah Taco turrets are
fun I hope we get more stronger turrets
in the future
we should just burn all of these
suckers
oopsy do
something they're endlessly spawning I
think fatal Mount Echo so if I spawn
this there'll be endless speed Us coming
out
crazy so KN to have an Overworld boss
with an unmarked fail condition yeah for
real no that is really uh too little
distance like I'm literally just pulling
him out and then I fail but then another
time when I stepped pretty far back it
didn't
happen that was pretty
lame but it was exciting nonetheless I
had fun o full charge
okay cool that was a little
[Music]
surprise now no damn it mistake um I
thought we would find an opening here
cuz that's what we're actually looking
for but the PIN is also still there but
I think the map the the quest wants me
to
find the rift stop by searching area
around the large Rift
yeah so I don't think I'm wrong
you like spamming
bats damn it why do I I did that again I
did it again I wanted to press this bats
huh maybe I should spam some
bats
oh we're out of that area
[Music]
okay guys I think there might be an
extra stream coming uh that's not on the
schedule
either this week or by the latest on
Monday
[Music]
maybe adding something new
still
yeah we got a it's a it's a collab um
not a one-on-one collab even so we we
still got to figure out like timing
but hopefully it will work
out oh my God no is it the
scos
no no I hate
them
no no not taco t sales team no
no hey I got a way point ah no they're
screaming already oh no I hate them I
hate them I hate them and there's so
many enemies I forgot how to
fight do
something what is you
doing they're spawning endlessly I think
they're spawning endlessly
help no
don't the rain read that I hate
them forgot their
[Music]
name is it more calm here it seems
so calm enough to
[Music]
sleep they got the Wind Waker design is
that
[Music]
so that's rough man
they're all spawning around the ruins
how do I best fight those freas I just
got to stay away from that oh
hello are you guarding maybe perhaps a
possible entrance into the rift
somehow huh you're not a guda what do
you want hey for the first time ever we
don't have the problem by the way of uh
you know being a
male we we don't have to like we can we
can actually talk to these ladies
without dressing different
L only those authorized by the guda
chief are allowed to enter noo the guda
chief where is the Garuda Chief oh
hello oh you found something now I
already ran around here I
think I had a feeling it would be
there but that was the best
part would be funny if had to dress up
as a boy somewhere somehow for some
reason I can create a rift entrance
beneath here come on
Zelda oh you can't come with me can you
oh so what should we
[Music]
do had the feeling
we go try talking to her maybe she knows
a way you can get through to
sand
dig just
dig what you again get for the sand oh
no you aren't getting past me only those
offer I don't think she's going to
move oh
she what was that is someone hurt I have
to stay at my post otherwise I'd go see
what's going
on no just go there check it out so that
we can go through
there no it's a
Princessa oh she's
cute is she
okay wait she's so cute she looks the
same like the one from face of the
Kingdom
stop talk what do I do do I move her no
yum I'll tell her about it the princessa
R yeah R is
there you just going
to
what okay I'll try to but don't they
keep on
[Music]
spawning oh [\h__\h] beds won't help
now how about about one of these big
boys oh yeah oh
yeah oh yeah oh that did do the
trick okay she looks a little bit more
adult than
oril but the hair is similar
no what happened the monsters they all
gone a should defeat them for
me it seems they post no threat to you
and yet I assistant VOR couldn't handle
them thank you Mercy Buu you saved my
life I suppose I should introduce myself
I'm Donna Donna like Donna in German is
funer but not written like that the
captain of the
of but I wonder they must have done that
on purpose maybe it's also similar in a
different
language because fer makes a lot of
sense for them a d a c
up what's your
name nice to meet you selda has she
never heard of my name before so what
brings you out of this
way oh I see I see ah you're traveling
around fixing WFTS uhhuh
you you're fixing
Rifts pardon my ah pardon I was right
pardon my sh it's just that the Rifts
have been causing us serious trouble
lately we heard that taking care of the
monsters would also take care of the
Rifts but it
hasn't the Rifts haven't gotten any
smaller and the Monsters keep coming
without end it seems if we could read
ourselves of these cuz the cuz that rft
and then nobody else would end up
getting
hurt hey Zelda do you think she might
know how to get you under the
sand no way she's going to teach me how
to get under the sand and then I can
fight that stupid mova or whatever way
easier is everything all right
[Music]
s you want to Burrow under the sand
M well the S jum is beneath us oh I
understand now you think you can get rid
of the reft if you get into the
[Music]
S you like my friend wife thank you
normally the entrance to the sanctum is
where we are standing uh but as you've
probably noticed is flooded with sand
now so nobody can get
inside if if you want to get into the
sanum we first need to clear out the
entrance how can we clear
it it's better than my British one guys
somehow it's easier to make the French
accent even though British one should be
easier I feel like
sand a soldier is guarding s back
entrance entrance if we go through there
we could clear the sand out
of course we doing that would release
the monsters as well our chief gave
orders to keep it block force of safety
so I'm not sure how to
proceed if you want to get into the
sanum we first need to
oh the sanction was pulled into a large
Reef after that tons of monsters began
swarming out of the entrance to the suum
at that point we blocked up the entrance
crapping the monsters inside if it's
like too much I start to like not know
what I'm saying
anymore in order to get rid of the rift
you need to get into the sanctum
right oh
understood well then it sounds like we
need to discuss things with the shef you
saved my life so I'll do all I can help
to you and if you're able to get rid of
the rift that means means our Warriors
won't be injured
anymore let's meet up at a palace in
guto town it's just Northwest of here
Northwest of here you guys don't need a
French member in whole life you've got
me I'm frencher than any french fry out
there or french toast normally only gero
allowed in the palace but I'll put in a
ver for you ahead of time all right
Zelda I'll be waiting for
yourself FR
[Music]
Joe wa I want to look at the
map you're going to the
Oasis no we're going to Raton why did
you run that
way she's fluent in French maybe but
she's not French is what I'm saying guys
I'm French maybe more French than french
fry at least is what I'm saying
[Music]
let don't even talk to me
buddy hey
ha our science might finally come in
handy I mean it didn't it doesn't have
to be the science although how do I
place them when
[Music]
I maybe not sign Maybe not
today
easy
easy damn it damn
it no
dep perception ahit I didn't see I
looked at the chat well I guess I made
it why would I learn
these that's my favd freaking
pot what does it do
differently maybe
it's
heavier does the pot do something
special
no why did I learn it
here just ignore
this what the
hell this looks exactly
like a room in a different Zelda game
where there was a lot of sand that you
had to suck up
gives me
Nostalgia what what are I I'm still
wondering what these things are
for can I move them
no I have fire but I don't think I have
wait a second I was going to say I don't
think I have anything that blows well I
do I actually do
I didn't realize this at
all surprise
[Music]
surprise but I can't select the sand
pillars that I
want
oh oh good job oh good job
oh secret
treasure mayhaps a secret treasure
I like how they're being sent
flying what are you
doing oh sorry about
[Music]
that oh wait what can I use the fan some
but it's not an summoning item
right anyway
I can learn the way
[Music]
oh ah this one I didn't see it I mean I
didn't see that it was sparkling like
that my screen is kind of bright over
here
so it's harder to see the difference I
[Music]
think but you know all these things are
optional
so at least like Echo like these are
optional I think like echo in main
dungeons you probably some of them you
have to
learn but there's always one way
around like an optional way oh
okay
um what do we want to use
[Music]
this
one fight for me ah no
[Music]
wait okay you know
what no wait my plant is flying all the
way up there
now can you guys come
down
hey come
down oh
well
no oh good job buddy it somehow worked
out how often do you go to France if you
don't want to say just say what you had
for why would I not want to
say why would I not want to
say what is that a weird
question but
also why why are you curious about that
is it because my accent is just so
[Laughter]
accurate I've been a few times I don't
know
maybe three four no probably minimum
four times by now maybe four
five oh wait I've been there already
yeah Europe is convenient and
uh I've been there once to just
um
sighty and then once for Disneyland
because Paris has the only Disneyland in
Europe and a long time ago for Japan
Expo but I think I only went to Japan
Expo
once in
person never admit you will why
not there's no shame in
that but yeah France Disneyland back
then it was pretty
mid I've been to Japanese midy midney
land
mid Japanese Disneyland which was not
mid really has always been a place
meure
um
and French
Disneyland but I don't think I've ever
been to any
[Music]
other all right cleared up another big
region nice I'm not going to walk in yet
I'm curious about over here what is this
[Music]
all right I do it I'll do it with the
wind machine
[Music]
now ah wait stop no stop wait what if I
what if I make them look against each
other will I end up in the
middle purple
[Music]
let me
up how
convenient Disney in the states
extremely
expensive I can
imagine did I just F find a secret
entrance that I wasn't supposed to
know oh there's a lot of side quests
here and this is like big sea
meow wait can
I
no if
only all right what's wrong with you
girls what see the woman sitting over
there she was stolen away a long time
ago and she has she only be also became
mute before that she was a really Lively
chat box she was telling the dad that
she's changed a lot since those days RI
are really disturbing things how did you
get her out of there
[Music]
H wonder what that does for
us
[Music]
sorry I'll I'll I'll put it away now
talk to me
yeah L again hi hello welcome to the
stream hello there highly uncurious
about me I'm one of the many G soldiers
I'm off duty at the moment but doesn't
mean I'm not going to slack on my
training my confidence comes from my
agility and gra behold my
skill what of the blank expression it's
almost as if you don't find me
impressive well then I prove my skill to
you hand to hand
tag tag oh all right oh is she going to
cheat I just have to run after her I
[Music]
assume oh you get a head
start you can even block the path if you
want oh [\h__\h] I should have prepared some
item wait wait oh [\h__\h] ah ah wait I'm
confused
maybe a
[Music]
box so
close how come I can't touch
her all right all right girl
just got to get her to run into that
part again
[Music]
no what it's literally touching you oh
okay ha no what oh T
ha it didn't give me a prompt before but
now it gave me a
[Music]
prompt was there a
timer was is there an invisible timer
maybe or she's going to make it more
difficult
now no oh no more
Quest I feel like there's no level up to
[Music]
that oh aen I'm impressed you made it
all the way here for the desert you must
be quiet the Explorer to like Dora the
Explorer ha come on this way which
reminds me um I'm looking for these
elusive tumble weeds maybe you've seen
them in one of your travels so you can
find them the yeah I've seen them but
can I grab
them can I control
[Music]
them vamos
Amigos the tumble weeds shall be mine oh
there's one there okay
so no no don't hurt me
ah
H oh I should just jump I should just
jump
[Music]
probably ah
wait I don't know I need to keep it
behind me maybe I was thinking so too
just
now
like don't hurt
[Music]
me if
I God I made
it if I let it go it will continue to
move right you
B we're too distant
[Music]
a don't you maybe the main entrance is
easier I haven't even tried walking
through that
[Music]
yet I just need to be close to it be
careful is that is that
[Music]
safe all right
o wo
oh I love this
game this game Zelda games Zelda games
good ah seen the delicate dried falling
and explains why they tend to break so
easily no way it's not right this is
just particular type of plant matter
what are these poke bits H the more I
look at it the more fascinating first
person I met to find these kind of
things
fascinating oh I could spend all day
gazing at this beautiful full
magnificent tubble weat I would find it
fascinating too when I would see an IRL
though my dream has come true my wish
granted oh what did I get
oh more crystals we must have a bunch
now they have such peculiar shapes don't
they yeah well okay we already did two
side quests
here um
no no no no
no no no no I'm sorry I'm I don't even
know I don't even know I'm looking
for
this
bro you made me worry for one
second that you had something serious
and concerning
you little [\h__\h] is there no other thing
to light
[Music]
up another
cat oh this might sound a little odd but
do you believe in tornado ghosts I see
oh you want me to bring you one I
already got one
M
easy
hey ghost
boo well he might really have that I I
believe it
[Music]
too it's it causes people quite the
suffering it seems terminal
it just chased me because I wanted to
send it wanted to send me flying across
the desert it didn't anger I didn't
anger in spirits I've really been
overthinking things well that clears
that up I suppose thank you for so for
helping me blah blah blah blah blah
milk let's go
ooh you guys got to teach me recipes
where are the recipes there must be
recipes written
somewhere I can't have to guess every
single one of them
howdy
yeah the weather sure is nice today
isn't it on days like this I feel like I
could sleep forever same no I could
sleep forever on any day though you have
a lot of fruits here do you know any
recipes sorry had to do it looking for
recipes don't hold them hostage tell me
about
it no I'm not going to cheat it
no 99% you got to guess really oh look
at those shoes where
do a they prevent the word from taking
comp wow 400 I could almost afford it
bro really that's so
expensive are you sure
lady will I get them cheaper maybe for
the main
quest no way right I mean there must be
a reason why it's in the store
[Music]
I sell oh only these
things collectible are these just to
sell or like
better not to sell
[Music]
anything well I got to save my money it
seems
[Music]
um no what am I doing I don't know
what's wrong with me right now see I've
been playing this game for too long
today and I can't stop myself but I
should probably stop myself
[Music]
soon yeah I'm losing the ability to
think it is clear to me now
[Music]
W what's the secret
here something to
gain why can I not do
anything why can I not interact with
anything in the
[Music]
room yeah I think I've tried the crow
already you guys hear crackling sound
because I certainly hear
it there's a cat up there I need to Res
res skue it I need to save
it
[Music]
oh it's definitely there
now I can fix
it I fixed
[Music]
it no
say more cat say more I came all the way
for you and she's just like leave me the
hell alone I'm up here on the roof so
that people don't talk to
me all right what's the matter here do I
burn the lid or something
[Music]
well I'm on it now what do you mean it's
just decoration I mean there must be
some kind of reward for me coming up
[Music]
here wow that flies
far what could I possibly do
[Music]
okay I give
up the meow was
my where's a cat cafe is that a cat cafe
are you kidding
me since the appeared to be Warriors
have inviting non stop pressing in shift
I'm off duty but I might do a quick
Patrol on my walk pitching a bit
more yeah so little one who do you think
the next chief will be do you think it
will be Donna don't you you're talking
to the cat I don't think the cat will
give you an answer H can I help you it's
R to stare you
know she was talking to the cat don't
ask such deep questions to the cats
they'll be very very confused
they talking to each
[Music]
other what about
you
cute but besides that nothing in here
really
perhaps now I shall go inside the palace
I totally forgot about the point pointer
or the marker in my never mind I
actually want to go in here
first oh they're fighting they're
training in
here okay no talk now
okay h
I am special I don't take the main
entrance ooh
oh
oh there's like an even more mature
version of The Princess we
found I'm very much enjoying the game
thank you I cannot stop myself but I'm
think I'm going to stop after this
conversation with
[Music]
them Chief Sarah S I don't know I have a
report concerning the blocked up
entrance to the sanum as predicted the
number of moners is
dwindling ah that I've been waiting for
you chief chief this is the hen I was
telling you
about with her help we may be able to
get rid of the giant re here here in our
desert but in order to do that she'll
need to get into the sanum if she can
get rid of the rift rid of the rift as
she claims will finally be done with
this long
battle to this end will you please
restore the entrance to the
sanction Captain Don do you comprehend
what he said you asking if you recall
after the sanction was consumed by the
rft the surgeon the monsters began for
the town Safety we blocked the sanctum
entrance to prevent the monsters from
coming out since then we've been
eradicating the rest of the monsters
which will fix the rift blah blah just
let me open it trust
[Music]
me we should be acting with urgency to
be rid of the rift they keep on saying
that as soon as possible and Zelda can
help you can't expect us to trust this
toer hello I am the princessa
you said Chief's Chief's daughter I'm
shocked by your severe lack of
judgment
bruh peace
foret my
[Music]
chief I understand the concern you feel
for the Warriors I feel each injury to
our viors as though it was my own that
said have you seen this alien Eradicator
Rift
I did it already believe me how can I
prove
it maybe I should just summon all kinds
of things right in front of their eyes
and it will make them realize I am quite
powerful and
worthy also did you notice she has a
thunder Trident
amazing they don't trust me I get it
really I'm wearing female clothes and
you don't trust
me what do you want from
me I am s
[Music]
Princessa
disrespectful not very mindful not very
demure she saved my life how dare you
speak of her like that I trust Zelda and
I will prove that she can get rid of the
re thank you let's do it
together we don't need their permission
no matter how many monsters they fight
the rift isn't going to go away on its
own Dona is correct about this so why
won't they trust us
[Music]
Impostors did they get
impostor well well how do I save this
game here I save this game for the first
time
perhaps will both sides better we'll see
we'll see I feel like maybe you know
they'll be nicer after after we save
them from
themselves I saved
[Music]
Right double saving is
better
[Music]
okay
tired we played for almost 6 hours that
was fun
a good start into the game you guys have
one day to catch up with me and maybe
get a little bit ahead of me if you
don't want to get spoilered because
we'll continue this on the day after
tomorrow so
this really good game so far I'm so
happy to to be playing this game well
let me look at something
oh oh I didn't mean that
oh wait I just saw something uh
[Music]
h
no I didn't type a whole essay I only
tyed a little
bit it's important because it's about
the 3D model I'm trying to make but we
already lost so much time and now it's
really tight like barely any time left
to uh like get
things like
[Music]
proper yeah yeah yeah
yeah I've been kind of stressed out
about
it because yeah it's not going ideally
but
hopefully it has to make it in time
because
otherwise I don't
know it has it has to it has
to hopefully we can catch up in time
[Music]
somehow well okay I don't know I don't
know I read a few Super Chat
let's use my RPG office while I'm
dressed like this HH haven't been there
in a
while man my neck really hurts so
much um you know um the pizza
friend that I
have
um he like bought himself like a 100
what was it $160 pillow a while ago and
really liked it and then because his
girlfriend tested it and really liked it
too he gifted it to her as a present and
now they both have it and I was thinking
maybe I should at least for now while I
can't get the mattress
immediately maybe I can get the no one
no 160 not 600 maybe I can just get the
pillow a pillow a nicer pillow for now
but it just looks the same as some of
the pillows I have but but I
mean with 160 and they're swearing on it
maybe it is really
good thank you I'm glad you enjoyed the
stream let's do more the day after
tomorrow I'm a bit like exhausted now
mentally so
my it's like the the coffeine is gone
from my body immediately I I feel
dead it just looks like a
normal
like I don't know like one of those squ
somewhat Square
pillows that are a little bit higher on
one side than on the
other yeah I already have some of those
but
H I guess this one's special and it does
say oh or he said that you can change
the height of
it
interesting yeah look looks like one of
those memory foam
pillows but apparently it's super
special so I don't know if I should risk
it and try it
out the hotel pillows that I like they
very different they don't they're not
like specific ergonomical pillows or
anything
anyway can always be fun if you don't
like it really even after I used it I'm
not so sure about
[Music]
that that pillow better sink youa
if it's singing that how can I sleep at
least sing sleep talking to me okay
Chan you'll give me free 50 what the
hell
scam sleep
talking my sleep
talking all right I'm going to read some
super chat but only a few I'm tired and
I really need to record the emotion
still before I die from from
sleepiness
okay where shall
we what shall we
read also I I I realized the Polaroids
I'll probably forget about it today
again maybe I'll remember
[Music]
tomorrow yeah before I before I become
motionless exactly
l pull up cube pillow pull up have you
ever tried a neck pillow pullup Cube I
don't know what you're talking
[Music]
about yeah well feel free to remind
me on Twitter would be good before my
stream before or after my
streams where's
GD Bruce J Le of course John Cena
[Music]
wins I have to talk stream ooh withit
the breaking Dimensions o okay okay okay
okay right thank
you yeah after Jer Kunes
well I I barely got no okay I mean
considering how many pinks and reds
there are I got far enough
[Music]
so did I read the rainbow from junas I
suppose
not there a fro candy over
there it's tomorrow Thursday no today's
Thursday cuz I got my new hell fresh
order tomorrow's Friday so tomorrow
supposedly someone's going to come to
fix my dishwasher
and
[Music]
supposedly
maybe
maybe yeah I hope so because I did all
the dishes once now now there's some
dishes piling up again I don't want to
do
them I don't want to do them
anymore e why is it so why is the paper
sticking to the cop drop what the hell e
why is this so m
melting what why is it why is it like
this
e can they go bad this one's
[Music]
weird I don't think they can go
bad but that one's
weird let me check a different
one tomorrow is your
birthday exciting let's go
and this one's kind of melting too what
the
hell okay I'll try it
[Music]
e snea
snea as normal I
guess how hot did it get in here
okay Jerry for the
[Music]
rainbow should I put up the
thumbnail
probably here we're reading super CHS
W you were incredible fire ice made me
completely lose it and the day before I
almost broke my voice from all the
chanting these free concert has been the
first time I've attended in person and I
can't believe I've been missing out on
all this a I will definitely be there in
the next one you can count that which
one the one like in Japan or the next
one in
America well well I hope you make it to
every single one of
them thank you so much probably Japan
really oo that would be so fun it's
always nice to see you guys make the
journey and then have an incredible time
with really special
memories cuz
like yeah you guys traveling to Japan
it's more than just going to the concert
it's like you know a nice vacation that
probably a lot of you guys wanted to do
at some point in your life anyway
so it's a great opportunity to mix those
two things
together I'm hoping the best for you by
the way I speaking of Hol
Fest
um I mean I I I I think it would be way
too late at this point to implement it
in the next one but
um uh I think was it Yia or so who sent
me on Twitter a remind her about my idea
about the giant like making us
giant um it sent me a screenshot of how
new jeans the K-pop idle group did it
recently apparently more or less like
they were still there in normal
size yeah and they're
not vtubers right so it's different
they're just being displayed on the
screen but they made themselves like
full body full size if you have a video
to that performance I want to see it I'm
guessing it's the
Japan Tokyo Dome
performance but that reminded me like a
okay you know actually you know I was
just like
previously half jokingly suggesting
it as a
gimmick and bought uh well you know
probably we wouldn't do that
stupid but then I saw them doing it
similarly so I was like I should suggest
it again so I did suggest it again and I
showed the screenshot too I was like hey
so I previously suggested this jokingly
about making us huge on screens so that
everybody can see us
clearly um but now that I seen eug jeene
doing it um perhaps we should really
think about it seriously I am aware that
it will would be too late probably for
the next one of course but maybe for
another event in the
future please consider my
suggestion but I have received no
[Laughter]
[Music]
reaction I wouldn't I don't even really
know who I'm supposed to throw these
random Big Ideas towards because Ian
management is not in charge of something
like that
well I just want someone to take this
into consideration for any kind of
future concert any
any they kind of did that the vertical
streams not screens not really not
really because that wasn't the main
screens I'm saying put us on the main
screens like go but then you really need
a huge screen first of
all like it has to be a huge screen if
we ever performed in something like the
Tokyo
Dome that's where you got to bring
[Music]
that but I don't
know huge screens like that would
be expensive I
guess when I'm talking huge I mean
really huge
like maybe 10 times the size of what we
have
now a projection could also be like
interesting I wonder how Advan is by now
why is there cough drop So Soft I'm
falling apart weird
crumbly well anyway thank you
jness let's hope my idea goes through
huh
thank you so much for the support Papa
mer P Dan space wonderful
than cough syrup n Lun or l d or
L chocolate and S FX for red Super Chat
hope you had a wonderful New York trip
and got to try some delicious food
tal I got home safely a few hours ago
after a long flight back to the West
Coast
M
long how long could it possibly
be can't be longer than my flight the
trip has come to an end and back to work
I go flipping burgers at kfp of
[Music]
course do your
best soon we shall return to bakon watch
alongs yeah now that I've done the art
stream I think next week will be a watch
along
again this Cop Shop is so
weird it's freaking me
out it tastes normal
but it's
weird how's the drawing coming along I
have not continued
[Music]
yet 10 hours of watch long to catch up
no no not 10 10 hours now not all at
once but
anyway thank you so much chocolate and
Sonic for going all the way to New York
for me it's an honor thank
you thank you sh hope you had safe
travels too travor G thanks for two
pinkies Al after taking some time to
collect my thoughts about this amazing
weekend I've arrived at one conclusion
owls are the
best huh
what does that have to do with
anything seriously though I hope you've
been able to rest well and are feeling
good you've been working so hard and it
shows like a flame Burns oxygen wa all
your performances took my breath away I
couldn't be more proud of my high
kicking
Oshi though I'm sad I could only see the
WT swore performances
once Oh you mean because you won't be
able to go to any other future ones
that's fine I mean honestly that's it's
so hyped that you got to see the first
one it's
legendary people probably Envy you a lot
it's scal that your sleep talking
performance is not
rewatchable so yeah I I agree like would
been great to have it streamed or like
rewatchable somewhere but this makes it
more exclusive and more
special so ah seems like you had one of
the best weekends of your life and I'm
so glad thank you so much for coming all
through for me every time all the time
always being there thank you so much TR
team ows are pretty great I
agree Flappy Boy Thanks for the red of
chat sing T's dance cles in full Frey
Glory alone is worth getting the ticket
especially that pineapple
Coral so playful and burst full with
energy and cuteness you make it all look
so effortless if only I had the chance
to see more of it during World Tour
thank you I do really like the pineapple
Coro it's one of my favorite coros like
I mean especially the
chorus it just is like very H it flows
so
well
and yeah I like the move that uh I
during one two one two three he T so so
so ah it's just so good it's so fun the
big swing around my head and then the
pointing to the
[Music]
sides and then the
picture where I stick out my butt while
I'm like twirling my finger towards
you I really like this
Coro yeah one of my
favorites thank you so much for
appreciating you're the
best Jacob 47 n tyon n for the r of
chair woohoo back from New York City and
it truly was special being in the crowd
to see the world tour and then seeing
you and Cali do fire night in person oh
wait were you not there on the first
breaking Dimensions day
then did you only go to World Tour and
then day two of breaking Dimensions is
that what you're
saying it's a highlight that's heart to
top thank you and kfp for making my
vacation something truly Unforgettable I
truly have amazing ories a thank you so
much you chose some really great OES I
must say Good Taste from the very
beginning and I feel
like yeah you'll never you'll never
regret it thank you for staying so loyal
and supportive all the way D thank you
thank you thank
[Music]
you golden I than for the pinky wow
you're very busy l right now so I'll
keep this short and sweet your
performances were beautiful I didn't
expect you to choose pineapple as your
solo I think a lot of people didn't
expect it was actually my favorite
pineapple performance yet it really hit
different o thank you so much my your
favorite well they haven't been that
many but I think it had a great impact D
thank you so much one two one two three
it tastes so so so sweet when you go and
kiss me I'm taking the
[Music]
picture me like
a you got that
pineapple I really like it pineapple
pineapple
P come on New York hey pineapple
pineapple so
fun jelly red thanks for the red super
chat hi wa I'll be working during the
stream so I wanted to say now seeing you
live during day one and cosplaying
Sparks for anyim see oh was such a
amazing experience I CRA my eyes out
when pineapple came on sorry it would
have been I guess so much more hype if I
danced sparks
then if I performed Sparks for you okay
p is the best out there W love forever
thank you so
much ah it could have been even better
huh ah well I hope you still had a great
time it seems like it thank you for
cosplaying it must be kind of difficult
like or uncomfortable to cosplay while
being at a conert where you want to move
around I hope that cosplay survived
it I hope that it wasn't like painful or
anything
or restricting or so but it's so cool to
have like cosplayers at the concert
too thank you so much
you m than cross J thanks for the pinky
oh to concert hope you had a lovely time
with the girls to in New York I totally
did I wish I had even more time there
but yeah most girls left so early anyway
like pretty much everybody like nobody
really thought about extending their
stay I guess
so I guess if I would have extended even
longer I would have just been alone
[Music]
oh but I had a good time I hope I hope I
can go again sometime I really like New
York it felt more walkable and enjoyable
than LA but maybe I just haven't really
seen the right spots in La I I guess I
really haven't done proper sing in
La yeah I don't think I've really seen
much I've seen like the Jaan town of
La um with like the Japanese cafes and
supermarkets and stuff that was
cute and I've seen the
beach A Little Tokyo
yeah Suburban
hell
yeah New York is just better for
tourists isn't it he went to the beach
and ate elotus what's more to it I'm
sure there's more to
it New York is much nicer to see in
La I agree I remember in La I I smoovie
really I'm honored to have your presence
on my guest bed
randomly like it makes sense when you're
there since before the stream and then
stay but she chose to randomly join me
now in the middle of it
oh my God I need to hug her what was I
saying I remember in
La um was it Chipotle Chipotle
Chipotle am brought me to a I think I
remember cuz you know when she when she
stayed with me in the
hotel I think the next day we went to
Chipotle I just wanted some food
that I felt like
was was chipot I think what does chipot
le serve
again you need to get scammed in a light
also to compete complete the no no thank
you already got scammed in New York
burritos yeah we had
burritos yeah yeah yeah yeah sounds
about right it was a huge burrito m m
Mia but you know I'm I'm glad like I'm
you know hangs out with me in these like
occasions La is a long time ago but you
know I felt so de honored that she would
come to my hotel you know she had other
choices too but she came to M but
probably just because I was the quickest
to answer her
[Laughter]
call probably most
likely yeah but I'm I'm happy for all
the memories I've made with her so far
and you know all the times I I visited
her for 3D stuff too you know for my for
my uh pretty live and then on separate
occasions for recording
choreography
um like she always like worked so hard
to make things possible for me and she
had fun with it too experimenting and
improving her setup for both of our
sakes and I I really
appreciate everything she's done for me
and all the time we spend together
yeah and when she cooked for
me she's
sweetie or like when I remember when we
got lemonade from the lemonade stand
random lemonade
stand or when we ate Mexican food
[Music]
together that time I didn't get anything
spicy thank
God yeah I have a a bunch of memories
with just her thankfully like those are
precious to me when when I got to spend
time with her alone
I remember that forever I'm I'm I'm
really glad she like hosted me several
times before let me do stuff with her
studio and when we when you know when I
came over for you know just recording
pineapple Coro we ended up doing a bunch
of fun other
content um so um like the the stream
where we played that switch game where
she was just just uh oh yeah and my
dancing we did so many we did the
dancing stream we did the one like
sports game or whatever that was and
then we did the one Shooting Range thing
like all kinds of
things I like her sleeping with her bed
to protect you all yeah oh man I still
remember I wanted to say goodbye to her
but she was
sleeping I don't think I was able to say
goodbye in the
end I didn't want to oh no I did I think
I slightly woke her up did I but I
really hesitated for a while I'm like a
damn it I got to go I'm so
sorry I was just hoping she would
naturally wake up of the sounds of me
walking
around yeah but I I do think I got her
to wake up for one
moment and then I left so so
sentimentally
is that the right word I felt very
sentimental leaving at that time
because that was one of the first
times wasn't it the first time wasn't
that the first time we all got together
I don't know anymore no I think that it
was the first time where all five of us
were together
maybe
yeah I remember I was going to the games
C
[\h__\h] and then oh remember I think we
told you about that cuz her her relative
came by and we had burgers
and I didn't like those fries they were
so mid and
lame I didn't know what what the fuss
was about the the fries yeah Auntie
Watson I met Auntie
[Music]
wson oh yeah and then I told her aunt
like how great is
[Music]
y was sitting next to
me damn it I made myself cry
I want to blow my
[Music]
nose I hope smooy doesn't get
up don't get up smooy
[Music]
sorry
man I'm going to miss her
[Music]
I'm sorry that
I bring back the
[Music]
sadness
okay where was I m I think cross
[Music]
J
okay
chill Justin
lamber passion hello T welcome back I
really enjoyed the concert your
performance was amazing as well as the
other
[Music]
members also DS congratulations on
approaching four years and whole life
may you
continue your Idol Journey forever as
you live we love you thank you you're so
nice thank you so
much I appreciate it I'll continue doing
my best please continue following my
[Music]
journey than sorry for the wait on
answering your Super Chat
[Music]
hi thank you also for the pinky welcome
back laa your performance is so great
love you my Kam o thank
you thank k for letting me be your call
me oh she still who is that cute girl in
your profile picture
H thank you very much for the
support Joshua hug
D thank you oh thank you first time
let's go hopefully not the last time
Joshua
thanks for the right of chat you've had
a lot going on lately you EU cooh High
to harass and train huntings by a mage
go and of course wonderful performances
at a concert the return of Takami the
Legends were true sorry you're so busy
but I'm also glad we get to see it works
thank you yeah that was a very busy time
and I
was breaking and falling apart not
breaking Dimensions breaking my mental
health but it was all worth it and paid
off in the end I
think thank you so much for supporting
me through this busy time now we can
chill a little bit
while while I'm in Austria you know
usual kind of schedule usual kind of
streams
playing Zelda for hours at
home cozily it just feels
right just feels right am I
right what the [\h__\h] are you talking
about
[Music]
whatever just a weird weird comments um
but
yeah thank
you I'm I'm really grateful that you
know you guys have been so understanding
and and helpful for the busier times you
know I really personally I didn't want
it to be that busy and personally I was
very very looking forward to the whole
that whole Arc ending I just had too
many things going on at
once um if if my birthday life wasn't so
delayed again
then perhaps it would have been more
spread out
but yeah
yeah yeah but we're going to
see we're going to see soon
that that was worth it parts of it we
already saw
so I'm really excited for this one this
last last piece of uh result and
evidence from that trip is coming up
soon
last last one yeah thank you so much
D for the red super chat thank you for
the amazing concert your performance was
really really fantastic did you watch it
in like a live feeling venue in
Korea really happy to see that there's
always some kind of live viewing going
on H
I wonder if you watched it together with
other Korean
viewers Korean Korean viewers they're so
fun too and so hyped I hope we can do
you know a concert in
Korea at some point that'll be really
sick I want to I want to interact with
my Korean fans again to like you know
whole life has had a few Korean
convention expences in the past 2 years
and so on but oh it's been a while since
I got the pleasure of being host it at
one and I really want to again please
Korea please I want to use the
opportunity to do a meet and greet
whenever there's a convention going on
too I want to talk to the Korean
fans please please please please please
I'm waiting I'm awaiting your
offer Korean
conventions I know you had me before
please call me
[Music]
again the Korean reps yeah I really I
really should man I'm so
useless I wish I could pick it up so
easy as I did with Japanese but I was
just really young when I learned
Japanese and it's so much easier when
you're younger why does my brain decline
so fast
but thank you
Kam I hope I hope to visit Korea in in
person but also virtually again
sometime Studio Rob thanks for the
pinky you just don't have the time for
Kine reps you're just busy well yeah
that too but I think it counts a little
bit you know the
age yeah
[Music]
Studio thank you so much for the sweet
support Firefly taken thanks for the
pinky I'm on vacation in Mexico so I
have to watch the live stream oh Oh you
mean as you couldn't be there in person
sadly I missed two of the last because
was I had to go to a kfp
fight chicken fight you mean like a
chicken
fight I feel like I heard of such a
thing before heading back to New York so
here's my winning you winning
from the Chicken F did you beted on
chickens is that a
thing tell me more about it is there
footage from it I need to see it were
there any chickens
harmed yeah rooster
fight what the
hell wait it's illegal oh because they
end up like ding what the
hell
oh
what how common is
it those poor
chickens do they wait do they like send
in two roosters
and then is it like they are aggressive
for some reason do they just naturally
have to fight each other or do they
get
like knives in their feet you kidding
right iron
what oh my God I want to cry
that's [\h__\h] up
what oh my
God I want to CET I don't like knowing
this I don't I want to erase my
knowledge I want to raas my knowledge
H what the
hell
[Music]
be but he says he had to go to one I
don't know maybe you he he went to
uh on a vacation with someone else and I
don't know they forced him to go or
so
Unown for the pinky congrats on rocking
it out over the weekend I was blown away
seeing your performances at both the
world tour and breaking Dimensions Hope
New York has been treating you well it
really has maybe I was just lucky I
could have been unlucky too and some
[\h__\h] could have honestly well I did get
get unlucky a little bit when I got
scammed we'll never forget
but oh actually it reminds me I did ah
[\h__\h] I forgot following up I did uh try
to kind of like a while later but I did
try
to um dispute it via my bank and I think
they replied to me somehow but I didn't
check back on it
oopsie I probably
should no it might not be positive it
might just be them asking for more um
details
who the
hell I'm out my
friend you're spamming weird
comments don't don't do do
me I'm at least I tried and I'm on it
kind of I just I've been busy
too know I need
to I think I think I probably like wrote
to them before I went to Italy and then
they probably like replied to me while I
was in Italy and I didn't have access to
it cuz like I got to log in to it with
my special phone that gives me access to
my account and blah blah blah blah so I
was like okay I got to do this when I'm
back
home don't judge me I'm just saying
probably because my memory is so weak
but it's probably how it transpired
Sak sphe thanks for the red super chat
so great to see you in concert free
times in New York that was the
experience of a lifetime must have been
kind of exhausting to just be so excited
for three days in a row huh I'm so happy
to be home with the katas though KY yeah
I get it I get it you guys must have
felt a little
bit mentally and physically exhausted
too right cuz like a lot of you guys
didn't not only go to the concerts but
also to the to the
convention yeah spent your whole day
socializing and cheering and standing in
line for things and
stuff you had the sinus you had sinus
problems oh
[\h__\h] w i getting old it is true it is
true I am old but
gold loved it 10 out of 10 would do all
three days
again did you also go to the convention
too had blisses the whole time oh man
you need blister
um Band-Aids they're really
[Music]
good yeah you did oh crazy oh my God but
yeah like even like during it when you
feel exhausted it's the adrenaline and
all the fun and then you feel like you
got to do it
again thank you spank High m Kashi
thanks for the pinky ala wa Aloha want
to give a big congrats on your multiple
amazing performances you killed it as
always like the brilliant Phoenix you
are wish I can one day get the chance to
see you live in person are you from
Hawaii hope the rest of the year goes
well for you thank
you I do you live in Hawaii why did you
say aloha I hope you do get to see me
live one day
day really I know that like traveling
and going to concerts is expensive and
all that and getting a ticket is
difficult too but I hope everybody at
least once gets to experience
this Alo happy oh
no they're are from Hawaii wow cool
that's so cool Loki I nbu thank you so
much for the
support thank you thank you
Alex keeps d g d for the pinky congrats
on the successful concerts I was very
proud seeing you on stage it never gets
old even after a few after a few
concerts you were amazing K my Kam oi
will be there for will there be a
Blue-ray for those of us who can't watch
the world T live no I would say no most
likely uh
yeah sorry I'm sorry I know it feels
like really missing out on something
cool but I mean you know there will be
more opportunities like this in the
future more concerts and songs will be
performed again maybe not in the exact
same lineup
but poor person do you forever L well
who says that Maybe not maybe we'll come
[Music]
again I will say that that um while the
world tour
has um different set lists each
time uh there are
some things that might
repeat
so you
know I can't tell you what happens at
which concert but
but there might
be
some repeats you know
[Music]
so now you know what I'm
saying some some
[Music]
yeah
than I was tired because it was morning
but it was a very happy time but I was
disappointed that there was no happy
next time I'll definitely wear happy and
cheer I was proud because it was
kfp
oh what does this
say what you don't have a happy time to
get one one the official
one
y let's see what this means oopsie both
the dance and the song are cute and sexy
wow o thank you thank you thank you I
appreciate
it and don't worry I'll still make your
Polaroid just give me a little bit of
time to remember when I have time thank
you thank you thank you m an fan 17655
d d Dominic k d for the red CH thanks k
for so many great New York memories s
was killing my FR and breaking
Dimensions one and two were the best
concerts I've ever been to
ooh didn't you go to the Fest as well
you got me to meet many people help out
others and just have fun again than
shuni wa for being the best wa shimkin
could wish for yo you've traveled a lot
for kfp you've traveled to Japan you've
traveled to
[Music]
America all the way from
Germany yeah must have been crazy going
all over the world and meeting kfps from
every
continent you're happy to see them yeah
you guys are so sweet you guys are so
titty I'm happy to see
it Dominic I I feel like I can
understand why perhaps like you may have
had a better time at break dimensions
compared to Fest because Fest is bigger
but that doesn't necessarily make it
better if you are originally an Ian fan
then an Ian concert will be just more
hype and also a smaller
venue bigger venue will like be
impressive and hype and louder and all
that but smaller venue can also just be
more intimate and that's why makes it
more hype it's all like contained in
this smaller space like it feels more
like
everybody's one you
know everybody becomes one
G it it just becomes more personal
too a little
bit and more familiar maybe if it's like
like he's from Germany so America is you
know not the most familiar but still
like speaking English is probably more
familiar and the culture and everything
is more familiar than when you go to a
concert in Japan where it's so very
different from what you used to and yeah
for you guys in in America too going to
a concert in America it just feels like
you're kind of home even if you travel
to a different city you're still kind of
home and and it's it's different but you
know at the same time we can say that's
what makes going to Fest so special
experiencing um whole
life you know in its headquarter country
so to say where it should be at its best
and at its biggest and you can really
feel how big whole life has become going
to Expo and
Fest where it's grown so big and you can
feel like
damn this is the f I'm in it's so big
whoa so many different people so many
different osies
Idols
yeah a lot to see a lot of Impressions
to take in so it's different
[Music]
experiences very
nice thank you Dominic M Unity chat
thanks for the pinky congrats on the
amazing breaking Dimensions concert
every performance was special
pineapple was so smooth and sweet bird
collab was Kino and Fire and Ice was
great with the new Coro the finger guns
were so
fun those finger guns I'm also so proud
of all the kfp who cheered so hard me
too can't thank you guys and enough
thank you un need chat I'm assuming you
watched it from home I think 26th
today isn't it
the I read something about 26 being the
last day of the archive I don't know if
it's gone
now um if it's not gone yet then this
might be the last chance for you guys oh
it ran out oh okay
Rip but I hope you all took your time to
watch it at some
[Music]
point oh
no that's H sad
I should have watched
it some
point oh I'll wait for an inevitable
Blu-ray yeah
yeah um he who faces than cool for you
than Wiki Tunes than for the
pinky that reminds me I was still going
to send
in into a form well got to got to be
reminded of
it let me tell PMA to put this on my
task
[Music]
list yes yes PMT
thank you for watching Sora D
soon appreciate it see you again we
pinky I never thought I'd see the day
where I'd see you live and find myself
dancing with
fell yeah did you dance the Coro along a
little bit did you try the do collab was
awesome and I got so hyped for the
Saturday concert I shouted I love you
Kata you're amazing bus I hope to see
you again someday I hope so too thank
you so much a do you collab was awesome
means you got to go to World Tour as
well did you go to
everything no wait you say hyped for
Saturday concert so maybe World Tour and
Saturday or all of it crazy you guys got
so lucky so many of you got so
lucky wait I hope your luck doesn't run
out thanks to
that just meet out on Sunday ah okay so
Sunday that's fine I did say that
Saturday was the more heavy WWA
one white waha appeared in
it thank you wiy
Tunes
yeah let's make it happen again thank
you so
much let's remember it forever
[Music]
thanks for the red super chat thank you
for the amazing concert wa as expected
you smashed it hey I really loved the
United kfp chance in the United States I
wish I could have also been there but
hopefully I'll be there next time sadly
I can't stick around for now cuz of work
tomorrow but I'll watch the vot later
thank you very much yeah I hope you get
to go there
too yeah my European fellow my German
fellows you deserve it but who knows
maybe we're four years in maybe at some
point holen will do some something cool
in
Europe not just a convention
appearance you set up your vacation for
Atlanta you're planning your trip oh my
god let's
go what
I hope for the best for
you going so far for just one concert oh
thank
you please have a great time and kfp who
go to the concert too in Atlanta please
treat tasim Mo well take care of my
German kfp
please take care of
them well iron Vader I know and I like
also so have been advocating for a
change there but you know it's contracts
and stuff um like contracts of streaming
services so it's
[Music]
difficult um well thank you T mom thanks
shyami thanks for the
pinky am I going to finish these n
there's still so much
I don't want to I followed your commands
and broke into breaking Dimensions
legally and carried my small Val plushy
the entire time a thank you for keeping
her safe it was a dream come true for me
and I even teared up doing
reunion sweet I'm so happy I got to
watch my Kam o on stage nah thank you so
much I appreciate it thank you for
bringing me to the stage if it wasn't
for you I would have missed
it I wouldn't have been able to reach
the venue on my
own thank you thank you I'm so glad you
could make that memory core memory
unlocked than soon hopefully it's not
the last time right thank
you after like how long have you been
watching my streams I wonder but all of
you guys I feel like a lot of you been
watching me for a long time time and
after watching me on the screen on your
phone or on your PC or so for a long
time must be weird and and like
really special to see me in a different
form right go out there to see me on
stage on a big concert and then be able
to cheer for me
loudly with other
people tomorrow
is your four year anniversary of
me let's go been here for so long thank
you I like watching on a big
phone M anniversary is
tomorrow oh we can you can see different
emotes for the first time not emotes but
like um icons
badges let's go that's exciting golden
chickens who will be the first golden
chickens who can Flex their
goldness thank you San Serv thank
you three more weeks ooh let's go let's
go I don't want to lose my armor stop
crying stop crying about it I like my
armor stop crying stop complaining be
happy that you're going to be gold
you're going to be so cool people will
be like
oh yo so cool I wish I was
[Music]
gold don't you
dare don't you
dare we get golden or gold armor well
let's just say let's just say you become
like kind of golden but I feel like you
can see it as a full like your whole
skin has thickened into golden material
yeah you're like a gilded chicken and
it's not quite armor but like your whole
body has
become like gold
medal so it is kind of
armor can we move we'll have to test it
out I'm not sure we'll see it
tomorrow yeah yeah like Iron Man mhm mhm
like your whole although did Iron Man
become fully iron I don't think so
uh it's like you freaking the chicken
skin
accept
it it's like um you basically were
dipped in in uh liquid gold and then it
hardened over your body is how I imagine
it but don't worry you're not dead or
maybe it's like a
cocoon you have to be in a cocoon golden
cocoon for one year to get even
[Music]
stronger whatever you want many options
see it how you want to see it however it
makes it better for
you no you guys can take it don't worry
you guys can take being uh dipped in
gold Liquid
Gold you've been for the fryer you've
become you've become a chicken bucket
and see how much stronger you've become
after that trial of hot
oil you've been through so
much it seems like you're immune to heat
at this point but but we got to we we
got to make your immunity even
stronger so that even the poisonous
fumes from liquid gold cuz I assume that
you know it's not healthy even if you
take away the heat
aspect uh we have to strengthen you
against that too you know we're just
like making you into the most immune mut
mutated chicken ever never trial by fire
exactly does it sound exciting
now let me think for another year about
the rainbow chicken lore let me think
about that I need a year to
cook but that's maybe just you consuming
uh one of those mushrooms and then the
whole time once you hit that year and
become rainbow you will hear this music
in your head the whole
[Music]
time and will never stop until we have
another rank after
that yeah you'll just constantly be on
an invincible you know what you know
what all of you will gain usual room
immunity but at that point cuz you're
rainbow that means you're immune to
anything I can't touch
but in order to get there you have to
first go for all the fire trials and one
of them is being dipped in liquid
gold so stop bitching around about it if
you want to be immune
someday it's a long
[Laughter]
journey no payment will not be a benefit
of being rainbow no why would it
be you cannot skip any steps daku but
you can draw me uh offer me more art and
get on my good side that
way yeah let's not get ahead of
yourselves no salary of course not I get
the salary understand little chicken
brain can't comprehend
all right all right all right
guys uh where was
I ah I guess I was here at bang gami
right
[Music]
for
for the pink Super Chat I'm glad you had
a great time even though I wasn't in New
York I think the experience of cheering
kiaha with many kfp colleagues in career
will last
forever I want videos I hope there will
be a time like this again
[Music]
sounds so exciting I want to see Korean
Bros and girls
again let's meet again let's meet again
please thank you so much for supporting
me even when you
know it's become a bit more calm and
quiet in terms of our interactions and
me uh doing Korea related stuff yeah but
I hope you can still support me AK sf2
dun spam D Domin k d faction D I ate Su
and cake of course I
did quacky
D yeah yeah it was with cream cheese
[Music]
mhm USS anime
and thank you Cosmic
Collision Collision Collision thank you
for the red Chad I'm a lurker and vaer
take my money because you deserve it
thank you oo I am
honored lurker and voder wow we need we
need people like you we need everybody
to take up a role and you taking up the
role of V watching and we respect it w
on theand thank you for supporting even
on off
[Music]
hours he 99 Dan M Dan KY thanks for the
YY at work so I can't stay but I just
want to congratulate you and all of Holo
Ian uh Unbreaking Dimensions the concert
was awesome but also I love hearing Ian
getting to live that Holo style Idol
experience not just the concert but
hanging out after parties Etc yeah it
was good it was
[Music]
fun was nice nice uh getting together
and yeah getting massages from crony
stuff like that the good
stuff yeah I remember like when we were
saying
goodbye um cuz like most of us were
going to not see each other
anymore uh at least for a while
obviously
um like people were saying goodbye to
each other for like 20 minutes I swear
to
God it was so late and the place was
already closed for a while and they were
like oh don't worry you you can stay
longer don't worry don't worry but still
um I thought oh I should probably go
sooner you know somebody's got to leave
to make other people leave but I I
wasn't the first to leave at all but
yeah it took forever people kept on
saying goodbye to each other several
times and I hugged crony like five times
like we all hugged each other like
million
times yeah yeah yeah you know when you
say goodbye to someone and it just takes
forever
[Music]
but it was just also so so emotional
after such
a how to say what's the right
word
Co strong now the
[Music]
yeah F yeah but like in in in a sense of
um the experience was so fck but like
what's the better word for
it
uh I don't know but
yeah
yeah feeling
yeah yeah meaningful momentous sure
substantial sure all of
that and then saying goodbye you know we
all felt I guess like it was a very
special weekend for
us
so saying goodbye was
difficult Rich yeah impactful
yeah all of that
it was a special weekend for
Ian
so historic it was
historic
definitely thank you crusty so much
thank you thank you thank you thank
you hi fructose corn syrup tun na Super
Chat hiel I missed these tangents please
inject them directly into my veins like
to sugar and that sweet tea we make here
down south ew so
disgusting so disgusting but sure I'll
I'll inject them directly and just like
don't inject the sweet tea then right
we'll replace it it'll be so much
healthier I'm
sure thank you Nathan you're surprised I
didn't like this really sweet tea is
just not good it's really bad I'm sorry
guys drink drink some I don't know nesty
lipon
uh ice
[Music]
tea fuse tea any of those those are
better what do you want to live forever
what do you mean because uh high
fructose corn syrup IC tea makes your
life shorter is that what you're saying
like like what you want to live forever
nah just drink this tea it's great you
may shorten your lifespan but it's great
is that what you're
saying the Arizona ones aren't
they
um what's the word aren't the Arizona
te's um what's the word disgusting no
aren't they uh what's the word
no when when
when like an
uh no no no no I
mean
um don't they taste weird I might
thinking of something
else like when something's like
H [\h__\h] what's the word
you have such a way with words
mm no I don't mean artificial I mean
when
something uh like not like when a drink
not when it becomes moldy or so but the
Step before
that uh it's like not something you
normally would want your drink to become
but there's some drinks out there that
yeah fermented yeah that's what I
mean
fermented there's some like iced tea
drink or so that's fermented and it's
disgusting kombucha yeah I don't like it
I don't like it I don't like it at all
so that was kombucha not Arizona okay
okay okay I mixed it
up see like normally you wouldn't want
your drink to become fermented that
means it has gone
bad mysterious
[Music]
they just make nice tea and punches it
hasn't gone up in price since the '90s
oh I see
oh that's why you guys were saying it's
cheap uhhuh I see must try
then I take it you don't like Nat I've
never actually tried but I assume I
would not like it
yeah I'm pretty sure I don't need to try
this one to know that I wouldn't like it
and nah you just the thought of the
smell makes me want to throw
up I would probably vomit yeah yeah yeah
I don't think I could even put it in my
mouth or anywhere close to
it okay what was
I ah yeah Nathan thank you m Elsie L dun
Dusty D for the r chat my beautiful Teno
how wonderful it was to see you move at
the concert I feel like I can burn up in
peace now wait you also went in person
already missing the feeling of the
weekend I hope to see you live again
next year I love my Phoenix
Kos thank
you burn up in peace please don't please
stay alive you still got to go for the
next fire trial
getting dipped in gold there's still so
much to do Dusty don't turn into dust
and Ashes yet you're not finished here
our Quest our quest line is still so
long please
SC thank you thank
you faction D hero 85 thank you for the
red of CH hi K you're my favorite Ian
Idol thank you really enjoyed breaking
dimensions
and looking forward to the next end
concert let's sell out the whole stadium
next time for real bro like you know
they really just got to get a bigger
venue the first time it was
understandable because we got a proof to
the to the
upper management that we can get a
bigger venue that we can fill out this
one and then get a bigger one but then
this time man it was cool that we had
two days though that was definitely
cool it made the whole experience
uh longer and
therefore even
more
memorable yeah big venue needs to book
be booked way way more in advance so
please management son Let's get a bigger
venue it doesn't have to be like Fast
size of
course but at least filling with like
2,000 more people or so would be
nice minimum 2,000 extra would be
nice please please please
pleaseeeeee please please and let's keep
the two days though can't go back
now please hero thank you so much I hope
whenever it is wherever it is I hope
you'll be part of the next one
[Music]
too thank you don't worry about it Black
penguin Danon Sky Danon blue vest guy
[\h__\h] thank you for the r ched thanks
for giving me my part part of my money
back hey k sorry about scamming you if
we had known you were such a famous bird
we wouldn't have targeted you really
really
that was really the only negative memory
but already now weeks later I don't even
think about it anymore because
everything else was so
nice so uh [\h__\h] you blue vest guy but
thank you so much to the person behind
who sent the Super Chat thank
you alud thank you for the red super
chat I saw you in chat did you make a
wish where oh at the I showed that
picture with the coins uh in the weird
place right didn't make a wish didn't
even throw anything in there I
actually um kind of regretted not
bringing my remaining US money that I
had from my previous trip because I
still had some cash left over and I kept
it in the bag at home uh cuz I didn't
want to like change it back to Euro so I
just wanted to keep it for the next time
but because I was in Japan first for for
a long time I just completely forgot
about bringing it so I tried to go
through everything only with my card it
worked out with my card and with Uber
Eats don't work down I didn't use any US
money then touch and chat are you
okay did I bore you wake up wake up
we're almost done actually with these
super chats isn't that
impressive I'm finishing
them h are you
okay life check are my chicken still
alive balacha mobile dropped oh just
today that feels
random have fun I
guess you're terrified of being dipped
in gold no you should be excited don't
be scared you've been through something
similar before now probably no maybe not
even but most of you
guys just ch staring at a chicken friend
who
H I'm eating food B is my lunch book I'm
hungry you're yeah you're going to be
worth a lot of money where do I even get
all this gold Liquid Gold from
huh from rings of power from watching
rings of power you get rich when you
watch rings of power guys watch
it anyway thank you so much
aluda did you watch the stream or did
you go in person I want to know for the
concert cuz you didn't say anything
about it in these Super
Chat you watching stream okay I hope you
get to go in person someday where where
are you located you don't have to tell
me but
if you want to in the middle of nowhere
so I said this before but like so Texas
no Texas I would not and I feel like
I've said this before too I wouldn't say
that's the middle of nowhere because at
least I know that it
exists I don't know where the middle of
nowhere would
[Music]
be but I hope you get to travel sometime
to a concert one of these days you got
to you have to rural East
Coast we were on your coast and you
didn't take advantage of it
why why is there a reason why was it
still like pretty far too
far 3 hours away for the nearest airport
oh my God
well it doesn't get much better than New
York for you
probably
realistically I mean we're not going to
perform in your rural
[Music]
Village you don't know that no I know
that I know that come
on N but you know watching from home is
totally fine of course
basically we can come to your home no
matter where you are if you watch the
live stream where we are where you are
and that's what's so great about virtual
streamers and
[Music]
Idols anyway thank you so much Firefly
thanks for the red super chat I'd like
to buy free tickets to the Moon please
eh when was I selling that am I scamming
you guys where without knowing thank you
Firefly sorry I don't think I can send
you to the moon but I can send you to
the usual room ends with the same kind
of syllable good enough
right thank
you and on ears D thank you don't worry
don't
worry the squirrels they didn't look so
fat uh M eight thanks for the r Super
Chat while the money is lost you should
definitely cancel the card when you can
just be BL when you can just to be safe
probably tell Amy to do the same I'm
glad you liked NYC hope you can come
back and maybe experience it in the
winter too love these travel tangent
streams thanks
T I
imagine winter if you're thinking of
snow in New York I imagine it to just be
like like dirty
gray mushy snow like like you know what
what I mean like usually busy cities the
snow doesn't really stay nice
anyway why why are
you why are you suggesting winter what's
so nice about New York in the
winter
right am I missing
something upset New York is much
prettier Upstate girl have I seen
Upstate New York I feel like I don't
know what what is up have I been to
Upstate New York judging from my travel
report I
haven't oh what's
there where where is upstate New York
Upstate is it like across the water
Upstate
[\h__\h] oh
[Music]
Countryside
bro wait so here's Oh you mean like with
Upstate New York is that still New York
though ah wait the the whole place here
is cold New York I'm looking at the map
Oh you mean oh like Rochester
Syracuse
UA
Buffalo that area oh oh that's so far
Mama
Mia I want to go to Long Island have I
been to Long Island don't think I've
been to Long
Island oh God my PC lagged I'm scared
I
see so the state of New
York we're talking about the state of
New York I thought there was a like you
know in the city I thought there was an
Upstate New
York oh BB is raing me now oh I'm so
close to finishing the super chats and
finishing the stream
a stay determined I shall stay
determined to finish the super chats so
kind of
you I don't even need that determination
anymore I'm pretty much
done but I appreciate it I I been done
at least with this one stream super
CH oh did you guys play undertale
what oh God the sound
is weird let me close this
now go away go away
okay undertale
whoa hey getting into undertale so soon
I I have it on my bucket list for
whenever I don't have anything else to
play and I want a
series to
play oh I'm sure her voice acting was
great welcome welcome welcome we started
playing the new Zelda game today and it
was oh oh my God it was just so good I
hope you guys all check it out like the
game and maybe my
[Music]
stream you love the characters yeah I
hear so much about it but I don't know
when I will ever get to play it sometime
maybe in 2025 who
knows who
knows it's definitely a wa game are you
sure I would categorize W games more
like you know like a Zilla game more
like uh tailes off game those are the
waa
games but sure I would probably enjoy it
you guys say so it's probably
true you Vibe of it emotionally oh
really
wow
okay good thing 25 is only three weeks
away what the hell are you talking
about it's relatively close at this
point but not that close anyway thank
you much eight may musician action FAA
step sings and the last one is the pinky
from I am a te beep thank you shiran for
the pinky congrats on your performance T
I haven't gotten out much lately so I
was nervous about going to the World
Tour but it ended with being a great
experience you were stunning I watched
breaking Dimensions from home but you
were wonderful there too
oh oh so you watch World Tour from uh no
World Tour in person and breaking
Dimensions from home oh why not that's
nice you get all kinds of
povs her never played a Zelda game maybe
now's the time now that the new one came
out it's so cute and so fun but yeah I
mean if you
don't necessarily feel like jumping on a
new game right now is what you need to
do
maybe later down the line after you're
done with undertale or
so I'd maybe recommend a different
one yeah thinking Link's name is yeah
yeah I I mean I think we all had that in
the big very
beginning maybe I would recommend links
Awakening
honestly at this point if you want to
play something that's a
like on the newer
side but has the
charm of Link uh of Del
games and it's relatively beginner
friendly I would say mhm good call right
yeah yeah yeah the Remake mhm cuz it has
a remake so it looks really
pretty and it's not too long either but
my favorite Zelda games are tears of the
Kingdom
uh the one the previous one and uh Wind
Waker cuz Wind Waker is just so
nostalgic for me and so cute and so
Charming but I I feel like it was
difficult more difficult than
uh what which one did I
recommend links
Awakening you're
charming no you oh my God you charming
soong
so nice she's so nice guys she's so nice
she's so sweet I hope I hope we get to
meet
sometime yeah I'm always so excited to
meet members for the first
time IRL I can't wait to meet you can't
wait to like compare how you are IRL
like your energy and your Vibe but it's
probably similar would you say it's
similar would you say you're like same
IR would you say you're shy at first
meetings are you like super energetic
you say you're the
same I can see you must be confident in
in
your life in your personality and
yourself you know what I mean like
you're not shy you're probably not
shy I mean just by hearing you saying it
I can like feel sense the
confidence it's
[Music]
exuding
yeah need to learn from
it I'm Shing the inside I don't like
regretting shying away yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah that's a good like fear to
have like regretting something because
you were shy so that makes you too makes
you push through it no regretti
spaghetti yeah I wonder I wonder what
will be the when will be the first time
when we would
meet I hope it won't be too far in the
future want to meet everybody I already
had the pleasure to meet Raa of
course but when I meet everybody
EU off I mean of course actually yeah
like we don't have to wait to meet like
somewhere in Japan or
so H you got to meet pretty kitty
yeah Rich
[Music]
Girl does she not like smell and look
rich to you
herb that's like that was my first
impression tell
me no but uh if you ever feel like com
to Austria let me know our Christmas
markets are nice got something to do in
December
huh come over she sniffers sniffers MOS
that ooh must be wearing nice
[Music]
perfume you know so my invitation is out
there if you're like bored or
so um my doors are open and U my borders
are open
um yeah one thing with like European
members that I was always looking
forward to is having some people close
to
for off collabs being more realistic
it's always fun to have crazy off
collabs yeah
Christmas beautiful beautiful Christmas
markets with roasted almonds and all
Austrian kaash
Shan Austrian kaash Shan at the
Christmas Market is so good it's a
shredded pancakes with um there's
usually two
go-to uh sauces with it either
applesauce
or how to sayet Mo in English again uh
Plum Plum some kind of Plum
thing it's like fluffy shredded
thick pump uh pancakes I wouldn't say
it's you know it's like way thicker than
pancakes normal pancakes that you
imagine it's thicker and H you kind of
make some sides of it a little bit like
crunchy with the sugar and and giving
you a little bit a little bit of a crust
mhm wait let me show you a picture it's
so simple but it's like my one of my
favorite desserts ever and just a
picture of it will not do it
justice
justice let me show
you this is kaash man oh why the hell is
there Ling bearry Jam are you [\h__\h]
kidding me you don't eat that with
lingonberry Jam but the apple sauce is
correct I mean I guess you can eat it
with lingam Berry Jam but that's not
that's not the go
to shame ding D ding ding shame d d but
here you can
see like it's fluffy and all that but
there's a little bit of a crust cuz
first you you just put like so much of
the batter into the big pan and you wait
and wait and wait until the bottom be
gets a little bit of a crust and that's
when you start shredding it all apart
yeah extremely specific rules of Ling J
must be respected exactly thank
you yeah I mean you know you can of
course have it with any kind of jam of
your liking it will be nice even
sometimes I even see it with
Nutella but I like to keep it fruity so
best is the applesauce or the plum sauce
and imagine eating this and this warm
dessert fluffy dessert in a cold snowy
Christmas Market in
Austria okay I I've done enough uh
pressuring you I'm sorry I'm sorry don't
worry about it I'm sure you got nice
Christmas markets over there
[Music]
too hot chocolate in hand yeah or no
uh at Christmas markets you usually you
can get hot chocolate but the go-to is
punch uh mold wine
whatsoever either punch and or mold wine
those two things I think are separate
things but yeah and then there's so many
different variations of the punches
T punch
yeah is that not too common it's it's
definitely the English word for it I'm
pretty
sure Punch drink
the term punch refers to a wide
assortment of drinks both non-alcoholic
and alcoholic generally containing
fruits or fruit juice and it's supposed
to be hot it's in this case at least
it's
hot yeah yeah so there's usually a lot
of different
flavors hot
punch hey of course it's hot it's nice
though it's really nice
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah there's like um
usually it's like either like something
with like mostly Apple flavors or orange
flavors and cinnamon and so
on hot Fruit Punch Yeah if you never had
it before you can actually easily make
it yourself like my friend my best
friend she likes to uh make big hot
punch servings herself sometimes because
it's cheaper because honestly the
Christmas markets here they're so
overpriced like getting one [\h__\h] cup
of mold wine or whatever oh my God you
pay for the cup as well and if you
return it you get some money back so
that's why it's a little bit expensive
in case you take the cup with you but
even considering you giving it back it's
there's it's
so yeah um what's the word inflated
inflated as [\h__\h] just because it's a
Christmas
Market mhm
it's ridiculous but it's about the
experience anyway I'm going to go record
some hand motion hopefully um I charged
my my exent gloves so I hope I can do it
quickly and give smoothie some love cuz
she's waiting for me thank you so much
for watching tomorrow is the the big
Amelia Watson Valve game marathon collab
I'm joining for the first one on the
list Team Fortress 2 which I never
played before so will be playing it
tomorrow for the first time I'll start a
little bit early to practice because I
have no idea what I'll be doing I don't
know
anything um so
yeah I've never played either are you
also in Team
Fortress I don't know anything I
generally don't play FPS games so it's
in its own a miracle that I'm going to
be playing an FPS game anything for
I'm going to play Pyro that's the one
thing I already
know yeah so I'll try to train it I hope
I can pick it up
fast yeah B if you want to join me for
an early practice I'm starting two hours
before uh it begins so if you just want
to join me let me know hit me up
spontaneously it's fine
too we can learn it together
flame WWA yeah pyro wa CED open eat
right okay just let me know
whenever en okay I've stalled enough
I've stalled enough I felt like I
shouldn't just leave quickly because I
just got
raided yeah thank you see you tomorrow
guys byebye I'll be the see y
sorry sorry
[Music]
sorry so me I'm
sorry I'm a
raid what she what is she up to
[Music]
now ah El in the ring still
ah
[Music]