[Music]
do
so
[Music]
hmm
oh
[Music]
um
hmm
[Music]
osha
hmm
i just woke up uh surprisingly i have
some energy right now
can i go back to bed no i'm doing this
for the sea bros
sorry that it's not um gingerbread house
baking
however i figured you know when my mom
is here
[Laughter]
uh maybe on the 25th before she leaves
she can help me to make the gingerbread
dough because i already have all the
ingredients ingredients i was thinking
maybe
maybe she can help me bake them
yeah cause cause then i could do it
easily next week
[Music]
i don't know if you're watching this
probably not but
yolo scoop
that's a good idea all right i mean i
could probably do it myself but i never
used
that kitchenaid before that i got
and i'm i'm not quite confident in it
yet
where are we playing uh there it is
there it is
oh man so many cool games on my switch
want to look at all of them
oh i doubt i bought and downloaded old
trines in hopes to play it one day for
you guys
um i'm also still waiting on i am
setsuna and onignaki and octopath
traveler and moji pittan anchor
i'm waiting on all of these
ring for the adventure of course of
course although i have no space on my
switch so i got to delete them all the
time
play octopap
yeah i wish i could
uh
one day one day one day one day
one once one one day
one second
okay
what's trine
good question what is trine i don't know
how to describe it uh look it up
uh yes it's a side scroller though by
the way that's all i can say i think
that's all i know
so
gonna play mario kart 8 deluxe because
because
i i need to put up the logo um
wait let me okay okay step by step uh i
had to clean this screen because
yesterday i messed it all up with uh
with um
in a inaudible lab uh
do i have the logo
mario cart logo
mario
mk logo
goddammit why is it local
i need to name these logos in order to
find them oh man i have so many game
logos saved on my pc
[Music]
although i could also put up you know
what let's pick it let's make it
interesting
uh here let me put up the
the whole live new year cup logo
it's not quite the new year cup yet just
yet but
but it's the practice for it here it is
it
there it is
nice fancy logo
it's a bit big
this is as big as i can make it so
i need to sneeze
i ah
i needed to sneeze excuse me
um so
[Music]
on the
what's on the 7th of january
1pm japanese standard time
uh we are having uh
an almost all whole life members
mario kart tournament almost
almost all of them
uh i'm in the first row you see me down
down there with the myth girls yes yes
something is off on this picture what is
it something is different than the
others what is it try to find it
uh
yeah
um
uh this is this is uh
gonna be
fun
i'm actually not sure are we all
supposed to stream i think we are
all supposed to stream our own point of
views
um
uh however i am wait where is that that
this is this is that image
um
and then we have this one i love the art
for this so cute um so this is the
lineup
um
i will be in the d team with
uh also with ina
and raine and super senpai
um
and a couple others bales yeah yeah
uh
which makes me think that i could
perhaps if i were to stream because i
think we are being asked to stream hi
chunkers what is it um
oh she wants some belly rubs she jumped
up to the chair next to me so cute and
now she's showing me her belly um
uh so uh yeah i was thinking because the
team starts like approximately two hours
after the whole
event starts
so in theory that would mean i could at
least get maybe one and a half more
hours of sleep this starts at a really
bad time for me so every hour counts for
me every every half hour counts for me
so and then and then and then we talked
a little bit about it with ina yesterday
but there is a zako high which is like
for losers a loser cup and a winner cup
um
now i wonder if like everyone will end
up in one group one way or another
or
only the really worst ones and only the
really best ones
but i don't think i'm gonna get end up
let's be realistic like my mario kart
skills improved a while ago but i
haven't played for a long time again and
now i don't know how to play anymore
and um
also
uh i just even when i was decent at the
game i'm i'm sure that there's others a
lot of others in my team in my in my not
team
in my group that are better than me um
i'm gonna try of course i'm not gonna
lose on purpose
[Laughter]
but
i'm just a realistic type of person
yeah emma's birthday is very close to
the tournament
um
so anyway we wanna
we want to try to
um
at least not be lost
which i think should be possible
um
oh my god so much cat hair where did
that come from
[Music]
yeah to be honest since it's on the 7th
of january practicing today will not
really help me much unless i practice
more in the following days as well like
of the days following up to the event um
but yeah today is just maybe like i
don't know today is just to
to
um
replace the the gingerbread stream
[Music]
[Laughter]
i heard that mario senpai is so strong i
never actually saw her racing i need to
check it out but apparently marion
senpai is really good at it
uh and someone in the chat just said
that fubuki senpai
is also
pretty good
luna's the best new bracket in my
opinion what
luna senpai as well
oh dear
but um
i feel a little bit uh worried for a
good ah because then you know she's with
aqua senpai
and from my impression ako senpai is the
best uh mario kart player in all of her
life
so
she has no chance of winning
i mean in the end
you know once we are all in the
like cups of like winner cup and loser
cup once gouda is if she makes it to the
winner cup then it's like aqua sempa
will be there too and that's that's
where she will not be able to get number
one
[Laughter]
sorry i'm just very realistic a suicide
senpai
ah ah so we say somebody lost and won
the last uh um cup i guess uh yeah i did
watch something like that uh ages ago
one year ago i barely remember but
something happened there even though
like you know ako senpai was obviously
also very much up there um yeah toy
senpai too i guess i mean she's
organizing this you know she must be
good at the game right
oh well yeah so this is this is it this
is it this is it
um
then
i'm gonna start off by playing one or
two rounds oh
oh wait i have to download the game
[\h__\h] i deleted this one uh shouldn't
take too long
just give me a moment i should have done
this now while i was talking the whole
time
give me the moment it will yeah
uh i need to delete games um ah we don't
play ori anymore we're done with worry
uh
[Music]
uh what how did you hear
delete software delete
is that enough
uh pokemon i'm done too but i want to
keep it because in theory i'm not like i
still have some stuff is that is that
enough where did it go
ah here ah okay it's download is it
downloading is it
[Music]
is it downloading is i think it's not
downloading
it okay pokemon
come on
archive this one
now how about now
what is it did you guys hear that uh it
is connected to the internet god damn it
how about you download that [\h__\h]
i think it's downloading now
yeah yeah okay
what no no it will go down it will go
oh god i'm so sorry
i'm so sorry i thought i had the
important games all like you know up
there but there's only so much space i
have no
uh oh dear um oh god um
um
uh magikarp
super chat oh yeah i can okay you know
what we can do that indeed she's
scratching the tree right now uh
i have some super chats to read let me
let me
um oh
let me use the time uh wisely
yeah
i'm sorry cat i'm sorry
you know originally i wasn't planned to
be streaming this today um
i was gonna do gingerbread uh today yeah
i thought i thought that uh i already uh
i had this one
why did i delete mario kart because i
needed space for for
super mario and maori party superstars
and and all that damn it
okay i'm going to read the
what sims 4 already read i need to read
the the
super chats okay
let me just put up a sign um
uh
so that people
will understand what i'm doing i'm gonna
i'm gonna get there i'm gonna get there
um how about this one yeah yeah
uh
we're not singing
i shall
oh my god i am so sorry
i am reading super chat
until game download is done
okay this is really my bad i'm sorry
oh my god yeah i know there's like sd
cards but
let me put on some bgm
uh
oh my god it hit stream
meow indeed
what's what's going on
good thing
she jumped on the chain for herself
uh sideways flopped over immediately
she's like pepe pet me pet me pet me
okay music chunkers what do you want to
listen to
let's listen to this one
christmas lo-fi
you you will like this one
i'm petting her don't worry
your show is that on no
i downloaded this one from audio stock
it's so good
don't go behind there
okay
a bit more quiet i guess is this okay
maybe too loud still
[Music]
um
oh my god i need to take more time with
this
why are you on my playstation chunkers
get down from the playstation jokers
come here get down from the playstation
chunkers
yeah okay good baby yeah yeah come here
yeah okay
i don't know she's she's in an exploring
mood right now neko
[Music]
thank you very much
thank you thank you thank you no no
message with it unfortunately as per
usual what a surprise
[Music]
from
love this so much thank you
i've gotten a lot of great feedback for
the new song cover i really appreciate
it guys thank you for listening to it
everybody everybody listen to it right
right
yes yes yes yes hell yes um
yes yes yes yes
[Music]
i'm glad you guys like it i think the
song choice was
absolutely exquisite
[Music]
what what do you mean final message
what do you mean that's like no don't
say goodbye say see you again what the
hell no
that's sad don't make me sad
divine divine indeed the chorus is stuck
in my head uh that's how it's supposed
to be
ice ice
it's a meme
oh oh that's what meme that scares me i
don't like it when people say goodbye
you know i don't understand memes
mv is cute as heck as well it is i'm so
happy with the all the cute animations
um
google it it is fun
change the world my final message the
whole thing
see you on the track in exactly an hour
wait when exactly an hour my my download
will be done sooner than that
eh
what was it uh change the world my
physical change
change the world
my final message goodbye
[Music]
oh
uh-huh i feel like i've seen that before
[Music]
the deformed rat is smoking a cigarette
common in historical executions along
with his final words
[Music]
oh wait that's so rad the moment i just
looked at it it looked like uh like a
like a a camille what's coming again
why did i think yeah camel why did i
think it was a camel
i looked it i glanced over it no even i
looked at it for two seconds and i was
like oh camel
click on the video that sounds good i
don't know about copyright i would have
to mute my my part okay one second
that's so noisy
[Laughter]
okay well i'm glad that it was not a
real goodbye
yeah
changed our world my final message like
okay
you did this to me now i'll do it to you
chain
change the world my final message
goodbye bye
bye this is how it sounded
that's what you get noisy robot kiara
yes
wait did you hear did you hear the the
video
wait did i not ask uh not actually mute
it
oh well
uh how's mario kart looking i'm i'm i'm
censoring the pro progress for you guys
so that you guys don't so that you guys
can look forward to the future a bit
more um okay it's it's looking all right
captain jerk pants duncan i did mute it
okay good thank you for the pinky
captain jerkbands i appreciate it thank
you no text again as well
[Music]
salubrious beats thank you i think there
was no time to really write the proper
message huh
it was so hype it was so hype i was
spending a lot of time yesterday reading
everyone's reactions um it's not getting
out of my head nice
[Music]
nicer
than
quite interested in the one you're doing
of ammo and why it's the most expensive
oh
uh
you will see
celebrities beat sanchez and cruz duncan
jim tracey
naked
that was so good a perfect choice for
the two of you thank you takoyami duncan
traversing that was amazing such a
catchy song you two were great and
akashiba begs our
art was fantastic thank you art art okay
thank you indeed yes
i
[Music]
be
yes yes he did great work
thank you for the pinky that cover is so
good thank you kiara and ina thank you
as well for listening to it and
supporting
um the music on my channel i
i have been planning and and putting out
all these song covers with my fellow uh
myth members
um mostly it was me who chose all the
songs and who did all the lyrics
distribution and all that and organ
organizing and choosing which uh which
artist and what art we need the blue
blah
um yeah yeah and i'm really really like
always very happy with the outcome of
the video so it's really really exciting
to work on these um
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat thank
you
[Music]
awesome you all did a great job again
the lyrics uh are low blow dough
yeah the lyrics are depresso espresso
very different from other
cute songs that i've sang so far
[Music]
yeah but um i think that's good and a
lot of people said they could relate to
the song lyrics um which
is
i think a good thing right being able to
relate to it um
i mean currently like for me i'm doing
i'm doing fine um i don't exactly relate
to the to the lyrics of the song right
now maybe but in the past i can
definitely see myself relating to it so
but i didn't exactly choose it uh
because of the lyrics the main reason
why i chose that song was because of the
the instrumentals the the beats the you
know the whole song was just so
so good i thought you guys would really
like it even though a lot of you
probably didn't know the original
[Music]
because it's not one of these like i
mean it does have a lot of views but i
feel like it also never reached me
before like like i said i didn't know
about nero sun beforehand um
but
uh yeah now i know his songs i listened
to a couple of his other songs and they
were all really really really
cool
he has a very interesting
style
you made a great choice kara thank you
the whole song was amazing indeed
my first time hearing it too um
checked it the morning before you mean
yeah because uh
because i already told you guys what
song it's gonna be a bunch of you guys
heard the original beforehand but
[Music]
yes yes
yes yes it was a great pick thank you
took me down memory lane oh
[Music]
concerning legs
i like it though because i feel like you
know so many
um
huh but no maybe that's a bit
generalizing but i feel like so many um
like i idol songs and and like also the
songs that whole life has put out so far
uh no hate but they're mostly like yeah
yeah yeah i know yay cute love um happy
love peace
so i think it needs a little bit more of
a of a change in between you know some
something different
[Music]
love and peace
uh thank you for a sec
wrestle buckets thank you for the pinky
i have found a new song to set my alarm
to oh did you really
thank you again for this lovely vanga
you to have a happy holiday you too
oh my god tomorrow's christmas at least
for me like we celebrate on the 24th um
it's it's it's exciting christmas is
happening oh my god thank you russell i
hope you have a lovely christmas
uh happy holidays stay healthy stay safe
thank you shin for your lovely support
and i hope waking up too
is uh comfortable
[Music]
thanks for the song
had so much fun listening to it thank
you i'm glad i'm glad to hear that
it is a very fun song
mr kasper's dancing
i'm speechless after this cover hi
speechless after this
you did it to yourself oh you see the
bar you see it you see it oh my god
we're getting there
it was so damn good kudos for the song
choice it fits both your voices damn
well thank you
[Music]
um
yeah i guess it does um
you know when collabing
in a song cover with someone for the
first time which is kind of always the
first time uh it's kind of hard to tell
whether or not um the song will really
fit the voices beforehand uh but
it did it did uh fit very very well i
guess
yeah you know first originally
i think originally i was going for
completely different songs that would be
more on the cute side or so
and
um
yeah
but i'm glad i ended up with this song
instead it's more special
yeah the other song choices were a bit
more basic i think
[Music]
at least it's a new song i haven't heard
i just came from watching the cover oh
thank you thank you
i think usually when it comes to song
covers
i feel like they
um
get more attraction if it's songs
original songs that are already like
originally popular and well-known and
this one isn't very well known in our
uh
in in in my community i think but but
it's still doing well right now because
it's so funky and so good
thank you guys for sharing it and for
listening to it
[Music]
for the pinky
bloody helmets the song was damn amazing
i'm really bopping to it your voice
perfectly blend well together gotta loop
this song thank you
yeah uh
i i guess so i guess they they blended
well together you guys say that uh i
guess it i guess it did blend well
together
uh inna has uh
when she sings a surprisingly high uh
sounding voice and i me too so um
yeah we ended up blending well i guess i
guess we did i guess we did
change the thumbnail huh
what do you mean change the thumbnail
[Music]
huh
uh taxi thank you for the pinky as well
thank you shirt what is the board
it's a drawing stream
oh uh what
no the one up above me is not supposed
to be the super chat reading funk name
it's not it's just it's just promotion
up there
uh
so yeah time to dance
yeah right is that a red heart or an
orange heart red hot purple heart
yeah
it was an amazing cover both you and ina
harmonized really well thank you
[Music]
i actually i had speaking of harmonies i
had uh gojo gojo-san the one who mixed
uh the the
singing the voices the vocals um because
i couldn't find a guide for harmonies
i asked him to create harmonies
beforehand um so that we could record
them because songs always sound better
with harmonies
um
so uh he made some great harmonies for
me to use the action very much
appreciate it
[Music]
i'll be back in seven minutes i'm of
course going to listen twice so thank
you
yeah looking at my downloads uh yeah you
could probably take seven minutes yeah
sounds good sounds good
uh loud bird thank you for the pinky
bless everything about this it is my
favorite piece of music music to come
out of our life oh
thank you kiara thank you ina
[Music]
yeah thank you very much i'm surprised
it's your favorite out of whole live wow
yeah vampire is also very close to 1
million so please guys while you're at
it i would appreciate it if you guys
would give vampire another listen as
close to 1 million no i know
i know
[Music]
you changed your name to japanese
writing why
is it
[Laughter]
thank you
very much a slackers and from yes
yes
anton m
for the pinky as well without a doubt
one of the best covers i've ever heard
well done inna and kiara thank you wow
i'm i'm i'm i'm a bit overwhelmed with
all the
i mean i knew it was good but i i'm
overwhelmed with how how much praise i'm
getting
even kelly um wrote to me that she
really really likes it
i was i was surprised like not only on
twitter she even dm'd me and this
morning i looked at it and it was like
again
wow you really like it huh thank you
[Music]
[Laughter]
a banger
apparently
dragon's fire thank you for the pinkie
an amazing cover you and eno sounded so
good gonna have to put it on repeat
forever thank you
um i'm glad you think so because we also
um
both of us uh did a lot of very low
lines for this song um maybe you guys
noticed especially i think me i sang a
lot of low parts actually my voice went
lower than usual did you guys like it
did you guys like it
[Music]
actually
when i listened to my original song i
thought hmm
then there's the boy right so she should
he should have the lower
uh key lines right and then should have
the higher ones right and listen even
listening to the song i didn't quite
realize yet that it kind of is the other
way around but that's why i thought ina
would be better at singing lower uh
lower line so i gave those to her the
ones that i fought that would be lower
but then when i started recording i
realized wait a second i've bamboozled
myself
er
for some reason my lines are lower
but
it was it worked it worked out fine
happy accidents yeah
[Music]
because i thought you know
singing in a low key is not really my
strong suit i thought you know has
she has a high voice too but a little
bit lower than mine i think like i felt
like she would be doing better in the
lower register but
uh
actually she also said she struggled a
little bit
[Music]
hmm
i had a hard time recognizing her really
[Music]
the ladies lyrics
yeah really good lyrics
[Music]
this might be the catching song that
i've heard from you oh yeah yeah i knew
you guys would think it's catchy i'm
glad you guys gave it a try seven chica
seven thank you soon thank you
and i gave you those cookies no problem
mh ziggy duncan we're almost done with
the download
almost done
i'm so sorry guys
i'm so sorry for that
uh google translate
korean
also you
[Music]
never heard the song before the cover
and just wanted to say what a choice the
lyric is dark but then but when wrapped
around the upbeat music and cute singing
it becomes oh
motivational it doesn't matter what you
are today give it your all tomorrow
yeah you gotta look closer if you look
at the lyrics it might seem very
depressing but
uh
yeah it kind of it kind of has a
motivational twist to it as well
[Music]
she's excited she wants to play mario
kart 2.
okay so let's end it here at carp
upstairs and the rest i will read after
the stream
meow
meow yes meow i'm finally done let's
turn off the christmas lo-fi did you
like that one i really liked that one
that was really chill
oh [\h__\h] there you go
ah yes use uh this one for the code
later
[Music]
let online try to get back into it
uh
um
by doing one or two rounds against npcs
please
[Music]
oh it's been a while oh it's been quite
a while
okay so single player we started off
with single players excuse me give me a
moment please
um look look when i practiced last time
i collected all of these uh golden ones
yeah yeah uh some of them better than
others
uh okay so i'm i'm assuming 150 cc
and someone sent me
uh a guide on what card i should go for
this time and you know what i'm just
gonna trust you with that
i'm just gonna do exactly what you're
telling me there's three different
builds which one should i use
okay
okay no more wait is that baby daisy i i
i don't mind i guess going for something
else to be more serious this time wait
what which one is the most
um recommended here
[Music]
regular day regular day is that regular
days ah i guess it is
okay okay
then let's shoot daisy what's up
oh new stuff
okay let's see if i have all of this uh
this card is uh do i have that card
oh [\h__\h] i think i don't
even though i already played so much i
don't have it
[Music]
can i use
the one that
peach has or yeah do i have that one
what is that what is that card
oh
god uh
what is that oh what's that what are
those what is that
what is that is this the one no that's
not the one i did
oh my oh that's that's the one that's
one of them yeah i really don't have the
other one do i
yeah i don't okay okay
so this one should work too
uh
and
it barely makes a difference yeah i
guess so and then the wheels are the
just these ones i think yeah and then
this one
i don't have the one in the
image well i don't have the one
so i'll this one looks funny
i'll just go with this oh wait maybe
that is that one
okay
well which one should we practice with a
little bit let's do one one cup are you
guys okay with that
online
[Music]
okay
let's do it oh god guys i really haven't
played in a million years i don't know
how to play anymore i don't even know
how to uh i don't know how to use
[Laughter]
[Music]
items wait do i have steering
oh [\h__\h] i don't know did that
ah i have staring on her off at all auto
steering you guys see it
[Music]
cause if i had it on then it's not gonna
be proper practice i'll have to cancel
you can turn it off even now
hold on
smart steering is it right smart
steering is off
that's the one right
okay
okay this ass
starts off nicely i i need to get a
feeling for this new card okay i gotta
do tricks as well when jumping
i gotta how do i use items again what
the hell was that ah that was a
different camera how do i use items
how do i use okay
oh i'm kind of kind of was a shortcut
and then yeah trick okay
oh i could have kept that one but oh
well i don't like this item
it's kind of hard to use oh i got him i
got him
i got him
i'm second now
okay not so bad for having not played
this game in a million years
never mind there was a
gap there please mind the gap
oh god no ah
the inside
of those curves
gets me a little bit too often
that's a good trip don't eat though
okay i got someone with the bomb nicer
but uh
the girls are not as stupid as these
npcs
oh god oh god
oh god
the bananas the bananas
[Music]
oh wait this is not the last round yes
where is your excitement i need your
mental support
[Laughter]
[Music]
if i can't win against npcs i'm never
gonna win against uh alive girls
oh
[Music]
this is not this is raked i am
officially number
i'm officially number one
that was fake that doesn't count
at the very end no chance to catch up
anymore that's just not fair
oh man
official number one
[Music]
i
don't have much experience with this one
the [\h__\h] toads they're so excited
go
daisy looks so good in that suit
okay item ghetto look at me doing those
tricks yeah
eat this
oh oh oh god uh
put this behind my back i guess
i'm number one easy
[Music]
eat this
you're not gonna be number one for long
look at here go yup
don't eat me plant please
it's the revenge of the plants
it is
[Music]
no problem first again no [\h__\h]
problem
ah
okay i didn't really lose much from that
thankfully i only had a coin
okay banana on my back
playing it safe this time i got this one
at least someone right
oh my god so many bananas let's leave
one there
and throw this down
oh i've never tried that one before
[Music]
okay stir a little bit up so that i
don't
uh fall into the voids oh oh oh
oh my bananas
[Music]
my bananas
i need my potassium come on
i really need it health wise i haven't
been doing well
hi cat i don't know which one it is but
i see a cat in the corner of my eye
thank you for the mental support cat
oh there it goes there it comes oh oh no
it disappeared
i don't like that curve
yeah
styling
that's also something i need to practice
but i am doing
stable
movements oh [\h__\h] that was really bad
oh no not at the finish line
[Music]
[Laughter]
i ate two bananas and i still made it
oh thankfully
okay
volcano volcano time
[Music]
let's do this
after this cup i'll be doing online
matches with you guys where i'll
probably do much worse but whatever
it's about having fun in the end
go
oh [\h__\h]
i should too early
i [\h__\h]
oh yeah oh [\h__\h] oh
oh the curves
oh that that was a
pretty curve
ah
oh shut up
[Music]
okay i gotta catch up a little bit
i'm gonna follow oh
i should not have fought oh god oh god
danger zone
one luigi
i don't want to see your butt all the
time please get behind me
[Music]
okay second
what do you guys say is this oh god
i was just about to ask you if you think
that my my doritos and my driving skills
and all that are decent enough but i
take it i don't want to know the answer
i don't i don't want to know
oh oh good timing
oh god
i was too fast to see that one coming
i feel like i have some good moments and
did i have some really bad moments
i don't need to rewatch tutorial videos
i'm doing just fine
i think okay okay nice
we're going this way now i don't know
which one is the better way oh god oh
[Music]
you still have a chance
go get him go get him
i got someone i think
[Music]
there's barely a path left man
oh look at me oh [\h__\h]
i can't
why the [\h__\h] did that hit me
you're supposed to hit number one not
number four and five what the hell
that was decent
okay okay okay
[Music]
okay okay okay okay
number one in the end that's all
[Music]
i feel like i can't be too proud though
because these are npcs although they
aren't
the top two like baby rosalina and peach
they are pretty decent npcs
they are pretty decent
number one number one
oh no oh no this will ruin my rating
oh [\h__\h] now
money money i i hope to the gods that
this one will not be in the in the new
year's cup
it will be random right will it be
random
was it random last year
which cups are gonna be on the race
oh i'm number one
at this maybe this was one this one was
the one that's fairly decent because
there's more than one rainbow road
so far so good
it's wait i want to read the comments
this is random you get to choose
uh is it like our tournament the iden
tournament that i did where we were able
to
um like
put up some suggestions and then it
would go randomly by those suggestions
meow
oh god
i'm gonna catch up again i'm practicing
i just wanted to get an answer to my
question
we should it's still practice you know
having to catch up is realistic
and it's gonna be a thing that i have to
do in the match as well several times
probably look at my moves
so far i haven't
fell off the cliff yet haven't i
oh my god
i'm trying to be a little bit careful
with my driving right now
yeah okay
you gotta go oh tonight
[Music]
okay
the ink the ink
[Music]
no no
give it a [\h__\h] item
[Music]
hi baby i'm okay i'm okay i swear
i'm not okay did she literally me out
into my face she came up
she wants the cuddles too
that was a very audible me
[Laughter]
oh man okay wait was that the last one
i guess it was
okay ah that's okay
that's okay um
what i won
[Music]
in total
oh
congratulations yeah that's how it's
supposed to be a thousand fifty coins
nice a new vehicle customization nice so
okay we're gonna do online now
[Music]
i'm gonna do online now
after i give her some belly rubs yeah
she want the belly rubs i know you do
okay how are we doing this again online
play
and then we're going to choose one of my
tournaments
uh
tournament
i
will
um
how do we do this should i immediately
who's so totally for example one second
let me hide it for a moment
um
[Music]
uh uh-huh
okay
and then let me type it
here you won't see it yet
[Music]
okay everyone uh if you participated
previously you're welcome to
participate again today but please only
participate once per stream okay
um okay
uh
yes
yes join
uh and we go with the same
options let's go
here it is
please
please join and enjoy
i just realized i didn't have my
hashtags up whatever
hashtag is local good question
they are up in the title
i hope i get in
can i get in please
let me in
let me in please
communication era let's go
[Music]
let me please
hi yo
how you
please no communication era
internet says yes yes
let me end in my own tournament please
it's called kusa tony for a reason
only guy
oh my god yes i am in who else is in
oh
yokomido na a face i've seen a few times
too often
[Laughter]
famous famous mario kart
player um from
the whole live viewers always shows up
in literally every
single
uh mario kart online play stream
doesn't matter if it's pekura or someone
else
oh oh game goku oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
yes we have kadapuru pekora
how do they do it i wonder they are they
are
they probably have some kind of like
code
they they coded maybe something to let
them know
whenever someone is playing mario kart
with viewers
okay let's go
oh we had a
failed start kusa
oh yeah
great start
not so bad
i can do some styling here
let's go
i'm 12 let's go
[\h__\h]
yes catching up as i said will be
something i will have to practice as
well
[Music]
if only the star would keep you from
falling down cliffs as well that would
be amazing
[Music]
passing through
okay now we're talking here everyone
look at this
[Music]
i'm gonna draw something on your screens
oh come
come what the [\h__\h]
all of you spiderman what the [\h__\h]
no i even stopped i need to stop um not
only stop drifting but also maybe stop
like speeding in general when i get to
those curves because otherwise i can't
handle them
[Music]
polite mikko
polite instead of elite mikko no no
is this one how was it with this one was
better to like smash them all uh uh
really fast or
or in a
decent
uh
have some decent timing
probably should smash them all at once
huh
i'm bigger than all of you and stomp on
your little heads and smash them
oh [\h__\h] yes that was not good
[Music]
intelligent boosting is better overlay
okay so like i'm doing it now i mean so
being too fast in these curves won't
help me either
[Music]
give me those yes
thank you
some
some races
i am a bit better because there's just
not too many crazy curves uh but this
one was not one of those there are a lot
of crazy curves thank you everybody
please leave the stage and let some
other people in thank you thank you good
game gg
gt indeed
um
royal raceway looks so pretty i don't
remember
how that one
goes i do want that one
i don't really like the subway one that
much
[Music]
i should learn
i should i should obviously practice all
of them but i should also maybe practice
one that i'll be specifically good at
and i will continuously like vote for
that one
to have that one
chosen so that i have at least one one
um one
course where i'm really good at maybe
is that a good plan
new people come on
come on
yeah it depends a lot on chance indeed
but i feel like sooner or later um
especially if i choose a course that
um
that oh
that uh is maybe a little bit popular
then there might be higher chances of it
actually being
chosen
[Music]
i'm not sure if everyone left properly
but please do next time then please
if if someone stayed please oh my course
has been selected
so many japanese people
maybe he didn't make it in time please
leave next time then everybody let's
let's others peop other people play as
well thank you
oh
yeah i want to hit one of them
no [\h__\h]
it looks like i'm drunk or something
[Music]
i'm coming
i'm drunk
[Music]
oh
i was kind of catching up my
[\h__\h] grass man
who said
turn the [\h__\h] around now
i hate this course there's so many cribs
[Music]
go
eliminate all enemies
[\h__\h] it
sorry
japanese bro
i don't mean it okay
please don't hate me
[Music]
oh i stopped speeding there for a moment
okay
on purpose of course
it's so exhausting
oh my god
yeah you gotta keep in mind that uh i'm
really not familiar with some of these
courses not that much so
uh if i get to know them better i'm sure
that i can improve a lot i thought also
you know what yes we still have a lot of
time for this maybe i'll try to learn
some shortcuts even
oh why are you waiting for me
again number nine number nine
thank you
[Music]
next people please
hi chunkers hi why is everyone saying
hello to me today
these cats are so needy
yoshi circuit let's go oh i should have
uh voted later so that they have time to
come back in
that one looks the same as someone else
who just entered oh uh more people more
people please yummy
ah
well this means that i can at least not
become 12.
yeah yeah
i cannot no okay i like that one too i
like that one a lot
uh
[Music]
like three people who were in the last
race but they might have not had enough
time to leave
because i immediately
selected a new race
i'll give them the benefit of the doubt
because i think especially the japanese
bros
know these manners
don't get too close to takanese
[Music]
i think i'm fairly decent in this race
not sure if i should go up there if
that's better
look at me being number two hello
hello
as i said i do like this one
i feel like i'm super slow right now
okay caught that one oh it's a fellow
australian
tommy yes
it was good
for me
and i'm good
i'm sorry link i literally waited for
you
and what did you expect huh
[Music]
okay i mean this is really decent so far
no
no you messed up my perfect race
okay this is good she slalom my ghost
jacket
as an austrian this
uh skiing place is
easy my territory
natural territory okay let's go
okay
got
yeah it's still a star
that's that's a good item to steal
number three
okay
i mean out of these people
what were they doing did they leave
what were my japanese bros doing
okay
not many people there
thank you guys thank you
bye bye
next people please oh
yeah let's wait for more players indeed
let's wait for more players go easy on
me you go easy on me
you don't have to go easy on me
yeah no tanky style brain empty style
is my driving style
no tanky style
are we complete
[Music]
i'm using tails controls really amazed
fist
is that you that looks like a chicken
you look like a chicken nice
on the bottom right looks like a chinkin
[Music]
oh the dragon
thingy is really popular huh
oh oh it's the piranha weren't we there
before
oh
next entousan
let's go everybody
thank you amazing cover and the song is
extremely addictive to begin with true
i agree i listened to it a lot when i
first found it
i was addicted for a while as well
hello cat on the bottom of my chair
how's it going meow meow i need some
items please hello
yeah
i think that's chunkers
oh no
it's not looking good for me
[Music]
okay nice styling nice flexing okay
okay i got the shortcut but what the
hell
at what cost
i got the shortcut but at what cost
[Music]
at least seventh is better than what i
usually get
ah
[\h__\h] i wasn't sure if i wanted to go
left or middle
okay
[Music]
save me save me
save me
everybody's riding on a bullet right now
bye bye
okay
i don't want to be 10.
[Music]
oh oh it's still going we're still going
i thought it was
[Laughter]
okay
oh thank god this difficult part i can
skip it
miss face come let me catch you
nah
boring
no
8472 give me those items those are mine
oh man oh man
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
man
oh man
um
[Music]
okay
no
i don't want to be tension in that sense
ah
julie no tension
oh
i can do i mean okay i'm not i'm not i'm
not mad at myself i mean i really
haven't played for a long time and you
this is really like if you are not like
a mario kart pro player then you're
gonna forget the
like you're gonna get out of the feeling
if you don't play for such a long time
it's okay it's understandable
okay everybody come back in i'm all
alone here
nice excuses one maneuver usually room
uh five days bye bye
[Laughter]
come on hello
hello
all around me
[Music]
and i find it kind of funny i find it
kind of sad i indeed find it funny and
sad there's a fish
there's a fish or is that a kappa or a
fish
oh wait there's ah
downtown let's go downtown
there's a famous comedian um look alike
here
right uh like behind me
to my right side no to my left side i
guess
ah that's a math carp ah
i'm gonna go with shy guy false i guess
i don't care all of these are okay
matsumoto
taikiku
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah
uh if you guys know that program then
you will understand
i explained it before though
this was a strategy because i didn't
want to get mixed into all of the
um
crowd
into the whole crowd in the beginning
you know it gets very busy in the
beginning
it was a strategy
oh [\h__\h]
get out of here just keep playing
[Music]
why do i not have an item in my hands
fly high burp fly high
yes going for that and grass i hate it
this is why i don't go outside to touch
grass because it always stops me it
makes you go slower you could go so much
faster if you just don't touch the grass
you know
oh
i'm not gonna use that here no not in
the curves
where is a good spot to use it
maybe here
[Music]
and start
i feel like i'm driving okay-ish but i'm
still very far behind explain this to me
explain it to me
[Applause]
thank you for the super chat but i'm
just confused at what you're trying to
tell me
[Music]
it's the battle of the
the giants
[Music]
okay
yes
yes my best one so far
[Music]
nice
that was fun it was an interesting race
thank you sir i appreciate it
good good driving everybody
drive safely oh my god what the hell was
that face
that player's face oh my god
it's disturbing was that dude already in
here
could be
or like sometimes when you go back to
this map there's already new people in
here
so that could be it hello commerce dome
hello where is your where are your
friends where's your family bring them
here
oh here we are here is everybody ina is
also here um
i don't care
i don't care give me whatever
oh ina chose the same one
synchronized
i'm sent to the old tournament um i
think there are
like two different rooms um
for the tournament
like you could get into my room or you
could get into a different room i think
inannu
sashimi out of inna says that name
please
tell me that that means
you are the session before you know not
discussing me out of inna it could mean
both things
very concerning
taco sashimi
number one number one take a screenshot
[\h__\h] you daisy get out of here
what [\h__\h]
i want it up there
ah
this one come on
oh i couldn't even do a trick
okay i don't know this one so well
there's just a lot of cars
no give me one no i want an item
for a little bit
out
[Music]
so far this race is boring because the
track has not much to offer so far
um
stupid cars you should be driving faster
this is a highway
i got a star too you can't hurt me
this can't hurt me either
[Music]
oh my god so many bananas
[\h__\h]
i wanted that one
don't bump into the car
daddy stole my fire flower i wanted to
use it
can i go here
that's a box bag
what is going on with this race what is
this kind of cursed
can i not do a trick up there i was
pushing this button
maybe the timing was all
[Music]
and start so that i cannot bump against
these walls
[\h__\h] what the hell man
what's this going on it's like my game
is rigged or something
[Music]
is that think yeah seventh chill seven
joe
seven joe
sounds weird but that is me indeed thank
you everybody thank you soon
good match good match
bye bye bye bye bye bye next people
please yeah take that crown with you i
guess
could have left it here out of
politeness give give me the crown for a
moment so that i can feel good too for a
moment but no
no apparently apparently i don't deserve
it
is that a bales
oh my god what is that on the left side
what the [\h__\h] is that
is that batman or
what is that
what's that supposed to be cool
darth vader
mummy's drawing
you gotta earn the crown boss i already
earned it
[Music]
just by existing
oh emilia from fate
oh
oh welcome matani oh yeah
okay can we win against jungle
can we win against yaga
yes yes we can
yeah
come on start it already
start it
don't have time
tomorrow's [\h__\h] christmas i gotta
clean my apartment
for real
my family is coming over i got some
stuff to do
oh my god
hey
i totally got like
mixed into something i shouldn't have
been mixed into
give me double item yes
i'm currently tencho but i want to be
seven chill
if i were seven in the actual tournament
though i guess i would be in uh
zako taco cup
which is not good but okay
oh look at all the items i don't know
which one i throw out first but
out of the way
my god yes oh that won't do anything
oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] i like the the
climbery sound there though
[Music]
go at least
but jago is so far ahead his face
this freaking face
[Music]
i used to be better on this race man
oh i know come on you love me so much
don't you
why won't you go behind me
please
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
into the race
the one who made the google art for the
music video
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh did that just happen happened
unknown
ah
back to tanjo
it was nice being seven joe for a little
while
ah
this is my fate
will i forever be tensile i'm a little
nervous oh oh oh you're saying that you
didn't you didn't do it on purpose you
know cause you were you were
you were you were nervous
okay i got the crown look at me
i know you gotta go though you gotta go
though you gotta go though before before
the next thank you wait before the next
race starts okay
dolphin shows i don't think i know that
well
hello
oh okay bye
is that supposed to be in your center or
no wait that looks like coyote oh that
looks like coily
you guys are so good with creating miss
i think that's cool dude
cause that face looks so much like her
uh
[Laughter]
i called into her stream
uh yesterday or the day before yesterday
i think i told you guys already
oh
it is supposed to be coyote the name
says pink head
uh coyote
um yeah we fangirled over game of
thrones because i saw in her debut
stream she's she wrote that she likes
game of thrones and the moment i saw
that i was like oh my god we got to talk
about that
and i was wondering if she knew that
there was gonna be um
like a spin-off
so i figured she probably doesn't know
so i called into her stream to tell her
that
and she didn't know she was
excited to hear about it
did you guys know
oh [\h__\h] oh wow
i'm excited for the spin-off
2022 let's go
also
speaking of new shows coming up uh 2022
january or february i think february
is where what another season of one of
my other favorite shows
is coming out
uh which is oh my god
uh
the great uh no no no
oh
uh miss maisel mrs manuzelle
yes the marvelous mrs mazel not the
great mrs wiesel
oh this is actually quite a fun race so
far i like the the tricks that you can
do in all these places
some good spots here and there
it's still challenging oh my god that
was not fair i landed literally inside
of that and i had no choice
and i like the music for that one too
i am your senpai although this is not
the real you i understand that but you
must let your selfie go first i'm fifth
show right now five show five so let's
go
whoa
i'm four two
[\h__\h]
[Music]
one unlucky mistake
no
[Music]
never give
up no not give
[Music]
up don't wanna be friends
oh thank you for waiting
oh
ten shots
i was supposed to be higher up i was
doing so well but that that
i fell down at the spot where i
shouldn't have
i could have could have gone way higher
this was supposed to be my
time ah
oh man
okay i'm just practicing
[Music]
why are we still searching for players
nintendo are you gonna give me an error
and connection error i feel it it's
coming
here's a card no we're going for speed
we are going for speed
i've been told to go for speed so i'll
go for
speed there are different play styles
and we're going for speed
no it's okay
i might take some time to practice off
stream with a non-speedy build as well
and see maybe if it really feels better
but
so far um
i'm gonna go this way
i'm nintendo
[Music]
let me open it up again
are we gonna be able to get in we're
currently spectating so some other
people are driving right now
i don't want to look at you guys oh
someone's called phoenix
come on let's go
phoenix from france even
excitebike arena well then show me
something
quick
hello
there we go
you will join the next race sit tight
they just started
oh okay
uh oh
number one draco let's look at him
okay yeah yeah the link built and that
cart i need that cart
we're supposed to be
wait was that a cart
is
oh that's okay okay okay that one was
unless there's a bike version of that
this one is the one i'm supposed to be
using
which that one is a cart so
uh or is it is it considered a bike
it's a quad uh-huh
i want that one how much longer do i
have to play this game to get this cart
man
i've been playing quite a lot before
i still don't have that one
it's a quad and it's great the metal
cart oh four wheels so it's a car yeah
that's what i thought too
go go oh oh no he got hit oh [\h__\h]
will he still win
we will see shortly
he's doing all those
styling flexes
i mean this this this track is fairly uh
easy for me as well
it's quite fun
it's very repetitive but that makes it
easy and he won
oh no there's one more round there's one
more round never mind that everybody
we're in for one more round
and link he goes stable and steady
as he usually does
maybe in 2022 we'll also see a sequel or
prequel of his
game rebel of the wild two let's go oh
oh no the blue shell hit him oh no
it's what makes the
mario kart game is the most salty
they'll be like oh this is not fair [\h__\h]
this [\h__\h] and throw down the controllers
like little babies
oh but he recovered he recovered nicely
no one got anything on him
no one in sight
only items flying at him
and he won the race yeah
number one draco
look at his happy face
the excitement
it is so obvious
let's go
okay finally
you guys are welcome to stay in the race
uh and drive with us because you didn't
drive with me yet if you want to you're
welcome to do so
uh we're back in the game
oh god although draco he was number one
maybe you should leave
[Laughter]
just kidding you can stay you're not
school
throwing down the 80 joy-con is the pro
controller 80 i don't remember how much
it was
yeah well
gamers don't care they destroyed their
keyboards they destroyed their
controllers when they're salty
um i don't know which one i want
mario kart stadium because i'm probably
the worst at that one out of that
selection
nihongo yo mario
yo yo yo
okay
which one is it gonna be
i'm running out of water by the way
wild wiggler unlocks via coin collecting
yeah but when i was playing the game
privately i was trying to collect a lot
of coins as well
because i had barely any cards
um
unlocked
oh it's a blue yoshi cute and then
tanooki from the back but mario from the
front
cutest from the back definitely
[Music]
oh no
oh [\h__\h]
[Applause]
[Music]
okay calm down kiana
you can still win in theory
a theory only
[Music]
a lot of lot of nice items i'm getting
at least something to help me out here
oh
get that double item
yes yes perfect timing
perfect timing
[Music]
[\h__\h] five joe let's go let's [\h__\h]
go
i hate you
i never know
you made me tencho again
[Music]
stupid [\h__\h] game i hate it
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] uh please be quick everybody
quick quick quick quick i already chose
the rice unfortunately thank you
thank you
yeah
i was screwed over once again
so painful
i don't know if i'm improving at all
though
um
am i improving
you'll get them next time you think so
i'm not sure
what team is cat uh you mean in the
tournament i'll be in the d cup
nope little no
oh come on
questionable
[Music]
um ella where is everybody there they
are
oh
oh another pack no saki no saki
which one was that one again
i've seen that one around as well
and this is that one supposed to be okay
let's see
robotnik yeah he's here too
i like seeing what people do with the
with the knees
oh
[Music]
oh oh okay that's good um i feel like
they keep on repeating anyway nice drive
okay i'll go get nice
a lot of germans right now scott is
clapton
there's so many germans to let me speak
in german
and we want them to feel comfortable
why we want them to feel comfortable
venting
foreign
[Music]
oh look
look at all my mushrooms
[Music]
wrong with you
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
m
[Laughter]
[Music]
fun
i for some reason sometimes uh managed
to get seven not eight not nine but
seven
thank you arigato
german boosted my stats
time to enter why did you wait one hour
maybe you waited for me to get better it
didn't really happen i guess
thank you thank you for participating
hope that was fun for you guys i like
playing games with you guys together
audience participation streams always a
lot of fun also i'm running i have no
more water
damn it you guys think i can
make maybe after the next race um i'm
gonna run to grab some water
and brb
that one is so cute is that
wait is that a good
lookalike
[\h__\h] you is love
indeed poor
cute
welcome welcome
hello hello
kind of similar to small and it has
those little mini twin tails
okay guys i'll wait are we 12.
let's do sherbet land i guess doesn't
matter one two three four five six seven
eight nine ten yeah we are
i think we are
let's go
[Music]
wait we're not 12 are we 11
that's okay
that's all right
okay wario
which one is that wario something
something wrong with stadium
okey-dokey
there's two koreans as well
and
number one to say all
please
please number one
okay
you'll get a purple if you let me number
one
understand
oh my god oh hello look at me look at me
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
oh my god oh my my
oh my
oh [\h__\h]
nice
nice get out of the way i was supposed
to be number two
oh god oh god safely safely i don't want
to fall down
at all costs
[Music]
[\h__\h]
didn't get the speed thingies
unfortunately
[Music]
okay
okay oh i jumped above it
that saved me some trouble
look at all those stylings
[Music]
he goes on the bad kids list who won't
get presents for christmas this year
that's that's
for sure
i have my contacts with uh the santa
claus man
i don't like that curve what the hell is
that curve it's not even a curve
[Music]
oh man okay
desperate situations call for desperate
uh
means
oh
holy [\h__\h]
wow
that's why i'm supposed to be hell yeah
that's right
everyone was so close together
at the end
oh no not this part not this point what
do you want
what do you want
[\h__\h] is that the finish line there
[Music]
ah
three
that ladies and gentlemen was not a rage
quit that was just me
getting water
[Laughter]
there were sometimes there where um i
was doing pretty good though but that
that curve
which wasn't the curve it was just a
corner
two corners i hate that excuse me
how do you not fall down from there
a rage continue
ten really likes me
well you know what we will at least get
into the zakohai and maybe we can become
number one of the taco high
maybe
that's at least something what the hell
is that face is that a garfield or
that's [\h__\h] garfield
that person may [\h__\h] garfield me
that is cute i i
i appreciate that i feel like you did
that for me
is that supposed to be that
niko
i know
no
there
that's [\h__\h] garfield what happened to
the free cheese pizza scarfield
where is he he's called garfield
welcome everybody
lots of americans in this round
he ate those food
well he he shall try to eat
those food that i will throw at him the
mushrooms and and [\h__\h]
no no mushrooms no mushrooms that will
only help him
item item let's go
i'll go here
okay banana to save my ass
almost bumped into the car be careful
everybody
safe driving is best though
okay i guarantee you i didn't even
intend to specifically hit garfield but
well that happened
number fantastic again
hallelujah
oh sure
this race this this track is really
boring
oh i finally did a trick on that one
nice look
uh okay got that item
double item
and time to speed no no no no
[\h__\h] took it i wanted to use as much
as possible before it would take it
[Music]
how did i manage to miss that one i was
literally right in front of it but the
banana scared me
oh i got the plant the piranha plant
okay
could be pretty useful here
yes okay
we got two two people
uh no item up here anymore damn it
okay time for a little bit of a dorito
and some more speed
[Music]
okay what the hell was that
oh my god
wow for joe
hey
i could have maybe even gotten food i'm
not sure because i just kind of stumbled
there at the end
at the finish line
could have maybe gotten first kitty
nice okay i'm happy with that currently
spectating why are we spectating
okay
my friends
what a lonely race don't worry i'm gonna
watch now it that makes it at least a
little bit more
meaningful
oh oh
you can press the item button to stop
the item relax sooner
oh
no
i mean
i didn't quite feel the need for it uh
until now but i guess so
hold on
[Music]
luciano
what is that face oh my god what are you
why is your nose under your teeth
that worries me we should probably do
rainbow road to practice it
are you practicing to be in the middle
of the i'm not sure what i am trying to
do
[Laughter]
i'm just trying to be decent i guess
even though i said i want to lose so
that i can drop out
[Laughter]
but i am going to do
as good as i can i'm not gonna drop out
on purpose
if it happens it happens and i will be
happy and go back to bed
huh i am practicing guru feet oh no
once are you a twice fan
okay
time to win everybody
time to win
[Music]
i'm gonna try out the item thing
perhaps
oh my god i i forgot it was uh already
too fast and i forgot how to use an item
are they using item again
sometimes i forget the easiest things
ah there it is
stop what's going on guys are you trying
to bully me
mental friend request
makes no sense to send me those i'm not
accepting them anyway
[Music]
here we go stop it
stop it now they're doing it
[Music]
okay stop it stop it
oh my god hello decent race though
he said i would say
oh
blue shell coming from
takanashikuwa you are welcome
you can't run but you can't hide oh
where are we going
[Music]
i seem to always get a
[\h__\h] a speech mushroom at that quarter i
can like cut that corner so often i'm
quite lucky there
um can you please like stop um excuse me
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
it was going so well
[Music]
no not that i wanted something else but
okay
yes
[Music]
oh
that doesn't count i was supposed to be
six joe or something here
i got stuck
i hate when that happens
i hate it
it's yeah i was sabotaged i was
sabotaged
uh thank you guys thank you for
participating please let in the next
people donkey should how much longer
should we play this i'm not sure uh
cheeseland perhaps are we we're not
complete
but okay
[Music]
nine
sabotaged by a friendship oh wait a
second oh wait a second
i wait a second wait a second it's wait
wait what is the video when is the video
coming up
when is that video coming on
shouldn't it be coming out now
i don't mean kelly's video i'm in a
different video by the way
someone just asked
okay
um
i have yeah i wrote in the title didn't
i that or did i yes there will be a
present today
uh i wonder when that one's coming out
it should be like coming out soon
um
i have a present for you guys
something that uh
originally i kind of wanted it to be
uploaded on my channel but due to
copyright reasons i couldn't
but we still made it anyway
and it's going to be up on
kana
by the way
i always wondered
uh
it's it should
be like sometime around now not quite
sure
when exactly
i don't see
a premiere or anything up at the moment
modern problems require modern solutions
exactly
i got this idea spontaneously and i
really wanted to make it happen
so
thankfully it's still on kind of
maybe
maybe maybe he's waiting until i'm done
driving
i've never done driving
my whole life is a race
i'm young
[Music]
oh my god i'm six joe
wow look at me speeding
[Music]
let's
go pretty good at this uh track
for some reason
[Music]
still decent
how did i not hit
[Music]
wait i'm not losing it i'm not quite
losing it oh thank you
[Music]
seventh joe let's go
oh oh
okay
um
next race last race and then we'll
upload it
we'll public publicize it how about that
next race last race and then video and
then super chat reading
next race
i want you guys to watch that video
together with me i want i actually
didn't see it yet
i i don't know how it turned out it will
be a surprise for me as well it's
already up no it's not
no it's not
well it's not
it looks really just checked
no it's not
eh you guys mean
it's not this
it's pasito i mean um
no it's not i don't see it
no it's not
are you guys talking about kelly's video
i'm talking about a different video
a video from from my side
huh
how do you guys know it i don't see it
on the channel either
what how do you guys know
huh
act as if you don't know you're not
supposed to see it yet what the [\h__\h]
when do some of you know
check twitter i can't keep on refreshing
i don't see it
huh i don't see that
i don't see it did he delete it again
why is it not here for me
huh is it unlisted
okay well
you need a lot more practice i know um
the the
tournament is like three weeks away
don't worry
also this is not a life or death
situation either
it's okay if i don't get number one like
it's impossible to get number one
oh this is the
this is the track where i said the thing
about putting a banana up up in your ass
remember the good times
the good old times
eat fire
oh my god five cha
go get
it potassium up your ass
a different way to phrase it
more
intel intelligently i learned the word
potassium from gouda by the way
i didn't even like i didn't know that
words were like yeah
thank you good after teaching me
i mean hey english is not my first
language okay
i don't know some of these difficult
words what the [\h__\h] happened here
[Music]
oh
look at me decently true
let's go just the last race make me
proud
make me proud
go make me proud make me proud myself
[Music]
oh yes yes yes yes yes
but we'll we'll not get tension this
time we're gonna be for joe at least
come on oh five job
oh six straw
oh god why am i so bad right now
come on key yes yes yes
yes
[Music]
what a nice sweet
we're gonna watch a nice video now that
you all haven't seen yet uh don't watch
it yet watch it together with me let's
do a countdown where is it where is it
dokodoko
i don't see it why do you guys see it on
twitter
i don't see it anywhere
there it is
four or six seconds ago okay okay okay
i'll give you guys a link don't don't
start it yet don't stop it immediately
here's the link
here okay it's it's pinned now
i will mute my desktop audio oopsie
um maybe however maybe i can show the
video on screen at least
[Music]
hey
or maybe maybe not maybe should we i
don't know
let me at least here put up a screenshot
that's easy too
sure okay
one second give me one second we're
almost there
all right korea
is
[Music]
okay
are you guys ready
it's it's
present to me originally it was supposed
to be my present to you guys but i
couldn't do it on my channel so it's
more like canada's present to me and kfp
okay ready
and
audio muted okay three two
one
go
oh crap oh yeah pizza
iris danger
oh she's that sick
go down with that scribble
a six
[Music]
that is a good ending
oh one more time one more time three two
one go
whoa oh nice flip bales let's look at
all the details
oh my the chicken drawing that i did in
the bag clap
what is that in the background behind
kelly
nice nice twerking
crony at the top
good ass drawing
oh then my drawing
six
and this is a sims reference yeah
um
i heard it's sloping i like how iris is
like ascending in the background
[Music]
oh one more one more three two one go
jingle bell jingle bell rock
look at that sexy dance moves
that was genuine in the background
jingle bells has been jingle rock has
begun
jingle bell jingle bell rock
cute
[Music]
what is that one kiana doing she's not
dancing properly
i love it
has kiana even seen
mean girls
no
[Laughter]
tweeted i can't find it it's in the
pinned comment it's in the pinned
comment um
i know this i know this clip and i know
the song and all that and and just like
two two or three days ago i i saw the
clip again
um uh of like you know the the movie of
them dancing along to the song and i was
like
that that was i saw it literally like a
moment before i saw the new christmas
outfits that i got for the wealthy model
and i was like so inspired like it it
perfectly matched i was like holy moly
holy moly
i want to do that dance
and i i i first was just gonna i was
like should i just do it like in the
like in
myself in the vr chat studio with a
green screen and then upload it that
simple but then i was like no
no it has to be has to be proper so i i
asked
[Music]
yeah this is a little bit of a christmas
present for you guys mean girls watch
long you know what i would love to do
that is is it christmas themed or is it
just that one scene that's kind of like
christmasy
cause uh if it's christmas themed we
could watch it as the members watch long
video
i don't know
just that one ah okay and let's watch it
after christmas after christmas i do
really um want to see it because once i
looked closer at the clip for the first
time
for the purpose of this video i saw so
many of uh like my favorite actors are
in that movie like someone who seems to
be the mom of one of the mean girls and
someone who seems to be the the dad of
one of the mean girls
um i i those two parents are uh some of
my favorite actors
um
yeah hell yeah
so i do i do want to watch it i'm
i'm i'm very curious
so thank you thank you canada for making
this video even though i couldn't upload
it on my channel but
maybe it's better this way please please
send kanoru some likes and some comments
and some appreciation for making this
even though it couldn't be on my channel
please please send him lots and lots and
lots of support i'm really really happy
it was it was still created um
please send him some support
please
i think he was already really really
busy and this i i had this idea what two
two days ago i came with this idea to
canada two days ago
and he was already working on other
things as far as i know so
big [\h__\h] respect for making it so
quickly and still implementing some
recent
i mean i mean it's probably good that he
made it so last minute because otherwise
the whole sims 4 joke couldn't be in
there and the three plus free joke
couldn't be in there either
right yeah
so i guess that's that's actually uh
the stars have aligned you know
the fire was just yesterday yeah
six it's six for god's sake
we don't wanna launch one more time one
more time one more time just one more
time can we watch it one more time can
we watch it in slow motion let's do it
let's do um
zero 0.5
okay
change it to 0.5 guys
thank you for the membership welcome
0.5
not two five five yes i want to watch it
slowly
okay three two one go
one mouse she goes look at me so cute
well for kiana so cute look at her
dancing
yeah
rocket girl
shake those hips
mmm i'm enjoying it
is that even a functional camera
yeah that's christmas ball ah now i get
that
no what is she doing what what is that
one kiana doing she's been [\h__\h]
around the whole time
oh my god i just noticed that huge
chicken in the background
she's doing her own thing man
cute
how did you do that how did you add that
onto her
and friends thank you
seeing you three plus three six
in the frosty oh [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
i love it i love it
i love it thank you
why did iris burn the tree you need to
watch my sims 4 stream from two days ago
oh
that was that was amazing
please watch this please watch this
everybody please watch it give it
support i need to do let me do a
community post here um
you wish you'll
let's make a community post
originally wanted this on
my channel but couldn't so
here it is please
watch
it
and
support
bye commenting
and
merry
christmas
that goes
merry christmas
[Music]
almost
i already feel the christmas is there a
tweet that i can retweet
perhaps
let me see
is there a tweet yes there is
wait wait wait wait and quote retweet
look
merry
christmas
yeah
with the model from seafoam boy of
course i'm so glad seafoam boy made that
um
made that christmas uh santa because
otherwise this wouldn't have been
created
i switched between english and japanese
keyboard while i was writing them
feliz navidad
[Music]
oh yeah
okay so now we'll read some super chats
um
i i can spend
one and a half hours more with you and
then i have to go because uh
someone's coming by to help me with
something
that i have been struggling with
and then and then yeah uh i won't be
streaming tomorrow
uh i'll be streaming the day after
tomorrow on the 25th for a members only
stream that's the next time you will see
me and then on sunday we'll have a big
christmas karaoke stream unarchived and
archive please watch both of them and
i'm trying to make it happen in
the vr chat in wealthy style so
hopefully we can make that happen please
i hope everyone will be there and the
tree isn't over i don't know what you're
talking about oh exciting
exciting so let's let's move over to my
office
oh
okay i need to fix the chat as always
thank you guys for playing mario kart
with me today sorry dad uh
i kind of um
messed up in the beginning but i still
had a lot of fun today with you guys
so we had a lot of fun playing mario
kart getting back into it
now that i have
um you know a feeling for the wheel
again i think uh after a little bit of
practice we could be rather decent yes i
i want to make
uh at least a little bit of a of an
impression a positive impression
um have you decided on the movie i
haven't yet sorry i've been like so busy
with other things like i woke up
tomorrow
this morning and i had uh 11 mentions
on our discord there's really a lot
going on at the moment um i will choose
it uh uh
a asap
i know there have been a lot of
suggestions in the community board and i
have to go through them
but well watch a nice movie together
yes
die hard
die hard is is that a christmas movie
10 minutes before watch along no no no
no no no no no way no no no
okay so we are going to
read some chats from
a few more from ya ya i think
and then from this stream
yes yes
[Music]
so okay
okay here's some
uh
christmas lo-fi again
let's get low
let's get low let's get low
it is the christmas movie
die hard
die hard is the christmas movie
steve langsam
how is that
how is that the christmas movie it
doesn't look like christmas at all
[Music]
it's not a christmas movie
it plays on christmas oh come on no i
want something that's actually
christmasy we can once that another time
okay okay
um
yum yum yum business thank you soon
already had it open
viable monkey duncan five tubes of boost
thank you if we have time at the end we
can already choose it maybe
or i will choose it in the evening time
it's a mystery danke shin missed this
danke soon small navi thank you
thank you for the red
[Music]
i don't know if you know this guys but
like i tried to
have um
fans of mine
participate in the creation of my song
covers
like for the art or for the music for
the logo creation or for all these kind
of things
um
yeah
last time it was uh chiomaru-san
who also
was a fan of mine for a long time and i
wanted to use her beautiful art
eventually
yeah it's great to have amazing creators
in my fan community and then be able to
hire them and give something back and
yeah
yeah mama you know
all these people
[Music]
yeah and i think like i mean it also
makes me feel safer because like they
obviously will accept the offer
of working with me there's no
chance that they would decline
and and it also
um
gives me an assured feeling of they know
how to
draw me or how to
how to say how to make me look um
or for akashivasando
some of the animations he had to come up
with himself uh others i fought up uh
but but some of them since he
came up with himself um i think he
captured me and ina very well because he
also watches our streams properly i mean
at least mine i don't know if he watches
in a stream but he does watch my streams
very often
yes
pk's garfield video uh it's not a music
video but
it's also again a time where i
used a fan's work to
include it in one of my creations
yes portrayed they know how to portray
and illustrate me takanashikiyada and i
really appreciate that akashibasan
[Music]
um
and that means die hard is a christmas
movie
that makes no sense black friction
looking for the tough dankest and dave m
plays dante's an old hunter arrow duncan
um
as someone who is 30 been to the psych
ward for suicidal ideations
as a kid been struggling socially all
alone since the pandemic and now takes
anti-anti-psychotics
these kinds of songs feed my soul thank
you kiana and ina for putting people
like me in a positive spotlight
well you you're welcome
i hope however that it also kind of
helps you with some motivation i mean
the song is not the most
motivational song but
that sounds like you've been for a lot
of tough [\h__\h]
yeah
i'm sorry about that i'm sorry that life
hasn't been very nice to you
even though it should be
[Music]
but
i pray that you will eventually be
rewarded for all the [\h__\h] you've gone
through
i've been rewarded too
eventually
we all should be rewarded and i really
hope that that will happen to you as
well
in the meantime
watch whole live streams and get some
happiness from us
we do what we can
yeah thank you inside the person wow
let me give you a hug though you deserve
a hug
you deserve a hug oh where is my
where's my baby
where's my chicken
where is it where is it
uh
uh i can't find it
where is my chimpkin
where is it
uh
[Music]
i hear this
let me mark it as something set color
pink
okay come here inside a person
hey let me hold you gently
okay
looking for the top thank you thank you
oh pre-debut art
i didn't lose it i found it again the
other day but now i again don't know
where it is i could find it probably
small navidan dave employees thank you
and mysteries and dave and planes
cy free q i danke shin
uh kirito av is duncan
aka madras dankesh and lunar telparion
dancing
random channel dankeshung kaiser dan
kitchen
[Music]
tantra there's no skipping out on race
day if the kfp pit crew has to show up
so do you
yes yes don't worry i
i am participating even though it's a
really really bad time this was the one
that i was talking about that i was
originally thinking of skipping but then
i saw all of the other whole live
english members are participating and i
didn't want to be the only one not
participating so here i
am but at least i'm in group d so that
could mean that i can get up a little
bit later
um
yeah at least something um but i think
and of course it will be fun
uh so
yeah
i'll just have to make sure that i have
some time to
go back to a second sleep afterwards
eric neustrom duncan epic frost thank
you and huckle
i randomly woke up at 6am and tuned into
coyote's stream right when you were
calling in which is the second time that
has happened to me this week
nice sue
what a good timing you have it's like
you have some kind of
special connection with me you feel it
you feel it in your veins it tells you
to wake up and find me
find wherever i am and which stream
wherever he had a sensor
a chicken sense
[Music]
crow kenti tankishan
colonel kotori
oh my god
zombie thank you so much
[Music]
1846 six duncan arch ellen duncan
feather pinky
i just watched your new cover it is
amazing the art is so cute and your your
and inna's voice fit well together also
the drawings are both super cute if it's
easier for you to cook without the
camera then go for it as long as we get
a photo of the result no no no no no no
no i do want to do it with a camera i
i'll try my best to set it up properly
when i got some time i think next week
in the first couple of
um days like monday tuesday wednesday
i'll have some time
um
about the schedule for next week i might
not put it up immediately on monday i
will have to see how how it goes or i'll
put it up and leave some days open for
gorillas
yes because i'm not sure how next week
will go
um
also um about the marathon plan so i am
definitely planning to stream but i'm
not sure if i'm actually gonna do like a
super long marathon because um
i
saw you know obviously the other girls
are gonna do some stuff too
and um
uh i don't wanna like
overlap too much with with all of them
you know and also i do on the 31st my
time zone at 8 00 am
um yes 8 am i have
a
a stream on a different channel more
information will come soon
um
and that one will go
fairly long as well perhaps wait the
stream might not start at 8am maybe it's
just the standby at 8am i don't know
um but that will occupy me for a couple
of hours and i reckon that i will need a
nap after that as well
so i can't start my marathon too early
either yeah i'm not sure
how
how that day will work out i will need
to
figure it out as we go perhaps
yes another early one another early one
but i did not
under any circumstance once wanted to
turn that one down and 8 am is decent if
i managed to sleep a little bit early
then it's manageable could get at least
five hours of sleep maybe
it's almost a.m right now you stayed up
for me thank you
it must be worth it then it will be
[Music]
yeah i might not do like a proper
marathon maybe just like five hours and
then you know have five countdowns
something like that
five countdowns already enough
[Music]
and we'll do we could do sims we could
do drawing we could do q a we could do a
little bit of a singing stream as well
we could mix it all together we could do
some minecraft we haven't we've barely
played minecraft these days
um
yeah because i see some other girls are
planning to do some kind of marathon as
well
um
at least i see one other person doing a
marathon
and
some other girls doing just like normal
streams as well and i don't
i don't want to overlap too much you
know
yes
i know
[Music]
why not happen to voice chat with the
other girls uh
i don't know
not i don't know they can hop into my
voice chat if they want to
maybe
maybe we can do that
um anyway uh mundo thank you put down
your leg and sit
okay
how did you know that i have my legs off
thank you
extra light
barrack duncan
and wait there's a
name that i cannot read
[Music]
thank you
because i always do or don't call me out
like that
every other
[Music]
[\h__\h]
we're done with these we are at the
current stream
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
still cute i used inna's art
all according to k kaku
inna's art
taskaroo
[Music]
which chimpkins will watch you no matter
what you do whatever is comfortable for
you as long as kiwawa is having fun and
feels good we chimpkins are totally fine
we love you okay
thank you i
i normally understand that perfectly
fine but you know gingerbread stream i
thought that you guys looked forward to
it
as well a lot
um
so it must have been a little bit over
disappointing but it's okay it's not
completely canceled we'll bring it back
eventually
and who knows maybe i can get my mom to
help me
wait a second i actually
[Music]
rachel
i'll i'll ask her
[Music]
oh no
wait no shut up windows
shut up
uh well thank you for
feeling leave and dunk um
yeah it's my seat spicy
i know you guys i know you guys are very
supportive um
at least i didn't cancel the stream
completely and and and just took the day
off i wanted to spend some time with you
guys before christmas because i'm taking
christmas off
but
yeah thank you for being so
understanding everybody for thanksgiving
christian
pakistan
what's in thank you for the pinkie
i returned now oh you're back from your
break i'm back before christmas i want
to go back to work at kfp is there a
seat
of course welcome back what's aim anyone
on your and thank you for coming back
and not forgetting about me you're
always welcome at kfp honestly it's uh
you should be
going straight to the usual room for
leaving to begin with because that's not
really an option for all the other
chimpkins but okay just this once i
forgive you because you always said you
were gonna come back
[Music]
but don't tell the others because
they're gonna ask for a vacation too
and i can't have that
and have that happen
thank you
[Music]
now i am refreshing
no no no no no no no see that's what i
said no vacation days no no
i really love your clips by the way i
watched the sims uh four clip
today
and it was so funny the way you edited
it
i even left a hahahahaha comment in in
korean
i hope that was really haha i just
copied it from other people
[Music]
you guys need to watch these korean
clips they're they're so well edited
loves in korean
[Music]
big kusa
oh sh
magi
i love your clips
you know you know which things to clip
too you have a good feeling for it
katie danke soon hi from japan hello
[Music]
that made me think that you were gonna
leave me forever
don't do that again okay you broke my
heart for a second
i don't know how to deal with that on
stream don't you dare do that to me
again
can't be rebel chicken duncan russell
bucket thank you with a follow-up pinky
to
say it was a joke see you on the track
in exactly one hour okay see now you
deserve a kissy because you sent two
pinkies
thank you i was very relieved
maxi king nine two donkey shoe and
deeply one two three four thank you
bryce iverson
happy birthday
kara hi today is my birthday it has also
been almost a year since i discovered
holo ian and you were my first oh
oh
i was your first thanks for holding
entertainment and guiding me down the
rabbit hole much love you're welcome
i hope you still actively watched my
streams though and didn't go somewhere
else
after all i am the reason you came here
to begin with
huh
you better be coming here on a regular
basis yo
got my eyes on
you and my spies got their eyes on you
as well
hashtag will catch that yolk exactly
and but happy birthday mmm stay healthy
and merry christmas as well yeah
[Music]
bryce iverson viva
sanguini foreign
[Music]
merry christmas is my first super chat
potential i was a quiet type of audience
and normally can't catch your stream
because it's too late for me
yeah you're a sea gang but i love your
new cover with ina awesome singing
amazing and cute animation thank you
thank you very much i'm glad you like it
don't worry about it it's totally on me
for streaming at shitty times for you
guys but today today was supposed to be
for you guys so i'm glad you were able
to come
merry christmas to you too
okonomi thank you black friday
seventeen b-42 duncan
[Music]
on the eighth day of christmas tantra
sent to me
eight inna's milking seven only
screaming six shoe buns laying five
five council beings
four hollow burps three money chance two
in the pear tree
merry christmas thank you
original lyrics hair thank you very much
time to document angel thank you for the
red super chat
i appreciate the competitive spirit
tension rather than racing npcs playing
against ghosts might help you better
improve ah
general handling and course navigation
once you have those down the rest is
just improvising
yeah yeah i did see like in the
preparation for the iden tournament
or enid tournament i saw some of the
girls were practicing with ghost races i
guess so that is true
not a huddle
i might get into that then
[Music]
if you guys have some advices feel free
to send them to me on twitter whenever
thank you angel mwah kiss for you please
uh pray for me that i get somewhat of a
decent
placement
in the tournament
harvard line thank you so much
[Music]
oh you joined the race thank you yes i
did see you
don't worry i'm i'm glad you got last
because then i wasn't last
[Music]
you draco
the link uh
drifter
nice thank you
wrestle bucket thank you for the pinky
okay an hour's passed time to enter what
were you doing were you waiting for the
right moment
thank you for joining the race today i'm
always surprised that there are so many
people
uh who are ready to play the game with
me at any given time thank you everybody
i hope you had fun
i hope i think you'll be better at
drifting with a car i can suggest you
some setup very handy and fast on track
oh well actually
another um
setup that i wanted to use is not
available right now because i don't have
the card yet but i'll try to get it
[Music]
let her fly thank you so she don't
dance
on thank you
thank you very much
[Music]
tomorrow is my birthday and you already
know us chimkin's gotta share some
birthday money with you before we get
beat up anyways thanks for everything
you do for us at kfp and wow the jingle
bells do be rocking huh
oh wait is that a reference to the new
video
i think it is
[Music]
thank you thank you i hope you all liked
that little video
some people also suspected that it would
be padoru padoru
um but no
i was really inspired when i when i was
reminded of that mean girl's clip so it
had to be that
four kianas dancing four kiaras dancing
[Music]
but
i will sing it for you if you want
um
[Music]
thank you
thank you everybody thank you so much
that was my rendition of
you're welcome to use it and make
something out of it
um
[Music]
wonder is that a meme in japan as well
or
only outside of japan
all right i will i'm looking forward to
it
um
thank you spx is the case
i know it's from fate but it i feel like
it's only a meme outside of japan
[Music]
spidey duncan
oh thank you
oh thank you black preaching donation
for the pinky
if cats is a good movie then that means
die hard is a christmas movie those are
the rules
that makes no sense as i already said
that makes absolutely no sense
no no the logic is off
alex's song
[Music]
there's something i want to say to kiara
i don't know if you can uh understand
let google translate read this in korean
oh that sounds suspicious
[Music]
what is that
is that safe too
what does that mean
i feel like maybe that's is that your
thing
[Music]
hello here if you want us to check
unbelievable teaching control
[Music]
huh
was i suppose supposed to hear something
english out of that
body health body
body what does it mean
what does it mean
popcorn
[Music]
hello kiaha young couple and task wigs
on you love thai
[Music]
whereas german
is this something bad
even in german i don't understand what
are these words what are these words
[Music]
okay i do not understand
thank you though hokan danger i'm not
going to read your name like that
anymore
jim tracy thank you merry christmas
jean-paul danke
fried school duncan feliz navidad
refresh maybe last time
maybe maybe maybe not
uh
great human duncan
wait what's uh what's merry christmas in
korean
[Music]
it's the same as in japanese tilde
oh i guess i could have guessed that
[Music]
in one we have our own way of saying it
wiki dpr thank you and dragon fire thank
you for the red super chat
merry christmas kiana thank you for
giving kfp the greatest gift we could
ask for time with you
oh
any time
i love you guys thank you
merry christmas dragons fire i hope you
have lovely holidays
great food some time with your family or
with friends or with anyone really
thank you for spending time with me for
spending your precious
important
special time
with me
very often too
thank you i appreciate all the support
and your generosity
[Music]
for
merry christmas kiana i hope you'll have
a great time with your family also thank
you for your efforts in providing us
with all the good stuff i really take in
the christmas spirit on your streams
although i celebrated in january it's
like having two christmases
oh in january
why in january
who celebrates christmas in january
in in egypt it's also celebrated 7th
january oh
this one was russian though
oh
orthodox oh egypt in russia
[Music]
so you celebrated twice that's cool oh
my god i wish i could celebrate
christmas twice
what
what that's so cool
let me join in on the fun
[Music]
sun
russia
[Music]
i wish you happy holidays
and stay healthy
and please
enjoy a lovely christmas and a good
watch
we're not there yet but i like to say
that in german
uh we always say
uh foreign
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you
skye thank you for the red super chat
potential because i have a working shift
on the member stream day no so allow me
give you an early merry christmas now oh
keanu you give me so many joy this year
and i meet lots of great kfp employees
all of you are wonderful foreign
oh that's sad that you can't be there
but
[Music]
oh it's supposed to be in german oh i'll
try to read it again in german then
thank you skye i wish you merry
christmas happy holidays
please
um i hope that your day at work will be
somewhat
uh bearable
i will be thinking of you while watching
the movie then with my members um we
will not forget about you skye thank you
so much for supporting me all this time
thank you
[Music]
merry christmas
material girl in the um
[Music]
please remove me why would i it's been
there so long now it's kind of a long
stay
huh okay let me go there
yeah for some reason in my minecraft
playlist i accidentally added madonna's
material girl before there it is
okay i'll delete it why
[Music]
it's
it should be gone now i think
it's a great song yeah
doctor
[Music]
i really need to go to an idol meeting
but i'll sit this one out until the end
uh
blackfish induction hataman crony's
footrest duncaschen
[Music]
what is this
i don't know if i should read that
sorry
i don't know
how large
merry christmas huddle one three seven
five thank you soon del stardon
david thank you shane thank you
oh god i really need to go to bed
[Music]
in russia so you also celebrate it two
times or only one time in january i wish
you happy holidays oh thank you for your
support for zach always
[Music]
fourteen uh uh fourteen i think thank
you
i'm done i'm done i think i'm done i'm
freaking done okay okay i think i'm done
i understand everybody uh oh my god oh
my god um
[Music]
thank you guys for
celebrating uh letting me celebrate and
thank you guys for spending a second
christmas with me it's nice to to still
be around and still have you guys around
nice to see familiar faces um
and uh please i will have you know thank
you patrician i will have you know that
i will that i love you all very very
dearly you guys are my christmas present
yes i love you guys thank you for all
the support you give me thank you for
being so caring and so forgiving always
now maybe
since i'm not there for christmas maybe
on christmas you can
uh share and spread the love in in real
life somewhere
yeah to people who who need it more than
me anyway
since i'm not here for christmas
yeah
um
thank you for being you guys
you're all lovely you all deserve lots
and lots of love and presents for
christmas i hope santa is nice to you
guys i hope santa doesn't burn your tree
um
christmas
[Music]
um
oh man no they i thought it was done i'm
gonna read those um
next time then
i was finishing off here nicely
um
so um there might still be something
coming up on maybe on the 25th
uh you know the thing with d more hollis
uh if if i get to it then i
might maybe upload it on the 25th i'm
kind of busy on the 24th
uh
well yeah that one's still gonna be up
eventually
um yeah sad spikes indeed
[Music]
um yeah well i would spend new year's
eve with you guys if you would like to
spend new year's eve with me as well
mark your calendars you know when new
year's eve is right merry christmas
thank you santa maria thank you
my favorite whole live original
[Music]
thank you everybody
thank you thank you for the membership
welcome
you're just in time for the members only
movie watching long then
um i will go decorate my apartment now
and clean my apartment let's go
[Music]
wow the year is ending
it is real it is happening oh my mom
wrote me on discord
[Music]
what is she sent me a link
from some youtube video mommy if you're
watching right now
do you think you can help me on the 25th
before you leave to
make some
uh lip cuchen take i have all the
ingredients and i have a
kitchen aid machine
maybe you can help me mommy yoda school
i needed for a stream
yes i really need to go to the idol
meeting too
[Music]
oh she's typing
mama please help
ah what members movie okay no i can't
decide right now i'm at you i'm too
stressed out because of the idle meeting
oh
[Music]
okay
now
everybody
[Music]
what's up thank you
i'm so sad i don't want to leave i feel
like
this is kind of sad
play sad sparks alexa play sad sparks
please
[Music]
bye bye everybody oh
mommy said to wait
[Music]
does mommy have something to say to you
guys
[Music]
ah
merry christmas from my mommy as well
[Music]
[Laughter]
merry christmas
from the the takanashi family i guess
bye bye
[Music]
look it's snowing white christmas yay
bye bye
bye
forest fest
we'll celebrate everybody
bye bye
[Music]
you all have been good little chickens
thank you for supporting takanasi kiana
old is here
she really really appreciates it
thank you
but you know what you have to do ho ho
ho
you have to continue
being a loyal chicken ho ho ho ho
hashtag whoa ho ho hulk and yoho
[Music]
oh man