[Music]
oh
for
[Music]
Yum Yum
Yum Yum Yum
Yum
[Music]
k
hello
hello what
up wow pretty game
hello everyone it's the first
[Music]
December you know what that
means everyone can open the first door
of their Advent Advent calendar which I
did and I got um I have a lint calendar
I don't know about you guys but I got a
lint chocolate
Calender and um out of my first door I
got a little chocolate bear I didn't eat
it yet it's in front of me I'm holding
it yes so let's eat the chocolate bear
chocolate bear I'm going to decapitate
you yay
yay it's um empty inside Holo Holo
[Music]
bear
M good chocolate m m
M I should buy one as well what it's
still the 1st of December
so they I think they still sell it like
even a while after the 1st of December
has
[Music]
passed chocolate bear isn't that what um
JD calls Turk and scrubs
[Laughter]
mhm I think he does sometimes
yeah
M now J's vanilla
bear one of the best shows ever
scrubs yum yum
that was
good my dentist will be so proud of
me for eating chocolate after my dentist
appointment all right so we're back to
or in the blind
Forest I feel like we're going to have
more issues today done before but at
least I am going into it uh with a
little bit more of a fresh uh memory
which means that I might not be as
frustrated as I was before but also I
will probably have forgotten their
[Laughter]
controls but you know what I've have
decided for
myself um if today doesn't go well and
by the way I'm not playing on finishing
it today I wasn't seeing it that as a
realistic option if today doesn't go
well I'm not going to force myself to
play it any longer uh uh or finish it
that will just be well I will I will
drop it then which is okay I'm allowed
to drop games sometimes if I'm not so
good at the genre or I don't enjoy it
that much not not saying that the game
is bad or anything it's just that I I
suck at uh Metroid Vania games as we've
seen but but I'll give it another
try and if we drop it we drop it no hard
feelings M
yes so I uh even if we don't drop it I'm
only planning this one to be a short
short
session as in maximum 3 hours es
especially if it doesn't go
well um so that I don't push myself too
hard and pressure myself too much uh
yeah the gaming portion I I'm not going
to play longer than 3 hours maybe even
less who knows who knows how it
goes
[Music]
yeah only time will tell yes so we are
going back into the Gino
tree difficulty
easy as last
time so let's go into this beautiful
sunset let's dive into it
again how do I play this uh where am I
I'm here okay um okay a is this menu
jump is b double
jump this is is the attack
thingy what was what was
that what's that jump what's
X I can do a flip I don't remember using
that that's
bash what I don't know how to use
it
what what was
that
I don't know how to use
it what to catch ah H uh B use right
before being hit or near an enemy B use
projectile it's a it's a jumpy thing
that they Tau us last time at the very
end okay well uh let's kill that thing
are we going up or down
here uh I think I think we're going down
right are we going down where how map uh
no map is uh here that's that's the map
oh no we're going up I guess that makes
sense yeah if we look at the map we're
only going this looks like jump
[Laughter]
King ah okay oh God I I don't
remember how do I O O Okay jump up the
trees oops uh how does one save again uh
with this okay I wasted something right
there oh God damn it um and
then ah ah uh the other way around
though no I no this is correct
okay oh okay so we did
Dad okay
okay God no I remember this uh so I was
struggling here I wanted this one to
catch that one oh no
wait no what am I done
here what am I doing with
[Music]
you
can't catch me I am it can't catch
me starting off great just need to get
used to it again just need to get back
into
it
ow well starting off fresh again it's a
good thing what you can bash off the I
right
out hit me
I need another one
please okay so apparently I can use oh
[Music]
yeah I can use the lamp I want to try
that can I can I do it h i want to try
if I'm like already being projected at
the very
moment if I can immediately jump into
the next one
but either I just did it wrong or it's
not possible you know what I mean like
when something projects you and then you
want to reach the next thing that could
project you I can oh okay I'm going to
try it out a bit
more hold on hold
on should be possible right okay okay
we're already progressed guys oh and
there's a there's a thingy over there
how
ooh is this literally asking for what I
just
explained in order like if I don't want
to get
hit I should I should sa yeah I can't I
can't looks like it because I have to go
to the left and then I have have to go
up without touching the ground or the
wall on the left I
thinking that's
no we're having a problem with safe
points here I can't
save hit me come on faster don't want to
waste my
time
[Music]
I wanted to project myself into the
earlier but it didn't work so I got I
fell back down and I hit
myself I'm using the controller mhm you
can save no I I can't I can't it has to
be a full blue
circle see I can't
I don't know many things about this game
but this is what I do know I cannot save
what Super
Chat what's with
that good
news you got a new job yo let's go wait
does that mean you're not coming to my
streams
anymore you're not saying anything like
that it looks like
so okay
H we have enough Health to kind of
somehow survive this I think
uh oh
no I'm trying to once I get projected
out of that I'm trying to like jump
again to stay in the air but it's not
working I fall on the ground and then
I'm
y
wait go away I wish I could shoot
those would make my life easier
go upward first oh
okay the
okay go up first don't go straight
to keep this
okay get secret to the left then you can
save okay uh up up up
ah
here okay
okay where was the secret did I miss
something there was only a teleporting
portal what no
no I want to double
jump oh look actually I wanted to
project
myself go here again oh okay oh okay
okay interesting n
[Music]
n
uh oh I didn't get them
[Music]
allo I'm missing one I know which one
now how can I catch that without
dying also why is that secret that you
guys
said I don't I don't know where that
is I project myself right into my own
death that's so
tricky
huh I I will try
I will not let this take me down or
anything let's
go so at first anyway I
guess why you shoot me so
[Laughter]
far fall then double jump okay I'll do
that on my way back I'll I'll
try oh
no Get It Go Get
It Before I was able to reach
it I'm out of
here you know what I'm going to try to
get this one first after all
because it doesn't matter if I catch all
of them at the top which are somewhat
easier if I can't catch this
one no no
uh okay you know what I survived so we
we're
good that always freaks me out because
I'm so scared to jump too far because
it's so easy when there's barely a
platform
here to rest on
I only have one Health
left uh let's go
herei and it kind of pisses me off that
I have to keep on redoing this
here
okay what the hell was
that I want to redo it kill me
I need more Health to go for that
secret is down to the left where you
trapped before it's
an down
here don't to the
left it's really difficult to
describe to me where I need to go
because of the crazy
map up by the tentacle a
here
here oh wait at least I get some
help here
no at least I get some help
ha oh maybe
here
no
ah leave me
alone that floor if the monster Hits a
this one ah oh yeah right that's okay so
the one thing that I tried before at the
end of the last stream and I couldn't
get it right maybe I no I can't do
wait o
o you can go so far with that I'm here
not up there where are you looking
at uh oh no it was the other way
around uh so
no oh this will take a while is this
even worth
it I mean I can save yeah but I'm going
to lose all my health ah
[Music]
close I was supposed to get that
one
hey the angle how the hell are you
supposed to shoot that
one
higher oh this is a good
angle this is
good ah finally for
sake I hate metr Vania games so much
already
this
it I'm already angry I'm already
[Music]
angry no you're not going to hit me with
that no hell
no next
one what do you want what do you want
what is
this die am I trying to kill it with its
own
projectile I is that what I'm
doing
okay just the for the P okay byebye oh
oh that thing Hallelujah ah it's just to
go back up maybe I don't know I don't
know why that thing is there
oh hi I'm out of here
sucker okay W
Hallelujah
save that
time okay step by
step step by step so now we go
up and
then we could try to let us hold
on that's not going to work
but it's okay we have a safe
spot I don't want to set safe with so
little
Health oh oh
let me do it again let me do it
again please fall slower that's like
telling someone to wait
faster like how can I
I understand you want me to double jump
blah blah blah but uh the the the fact
that you're telling me to fall slower
that's impossible because you only fall
at one speed in this
game let's be real here okay don't tell
me to do things that are
impossible I don't trust myself with
that one how about wait how about to
wait the if
I
ah do they want me
to oh wait we could jump we could save
here again don't want to waste too many
safes and run out of them again though
but what if I yeah you know what that
was so unnecessary
um what if
I uh what sorry my my actual I can only
read the chat right now in OBS and
there's not so much space to read long
sentences because my real chat is broken
again jump pickup sorry
what so
[Music]
what can you say that
again can you say it's
[Laughter]
slower hell I'm going to fix my
chat I have to reload
it sometimes it fixes it on its own but
it takes it takes way too much time I
don't know why there that only started
like maybe one or two months ago one
month ago I would say and I'm having
this issue every freaking day and I
don't don't know I really don't know
why deleting cash and whatever it didn't
work so please do not tell me to do
that just YouTube being slow as
hell okay
wait wait save your advice guys I don't
have the chat open right
now can't read
it wait
okay St okay I'm back uh so okay now my
question is do they want me to
jump up to the projectile then project
myself or do they want me to jump down
and then jump back up up I don't know
man now I can see the chat jump to the
first key double jump to the Lantern and
Bash away which one the upper one or the
right one I guess the right one cuz I
can't jump that high for it to catch me
back again okay jump down to the key
jump again try to get to the right
Lantern I
guess why why do you need to get so
close to
it it's okay
one
more kill
me okay I can do the jumble jump I just
need to aim better for the yeah yeah
yeah yeah
yeah
the
range I know what I'm doing now
just oh
yes should I
save cuz that one feels like the most
difficult
one going to
save
okay
I'm coming back to you later oh oh oh
one more one
more straight
up
no kill
me hold hold hold we're going to get
this one right don't worry about
it
uh no no
get ready put a
jump oh
yes why did you miss
it
oh
W
oh okay well I got a little bit of a
damage but that that's okay
M I'm not going to save again I don't
want to waste them all okay now we can
focus and going
up uh oh I didn't think I would
make that
[Music]
jump
one I should say what do I want to save
with one
heart there's the the thing
is yeah
baby I saw
that
no wait is it back if I
no
okay no damage
run
yes
Hallelujah the gates To Hell have once
again opened for
me
D oh
man oh what is this are we at the
boss or at the goal was I so
close it looks like something but maybe
it's
not
no what who am I
fighting this is not going well why
would you save there huh
okay what how do we fight this
thing uh like what what what
what oh I use his projectiles to hit him
rather than me myself okay oh it
but won't I won't I hit myself by
falling back
ah
uh
I don't know if I can do
that I don't want to shoot myself on the
ground climb the
wall ah you mean okay H that's what oh
and then
ah
ah wow smart
this
oh
what wait no I want
that
what
what that
was easy Once I knew the strategy of
going to the wall going up there oh
thank you not
a wait do these things what are those
again they save right they save without
me wasting my blue
energy and warp
okay
o wait I forgot how
to sometimes you just forget the things
you've been doing seconds
ago oh
okay oh what's
that the heart of the K tree Once kept
the element of water safe but now it's
corrupted all foul and
decayed scly
[Laughter]
speaking you have to help it cure it and
cleans it all the bl by removing the
correction on both of the
sides oh not a hold so the tree has some
kind of virus that we got to get rid of
where do we start
though oh no more of these
projectiles ah what are you how do I
fight you again oh never
[Laughter]
mind uh
uh how do I get that over there
M first of all get up
here oh wait oh
oh stupid frog monkey
again I guess I just got to do
retreat
no what launch enemies close to are you
right oh is that what that enemy is
there for to begin with
anyway kill
me these giv so much
damage
[Music]
take
excuse me I'm going to save up there
because I don't want to do this again
and
again
okay oh you're going to tell me that
again no need for
that imagine the damage I do on normal
or yeah even difficult yeah
sounds
crazy sounds very very
frustrating so uh how
no leave me alone leave me
alone I'll go up
here yeah I don't know how to I don't
know where to use him
though how what position I want him to
be but I don't need it what the
just
happened
what why did it die what happened n you
got that also I have a I have a skill
tree thingy
uh I forgot how to open
it wasn't this
one wasn't this one how do I open it
again was it I thought it was I thought
it was one of these
buttons
before leave and reenter why
need to use the safe one
oh oh
oh okay so I think I was saving for
something right this one was I air Dash
requires two ability
points sh doesn't work oh if you
don't have the dash I don't have the
dash yet
but apparently I do want it
so but this this this is this will be
the dash right
now I
suppose but now I got these back
again
no see what I don't get back is my
ability points that's
sad no get out of here get out of here
oh get out out of here oh
oh oh
frog k
k go home frog it's a it's a pun in
Japanese
K going
toaa
Ori is
mad oh did I need the fck to destroy
that maybe I'll find something else you
perhaps
uh they fell me stalker
frogs get out of here
no get me those free speed hell
yeah they scam me they're so
aggressive at least these projectiles
they don't leave anything on the
ground no
no
no I'm so sorry
guys you can Farm ability points here I
guess so
but do I want to spend my time doing
that no not
really okay uh wait
so oh no ah you come out of nowhere
you little
kill me kill me kill
me wait when you
die even when I die the ability points
that I saved within those save
files am I keeping them
spam bash again and again
when okay okay what what
now why do I jump into
you leave me alone leave me alone leave
me alone actually I do need the frog for
this oh but can
you n how do I make this thing work
maybe later I'll get a chance to do
that
can use the spider on the
[Music]
left
it but doesn't it it doesn't shoot that
far does it oh maybe it
does I work
yo when you got to aim and you don't
even see the target that's real gamer
skills
yo
W not
nice A little bit of the corruption has
been removed successfully and you guys
are back
again
nice can't reach me do I still need you
for
something probably not am I done
here
nice oh there's so
many I want that stuff over there thank
you okay let's go to the other
side let's see maybe it's similar also
should I save again I'll save
again what do we have here same
principle
no
n use this to
go I don't know I don't know I don't
know what I'm
doing what are we what are we doing
where am I
going
that hurts mhm this one's tricky this
one's hard observe and
think I want to land on that it must be
possible just need that fine spiten
fer fine in spit
f ah I probably want that one alive huh
or do I
do I need
it okay so far so
good oh
wait oh no it ah I got to use those
things oh
no come on shoot something then let me
catch
it wait I
can't trying
here nice landing
though I can't use the small ones Oh I
thought I need to shoot them through to
the to these
tubes cuz obviously they're going to ah
but I just got to shoot the the lower
one through it uhhuh I see okay okay
okay
okay oh
no
oh ah too
early
no
[Laughter]
to okay
so here and then this way
almost did I figure it out this is the
second hardest part of this area hey
will you not shoot another one until the
other one hit
something y
oh and do I have to follow
it oh yes I do have to follow it oh dear
that's going to take a lot of tries I
think
nope okay come come
on
uh even had some time to drink some
orange juice
oh I need some more time to choose a
Direction please it confuses me because
you know the arrow I think your brain
will automatically try the logic logical
thing and let the arrow go into the
Direction you want to shoot whatever
you're shooting but you got to think the
opposite way you know that's
difficult it's
contradicting
just aim straight upwards come
[Music]
on yes oh
god oh
uh uh sh oh no it wasn't good enough
okay but this is fun this is actually
fun because right now I'm not even
getting disturbed by
enemies that
worked oh God but then ah I didn't
work
uh where do we go where do we
go so quickly
oh okay okay okay I know where to go
now it's time it's there's an enemy in
the way now it's not in the
way anymore
let's go
no I got this down guys look at this Pro
Gamer
uh
H wait wait no oh
[Music]
ah oh but if the enemy will be in the
way and they respawn until I'm back up
there I will even have to kill it with
my zip
up yeah that that's that's the only
choice I
have and because the enemy will come
back from at least from my experience up
until now maybe not because but the one
the left it respawns so quickly the one
here over there
there maybe it won't
respawn
okay
uh wait wait okay and then and then y y
no no one more okay
but I need to figure out anyway where to
go from there from there I will have to
go go back up
here follow it take this lamp get back
here and then shoot it up
okay okay I
understand no the thing is back
okay now we can
talk go here
I go there oh will the snail be back
again on the top one as
well
[Music]
no
here
Ash that was apparently forgivable ah
it's back
you I got some bles to
be I did wait where do you go from there
where do you go from
there don't tell me that from here on
I'll have to catch it here in the air
and then let it let it project itself
downwards no
wait no wait did that just what did that
do did it open me a
path I'm not sure what that P was I able
to come here
anyway I opened it but why was it open
already oh maybe one time how is that
how is that possible how did I already
project it up here to open something
[Laughter]
up okay good for me I guess um so now
what do we do
now oh no
what are we
doing last stream no no no I didn't get
here last stream uh this is the part
hardest part now okay can I even get
back up here I think I
can I have to shoot
this drop okay
okay oh signs
now we can restore the element of waters
with this one rekindled there's two more
to
go oh
oh
this part of the game really game
saved is this is this oh run for
your great let's
go gamer
skills uh wait can I save no
okay can I do it again I found at that
spot I could save for some reason
uh wait wait wait
what I could go from the other side
before why not
now all
right is there certain sides that are
better than
[Music]
others
y can I save there though time for S
what can I can I save there where do I
go where do I go
go no okay keep going keep going hello
is the one still
coming it's still
coming where did I go where did I go
okay okay okay p
hello hello hello hello show something
show
[Laughter]
something let's
go are you guys hearing the music is it
too quiet I feel like it needs to be
[Music]
louder I don't even need you
come shoot here shoot
here
and you're coming with me let's
go wait what what wait
what I didn't know where to
go
wait does it need to be louder I wanted
to even louder I hope it doesn't get too
loud oh wait that's too
[Music]
loud maybe I don't know one more time
okay okay it was good until that point
uh when I
died which is a logical conclusion I
think oh look at those ah ah look
at those jumps though I realized I can
just go straight from there now
leave me
alone
sh
sho yeah
baby still have enough
Health yes had maybe helped a little bit
with
time oh God wait
what what's
that oh
wait oh
flash you guys have such good
manners I do have a question about this
though but I don't have even time to ask
it come on thank you
ah wa whoo whoo
oh oh wait
no a that one 1
cm take it oh no oh no oh
no
oh this time I'm not taking damage from
you
bastard
yeah come
on I
no thank you for the help you know maybe
they're just trying to
help uh that part that part makes
me nervous cuz for one moment I'm like
where the do I
go
what oh sh uh
not
wait wait I forgot wait what this is the
part that I don't know what to do I
don't know what to do
I just kind of went left and it kind of
worked I forgot have to play this
game oh it saves here
[Music]
hallelujah I got to the safe
point
oh
man oh man
okay okay I can do
[Laughter]
this maybe it only saves on easy mode I
don't know cuz many of you are surprised
uh wait what what what okay okay okay I
I see I see I see I see I see I see
um
wait uh hello projectile projecti so son
can you come a little bit faster there
ah ah okay I see I have to go up uh can
I get that oh would I regret that
go and
up oh here oh God oh God oh
God what the hell do I that do I do that
jump uh where am I
going
wow wow
frog frog oh let's go frog
no it's fun but I'm freaked out wait can
I do it again one more one more one more
one
more I don't need that energy thing
anyway do I oh oh
the green thing I I oh no wait that's my
health that's my health I need
it uh are we going
here I wish you could just get it by
bumping at it not just
by
um jumping on top of it because
sometimes it's really
difficult
this one as well the you wouldn't have
to hit it like directly on
top oh
don't be greedy just go up maybe
just one maybe just
one oh I wanted to jump into the
one on the left but couldn't make it go
go go go go k save the forest take that
kill
me great got the second one yeah maybe
the second one is easier to
get uh
go go go go go go go go go
go
okay okay
okay no I'm
drowning
no
help me there's so much water
here Pro
moves okay nice beautiful beautiful
beautiful oh yeah oh yeah now we're
gaming oh now we're
gaming
oh come back from this is like
we're in the
Titanic
ah
come here come
here that was New Territory I didn't
know what was going to
happen but we're getting better
here
doy also my my Thum starts to
hurt come on
no the stress it doesn't even get give
you any time to take a break between the
deaths um which I mean I guess I could
do it myself let me shake my hands a
little bit shake shake shake shake shake
shake shake shake shake shake shake
shake shake get PSD on my broken thumb
yo my thumb hurts y
sorry for the PTSD but it's a tough one
yeah this Metro
station shake shake shake shake
sh I like I like that song when I was
younger at
[Music]
least
up up we
go no no why would you fail me like
that was I too fast for you projectile
son I want this one to be
perfect yeah I'm using a Pro
Controller oh I wonder wait on Steam I
guess yeah you don't you don't play this
game with a keyboard do you like who
does that who would be that kind of
crazy
person that wasted a lot of
time oh yes I saved some time
here oh come come monkey frog no Frog
died my frog died let's
go my RO
drown I led him to
death
oh I I forgot to get the
projectile still can still save it no no
what a horrible
run hey but I got I got all that Health
to go
with so who is really winning
here I this is better come here come
here come
here
what
what oh my
God how much High we
go my chat died again quite a while ago
why come
[Music]
back I want to see I don't have time to
read the chat anyway but I want to see
it moving in in the corner of my eye
that was good wasn't it that was so good
was I close to the end really okay I can
do that again Let me refresh the chat
once more I can see it in OBS but it's
too far away I want to see the chat
[Laughter]
go
tipping
Sky let's go to the top B to the
Top This actually fun I don't know this
this part is more fun than before than
what I played before of this
game
toing uh no I can't do this I need to
crack my fingers
okay T to L on
y the music
Beautiful nice
landing y it
okay
oh frog come here
frog a BR kill
me what's that Frog song
again that's kind of like Scatman
no what's that frog thing Frog song
no I can't save that N I don't want to
live like
this crazy frog oh
yeah
k no ah the angle I was too close
to honestly we can do this all
day we can do this all day I don't
mind on this part I have no choice but
to uh jump up the wall right there are
no projec out unless I'm missing
something F no FR not
again
[Music]
no
sh I need you
there
o fro go I'm really counting on you on
that point normally I don't care about
using you no one left one more
please I know I could get him in the
very moment when I'm arriving which I
would like to try or I'm lowkey
trying
um but most of the time y most of the
time I'm not able to do it just like
here just like here where I could
in
Fury jump right into to it as
well but you know things don't always go
the way you would like them
to not everything is ideal and
perfect except for my kfp chin
I'm
drowning it bad
jump
oh almost missed that
[Music]
one yes that's what I like to
see perfect jump
your y it y it I got nervous I got
nervous come
here what happened
what
happened go
oh think my chat died again maybe it's
the amount of flush
Chets
yes no that jump is pretty big oh come
back come
back yeah oh God I can't
oh no
no my
fingers my
fingers I did
it my chat is
back oh my my
finger
oh holy moly we finished the train are
we done with like one
section ohoh
[Music]
oh oh I was about to celebrate and be
happy oh M why are you so mad what
happened this is the inner darkness that
m is hiding but she releases it when she
draws if you haven't seen her art then
you don't know how disturb she is we're
continue what what what oh
[Music]
no you have no idea how hard I work to
get to the
[Music]
top catch me at
least not like that J
was Delight she hated but or's kindness
would once again save my
child huh
or I am ory right the bunny is ory the
white bunny or's kind of safe wait a
second is
it I'm a bit
confused
[Music]
or
or I thought I had lost you to put us
Talons of hate but it was gumo who saved
you delivering us from uncertain
fate you save or
kindness what I'm
confused ah wait the one who spoke was
not was was Guma the Voice who spoke was
Goma
no okay so the Voice who spoke was my my
mom the voice is a tree oh okay
oh oh it's so peaceful and pretty
here but look here with the G tree
restored Neil's waters are
clear but there's no time to lose we
must make haste the element of winds
next resting deep within the four lone
ruins inside the Misty Woods there's a
key that will open their
[Music]
Gates
oh wow wow okay now I'm a bit more
confident about finishing this game now
than I was
[Music]
before
let me eat a strawberry I got some more
strawberries you guys want
one
y no not chocolate covered I like that
too but sometimes you just want to eat
them pure
it's
pretty so wait am I going under the
water
whoa but I do have a breathing
thingy
ow wait I only have one health bar right
now maybe there's something here to heal
myself I don't know this is fun can we
not stay here
go away go away feel like we're in a
different game
now what is this oh
shoot why would I do that oh uh got
confused uh to help me go
faster oh already found one door puzzle
piece even though I was just casually
exploring
down
oo like this new
mechanism
ow ow uh I'm guessing I need to o no
guessing I need to go down from
there oh is there a puzle piece here
too go
away y y y y y I can use them though
oh that eats them into the
Netherlands
but H are you telling
me most that I
can't
the neverland
yes yes so
what
sh I don't know why aiming downward is
so hard for me leave this place for now
okay yeah but I need to get the the door
thing is
right I like the lowkey trop iCal
music I need more help come
on
hello help
do I can't just go with one piece of
Health
no
no wait I forgot how
to
go left there was nothing there at least
I didn't see
anything ah saving oh oh CR okay gives
me only one Health
though what do you
want I went there but there was no
healing option
there ah but okay that's a perk that's
an ability I taught myself huh oh come
on
these
fishies funny little fishies I wait to
the left
first
carefully
I okay could save here again let's do
that I I like the the controls when uh
swimming it's very
smooth
okay what am I even trying to
accomplish here wait I want to kill
myself out here I need that I need that
thing I need it to protect
myself or's nose Gone
Forever ah wait
[Music]
air go go go go go go go go go
w
oh wait is there no air here y it y it
let me out let me out let me
out all
right wait ah the slug can the Slugs not
be used for uh
projecting damn
it um oh ah
a it's okay I don't need
it give that to
me give that to me too nice exp yummy
yummy yummy don't die and
save and now we already have two pieces
but I think we needed ow think we need
a four
probably can project off of them I tried
that I didn't want to use their
projectiles I wanted to use their body
but I don't know maybe I was too far
away I needed two only oh well then
we're ready to
go
you came out of
nowhere no it was a g
far attack the fish are you guys meing
at
[Music]
me just attack them oh wait know you're
actually honest why would I do
that wait maybe I need a dead air maybe
it will be really gy
gy look at
me look at me yeah the water section you
mean the one where the water was coming
up it was
fun it was stressful but it was a like a
good kind of stress in Adrenaline
especially because it wasn't that
challenging give me
that all right now I can uh jump into
the water I was like I can't touch the
water but no I
can
W
oo oh how do I break you
that's why it's a good game save boss
okay uh wait let me eat one more
strawberry
and
mhm
yummy hey random topic
did you guys
know that
there's secret
bars in
Paris doesn't
work I killed
him secret bars as it oh
no didn't realize secret bars as an um
like you won't find out about them uh
uh who told you about my French
French who
else she said she wanted to take me to
one of those because she knows one but
uh because I don't drink uh alcohol she
was like ah I guess it's probably
doesn't wouldn't make much sense to
bring you
down but so apparently
ow so apparently there's like uh yeah
bars or like maybe even restaurants no
but I think mostly bars that are just in
random really random hidden places it
would have been a good story yeah hidden
places in uh in the city uh and you
wouldn't really normally find them it's
not really easy to figure out where they
are and you can't find out about them
online either
normally yeah and that got me thinking I
don't recall having anything like dad uh
in in Austria or I I haven't heard of
anything like that in any other place
evil also I don't know how to continue
here and so my French f f f f fmt my
French friend she she told
me she told me the one that she knows
it's like like
uh
oh Oh I thought that would work it's a
it's like behind a a washing machine you
know those those washing places where
the washing machines those public
washing machine places you know those
you know those ah slide off thank you
that's actually a good
idea yeah so you would randomly find it
if you go to one of those places and you
open the washing machine to wash your
clothes and you open and then behind the
washing machine door a laat yeah behind
that you you discover A Whole New World
A Whole New
[Music]
World yeah yeah yeah yeah isn't that
crazy that's like in a
movie that exists stuff like that exists
I thought it was only in movie movie
yeah maybe maybe someone also made
something like Narnia where you would
open a closet maybe in a shopping mall n
probably not in a shopping mall but like
maybe in a random street there's just a
closet and some kind
of establishment and you open it up and
then you see a bar behind the closet
that's so crazy is that a is that a
common thing in in
anyone's cities
guys
not in Italy maybe you just don't know
about it maybe it is and you just don't
know about it they exist I would not
know yeah you probably don't know but
there are some quite a few in London I
can imagine it being in London
yeah
[Music]
for m H our local regulations here in
Germany make that almost impossible well
I I'm assuming that the secret bars in
Paris as well don't really have a
permit and exist there maybe illegal I I
mean I don't know but I would
automatically assume
[Music]
so
I thought that was like movies only yeah
I can imagine they're like illegal but
yeah you don't talk about see well I I
don't know where that one is the one
that I
mentioned except that it's in
Paris I don't know anything else I
haven't been there but if I ever go back
to Paris I want ffmt to bring me there
even if I don't drink aloh I don't care
I want to see it that's that sounds like
so exciting something really special m
sorry I wanted to focus on the topic
that's why I didn't move
[Music]
uh I hate
you I hate
you now I got to go find one of those in
in my city but I don't know I don't go
outside side so how do you find bars
secret bars when you don't go
outside if it's owned by a burp I'd say
it's legal oh you
[Music]
funny is there no easier way to do this
than how I'm doing it because I'm just
too stupid to land on the top of these
things search for them on secret
Google make your own secret bar at home
I guess so no that's
boring no I wanted to project myself
into that I messed
up it jumped away from it I wanted to
jump into
it oh this thing is
[Music]
back no
no can we save midap no as far as I know
on unstable surfaces the game doesn't
allow you to
save I'll do it don't worry I can do
it don't worry we need secret
restaurants you know the worry
about that that I would have
is that they don't make enough income to
really operate properly CU they don't
have many customers
right and also I don't
know isn't it kind of worrisome if a
place like that they they obviously
probably don't have a liquor license or
anything like
that so I don't know if I would trust to
hygiene and stuff like that
either
you
m
and play this game I can't do both at
once it
[Music]
seems come on Focus Orie Focus my little
weird Bunny with the long
tail
no we could always take Kelly no I could
not because she lives in a different
country than I do
I think you have a little bit of a
thinking error
there see I can't save here unstable
ground they say
unstable it is indeed unstable I agree
with
that I didn't die but oh I wanted to
protect myself into I know what I'm
supposed to do here guys I understand I
understand I understand I
understand okay okay that was at least
smoother than
before did you see
that
okay okay that works that works oh
Hallelujah quick oh my
[Music]
God we're out of the water this is kind
of like a jungle Isn't
it
nice we're taking it we're taking it
nice and easy from here
on we had a really exciting and uh
challenging part right at the
beginning oh I wanted to use that damn
it and now we'll take it easy guys we'll
chill and relax while playing
[Music]
aie give me that health
and we go up up up up up up
it no rest your progress yeah
g I should get it as high as possible
and then this is as high as possible
yeah uh where are we
going
w we reached the skill tree or whatever
that was
again ELO was the stest of all Spirits
the most powerful ever seen now here he
rests turned into an ancestral
tree
n absorb the
light wao I'm getting thrown
[Music]
I've Got The Power you've learned stomp
oh I want to learn Dash though please to
use this ability press B and leap into
air
then what down dive powerfully towards
the ground what I need to try that
out
what be be doesn't
work
is it really
be be is just jump be to jump and then
down
oh I can break these things now yeah oh
it's okay can you shoot something over
here so I can come back
hello
hello safe
oh I guess so hello noce me
Senai I'm trying right but here it
doesn't
Okay one more
please
uh so I wonder can I kill these now of
the stump probably
[Music]
not oo ooh uhhuh and
then Oh I thought that would work
here or do I need to go from even
higher oh
what it's like I'm a
hammer
[Music]
uhuh
oh don't I need
[Music]
to
what you are the key
not uh I really panicked there that was
unexpected uh I guess now we can also
fight
that isn't this where I came
from nice
landing is this where I came from yeah
why are we back
here I guess I'll go the other to then I
think that was a different path as
well wait do I even need to go this
way
ow huh could I
not I'm done with this part really Oh I
thought there was still something I
missed okay so we're going out of here
let me look look at the
maple
oh oh I guess I saw pretty much
everything here okay but it looks like I
would come back eventually cuz there's
like a this part here looks like I will
stomp through it
eventually
anyway wait can I jump
here
oh not oh that oh that only gave me that
I thought that would be more there never
mind so maybe this
way oh dear oh dear oh dear oh
de D
it uh I need to I need some time to get
to know those mobs
mhm some quiet alone time with
them to learn how to handle them shoot
it ah after it's broken I can just
attack it normally all
right leave me
alone I'm already down to two Health
again God damn
it I kind of just have this feeling that
in order to stomp him I just need to be
way higher than he
is but it seems like even when I don't
jump that high and just touch him
basically while doing the stomp attack
it still
works oh it even works like
that come
here okay I'll save I'll save this time
uh when I'm closer to the Mob sorry we
keep when coming back
here it's it is an AOE skill
[Music]
okay I guess it is cuz that was also not
exactly on top of the broken
part and it still work oh wait I wanted
to
say you can use your bash on him
oh it
ow what does he die when he falls into
the
water wait give that to me the all
belongs to
me did I drown
him oh map Stone
fragment let's take a look what do we
have
nowo so we're going to go to the left
and explore the ground
there halfway to there really what do
you mean halfway there I don't believe
that that must be a lie
you I have to do that come
[Music]
here I need to drain the water
huh how do we do
that me maybe somewhere oh wait over
here right this
where where I
couldn't damn it I need to do that
again
what
yumy
go well I couldn't continue before
M kill fishes yes yes okay
[Music]
okay
okay so there was some path here where I
couldn't continue
before I'm assuming now I
can can
[Music]
I wait I didn't save again okay I'm so
sorry I need to I need to um focus again
I need to save as
well BR forcing
it don't we have air Dash I got the
skill
thingy but
apparently
wow apparently
that's not the only thing I need I need
the game to give me the ability first
we have air Dash but not Dash yeah
that's the problem cannot use air Dash
without
Dash seem safe
okay
no sure get some air brief
ow
uhuh
okay
and there we are
okay they need to build the paths so
that
even even PKU like me can land on it
please yum only one Health though that's
really
tough
oh I didn't realize there would be more
of that
[Music]
there I can go there though right make
safe got heal yeah I should do that when
I reach that point again where I can
breathe I will do
[Music]
that okay so far so
good I want to save
[Music]
here okay oh and there I get my health
back wa did you see me styling there did
you see that I'm
proud
okay uh beak jump to the
left and
up get that un safe
here wait
[Music]
how
bump what do you mean bump oh I forgot I
had that
opportunity I forgot that that was even
a
thing I
forgot I completely forgot about it I
gained a new ability
[Music]
point and what do we have next Ultra
Spirit magnet most pickups will Auto be
absorbed doesn't really have
priority um improves the radius and Dam
that's to that's to this one I think
that's my normal attack right that would
become
stronger I did too when I was here yeah
it doesn't get used very much does
it that's bomb
[Music]
attack oh that's a big bump oh
h ah spit Flame the
one two Targets at once oh is this the
the one attack that I use all the
time low Spirit Flame Charge flame
Spirit FL split split split flame Spirit
flame becomes split flame oh I do want
that so I kind of do have to get the
bomb even though I don't use it
much
okay zip zappy the zip okay okay
okay
hold so I drank the water I can't
continue here so I got to go back this
way and then enter from the top or am I
being stupid and I'm oh and I missed
something did I miss something I don't
think I
did H
dony speaking of Paris you want to hear
something
funny it's not really funny it's
fascinating
honestly it's fascinating when I was
eating breakfast in my hotel there was
like a there was a older
couple stand uh sitting next to me
eating
breakfast and
uh they were having this
conversation and the dude was like
telling his wife the older guy was
telling his wife like oh oh by the way
our friend blah blah blah invited us to
his castle in England to stay at his
castle Yeah
yeah and I just thought it was so weird
because the latest the lady's uh
reaction it was as if it was such a
given such a normal thing for everyone
to to have a castle
Yeah she was like uh okay she barely
gave a reaction at all no it's not just
European things I think this is maybe if
anything it's like a
uh it's a maybe England thing so
apparently castles are not that
expensive in
England getat yourself a castle too I
was talking about that with
ffmt oh Europeans have a castle of
course we do of course we do yeah I
don't want to hurt
[Music]
myself she was so how do you say it
unfaced is that that's the right word
right do I want to kill you do I need
you
projectile guess I didn't
oh the music
changed it's so medieval now oh
[Music]
uh oh is that a secret over
there
[Music]
no how can I not hurt myself
there nonchalant is the work but unfaced
isn't wrong
I I want to say like she was not
impressed with it it was like such a
normal thing oh he has a castle let's go
there
what ah this is for the dash lader maybe
okay maybe maybe it is let's remember
it
uh where am I going okay
oh the music once again became a little
bit more mysterious
here should I go down first let's see
what's down here oh yeah oh
yeah ah the left side is connected to
the top anyway where I it seems like I
was before but there's something I could
break right
[Music]
there also apparently this part is
connected too
I want to go to the left here 4 four
oh ah now I want to go up after
[Music]
all so do you guys have a castle a
castle
castle you guys have
one
woo I of course I have many castles all
over the world I have five I have
six
oo I don't even own an apartment oh no
Lego castles oh wow respect can you you
want to invite me over one day to your
Lego
castle Minecraft
castle
lame it
uh can I project myself with that
laser oh oh I I I know I know I know I
know I know I know don't tell me
wait this this is what they want me to
do all wa I I'll wait a little bit
more and
then the big brain it's it's almost I'm
so big brain it almost hurts you
know
oh
wait eliminated k
out oh I see the
spikes and I raise you
laser remember sa do can be used to warp
around oh yeah yeah yeah if I want to go
somewhere else that's far away
indeed oh there's a really short time
frame
here I made it I made
[Music]
it Kaboom what was that again is that
the thing that loads up my blue energy
if yes it didn't what that do again what
did that do again you EXP
ah okay uh now let's
see I need
[Music]
to need to go back down now the part
where I said I'll go back up the
road can you not hurt yourself all the
time what
the okay ah be careful there's a there
is a laser there
need to teleport need to save to the
blue marker
what
what I did save
again
Wait no that's not what I wanted oh my
god oh you or you're so
aggressive I guess ah now if you tell me
to go down faster to jump
to to to fall down fast and now this is
actually a thing that's possible for me
before it wasn't now I
can
uh
die oh I see an altar I should have gone
here first after
all oh
[Music]
well okay
okay
uh I don't need to warp I
think wait did that
save the first time I touch it does it
automatically safe or do I always have
to extra
save maybe I do have to extra
save yeah I guess I'm enjoying it a bit
more than last time maybe although the
beginning last time was fun too it just
became too stressful later on
get out of
here we could go down and then right oh
wait
yeah want to go here oh put there spots
in the way I mean I can take a little
bit of
damage
I guess I can't is that for dashing
later as
[Music]
well why are you going right because
there's something here that I want to
explore this
part water is safe now oh yeah what did
I did I try to stay away from
it you need Dash or triple jump oh
okay then I'm going to the left after
all
bu so we
go
down oh you
again oh I don't like fighting these
because I always hit myself when I try
to hit them
I didn't see that
coming and now it occasionally will do
the this attack the ground pound attack
even though I'm not asking for
it okay come
here
ow
ow I totally forgot about that thing
again there's more than
[Music]
one there's more than
one let's try to remember that never
feel safe kada not even in your own
home nowhere nowhere in this world is
safe
ow
who wow I'll save here nowhere in this
world is safe unless you make a saving
point right hello hello
hello wait
uh
okay
okay perfect cleaning lady
Desu m
[Music]
oh that's the EXP thing isn't it oh I
see I need to crawl on top of dead wait
oh oh wait no that's the energy cell not
exp you found an energy cell I can
collect even more energy
nice uh is this where I
not so this time we go left
up game
saved they come out out
nowhere seems like I have no eye for
them oh
hello I don't need you anymore for
the we're stomping things
away I can do it on my own
the sounds that these slugs make oh no
wait is this one is safe too looks a
little bit more
spoopy
yeah okay yeah seems
so ah energy
door I got enough actual
surprisingly is that
oh yes I have barely been finding secret
rooms
though if I can't find secret rooms in
this game then how will I ever find
secret rooms in secret bars in Paris and
other cities I willon
never but I've made it into one of my
life goal
to to find one of those one day
somewhere it doesn't matter where I just
want to find one this is what we wanted
let's go my spirit flame is stronger and
it now can Target two Targets I want to
test it out only if there's two Targets
in reach I
suppose we sure what is that is that a
secret room it is I was just talking
about it it's kind of obvious though who
I feel like the range was bigger
it's bigger isn't it what is that
that why does that not disappear is that
a
bug glitched
corpse
okay oh another one ah I don't have
enough
here where would I get some
more time to farm go back to the
Fountain uh
uh wait what's the shortest
path I could go from the bottom or from
the top doesn't
matter you recharge when you level up oh
right I'm so close to leveling up so I
guess I should just uh stay in the same
area and kill some
mobs there's not many mobs here
though very
close oh did you see that it did hit
both
yeah
[Music]
taking I guess I'll leave that place one
more
time
is that this doesn't come down does it
oh
uh
you come on come on over
here oh
hey that's kind of rude I must say
uh okay back to leveling I didn't want
to save because I didn't want to waste
my blue
balls I guess it doesn't matter when I
when I level up it it heals it all back
up
again the blue balls the energy
balls or only a few
ones I found a
secret
what it's free when I reuse it
oh oh give
me that one dropped a lot of good stuff
thank
you I got the
thanks
mhm does that one give
XP it does a little
bit now I'm all the way here again oh
let me get some health while I'm at it
oh no wait wait that's not Health give
me
exp
ow
I'm going to go back you can use the
fountain now yeah that's that's indeed
true let me go back please go to the
well if only I
could that well the well was I think
above me hey can I please uh please
please please
please there you
go sometimes I make the easiest things
very
difficult forgive
me here it
is game saved
oh now we got all the balls I
needed I'll take
that okay let's make our way
back oh down here now don't get crashed
don't get smashed don't get
crashed oh no damage was that I think
I'm getting the hang of it
guys yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah
um all right
I need to take that again Ah that's why
someone said something about my about
the secret I guess I needed to take it
up
again we have arrived and opened another
door oh wait that's the other side from
someplace where we've been to
[Music]
before
it's so pretty look at that
background with those tall ass trees oh
and the
corruption can I not help or do anything
here wait can I
jump oh wait I
again now would you look at
that would you look at that
I've seen it before it's
beautiful where do I need to go though
do I need to go here
now why did I come back
[Music]
here is there oh y y is there
something I have missed
here the big blue marker where is that
one
no
ah over
there go to the Fountain which one wait
where am I where am I here ah to that
one down there all right
R
uh are you okay frog it honestly just
sounds like you're hurting yourself
how do I why was he able to go down but
I can't I thought I could kind of like
do it like in
Mario oh down be
ah another thing that I have forgotten
since the last time we played
aie
oh
ooh this place seems
[Music]
familiar hydration check oh yeah do you
guys want me to war from
here oh do I want to war
here oh go to to the right go to the
left oh yeah right weren't we able to
not move on from here last time we've
been
here why this statue looks familiar I've
seen it
before doesn't look familiar to me not
sure what you mean let's take a
look what is
that they found the
home
[Music]
of the child who embraced Our
Lives I I I I remembered them many years
ago when the spirit Tre was but a
sprout Naru the young one looked after
us whenever she
good Naru
Naruto
Naruto sasuka Naruto black root
Burrows it's so dark in
here someone turn on the light this is
the DLC
oh interesting the extra
area do I have to do it
[Music]
the one that came with the definitive
addition I suppose you got Dash here oh
it's optional but I get Dash here I need
Dash what is this what is this what what
what what what what where the am
[Music]
I I I can't I can't do this
what no needs Dash in again really dash
is pretty strong well we did get air
Dash so it would be
nice would be nice if we i' save it for
later it's going to be very hard but
chat can
help it looks so
[Music]
difficult
but can I save here
again okay
um that's just too useful I recommend
okay but how the hell are you supposed
to do
this I don't see
anything uh
there's nothing on the map
either going to be very slowly slow and
careful is this the one where I dropped
myself and fell all the way down what's
what's
this Dash
do hello
Dash I came for you to pick you
up what's what's down there what is that
what is
that look down look down is that where
Dash
is it's very bright and
[Music]
shiny eventually you'll find a light
source oh oh oh L
door I don't know what H there's spikes
down
there I don't know where to
go
ow I don't know where to
go well thank God I had so much health
but what
now they're leaving me completely in the
dark
haha is this what they want me to do oh
God there's it no there was another door
thingy
there restart follow the
light Ori and the blind play for
and now am now I feel very blind
indeed makes a lot of
sense
[Music]
that
what is this place you guys said go left
but this is where I'm
[Music]
stuck probably better not to save down
there not a hold
[Music]
it this is very very very difficult like
absolutely no idea where to
go
important places light
up well that's
great so now I'm on this thing here can
I go to the left oh I can
nice
uh
uhhuh
I
oh uh oh wait there's something there
ah I can't reach it there's a wall
there what's here oh W oh there's
something there too but I guess there's
also a wall there yeah okay what's here
another
wall
help should I save now maybe
[Music]
to wait till you get a lightning ability
but that's going to take a while to okay
we can we can try
this we can
try I'll save them I'll never get out of
here
but okay just
follow these Lit Up bouncy things oh no
not these these things
do you know I'm too stupid to land on
those oh
[Music]
dear I hope you w stay stuck I hope so
too otherwise we'll have to end the
stream while we're stuck
here oh
nice oh I got one of the things that I
need
apparently a slide from the spirit tree
it was a gift from our kind it was given
to n who stood by our
side
okay set are to pick up
objects I give to this door no hold
it
o
it I can still attack while I'm holding
it that's good oh the statues move
because I bring the light to them so I
need to go up
now I want to kill this thing
first are they trying to move closer to
me wait I'm too stupid to jump on
you
I think I want to save
again too scared to die here yeah
uh oh thank you for watching my stream
welcome hello
hello and then jump to get
higher I cannot do a double jump when
I'm holding this St it
seems where we go from from here it it
it oh oh oh wait no come back
oh
no
okay I wonder can I do the projectile
thing no I don't think so it doesn't
react when I try
to ignite it
I saved here don't
worry okay go
up is the spider still alive
no oh this one goes from left to right
okay this is it's so dark I literally
don't know if I'm even
moving
hi no no no no no no no no
can't even try to damage control
because don't see where I'm
falling is this trial and error
experience stupid ass
sper can you
not
mhm can put the light down
oh not a whole but I mean it's not
really that necessary right now cuz I
can attack also while I'm on the
[Music]
platform but but no no I left it
there yeah uh I think I want to hold on
to it
generally oh
no by the
way what the No No I'm going to
another uh
appointment at the dentist on
Saturday uh yeah yeah just getting some
things done there were kind of overdo
while I was in Japan and couldn't do
because I wouldn't didn't want to really
go I wanted to avoid going to the doctor
when I was in
Japan no no
no can I even get there
now at least I can do bigger jumps now
but no I don't know where I'm jumping
to I will kill
myself Japanese doctors must be good um
I I guess so I just you know because the
whole healthc care system and all that
is so diff different in Japan
and you know I don't know it just seemed
so unfamiliar I felt
[Music]
don't kill me don't kill
me I always fall there once until I kill
the spider and come back damn
it I don't know how to kill it without
falling down it always hits me at least
once yeah in a foreign country it's just
kind of
intimidating
and I I don't know I just prefer to go
to a doctor in my own country you know
cuz also like medical terms I speak flu
and Japanese but when when it comes to
medical terms I had a feeling that I
wouldn't understand
everything that he would say the the oh
hell
no I don't want to do
this no the problem is not the insurance
I had an insurance I was literally
forced like when you were a foreigner in
Japan
with like unless you have a tourist visa
if you have any kind of working Visa
then you have to get a health
insurance
no
no yeah most mostly the reason was just
because it feels more familiar to go to
a doctor in your own country number one
and
communication you know there are some
English clinics I think or like clinics
where there are doctors that speak
English but I also think those are from
what I've
heard M oh come on more expensive
because they offer that
service don't make me end the game play
here please because it's just
too too frustrating please please please
I don't I don't want to get some
progress
today
anyway you know what was funny today at
a dentist I'll tell you at the end they
put some
[Music]
something uh
weird they put something like uh what do
you call it something that's good for
your teeth no
no
[Music]
it was a mistake to go here it was a
mistake to go here fluoride yeah yeah
yeah yeah
so they put this yellow thing that looks
like a duck mouth into my mouth and told
me to bite into it and it looked really
funny or at least I would imagine it
looks
funny
[Music]
okay freaking
um what's down here
n
n so they put that and then said y don't
don't move don't move your mouth just
wait until you know it's it sets and
settles so my teeth can enjoy all the
yummy yummy
fluoride uh
hold but then the doctor the dentist he
came back to me and he started talking
to
me and I was like he was asking me
questions where I would have to answer
but I still had the duck thing in my
mouth I looked like a freaking duck no
it didn't have taste of banana but but
it didn't taste bad but he was talking
to I was like even smiling was kind of
awkward because I couldn't really move
my mouth and he was like so next
appointment this day that okay for you
and I'm like uh I wanted to say I have
to check my schedule
but so I was just like uh
uh Saturday and he was like Saturday I
also work on Saturday and I'm
like was trying to say I want to check
my calendar
but he kind of already set the date
there why are you talking to me when I
am literally becoming shoua sha right
now just wait 5 minutes and then I'll be
able to talk to you
maybe you guys put that into my mouth
and now you expect me to answer your
questions you know exactly that I can't
answer your questions oh wait so this
opens all these all of these doors
oh what did it told me
what is how does this work you want me
to land on that but how would I not get
hit
from let the torch troll DST yeah I felt
kind of trolled at that
moment uh but uh it's it's a nice very
nice
dentist very kind very understanding
yeah in general it was all good just uh
that moment when I was literally not
able to speak and they were asking me
questions I'm like how do you expect me
to answer
you wait am I supposed to get this one
down
no
so
H oh wait this is this working as a
torch right now
safe well I mean I just saved over there
but
okay that's a rarity you think
so how
wait how I guess I need to jump in the
moment where oh um I need to jump in the
moment in the right moment to
like jump above it
so almost like that almost almost had it
oh well we
survived but how much longer will we
survive that will hit
me w w wo wo bo bo
[Laughter]
uh ah we survived but at what
cost
don't get too excited
takii this thing is forcing me to
improve y my uh Landing
skills
drastically oh yum it oh
oh no let me up okay okay okay
safe okay so wait no
no
uh uh uh uh how about not jump into the
laser wait I don't
know I was
stuck D
it I'm trying to get some record numbers
here you know o
okay what
[Music]
the one more millimet is what I needed
one more
millimeter no no no no
chill wait chill oh oh I'm top of the
world I'm On Top at the
world oh oh oh my God okay so far now
we're we're on a roll again it was
painful for a
while but now we're on a
roll what do we have here oh some
platforms again now the H is land on the
platforms
I'm going to eat more
strawberries I want strawberry cake that
would be so nice think I see some box on
my strawberry
again
M
M yes
mhm it's December but
they had some good strawberries at the
supermarket I'm actually
impressed
uh
here go away oh I killed it okay are we
going up what what what in here
oh wait
uh
thank you for playing this game I hope
you also play it sequel oh I don't know
about that I have it I bought it and I
downloaded
it um I don't know if I would be allowed
to play it to be
honest so I can't really say
no if I am allowed to play it then we
might play it sometime as
well wait was that the one right below
me the one right here is it here
[Music]
apparently
oh well I thought maybe I need to drop
it
here to like give it energy or maybe I
am supposed to drop it
here no no
okay okay then that's just kind of sus
there not yet he should I I
leave I guess I'll bring it with
me where am I
going huh well how do you expect me to
anticipate
that N N
N I should actually drop it
there maybe I'm in the wrong place
here
platform's on the left of the
room oh
wait
uh I don't even know where I'm trying to
go there was something to activate
[Music]
Oh Oh you
mean what o
okay try to land on that one
yeah oh oh whoo whoo whoo what's going
on
there oh okay when I saw a platform then
I have to land on wa once we get
back here and
now
what what am I waiting no no
no not sure what was going on
there leave the ah leave the lights on
the the left one
perhaps drop it on the
platform
[Music]
okay
sorry drop the thing Okie doie did you
guys see I'm in stream yesterday she
streamed Minecraft I'm so happy she's
back I missed
her did you watch of course I did nice
I'm as back I'm is back great to have
her back yeah now that she's back I felt
even more that it was lonely without
her no sorry sorry I ruined it myself
like OB
[Music]
nous yeah I don't know I I I missed her
I had to express my feelings to
her sorry to the Amit jat for being so
obnoxious as I mean I mean myself but
honestly sometimes I wish that the
people would just when when I entered
someone's chat I wish they would just
not spam like okay the first time it's
okay to say hey Kiana But like after
that it would be cool if
they
no come back to
me it would be cool if they could stop
spamming it because then I just feel
like I'm disturbing and I need to stop
uh I need to stop chatting in order to
not be disturbing because every time
they say hey Ki hey K every time even if
it's just 3 minutes after my last
message some people still think it's my
first message and they're like hey K hey
Ki hey K I don't want the whole chat to
be k k k then it's like it's only about
me when the stream should be about Amma
or whoever is streaming and I feel bad
about that but I do want Amma to know
that I'm watching her stream and that
I'm enjoying it as well you know
sometimes sometimes I want to enjoy the
Stream just just like you are and and
let Amed know that I'm supporting
her you know I know I could watch it
silently but then Amed doesn't know that
I'm
watching that's the
thing I want her to know
we stand
still what
now ah I see
something
[Music]
oh what what what n
NY don't think you un stop that yeah
yeah I was about to write please please
don't say hi K anymore please focus on
am but I I guess it wouldn't have helped
either I didn't want to make a big fuss
about it wait was I supposed to retrieve
my no it's here okay ah now I can put it
there
W is there more to it or did I just
finished the DLC please say I finished
it it would be short but please give me
the dash
[Music]
please give me
Dash yeah they would have just said okay
K now 5 minutes later if I comment again
they would again be like hi Kiana which
I I guess I get it maybe some people
miss it or they literally just ENT the
stream and then they want to be polite
and say hello which I think is cool in
itself but I don't want to I don't want
the streamer to see hey my chat has
constantly been all high kada I just
feel like that's so so obnoxious for the
streamer when especially when you're
just trying to have a normal stream and
have a conversation with the viewers or
whatever and all they spam is
hiana so I kind of I kind of stopped
yesterday eventually and went to eat my
lasaga but I was happy to see Amy back
yeah I missed her I want to I want to
collab with Amma
again no no one ever said anything about
it I just personally feel like it's
disturbing and who knows what they feel
but don't actually say out
loud I'm sure that a lot of the girls
including me
have many things that we're not happy
with but we don't say out loud because
we don't uh want to spread too much
negativity yes I can confirm
that or look even though our light had
grown weak in this Haze it lifted the
darkness that held claim of this place I
rhymed what a
pet so wait everything's bright now oh
hello tree wa is that the
Das hey was looking for Naru but she was
gone when he came he was Swift like the
wind and sprinted with haste but
surrounded by Darkness he lost his
W really that's
it that was surprisingly short you've
learned Dash she usn't press R order to
dash into the direction you're
facing oh my
God what what can you say it again I'm
pressing r i no I'm pressing dead R oh
oh
W oh my
god oh so you want me to use it right
here wait
uh I found a mapstone
fragment wait so wait that's Dash and
then the other thing
is uh wait this is considered as Dash
and then this is considered air Dash
normally I wouldn't be able to do
this but I already have the skill so I
can do
this
oh G
all right wait do I have to pick up that
thing
again W look at
that go go go
woo oh that's freaking fun hell
yeah uh did I save there
before ow no
why did I do that give me back my health
give me back my
[Music]
health okay I wanted to save there but
it's in the aor so I couldn't because I
just don't care ha oh another level
what does this
do
oh oh is this a speed
thing oh you want me to reach that point
before it goes all the way down
M well how about I get rid of the
enemies first do you think that will
help me Maybe
not maybe not
necessarily
but I can at least look at the path
Scout it that's an easy
path it's a simple path and then up here
okay but before we do that we can also
go down
here last
grow not okay I guess we should do the
door thing first
look at me
zooming holy
ory what did you eat these
mushrooms that LD up here oh no
ory
Sonic
[Music]
all
right
Cheerios o what is this what is this
what is this ooh is that thing going to
fall down is that Big Stone up there
going to fall down and yes
am I supposed to go up or
right go right okay
well but I have to wait for it
to oh no oh oh oh I can basically wait
for it oh to go in front of me oh
oh give it give it what am I
doing
why did it kill
me why did it kill me now but not
before maybe I need to be the arrow
no it killed me it killed me why did it
it did I survive before because of a
[Music]
glitch I got
lucky why did I miss it
up I'm not supposed to go behind it but
then I don't understand how do
I if I have to wait for the rock to
crush it N I guess I I just need to jump
over it in a better way but I'm no I'm
not smart enough for that what if I what
if I trigger it come on and then oh no I
can't wait
AIT I wanted to go
behind uh like all the way back to
here and then
[Music]
oh
my oh
M let me create a freaking sing thank
you did I just create my path too go
[Music]
up
from if I can't go
there
jump I'm not jumping from the
highest oh wait what if I
what what if I jump to the left oh wait
like so and then Zoom to the
[Music]
right
oh
how is this so difficult Stomp the
pillar uh yes I would like to go up
that's literally I'm trying to reach
that very pillar right now doesn't look
like I can make it does
it
that was a feel
close how can you make this one so gidy
gidy though like why why why just give
me a little bit more ground there to
stand on
huh why you must make it so
difficult and and another path opens am
I out of the DLC now or am I still in
the
DLC wow lifestyle I got a new life
thingy I'm still in the DLC
oh not to the
Hodo so it's not as short as I thought
it was well I mean I would have been
surprised if it was really that short
can I go down there
no zoomed too
much ory is a
Zuma can't
relate yeah it's nice of them to give me
the wait so the dash is DLC only
is a dash DLC only
wow Huma do they want me to
go here and then here and then uh
explore this
area is all of that
DLC all of
it ability cell oh we got two ability
points right
now
wow two ability points uh ultra light
burst increases the strength and radius
of light burst what's what's light
burst where's light
burst what do we have here Ultra soling
creating a soling restores two live
cells
oh interesting or Ultra Spirit magnet
the basic
attack that's just that's the basic
attack I thought it was called Spirit
[Music]
flame when you hold to oh so it is the
explosion I guess that's the explosion
most pickups will
be energy pickups reward 50% more energy
oh that would be nice to
have m
triple jump is it
there oh triple jump is here first jump
that would be beautiful I'm going this
way and also the life cells are nice too
yeah yeah this path is maybe the first
thing to fill up charge Dash to attack
enemies
Y water
breath isn't that ah ah you mean I can't
I I don't have
to go back to the to catch a breath
anymore so I can should have to cost o
triple jump and Ultra defense all right
all right
[Music]
uh I will go to the left
then
uhhuh time to explore some
more Orie is doing yoga
poses that Dash is
so strong though because you can do it
endlessly right oh my god oh didn't even
need that oh wait this is close oh can I
open it yes ah
down okay new
area where the hell did you come from
game is easy
mode I want say
so not
necessarily
boing o what's
this did you guys see the uh part of the
collection that came out from UMO Kad
the one from Ena that was posted
today
did you see
that I really like her
sweater I think that one
also is
very like it doesn't stand out too much
as like an otaku item if you know what I
mean I just wanted to kill that
[Music]
thing M yeah the the sweater I like the
sweater M the t-shirt is a bit more like
bam in your face because it has that
huge piece of art on it
so for the taco dasis who want to show
off they're
oi I also like the pastel color they're
really really light pastel purple
lavender of her sweater
m
I thought that was
[Music]
safe
I wear lavender every day already
really oh you must like the color I love
it too Lavender is one of the best
colors I love purple I I can tell you if
if orange wasn't my image color I would
go for purple I
think purple and lavender those are like
my favorite colors besides Orange of
course
yeah uh I see something there is that
not a
secret huh
huh time to draw lavender K oh like a
lavender version of me
interesting tell me more tell me
more
nice you're right in the middle of that
what's your favorite color
everyone going to have a lot of people
who lie and say orange now
right even though you don't mean
it it it oh you again
ah for real purple and orange really
green blue yellow aquamarine
M aquam Marine Senai is that is that
also who your Ori
is Orange let's go blue blue green
purple blue blue black orange orange is
the new
purple Orange Is the New red or black no
it was black at that show on
Netflix orange nice
Tanaka what is this am I supposed to go
the opposite direction
here a bit too
slow
oh I used to watch it is it a good show
is it worth
watching burgundy seven months
nice W made
it
wow he was I here before or
no look at
[Music]
that what what the are you what's
that
oh my
God mommy I'm
[Applause]
[Music]
scared okay
uh where did I go from
there to the right to the right and
funnel
this kind of thing you know only real
Gamers can take it and manage it
oh I would say the show fell off almost
as hard as the good place what does that
mean fell off you mean it was
bad I like the good
place what the
no what the what the what the
what is that that's a new
mob what taking
[Music]
like if I go all the way to the right to
get this thing then I think I'll have to
go from the bottom up again or from the
bottom and then to the ah but that door
is closed here so I got to go back all
the way
around wait if I kill myself here now I
should spawn at the top
again can I reach it from there I should
be able to
know wait air Dash only once I made it
somehow but I think think air Dash is
only once
huh you can't get it for now
anyway I think I proved you wrong didn't
I yeah about
that
timing double jump and D Dash yeah I can
do that but I don't didn't need
it the laser thing is freaking me out
yeah oh come on why do I always get the
timing
wrong too
fast are you bad at jump bro
back at school to be honest I wasn't bad
at it but I was I couldn't do like super
pro tricks you
know like when you twist the rope and
stuff yeah I could do
that okay and now we want to go
[Music]
up hello hello uh-oh you again haven't
played with projectiles for a while well
I'm going slowly there's story
[Music]
happening light and dark and innocent
born was
[Music]
lightch still for
but the that was
[Music]
made would soon be
disolved
don't all
right we shall go down here oh nice
landing why is that lamp over
there is there a secret room is that a
hint I couldn't reach
it Pi real voice revealed sure sure sure
sure sure
sure what if what if what if this is my
real voice Soul could cast our light
even in the DI she would see she'll live
deep in this Grove now she rest here in
peace
rip soul I guess it's the word for sun
isn't
it more power to
me light burst I yo this DLC is
op you've gained light burst use his
ability press or hold l in order to cast
a light burst which will show me the way
in
darkness
oh it also attacks things I can break
things with that as
well doesn't break that though can
I
not do I need it for
that Lantern up there
oh c
SK oh oh I can aim like that
too almost
wait
H I got it
oh hold oh another one
here but will this be implemented in the
rest of the game or only in the DLC I
mean will it be necessary or just
useful
consumes energy oh I didn't notice
no I don't want to lose all my
energy it doesn't uh like half half the
energy oh
dear can I undo it when I'm already
holding
L uh I don't think I can yeah
[Music]
it what if I run out of
it I still need it oh managed this one I
think that's it explosive
love achievement
unlocked ahuh okay so we're done with
this part but we can I guess maybe now
go up
here oh the laser the laser
[Music]
stopped oh strong
is that a
crow oops
no
uh is it possible to get
there down to the
right oh this one did not
stop what to the right there's nothing
here
it
leave me alone give me no why did I I
automatically pressed L out of reflex
now okay um I think we're done here I
mean I don't know what that part is but
I don't know how to reach it
either
um so we're going to go down here down
this way
de
get out of here get out of
here
so
okay life saer oh why why didn't you
give me that achievement thank you
goas can I even go down
there maybe would
Doom B one
[Music]
more oh yes
is there something to check out here how
do I get up
there the the thing that I just
learned can I use it to to catch
items probably not right it doesn't work
like
that
bash
[Music]
really
huh I I can bash off of it what
wait let me redo that
then I can bash you mean like a
projectile
okay so
wait come back no come back to
me I shot it too high can I shoot can I
control not only the angle but maybe
also the
um the length of I yes I
[Music]
can okay that was not good enough and I
need more of that
M sorry I have to do it like this
because otherwise I run out of
energy very
[Music]
quickly no no no no
no one
more
okay
yeah wow that's
fascinating ability
sh is there something here no okay hold
[Music]
then
okay ooh and once again my
double double Target thing is working
wonderfully I guess I could go down here
as
well H but I
think I think going right is better
because it looks like a dead end
[Music]
there n now I know what lies beyond that
half
wonderful
and kill you as
well so wait back to omocat topic ena's
got revealed so next I guess would be
theoretically if we go by deut order
which so far it has been deut order next
should be GAA huh you guys excited to
see what gaa's stuff looks
like I already know what it looks like
but I can't tell
[Music]
you you should follow ocat on Twitter
guys to never miss any of these
updates nice that she's back H what do
you mean oh she's
back oh she's also back okay nice good
good is she streaming
tonight
W I hope she's feeling revitalized
then
no I don't know I thought there was
something there but maybe there wasn't
oh no there
is that's the thing I'm trying to reach
there anyway come to Brazil ha o uh I
almost there
already
shark tries to saying oh she doing
a singing stream M stream
ah you know what time for drop is uh I
think in GMT plus 1 it's 4:00
a.m. oh no you mean the I thought you
meant the tweets I don't know what when
the actual releases actually I only know
December 3rd I could probably ask but I
don't have that info and as long as long
as ocat is not giving that info out
publicly then I won't won't be giving it
out
either whoop I will take you to Tokyo
come out side I highly doubt that I
don't know how you would accomplish
that
cuz it's uh if it were that easy
then we would already be
there
yeah
W two ability
points
y nice
catch okay we got two ability points all
does the next one cost us three no two
charge
Dash either get that or HM
H show up on the map increase the Spirit
light
oh makes show up on
the ah what should I
do cinder flame increases of spirit
flame increases radius and damage of
Stomp allows the spirit flame to be
fired more rapidly
oh these ones are not bad either all of
them are good what what four
targets four targets you can eventually
hit four targets triple jump I can't get
there yet but I guess should we
prioritize that go for triple jump not a
h yeah the way that I play this game I
think it would help me a lot won't
[Music]
it
what just
happened I'm charging it but I thought
that I would oh wait no give me that
back my ability point is used up okay
wait
what I don't understand what ah wait no
I messed up the controls okay so if I if
I charge this and then Dash oh that was
powerful then I can attack someone yeah
it did feel like it could
definitely blast someone into
orbit
w h no nope no it
NOP no and we gain another building
point this DLC is full of
abilities so we cleaned this part now
we're going to go back up and then
ah was there even a way to go down here
because I thought I couldn't go through
this
one there must
be there must
be
okay
safe left and then down there he is
there was
really how did I not see it I thought I
couldn't go down
there I see some energy give
me oh by the way yesterday the lasagna
was so
good
it was not selfmade but I ate those
lasaga
wait
it sometimes you just want a effortless
lasaga you know you just want to eat
lasaga but you don't want to put too
much work into
it and even though that lasaga from the
supermarket the Frozen one that I eat
even though it's kind of like watery I
don't know sometimes I like
that I I love and I appreciate all the
lazas in the world so that they don't
feel bad about themselves you know every
lasaga is
beautiful and so are you
chimkin so are
you she ate those Foods I
did certified lasaga Cor no sir yeah
that's me you when that's me you already
see it right in front of
you oh wait now I now I understand no no
no I don't want to no I don't want to
die again wait wait I have to stop in
the
middle what the
no what hit me
there oh sh
[Music]
m b
what oh ah this is this secret that I
found now okay wait wait wait stop it
will
[Music]
you what just happened no I
died I thought it was
safe
chill okay now I came here with much
more health so no
problem give me back that energy okay so
oh I can't just go down here that way
after all I don't know why I thought I
couldn't oh I need a
key
K thank you thank you for the member
message love you
free, wait H were you trying to was that
the maximum you could write were you
trying to say the 3,000 members uh kfb
Discord if you yes your message has been
received thank
you where am I
going oh no it's a Marvel reference
oh I once again feel like a
boomer I don't watch Marvel movies love
your free Oh I thought he got cut off
there when he was
typing
oh wait am I supposed to bring them over
here oh I needed
them did I need them maybe
not I hope
not a there's so
many can I make this
no wait maybe I did need them
no H
wait no
wait I want I wanted to throw from up
here but apparently when I stand like
this I can't throw the
ball
oh see it landed on there but apparently
that's not strong enough either is that
really how it's supposed to be done
because it's not working so
far
it's funny how when I stand like this I
can't throw it but when I'm hanging onto
a wall I
can oh
wait do you want more than
one I'm just wasting them
now you don't need to pass there oh I
guess so there's nothing really
there except
for no idea what's there
oh
wait you got to come here you got to
come
here I thought you could take the weight
off of me by putting your weight on
there but I guess you're too fat to move
on to the
platform okay um
so but if
I'm but if I'm not making use of that
then I have to go up and then maybe here
maybe there's the key there or the key
is in here where I'm I was just trying
to go now throw the orb from platform
then
Dash Oh you
mean
oh oh this is what you mean oh that's a
pro
move you expect me to be able to do
that uh
wait wait what oh wait I can destroy
them from here as well that's
interesting that will help maybe so that
I won't
die oh wait maybe I don't even have to
go
inside KN I thought they want me to go
inside I just had to throw my ball in
there
oh oh
okay I I guess that was maybe the same
thing as the chat was saying but I
didn't I didn't understand it what you
guys were
saying
n oops oh
sorry OD be like
e only only just wants to play uh baseb
you know and had no one to play baseball
with can I shoot the bird a
[Laughter]
b that's a funny way to fight those
birds any stop it stop pooping from the
[Music]
ceiling
I don't have
key where is
key do I need to attack them than
you oh
my last one y it
no is that what they're asking me to do
though I need to die once I think
I need to kill them okay okay okay okay
well then let's not waste all my
balls oh
that went out of
control but maybe the first hit like
this cuz that's very Comal for you like
[Laughter]
that I no no
[Applause]
[Music]
gag you can bash attack ah I don't think
I'll really be using that I I don't I
don't know
nah wait it actually targets the bird
even when it moves nice I didn't
realized it was uh like finding the
Target on its own automatically
oh it it
does kind
of no no I ran out of them
[Music]
again oh shut
up oh what the was that I wish
I could retrieve them like this
what
now free I am here but still miss you
why you miss me I'm
here I'm
here oh
damn God
damn oh
D
it uh can I have
those well no no you need to bird
oh oh that's what you
meant bash prot in
Spartan oh
oh oh come
on wait now it doesn't automatically
Target it I wonder what was the problem
there cuz I moved it why did I waste
them all
sorry yeah can I I can launch from the
bird but the first one I will kill so
that that it won't disturb
me
mhm and then
oh I need one more though I didn't
do enough
damage ah D you
it wait oh no I completely forgot I can
I can go I can uh Dash through their
projectiles as well no oh what was that
the small slugs I can project myself
through them but not through their
project
St very uh
[Music]
confusing and did I kill
them I think I killed
them
I whatever doesn't matter we did it
anyway do I need you I need you a
alive well it kind of worked just do as
much damage as possible when I'm at the
top no wait I
cannot no I am not able to use their
projectiles I have tested it out
[Music]
now but how do I get to the top from
there I want ah I don't have to get
there because I can just
shoot what a
waste just
shoot oh so
close o think I'm going to die would
probably be better to die
[Music]
now it like kind of aims at them but
they move so far
fast
what okay hit me then I move so fast
that I can't keep up with it oh I could
use the
mai oh
no
oh trying to
focus there we go that's what I wanted
yeah I'm out of here suckers
later oh
C where are we oh new
section for a moment this place look
like a worms world to
me just for a
moment how long did I say I would play
the game today did I say 3
hours it's been 3 and 1/2
hours didn't I say 3 hours today or did
I say 5 hours a probably need can I did
say it didn't
I oh right now it's not that frustrating
so I'm actually
good water
wow Pretty
Water stupid
fish
yeah yeah
yay yeah
yay probably meant 1 no no no 13
Impossible on youtube cannot Stream So
Long use bash on light bursts to reach
greater
height are you teaching me something
that I've been doing all
along
onl oh wait no you mean my yeah yeah
yeah ah you mean this this stuff yeah
yeah I've been doing that I know what
you
mean oh I'm just really bad at
catching I didn't have a dad to teach me
baseball we don't play baseball in my
country to be honest at
all can't do this no one t me and I'm
not interested anyway it's not like I
wanted to learn how to play
baseball it's not like I care h
sh I'm the pitcher yeah not the catcher
why am I all the way back here no I
didn't
save byebye
byebye
[Music]
byebye bye-bye
I'm real no actually you know what in
real life I really wouldn't be the
picture as I told you guys I'm really
bad when it comes
to the ball
games anything when you have to throw
any kind of
ball no matter which kind of
ball it's not not my table
game
I'm back I'm back I want to save can I
save
here hell
yeah cheerleader
kada we didn't have cheerleaders I think
in sports class in our
schools we don't have that I think
correct me if I'm wrong
Australians you guys in America and
Canada and so on actually have
cheerleaders for like
in school do you actually have
cheerleaders feel like that's just like
a Netflix
thing oh we don't do that in
Europe is that an American thing North
American
thing I think that there's definitely
like a possibility to practice that
sport in Australia as well like maybe
some some you know groups like cheely in
classes but I mean I would never heard
of it but I'm sure it exists
[Music]
somehow but we don't have
that
hi
uh nice I've gotten really good at this
like saving myself when I'm in the air
what are we doing
here
[Music]
huh does it want me
to does it want me to
throw one down
[Music]
there no that's not what I meant
what's light burst can bounce off the
pads but where would I want it to
go didn't want it to go that far I
wanted to see if it weighs on the on the
it no
[Music]
stop not sure what to do
here ah wait oh now I see H once again
again I have to think the opposite way
I'm not the one going up there this ball
is the one going up there am I
right
oh oh
[Music]
holy moly
macaroni and now
what ah I
see now I go up wait wait can I uh redo
cuz um my nose was
itching let's hope I get the ball right
again mo guy mo
[Music]
guy
kaboom can't save here okay
survive survival
time really good that I'm playing this
game with uh on easy mode so that I
don't take too much damage so wait how
do I open this
door what do you oh do I need to go up
here yeah more arei today I am doing a
better job than last
time I feel like Sanic here look at that
pH those moves look like Sanic oh wait I
just I didn't see this I didn't see the
level hi Ai
master I'm doing much better
right agreed waom AB ability we got two
again can I get something new is the
next one free what a breath hell yeah
ding d d ding cing
cing gamer mindset yeah yeah well it's
going pretty well must say after all I
am a gamer we all knew that since a long
time ago uh I think they want me to
shoot myself
again the values that this game is
teaching me
though although I guess they're kind of
similar to Phoenix mindset like when I
see that I that my health is too low
anyway I just go from myself into death
and then restart start over I guess it
is kind of like a phoenix huh or is a
phoenix
n could you come back here so I can kill
you thank
you
hello
[Music]
really not doing bad right now I have to
give this to
myself I am really not doing
bad it feels somewhat smooth right
now oh okay so that door opened but this
one didn't so I got to oh
no you want me to throw some moving
[Music]
again a dash oh maybe it doesn't close
that fast okay no it
[Music]
work where am I I've been here
before ah I need to fall
down
poana yeah and the music honestly is
motivating me right now too because it's
so peaceful and positive right
now it's it's having a positive effect
on me but here it's looking darker
again there's a there's a pineapple
Slice on the ground here right now where
I'm
standing
pineapple
who who who dropped this
pineapple dream catches I loved the
dream catches when I was
younger I used to have a lot of dream
catches and I think my mom made them for
me too or or it was the lady from like
the daycare after uh junior not Junior
High the thing that's Elementary School
anyway I love I love dream catches cute
cute cute
[Music]
cute I don't have them anymore now but I
think dream catchers are even even just
as a decoration even when you don't
believe in their cause
anymore even has decoration I think
they're
beautiful I think rmt actually has a
dream catcher or something like that
hanging in the living
room of the apartment where I lived
before
but like a not a childish looking one
more like
a a ma m mature looking
one they they are super lovely and you
can make them with feathers and you know
as a phoenix of course I like to do some
stuff with my feathers just like these
these two dudes are doing it right now
oh he
died oh no she was bringing him feathers
my sure drink adult drink shut
up after his passing she left and never
returns and that's how she decided to
never eat pineapple pizza ever
again they are gone from our forest
there is no time to grieve remember
those who have passed and they will
forever live
on did I finish the DLC now or is it
still not over achievement unlock the
cycle I think I think it's done it
sounds like the story is
done it's the mama backstory yeah I I
felt there was something like that mhm I
[Music]
did nice DLC tells you I guess a
background story of a part of the of one
part of the parents that you normally if
you play the game normally wouldn't hear
anything about I
[Music]
guess
n that was
nice what is this beautiful
Oasis I like these um pearls or uh
marbles as well that would be nice
decoration as well and maybe not that
big like um compared to let's say ory is
the size of
Me Maybe Just smaller than that that
would be a cool decoration that home as
well and in the background is that
shells on on Fred
nice yeah that's pretty and wait that's
the treeh house there like there's like
stairs going up to the tree oh cool and
the that chair in the background I'm
waiting for a chair like that for my
balcony since um since the end of spring
when I ordered it and they said they
were delivered in summer and then in
summer they sent me a notice that it's
going to be delivered in
February and I was like what do you mean
February that must be a mistake but
apparently they mean February
2022 so I wanted that that balcony chair
you know the swinging one I wanted that
for the summer to hang out on my
balcony but I don't need it in
February I don't need it in February
when it's snowing and ass cold
you don't really say ass cold in in
English do you we say it in German a lot
Ash cut 9 month delivery yeah I think
they kind of ran out of that furniture
and I suppose there's an issue with
restocking
it onee
delivery onee delivery I don't know what
happened there it's like one of the
bigger
um it's it's not just some random ass
furniture place it's one of one of the
bigger ones not Ikea or so but one of
the big ones in my
country pisses me off man but I
already kind of forgot about it this
this reminded me of it it's been so long
that I forgot about that piece of
furniture
anyway game
saved H I wonder if I should continue
this is kind of I said I don't want to
play too long and maybe playing any
longer than this isn't a good idea
either maybe I should rest my
thumbs we only really did the DLC though
we didn't do much progress with the
actual game at all though I feel
[Music]
like
I have that I ordered
what I ordered what from
GLA you mean the merchandise time flies
when you're having fun yeah it did end
up being uh it did end up going by much
faster than I thought it
would yeah looks like a perfect rest to
s yeah right I just want to be here
forever the forest looks perfectly fine
here or I think this is a good place to
grow old you have a treehouse in the
back you have a nice swing set you have
the ocean there yeah just stay here what
the hell you can eat fish from the ocean
probably don't don't care about the
forest stay stay here and have
fun I wouldn't mind living here for a
couple
years it's so
pretty even with this it's almost been 4
hours so I honestly also don't want to
make my way out of it I guess I could
teleport home oh oh that's why this
thing is here so I can teleport the hell
out of here and don't have to walk all
the way back where would I go
anyway if I were to continue where would
I
go where would be a good place to H
around around here maybe this one
or or that one and then go up here how
much do I have left of the
game um experienced people please tell
me
the giant tree
or giant
tree
tree a lot more I'd say you are like 50%
40% maybe I play a little bit
privately I always say that though and I
never
do which Gantry there's a lot of
gantries and then when went to you have
two3
more yeah makes sense Holo Groove
ah
H yeah okay and that's what I was
looking at no
h so I would probably continue here if I
play if I play it privately would you
guys say I should continue here and then
go up
here and then go here no go here I think
maybe maybe maybe I have a day off
tomorrow m i could also play some
Pokmon or Tales of R tomorrow if I play
anything at all maybe I'll just do
nothing because as a streamer who plays
games every day you know it's kind of
like you don't really quite feel the
desire to play games
anymore on your day off but I do need to
finish El so maybe that's what I'll do
tomorrow I think I want to move my
PlayStation over to the uh to my bedroom
TV and then play it in bed if I
can tell that to crony well but she
doesn't I'm just going to say she
doesn't stream as much as I do so she
she by far doesn't play games as much on
stream as I do so I think that's still a
big difference if I wouldn't stream that
much not trying to roast her okay I
think it's cool that she um you know
takes time for herself and all that I I
wish I wouldn't feel so um I mean I
there's part of me who feels like I am
obligated to stream this much you know
but then there's another part of me who
of course enjoys all of this and I want
I want to be with you guys as much as I
am so I'm not complaining you know but
if I were to stream less I would
probably be able to play more games
privately as well
because then I wouldn't have anything
else to do then I would be
[Music]
bored yeah you got just as a streamer
you got to find your balance you got to
find your streaming Style no one said
that everyone in whole life has to
stream uh 100 plus hours per month and
not everyone in whole life does so
that's perfectly fine people like auki
sfire for example as well I also don't
stream that much right auki sampai I
think Aqua sampai I am a sampai no you
do you you you find the way the
streaming style the lifestyle fits well
the way that you don't feel like you're
putting too much pressure on your own
mental health yeah if you have a job
like that where you can control all of
that on your own anyway then you better
take advantage of that I am so glad that
I have a job where I can decide when I
stream how long I
stream and I can say I'm going to on a
vacation right now because I'm not
feeling good this is such a blessing and
I hope that I can keep this going for as
long as
possible yeah and I don't know there
might be a time where I will also stream
Less in general for a
while that might happen as well for at
some point I don't I don't think I can
keep this up forever
either I will try to keep it up as long
as possible though cuz I do I do enjoy
these making these memories with you
guys playing these games with you
appreciating beautiful beautiful
masterpieces because you know this is
like this is Art I mean look at it
people
say anything can be art and if anything
can be art then this is definitely art
so we're always looking at beautiful art
as well while we're playing this gam and
I think that aspect should
be focused on as well mhm mhm I do
appreciate some beautiful art with you
guys this is much more fun than going to
a museum Art
Gallery sorry I don't know why I'm just
bouncing around
here PE fireworks
yeah oh by the way guys I've been I've
been thinking about what to do for New
Year's Eve because I'm spending
Christmas with my family mom and my
brother and my uh half
sister and and so on we're spending
Christmas together but I think New
Year's Eve I'll be spending on my own or
I mean I could spend it with my friends
if I wanted to but I don't know I want
to do the countdown with you guys again
but at the same time I want to see um
the fireworks from a good spot
M because last year when I was in Japan
I couldn't see fireworks because there
were no fireworks at
midnight so I guess I could just uh
since there's time zones I could
celebrate other countdowns with you guys
I guess and act as if it happened for me
as
well I guess yeah but would that be so
special for you guys cuz it's kind of
different you guys know that then it's
not my countdown
yet ah am did that as well last year
oh cuz I do want to if I can't spend
Christmas properly with you guys then I
do want to spend New Year's Eve in some
way with you
guys yeah I'll definitely stream on that
day I but I also want to go check out
fireworks
yeah I think I'm going to chill on some
rooftop bar or something like that and
check out the fireworks hell yeah H but
you know in places like that uh you know
what kind of people will be there Party
People social people who drink alcohol
and they like whoop who whoop and they
dance and stuff and they're like
flirting with another and grinding on
one another whatever oh I want to be in
the place like that I feel uncomfortable
in the place can I have like a nerdy
Rooftop Bar I need a nerdy Ro maybe I
just rent a whole Rooftop Bar to
myself and invite my friends invite my
BFF cuz like ah I'm not the bar type of
person I'm not the Disco type of person
anything like that I I don't feel
comfortable in a place like
that touch grass sometimes as well I
want to touch the sky hi hi hi
to space t me through the
sky that was
random my English is the easiest to
understand among your friends I often
hear that from Japanese people saying
that my English is the easiest to
understand I guess because the
vocabulary that I use is very limited
and a baby
language and I try to speak clearly I
guess I just don't have some kind
of weird English accent H although
sometimes I feel
like you other girls speak way clearer
English than they than I do ah but I
guess they speak
faster they speak faster than me I think
cuz I I I need to take time to pronounce
every word properly that's why I speak
slow
[Music]
well
I just use either words and sentences
yeah I think so too I speak more clearly
really I do try to do that but when I
listen to myself I don't quite agree
with
that just chatting here hanging out in
the Oasis having a good time guys want a
pina
colada I can make one for you maybe I'll
just order
one you clear of your words oh well I'm
happy to hear that cuz I feel like in
the past
um
especially before whole life but also in
the beginning of of my time at H life
when I listen back to those old streams
it might also partially be the mic
microphone but I I do feel like my
English was not as clear as it is as it
is
now uh back then
but maybe that's just
me your accent was so much stronger
really you're rarely Mumble and and no
she probably that's better than a lot of
you you think so but I do think recently
I've been stumbling over my words so
much and repeating the beginning of
sentences so much I feel like I started
to
stutter have you noticed that because it
really pisses me
[Laughter]
off
no hav not really I keep on cutting
myself
off even when I haven't said anything
wrong even when I started the sentence
correctly I cut myself off and start
over again you got to um pay some
attention to it and then you might
notice today as well I did it so
often I'm too accommodative of you n
you're used to
me locational Japanese probably helps in
the Japanese yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah I guess maybe maybe it
was also because I was distracted by the
game maybe or is doing parkour the whole
time well anyway okay then I guess let's
read some super chats and
then make an end to
it yeah I guess let's do
[Music]
that I still got
strawberries I still have one
M I cut them up by 1 2 3 4 5 six yum yum
yum
[Music]
yum thank you for the great gameplay
thank you for watching and having
patience with
me I think we had
um just a few tiny rough patches but
overall it was much better than last
time
so I think I'll give
it a chance and continue with
it um yeah I guess I'll do another or
stream next
week but if we're only one3 through the
main
game
then uh I think it will need two more
streams I will not force myself to
finish it in one stream I think doing
like 3 hours three hours or so would be
good uh m m yeah now I have many many
more abilities that I wouldn't have
otherwise and they will probably help
[Music]
me
T happy early
birthday nice I'll read you Super Chat
properly
afterwards I think you can finish it in
two streams I hope
so thank you for streaming I love
listening to your energy every every
morning thank you you don't always have
to do fin out streams you can just
finish it no no uh it's the thing is the
thing is like I kind of need to plan it
out because I don't want to play let's
say let's say I don't plan it out
properly like
that um and I say I'll just play and see
what happens what I don't want to happen
is let's say that I have 100% left and
in the next stream I would play
80% because I didn't know there was only
20% left and I didn't you know separate
it properly then the stream after that
would only be 20% would be super short
so that's the kind of stuff I'm trying
to avoid to have like only 1 hour of
streaming time
left in another uh in the following
stream that's why I ask you guys how
much uh time you think is left in the
game yeah no it's better to balance it
out so that the parts are uh a good
length yeah yeah
yeah you can always switch your another
game if you end quickly
no um I at least not in the same stream
and I don't want to make a new stream
because then the one stream would be so
short I want my streams to have a good
length I don't want to end the stream at
like 40 minutes or so because I I
finished the game earlier than I thought
but doing it in the same stream is also
you got to think of it in a streamer
point of view you know doing it doing
two different games in one stream even
if we have the permission to do that for
certain games maybe then I think it
might still be kind
of not disrespectful but weird towards
the game creators now this is a thing
that you can maybe on Twitch I guess a
lot of people do it on Twitch they do
long streams and they start by
chitchatting and then play a game and
then play another game and so on but if
I advertise a certain
stream as a certain game and also have
that game in the thumbnail then I'm not
going to immedi uh uh suddenly switch
onto a different game that's
like if the thumbnail is or then I'm not
going to suddenly play
Pokmon
yeah
oh if if I were to open up a different
stream okay then that's that's fine but
I wouldn't want to do it in the same
stream
mhm
M office
[Music]
time and anyone here who saw my burp on
my head for the first time
today I got that addition
yesterday CI has finally landed and
perched on my
head
finally the day that we've all been
waiting
for best bu yeah the office looks so
cozy it does it's so
Christmasy
[Music]
also today I think it was at the dentist
in the radio they were playing Mariah
Carey All I Want For Christmas Is You
All I Want For Christmas Is
[Music]
You yeah oh that reminds me I kind of
wanted to play this ore music in the
background but you know what now I want
to hear Christmas music did I save in
the game I did right I was I saved and
then I started jumping around let me
save one more time just in case and then
close it
okay I want to play Christmas music
let's see let's see what kind of
Christmas music uh what oops dropped my
controller what kind of Christmas music
audio Stu
has audio stuck the music that Amit
chose yesterday and was playing you know
what that reminded me of maybe I
shouldn't say
it I said it sounded
sensual did you did you guys hear it too
it sounded very sensual I
think it sounded
sexy it sounded like a censal
advertisement music that's all I'm going
to
say
okay no
[Music]
audio
stock uh don't I shouldn't choose the
the first ones that come out here huh
but there's a jingle I think Jingle Bell
has no copyright right so if it's an
arrangement from audio stock we have
rides to the audio stock stuff so it
should be fun so for example if I were
to play
this St what is this
this is supposedly jingle
ah
oh OD
[Music]
do hey jingle bells jingle no kind of I
I don't know I don't know how that one
works oh you may
Christmas
[Music]
OD We wish you a Merry Christmas we wish
you a Merry Christmas and a Happy New
Year can I really play this song on my
stream or will I get bunked I will risk
it anywhere cuz dmca can't get
[Music]
me oh was
that what's this one
go AIO St what's this one AIO St oh I
get it the song is called audio
St wait that's still the same one
a I thought it was a
[Music]
mlay
Lo
[Music]
Christmas
St all your
stks oh H ho
ho St were you not you nice this year
jimins H this a nice
s but I don't know how that would sound
as a super chat reading
bgm hey this is the kind of obnoxious
Christmas music that I was looking
[Music]
for it's a merry chist
Christmas in
[Music]
town
yeah all I want for
Christmas you
oh is
[Music]
dark okay I love that that's calm and
not too
obnoxious only the first 10 so so what
so what
my office is ready for Christmas let's
[Music]
go I'm taking this this is wonderful
this makes me go doky dokie this makes
me feel so warm inside I bought I bought
I bought um hot chocolate uh powder
thing you normally
uh uh I don't do that because I feel
like every hot chocolate powder that I B
in the supermarket or so uh it never
ends up really tasting like good hot
chocolate that I get in like a in know
in a cafe or a restaurant so I kind of
gave up on it but I'm trying again with
a different brand uh I think it's a
Australian brand called uh Mana yeah I
think it must be Australian because
people always bring that as a sorry as a
um Omi as a souvenir as
well Manor chocolate we have this
chocolate
in in Australia that's uh called Manor m
a n n e r e r like
manners uh and yeah they not only make
chocolate but they also make
chocolate drink powder thing as as well
apparently so I'm going to try this one
out I'm going to test you tell you after
I tested it if it's good or
not never heard of that here in the US
if you ever come to Australia then it's
of the souvenirs that you should bring
home we have you know because Mozart was
born in Australia so we have a lot of
Mozart Chocolate they're called Mozart
kouan kugan so it's like Mo Mozart's
balls
huh it's it's chocolate balls um yeah mo
mo
mo chocolate balls you can take them
home as a Sou it's a famous souvenir
I'll take
20 yeah and depending on the company
there's uh some that are considered to
be fake and some that are considered to
be the real moad balls and and the
inside is generally similar similar
because it has like maripan maripan
maripan how do you say that in English
maripan cuz in Japanese it's
maripan uh they have that inside but uh
they are only a little bit different
depending on the morat ball anyway what
I'm saying is that if you ever go to
Australia then you basically have two
famous choices of souvenirs I would say
actually I mean of course there's more
you could also bring home a Saka uh cake
from the famous Saka Hotel yes yes you
can bring it home it actually um doesn't
go bad that quickly so it's a
great cake yeah hell yeah hell
yeah yes yeah yeah I don't like them by
the way because I do not like maripan
maripan I don't like
it so yeah the the Mozart balls pretty
much always have that
inside is this too loud do you hear this
is this too quiet or too loud or
[Music]
perfect yeah I don't like
marip
[Music]
okay but is maripan is being used in
confectionary in Australia and I think
in Germany as well quite often it's
pretty popular so I thought it was a
normal thing growing up here but when I
went to Japan for example they don't use
Mar Japan at
all yeah I have looked around and it
seems to be a really rare thing in Japan
I think it's just very common in Europe
do you guys have it a lot in
na or any other
countries the maybe it's just popular in
Europe maybe it's one of those things
that are very common in Europe not a big
thing in the US either
really in the UK we do don't worry I
still see you as part of us when I talk
about Europe uh uh the EU I'm kind of
also always in my mind including you
guys just whenever I talk about you
think I'm including
you
[Music]
thank you you're
welcome the pend on which area in within
the
[Music]
US
anyway let's read some super chats okay
while listening to this really cute and
calm Christmas music yeah and by the way
tomorrow I think is my day off let's go
I gave myself two days off this week
holy moly I'm so proud of myself wow wow
[Music]
wow
wow rest day yeah I don't know I think
I'll CLE my apartment and
I'll um I will uh play tailes of arice
maybe
and uh is there something I need to do I
always need to do things no I'll just
take care of some
things but I have no doctor's
appointment
tomorrow yeah I have the whole day to
myself
why are there so many cat hairs on my
face God damn
it noal whole life homework no there's
always a whole life
homework will Christmas Day collab of
all Yan
members maybe one day before Christmas
or one day after Christmas maybe I don't
know if we can
actually get all together on
Christmas because I think this year
everyone's kind of prioritizing their
family a bit
more although you guys are my family
don't take it wrong okay don't don't
don't get it wrong you guys are my
family too but I can't be in two places
at once not
really you understand yeah yeah book
book
book family oaba
family seems like you guys didn't get to
see family at all last Christmas yeah
Last Christmas I mean I was I was in L
Japan for one
year so I was not able to see them which
is okay I mean I'm I'm a grownup I I can
take a while without seeing my family
actually this kind of been like for my
whole life
uh not my whole life but uh for for a
long time since my teenage H I've been
mostly been on the road like I've been
here and there and everywhere and
haven't seen my family in a long time in
many occasions so I'm kind of used to it
yeah but this year spent with oaba
family oaba
oh my God there's like so many blue Sila
chats there's like millions of
them wow what's oh have
[Music]
it I want to grab that
yeah one last strawberry last
strawberry come in my tummy for the very
last time I'll eat you all
[Music]
up isn't this cute the
art so
[Music]
cute I am new here and I'm a fan of your
friends and you thank you
[Music]
welcome all right I guess I'll work
myself through these super chats
now Monument reminder stream frog D
close to a million
really let me
[Music]
see where's M
frog
oh it's so
close oh there's only like 5,000 views
until 1 million views on M
[Music]
frog that's my best one that's the first
one and the legendary one
M oh my god well well deserved frog Yana
oh look at look at her happily spinning
down there she's spinning towards one
[Music]
million huh I swear you once mentioned
wanting to interview someone special for
H talk on your anniversary since that
passed what did you have in mind
oh
uh I cannot say because it's not
actually happening after all I kind of
forgot about
that
uh
[Music]
H
uh I
forgot I forgot I was going to do that
and I didn't really have the time to
plan it out either but uh I will bring
that special guest in eventually maybe
maybe for the 30th
episode the 20th is coming up so
soon I I guess I kind of want to keep it
keep that uh excitement still for
another time I don't even know it's
going to if it's going to work out
but
[Music]
25 H it doesn't sound so
special the number doesn't sound so spe
so
special second year
anniversary you think it will take me
that
long I'll figure something
[Music]
out H for the next little talk I already
know who I'm calling
over
and
so yeah the next guest is already
decided and it will be next week next
whole talk next
[Music]
week I will not tell you yet who I'm
bringing in but it's not a difficult
member to
contact
[Music]
thank
you thank you for the red super chat
sh hi today is an important day to me
because I became a uniform chicken oh
let's go thank you for a great time in
the past 6 months I will keep supporting
you in the future I can't wait to see
the new
Merchants a merchandise and put them on
I love orange thank you I'm glad you
like orange orange is a good color
yeah people should wear more orange hell
yeah thank you thank you for planning on
getting that merchandise I hope you will
like
it still going to take a while
but although from what I've heard is
that omocat delivery doesn't take that
long
yeah I don't know for sure though but I
heard that usually at least for example
in America it really comes fast but even
outside of America
America why is there no car brand that's
called
Americar wouldn't that be a
genius
H anyway fainu thank you so much for
your support and thank you for working
for kfp yeah hoping to count on your
support in the future as well than
ta D proud of you for doing
your daily stretches D I didn't do them
today Rocka dear s d for the pinky yeah
how many cats do you think you'd be able
to take care of at once there's a Korean
YouTuber Who currently owns 10 I think I
know who you mean could you manage that
or is this too many cats I think I could
manage but if I had the choice I I would
manage less at the moment yeah that's
why I didn't adopt any more cats even
though I kind of wanted it but I feel
like uh my current two cats there they
would be probably kind of
jealous if I got more
cats and I already got my hands full of
them to be honest I mean I can handle
more
but like
recently when we're watching yes we when
we watching Netflix with one with my
left hand i'm petting chunkers and with
my right hand i'm petting um smoothie
smoothie sitting on the higher pillow
right next to me and junker sitting in a
cardboard box next to my pillow yeah I'm
very busy with my
arms no I do think I could manage a
third one
but the question is if my cats will
forus give
me cuz it also means that they will get
a little bit less attention and I don't
want to do that to
them I don't want to do that yeah trun
likes to sleep in a cardboard box right
next to my
pillow so I literally have a cardboard
shoe box on my bed next to my pillow at
all
times
[Music]
yeah
and that box that I currently am using
it has two holes uh one on each
side only two sides and um yesterday I
was like poking my finger through it and
playing with smoovie yes smoovie smoovie
stole the box for a moment to play with
me she went so
crazy I was poking my fing up her and
she was attacking it even though she
knew exactly what I was doing she knew
it was me but we were having so much
fun
boxes are so
versatile cardboard boxes so versatile
[Music]
H hell
yeah
b73
[Music]
D oh oh oh oh I'm reading it
quietly thank you
[Music]
Dynamo thank you for listening to Sparks
and I'm glad it was able to help you and
motivate you and bring you back up on
your
feet always keep on going always look
forward
yeah and and I I um had a similar
experience before when it comes to
school so I know how it feels I was very
ashamed and devastated as well I can
relate to that but but look at where I
am now so I think you really shouldn't
be too hard on
yourself
failing in school is is
really not something that should Define
you I know they I know when you're in
school it makes you feel like that's
what life is all about right now and if
you're not doing well at school if you
get really bad grades and you get maybe
stuck in a in in class while all your
other classmates move
on I know it must feel like you too
stupid for life that's how I
felt no I just felt like
I I was just in unable to learn when it
came to mathematics at
[Music]
least but you
know you're going to figure out your own
way of living
life and as much as I think people
really only say that for example you
need certain things later in life as
well because they want you to do your
best in school but it turns out you
really don't need a lot of these things
that you learned
there but you should still work hard so
that's important to do your best and if
there's things that you feel like you
really can't do then don't feel bad
about we all have our limits we're all
human or
[Music]
phoenixes as I said don't Define
Yourself by these kind of
things you have other strengths
somewhere else then yeah just like me
H we all have our strengths being strong
and our weaknesses being
weak as a certain whole life member once
said Mom G thank you for the two
[Music]
pinkies hello Tel I can't wait to share
this good news of you and kfb that is I
have successfully accepted a new job
another one although these past 3 months
have that have not gone well have been
very tormenting for me but now I am both
excited and happy for this I want to
thank you whenever I am down or
frustrated your live broadcasts give me
a lot of motivation it is your laughter
and screams that make me teer up again
and again I love kfp and love you
forever thank you I love you
too congratulations on your job good
job that bird why would you ask such a
question no of course it
[Music]
doesn't congratulations yeah I'm proud
of you
m I knew you could do
it we both knew yes yes I hope that it
will be a great job I hope the people
will treat you well and that you will be
happy there as long as
possible thank you so much for your
support and I wish you a lot of success
Mommy
G Val thank you for the pinky I wanted
to send this during whole talk but
thanks for always entertaining us K of
course I'm trying my
best sometimes I I feel like
I'm even though I try my best I'm I just
not have the full ability to really
entertain a as much as I wanted to but
as long as you guys feel entertained and
I guess I am succeeding thank you so
much
meow sad L
showy right d congratulations to get out
of your egg oh wait you say that's a
pinky it doesn't get recognized I need
to tell uh need to fix that in the in
the Chrome extension uh one second let
me let me note that down before I forget
it so I don't miss out on these things
wait one one moment
[Music]
um
uh uh uh uh uhuh uh
[Music]
um so that's really a pinky right I I
can be sure of that
right EG EGP
[Music]
okay it has been noted down thank you
for the pinky I finally out of the egg
to celebrate here is my first pink Super
Chat I look forward to the journey of
becoming fried and I'm grateful to the
journey I had till now
a oh it's so sweet when my chickens grow
up but they grow up so fast I first
discovered you N9 months ago my life
became more fun because of that thank
you oh thank you to
oh I'm so happy to hear that thank you
please stay with kfp let's have some
awesome times together make nice
memories play amazing
games yeah let's just have fun thank you
so much for your
support I blinked and I was in a bucket
oh oops
oopsie when do we get fried again after
one one year of
membership Patrick teror M D Toran
D ah don't worry I actually I think it
was not only on Steam on sale it was
also on the Nintendo shop on sale
because I definitely bought one of the
or games I think it was a sequel um I
bought it very very much cheaper than it
usually
is I already have it thank you
D D D D this is where the blue Super
Chat
start Toran Jacob
D
Kate CH for cotton chicken R cotton
marel marel tea L
Lounge
Kate did you guys expect me to read all
[Music]
these
y
k no you didn't
Lord the Lord see the evil black
Mo you know what can I leave out the
bot it feels so wrong though it feels so
wrong I want to do it to save time and
my voice but it feels I can't it's like
a
reflex I'll try B fra for J SW say it I
want to say
[Music]
it g cotton B forac Elan cting chickens
Kitty to H Daisy tea loue Jacobite koton
Kate R GD me lag Anon M forac Daisy
forac GD ya Las
Fa for I need to really focus do not say
it
[Music]
forac coton Dy Rana GD da forx bigwig
high fructose corn syrup Rana suu lemon
coton forac Daisy f g pountain chickens
Anon M forac Jacob cotton M lagen high
fructose corn syum Kitty tole for Daisy
sad H
nighton forac Papa Anon M coton un Chad
forac Daisy cotton Laz whale G rag forac
Anon M counting chickens all
night for for everyone who joined later
in the Stream and uh I want to explain
that in the beginning of this today's
stream there was a section where I was
trying to get from the bottom of the
forest to the top of of the forest
because from the bottom to the top the
water was rising and I was like really
quickly running away away from it and
climbing and zooming away from it and it
was quite a
challenge that's why people sent like a
million of blue super chats flushing
like the water was uh coming after
me uh
for Daisy faon forac J jaob 47 black G
forac night fish mlen Leva coton Kate
Rana forac Anon for I can't this is all
the same
names cot no it was not a super long
Idol
meeting so Daisy FR screw H Night P CH
taii forac sub GD maen forac Rana Anon M
black F taii Daisy mlen forac Anon M
Hollow night forac you guys were doing
teamwork yo
respect for G fa
counting chickens Rana taii Sy Rita Anon
Jacob night forac
Rana
for for this was going on for quite some
time Anon M for TI H night Daisy black
Chan Rana for J Anon M big for Rita
[Music]
TI
for Ryan bince a new one cous beats GD
ta for FAA weather hacker Anon M for Tai
raana Daisy GD for
Anon Jacob NX brutal
Fredy oh this is where the flood ends
[Music]
okay back to
normal
Harry Oreo
cookie Daisy
Anon thank you for the pinky
congratulations on beating the one of
the most difficult parts of this
game it's the worst for me
really I mean it's it needed several
tries but because of the speed I guess
it was difficult but the mechanics and
the the
logic and all that I think the level
design was
easy yeah you just got to be fast and
and maybe try a few times to be able to
know what comes at what point so that
you know where to
land but I'm happy you say that that
makes me feel a bit more confident and
M the other parts are more difficult to
me yeah I can imagine the game will get
a bit more difficult
though most people have to restart from
the very bottom oh damn yeah that that's
pretty bad cuz it even felt very long to
me with the checkpoint
[Music]
M now imagine without the checkpoint oh
my
God b h
black thank you looking for
[Music]
a squeak EES what were we talking about
there you say in America they are called
speak eases what is
that what is that what were we talking
[Music]
about oh the the secret bars what why
are they called that that sounds weird
speak speak
eases what does that mean because it's
easy to speak about
them why why that
name secret bar during
prohibition from Pro what's
prohibition probation
era what is
[Music]
that where alcohol was
illegal
h a alcohol
was completely illegal before in
[Music]
America
what wait is that a common thing all
over the world because why why why why
did why why for example drink did did
did Henry in the tutors in the medieval
times already drink
wine oh just a okay okay then then I
guess that's why I never heard of
something like that before
a
oh hey
is that
why is that why in America you got to
hide the alcohol when you have when you
drink it like outside you got to hide it
in like a back that's not
seethrough is that basically the
evolution of
that I think that's so funny because
it's so obvious that you're drinking
alcohol if if you have it in a bag like
that it makes it even more
obvious
oh
[Music]
man it's legal you don't have to hide it
anymore since when one one public
drinking is
illegal
what that's so I mean I don't drink
alcohol so I don't give a but it's
just weird because it's not illegal here
in Europe right we can drink on the
Street if we want
to that's so
funny can I roast you guys can I roast
America for one
second aren't you
guys supposed to be the land of the
freedom is isn't that your
slogan isn't that when you're
advertising
[Laughter]
I mean honestly though you got to you
got to put a line somewhere you got to
draw a line of course it would be crazy
if you could be free to do literally
anything like anything like you know
anything kill people
obviously that's not
good but yeah that's that's a weird
thing because in Europe it's just so
normal
m not the hold I learned some I learned
some new
[Music]
things EST
land Yum
Yum
[Music]
Yum botom
FR uh wait Wy Tunes D should I miss that
one there's a place in La when you where
you go to a rundown office building and
there's a secretary at a front desk she
puts you in a small closet but then a
door opens up to steps that lead down to
a nightclub that's cool that sounds like
something out of out of a movie
again bottom frager d
h d you guys were sending some really
weird super chats today like Castle
funds and the whole flood the water
flooding J swack some Prince danan Cy
danan R fre
[Music]
danan
what gamer Robin Anson
[Music]
D what's a tall
tail what's a tall tail t a l l
[Music]
tail
a myth
ah shouldn't that be a Telltale not a
tall
[Music]
tale which out of these do you want to
be if you wearing a tall
tail thought it was a
Telltale not a tall tail fire find a
daredevil Matador import youo wrestler
rocker astronaut private eye jet P pilot
or time
traveler
time
traveler of course that's so much more
powerful tell tail is a game
[Music]
[Laughter]
company but you know I thought because
you tell a
tail
[Music]
blaz thank you for the red super
chatama tomorrow is my birthday thank
you always for making me smile and
everything by the way the membership is
going to 6 months next week sorry for
the poor English love you no problem
your English is very easy to understand
for me don't worry about it h I guess
[Music]
I if you don't mind I'll wish you a
happy early birthday some people say it
brings bad luck but you're literally
telling me about it so I feel like
you're asking for it happy
[Music]
birthday early
birthday I hope you will have a
wonderful birthday and a wonderful life
ahead of you
yeah of course for the rest of your life
you will also have to work for kfp
though so I guess that's a guarantee to
a wonderful
[Music]
life thank you so much for your support
and yeah 6 months so you're about to get
into your uniform right nice your
uniform is ready and waiting in your
closet thank you for your hard
work Halo infinite comp
P
Halo
Halo I know I've heard of Halo
but
Halo I don't know if I want that to be
my first fpn H I don't know how would
that work if I it's a campaign is that
like a DLC or or what how does that work
if I were to play the campaign only what
is a
[Music]
campaign I don't even know if I can play
it
though ah ah it's a ah it's a story line
ah uhh yeah yeah I guess I've seen it
being used like that before
[Music]
mhm also there's a new story line
coming but to be honest I I wouldn't
mind getting some new recommendations
from you guys again not right now but
like uh maybe on a community
post H for single player FPS games
because I don't know when my freaking
PS5 will arrive so I'm just like I guess
I'll play something else then
M and get started because I I promise
you guys I'll try the
genre I promise you guys and I don't
want to have you guys wait for too
long yeah I don't know about this
honored either at the moment I can't
play it
so and death loop I would have to wait
ah or I can give it a try ah
maybe but then there was so many people
saying that it might not work on my PC
blah blah blah I just don't want to have
a
stream that kind of hyped up because
it's my first FPS game and I'm getting
like excited about it and then I start
playing and then I have all these issues
of streaming it you see I don't want
that to
happen that would be very sad
[Music]
Bioshock isn't that one of those that my
mom have been recommending to me
too portal
oh
portal
[Music]
portal wouldn't portal be kind of
fun ah it's puzzle no more puzzle
[Music]
please okay maybe Bioshock I don't know
I don't is that I told you guys isn't
that the like a science science fiction
one sci-fi not science fiction wait
that's the same thing right I told you
guys I don't really I don't really like
that no wait that's the but that one has
the the pretty
lady
uhhuh no not fortnite no I said single
player is that single
player not
fortnite
[Music]
no uh I think we're talked about
Bioshock before though but there's so
many you guys are saying Bioshock you
guys are talking about BioShock
[Music]
Infinite anyway I told you guys to not
give me recommendations now cuz I will
forget about it anyway I need it to all
be written down in something that I can
look back on and research one by one
slowly oh that's the worst one oh
okay okay anyway uh back to the topic R
free
[Music]
d AIO St onio St onio stock all the way
oh what f is right in the one open oh
areio St AIO St AIO St all the way oh
what fun you could have changed those
lyrics up a little bit more more like
like something like oh what fun it is to
browse on you stuck all day hey see that
even rhymed with slay oh my God and it's
and it rhymed with
whey I should become a lyric writer CRA
you're
out kak dun the shortest giant dun oh hi
T my family is going skiing in Australia
later this month oh any food or drink I
should try while I'm there aside from CF
of course love the stream so please keep
them coming but remember to take care of
yourself at the end of
December then you should be able to make
it to Christmas markets too if they open
again they should open again once the
lockdown is uh over and I think it was
like uh was it the 12th of December or
so I think so when you come they should
be open again in that case go to
Christmas Market and drink some glue
Vine and and you know the the typical uh
anything at the Christmas Market to get
that experience and besides that you
should eat the following things um
schnitzel H classic with wh PR
bear
M normally they should always serve it
with that don't be afraid to use the jam
they bring a jam that you should eat it
with uh you need to combine the meat
with the jam yes it's
yummy uh you could also eat
[Music]
um uh h a dessert that I love it's it
doesn't look like super fancy but I love
it it's so yummy it's called
kaisar Uh and then uh uh oh uh an
Australian soft drink that I normally
wouldn't always go for but it is quite
yummy um it's an
herbal uh fuzzy soft drink it's called
I'm
D I'm dudla they have this funny um
advertisement where they
yell I'm
[Music]
D in the AL
yeah it's
nice it does taste really good too you
you definitely should um find a place
that sells s Tor basically they have
it's it's the famous cake from Australia
a chocolate cake you could either find
it in a Saka hotel but you can also find
the original Saka Tor in other places in
in stores or or also not even the
original you don't have to go for the
original other places that are not the
Saka Hotel still make the s t and do a
good job at it so you should find you
should find the cake in like
a a a
patier in a in a cake
place and and then another food that's
very famous in Australia would be uh
taffel
Spitz which
is in order to cook it it takes a lot of
uh
effort it's yummy it's with meat and
stuff maybe Google it I mean I wouldn't
say it's the most yummy thing ever I
think schnit is still yummier but T
Spitz is very Australian yeah and
then are there any famous seafood dishes
customed to
Australia to Australia probably but not
to AUST
Australia I don't think
so um what
else I
mean if you come from up there now this
might not be originally Australian but I
think you should go for goulash as well
we make some great gulash there's
several types there's a Rin goulash with
beef eh beef there's he H gash H is a
elk I think then there is a h potato
cartel
[Music]
gash uh and all that but the best one is
still like the one with the beef or with
the elk I guess rabbit and
potato um I do love the potato gulash as
well but the the meat ones I think are
more impressive to you ah it's deer not
alkoh
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay curle yeah canle canle I think
canle is also served with The tavish
Spits I
think San canoodle saetan canoodle is a
a
popular
side uh in in German I think and
Australian kitchen I think not only
Australian do they use svod in
Germany yeah this is the word
svod cloud holy moly I love Road Clouts
anything with Road clout no
um I think that's all I can think of
right now but but if you like desserts
and I also recommend something like
Maran they have several variations it
could also beet G noodle or a
bearle etc and these are um
Marilla are the fruit inside of the
noodle it's like a yummy dumpling and
they're they're served with brel h brel
is like crumbles of like uh
something H oh yeah um SP yeah uh yeah
blah blah s feel ESS
yeah but I that's a that's a simple
dessert that uh I always enjoy to eat
mhm C oh yeah if you go to the
supermarket to the bread section you can
probably also find
CRA Le oh that's a good idea if you need
a snack if you need a snack listen up
you either go to one of those places
that sell meat like uh separately from a
supermarket just like the meat places
what do you call them or to supermarket
to the meat section and tell them you
want a a
li sem because you're going to Australia
you say seml and not veal or anything
cuz we call it
seml uh Sam Sam is the
bread you can also pronounce it a sem
labor C and if you want to enhance your
labor C sem even more then you say
miten yeah a butcher m guen is with
pickles or you say you wanted with uh M
um uh
uh uh what was that thing that looks
like a looks like
um
no no no I know G is actually cucumber
but in this situation it's a
pickle there we in in German in
Australia at least we call H
pickles and but we also call
[Music]
cucumbers but shortly we just
say H I want to say what's the thing
that looks like um like a like a what
was the word NE with
um looks like
paprika
paprika what is the word I often use
this one instead of gy it looks like a
chili but it's
not
uh looks like a
chili but it's not spicy Bel it looks
like pepperon yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
Leoni I like the one that are not spicy
this is a good combination
too this is how we eat Lea in in
Australia I think maybe in Germany
people prefer to just put ketchup on it
or whatever which I guess you can also
ask them to put ketchup or or
anything on it but I my usual order is
a with pickles with gu or with pepperoni
ah the pepperoni no it's not the
pepperoni it's a pepperoni it sounds
similar but it is not a
pepperoni it is not a
[Music]
pepperoni no no no no it's not the
peon okay is that enough for you did you
write it all down I don't even know if
you're here right now I didn't see you
uh the shortest giant did you write
everything
down not the
[Music]
pepperon ah Peppa cor okay I see you in
the chat so I guess you wrote it down
you
better please enjoy yourself and I hope
um that you're not going to have any
accidents when
[Music]
skiing yeah the Babalon you know the
Babalon the
balone yes yes all right have fun
uh so I am a
d Let me
refresh I was actually I was done with
the super chats I only had that one name
left but now here I am giving you five
million things to write
down the
pepponi you know I'm fine if someone
clips that because if someone ever asks
me the same question again I can tell
them to watch the clip that would
actually be helpful
JT d m
d thank you too you guys are
[Music]
sweet Johnny Bravo D looking for the
collab
D after the am am chest for I told only
about when you asked him if you teach
you chess and she was happy at the idea
of teaching your chess uh caching amator
for a thir match
if you're interested only but she felt
shy of contacting you so I'll play as a
wingman what you
[Music]
say
um no no it's just I'm kind of over
chess uh I I I I would
probably um I would probably get back
into it but I I think Amit is even more
uninterested when it comes to chess than
I am I don't think Amy wants to do it
anymore at
all yeah
uh the chess Arc if is over I
think yeah I'm a to in general I agree
no Puzzles anymore I want to do normal
collapse of
am I want to do other other kind of nut
puzzle collabs or like Minecraft just
even even Minecraft would be
fun or FPS yeah you see I think what
would be good is me playing uh a single
play FPS on my own sometime soon and
then doing a FPS collab with am yeah
yeah oh yeah bus feed quizes oh yeah I
wanted to I forgot about
that
oh bus feed
[Music]
ques I'm probably going to forget about
that
again no Apex nah nah n nah not
currently
interested unless I really really really
get addicted to FPS I don't see myself
playing Apex
if I really like the genre if I end up
really liking it and digging
it then maybe it happens but at the
moment I don't really see myself getting
too much into the
genre anyway Ezekiel thank you for the
pinky Hi boss I'm here to submit submit
my PTO request so that I can go play the
critically acclaimed mmpg ff14 which has
a free trial that includes an entirety
of A Realm Reborn and the awardwinning
heavens word up to level 60 with no
restrictions on
playtime
[Music]
cool understandable have a nice
day I don't know what what that means
though PTO
[Music]
request oh
man
these ff14 fans man they always
advertise their game like
this a personal pay time off personal
there's there's a difference there it's
important to know if the personal time
off is also paid time off is it
automatically considered to be paid or
is there this big difference between
paid time off and personal time
off is personal time off
paid is our time off
paid there is no time off that's the
problem
guys elt good d d thank you K is my hor
she always makes me smile when I'm
feeling down she's not afraid to show
how she feels and though she worries a
lot about doing her best and that makes
me respect her more I love you g d Sky
danin Dominque k danin
and Mary cat speaks
dun Eden dun you should check out prey
same makers is oh same makers is also
same
Publishers
pre pray the
game Aliens no I refuse no
no
no no thank
you alien sh
shooter sounds
[Music]
lame yeah yeah I'm open to be Loop and
Dishonored but but
no
no not no I don't at least not as my
First FPS I want something more
Charming something that has something
special about it yeah
yeah my mom's probably typing a message
again right
now my mom's
[Music]
like there's always portal yeah but
that's puzzles but but um I wouldn't
mind playing Portal sometime because
I've always heard portal is a funny game
and it just creates all these memes and
it's a Legendary game so at some point I
don't want to play that that's for
[Music]
sure is that the one that I
saw advertisements of on Twitter
yeah yeah you don't you guys don't have
to tell me about that game I got it on
my radar little K little kitty big city
I have that one on my radar so don't
worry once that comes out I'm playing
out sky D Dragon SP D for the pinky got
my Spotify WAP Spotify WAP results
results I'll give you one guess what was
my most listened song of 2021 hinted
with spikes have a good rest day
tomorrow thank you a it is quite the
honor for me that I would be even like
regularly listened voluntarily by anyone
so thank you to everyone who listen to
my music doesn't matter if it's on
Spotify anywhere really thank you very
much
Jo thank you Dragon
Fire no I'm not saying Halo isn't
special I'm sure it's a great amazing
game also I kind of talked about prey in
that moment I oh oh are you saying
because Halo is also an alien
shooter oh I just don't want to shoot
aliens this just sounds
so I don't want to shoot
[Music]
aliens m
H I just want to shoot something
else yeah I don't
know just just I'm sorry I'm sorry guys
I know you guys love your shooty games
the pew pew games I love I I I I love
you guys who love the shooty
games but I I uh if if I I'm I'm I'm
giving it a try okay don't worry and I'm
going to take you as a suggestions but
there's a
certain type of game I think that speaks
to me and a certain type of game that
doesn't hell yeah Turok I played that
when I was a
baby shooting demons that sounds
interesting but it sounds very dark
H I just want to play Death Loop
man
see I know people tell me to just
try it out but I don't want to spoil it
myself I want all the Impressions to be
on stream so that's problem number one
and then there's the other problem that
probably you know things go always
better behind the scenes and then when
it's actually the live stream then
things go bad and everything fails and
lags and yeah
glitches yeah it's always like
that it did get a
patch
when are you for realos
[Music]
now did it fix the problems you
say does someone know there Happ beened
two patches it got updated weeks
ago
[Music]
I know that death Loop is probably a bit
difficult for me
though what what do you think you guys
did you guys play Death
[Music]
Loop thank you thank you
asrael it's not that hard or that long
but you got to consider it I never
played FPS games any FPS will be kind of
difficult as your first one
H stealth yeah stealth is important huh
that's
okay that's okay I
mean that's that's better than you know
it being focused on puzzles or focused
on
strategy it has a lot of room for
creativity got stuff to do other than
shooting so it's kind of hard but it
just looks so interesting to me you know
what I don't care if it's difficult I'll
play
it okay e if you say that I got an
update then now I'm now you got
me
[Music]
wow
w
wow thank you for letting me
[Music]
know I need to go an idle meeting but
I'm done here Cy
Junction um last
[Music]
refresh TR there shortest giant D black
d Big D the chain TV d j x d v d
e and we're done we're
done thank you guys I had a chill time
with you guys
today had a fun
time thank
you saw how you played Outlast you have
a movement you have movement down pretty
d done well movement you
mean as a first person
[Music]
oh 263 times
nice what's my next
stream super liino on
Friday
[Music]
probably yeah next stream is super
Lial I'm taking a day off super
linal that game always looked so fun I
always saw like little Snippets of other
people playing it and it looked
funny
yeah you did a great job today thank you
was comfy I Wasing oh oh nice you're
welcome so looking forward to Super
linal if you like that you like portal
oh
okay big brain puzzle
solving yeah we tackle it although
that's a shitty attack but I'll tackle
it I'll use tackle my best
move no my best move is Brave Bird I'll
go all Brave Bird on super
[Music]
have you started eating
chocolate the chocolate I mentioned
yesterday you mean you mean the Advent
calendar calendar yeah yeah I ate that
one in the beginning of the stream it
was a bare chocolate if that's what you
meant I did that's the spirit hell
yeah
[Music]
okay
yeah open up your own Advent
calendar all right then I'll go now I'm
feeling chill I want to cuddle my kit
cats and in German we
say
I just got here you can watch the
archive and you can decide how fast you
want to watch it you can speed it up if
you want or you can like stop it at any
time to go get food that's like that's
like
pro pro vtuber watching Strate
strategies
mhm
yeah
in
my sweet lovely
chin
byebye me I'll see you guys the day
after tomorrow I'm
taking actually you know what if I end
the stream now oh it's like almost 48
hours oh you guys are going to miss me
right I'm going to miss you too 48 hours
without
me
you going to be okay
no that's
unfortunate
[Music]
W don't
cry don't
cry yeah you can catch up on my
vods Christmas Market on jelly I want to
go too
our Christmas Rockets are
closed when you say you're fine but
you're not really
fine I can still hear her yeah cuz I'm
still
here we don't have BS we're always here
uh not all of you but yeah there's some
some extremely addicted loyal chimkin
here
Aus h
oh I don't know about doomi yet if I can
I would love
to yeah thank
you oh thank you for renewing your
membership I found the Christmas Market
and I'm going
[Music]
noce never want to be cute you're
cute let's stream h no also M frog let's
stream everything but stream the remixes
please listen to my hot remixes while
I'm going yeah they're
[Music]
fire I love you
guys
love look into my
eyes you see the
love
[Music]
look do I need to get
closer
[Music]
hello
hello ah look look at my ti I went to
the dentist today
ah ah that was
exhausting that I was like ah and he was
like open up more and I'm
like
how it's already the
[Laughter]
maximum cute teeth thank
[Music]
you
ah that stupid tube that they put into
your mouth that sucks up on the spit and
then when they take a break and they
take it all out and then you're like
feeling like Sahara inside of
your
mouth dry as
[Music]
drier than I don't know California
is it dry in California or is it the
other way around is it moist is it humid
what's a good example I hate that like
everything just feels so dry and
[Music]
disgusting Arizona is dryer California
pretty dry dry and okay uh I guess the a
good example would be my mouth was as
dry as
Arizona my mouth was as dry as the Grand
Canyon could I say that would that make
sense is the grand Canyon dry or is it
human it looks dry looks pretty
dry that would sound
[Music]
funny okay I should
go Tangen thing into the orbit
again there's a river oh so what can
still we
drve there so what so what so what so
what so what so
what
so
what doesn't mean that the rest of the
ground isn't fairly or I mean more like
the air to be
[Music]
honest anyway I guess you guys win okay
guess the Grand Canyon isn't dry okay
it's
wet
okay why not just a Sahara yeah that's
what I would usually
say as dry as Cron's humor
[Music]
what is that me does it mean cron is not
funny is that what you saying really is
that so I have not had the opportunity
to talk with her that much until now so
I can not neither confirm or uh deny
that dry humor is funny what's dry
what's dry humor compared to humid humor
Mor
humor what it's not bad humor what is it
uh monotone straightforward
[Music]
a what's my humor
then am I dry where am I
[Music]
moist which
one tell me chat I'm looking at you here
look I'm looking at the
laptop no for real though answer the
question seriously what would you what
would you say do I even have a humor
maybe you call it uh uh uh invisible
humor because it's not there I'm not
funny wait that doesn't mean humor even
like doesn't mean that doesn't
necessarily have to mean that I'm funny
it's just generally what I think is
funny as
well my humor is interesting what do you
mean European huh H dorky little
damp I'm
damp very moist Exquisite
Divine it's cute Sil energetic
goofy goofy
goofy soggy wet
humor I'm I'm leaving now I don't
understand this conversation anymore
[Applause]
[Music]
in