[Music]
hello
hello hello is anyone is anyone there
hello where am
I
hello
[Music]
hello is there anyone
there
hello hello
am I all
alone is there anyone out there
hello
hello I I am getting quite frightened
being alone here in this white empty
vast space hello hello if you can hear
me please please call out to me hello
[Music]
hello
hello is there anyone around
[Music]
hello there doesn't seem to be anyone
around quite a mysterious
sight oh what is this oh on the ground
what is down
[Music]
here a fair
bird hello what is your
name
po I
see are you perhaps stuck here too poo
[Music]
what do you see around
there what do you lay eyes on do you
know where we are do you perhaps know
why we are
here I suppose
not
alas what strange happen stance must
have befallen
I I've awoken in this most peculiar
white
space my memories as lost as they've
been
stolen by a mischievous being or
something
else it's quite lonely here I don't know
what what we're
doing what is the purpose to all this
who am
I I cannot recall who I am if I am just
a lowly commoner or perhaps something
more
[Music]
my own name alludes me as as if this
were a jest just being played on me by
the gods of
Fate so
scary come poo
[Music]
hello
hello is there anyone in this space with
me
here I stand in this quite bewildering
scene this bewildering white scene with
not but a vague recollection of
clenching mine Fist and
feeling of
familiarity as if I've clenched my fist
many times before in the past
mayhaps I am proficient in the Arts of
fisting
per chance I am a renowned
champion of the
Fist or mayap I am nothing but a mere
amateur just an
amateur I will never find
[Music]
out if I am to uncover the truth of my
lost
memories I suppose we will need to start
somewhere who am I where are
we mayhaps the
people someone out there must hold the
key to mine own
Identity or at the very
least they may provide me a clue as to
who I am or why I am so Adept at
fting
mayhaps op are you with me shall we
embark on this magical journey
together but first we have to discover
how to get out of this white room this
white linal space pople
[Music]
a name
tag seems my name
[Music]
is s Jonathan
G Jonathan is spelled strangely with a
G I am s Jonathan G spelled with a
G goodness what a strange name
[Music]
hello
anyone I am Jonathan G
[Music]
I am seeking allies in this journey
hello
perhaps I must leave this room for
several moments to
explore and discover
technical difficulties
[Music]
yes you do
not what are you thinking Maiden my fair
Maiden Fair
[Music]
Lady yes Jonathan spelled with a G it is
Jonathan spelled with a
[Music]
g no it's spelled
Jonathan yes yes
Jonathan that is potentially Jonathan G
is my initials leading to
GG yes Jonathan G
what what is your
name my name is
uh my name I don't know actually I can't
hear what is my
name I don't know you look kind
ofar have you ever G that before you
have like a fatherly VI
you
right your name my is
what your favorite color do you remember
that figure I think it's I think it's I
think it's
blue though that sounds like a lot of
responsibility the Azure Maiden that's
so
[Music]
wrong us make a very fast decision okay
my name is what's my last name I think
it's
like am
Gander I wonder what
color settles
[Music]
in oh what ceremonious day
your
name I know
there
Gand sorry out of character chat I just
there's a lot going on right now and I
had to do push to talk so I couldn't get
the thing on on the screen and then we
just got warped out sorry for the
technical difficulties I will bring the
gaming screen real quick I I'm so sorry
there there's a lot
happening this
okay who I am the world I live in sorry
out of character sorry sorry let me move
over here where am I I'm so
small okay in character we are now in
character and more than
anything the people I hold most
dear faced with
Oblivion I
feel
empty reliev
perhaps
[Music]
distraught I do not
know so much I don't know and yet so
much I don't know I don't know and yet
and yet who the hell just said that to
at the sneak Point hello so much I
bright light it calls so much I don't
know I didn't I just say
that just say that the voic is coming
the bright light calls who's saying
that someone's talking that one they can
hear you that hi we have to go towards
the light this thing the light hell
what's your
name I don't know it says on her
head my name is Jonathan spelled with a
G oh cool Jonathan Jonathan I just saw
heaven light where shall we head the
Moon that are we the fastest readers yes
I think so I read fast it was it was in
my head oh they're they're even faster
at
thinking hello I hope there's food over
here like a soul it's like a broken egg
what is soul is this a hole but what
came it looks like a oh it's not a hole
okay which one's around this way this
way the white light
[Music]
liest still
Castle you there what are you doing here
you have the look of Outsiders about
you wait could it be quick send word to
his
majesty the the heroes have arrived at
the sanctuary run away
hello welcome Heroes this is the kingdom
of leest how do I pronounce that you are
not beaming the correct pronunciation in
my
head hold
on let me play music inside of my
mind what kind of beautiful music can I
play inside of my head right
now this
one this beautiful music I will play
inside my head
head jump scare
[Music]
warning the guards who brought you here
have informed me that you remember not
but your own
names a side effect of travel Between
Worlds no
[Music]
doubt this must all come as a surprise
to you but hearken well TW was I who
summoned you here you see an
unprecedented Calamity now threatens our
world it has sewn the Earth with
corruption and driven us from our homes
this blighted land now gives rise to
creatures of Shadow known as
stains this Kingdom ofal and
surroundings are now the only safe place
left to us lustin but should the
Calamity be left unchecked is only a
matter of time before it consumes the
entire
World faced with this Prospect I scoured
the ancient text for a way to combat the
Calamity and therein I found one the
ritual of hero summoning you who hail
from another world have been summoned
here by me to become the saviors of
listl naughty only you have the power to
save our world and so I ask you will
you who is
this your majesty what is it a great
host of stain has broken through our
defensive line no we are rushing to
mounted defense but the situation is
dire Majesty we must get you somewhere
safe who are these
strangers let's say you Heroes will you
accept this Destiny there is great power
within you will you use it to save us to
save this world ah mine eyes mine two
eyes oh hello what's up Heroes hello
maidens beautiful maidens it is so good
to see you I would you like a piece of
bread may I would love thank you bread
and I like carbs oh would you like some
bread too are you getting some did you
give me bread I don't I don't feel like
it's bread I Dr the
[Music]
bread there r my name I think based on
in my
head I
am the king might have been mistaken you
guys I met the king you met the king the
king mistaken if he thinks that I can
become
AAR of this
oh thank you
I from another world I think the king
made a mistake with me to be to be Hest
great
mistake so many voices
are
[Music]
you more like dog behavior
my head I am going
[Music]
to okay okay
I did not realize I'm in the face I'm a
big I'm very first and I'm predat that
means I can kill you any moment at any
time can you Pur okay yes you told me my
name was fair Maiden you are speaking
quite quietly is there a way that you
can raise your
voice I I know we have just met but uh
with so many voices around it is quite
hard to hear you I might I might die if
I raise it up much higher but I can I
that that's probably as good as I can do
is that any better I'll my sword
um one moment I go look at this wall and
ponder over at the Horizon oh yes please
Ponder at the wall stop leave me alone
that is no oh my
God
it there is much to ponder about this
wall yeah there's so much to ponder
about this wall honestly do you see what
do you
see are they speaking to us I I don't
know honestly oh my goodness this they
speaking to
[Music]
us many don't understand words we come
from a land of simple words
[Music]
not my Dy this is not
my we must fight
them they can't handle all of us at one
[Music]
I'm so
hungry help help kill it am I helping
yes please please
help get the r
first so hungry I am so hungry I am
eating in the middle of battle
y get the large one I'll protect you I
will protect you fair wor we not
might be a thing I am hurt may not hurt
him it hurts oh it hurts so bad wait
where did it
go I'll help I'll
help yeah they're tanky they can take
many hits from so many of
us kill kill it kill the St
King believe in yourself believe in the
me who believes in
oh
[Music]
no are we doing damage to
him
no are we are we damaging them
strong we're too low level too low level
where is he where is he oh God goodness
[Music]
get he will not take our
Castle oh great the lights in my head
shout Revelation hold your weapon and
Revelation what is my weapon
um re
Revelation
[Music]
Revelation revelation
this is it's quite
[Music]
awkward
Revelation
[Music]
oh I
see I am not worthy to hold the
sword I I am not worthy enough to hold
this sword
just a shame it is a
shame oh
man am I
dead I got it I know what to
do I
[Music]
understand revelation
you can go back at his hardest finish
the proposal and you can get me out of
here the voes not to do
know is our second chance to save the
world we're going to call off this
journey thank how much bread do you have
you have a nice sword too thank you you
like my
bread we have return oh
goodness oh no cra oh it looks the only
way that I
[Music]
can will you mayhaps trade with
me I would like to give you a piece of
[Music]
bread thank you bread for bread
thank you it was quite
delicious although I can't really hear
you yeah there is a lot of voes in my
[Music]
head you seem sturdy oh I I think I am
Prett they they look like rock candy oh
please don't eat oh my goodness I
need please don't eat my feet
wait oh my goodness w i buy items what
you
do did you take
them no no mine's too I swear did you
take my
items no I didn't you were the last one
in front of me it must have been
you no it wasn't me I don't have any
look at my it was a pink cat
Okay ni is she what are you doing I'm
looking for my you I heard you stole my
item pink
cat me the green woman told me that you
stole my
item the we oh oh my
goodness was it
her was it her to have stolen my my
[Music]
guns feel like I've I've seen this
before more than anything more than
anything was what the people I hold most
dear face with Oblivion I feel empty
relieved perhaps
distraught I do not
know so much I don't know and yet which
I don't know and
yet I hear a voice in my head who was
the fastest to Skipper Skipper I wasn't
skipping I was reading I was thinking
that it was in my head yeah I was not
skipping I was yeah it was all in our
head there's no skipping I'm going first
no let go let's go to the lights slow
down you are cheating you are
[Music]
cheating oh wait nothing
happened oh what what's all the way over
there if we go to the end of the world
what is there oh nothing I can't go
there's invisible walls who placed this
invisible wall in my mindscape has to be
an open open block somewhere yeah there
has to these lands and claim them for my
own I'm going to start my own country
you're going to
what I'm got to start my own country
Blaster what you're going to take over
the kingdom that we were
in can I have a no don't don't tell the
king that oh okay so you're not of land
I I I misread re I misread it as
Revolution I thought we were going to
over you're going to overthrow the king
I'm going to tell everyone of your Deeds
I will tell everyone of your plans what
is your name what is your name
traveler you can only assassinate me if
we trade names we must trade
names you can't kill me unless you know
my
name I see it right above your head
that's not my name I don't see my name
above my head no what's your
name I'm going to tell you wait but then
you can't kill me that might you must
you must we trade names and then you can
kill me my goodness I promise I promise
all you tell me your name okay my name
is Jonathan g spell with a
G yeah that's pretty close to my name oh
what's your
name John
Watson down joh
[Music]
Watson I will not doubt you it seems
that our names are very
similar mayhaps we are
oh it's g o n a t h o
n Jonathan that was
Jonathan are you sure yes I'm sure I'm
quite certain I would not lie to
you how do you spell your
[Music]
name she was going to tell me her name
no no I never tell her
name I don't know I feel like I've been
in this conversation
before right
away I gave her my name and she she
knows my name but I don't know her name
and now it's unbalanced the person that
knows the name holds all the power
[Music]
oh no I have to quick quick she did this
she planned this she knew that I would
use her name as if I found out her name
I would tell everyone that she was
trying to take over the
kingdom King King Le bestl it was John
John
Watson
hello what I told the king of your of
your plan no you didn't I didn't but I
was thinking about it I forgot your name
cuz you didn't spell it you sound like a
crazy person so I don't think he took
any of it no I'm not crazy I'm not crazy
I'm not C I'm not crazy I'm not crazy
she's trying to k a
her be hearing
wedding czy I tell everyone tell
everyone wait I know what happens
there's going to be enemies
yeah how do you know how do you know I
remember I don't remember there was a
battle right here am I crazy yes yeah I
think you're crazy yes you crazy are we
in an endless
loop probably want to follow her how do
we break it I don't know doors to the
kingdom figured it out I thought I
cracked the code thought you could get
in here
yeah that would be nice I I don't really
feel like fighting again you're quite
cave likee take sh your voice texture
walls the texture of
your mhm
yeah is it not is it
not maybe you're EV one my
eyes that all of you my
[Music]
enemies please don't this a i your
tail not my
problem my problem sounds familiar yeah
you want a massage
yeah can you massage please please you
guys are massaging outside of the
castle Yeah yeah I don't know how she
knew that I needed that endless
loop we have to do it right this time
thanks that that's sword that's a nice
technique you got there thank you I
thought maybe some hero oh oh special
massage for hero okay okay all right
thank you I'll you back
eventually thank you you guys are
massing each other peasant the b
i yes I would love a massage oh I
see please please the
mushroom I will give you some bread I
will give you some bread you must prove
yourself in other ways oh what what ways
what ways must I prove
myself you must break this endless
loop I promise I will break this Lo and
I'll get a massage what is your
name my name tanak of the orang
Tak corrected
[Music]
mear of thees
tar can't hear
you any
just call me Shakira just call me
Shakira
Shakira Shak I
[Music]
know you fa through that I will free us
from this that hurt me made have me me
have
fallen God are the days of the walls of
white in my corner today I will uphold
this s and protect her royal what is she
looking
at what is what is going on oh
goodness's danger of this oh okay
oh y
y fall the C don't don't hurt me anymore
wait I'm ready they they were right here
I remember from my
past are we friends here it's going to
happen I remember the what do you
remember you're welcome I remember
you
what no my name is Jonathan G gathan
Jonathan
G
yeah gz G Jonathan
g
[Music]
king long live the king
are okay oh I
feel could ially be
[Music]
a like weak point why does he hurt so
hit him from the
back my specialy after all
there's some
here get get him get him down I'm I'm of
circle good job good job one
time really big
range
everyone I'm King him I'm King
him
the the big one has a the king kill the
king Kill The
King The King it's
a
maybe jumping he's
jumping conver convert good is there in
here go we must help I don't remember
what that is I'm smacking watch why she
jumping in the air watch out okay okay I
am moving back in here
on the head I'm sure chop chop chop
chop
[Music]
going hello are you guys not going to do
anything I remembering
[Music]
something
shout
Revelation
Jonathan you are building up to this
moment forever and
ever you are building to this
moment I can feel the energy the energy
that was denied me the first time are we
now worthy gods are you done playing
tricks against me
I feel I feel the spirit within me it is
bubbling up and spewing
[Music]
forth
Revelation the stain host has been
routed
you fought bravely kind Heroes I pray
you are not injured that Mighty armored
one must be their leader the stain King
fascinating Most Fascinating well I see
why they call you Heroes we'd be in red
pickle without your help we sustain
minimal damage than to your Valor our
kingdom is in your debt thank you I must
hasten to inform his majesty or Victory
will you accompany me
[Music]
I heard the news where's the king who I
speaking to though we called upon you
suddenly you Roose the occasion you have
my deepest gratitude where's the king
did Jonna Watson get to
him what interested me most however is
the strange power you manifested during
the battle with which you were able to
defeat the
stains that power May well be the key to
saving our world from
annihilation according to the heroes of
power came to them like a forgotten
memory when they spoke the word
revelation but once they used it to
Route the stain host it seems that power
vanished Without a Trace well that's
bloody brilliant in it so what are we
supposed to do with the next time the
stains attack revelation we must uncover
the secrets of this phenomenon if we are
to Prevail against Calamity many
questions remain but one thing is
certain the kingdom of Li still still
stands St thanks to you I I talking
to Jonna Watson get the
whole the whole party the whole royal
party marvelous on behalf of all the
bestin I thank you we are blessed to
have your Aid kind Heroes allow me to
introduce the four Great guilds which
are responsible for uring the Kingdom's
peace and prosperity The Haven for the
Curious where knowledge and creativity
are valued above all the Scarlet oneand
the home I know what are we pointing at
the home for our Glory Seekers with
ambition and vision where closest allies
become fiercest Rivals to am Rec coin
the sycom of healing where the spirit of
empathy and devotion thrives to celan
cup the beacon of the righteous and
loyal where great threats are faced with
even greater courage than Jade sword one
of these skills become your home bring
your time
here Beyond this door lies room of Truth
therein the will of the ancestor shall
decide your guild fear not interection
is a vital step on the road to liment
excel here as I always say ever higher
time to roll the dice eh be seeing some
of you L down at the Amber coin Guild
Hall let us save this world together the
room TR the Waits go forth with
Valor room of Truth
I am
ready I am ready to receive the
[Music]
truth what is the will of the
ancestor amidst the endless flow of time
seek the power that Amber
grants seruan
cup it is because Jonathan G is pure of
heart Dawn the cloak I will Dawn the
cloak
[Music]
how armed with an unwavering will seek
to defend the soul of
Jade
enigmatic
[Music]
recollection next speak to your Guild's
Guild Master wow what a beautiful
area I am here ready to speak the
ancestors blessings upon you hero
welcome to the Guild Hall the Cillian
cup I am Celesta A Guild Master that you
would come to Leal to Aid in her time of
need even so soon after your summoning
speaks volumes about your selflessness
as a member of this Guild you'll be
joined in the effort to cleanse this
land of stains and bring Salvation to
the world but one must walk for one can
run first you should learn about this
town we strive to protect as well as how
to accept and perform Quest within this
town There's a location known as the
quester
board you it's you again
Ming my name is Jonathan G with a G
spelled with a G he Jonathan no it's
Jonathan was a g g o n with g a t h o n
Jonathan Jonathan with a G thank you
Jonathan G what is your name Jan G um
ninoa ninoa it's nice to meet you ninoa
it seems that this is our Guild leader
Celeste celest oh Tam
oh oh
Jonathan Ste summoning egg what what are
all these things raino Wast steeve
summoning Map There's a map there's a
map I'm looking waist bin have a cool
clo magical to yeah M let me just uh put
on my cloak what happens if I Ste
summoning
it this horse is so
fast wow oh my
God okay that's so cool so we so
quick Kaki
beu oh I Jonathan do I have my Jonathan
J Jonathan G Jonathan g g for
short uh I think there's uh something a
little little the G different about your
kame oh yes you're oh oh my
goodness what is this are you an
imposter oh my you're going ah I cannot
bear look at you what you are an
impostor evil you're evil you're black
cap where is that where did you get that
from the the void
St what I'm one of you you're you're one
wait so are we all ceran we are all
ceruleans except one
how a different talk to the Guild Master
okay oh Guild Master Guild Master I am
on my
horse canas is busting upon you hero
welcome to the Guild Hall of the Cilan
cup I didn't read the first part where's
the quest board even so soon after your
summoning speaks volumes about your
selflessness oh oh as a member of this
Guild you'll be joining the effort to
cleanse this land of stains and bring
salvation to the
world but one must walk before one can
run first you should learn about the
town we strive to protect as well as how
to accept and perform quests quests
within this town there is a location
known as the quest board where is it
where is the quest board there you will
find the quest master who will import
his knowledge upon you you may also use
I meet you
[Music]
there quite far this gigant oh nope
where am
I Quest master I here to take your
strongest
Quest Hil you must be one of the heroes
then the guild Masters told me to expect
Thee I thank you for risking your lives
to protect our fine Kingdom this here is
the quest board Lees from all over town
come here to post jobs and request I
understand your main duties eradicating
the Staines but I hope you'll take the
time to help some citizens in need you
must be tired of my prattle by now so
how about we get you started with the
quest right away yes the quest Quest
board Quest board Quest board beautiful
STS
everyone you too thank you thank you his
name is he must be one of the heroes
then the Guild Master told me to expect
you I thank you for risking your lives
to protect our Fen Kingdom uh gilm how
do I get off my horse sneak sneak sneak
must sneak thank thank you thank you
thank you very much thank
you understand your main duty is Runing
stains but I hope you'll take time to
help some citizens in
need they must be tired of my battle by
now so how about we get you started with
the quest right away I see looks like
perfect job for you well best of luck
off you go now which which Quest should
we take complete what the options what
what are the side
class okay we can I can read these right
I think so yeah materials needed at the
Smithy I'm The Apprentice at the smiy
and my master says we're running low on
raw materials if you can help us gather
some please stop by the Smith can we
only take that Quest it looks like there
the only Quest we can take I don't think
so everything's the same okay Quest
[Music]
accepted I will get on my horse too okay
I accept it accept it where is the
smiy uh
SMY where is is the SMY where Where Art
Thou the Smithy oh there is a there is a
map so we can maybe look around and uh
it shows up what
ohc I'm still getting used to this the
blacksmith where is it where's the
Blacksmith everyone is this where a
blacksmith would be is this the yes yeah
oh is a
smiy smiy materials needed
what do you
need what do you
need oh great you saw my quest I posted
well to start with could you bring over
10 oak logs there are a bunch of trees
not far outside the town that you can
chop okay let's go check down that this
person over
here all The Apprentice we'll get 100
coins upon
completion 100 coins we can buy food
with them
okay I guess we can get out of the town
what's the name of your horse of your
Steed
GG oh mine is
ninoa oh wa what is
your yeah what's what's the name of your
horse
Tam I think it's
uh a co wait are you are you guys all in
the same party together not yet should
we We join a party shall we party up I I
how do I leave my party you're in a
party you're already in a party I got K
Out by a random party I don't know how I
did it you're just in a party yeah
without
[Music]
us let me let let me ask let me refer to
the scriptures I got kidnapped oh well
by who by I'm green someone named I'm
green I'm purple I'm green stole you
yeah she stole me I'm in her party for
some reason believe this oh that's
strange kind of scary I'm trying I'm I'm
calling upon the scriptures to see how
to leave a
party in my head I I do not know how to
leave this I've been
kidnapped okay
well let's let's see maybe did you get
that party
invite oh I did uh I did not hold on
oh how do I
accept uh let me let me look at the
scriptures the scriptures the scriptures
on how to free ourselves from someone's
party
yeah ahuh uh
the voices in my head are very it said I
have to find the person who invited me
but I don't know who invited
me oh there's I'm
[Music]
green so she wasn't just made up i' see
she's probably very far away cuz we
don't see
her re turn our member to
us oh maybe the magic to can help try
your magic toone oh Magic tone there was
something really sparkly over there for
a second did you guys see that where in
front of the quest board ooh the magical
toone wait Shin I'm not a member of a
party but I'm I'm in a party huh what
what I did not mean to trade you oh I
failed to invite you
maybe
mayhaps oh might I think that if you go
to page four of the magical toone you
may be able to
leave oh such magical to I I I think I
pressed that magical to and it says that
I am not a member of a party but on the
my screen it says I'm a part of a party
so perhaps you might
to
uh unconscious yourself AKA oh yeah yes
close your eyes and come back close my
eyes and um go to sleep and
then I will give you some privacy I will
look away from you as you are doing
[Music]
way where did she go she left this
world W she just came welcome back
welcome back to the land qu welome
back are you still in a party oh I'm I'm
good now I have to the grass of the
random people what yes wait why does he
fail to invite
player uh we
[Music]
good why why can I can someone else try
to invite her to our party I think only
party leaders can so
strange that is she's difficult it's
still in a party how about we remake the
party how do we remake a
party uh you click on your magical toone
the magical toone
yeah I've disbanded my party I will
invite you no no fail to
invite oh
[Music]
oh it's okay I
will I will
be the lone the Lone Wolf I I guess it
is my destiny to work
alone I suppose free her free arm member
who is
eating it's
Gigi
you I was hungry in Minecraft oh oh yes
what is Minecraft I mean I
mean you mean enigmatic recollection
what is enigmatic recollection we are in
li
no onward back to the quest board oh yes
yes I don't think we're in the we're in
oh wait they are there oh
oh there she is please free okay okay
okay stand still do not move I you I
will take you from my
partying wonderful moment thank you
okay I am I am
[Music]
inviting into the
party
y our
party we
done okay everyone let's go get wood and
beat the other teams we have to beat the
other teams we're speed running quick go
your horse go the other teams can't
catch up we are so ahead of them we are
so so ahead where do we get what this
way that's not the exit is this the exit
is this not the exit yes it
[Music]
is here we are okay I am killing the
chicken get the no that's not part of
our Quest that's not what if it's a part
of a future
[Music]
Quest die chicken what we seek your eggs
okay never mind you look familiar to me
why are you looking
away
okay 10
[Music]
wood we will obtain 10
wood I will leave it like
that how much wood do I have
[Music]
now feel as if I've if I were a beaver
I'd be eating so
good hey what are these whoa away from
her oh thank
you does everyone complet their Quest
cool down seems you're okay okay that
okay okay oh my God they're spawning
outside the walls at an alarm
rate away wow we're so fast when we do
it together yeah yeah we completed the
objective did you complete your
objective die die oh I got eight coins
from killing
that will it will it say when you are
you guys okay yes yeah I guess I just
got to keep
going you can also check your inventory
just to double check check your pocket
your pocket pocket
your bag the bag on your hip
mayhaps this is they
[Music]
sleep that is my seems my fist have a
long cool
down can we use our skill that is called
Revelation well not really it's not
called Revelation but you may use
Revelation okay but it puts it on a cool
down you seem to get
re
[Music]
Revelation need one
o oh that was very cool we got 20 coins
yeah let me see your Revelations it's on
I am tired
now I am TI tired now yeah I have a cool
down yes I have a refractory period of
using these are some magical trees yeah
they they come back to life the trees
wow the spawn rate on this is insane
crazy stained slime ball why would it
spawn on top of
me did everyone finish their objective
yes yes let us then make haste should we
go back yes we cannot let them catch
up I think they already caught up no
way okay let's just onward to the
the quick quick which is right which was
right
here yes he wa what does that do you
cannot use the enchantment table the
thank you so much see my bring the raw
materials of tools and it for
you people scare me
a pickax
[Music]
okay I do not have the required
materials we need o planks and from up
yonder hasth Fallen to their death hath
Fallen I notra this sticks he want two
Scarlet wand member oh great we the
quest posted you bring
10 buil to purchase we are missing four
five how do I make a plank 10 oak logs I
think very easy my friend
oh thank you important you gave me
necessary
information
exactly completed it just that easy my
friends all sorts of
tools interesting I have an
axe I think we need to coins did from
now on when you find any material stop
speak to the
m Quest mask I see you say what we
needed collect 10 cobblestones all right
quick before everyone catches up onwards
oh my horse is too large for this room
have to get
[Music]
onwards got this thank
you we will be so fast
the
cobblestones and some ore
mayhaps might this be coal is it what is
what's happening I think this is I don't
know I think oh this is bed
rock how do you know that I I don't know
it just popped up into my head you know
so much more than you let on oh you
being attacked I'll protect you behind
you
Revelation oh my God I didn't hit it are
you sure you protected me I jumped over
it it was merely a
miscalculation oh thank you oh you saved
me there we go thank
[Music]
you I collected 10 cobblestones have you
collected 10 cobblestones not quite yet
I I have now collected 10 Cobblestone
where are our party members so much
progress are have they been left
behind mayhaps I can give them a call
let me ring them up let me on the radio
party
call hello hello I in a party call it is
only us only only two of us is in here
because everyone only two of us no the
point of calling in nobody else is
picking up
the oh no we are in danger I I'll
protect
you thank you I very much app ah thank
you for picking up the phone where are
you you guys where' you guys
go I'm just doing the quests I see I see
where are
you I'm at the quest Master now oh okay
we will return to you
post haste with
haste post haste W with with haste with
the utmost haste I am on the way sorry
cobblestones and speak to the blacksmith
par okay okay I must go my people need
me oh
farewell oh you're talking to us I we
can leave the radio now oh yes now that
we are together we can hang up the phone
call as
the
good good day sir oh they need material
wait do we need to the materials I don't
know what the Apprentice we talked to
The Apprentice oh I must return to the
quest
[Music]
Master hello Quest Master oh hello what
I don't oh yeah where where are you
kose be you hit got hit a little bit too
hard on the head and is lost now um I
may I get pick up if you if you look
above at the top of your your your
eyesight at the top of your vision what
do the words at the top of your head
say I speak with Quest Master oh return
to the quest
board oh
okay yes I will wait you yay let us
speak to the quest master
[Music]
I hung up on you oh okay okay okay I
will also hang
up never mind I don't
know what I am
speaking is it working you just need to
you need to talk to him and then you
need to click here to accept the quest
on the actual
born hey this looks like the perfect
job of the smoothie and my master says
raw material
Place stop by this
Okay click to
order why can't I speak to this Quest
master I thought this was food you
finished the quest waste bin I did oh I
have now finished farewell maidens where
do you where do you wait farewell
maidens oh yes yes would you like to
um where did you get wood from
[Music]
head forward to the towards the city
gate and exit if you head yes towards
The City Gate there will be an orb that
will lead you outwards Outside The City
Gate do we have to go to the smithie
first or can we just go out yes you must
speak to the the wood first and then go
to the you can do whichever SM do
whatever you want AC all the quest this
way is out can we the wood and then the
Smithy can we can we who's interested in
at once I am
acting I'm going to go get some wood you
want to come with or do you want to go
for the maybe I should just accept
everything I'm accepting everything I'm
not
reading it's okay we can read it later
it is a future Us's
problem in the end we're helping those
in as as is the rule of the Cerulean um
um Team empathy
and and
devotion
a deliver a wood
shovel okay that's easy oh hello Quest
Mas hello hello hello we
have can they hear us in the call I
don't think so oh I can hear you I can
hear we can hear you guys yeah even if
you're in a call we can still hear
proximity because we have ears and you
are to us so
uh all right are we ready to complete
more quests yes I would love to complete
more Quest I just finished the the
cobblestones one I'm not sure what to
do to the quest MK crafting a stone
pickaxe and a wooden shovel oh I need to
collect a cobblestone I have not done
that yet yes yes
yes okay where where would splendid huz
go to choir said Stone you must go
outside where we got the got the wood go
a little further and there should be a
mound of stone oh let us make haste let
us make haste let us make haste with
Hast towards the outer walls the outer
Kingdom
walls
Adventure let's go ladies should we
create a should we create a party here
we are all right back again we back
outside the kingdom walls got our
pickaxes swinging side to side to side
side side to side this makes me feel a
little sick watching this happen what I
don't know I I just feel I feel some
sort of attachment to these to these
solid like beings worry not I feel a
little sick that you're kind of
destroying them apparently when you hit
them Tam says they become Bedrock what
are you looking
at but it feels like they I don't want
to I don't want to hurt them though it
feels like against my nature to hurt
them here I will give you I will engage
in trade oh trade yes and then I will
give
you 10 of these things and you are not
hurting them I've already it have to
hurt them yes you do not have to hurt
them thank you I hurt them for you
you're so kind of course it's part of
the Cerulean way of empathy and
devotion
oh so strong you are so strong you thank
you I owe you my life
Wow should we uh perhaps ask the uh ask
the to join the the group group call as
they call it maybe maybe we should stay
on the group call so that way we do not
get it perhaps when we get separated we
can
still
discuss okay
okay it doesn't work my my friends
woohoo Let Us
return
return ring ring ring yes this is Tam
Gander we are thinking that we should
stay on the phone call call just in case
we leave each other's get lost hearing
range listening range a splendid idea
thank you Splendid Splendid Splendid
Hazard we're good joyous day Joy yes it
is full of joy wonderful
feelings are you guys I'm learning out
of bread though I thought we had to buy
from him
maybe I should ride my horse so I get
hungry see I got this perhaps my my
group it it must I might have to resort
to the violence against The Rock why oh
you must do it yourself oh I do it
myself you she has to hurt very thing
does not want Cobblestone
16 where is the shopkeeper
done we I see it oh ra hero thank you
for stay in this town welcome to my
humble shop all you have to do is talk
to me I'll show you what then you select
what to buy I can't give everything free
make sure you have enough coin to stop
by you need something give me company
I'm sure fighting things all day will be
some when feeling weird take care break
do something we have so many quests to
do huzzah I love helping the town's
people wait these quests slop
is you can repeat the quest you can
repeat the quest it's a repeat Quest
they so
needy what do I well talk to the
shopkeeper you're tired from adventuring
or simply looking for a little div
verision maybe give one of the activ try
take your mind offr you good some now
Guardians children attending to them and
I'm sure they be overo to be a real hero
such as yourself um speak to the best
child in the gardens okay
10 potato salad maybe they have some
bread I have to speak to the child in
the gardens for the quest child in the
garden there's a child I must I'm so
sorry my the bartend
friends what's going on do you need
assistance no I killed them all okay oh
no what it must have been very hard Chef
my friends where did all of you go I am
trying to find a child okay I will meet
with you cuz I do not know where the
child
is oh I see
you my fellow Maiden hello Maiden don't
pubs usually have food did you speak to
the child in the gardens already
mayhaps where is the child in the
gardens I know not I was hoping you
would know where the child in the
gardens
rest the child in the garden the child
in the the
garden is this the child in the garden
where are you oh I see it's the child in
the
garden oh it's about what a few many Ys
away Ys away I have a feeling children
could be dangerous let us make haste I
am making haste to the child in the
gardens I Believe In the Garden is this
a
garden my horse cannot jump
you can't jump never mind moving on my
horse can
[Music]
nay yes there is a leeston child right
here I have found leest child
child let us speak with you you're one
of the heroes boy this must be my lucky
day everyone doing what they can just
like you right well this here is a
garden you're free to come and use them
whenever you like hey child does
absolutely nothing we are spreading joy
and her heroism to this
town this was where the sh ende yes yes
no we are inspiring him you too can be a
hero when you grow up if you just look
to the sky and Shout
Revelation and then you will die in Epic
Death because you are too small and puny
no no our devotion the Cerulean leaders
would like us to spread empathy and
devote all right empathy yes you may
grow up to become a shopkeeper one day
you may be a shopkeeper or a hero like I
or a great
NPC an
NPC what's an NP what's an NPC these are
just T I do not know it just popped into
my
head a lot of things seem to pop in your
head wonder what the city tastes like
it's like tip of my
tongue I wonder if it tastes like
cookies I like cookies yeah
cookies cookies something about cookies
the tip of her
tongue ah okay tip of her tongue the tip
of your tongue tastes like cookies what
are we talking about this is the only
thing you can buy the potions potions
they're very
helpful
so I have 693 coins what do I do we must
purchase okay this
I forgot what the quest told me to do we
have to speak to pit
Dorman that seems to be his name d pit
Dorman why do I have so much food now
who gave me
this
bread sorry I just get so hungry oh
where you can build oh Beyond The Garden
you can build freely I just realized why
is my horse and an
egg why not horses come from eggs did
you not know oh this must be the place
in this realm Mason I found Mason they
come from eggs well you seem to know
very well about this realm you are very
well acquainted how do you
know te are you does
down where the shopkeepers are across
the way from the Smithy the
Smithy thank you my trusty companion I
appreciate no problem why do we all talk
like this like what
idea like what wow it is just how we we
speak we can build our own Guild House
dear friends Guild House let's build our
own Guild House yes oh how joyous day us
huz let us make our humble AB yes our
humble
abod we have our little plot on the uh
near the wall let us Build Together Miss
Miss time lady yes
Rock I shop I I have seemed to have lost
my way shop is this way oh thank
you yes no
problem oh I I very much appreciate gu
thank you anytime
roock thank you
block oh nice nice potions
100 up I ain't buying this
[Music]
place a
Coliseum oh I like the way it thinks
what
please accept our where
is sneak sneak sneak why are you
sneaking so much I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm
sneaking sneaking sneaking reminds me of
a I don't know I think I'm starting to
remember a certain song about sneaking
like a
sneaky oh like a sneaky how do you all
know that song have you grown up in the
same area and it is aong no these
memories they ail me they ail you ah it
must have been a song you all grew up
with like a nursery rhyme
mayhaps it s you like
a
mayhaps mayhaps I was taught as a
child excuse me excuse me uh you you you
seem to have a blue aura around you oh
yes yes our our other our I'm I'm I am
on the way I found her with h I am on
the way te where is she do not let her
be taken from us she's ours I do not
know how to get out of
here where they're trying to take away
I'm on the
way what I am I am making
haste away from her she is
our you are our team to fight you are
not there needed you quick here come
with me quick join our team
no are I think it's too late now
so no you are I mean I mean what what
you're Curry my friends honestly you be
with us you can be with
us what
come here come here come here come here
let's go Iris come here you leave us you
are one of
ours
talking they're stealing
her do not stop taking her she's
our I know you have two halves one dark
and and a lighter
one give her back she's suddenly hitting
me she's suddenly H she's hting you you
are ours
never
you stop
[Music]
her
re
reation
reation reation
[Music]
Revelation oh nice fist oh thank you oh
my God such cool
moves they look like from a retro game
rations a retro game I know not a retro
game yes I know not of what you
speak who are you you beautiful
beautiful violin lady oh at least you
know I am to be the next Queen of the
kingdom of lesto what I did not know of
your intentions oh so that's how you say
it this is not an intention this is
meant to be your Des was meant to
be are you are you related to them are
you their Heir The King and I must be
blood blood related are you blood
related to that tiny King what no we
have blocked eyes and we knew that you
knew you were fed you married the king
that's are you under with the
King it's complicated
she you was toose to me
but you don't have you didn't have to
accept wait I wanted to to the
power I see all right all right this is
the future Queen of the LI yes
yes I'm glad you know fellow peasants
peasants my my queen I'm sorry for
speaking to you with such
disrespect we will not protect you if
you don't respect us that's why you're
in a different
Guild you need the you need the support
of all the guilds in order to be
successful that
was whoever you stay away from her she
is our Queen she is to be our Queen the
will of the king the
phone the where is she looking where are
you going off
to return wait I have no idea cute brown
owl what is what is your name I my name
is Iris oh nice to meet you I'm K yeah
nice to meet you what is your name my
name is Jonathan G spelled with a G
Jonathan g g for
short okay okay I'll call you okay for
short Jonathan J Jonathan G Jonathan
with a G Jonathan with a G Jonathan with
a G yes Jonathan call Jonathan then oh
yes oh okay yes I would like that no one
Queen Jan um who are you hello I have a
name not Queen I thought you were to be
the queen you don't like it you can call
I would like
to so sounds very cute and then who is
this rock that was trying to kidnap me
I'm we're going to go to the shopkeeper
Ki beu has to be after youed the quest
oh wow your name is
be I don't know why that sounds familiar
but slightly different for what I
remember different I don't know I don't
know I've always been beu yeah why am I
being surrounded by so many people we
are on the te you are one of us one of
us the celan cup but yes but I but I
joined another team no no you can leave
but you did not join another team for
one of us you you've always been one of
us we are desting for each other really
what what makes this what what what what
why why am I one of you guys I see it in
your eyes because you have empathy you I
feel your tion it's it's much kind of
being sa no no she's she's one of ours
you guys don't you I don't know
especially you you don't seem like you
would have empathy excuse
me I am made of empathy you are I I am
liquid empathy yes I've seen it in her
eyes in Tam's eyes the way she spoke to
that child she is full of
empathy I see yes I will I would have to
discuss with my current uh my current
team members will you return to us it
is Jonna Watson she wants to kill the
king wat she she told me Watson J Watson
to kill the kid oh no she wants to oh
it's EAS oh no she thought she thought
Revelation was Revolution and she was
planning and she want to kill theing
I mean I can understand that that
misunderstanding wat I don't need
something you you kill the king there's
some crazy beg on the
street help me leave my friends alone
back off she wants to kill the king
Jonathan would never kill the
king this one Watson the one with the
magnifying glass
excuse
me to K theing stay away from my guild
member sorry but she wants to
kill excuse me your excuse me excuse me
excuse me
excuse don't talk to my member like that
thank you your guild member was talking
to my guild
member my member wanted to Hur the king
my would never want to hurt the king we
are part of the Jade sword and we are
[Music]
loyal
empathe your father's a hamster and your
mother smells of
elderberries excuse me I bu my me I've
never known my mother you guys are
disturbing the peace you know that
sorry you're crazy hey hey hey guys
don't want to kill the
King which Guild is that which Guild is
that I know not I'm kind of interested
let's find out you know killing the King
let's let's find out we we should
they're
listening you what are you from where
you I
from why don't you
guess I don't know you are too evil
don't give up on that she made
no Amber you are correct you are correct
I am from Amber
disgusting disgus I am from that
place disgusting yes Amber is
disgusting do
not do not ever interact with Amber talk
to us I will be do not shush me there na
or else I will shush you in a moment I
can't you I
know excuse me the air is very loud what
gu are you guys from what Guild are you
guys from you are a king killer you are
King okay thanks now I can report you
guys no I will report you to the
what you
rep that's not a good idea hey hey hey
hey hey that's not he has absolutely no
power hell
she she's running where are you
running where are you headed to I know
where did she go us where is she
reporting us to I have no idea it's a
thing Quest Master honestly you just got
to tell the truth we are val honestly in
this group do you think do this
what honestly yeah yeah they totally
could do that what what else would they
do I totally see that happening in Nar
what what else did they do Nar what is
Naruto what do you speak of what it
sounds like whates I don't know what it
sounds like not not the first thing that
comes to your head this is my re my
Revelation is in
farting yourness no no never aart I
would never not a one movie not one
movie where they sing and make Prett
girl
yes I thought you were about to say do
you know John Cena I'm sorry I'm who is
John Cena joh Cena Cena s is he around
here I can't see him I Cena what is who
is Jonathan John Cena Jonathan do you
guys hear a familiar jingle whenever you
hear that name
Jonathan is this an
inside you know right know
iath safy are you going to me Jonathan
coming
back no it's no it's Jonathan it's
pronounced Amber if you kill him he'll
be gone but yes yes he would beathan I I
put my my name on the line us ambercoin
nothing to do amber you on the Amber
team are you of Amber are you he's of
Amber you of Amber
what's wrong there been a
misunderstanding Amber what are you
talking about I'm in your team I'm in
your party you on our
team on our team no you shut huh huh I
mean you you shut your humble
mou did you say to me I did
not I thought you're supposed to be a
part of the team I'm solo level have do
not yeah I I don't even they're the ones
who reached out of
helping supposed to refuse it man you're
in ceran Cup oh well I mean I didn't
know you guys were in
[Music]
Cilan Jo our party join our party I
think we should we should we should
remove ourselves from this should
I our part pleas our party we want to go
crazy we want to go crazy
go before they ask any more questions
that I don't want does anyone not want
be nice here all about
car us nobody oh nobody wants you except
us the
aan wow we are so
compassionate go join our side you must
open your magical tomb do you see this
the magical book open your magic book
and locate page four locate page four
magical book
yes resolve your
party wait click to disband click to
kick click to leave try try leaving try
to leave yeah yes should I maybe say
something before I no no just
leave just get out I mean yeah they did
just You Belong with us they ditched you
yeah they they they they did they ditch
me did they really ditch
me it's not a mising it's not a
misunderstanding yeah you were just a
decoy uh-huh okay you were meant to be
with us you are one of ours let me let
me just stay let me just stay in chat I
was ditched so I will leave we accept
you for who you are traitor or not you
can make a new I was abandoned we we we
have been tied by the strings of I'm
sorry I will
switch yes
yes is this really the right
answer this is the right answer nobody
loves you except us okay nobody loves
this is this is very toxic this feels
very toxic okay don't don't we we are we
are we are the empathy group we are the
group that is full of empathy you open
I'm trying to I'm trying to leave wait
wait wait okay okay uh I can't open the
book all of a sudden wait wait
oh there we go on page four of your
magical
tomb do you really want to leave your
party yes yes yes yes yes yes yes oh I
guess the sword doesn't know I have I
have I have alone now I have left now
join our team join us join our
party you are one of
us oh okay try you guys are actually
full of empathy right yes we are full we
are full of kindness and love take our
love okay all right now locate your
magic radio I am feeling the love open
your magic radio yes my magic radio I
have a magic this is Magic this is a
magic radio what do I do with the magic
radio and join our call us ring radio
call our radio is a party call yes it's
a group it's a group chat there we
go y now no matter where we are
[Music]
[Applause]
of she is
[Music]
[Applause]
oured to
be calm we are full of EMP we are calm
we are very calm we're full of empathy
we're kind
love we know peace
kindness love does our ancestors
actually know us I don't think they know
us yes they would know they were like us
and they wrote history they were like we
are the calm ones think all right
way sorry my beautiful te yes my
beautiful teammates uh uh how do I check
what side quest I'm on oh you done your
magic booket one more time and you you
flip to page
two oh check your oh okay okay yes it
says I do not have any active side
questt what
try you talk to the board okay okay the
board the quest board okay okay are you
guys are you guys you know fully
already much further ahead we are want a
different I don't know are you guys just
ahead of me we are three Quest ahead if
I were to
guess I see mayhaps mayhaps my hum I I
came I came a little bit you know a
little bit for you guys probably cuz I'm
just that important you know uh-huh you
are we are just so full of empathy we
understand we know why the board not the
dud oh okay okay oh there's so many
quests accept all of
them all of them because we are helpful
every Quest I think there's only one
yeah I think there is only one
okay there is only one it looks like a
lot okay and then I go to you want the
fast pass through some of the quest oh
there's a fast pass is this is this gizy
what is gizy L I have no idea what I'm
called the Nina special oh the inoa
special please give it to me at the
Smithy where's the
Smithy the Smithy the Smithy SMY this
way I would like a horse where do I
where do you get a where do I get a
horse Che your your oh oh my God horses
are are born from
eggs and the best that they are yes
oh well that's Neo knowledge is it over
here and how do I get off of it oh there
we go do I just abandon the horse or
just you shift the button yes you sneak
nice okay yeah
gotcha oh sorry oh there you are hold on
okay hello hello f F pass F
pass you are drenched you are
soaked I am drenched yes I just saw you
in the water wait I can't I can't give
items I think you have to trade you you
yeah you'll get a cold okay no I'm way
too you cannot you cannot fast done the
action drowning
help is drowning
oh yeah
you it was a click the red block you
you're just such a
joke thank you
fast so silly fast good
jic
Ted
drowning what's going on you're drowning
she's drowning oh my God what the hell's
going
on she was drowning
tortur are you guys torturing somebody
no no we are having a nice
SP I did not man this is such a peaceful
team I'm so glad of EMP under the water
though empathy was it you no we are
someone was holding me down it must have
been the Amber I couldn't get Amber ke
must have done it the Amber coin used
their telepathy on you is is the
ambercoin our like our our main enemy
yes they are our main enemy they are mhm
are oh they are so they're like they're
the ones that we should go out to kill
kind of En yeah in the name of empathy
we must kill them yes in
the we must I don't think that's how to
show how empathy Works yes I see I
didn't know empathy was so violent but
it makes sense one of them plans do you
mean Mak sense so sometimes violence is
the only answer to to have empathy we
have rest
Balance store balance I'm starting to
understand a lot of things thank you
this is what empathy means empathy is to
kill empathy is kill the bad in this
world empathy means to kill
unfortunately my my loyal companions I
have a a pool somewhere from the unknown
and I must
are you being summoned by the forces
beyond your knowledge Theos in and I
must sharks can drown of course um but I
believe in you guys you guys will you
come back to us will you come back I
will I will come back to you come back
to this world as soon as possible please
don't forget about me okay don't forget
I would I do not wish never we never
never forget you please we never forget
you
[Music]
and I will return to you my we won't
wait for your return we won't forget you
will never forget never forget you wa
for me I will I will see you again I
will see you again goodbye goodbye
fwell fwell
[Music]
fwell uh uh uh
uh oh she is gone the forces have taken
her gone she has
disappeared greatly forces have claimed
us all oh no but she'll be back will
that happen to all of us eventually
perhaps eventually all of us will will
be we why do you have to be so dark like
that because empathy is sometimes dark I
see that makes so much s there is
Darkness M wise words Queen wise words
wise the words Slay Slay the queen no do
not
slay like SL SL like Slay Slay
Slay I I do not understand but I will
try I will try I will
try good good
good now can someone tell me where the
Leeson child is once again he is in the
garden after you've spoken to him
oneon-one
H yeah about the ow
oh Ena how do I open this box that you
traded me with like items oh you just
right click after you have it in your
hand what is right clicking try placing
on the ground oh yeah place it on the
ground with your right hand yes with
your right
hand maybe try interacting with I got it
I got it on the ground thank you thank
you man my throat is dead I don't even
know why it's dead
why would it must be multidimensional
transfer that cost it ah that makes so
much
sense what what wait side quest side
quest where is the Jade sword Guild
Master does anyone mayhaps
sow if you um perhaps find something
green the
arena maybe you will find them inside
the
arena I'm not sure
but pitch
dor that sounds
to you saw the quest I posted what the
pit
Dorman is he a Dorman or is he a Pitman
he's a pit a Pitman
M no idea oh there we
go what do you mean
something
something with
you I allowed to be
here remembering the property allowed to
be here I'm remembering something about
Pikmin
and throw them at people but the art of
thund tell me where your leader
is leader is there any other Quest I can
do tell me where your leader is on our
team here your te thank you sh Watson
even though you wish to kill the
king huh excuse me do you know where are
you
guys wait Amber coin member you need to
kill the king you need assistance
noin how you sa him feel threatened I
freeing him from where where are you one
second I must hang up my phone call real
be right back I need to have this call
hold on wait come back where are you
going I hook up my phone call for
you Jonna Watson come
back return to me Jonna Watson you will
slow down your horse can you even hear
me slow your horse find K Slow Down slow
your
horse Jonah Watson you got run oh no
where she
going Jon
Watson where do you run why do you run
is it because you are guilty only the
guilty run shoot let's let's have a nice
peaceful conversation let's just have a
peaceful peaceful conversation where you
going where you going I just wish to
speak to you I wish to understand I want
to understand your side of the
story don't run don't run from me don't
run from
me no come back come back why can't why
can't I outrun you Kake Slayer do not
run let's just have a peaceful talk
you'll never catch me what are you going
to do jump off what are you trying what
you what do you plan on doing jumping
off you never catch me no don't jump I
am full of empathy you would fill me
with sadness if you
jumped listen the king the king is evil
trust me trust you how do I know I saw a
stain I saw a stain on his pants on his
pants what did it look like yeah it it
was like pretty big and I think it I
think he's corrupted where was the stain
located it's like you know like on the
backside
oh why are you looking
there I think maybe he got touched by
staining and like corrupted and oh my my
goodness I'm on a secret mission what I
know I know the Queen the queen is on my
team she said that she met eyes with the
King and they fell in
love it's all a lie it's Bruce yeah she
he's trying to seduce her okay I will
trust
you this once you were telling my secret
to everybody I'm sorry I'm sorry I
didn't know you didn't tell everybody
knows my secret Miss I'm sorry I didn't
mean to never going to be able to kill
because you you compromise my mission I
will I will make I will make it right I
will tell everyone that it was just a
joke I was it was just a Gest I a Gest
got to help me you got to help me kill
the king okay
how got find the king and you got to try
to kill him okay how should we
communicate uh I'll find you you'll find
me I'll give you updates then okay Carry
On we cannot be seen together they'll
know they'll know we can't be seen
together I am I have I am returned yes I
just had to have a conversation with
someone a a friend L conversation oh
welcome back cuz thank you why did I get
disconnected cuz Gigi had to go talk to
someone I had to speak to someone um yes
one
onone to spread some empathy she seemed
to have fallen on hard times and it was
a private
call oh I see
yeah pit dor there you are
hello oh where's pad
Dorman where I am by the door cuz he's a
door hello hi who who are you talking
about the one that required empathy oh
um I I spoke to jna Watson a little bit
and I saw her side of things uh she
seems like a pretty good person a good
fellow she's just misguided defected you
she's misguided she just she told me
that she doesn't plan on no no she told
me she told me I heard her side of the
story that she doesn't plan on killing
the King she
promised she promised she promised she
wouldn't kill the king it was only had
to do with her backstory her childhood
history what what happened during her
time stain
killed her Village and they stain killed
her Village The Village was sentient yes
the time the entire Village was the
wandering Village was sentient and the
stains killed her Village and all the
villagers and uh they left a note and it
was a note from the king so she thought
the king had done it the entire time and
she it was cleared up with the meeting
with the king oh I
see she had a one-onone yes we all had
one-on ones remember when you met eyes
with him and he proposed oh yes right
okay now IED he had proposed to our
Queen our highness in here yes yes MH I
remember a clear as day it's almost like
it happened like an hour
ago he proposed to you an hour ago it's
almost as if I can recall you know like
I can recall so well that it's almost as
if he proposed to me an hour ago of
course our our Majesty our highness our
lady in
waiting
yes I'm glad you are aware I am aware I
am fully aware well worry not Jonna
Watson does not plan on killing your
husband so not my husband yet your
husband to be you're yes
with hello
where is the Calamity
stains where did Iris
go has lost the
[Music]
call lament what has befallen the land
the powers of
[Music]
Revelation Glam understands possible Lan
sh mysterious ancient ruin we're not
really shaken to find ourselves in
another world to think of it Scouts from
our Guild are already stationed at the
run for invation in our fight oh then
then your Aid go forth with Valor for
you to regain your head to the Plains
and speak to Hess of the Jade
sword is this a call for
adventure
mayhaps why are we speaking to
disgusting Jade sword when we should be
talking with
heran cup leader who's Valor and why do
we have to go with him
[Music]
exactly oh the
Coliseum you're in
another why does she keep leaving us
again she keeps leaving
us no she she's in the party she's just
not in the call
if you see on the right our party still
has her in it
okay you trolled
[Music]
us prer prefer to page four once
again yes
[Music]
wait where did she
go it seems the
party is a little
bugged should we just remake the party
cuz we have to get meet at the the quest
board let us all meet at the quest
board if I can that sounds like a endid
idea if I can find it oh hello hello are
you going to go on an
adventure mayhaps we are soon when We
Gather our party members too oh do you
do you think that you maybe have some
room for more party members we we have
four hello
hello I don't think there's a limit to
how many people can join our party
there's a limit we shall remake of five
five yeah five I see they've already got
their
four so you two must fight each other to
the death no okay I'm going to bed
it's our rock is gone so we have four oh
true take care nice meeting you today
yeah it's nice meeting you guys okay may
our paths cross again goodbye good luck
thank thank you we should we should
disband the party you can join the call
again the way I'm a nice person I'm a
great fighter too I'm strong that's why
I'm in radi it yes
yes yes yes would you be okay with me
joining your adventure yes we would be
okay you must come to the quest board
with us though because we must remake
our our our mind party okay where is the
quest board I am quite
[Music]
lost it's Quest board this way
where am
I this this town is it's very very
large where is where am I Quest
Master okay
Quest
board Quest
board and be back wait a sec wait a sec
hello hello hello I'm trying to figure
things out I think I think something um
went a miss you know I will leave the
world and come back okay okay I will
also will refer to my tombs to spam this
party what went to miss
okay okay okay okay here here is an
invite to the
party where did my M there we go there
we go there we
go and now we can join there we go the
wonderful
radio
stereo the way you
moveir where what is that where
I don't know I don't want to get
involved in
[Music]
this people beautiful pink lady wa
beautiful um oh gosh these two are
exhibiting an aura that I've never quite
felt before what is your name maybe I
have felt it
I'm I feel like your legs are calling to
me your thighs th are call
to your thighs are calling to me I have
a scyth I sit on your thighs I don't
know why
hey your tast is so sharp you know I
have sharp sh
like a poopy amberin are you li am Jade
sword okay then you're okay sucks
but oh no she's been there so much uh
[Music]
I have no idea that's what my told me to
say it is focused onter as long as I can
join you for your adventure I
[Music]
guess maid my fair Maiden can you open
your magic tombs and go to page four
mayh sure and leave your
party whatever party you may be in we
are better than that so don't worry
going to need you you fine did you you
may have to do that say my brain is Tiny
I know this place by the back of my hand
I am very smart welcome welcome Jo your
party Welcome to our party welcome how
do you know this place like the back I'm
not abandoning Elizabeth she seems to
have made
friends what you are friends we are not
friends we are not friends we are not
friendly to each other she exed me I was
but about hush her gums a traitor she is
a traitor you can hush gums is
supposedly ambercoin Amin she is a liar
like this and she
is God what was that I just I just
contacted someone she is a harlot
too what what happened I know you happen
har what's
Harlot you do not need to know something
wet what
wet where did she go it sounded a little
wet don't you
think wait I'm at peace you know let's
let's let's let's forget about you know
oh recollection recollection Revelation
I forgot everything that happened where
get your sword upgrade you must be
flustered where do
iust amber
coin I will see beauti
[Music]
let me go find
out do I need
to
oh just grab some of these should I grab
these too maybe grab
these can I sell these can we not sell
things are these Quest
too lapis lazuli
where do
[Music]
I I want join the radio call and right
here and then you you click on it you
right click on it and then you ring ring
with the diamond thingy or I don't know
if it's a diamond thingy but the thing
what is Diamond thingy oh actually I
don't know it looks like a pile of dust
to me but it's fine where I'm trying to
I'm trying to recruit the pink th the
beautiful pink thighs to join our call
oh i in it let us Mead at the castle
Gates everyone to go on our journey
Castle Gates I understand everyone do
the quest up until the follow
me follow me up until the uh ruins the
ruins yes no I'm still at the Smithy
Quest wait wait let me let me finish
that real quick yeah okay definely is
there something we wanted to do after
that I'm assuming we speak to well like
you got to get to the Quest first cuz
our quests are so okay wait wait wait
wait sorry let me let me do this real
quick uh I will keep your secrets close
I will not give it up I am
still it's so hard talking to these um
these leest that you have to like you
have to like Crouch like
crazy Le sticky keys comes on I think
got my team off your Trail please have a
good I think they turned
off people maybe I'm the only one to get
the you
ien sticky in a long for but if you
press shift six times there so many of
them I have not flowers have advised to
turn off those sticky keys before how do
I how do I give it to them wait true I
want to give it to help I am being
swarmed at the castle Gates there are so
many many STS oh I only have eight hey
how do you
get some tell me how to get cobblestone
follow me follow me it hurt my queen
what KY Mory K they
hurt what what
happened what is your quest my quest is
to exit the Town Gate head to the Plains
and speak to hastas of the Jade sword
okay we're on the same Quest okay great
Iris wa is your name Iris your name is
Iris yes my name is Iris what yes follow
me here this is the castle gate special
okay we're all very special let us go we
are full of empathy mind
you empathy is our middle name yes oh my
God this world is so large all of our
middle names is empathy Cobblestone is
this
way see over there oh it's minecra I
mean Stone what is Minecraft yes
Minecraft what do you I have no idea
what I just said what how do you craft
the mines yes what are you guess yeah
bully that puppy bully that puppy it's
making pu noises bullying him we are
freeing him of his they're quite a
different crew why are you trying to
kill the rabbit yeah it's a dark
one what's wrong with The Dark
One rabbit what theit on the blue team
so you have to be
full no no it's not what about the cows
normal rabbit can we can we can we make
meat out of the cows wait sorry
instincts I want to get off the horse oh
there we go wait let me
Revelation Revelation Revelation ghost
stories Revelation the cow didn't die
from the Revelation wow this cow is
strong that is a strong cow that is a
strong cow die
Revelation
Revelation re oh my God I didn't mean to
kill those oh God why did I it didn't
drop anything it didn't even drop any
meat I will help you worry kill a cow
Co there we
hey the monsters Dro coins
they Rich well you can become rich I
suppose no we are not to be full of
greed that is not us we are full of
[Music]
empathy up to the I have no idea what
empathy means anymore what does empathy
mean can someone give me a definition of
empathy compassion compassion peace
empathy that's what it means empathy
are you Cerulean cup yes yes we are all
ceran cup we are all ceran cup yes nice
to meet you just very nice what is what
is Jade all about huh what is Jade all
about hey hey hey don't don't be so
aggressive we are courageous fighters
who fight for what's right oh wow oh
okay you guys seem like the actual good
guys okay what we good guys we are good
too the actual oh yeah oh yeah you're
right right full
and we force empathy on people by
killing them
right okay well everybody kind of take
away is that taking things into their
own hands I
guess is that oh excuse me sorry my
horse is a is quite a um you know Rowdy
fella you see I I don't know how to
control it oh what a Rowdy horse you I'm
talking to I'm talking to a Amber coin
member right now who is the Amber coin
member this ambercoin member is the same
member that adopted many children and um
and is and loves money I wonder why Liz
said
that she must love money cuz that's what
she say was Liz you know
the tast good you seem to dislike a lot
of people on my team she was very r w
what kind of money do you eat every
single for breakfast lunch and dinner is
it different every single time Iris Iris
where are you are you in the place I'm
at the Smithy you're at the Smithy I'll
come save
you copper flakes yes I will return what
about silver when do you eat
silver hey hey hey stop talking with
that fake Amber
coin hey get out of
here this place you're don't own this
place hey stay away from her cups are
here stay away from who away from our
team what what her nutrition D was she's
really not bad don't don't talk to don't
talk to her she's like a fake ambercoin
oh she I mean that's not a good that's
not a bad thing right I thought we hated
ambercoin yeah she's Jade sword
apparently not is she actually not
ambercoin she's Jade sword I am oh I
actually thought she was yeah I thought
she was ambercoin too yeah wait you lied
to me I thought you were I thought you
were ambercoin you kept saying you loved
money that was just like a full on
sign how dare you how dare you I could
never saying Amber coin wait where did
your teammates
go I have to apologize I was also lying
on her behalf saying that she was a
member of Jade sword she is
not no she wants to keep her her her
Iden she's not even J
sword oh she's a compulsive liar I my go
don't know where she is from you look
the first time I I I met the you were
try so so the get get your I mean it
makes sense hey hey you don't talk to
hey you don't talk to my killed member
like that yes stop stop it you shush
your mouth hey do not raise your voice
at me I am the next Queen in life
you will have sck on your KNE and I
swear your sword away to
be belongs on the ground is PVP I can
show you where there's PVP there is
would you like to follow me yes there is
that's our Guild the Jade I will take
you to the Jade I will take you to the
Jade sword Guild your guild PP at the G
Jade sword Guild it's right this way
follow me so she is Jade
she Jade sword is
she Jade sword was she not Jade sword I
should just remember this stuff welcome
to the Jade sword Arena guys are we are
we going to dungeon oh yes let's
go yeah you're right we should go to the
dungeon let's go lat on there's the Jade
sword Arena whenever it's waiting for
you where is H of the J sword I do have
courage is on the battlefield I need to
do my quest you guys can I need to do my
quest wait uh what was the next Quest I
need to go back to the quest Master Miss
ninoa where is hastus at the PLS you can
check the map where left shift oh is he
onwards I need to get check the map and
it should show you the NPC need to go
next I grave Duty Quest I do not see him
on
my very far south oh you are here coin
to get your started yay I'm money we
just go the shopkeeper I think it's just
straight where is the
shopkeeper the shopkeeper is right
across the the Smithy okay thank you
yeah I am here he has been expecting
me is it just oh no what is this Jade
sword I think I see shopkeeper
shopkeeper shopkeeper shop South huh am
I just supposed to talk to the shop
maybe
wait across the plains I see
oh hello we must kill all of these ooh
gold D do not be so easily distracted oh
I'm sorry I'm sorry my my empathy I must
return to kill them all you have to do
is talk to me and I'll show you when I'm
got in stock then s what do you want to
buy I must put the stains down do you
stop by if you ever need anything okay
hero youting us have a break and do some
okay you can try visiting the Gill Halls
of the four G guilds for instance each
of them has an activity
okay great ruin do I have a lot of
quests I need to
do not many main the
shopkeeper well these are all side quest
they're you're
like I think okay to go talk to the the
kid in the park you got some time and
why not visit the gardens the children
are tending to them I'm sure okay the
children children let's St some children
St oh wow wait wait while we wait for
friends I'm going to go ahead and pin my
my jade sword out emblem to my C where's
the children where's the children lead
me to the CH where's the children in the
garden there's a child in the Gard is it
the place with the Amber coin is it
where um Liz was trying to take us or is
that a different place no no if you if
you check your map you'll see a red
marker for the next NPC you need to talk
to do you want me to help you wait let
me see if I can figure this out why does
it say I don't have any side quests huh
I thought I
did did I like where should I pin it I'm
coming to find you where are you I'm in
front of the shopkeeper and I'm just
like wait I thought wait do I so I
talked to him he was like go find the
children but then like now I don't have
a quest and I'm just like where's the
children uh so like just follow me mm I
I think yeah it should be I think it
should be around here maybe it was this
way yeah I think have I killed stains uh
there there's a child like in the middle
of the garden there's a Gard sword
there's a garden he's just sleeping
awaken maybe this isn't it I have to
kill child yeah it's the Lees child and
it's in the must be one important child
to be called the Lees child I know right
he's the child of the country anpad
where where did crony
go
thought very cool thank you isn't that a
pen where's the sharp part going into my
eyeball theal child oh found it I found
I think I see the Leal child wait Souls
of Ste open the way I think it showed up
on my map now wasn't there surroundings
Brave Heroes The Secret of ruins I can't
find it I will now sort a part of me the
bestl child oh thank you for the let me
talk to you I just want to say hi the
best child in my head for gifting out
Leal child yes it's the best child ever
child call it battle in this ruin oh
wait is that the the besto child it
looks like any other kid what makes this
one so special ruins how to proceed oh
some have reported hearing a strange
voice but we know not what to make of it
okay let's see and then SS of stains
open the
way okay looks like our team members
already figured out the the rid I get
iron there's a
riddle it says oh slay 10 stains and
then we have find you want to do some
building or gardening got it leave it to
me I'm ready let's go find some iron
canot proceed yet oh yeah you'll we'll
see about
that I've been slaying stains this whole
time dang
it speak to the best in children okay
speak to the pit Dorman okay now I'm at
the pit Dorman pit dor okay you found
the pit Dorman where was the pit Dorman
again it was like in it was in the
yellow area right the green are we
collecting these here we go what the
heck is
this I remember crony saying she wanted
to see the pit dorant 20 minutes ago so
yeah who CR I can't climb I mean I mean
the queen I mean Tam Tam Tam oh oh okay
wait what is your
name Tam Tam Tam your name is Tam yes oh
where'd that come from oh I mean
Jonathan Jonathan named me Tam Tam for
the Azure Maiden C for short that I see
not hold on it makes so much sense
what I'm so soaking in all this
information maybe I didn't use it right
oh oh no not the
map I know you could make used to who is
Tam that's strange that's me
you we all have been in the same party
for tens of minutes and you do not know
her name you just revealed your name
isn't that a bit odd huh I was told that
the
faker are you talking about Liz yes and
you lied to us about affiliations why
did she yell at me then why would she
lie then she just doesn't want we can
gamble here apparently she's in the
arena but I can't find her
The Guild Master wishes to speak with
you please meet him at the J
confused speak to the Jade sword Guild
Master Okay Jade sword Guild Master
oh maybe after our
questell None Shall
breach wait oh never mind you're you
look har hold on I got to I got to drop
out of this call for a excuse me okay oh
oh my goodness she just dropped out of
the call to fight
[Music]
her I hear Harlot and then all of a
sudden the group chat just disappears
you heard the Harlot yeah I just heard
her say oh what a harlot and then all of
a sudden kicked out and then she left or
she would like discontinued the party
call or something I think she is
fighting the
Harlot man there's so many harlots
there's I feel like I've heard say harl
20 times
already's yes there's only one Harlot it
is Liz the
Harlot oh I see that's the Harlot okay
okay she's the Harlot gotcha cuz she was
kissing us called Watson a harlot as
well I would never call
that J Watson is pure of
heart she did kiss me yes who kissed you
Liz yes she she she smooched me and and
now I can sing a song about kissing a
girl now oh wait
congratulations will you sing now for
you I actually no I can't remember the
Melody I couldn't possibly remember the
Melody I just remember that it's I
kissed a girl and I liked it the taste
of her cherry CH I did
not no no no I didn't like it it's just
the lyrics you know and
IC the taste of her cherry I think she
was wearing chck I think it would taste
like Wax personally many around I will
[Music]
help I pray will eat
okay finding a way for you to regain
your powers of
Revelation yes and then you keepi going
down this you lead me to the loud one
what see she's so mean to me
[Music]
I will have a word with her from our
Guild do wish we could all get along
you're over 10 now oh there's no such
thing as getting along with everyone
what are you talking about thank you I
have to drop this call to give her a
piece of my mind oh there she is you
what you mean the loud one you disgust
me are
you to me what was I thinking think you
the loud one cut her some slack only I
can get her yeah yeah no I've been
bullying her enough I feel kind of bad
she's all by herself is she is she good
what you say I not I have my guild mates
in my heart Callie is in my heart me yes
let's not
be well only if she apologizes HED only
if she
apologizes I love all kinds of friends
so yeah of course I'm honored he hey red
red thing hi am Elizabeth
Elizabeth red red thing I'm talking do
you not see me talking to this no I
didn't hear you talking red thing can
you apologize to
Jonathan Jonathan Jonathan with the G
she's she's very hurt is will open the
see she's making her war
cry underworld we shall secure the
surroundings you may proceed undisturbed
what am I supposed to do apologize say
sorry I I apologize that you are sad
investigate the underworld dungeon then
speak to the apologize that you were a
lesser
[Music]
being here have some of my melons ladies
we all share the same goal
where I don't know I'm trying to F to
you supposed to protect the
land I should leave some stuff here it
seems I cannot give you my melons oh no
it's just what are we talking about the
Harlot is talking about melons now put
me into J
I
tried these melons are stuck to my
hand oh never mind I can't leave of her
melons I apologize for not giving you my
melons can I have your melons
too I would try but I cannot give it to
them why why how can you try and and
fail at giving
melons I am I am using the uh the musle
the muscle the Q muscle is not working
my
God okay I'm just going to pretend I
didn't hear that and just go oh is this
a shared chest you we have been
expecting you do you have do you see my
stuff way to enter the ruins we guess
everyone can use it some have reported
heing
aam
key good you have to slay 10 stains too
exit the Town Gate head to the PLS speak
to Okay Okay slay 10 stains and speak to
just it's okay okay I think I'm almost
at the the dungeon you just need to kill
10 10 of barrel will be mine I to kill
10 of them okay okay there more like ah
yes I will slay them I will take this
corner Barrel from me there are no such
thing as like you know okay I'm going to
go koing them with the I guess they did
get rid of the
recipes let me just kill more this
corner Barrel is mine
stop okay I
guess Wonder
they must have entered the dungeon
already where is this
dungeon it's uh you can get a key for it
if you slay enough
enemies Oh we must speak oh we have to
investigate is it this thing this portal
is this thing I got a key for it but not
everybody has a key for it I don't think
okay I will wait we will wait
[Music]
waiting for my
iron my tens of
iron is my skill AOE
Revelation
Revelation I can't tell how far it goes
oh my God it barely does anything you
killed my prey well I mean I Revelation
it what are you talking about I didn't
kill it I Revelation it
[Music]
I'm dying
don't two parties I forgive you dearest
some people said that what is
youra
Elizabeth I am Jonathan with a
G yeah oh ow it's actually Jonathan G we
have a we have a Jonathan and our girl
too but I do not know it is with a G oh
that that is fine that's a John does
that mean you are gathan Jonathan no no
no
it'ss I think there is it's in the other
shop I
see G I shall give you my melons another
time one step closer to Extinction
accept oh why are you eating your melons
in front of me fashion surprise
box just be that way build that way now
what do I do maybe I can trade my melon
with dude dude through the power of my
aathy I forgive you I know it must have
been very rough to have fallen in hard
times ow oh did you guys make up I'm I
made up with her okay that's good ah yes
I got the key I got the underworld key
thing I don't forgive okay me too yeah
shall we what should we do should be get
one yeah I'd like to go too but don't we
need to be in a party I can go to the
dungeon now
anyone does everyone have the map mean
not map does everyone have have their
key yeah I think Ena already entered
though didn't she can we go in oh give
me a second I'm I'm shopping last minute
but I'll be right
there is this key up here is this the
dungeon where am I World they has this
key where is the dungeon anyway I can
hear you guys now oh my gosh or you guys
can hear me sorry this way right there
yeah I got the key um already enter no
I'm back at the town just chopping a bit
I see it you have to use the war and
then you go all the way to the
end what wooden swords is enough what if
we made two parties of you think that
would be good H should we should we buy
stuff should we buy
upgrades wait she wants the well we
don't really have iron you know what
let's Let Me Mine a bit I see gold right
here the lady in the the in the flavor
text no what are you talking about what
do you mean that's your I was almost
done I was almost done fine actually no
get out of my way get out of my way
you no that's what you did to me you
will never you will never successfully
dig that one out you will never no no no
no I I will not allow
you
you're you know what it's probably
faster there are people in a cut scene
in front of us or they're seeing visions
in their head and they are reacting to
it and I they must be crazy then they
must be crazy then wait I I think they
must cleared the uh cleared the dungeon
do two other people want to enter the
dungeon together maybe let's enter the
dungeon let's enter the dungeon five of
us go then one person will probably be
left behind really only four can go only
five yeah we have five yeah but I feel
like we should also what about Liz we
she's not in our party we can go to
teams of three we can swi yeah we can
split yeah that would be the best way
everyone meet
inside are we really going to go are we
going to go in with um with wooden
swords I I think I should probably
upgrade sword can I can can you possibly
be kind so oh so kind to um throw me a
stone
sword gathan I will I will have to
return to town to get you a stone sword
let me make
haste let me come with I think we have
to split the party before going into the
dungeon there's a area in there that we
must make ready checks I think we are
allowed to split the party before we do
our ready checks okay if you say
so who there they
go all are repeatable I think yeah oh
okay
I am here Fair Maiden
Iris oh
gathan my lovely handsome gathan yes yes
you and your Jonathan maybe after we
clear it the first
time did just pronounce joh I am here to
purchase you I mispronounce many words
oh it's okay it's comically large please
accept this trade this is how a normal
sword looks like
yes I have a stone sword you may have
some raw beef thank you I will eat it in
front of you to show how appreciative I
am it's time for yes please eat the ra
eat it
ra so good how did that taste it tasted
so good I'm about to a backpack I'm
super happy to hear that she ate a raw
okay
um and then where's the oh okay I have
to right click oh right click like this
and then sure there we go o oh you gave
me the whole set thank you actually no
wait no sorry I misunderstood wait where
is it okay nice nice nice thank you nice
nice
nice I'll
just pickax this yeah okay nice Let Us
return let us return ow
[Music]
I'm getting the hang of
this
fast gidy Giddy Up gidy Up horsey why
doesn't it jump it only knows how to
Winnie this way towards towards the
bridge we are here my horse you
glitched she's still slang
SL okay I don't know do we do we have to
do this quest to be a do the next bit
yes did you guys kill 10 kill 10 if you
kill 10 then we we can go to the next
thing yeah
Elizabeth do you not have a normal sword
find a mystical
sounding my freakishly large one is is
wonder what I can do with the stone P
freakishly weak freakishly weak sword
attack
[Music]
Revelation Revelation copper
oh
[Music]
oops I finished my quest I'm just doing
it for fun now I love
killing what I love killing
things right I'm a grim reaper oh but
not you guys I wouldn't hurt you wait
you're a grim reaper how do you know
that that's what I did before is what
everybody told me wait really who told
you what we doing to oh the Kaya people
are
that float around in my head Liz her
Quest completion so she can enter how
close is she I think she needs to kill a
few more stains outside by the way by
the way Liz it won't tell you you just
got it you just got to know how many you
killed
wait there's one over here I'm going to
go dig for some more stuff
wow I got to hoard all the all the
materials you
see that's what I'm here for hoarding
yes
[Music]
okay hey what are you doing what are you
doing here huh how you my new
friend you hoarder yes you hoarded you
hoarded my gold you're a hoarder who are
you speaking
to I'm speaking to one lady that is is
not in our group call for some reason
even though she is a part of the
team how could they do such a thing Dam
man she she really likes hanging up on
us so you know I don't know I don't know
what's her
problem maybe it's the person who
creates the phone call hangs up and it
hangs up for
everyone perhaps
oh I'm going to test
it watch this what my fellow friend
thing did it work yes it did kick
everyone it does drop I see I
see oh oh I didn't mean to oh I can't
swim wait how do I swim oh there we go
oh there's diamond in here
[Music]
where' my call
go I was checking
something a that is a good
idea
hello sorry oh there's the I did not
mean to hang up the phone call
why do you keep hanging up my connection
I was entering a tunnel uh the tunnel
seems that the magical connection
between our brains causes it to to drop
the call you mean this is all this
talking is telepathic yeah I'm talking
directly into your head that's a new
word oh
[Music]
wow Sasa magical
world how do I throw thing oh waist bin
okay yeah recycle lady recycle you may
be a queen but you should recycle copine
what what excuse me I don't think I've
ever been called something so foul hello
kopine no maybe I have but that's
definitely very
yucky hero Theon
let autograph pleasure to see everyone
are you leaving or are you incoming we
are
incoming oh many people I wish you
luck this isn't the right way it's not
the right way you have to fall off this
Cliff here defin otherwise you to jump
promise okay I Tri promise as a member
of the ceran cup I don't know I trust
easily yeah don't do that just all the
way down I can't I can't don't want
there's a wall
there's a l i are you sure move further
move further are you sure follow the
light it means you're not ready I can't
jump it's not allowing me to she's not
ready she is not
ready what's under
here
into we're going to split into two
yeah is different all right sorry we're
pranking you Sor I have regret to say
that's the
B get inside the
D are we going in the dungeon first and
then we split no we yeah go inside past
the bridge and then we can split our
party kitty
cat turning back
now farewell bye bye
orang yes Tashi k kiar
close
enough I shall meet you
again past the rainbows of Greater
Tash goodbye Tanashi
Kiara her name was Kiara thought was
Kiara I don't know what they're talking
about they're making me really
uncomfortable
May Kia sounds familiar can you please
leave me
alone where is everyone I have issues
with people I am right in front of this
the Ed at the edge of the bridge group
chat okay Comm we should get out of the
call group chat hello group chat group
CH oh my God hey assemble assemble
assemble leave me alone I just want to
go in the dungeon with my
friends I don't know what you're talking
about please leave me
alone no I don't know what you're
talking about I just want to go I just
want to go into the dungeon with my
friends is someone stopping you from
entering the dungeon oh big up
sliz may I should get out of here who
was preventing hey what are you guys
doing to my
honorary guild member hold on there's a
CIA person that's being very rude let me
get rid of
them uh me put them in timeout for 24
hours there we go that's right I'm in
the toilet so
white should we go in you're
in yes come
just come come um that's not the dungeon
yet you it's the it's the path going
toward the dungeon so you can I get it
thank you appreciate that what is crony
doing in a toilet hey like I said group
chat assemble stop hanging around in the
toilet wherever you are yes yes not in
the
toilet how what what what what are you
letting out that you're taking so long
in the toilet just wait where are you
hurry up and hurry up and where where in
front of the
dungeon in front of a dungeon no no you
must not in front of a
dungeon You're the only one that's not
here use the War aren't we aren't we at
the
canyon no click the thing to go in after
you get the key oh okay
henceforth known to all we must enter
the
dungeon okay God we must split and enter
the dungeon yeah we got to split up I
don't knowz knows is Liz is does Liz
know okay okay let me go let me go see
if I can pick her up Liz I don't know if
she can read let us go to the dungeon
towards the dungeon if we're in a
private call can she not hear us I let
us go in Dungeon she can hear us we are
in a radio call okay yes yes all right
let us I am going to go to page four of
my magical Tob okay we can make a new
group and just band this party
yes party
disbanded I'll make a new one then
um all right claim your three two claim
your two my two claim your
two who's my my two claim your M
want claim your
two
yeah yeah yeah oh you guys y oh my gosh
they're very frightening but I'll invite
them what do you mean frightening
let me grab Miss
ninoa okay and let me grab thank you Liz
who I have forgiven yes I mean aren't
you also the aren't you also perhaps
like something that might be connected
to this dungeon we have a cheat code
yeah huh I mean I do get a familiar
feeling competition now accept our inv
Miss Liz Miss wait drop out of the radio
then I suppose so a new radio call then
yeah okay is everyone ready standing by
to enter the
dungeon oh there we go stand by we're
going to do amazing everyone stand by to
enter the Finish faster than the other
teams yeah yeah we will enter the
dungeon no players standing by you got
to St we got to ready up do we have to
ready first yes there you go enter ready
check oh underworld dungeon let's go
it'll be so easy what is this underworld
a domain of boundless oppressive
Darkness as feared as it is avoidable to
holds the final resting place for every
creature that walks the Earth yet even
in this realm of the Dead where are
those who live and call home I see naruo
do finding the final resting
[Music]
place oh I will
join I'm entering radio call yes enter
radio call so we're not lost pull your
your radio out and join the party call
dear Liz yes yes yes we're good okay
does not look like it is this
way we must go forth this
way
wow I've seen a lot of people die today
or I sensed it I've sensed it in my head
that's run let's go we are not going to
die through our empathy that is that one
of those transport teleport things we
got to go to then does look like egg
looking things maybe we reach it over
here let's
see yeah someone can Photoshop
underworld dungeon bracket s
yeah everyone rank whoever did the best
new checkpoint unlocked it's a
checkpoint
oh okay
ouch they're going to they're going to
be they're going to be monsters I think
so like this place seems like a good
place to fight my good very wide open
space I guess you should go
open oh she was behind us go towards the
oh you are up
there no I'm I am down in the lava oh
you can I perishing jump up yeah yeah
yeah if you're on the lava block you can
sneak and you won't take damage unless
you're in the liquid one then
pray and then you can get this
checkpoint this wonderful beautiful
checkpoint and then it seems that we are
going to engage in
parishing I am now going to engage in
the art of Parkour
huh I cannot I can't click this oh you
don't have to click on it I think it's
just activated on by team bases probably
it activates in your brain waves o
portable Lantern very
nice got a portable
Lantern yeah I bought it at the shop oh
what a good
purchase I will have to check the shop
next
time are you okay the draw distance I'm
fine of course I'm fine I am a a hero
are you frightened mehs are you mayhaps
frightened no I'm never
frightened you can make this jump I'm
hungry hi hungry hello hungry I thought
your name was
[Music]
Liz all
right let's
go this way and
up and
[Music]
H and H go first
you're doing very
well I do not need to hear that from you
loud one no what I thought that we have
made up we've made a meds no you are
doomed to fall no you are doing so well
we're almost there yes we're almost
there good thing we have the next
checkpoint does she revive at the next
checkpoint I am at the checkpoint I
wonder if she has to unlock at her does
if I get this doesn't it pop up on your
screen
too new checkpoint unlocked try try
dying dear dear
Liz oh okay if you say so try dying and
see what
[Music]
happens oh hi hey this is a Str you are
magic we figured it out we don't need
this as a strat I was just testing your
heroic
yeah that is all your strength it was
due to our strength that this was
possible yes I was seeing if I could
trust
you worry not I see it I see the
checkpoint Over
Yonder that was almost
dangerous
dangerous my middle name is it maybe I
don't know what my middle name is
which way is it this way I'm trying to
make eye contact with our next point of
I think we're supposed to go towards the
thingy so this way this way yes could I
make the jump
no it
hurts it's like you never left he yes
was just right behind you this whole
time suspicious castle looking thing
this Castle won't know what hit it once
I'm done with this
Castle it's going to regret standing
here in the name of
empathy oh we got to climb from this
side up this
[Music]
way this
way where is it where is the tree point
I see it I see her for
empathy is this a war oh my
gosh it is safe up here there is nothing
to be scared
of I'm not AF yes do not be afraid have
the checkpoint yeah yeah checkpoint
obtained so worry not okay need it
though you are so good at climbing like
a mountain goat she so good I well
Channel your mountain goat Channel your
mountain
goat make sure you're not hungry I'm
eating M
bread
oh all right man I love
Venture wao checkpoint do you think
something will kill us in here which way
shall we go most likely ah a
zombie be gone foul Beast what is this
very dark room they are red zombies this
a maze what what's in his hand a knife
what is that note we lost Liz where did
you go I'm behind you okay
okay I am discovering the secrets of the
the zombies
oh I found it I think I lost you
guys uh no you closer I'll go back to
you don't worry I'll make sure these
zombies don't hurt
you this way oh my gosh they are
spawning holding like quite frantically
the same way oh they have different star
key oh are you okay wait they have Keys
maybe have to
them they're hurting me are you okay I'm
getting surrounded by zombies There's
there there's many of them I got
you it
hurts wait I think we're supposed to
collect the shaped ke which one how many
should we
collect
um so far I have star triangle and
circle okay
[Music]
where do we put
them it
burns I also have a star two triangles
in a
circle okay I don't know how many we'll
need so maybe we
can I'll throw this
[Music]
up wait okay all right you guys good um
um I'm
okay I do not know where you
are what does this
say this is
nothing oh there's a keyhole okay okay
okay wait I can't put any oh oh I just
got to click the thing wait we got to
find Liz though I see her name she's
right behind us okay let's go to the
next
area H oh the recycling V TR oh no what
a joyous day wow do great
what is your name who me um
n Nino yeah can call me
n whichever
one Nina Nina Nina it is a beautiful
name thank
you we just call you li you may okay do
you prefer something else
[Music]
um H oh oh is this a puzzle as you are
offering
H
oh nah just Liz fine just Liz okay yes
just Liz I don't know why but your
majesty came we supposed to light up
everything every single one if we click
frantically this is what I learned in my
my past is that a puzzle can always be
solved through
the bruest of
forces
umm you
know yeah you know what I
mean this is going to take a while my
tummy is shook oh I did not mean to KI
you from the party you stood in front of
my face rejoin come back
please please rejoin the party I did not
mean to I did not mean to do that I was
please please
well gone for the first time and then
they leave me any of the blocks is it
only you who can click it I'll accept
maybe it this only me that can click it
well I'm I hope you can click it I see I
see I'm clicking I'm clicking I used to
be able to but now I can't oh why ex you
were clicking
them yeah I can click it oh maybe maybe
maybe it's a party thing maybe cuz I
accidentally did the thing what do I no
oh no do we even know what we're
supposed to do
here apparently other part of words are
being beamed into my head other parties
had the same thing happen
oh why would they who would put a puzzle
inside of a dungeon no nothing I think
it's just a
bung who would dare do such a
thing well it's all up to you let's just
[Music]
see oh
no oh
no
we you know we need your we need your
Superior brain
power should I maybe get out of this
world and then
return maybe that'll work I it'll kick
me out of the of this world hopefully it
do rather hopefully it does not I'll be
right back fingers crossed
[Music]
oh welcome
back I am here can you click it hold on
it's still
loading I
believe
okay oh I can click it now yay
huzzah huzzah than thank
goodness hold on should we just have one
person do it at yes time I I trust this
to
you you can do it I entrust this task to
you if I trust myself lady
[Music]
Nino not smart
enough you are so
wise wise beyond your
years I think you would do better than I
did the first time I don't know what
happened so much was
[Music]
happening so close I see it in my mind's
eye see you solving this yes ah you are
getting so close to solving it
[Music]
I am going to find fitting music because
right now the music in my my brain waves
are sending to be quite Jolly but this
is a tense situation this is very tense
my brain is being tested Sor right that
everyone that hears this it's going to
be loud again
[Music]
um
guys jump scare
warning
huh are you
ready my brain
hurts oops
[Music]
it's so close so much of it is lit up my
brain hurts Nino you are you are of the
biggest of brains you are so wise I
believe in thee believe in me who
believes in
thee you are this
moment
oh oh oh my gosh you are so close you
lady Ena what
I don't do what did you what did you
work out oh I don't know oh you don't
know okay I thought you worked it out I
did not I thought I
did okay feel like
you I don't
know is this the part where people took
the longest probably
Le this must have been what caused
people to falter for so
[Music]
long you got this
what is going on in your
head
nothing it is so full of thought that
you only think that way but I'm sure
that you are thinking many
things I am yeah you you are thinking so
much
ah it seems I cannot help with the
puzzle you may have to disconnect your
Consciousness and come back just as Ena
did uh what
completely yes well you will have to
return to to your
conscious your default state of mind and
then return to this
body okay I'll try as in
um
in
in apparent according to my scriptures
that it reads disconnect from the game
and and return and re reconnect okay
I'll be right back reconnect to the game
I'm starting to remove
wa what what does that eight stand for
oh my
goodness you did it all day cuz you were
starting to remember cuz you were
remembering
Hol Hol life what is Hol life what is
Hol live where is welcome back she
solved it while you were gone I solved
it I'm starting to remember starting to
remember things yeah but did you work
out how you how you solved it
we we saw Hollow live and then it was
solved what I think Hollow live is a big
clue yeah it made the letter H and then
she solved it immediately after because
of hollow l oh it's cuz of H I guess we
can go ahead yeah now we can
continue something something Hollow is
it telling us we are Hollow but we are
alive yes maybe we are alive the hollow
is alive us maybe we'll find the answer
at the end of this place
there must be something here please
rejoin my telepathic radio channel oh
yeah in case we are to get lost oh we're
here
okay ring I am inside your
brain hello you're in my brain I'm in
your
brain we
are what is that school
what does that mean wow I don't know is
it looking at me like that feel
danger oh no whatever is ahead of
us what the what what's
happening turn around we must run turn
back around run run run run oh there's
no Rock oh no oh no what's happening
uh-oh we're
fall I fell
what was that I would have do that us
thought I thought I could why that skull
attack us oh what is this there's a
mushroom mushroom d a skeleton are these
the skeleton that are oh that's your
skill okay I thought it
exploded do we have to survive this is
this uh waves of
enemy the way the W the skeletons are
they're really hurting us
make sure you keep yourself well fed oh
I am very hungry thank you for reminding
me
does do we have to do something with
this
mushroom how do we feed it oh oh we let
it have the
mushroom beautiful now what I did
something is there another
mushroom we just keep killing it I don't
know
[Music]
what the oh we can feed it these items
oh well done feel like it comes back
alive we need to bone meal
this it drops an
item if we can bring it CL closer I
couldn't pick it up oh I
see so we got to kill it here and then
the tree will grow cuz it drops bone
meal when it dies and it doesn't like us
picking it up die on the platform
oh oh it's growing she's growing hey
nice one and soon we can
parkour
yeah all
right nice okay we're getting closer
come here
skeleton do not come here
skeleton come closer skeleton come to
this middle platform with the tree I
need you to take
root I think we can already go maybe
there's like buttons here what do the
buttons do yeah I've grown it a little
more okay I think we're ready to go
okay
maybe the
sure oh yeah we can totally jump from
this let's go okay okay okay on my way
up make sure we were well fed there's
more more
trees to kill with the skeletons
I'll wait for
everyone I can't can't make this
jump you guys can climb the vines too at
the start
oh I'm climbing yeah
yeah oh gosh up two trees next up
upes wow I seem to have lost my climbing
capabilities
no why can't I why can't I too powerful
that's the thing we we it's hard to go
up but like on your own with the
skeleton attacking no I just don't know
how to climb in this game up up up all
right maybe I can shoot down from above
I am spamming holding the up button
wonder if it
reaches ow be gone skeleton
oops okay go go go a larger oh climb the
vine I'm climbing
how does one
climb my hands and Paws holding the
largest largest thing good job
Nino all
right oh there are buttons up
here all right keep going guys what do
they
mean I'm a bit
stuck you
good yeah I'm always good I am the Jade
sword I
am
yeah uh uh anyway uh do
anything well I was almost not good but
I'm good oh I'm glad you are
good I guess okay it's not I like you or
anything oh you good yes okay go we are
all good now there two
there should be another skeleton yet oh
no there's two come here skeleton all
right draw it here I call this the act
of hiting my
trees oh it was a little far
sorry you are so proficient
attack nice okay there's another one
here should we grow one first do we only
need one
seems like I might need two Spa one at a
[Music]
time
ow un hand me foul skeleton
Beast maybe where is
it oh it's still knock back
huh oh if only I can push to item it's
fine do they both have to be high in the
sky do they do they both have to do both
of the trees have to be upes I mean
let's start with one maybe and see where
it
goes maybe it's like a mechanic we need
but I'm
not okay got one here I see oh there's
another spawn
bring it
here push it against the Trigg get on
there
buddy over there come here you want to
hit me on this tree trunk so
bad mayhaps you are obsessed with
me this looks large enough I think we
can just jump
let's see where this goes okay
ow leave me
alone all
[Music]
right okay up up up
up and then over
here what
why does it look like
[Music]
this think we got to grow it one more
or maybe maybe we have to grow it or we
go over this way potentially over here
and up and then down oh yeah yeah yeah
yeah I don't think we can make
this y y y y yum yum
your way over here oh from that way okay
okay
nice
okay oh
goodness this this tree is in my
way oh this is a little rough we have to
gra one
more we do have to kill one
more I will fall from my high
space I'm okay I am okay you're good I
will kill the
skeleton
okay skeleton will kill me did it grow
did I make it grow no I think this is
the maximum
then I wonder if we do have to grow both
of them and then it links to the other
side oh yeah maybe oh yeah
that could unless unless unless I'm
killing it worry not stay up
there let me know if you see a
pathway okay I've grown it
more oh you have is there a new
pathway
[Music]
yeah ah I am yes good job have you made
it ah is there nearly I've made it oh I
I will die I will die I will I will
die but I don't want to
die but if you die you may live
no quick we miss you to
die M I want to just look at this how
amazing this
to the Denis of the Underworld the light
emanated by Souls was vital one one
moment teammates I just want to look at
this tree and Ponder it's just so
amazing what are you
pondering what is I just need to have
some thoughts to myself for a sec yes
yes oh if you see over here this oh no
how do I make this come
back there's a book in this portal
Light Em by Soul was vital needed it to
survive in this ever cold and dark
environment yet among them there was a
her a heretic who called their custom
into question do we really need to take
others Liv to sustain our own no there
has to be another way and so she stepped
into the plane above who is she she got
on a plane she got on a plane what's a
plane I think
so what is a what is a plane plane the
astral plane the plane
above the world the the plane of the
world above above
all the plane of Life the plane we call
Life ah yes I saw the meaning of life in
this tree what did you see what did I
say
42 42 42 42 I counted 42 blocks I mean
tree leaves tree leaves only 42 count
she can count it's kind of a lot mine
eyes mine my eyes your power of
Revelation has grown stronger oh
wow you recovered a portion of your
memories what did I remember hollow life
a memory H live H is this the timing to
live play the thing oh it's the time
okay let me acquire it it's time to play
the
thing hold on it seems that the thing
the the data in my head it seems to be
going a little slowly like it's a very
large amount of data transferring into
my brain
okay I am
ready
[Music]
Souls wow
a Reaper's job is to end people's lives
and take their
souls that's how it's always been
they're partying spirits of the
underworld need their
sustenance but I keep
wondering oh my goodness
is this go get him to do no is this it's
not the woman who joined our
party this is the woman who joined our
party what is she do what's going on
that's
her God her memories wow was that was
that from the dungeon the memory these
are her memories it was kind of
like she did say she was a Reaper when
we met with her Reaper should help the
living maybe she remembers more now not
take away future if the others can't
accept that that's their loss so cool
the Underworld the
underworld she so does that mean if we
I'll do things my way if we go ahead and
clear more of these dungeons we'll have
more of these memories coming back I
wonder I wonder who whose memory will we
unlock
next
wow that seems so
cool my
goodness that's my guildmate that's your
guild M it's true that was your guild
that is
true my God that's so cool it seems
there's a lot more to her than meets the
eye yeah well maybe maybe the Jade sword
Guild Master knows more yes we must we
must ask Let Us return to the gam the
master more of our own
memories oh it's time to play the Happy
adventuring oh yeah happy happy music
what
music wow
okay yay now it's no longer ambient
noise World wow great job guys hey we
saw your memories
yeah you remember how interesting I do
but did you guys just clear or did you
guys something else after it's a little
embarrassing clearbody see we cleared
and we were just like waiting and you
know we just having you know just having
fun in that L room we take that long we
were did we take that long yeah you did
oh yes we we oh yeah we we finished wa 3
hours ago even yeah yeah 3 hours 3 hours
ago what let's go turn into the quest
time flies you know oh yeah we can turn
into Quest did you guys notice that your
re Revelations are sparkly now are after
the after the dungeon they sparkle oh my
God they are sparkly oh we're too far
they can't hear what is our Revelation
Sparkle oh yeah yeah they do check it
out they are they're so shiny I guess
it's time to test them
out
cool I am on my
horse where do we my horse is amazing
look at my horse seems the same o t
amazing
wait how do you know that song I don't
have any memories know song maybe our
our parents sing it us
young maybe maybe it is it maybe might
have been your lullabi yeah maybe it was
my
lullaby maybe a damage P but maybe we'll
see oh just like that wait is it the
Guild Master outside or in this place
too I want to he's like underneath the
thing jingy hey
oh so the one in the
arena uh I think there like an entrance
and then you go in the little cave
looking thing I am here yeah there he
is I finished your quest I am heartened
to see that you have returned unharmed
pre tell what transpired at the
ruins a flashback I see to think the
ruins held such
Secrets okay Crystal deep within that
when touched returned a fragment of your
memories to you oh my goodness memories
which in turn reawaken the power of
Revelation AIT at only a fraction of its
potential that your summoning and the
discovery of these ruins should con
coincide so
closely there must be some connection
between the ruins and the power of
Revelation I see I see Brave hero seek
rubius to Guild Master at least I don't
have to read any of this anymore his
Guild has also been searching for
strange ruins in the lands of lesto
mayhaps they have discovered something
she has transcribing for him yes thank
you thank you my throat is dead today
from all the stuff that the Scarlet W
Guild
Master where would he be located
checking my map and just
following
ninoa uh there's a the a bridge here
onwards to
rubius show yourself rubious it's not
the right
way this
way this way
rubious where's the entry way
here ah you must be in here
[Music]
I found him no mayhaps not lost the big
hat oh wait where is he the
gatekeeper he's outside we need to make
these he needs to show himself more
clearly returned from investigating
those ruins are you I've gotten the gist
from Rus no nothing less nothing more I
now sense within you a trace of the
power big hat I love those I love these
hats they remind me of a certain Moon
Queen from we you're
right from a certain Elden game yeah
with with lots of rings goodness I I
think yeah I know what you're talking
about the lots of my preciouses
oh inv the power of Revelation
fasinating most fascinating I
hypothesize that those ruins are the key
to unlocking your powers we the Scarlet
one have also been investigating near
the Plains and wanted to know it just
off the coast we speak to Corin a spine
a spine a lighter with a striking
resemblance to Revelation the Scarlet
good hero would you be willing to travel
to the coast and Aid in our efforts
there yes members of our Guild are
already there hard at work I'm quite
sure they will appreciate your
assistance good luck and excelo
Excel go to the coast and speak to Corin
of the Scarlet wand all right Corin Show
Yourself ah my
horse ooh they're like
purple where's the
coast they must be pretty far I guess
they're outside huh my gosh it's Ki
beu she has wandered off she did not see
me but it seems she has returned from
her
mission is the
coast through a portal mayhaps
[Music]
what where is
itoon where Where Art Thou the coast the
coast is by the
sea I will seek the sea
do you see the sea oh it's you oh my
gosh it's keki beu she is back
she Jonathan gathan yes it is I
Jonathan I am at the uh um the coast is
by the Sea and the sea is near the coast
where is the coast and where is the
sea uh is South South
please what
what westest follow the I had
disappeared we got into a fight with
some people and then we cleared a
dungeon we did indeed yes we indeed
Theon how is the D you can hear me was
it can are there any dangers you can I
have found the ocean the coast there are
some dangers but trust your heart and
your empathy and it will guide you to
the end ah yes empathy will guide me
empathy will guide you are right empathy
will my I will Forge onwards keku I will
forge on I must meet
waves with curiosity yes thank you I
will go onwards
my farewell where is Nino Ena by the sea
I am by the Sea where is the
sea it is to the West after you get out
oh okay so I must leave the kingdom
walls you
must gathering
information object known as the rainbow
Coral
cluster we can breathe underwater I am
lost I am just going in a a
[Music]
circle rainbow Coral shards and refined
magical
energy need not concern yourself with
the lad good hero okay in search for the
coral shards iridescent as a rainbow
once you have found enough please return
to the guild and present to the Guild
Master I I am making
haste this kingdom is very
large it is
indeed quite a large cler oh
[Music]
that was
wake where have they gone where yeah
where are they Where Art Thou oh okay uh
oh hello where is the shoper
a really in Good Old
Days Cil
[Music]
tears thoral empathy our empathy will
keep us
together
together oh thanks to our empathy
I am headed west this West this is just
follow the road West Southwest westish
Southwest oh Fair Maiden it does this
feel like it's
East oh I am not the leader I think who
who do you see I see the fair maiden of
dark pink dark pink of the super hot
pink she says Super H pink super hot
pink she says I I need you I need
them hot pink hot hot super
pink yes okay I wait right here oh the
hot pink Maiden has is waiting for you
the hot pink Maiden you must join our
party once
more thank you I know hot pink m is very
popular a protect you thanks thank you
thank you my oh my God yes yes yo join
our weapon look kind of cool H that's
very cool t t just a book it's very cool
you're actually doing spells you're like
a
magician I'm just doing ninja stuff wait
she's a
ninja where's cro I guess crony crony is
too busy doing her her crony I mean her
Tam stuff yeah
yeah I mean mean the Queen the Queen the
queen Tam yeah Tam
Tim
Tam Tam how could Tam have done you're
under
attack save you yes
they cry like a dog to make us feel
guilty she's looking for the Scarlet
leader isn't it somewhere around here
that's why I'm also the Scarlet leader
is back in town this is the he is back
in town
uhhuh wait it's actually sparkling in my
head shiny right it's sparkling and in
the inventory too oh my God you actually
you have knuckles I need to see your
revelation can you re revelate for me
can you
reate
[Applause]
Revelation yo she's a
punch punching girl actually kind of
cool how about you show us how about you
revelate us are you talking are you
telling me yes yeah yes pink one okay
wait wait wait a sec let me let me just
get the Revelation um thing wait wait
here uh go let me get my goex I mean not
my go Exel what what
what no no no no sorry no nothing
nothing okay I'm ready now I'm ready to
revelate okay reate okay
Revelation that is crazy W where did
that go where dides that go I can't tell
where that it went to the ground I think
wherever you're aiming your or your uh
Vision I imagine yes yes where her aim
is true where her eyes aim exactly I aim
at my targets yes I gosh she's got them
re me into the
end revelate for me enaa I mean
n okay
[Music]
Revelation oo so cool oh my god oh it's
like a gun I
mean what is a gun what a gun is I have
no idea what a gun is but it must be
something like that if it if it work
knew what a gun was I would say would
it's kind of similar to a yeah something
like that like a
[Music]
gun man I love holding on to these two
stars you looks like you can assassinate
some people I can I can someone called
me Naruto who's Nar Nar I don't know I
have no idea you who's a Naruto it's a
what's what is Naruto crony not who is
crony was
crowny join our party Tam Oh yay Yes Man
wel imagine having a girl named Tam in
our party right now man it stands for
the almighty right yes Tam is great Tam
is great actually name me so yes yes I
thought for the almighty the Azure
maiden and then Tam said it was too long
so I said Tam is okay too
yeah it's a good name it is a very good
last name is Gander right yeah Gander
when you become Queen is your is your
last name going to change I'm going to
assume I kind of want to keep my last
name though I don't know but you're
going to get married to the king Tam
leest yeah well I don't want to be
called like you know
Tam Mrs Le best Gander laal how would
you
hyphenate uh you know I I want to I want
to keep my name you're going to keep it
yeah I'm just going to keep it I'm just
going to tell the king like no I see and
besides like stole my kill he's he's an
old going be my kingdom soon what mine
yeah keep
keep level 10 now but you you do you do
hold affection for him right
Revelations yeah yeah for
okay I I see it's because of your
empathy re Revelation yes Revelation try
reation she's level 10 your ration I
can't really tell what your Revelation
is uh
Tam yeah I'm going
[Music]
Revelation wow Revelation that
Revelation is
cool oh I'm sorry I'm sorry but we are
in a party empathy
kind of violent for I keep getting
scared
when yeah it's for the kingdom you know
I just realized your kingdom for the
kingdom I just realized I wasn't in the
voice
call isn't in the voice chat either yeah
Tam is too slow oh now I'm in okay it
does sound like you need to join a
dangerous dangerous monster from another
life monster from another we going
Adventure wow the water is so beautiful
it is a swim take a
swim how do you
get we got it we got it this is just a
little it's a it's it's just a little
splash splash in the
water hello we are dipping we are
dipping the water's cool I feel like I
remember your horse's name but it slips
my mind oh do you maybe from another
your horse another time what letter does
it start with an a uh yeah I think so I
think I feel like there was a strong
connection between you and the horse sad
yeah I just can't remember the name Adam
oh sad get away from the queen all the
stains she's remembering she is
remembering
she did see her memories
yeah I should get more RAM all right are
you guys ready to go to the coast this
is I'm ready to go to the coast the
coast yes yes we do I think so yeah hold
on how do I remove
someone I'm going to my page mag
four I would like to get rid of I cannot
get rid of our offline our I mean our
disconnected um I mean our sleeping
[Music]
member our sleeping member you mean our
our banished member right yes our
banished member she seems to have
disappeared I know not
where let me reform our party it is odd
yes we must reform I must
reform
okay sounds good take shape to a new
form
yes I will accept with curiosity you're
quite certain something I hear mumbling
I'm just
reading you got to open your mouth when
you speak crony what are you reading
sorry sorry okay no need for thex spicy
no it's okay I get spicy when I make
friends oh okay spicy spicy yeah the
must flow yeah oh I left all my
stuff in a different Barrel well maybe
I'll put it in this Corner Barrel
too
water yeah I always take breath under
water breathe underwater we believe this
is no M rumor as the Guild Master was
able to findex under water what does it
mean we're going to be able to breathe
under water it just came into my mind
yeah I think we're going to be able to
breathe under water I think oh next is
Atlantis what how do you what Atlantis I
not say that what
tantis T tantis tantis does have
something to do with it starts with
tantis
true from Tam oh were you originally
from were you originally a mermaid
Tam maybe that's that's why she's
marrying the king it's like a marriage
of different
countries different species you
mean
species different species and countries
lestans and mermaids they are joining
together she's a mermaid can they
reproduce I'm sure they can all right
let's go back to town guys if think
about that if you talk to the uh the
thing we got to go back to town okay
Coral shards huh is what we need where
do we get the coral shards corals it
says to gather them and then speak to
the Guild Master do you think that where
we yeah we need 10 yeah where do we get
the perhaps there there are some Corals
in the water nearby I don't know should
we go look wait why why' we try to go
are you leading us to them are you
mayhaps leading us to the
coral that you
flying okay okay I was just thinking
that you guys didn't see where it was I
will I see Coral see I see Coral rainbow
you see Coral are we collecting it uh oh
yeah I got four wait oh yeah I'm
returning I'm returning
[Music]
y I can't tell if I have how many I
have I need I did it Coral in the
water yes so
delicious uh-oh
yikes at least it's not dead coral it's
not like the coral is still alive and
fresh which means that the sea is very
clean and healthy we got to go back to
Ruby say no to
pollution not us where there's no more
Coral I need more
too so you can always go back oh speak
to the Scarlet Guild
[Music]
Master I make haste back towards the
kingdom me too let's go let us ride
together we ride I don't know if it's
just me but Ruby is remind me of
[Music]
another thank you ter is in another
world what's her name Pink
huh hot pink hot pink what's your name
though you could call me hot is it
you're not
[Laughter]
hot down the way because you will need
to kill 10 of these for the next part of
your quest I will I will only
Ru all right speak to the Scarlet one is
he not the Scarlet one he is a Scarlet
one we have to go see Ru and he's in the
village Iris will way okay okay let's go
guide my way
Ruby way yeah she'll guide my way
huh she
has and she is not I'm not alone yeah
literally okay you guys know so many
similar song please let me go back oh
please please let me go
back yo you guys follow you guys
following I I'm going I'm going to it in
a minute oh I see it it's right over
there I see
it um y it's a path right there's a path
need me to lead where are you no no no
there's no you go right ahead it's a
Sandy path right okay let's see and then
R is right over there moment there's
rubius yeah yeah yeah got it don't worry
about
it you guys don't have to worry about me
I'll find way you a
you
guys in a
tunnel they're digging a
grave could be I think they're digging a
grave heck yeah yeah I think wa grave
diggers it seems our next task would be
to explore but I think our path is
blocked you digging me yeah it feels
like maybe I don't know I am I am Hing
if we give enough time the path will
open on its own path will open on its
own eventually but today we have done
pink yes
what fairly well fairly well goodbye
goodbye goodbye lovely lovely gorgeous
ladies oh I guess this means I will do a
magic trick and disappear oh disappear
oh I didn't disappear right away oh
shoot I was I was planning on
disappearing okay excelsia is really
exelor
exelor okay where's
the there we go all right where where's
I shall do something that calls my
name what calls your name calls to me it
calls to me a small blue
box a small blue box small blue box blue
box what's the we're not talking about
the manga right oh wait no no what's a
manga what
is what is a
manga is that how you pronounce it I
don't think that's true I know I've
never seen one before how right know how
to pronounce this small blue I have no
room I guess I I can get finish oh what
did he
do rainbow Coral cluster an object only
red how do I use this waste bin oh oh I
know we become
mermaids just like
Tam just
like just like Tam investigate the temp
she didn't need this item to begin with
wait can we
farm
farm we can Farm yeah I think that's
what the shovel is for right like
growing things yeah where will we can
build at our Guild base oh yeah we
should build a small Guild House
yeah some some do some farming some
wheat so we can not have to pay gold to
make bread right can we can we make we
should do that yeah we should make our
own
G it's g g we can have like a someone is
calling me Gigi I am Jonathan
G but you were good game what is good
game one second I must drop the
telepathic call
it's going to drop it someone else
hosted
hello
hello what is your
name my name
is yes one second I forgot my name oh
you don't know your name no I mean you
know uh the Amnesia that happened to
everyone it's kind of like uh my name is
um what has everyone been calling you
Mario it's Mario everyone's been calling
you
Mario yeah oh hello Mario I am Jonathan
G spelled with a G I'm going to be J G
the name my name in your head okay so
you know how to spell it I
forgot that's how you spell it you see
it goon no it's Jonathan it's spelled
with a G Jonathan G can you come with me
because I have to do something come here
okay I've never met you before but I
will I will come with you no one's
pronounced
Jonathan I like I think gathan is better
no no it's Jonathan Jonathan G but I'm
not a big fan of go Jonathan that's my
name I don't know I don't like it person
I personally don't like it what are you
doing here are you
building no I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm trying
to farm my materials to build stuff
later
oh
yeah I I I promise to myself I'll become
the queen of this place so I need a
costume you're going to be the queen
ooh I don't know if I can associate with
you I
I I I know the person the king is
engaged
to
who your name's
tamam cam tamam t a m
Tam oh are you talking about the fake
queen the fake
queen yeah she said that they're getting
married and they're
engaged she is fake how is she fake I
know she is how do you know I've been
traveling with her she's been very
trustworthy and she has stood up for me
she is trying to steal my
spot how do I know that you're the real
queen look at me am I gorgeous you are
gorgeous yeah you're are quite
gorgeous what are you doing stop I've
never had a woman's touch before not
like that stop Yes woman do not do not
sit on my I I I I can offer you a very
nice position if you help me doing this
okay
what I not tell you later when I become
a queen what how I will not stand for
this as a member of the ceran team
listen listen we killed the king kill
the
king yeah we kill the K King he going to
kill the
[Music]
again she wants to kill the
king she mean it
do you mean
it you're going to kill the
king
[Music]
no are you working
with who are you working
with I'm working with um I I cannot tell
you it's secret what do they look like
what's your name n what's an NDA you
know what an NDA who are you working
with I can tell you if you tell me maybe
I will converse with you
okay I'm
working
with
someone who is on the top of
everything what
yeah what is your hair color what's your
hair
color it's
rainbow it's like it changed every day
your life liar you're a liar I'm telling
everyone she's not on she's not
on John John John Watson's John Watson's
side I don't know if I can trust
her I don't know I'm getting too many
sides of people who are killing
who who do I trust no we trust Jonna
Watson no we have to learn of her plans
yes we will learn of her plans and we
will relate them to Jonah Watson that is
the good thing to
do I've thought about it what is what is
your how are you planning on killing the
King okay I I'll be honest with you
okay I just have no
friends oh so you don't plan on killing
the King and I want to and because of
that I want to kill everyone I don't
care I'm leaving never
mind never mind let me let me call
the got to get out of
there hello Fair Maiden oh hello hello
Maiden it is so good to see you a dog
yes I've seen two dogs okay can you can
you lead me to the dog yes yes follow
dogs I found them
ah they're ready to go and fight they're
ready to go and fight the stains beu
could you lead the way for us to the
outside are we ready to go to the
outside world fair maidens yes Fair
Maiden okay onward farewell Good Luck
Good
Luck the they the rudius gives you one
yeah but put hand my inventory was full
oh no rainbow Coral Shard which was used
to make the thing hello Cerulean members
what is
happening uh's a coral rainbow Coral uh
cluster is missing oh check my check my
magical
book ah there it is where where was it
in your was it in a it was in the
magical tomb of greatness oh okay thank
God for that thank God thank you oh I
can breathe underwater now y Under the
Sea Under the Sea
Under the Sea Under the Sea Under the
Sea Under the Sea Under the Sea Under
the
Sea I have to watch out for something
called a dmca what is that I don't know
but it tells me careful that sounds
scary DC sounds absolutely scary I think
I'm going the wrong way oh is this it I
don't know this looks suspicious where
are you guys where have you wandered off
to I'm trying to oh I'm wanding I'm
trying to wander off to
the to the to the thing on the map
what's that that looks like numbers
which thing on the
map like there's a thing on the map that
we're aiming for it's the dungeon I
think the Red Dot on the map rub look
like dice no not rubius not rubius um
it's like on the right side I think
ocean temp yeah left side left side left
side inside the ocean I'm on my way hey
yeah I think we're all kind of split so
no
worries don't tell me I can't get these
no I can't yeah look so beautiful wow so
deep can I dig can I dig let's try
dig
wow wow oh she's finally joined I will
find this what do you mean finally
joined welcome back to
cam Pam doesn't want to join the calls
I've spoken with someone named
Mario Jonathan keeps droing the call I
had I had to speak with Mario Mario said
that she's the queen and that you're a
liar who's Mario um she is pink and she
looks like a
cat okay okay no wonder okay I get it
why she's called Mario okay okay that is
what she called herself not Luigi but
Mario okay yeah she said her name is
Mario
she was the one making fun of my name
she made fun of your name she was
calling may not be able to get into the
mysterious place she kept calling me Tam
tenders for no reason tenders that's not
your name tend tenders tenders T tenders
why would
she what an evil she said that she
wanted to kill everyone so oh wow that
is evil yeah that is pretty evil I bet
she's part of Amber coin yeah stupid
Amber coin Amber coin I bet she's part
of Amber coin are you guys very under
water we can't get to the dungeon
there's an invisible wall oh I see okay
I feel like time will solve the problem
wao look there's something called time
this is
Diamond I do have a pickaxe for
this I'm going to be
oh no I'm at the edge of the
map could whoopsies hi sorry I'm
here oh I knew you were going to say
that dungeon is still
dormant oh is that what it says when you
try to enter yes it is
dant seems that for now just
yet Perhaps tomorrow maybe we need some
sleep yeah maybe yeah I think it's about
time I need to I need to to get some
sleep yeah I need my get some Shi let's
meet again let us meet again R Vu when
time opens up a new gate towards the
next when the gate opens let us meet
again I will be waiting the ceran The
ceran Guild Masters will make us
assemble right the Cerulean assemble
right I will send a carrier pigeon and
letting you guys know with my pigeon
you're a love you you have a lovely
carrier pigeon by the way thank you
that's really cool yes I will send a
pigeon to your inboxes and they will
leave a note to you letting you know
that we have in boxes you mean you mean
our mailboxes right yes your your
mailboxes I will I will carrier pigeons
yes yes mhm I will send
note do not be FR you Stone thank you
well have a great one everyone take care
take care everyone
farewell meet again
tomorrow
tomorrow I love you
tomorrow tomorrow how do we all know
this song back very weird do we come
from the same world that's
crazy May oh you why
not why do you help
not I don't I don't
has her problems Tam has her
problems
I yes her name is Tam I named her you
say he don't put it like
thatw I don't like I don't like the
sound I she allowed me to a suggestion
farewell farewell
beautiful I am ending the
call what
oh
[Music]
awesome I'm
scared
wait oh no something is happening to my
connection to the
world I wonder what is happening ah
[Music]
what happened what just I just feel like
I woke up
from like a weird dream a strange dream
[Music]
thank you everyone for joining today I
don't know what just happened but my
mind is all
hazy very very hazy very strange thank
you for the gift thank you for the Su
thank you tager for do sh but he was
absolutely amazing throughout I don't
remember what happened but I hope that
whatever happened you guys had fun I I
would say that if I could remember what
happened that I had lots of
fun I'm glad that I got to chat with the
people in my dreams very very much thank
you for the gift it don't know what
happened but seems like we will meet
again we will meet again perhaps
tomorrow oh but tomorrow we also have a
Teen Wolf watchalong members members
Teen Wolf watch along we're going to be
watching episodes 5 to 8 and that will
be before we go
into our our thing so wor we not I will
be back okay take care good night
everyone
farewell
o revelation
[Music]