[Music]
Why
YouTube
[Music]
why
yeah
[Music]
back back all
right back straight back all right Ki
back all
[Music]
right
is your stream laggy or
not yes
no K
kitty
[Music]
kitty Hello I didn't even uh uh turn off
the PlayStation properly
but this time it didn't tell me that you
know it was unhappy about that it didn't
even tell me let's see 80% for no okay
okay okay but 20% for yes is also at the
same time kind of a
lot looks like it's fixed now man I was
a lot of lag at the ID collapse stream
too which is really unfortunate I wonder
if the vaud at
least like had everything thing smoothly
I wonder it's really unfortunate for
like really important streams like
that you don't want that to happen for
important streams like
that YouTube yeah YouTube probably I
think I know I know what their problem
is I know what it
is oh you want me to tell you oh oh oh
okay yeah there's a a lots of mice and
rats nagging at their cables I saw it
personally I saw
it I know I I thought you guys knew
too that's it's cuz they they don't you
know okay let's
[Music]
stop I prepare
tea cold brew
tea cold
brew from mui the lag is back tell it to
go
away
cold okay good for you you're such a
little [\h__\h] oneu it's unbelievable like
imagine if only you could speak Japanese
I want wonder if you would talk like
this to your beloved TOA Senpai as well
or you can't be [\h__\h] to her because you
don't speak the language but would you
would you be like this to her if you
could speak the language if yes then I
actually I'll be
insulted of course not oh my God what
did I ever do to you no what did I ever
do to you what did I do I yeah next time
I meet to Senai I will tell her that
your other oi me that you don't treat
her very well yeah I'll tell
her yeah you're a menace oh no yeah you
don't want your reputation to be [\h__\h]
right with toas and that's the one thing
you don't
want I'll make it happen I'll tell on
you to
her or is it because you just love me
more than her that's why you got to be
like this to
[Music]
me that would make you meet TOA again so
it's still win yeah but it will it will
decrease her good impression of you to
her
strongly you said such a little
[\h__\h]
like some things that you like that you
tease me with let's say
teasing cuz that's still
nice some things I'm I'm like H funny
yeah
self-deprecation so kind of true but
then other times it's like why why why
why why why there's nothing wrong with
what I
did I'm just trying to do my
best who to after hearing it that that
what what you how would you feel then
huh
who I remember you I remember you
strongly to maybe
doesn't I wouldn't care okay
whatever
um we are in the
game and we're right where we left off
where I didn't want to leave off I
didn't want to leave off but I had to
and now and now girl just wanted to yeah
I wanted to talk about my
drink but you don't care now um whatever
I don't care about you either so um
we're going to go probably to Titan I
guess uh but h no audio to to here there
there is the
audio
um 144 P
really I did increase a bit rate though
cuz people keep kept on saying that
Final Fantasy
especially very low bit r i only
increase it a little bit though like
from 75 still it's not muted it's not
muted now looks way better really I only
went from 7,000 to 7,000
500 originally I wanted to do 8,000 but
then I thought I don't know what's too
much what's too little it looks better
really really let's
go let's [\h__\h]
go do be
running this place is cool if I wanted
to find a place like this in reality
where would I go in the real
[Music]
world Nevada Morocco oh I've been there
didn't really look like this but maybe I
went to the wrong
place Utah Arizona you guys are giving
me American examples no I guess America
does that what is this place
everything this is the spring which
provides the water for the delam Inn's
famous healing BS I wouldn't mind having
a dip
myself if we didn't have more pressing
matters to attend to of course this is
the one thing that bothers
me like the water looks
great but when I walk in it it doesn't
really react to me there's like a few
splashes but like it doesn't move you
know what I mean
I I I'm very strict about these things
but I don't understand cuz like in
general it looks so
good they just didn't add the like
physics
really dead water and a little bit of
wobble would have been nice A little bit
of
wobble not super
wobbly so do do you in in Nevada Utah or
Arizona do you also have hot spr Rings
like this I doubt
it w connected to this little lake or
whatever it is River
Lake damn that's so cool that's so
cool where's this coming from though I
don't see any holes in the ground
where's the water coming
from cuz like it's not like going down
like a waterfall did someone manually
add it
in why am I asking so many questions
about this thing
why is this so so so strong in my
mind none of it makes sense none of it
makes sense there's no place like this
in real
life
anyway now get down get
down W okay
chill oh it's freaking loud
now hey over here oh [\h__\h]
wrong
hey I'm never happy with the
audio you know why I was like right
before the stream in the pre
chat you know how I was talking
yesterday
about
uh you know having troubles finding
people to be in my
3D uh stream
upcoming I I think I finally secured
someone I mean I already had some other
people secured but the like the missing
puzzle
pieces finally secured someone but
everybody's like oh busy
so might have to be a
relatively simple dance
well I don't mind either cuz I'm busy
too I can't learn too many difficult
dances cuz my own my the dances to my
original songs they're already like so
difficult I'm learning sleep talking
right
now and I got the chorus down I got the
first verse
down the bridge pretty much now the
second the second verse already looks
much more
difficult but then the is like three
times and it's always the same so that
covers already a big part of the my
choreographer K she wanted to do
different course at the end I said no
please keep the same cuz I don't have
much time to
learn so three times the same thing but
I think it's good CU then you can like
engrave it your brain Drake's Fang end
of
tangent for now why is it called fang
and like it's like weird shape it
doesn't even look like something will be
hiding inside special
this looks like another crater along
with goodness knows how many guards all
on highest alert you'll need to keep
your wits about you if you're to reach
him so
be I will Uncle I
guess Uncle daddy did you see the title
of my stream Clive allow me to apologize
oh it's too late to apologize
after what befell at Phoenix gate and
the crisis that followed in its wake I
fled I retreated to my Counting house
and danced attendance upon the vice rine
in the hope it would bring me
favor I betrayed my nation to save my
skin like the coward I
am wait Vice is the
mommy
Uncle
please it's not too late Clive Rosaria
is yours by right and there are those
that would help you to take it
back had I the courage of my brother I
might already have done so but that ship
has sailed you however no chuny wonky
forgive me but I
cannot I fight to build a new world
now yes a better
world where men can live and die on
their own terms he's teasing Final
Fantasy is
17 I was raised in a nation that strove
to improve the plight of
bearers toal was
smiling only later did I real
realize that spark of Freedom did not
arise by chance but was kindled by my
father you would see me follow in his
footsteps and that is exactly what I
mean to
do not by ruling
roseria but by extending his ideals to
the whole of the
twins every soul in the realm May judge
my actions heresy see I've never seen
them label their I am certain my cause
is just sequels like that they did that
you really are just like him you
know keep it to kfb will make it
work thank you Clive for coming back to
me I I am proud to call you
nephew a
TT well then this is where we must must
part ways why wish me luck in convincing
my Canarian friend to share his
considerable
talents well where's he going I mean to
plunder his coffers and prove myself
worthy of a place in your Merry
band till then damn my boy I thought we
would see a bit more of him till then
today go safely Uncle
daddy and you nephew son we have much to
catch up on you and I I shall expect you
to regail me with the tales of all your
adventures when next we meet going to
hang out with
gav man all the unused characters are
being thrown to the
side no I'm so sad so many people are
leaving I'm coming for you [\h__\h] lag
man
oh I have free DMs I have to check all
my DMs today ah thank God there
is oh my
god did you just have one
ready for situations like this
[\h__\h] there is she's like answering me
good morning I can help you and then the
code like she she she has one ready what
the hell okay sorry guys I have to do
this right now cuz I need to make sure
that it works otherwise I have to think
of something
else oh over Amazon o you are the best I
love you okay let's see if I can
purchase Family Feud now because I was I
changed my account to be American so
that worked but uh payment still has to
be like American even even prepaid card
has to be americ American so basically
same as the sua game
[Music]
so
uh why is cod so long
okay
think it's
working I added to my account oh
purchas marry
me it worked I love you it worked it
worked nice you got the I'm glad I love
Lissa thank God and today it was
actually Family Feud is like 75 5% off
right now it's like from 30 bucks it
went down to 7 something so that's
crazy first timing only until like 2
Days Later apparently not that I'm
sponsored and trying to advertise this
but I'm always happy when I can save
some
money it's a steal all right then I can
tell
JMA never mind problem
resolved he
best
wife and the out of
ubis
resolved okay uh yeah let's go into
Drake's mouth I guess cuz if those are
the Fangs then that's that's the froat
I'm going to dr's froat like a little
camera infiltrating
you going to take a picture
I mean yeah didn't lag for you well
thank god it's up to 33% laggy people
that's so sad
whoa he's got fingernails even on his
hands his new hands dude it won't work
you can't move it just put a [\h__\h]
hammer and an axe on it [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] what do they do Hur they hurt too
okay I feel bad what is that cutter rat
done to me he cut off your hands
obviously it's going to
hurt okay I feel bad and funny at the
same
time oh
damn out of my sight
w Wait I'll kill you
Ros all about your
heart I'll tell you li from Li this is
the one peace Hugo the table sh hurt you
any longer okay this is my uh fault this
is the one that was um standing there
yesterday where I was like oh must be
one of the blondies but like whom but I
don't think it's them but it looked kind
of blonde it's not quite blonde but
could be him I think so cuz I also saw
some like a braid I saw a braid at the
back of uh his head so it must be him uh
cuz he's new and still mysterious and at
the same time he might just be the one
in the cloak same person because the one
in the cloak like there was no hair in
the front um and all his hair goes to
the back so that's convenient and he's
mysterious so like you know one + 1 is 2
3 + 6 is nine I think so you
know humiliate me me if you hadn't
interfered he would be dead you TR truly
believe you would have triumphed at the
he's obviously a piece of [\h__\h] too right
would have grounded him into dust yeah
makes sense how would he have done that
without his head shut
up you weren't strong enough and you
call yourself a dominant seems like a
control freak you did you mock me
harbard
harbard fake Harvard
student I got a real one do you see
Hugo you are
weak
damn abusive relationship
much but so long as that fire burns
within you there is still
hope May yet be a way for you to take
your interesting choice of voice
actor tell me it's not UNF what must I
do oh dear please I'll do anything
just tell
me the
heart what of it he's so submissive now
a mother Crystal's heart is the most
concentrated source of ether in all
creation thanks Alo perhaps you could
take advantage of that of course the
crystal would not yield her blessing to
any ordinary
man but then you are no ordinary
man
Hugo no head pads please Clive rossfield
stole your power but others have
suffered a similar fate you still have a
d and still manag to find the strength
to conjure their
icon
[Music]
mhm just got to believe like benedicta
harm don't say her name
don't she too drank of The Ether and
gained a power beyond human
understanding oh she did it probably was
him she did controlling that
too
benedicto ptic such a pope
[Music]
name such a pope name
I'll do it my
love I'll avenge you he's
insane oh egg Benedict ah okay it's an
egg name
too run along now
Hugo you need only follow the
light
ah he's a zombie
now he lost his identity muos is
here Aus is what they called it shall be
so
Clive you may leave everything to me
Your Majesty oh three of
them
freaky
freaky yeah pretty sure that's like the
cloaked guy he seems to be the one
trying to control the strings oh I have
five DMS what's going
on
oh
what the
[\h__\h]
what on
Orcs
ORS let's
go who invented Orcs did the royalist
bring them from Ash was it Lord of the
Rings like uh the
world was it really
talken let's [\h__\h]
go that's that's crazy that like like a
a a creature that someone invented for
their
books has become such a common
term that ever since other gamesy and
stories use it too how the hell did that
happened maybe what else did he create
maybe that has been used elsewhere I
mean Hobbits are probably really just
used in anything that's L of rings
related
but yeah elves and trolls most likely
were a thing
before he invented
Rings modern elves are his
creation
really damn that's
crazy okay who created vampires that's
also interesting
who created
vampires who followed that first they
spotted us with me
tole oh first fight
today over
here no I want
to difficult to change the
target
k
I fkl yeah but then still maybe someone
uh I guess in medieval times that was
already invented more or
less seems like something they could
have already thought of back
then that's so long ago that there might
not be a record of
it've taken over the entire
place
yeah
yeah oh well Phoenix is
Phoenix yeah but it really shows how
influential tolken was that's really
cool or his
father going to take it for
[Music]
ride awaken
winds awaken wind
this one could it be that is so [\h__\h]
loud
[Music]
generally so I never get it right I
never get it right let's lower
this the balance like cuz I want the
voices to be loud but everything else
quiet
okay over
here
ow excuse me
right and how I walk purposefully behind
them to make sure so much for the men of
the rock I get both of them Delia's
finest
Dracula wased to take supposed to take
place in Austria Dracula what like is
there a
movie I don't even know I don't know
what are you talking
about on
YouTube my favorite flam of
vtu was a book first and then what why
was it supposed to take place in
Austria I guess I've heard of it being a
book and whatever but don't
really don't really care about that I
don't really care about like vampire
stories much and Dracula I
guess my kind of stuff is still more
like with
medieval fantasy okay I guess that could
be medieval too but I
mean well you know what I mean there
isn't
shs you know what I mean right I'm like
Lord of the Rings kind of stuff yeah
that's that's more what I like so dark
hello is this even the path see a door
to girl help me okay this was just
decoration it's do yeah to and high
fantasy yes yes oh underneath
it is this
a toy wony what would I do about
you what is this whole section
then
oh that was a big dead
end first no but I have like a friend
who's like insanely into it
yeah
stay
down attack I like his aggressive voice
acting pretty
dope you
lose get
him it's over
cam why am I not
like
okay
[Music]
um items items items
nope aggressively British angry clab is
better than normal CL yeah normal clab
is always like always like uh dark like
a low and Rusty husky voice sounding
very mysterious like
this but even when he screams he kind of
kind of keeps it up kind
of he had to go through a lot for this
role I was thinking to myself
yesterday that the way he
talks animals in a way it's just like
quiet
[Music]
sco making your voice like that it's
like gives me
meing all yours
tolea
die
hey
go get
him
this
one
attack well yeah he definitely did a
good job but sometimes I feel
[Music]
like a little bit less whispery would
would have been fine too oh wait there's
so
many wait I want to use come on give me
the skill give me give me there's so
many here there's so many here come on
come
on thank you thank you thank
you hey you little [\h__\h] I want to get up
there I want to focus on
them
go it's so
well okay you pissed me off right now
all yours
tole too slow
waa
wa wa hey this actually also makes me
faster not only stronger I
think
now
SI
get live streams into PowerPoint
presentation so true I can't get up to
him here I'll just shoot him to death
they have really really low
HP
surprisingly oh could have have grabbed
him maybe oh well um this way I
guess looks like Titan
domain maybe Titan's power isn't much
better for me than the Thunder one
because I don't really block much
yeah ooh but at the same
time that Thunder Crystal thing just ah
triggers me so hard when I accidentally
hit that instead of something uh the
actual Target so won't be going any
further this way
great so I'd rather not use
it hi block is whatever good no yeah
stairs maybe it's okay not to use it
the Titan
block is it acceptable help me
boy to
kill to
kill speaking of violent
animals I
recently found out something new about
my I had about chunky wonky in
particular this one even though I have
them for 5 years
now you know um smovie really likes
to um
need you know um but it's really only
like certain
blankets uh but I know how to get her to
need like I know where to rub her belly
and how to place the blanket so that she
will need it yeah but chuny wonky is
like she always Pur she's always happy
but she never needs right I've seen her
in the past like maybe once and that was
like only for a moment like if you pay
too much attention to her she will stop
and it's it's not common for her to
need oh okay hi who are you mid
boss nice I won't be sneaking past this
one
how did they get in
here sneaky sneaky sneaky
sneaky
go oh it feels good to dodge with that
it just ah [\h__\h] too late I didn't notice
it was time already
yeah wa I need
to rub my
nose sneaky at a
slowmo game brings out something in me
violence
oopsie let
try oh when I do that it even
oh it even gets him to um scoot closer
even if the enemy is pretty far
away oh [\h__\h] I canceled
it it's okay
okay all yours to
nice big damage but still cat
here
so I was I was
saying oh
[\h__\h] ow ow ow hey hey I'm hurt too I'm
hurt
too hey hey hey hey hey okay okay okay
okay okay
okay hey my my my my my Dodge is not
reacting
anymore that was
close oh that's not very cinematic
interesting wait I'll tell you about
chunky Wy in a moment let try oh hey I
dodged but it was like an
aftermath he keeps on kiding me
now
okay now
too all yours too
now to staggered while I'm in the prime
mode that is
awesome definitely
doing too slow big damage nice double I
got a double this time during the
Stagger situation now to oh oh okay okay
go okay
wow
all yours
tole there we go nice okay I definitely
missed a lot of the moves but U great
good big damage we we are happy we're
happy these
days with our damage output finally
[Music]
finally now for
junkers so yeah so her um kneading is
really rare but that doesn't mean she's
not happy or something like she
definitely is a happy cat right
um but I've I've noticed when I um when
she's like laying
sideways uh probably also only in
certain spots like she won't do it
everywhere but when she's lying sideways
and happy and I put my arm in a certain
position so that my elbow is closer to
her face and my uh hand is like closer
to her
belly then she will like knead my arm
she wants to knead my arm and I've let
her do it and it hurts but I I I'm just
so happy to see her kneading and
kneading me
directly even though there's nothing to
need I have marks of it like actual like
red
marks yeah oh beautiful looks like
corals the Flames worth it so worth it
so cute come on
tole your cat does that too you have
scars a g
geod inside a geode there's not this
this kind of never did do things by hes
big geod if taking the mother Crystal
for his own wasn't enough in reality is
it yet to build this Castle in
it I'm I'm I won't have enough potions I
think if this is all I'm getting another
small one probably yeah one like they
refills like usually it's just one
potion or like maybe two small potions
then no High potion or it's like one
high potion one small potion it's really
not
much myato used to do that really it's
so weird like you would think she wants
to need like soft things but there she
goes just in that specific situation she
will need my
arm quick game over to replenish potions
it might be worth it rather than
suffering through a whole thing and then
we can still kind of say oh this was
first try cuz I died
purposefully
this is in concept A geod that's
cool shame you can't put a blanket
over yeah I don't know what it is about
my arms the lower arms did you upgrade I
did upgrade my
pots VOD watches close your eyes for the
next 5 minutes what
why cuz I'm going to
die
fluffy
arms just like they said in the past
roasting me about
my monkey arms let the trial
begin
trial can I want to buy the full version
please I'm already like so deep into it
what the hell you with
me oh yeah yeah yeah I killed kill me
kill me kill me give me my potions I'm
going to I'm going to let him do
it I'm going to lose the trial that's
okay is it too early to die like does it
actually not work when you die too early
no okay could
work
okay with me
too
yeah okay the the Doom is really
nice all yours
to okay I'm so
stupid go
kill
okay oh go yay I got it I got
it to
oh
barely he's got n no HP
lame almost staggered oh [\h__\h] I did try
to dodge but too late I
guess oh
jumpy all yours tole
kill more more more I'm not
[Music]
done got to go got to go got to go
[\h__\h] got to go what is this
oh now tole nice try got him you're a
fine
Hound go
to
oh I needed that I'm hurt
too what was
that what was that
oh
oh a [\h__\h]
help
go okay starting with go this
time over here the
Undertaker I like the
name
kill now
to
did I do that yes I did
now oh oh [\h__\h] I'm on the roll baby I'm
on the
roll okay okay it's fine it's
fine
get
him TI I know I ended the roll at some
point you have to stop rolling it
seems all right oh nice s nice that was
nice quite quite the weak
Undertaker would have expected
more that was great H elen ring back
seaters finally
won that wasn't that wasn't about Ellen
ring no
[Music]
no two different
things
stretch they're too weak for me I've
Gotten Good like there's a good flow now
with indeed with all the the different
attacks it's a bit annoying of course
that you have to like switch between
them
but it's so it's it's fine with only
free I guess it's
okay yeah it's first try the death was
tactical
mhm for real though for
real if this an AE you are Ed in your
gamer
Arc whoa whoa hi so this is the power of
muthos you like it it's power of the W
myth I am from myth it's not Mythos it's
Mythos it's my it's not myos it's myos
it's
myth
crunchy
oh
oh did the ORS do this too we're
inside the
castle these dead people are originally
the guards
no
damn the power of
myth
the Orcs did oh high potion nice
oh oh WS weren they kind of
easy all yours
tole got to catch them all got to catch
them
all
go stay
down your F go
to toal kill
enough nice nice nice nice this isn't
Pokemon then you tell me why it feels
like
it is that a chest it's a chest
baby I have a chest
sensor 1,600 kill I got the oh this here
you can actually go up can you fall down
oh
wow most other places in this game that
was not
possible
oh what are you going of throw him down
oh no he stays here
okay over
here
go
to over
here
go lag what the hell is going on are
these things here for me off him no lag
please YouTu be nice to me
please what's
next ooh the throne room room oh bravery
some opponents will use the ability of
Bravery to invigorate nearby allies okay
okay just another buff
[Music]
then a [\h__\h] I canel
it over
here let's do
this a they did not get you get
damn
can you
guys box this
[Laughter]
fast wait wait wait no no ow I want to
kill you oh now you're
here yeah get him
yes go
tole
and if you can't then that's a little
bit of a skill issue got to work on
that too is so
funny get
him hello
Mom Mom oh yeah yeah I guess I hatched
you
oh
here
okay so this Throne Room nothing big
okay first Orcs now these nightmares is
this your doing
Ultima it's not too bad so
far
H
oh oh
what is that Crystal thing up
there Susy no
mistakes woo
woohoo
kill oh [\h__\h] I'm coming
to I wait he was 50% [\h__\h]
wow I needed that too slow too slow you
hear that got to get a bit faster than
that
[\h__\h]
no not good that's ready
get sh stop
it is the bit raid when I'm fighting
actually better today than
usual
so all yours
to still take nightmare oh
man so maybe I got to make it even
higher tech people when you think a good
bit rate is for This
Disaster oh chill out
man kill wow uh this is a long attack
from him a long
chain good
[Music]
okay over here too
slow uh okay oh I got
it
30,000
30,000 m
tole tole kill he's almost
dead
well pretty hard to make a game with so
many visual effect look great especially
with fire like I think you know fire is
a big culprit always isn't
it
oh okay now this way
oh this way there any more chests
here
no yeah rain and
[Music]
fire and dark yeah difficult difficult I
wish I could make it nicer man cuz the
game is so pretty you want to show that
off
obviously oh this room is also so pretty
you've been busy
cuh it's like he just while having lunch
he just in he looks like he maybe just
took a big bite out of the
table but where did you
go oh nice
bed Turn up the bgm I think it's pretty
a good volume or
now always go to the glowy big thing yep
yep
yep where is Jill by the way where did
we leave he's in the
sanctuary I can feel it come on
tole favor of her
upheaval I was about to
ask what do I think where she is
recovering well I hope she'll there
might be like a
moment where I'm like in big trouble and
suddenly she shows up maybe who knows
well it would be kind of difficult to
like catch up with me all the way in the
deep deep
deeper of this
place potion okay you giving me potions
means that's it's com it's coming very
soon
yeah it's very easy to read this
game yeah why is there no word for
deeper just what I
needed now
to get him
oh there a lot of
these
wait I could have gotten more if I
positioned myself a little bit
different Overkill
Overkill oh
Spectre this is the thing that Buffs
right at least it looked like it in the
in the
preview all yours tole can't watch
because of the lag man there's so many
people today who say that that's making
me sad sad
[Applause]
sad unfortunate over
here all yours
tole sick YouTube why you got to
sabotage
me all yours tole that's a lot of
enemies
bam go
to ah you've been you've been sharing in
Discord screen sharing oh you guys love
me so much that's so
cute
need to watch Waba stream at any cost
attack better be the last of
them I would like a few more
potions
5 Seconds every minute man go to kfp
Discord they're streaming it now it
seems
bened am my everything oh
[\h__\h] I I've missed you so much she's not
there
CA
a oh yeah it must be like Ultima
changing their form or something like
that I swear to you my
love it's fake you will never be parted
again it's fake what's wrong with
him today I have healthy
snack
cucumbers
you get away from her
why are you showing him Che
out I'll kill
[Music]
you he's so easily manipulated
damn oh [\h__\h] he's
priming
[Music]
ow no not
now oh
oh oh we haven't had this in a while I
think oh I don't like the
sound
come
on find
him you've done this before you can do
it again we're 50% into the game and he
still has issues with
this Let Them Burn
without come to me if
free
oh he's
watching oh
Joshy
fire wait that's not Joshy though he
would show they would show me that it's
just oh yeah the other dude also uses
fire what the
[\h__\h]
oh yeah cuz we already fought him so
this is like the the the big fight that
we still were missing
okay I actually I think I like like it
that
way
whoa D he still got no hats even in this
form
what was I
saying I'm tiny cuz he's a
[Music]
Titan Attack on
Titan ha ha
ha
Yoo
wo no
okay okay he's slow he's big but he's
slow voice of the land what do that
do okay I've not taken damage so far so
that's
good wait when he's 50% what am I even
supposed to do when I can't go for my
wind
lady he's so easy to
dodge what the
hell what why is it so easy to
on hit him
harder he's got cool moves though but
they're they're kind of
lame how do you not Dodge literally
everything with this
a it's kind of
lame cuz I felt intimidated but
uh wait can I use this this
oh a she just keep on using that
maybe when I'm when he's staggered at
least yeah I thought I thought he would
be crazy strong he was Stronger
when oh [\h__\h]
dodging
game which is also incredibly
easy okay but still it's
easy
oh nice
trick n NY but if you can do
it then so could
I
I've learned
Brimstone
okay was that a
shield BM so low I can't change now
maybe within the next
proper like when I can actually change
the
settings
it's moving so
slow how can I not Dodge this what brim
Zone C has learned to Ability Brimstone
from
Titan uh hold and release are two
and
square longer okay longer to increase
explosion
[Music]
CH okay R2 and square
uh okay so it's going to be like the the
icon attacks the abilities thing is
okay let's give this a
try not bad like this
okay get louder for you guys I think in
my ears it's well balanced but
okay it's barely going up actually un
OBS oh wait it's it's louder outside of
the menu
right oh
[Music]
yeah
part of his moves remind me of I think
it's called
[Music]
Kera that's fighting
dance
oh
wait come to Brazil oh that's from
Brazil oh
oh this
part that gives me a couple
ER oh can I like use Brimstone here to
do something
cool oh
yeah I don't know if it's worth it time
wise you guys tell me if you have
experience with
it it
is
okay what was that what is he do what is
he doing man I feel so bad like you
can't even fight like properly
anymore
weak look at how little damage I've
taken
oh
oh R1 cinematic
evasion
bam
oh
ah square square square square square
square square square
[Music]
square he sees the
light ay
light
upgrade become stronger oh wait eating
that is like like the the in in the um
in tears of the Kingdom the one that
wants to eat all the the glowy things
from the frogs and the
[Music]
caves become crazy
strong what the hell is he done no I
didn't mean to rock
people it's not the gor no
no ooh
man that place could be a great venue
for
concert the shape is like perfect for it
and and not anymore cuz now it broke
down we outside
now
oh whoa whoa okay yeah you Titanic
what what is
that founder help
me it's do or
die com I'm beating uh I'm just running
by automatically I don't even have to do
anything
okay
game
who did he actually say it's Do or Die
something like that is in the
[Music]
lyrics
funny
it's Do or
Die how's the rest of the
[Music]
lyrics uh what w wo W
oh this gives me Sonic Vibes now cuz in
that new Sonic game you had to climb
these huge what the
[\h__\h] what what am I what do I do with
that punch it
what I guess I still keep on
invading that's
try you had to climb these huge huge
Titanic
enemies and you small small and but
you're zooming around
them Punch or shoot oh
okay can I ah
what can I oh
okay but it's too late when I don't get
this
part first time I'm taking damage
properly I don't get it I tried both
dodging
and shooting one time it work what the
[\h__\h] seems like that part is over
already
so all is
well do or
die this is so funny somehow this is so
funny for
me
okay squ
s
what is a damage on
him I've got you now
okay seems like I have not
failed yeah
it so how we doing this now no no no
what
what okay oh what
what okay now I can
attack maybe I can do
this okay that was last
second okay okay
okay he what what what
what I I dodged it right but then he
still kind of went through I'm
confused okay okay dodged it we good we
good oh oh okay it has
a uh
a shock
wave
[\h__\h] can I
jump oh let me get some damage come
on jump
in
wo we still got new moves
and
oh there's like two yellow pieces there
if I stop in there maybe it's like a
rhythm game where it gets extra strong
cuz they were pretty small so it seems
like a challenge to
actually do
that oh no hit the Deep bread oh really
yellow's okay yeah I thought
so should probably hit the Deep
[Music]
Red I got the I got the yellow I got the
yellow
[Music]
yeah you done now Titan
no of course not
[Music]
we going even
higher oh thank God PR
do oh a okay same
thing
nice this music changed a little bit
funky don't we have it ready right now
[Music]
oh
okay a [\h__\h] no he was gone
oh okay damn he still got so much
[Music]
HP
nice I keep on doing the
things 150k now he's down to I would say
half all he's got is tankiness yeah but
it's understandable I mean look at that
b
R1
[Music]
w
I think I got
yellow I think I
did wow
wow w
[Music]
I did it I did
it a [\h__\h] way too early way too early
it's okay it's
okay all right easy easy mini game Dodge
the ball dodge
ball he just wants to
play I Feel for him honestly like don't
you guys feel for him too I feel like
he's he makes you feel bad for him
for sure that was right before the
yellow
probably it's yeah it's tragic like but
he seemed really he must have been
already pretty weak mentally to be like
so easily
manipulated cuz I mean snap out of it
dude come
on that's some intense love I
guess
yeah I mean yeah he did do a lot of sh
stuff
but they so feel for him cuz like I
guess what makes him seem like like
decent is the love he
has and how crazy he goes for the
love the the things he will
do that that makes them
lovable likable
spam spam spam spam
spam the best
part no more tentacle
Titan we definitely loved her more than
she did him
yeah she's very passionate that's for
sure it might be it might be
like the most likable villain of at
least in the
game but also kind of
[Music]
pathetic strong outside soft core
inside only only when it comes to love
though only way it comes to love CU
obviously like not soft when it comes to
War One Last
Time You Must Destroy no mercy what is
[Music]
this where's my ah there it
is there it
[Music]
is only the blue ones only the blue
oh this is the best part you
say it's pretty cool like they still
bring in some variety that's
nice
now we're done now we shoot this thing
it seems yeah can I charge it oh I can
charge shot oh it only took like two
charge
shots
comop Oh wait we're still in it oh oh oh
wait what what am I shooting
now nothing chilling we're hanging on to
dear
life head up
[Music]
here would I have done more damage if I
would have pushed more I
wonder all
right it's over it's over
oh all right guys thanks for watching
Final Fantasy 16 it's over he
says wow was that 2 million or two 100
something
what wait we're still not over what I I
I put my controller away we're cut scene
we're fighting in the air like we just
don't care what I don't know how the
physics are working right now but
somehow it's
working wait let me get closer to him
no why he got full HP again but it's
like normal Titan why would have
what does that hit him
no what is
this can we just go on the normal ground
please oh uh oh [\h__\h] now I'm not ready
for
that yeah okay this this part of the
fight is kind of getting
me it's crazy that's
crazy this is the most
intricate like big boss so
far my
God my hands are getting a little bit
tired of this now like
[Music]
literally
ow this is why Jill couldn't be there
cuz like obviously how are you going to
uh Implement Jill into this fight right
that's why they had to do that
so obvious all right I have a cold now I
have this St bad a little
bit I got the cool sorry tole
too still can fly yeah but it's still
like I don't know it's obviously a one
versus one fight here that we got what's
happening am I waiting for
you come here ow
oh
okay no I was it was I supposed to break
that like that cuz I I exploded it too
early well it didn't hit me
though oh
[\h__\h]
Earth Sher
sh Earth Sher
[Music]
sh
sh twice actually is a heart Shaker not
earth Shaker in
[Music]
reality do I even need to focus on him
just out of like um habit I keep on
pressing L1 but I don't even see me
being focused on him it's just automatic
I
guess just realized when he's away I
should just shoot him like this God damn
it I forgot about it
finally just
uh blacked out there flying in the air
far away from me what can I do besides
shooting at least I realized it before
the fight was over Midway
through that's still early
enough okay see the time
it
yeah
was that again okay
[Music]
okay
Shake hey I you really think I should
hit a red one I try the next one I
thought cuz it's
smaller that I should hit the yellow
one you first trying this yes I am
yellow means I
miss
what what ether from the mother
Crystal you can do it but it did damage
no
[\h__\h] what for real now it's too
late it does damage but not the most hey
and how much damage was I missing out on
Oh wait we're still going we're still
going wow okay this is so
much as over I'm not getting to use it
[Music]
anymore I
lose
no down down down
down
die
Okay C was always in you why can't you
do this kind of stuff
earlier damn son no spoils
hello
what there it is Earth
Fury the epic boss fight it was quite
lengthy how long did this take 30
minutes might not be an
exaggeration
sheesh sheesh
this time we destroy it in our special
form
nice wow that's why you guys didn't want
me to do it yesterday that's
understandable o this scam is it from
Ultimo oh c oh c he used so much ether
he turned into stone and his like broken
spot my
[Music]
God oh my
God here it is maybe they'll reveal him
to us
now
not another fight pleas is that you
Ultima
no what do you want it's dead dude maybe
it is ultim maybe your soul is Tainted
with worthless human will is Ultimo yet
your thirst for power remains
undiminished with every sip you take you
grow in strength and soon you shall
achieve
perfection I don't know what you're
talking about H you will accept as
newos it is
inevitable you were created for this
purpose and you shall serve it
[Music]
never
f it D don't let him in
Joshi
Consciousness we see now human will is
so insubstantial it cannot exist in
isolation you mitigate its weakness by
interweaving it with your
Consciousness we believed we had merely
to purge you of your will to claim our
vessel it appears we first have to sever
every thread of the Consciousness that
supports
it no matter the time to build a new
world is not yet upon us we will
contemplate all
right
Phoenix
Feather thank you Joshua Joy
Wy one can no more command the power of
ether by drowning in its
flood then one can constrain the tides
by standing in the
sea I had thought Hugo wiser than this
but it seems his head was full of rocks
after
all Titan was
strong your majesty M
where who that Mythos is
strong wait have we seen him before
no right for 5 years that man lived only
for
Revenge clinging fast to a fiction even
as it swept him into the
abyss looks like a hot
pirate one cannot change one's nature
through force of will alone only the
almighty can do
[Music]
that
is this the cult of
Ultimo Hugo kopka the man who gave his
life for woman's head Ah that's why he's
familiar he was in bed with benedicta a
fool like all the
rest cult them
all
oh that the death of a mother Crystal
should be so
beautiful it do be
beautiful it do
be oo
some medicine my
Lord I have salves potions anything you
need stop bothering me urchin or you'll
feel the back of my hand the
Lannisters you must consider your health
my
prince if a show of force is needed to
keep the DMX at Bay you may trust in
your
drons I beg you to call on Bahamut only
as a last res are his strength comes at
too great a
cost you know flirty together the Empire
agreed to an Armistice with the Republic
and yet the emperor still plots its ruin
I thought at the moment I saw them
together I thought for now the dmck
suspect nothing he's into and as long as
I can hold their gaze War need not be
inevitable
but more than that Bahamut is the
champion of the Empire when our people
look to the heavens the sight of him
gives them
hope oh
yeah
oh sweet good for
him forgive me Terrence why
would that you were my
master but
alas I will always be your loyal
servant
sweet
cute
it's a bromance should the council's
Brazen maneuvering prompt the Republic
to tear up their own treaty and launch a
new
assault our soldiers would advance to
meet them cutting across the central
aisles but not in time to prevent their
forces from breaching the southern
defenses and storming twins
side and so the capital would become a a
battlefield thousands of Innocents would
die I cannot allow that to
happen there is one small Mercy at least
you will not be forced to De battle with
Titan cuz he's
dead would that I could avoid doing
battle at
all
a a thousand pardons your highness a
thousand
what is it I need a
million
minimum Olivier has been made
Emperor what is the meaning of
this my father's orders what were they
quickly
yes your his Radiance requests that your
highness maintain position here
and yes my
prince manipul must go to the P I'll
ready your
steed
what is it
now Lan that women are
insane Josh for the intrusion your
highness I know
you we stand in the presence of the
Phoenix he
yes you do guys you finally realize it
your fingers
burned I hope I'm not
interrupting not at
all though I
admit I did not expect such a
distinguished guest
H Team Up how many years has it been
since the remembrance
ceremony
20 I thought you long
dead
do I address a
ghost many have told me that I look like
one spooky
season but
no I'm
alive
just prince Dion of the house lass I
have a tale to tell
you
let us hear
it taale of the
Cliffhangers N I was expecting it I was
expecting like a story
cutscene I shall not hear it you shall
not hear
it I see all right back to the
highway
look got a different cut
scene we're
back two years is lurker oh hey
yo yeah just out of the Shadow the game
is telling you better the good news Come
Out of The
Shadow can you imagine holy [\h__\h]
holy I was about to say it the game said
it for me I don't have to say
anything so will this
change your stance on how you support
me do you still count do I still count
as a
lier no I wouldn't say
so
called out immediately summon oh oh more
lurkers hey
lurkers your skin is so white because
you always stay in the
shadows vampire
luras get all little Sun from the
Phoenix lurking irking irking irking
iring irking irking iring looking like
I'm you're back a turd I am I don't know
and with with Glad Tidings for
once Hugo kooper is no more lur
to well I'll
be wait that's a all of our comrades FR
back at Sid's place be smiling down at
you R now we had a stall us from Lor
saying Drake's Fang had fallen I expect
that was you're doing as well was it
it's it's a long story one for the
history book
welcome home
Clive it's good to be jly
Willy you look better I feel it why do I
always have you got which means I'm
coming on your next little Adventure I
add you're not leaving me behind again
always another word dream of it toggy Wy
Jilly Willy Joshy wasi chunky wonky
SMY word on the royalist movements since
I've been away I like it should you be
put in your Fe It's My Kind of Love
language
if you really want to know go and have a
word with viven thank you I
[Music]
will wava
lava cie walkie yeah that's my
dog uh-oh it's time for another history
lesson ah the Conquering Hero returns M
and with hardly a scratch on him yeah
yeah did quite well one or
two well the fact that you came straight
to me instead of visiting our resident
physica suggest that you picked up
something more important there's
something about the way she is the scent
of
Wuda very same but whatever plans Koopa
was hatching with the
royalists he took them to his grave she
talks like like this but whatever plans
kupka was hatching with the royalists he
took to to his grave I know it's hard to
hard to recreate but you know what I
mean like the the ups and
downs as did his men slaughtered by the
Orcs who'd taken over the Fang a Nar
yeah theatrical narative I've never seen
such creatures in storm before the W
Ludas must have fed them over from Ash
but why why to rescue CA only to invade
his home the mother Crystal of an Allied
nation and let both fall it's very makes
no sense
do you know the tale of the Blind Men
and the
adamantis one can often be led astray by
focusing too closely on individual
details one must instead see the bigger
picture and what bigger picture is there
my map
no no that's always confusing me not the
map the kingdom of wude claims dominion
over all of Ash it is a nation forged by
the bloody conquest of Barnabas tharm
the dominant of Odin the Canarian war of
independence in
849 the TN Realms in
865 the Battle of bellus tour in
873 wheresoever his armies fought Odin
was found where the fighting was
fiercest mhm but of late the warrior
king appears to have laid his sword to
rest mhm yeah we haven't se battle rages
for control of the crystalline
Dominion yet th sends not a single ship
in support of his dalan allies hey
meanwhile the blight ravages great SES
of ash oh [\h__\h] yet warlike wude shows
not the faintest interest in laying
claim to untouched lands so why go to
the trouble of sending an Army Of Orcs
into the heart of Drake's Fang only to
make no attempt to claim the mother
Crystal for wude yeah why it can hardly
be for lack of men th's armies rival any
in the
twins
no we have not seen the last of the Wuda
standard Odin will ride again it is but
a question of when and on that day who
will be trampled underfoot
I think
she really likes in summary I know not
to attend the royalist Betrayed cka I
know only that it is part of some
broader scheme a scheme tied to the
Ambitions of one man king Barnabas she
loves the sound of there is no need to
wallow in confusion if one is to cure a
sickness one must first identify the
symptoms and your lord Uncle has
volunteered to do just that by keeping
an an eye on the royalists
movements he's really throwing himself
into this indeed he is which means All
That Remains for us to do is await his
reports well not quite all in your case
the people of the Hideway must hear the
news justice has been done mhm Hugo
kopka is dead scream it out loud he left
that night are still raw especially for
those who lived with Sid the
longest tell them that those wounds
might finally begin to heal consider it
the price of today's instruction I've
never known you to be
sentimental what can I say I am only
human and we are all of us sentimental
animals at heart we human I suppose we
are very well I'll go and spread the
word yes sshi
mush let's tell
everybody hey hey Titan's dead did you
here Titan's dead let me tell you and
you and
you I did it C is
down reminds you of
Rea
oh okay maybe no you know she could
remind you a little bit of the day from
Tales of Symphonia cuz of the hairstyle
and haircut and hair
color Black Thorn what is it I'm busy I
wanted to tell you that Hugo CER is
dead he
[Music]
yo I can't tell
you how long I've been waiting to hear
those
words this is it then so get do I get
a
[Music]
please I'll try to live up to the
name cuz you know I did so much for you
oh please what' you
need so would it be no the grind Stone
weapon
wow
oh wait this one's stronger
what is it cuz it's should I make this
one Earth and fury this has the item
from the from from
[Music]
Titan I make this no scratches
right enhancer is better what
yeah
uh okay a new waste cloth should last
you a good while I'll take
it I
guess nothing
here still upgrading a little bit yeah
that should do
you
and the enhancer right this is the thing
we just made
right is it
[Music]
yeah okay shortterm memory my best work
but it'll do anything else
no okay next person I'm telling about
it Hocus and
Sharon wait was wasn't Sharon the lady
who sells
potions that I
just went further
away why is the pole still up I don't
know out of Interest I guess back out of
laziness
really and I'm running away from them
but I'm I'm I'm committed to it now I
can't help it I'm going to the other
dude first I guess I don't
know running in circles in this hide
away as
always oh wait why am I talking to you
sorry do you have a moment Sid no a team
of Curse Breakers has gone missing near
North reach which team she also going to
be super angry when I say no they were
sent to liberate a carriage they were
moov a curse break they should be back I
can't they know the work but what if
I've before they go but
I sorry I understand okay let's hope
they're training okay she's not a [\h__\h]
about it
don't ain't got time for this obviously
like look at the what what kind of fight
I just came
from well someone looks plays with
himself it's true what I'm here in then
yeah nothing escapes you lady Karen it's
true I don't lie is dead this Phoenix
doesn't like to lie no more looking over
our shoulders
then good
start to get a crick in
NE don't let it go to yet though we've
been raided thank
you I'm
[Music]
never ah Clive have you come seeking the
gift of knowledge no
to share mine actually spoiler alert
Hugo CER is dead he's
dead oh my it's a nuts guy yeah really
be
true look he's crying shut up little
rats get out of here he is the big baby
U excuse me you seem sound like a big
baby get out of here these are tears of
joy we must offer up a prayer to your
par that the heavens might weep with us
there shall be no lessons today only
Thanksgiving and merrymaking go put away
your things they again all right
brilliant it wouldn't understand a new
dawn has broken it
do thank you Clyde I cannot wait to
share the good
news
hypocrates
after CA
fell Ultima came to me again I need to
know what he
is have you learned anything
unless no great and not for want of
trying I have scoured nigh every
historical to in our collection and
found nothing not even the sort of
conspicuous absence that might suggest a
concealment of fact so it's is almost
tempted to conclude that such a creature
never existed but I saw him with my own
eyes I don't doubt that you did alas it
seems you are the only one who
has to others he reveals not no we see
only that which he leaves in his wake
Josh was she saw him terrible force of
nature Beyond of mortal man maybe not of
death whether the Ultima you met with
was the being itself or merely another
projection of its power I know not oh
they all saw him until I do my
investigation shall continue thank you
and maybe only dominance here I think a
lot only those who wield the power of an
i anything else for me shall
see the ultimate Ultima
so now we're done with
flexing flexing our newest Endeavors I'm
telling you it's true yeah I heard it oh
now they're all talking about
[Music]
it I heard it from
UT didn't hear it from me but it's
true you barely said Dan since you came
home VI got you running airs or
something yeah just spreading the word
let me rest just write it in the
newspaper and let me rest why am I
running
around so the professor's got a soft
side as she I'd never have
guessed
no she was right though everyone was
glad to hear the news I guess it feels
good to flex but you ain't told everyone
I can think of plenty of friends back at
the old Hiway who'd sleep more
peacefully for knowing
not least of all
Sid you should tell
him you're
right I
should and I will well when you do be
sure to take mid with you she's been
going out at Amor and Tong down at that
Workshop of hers trying to do her Father
prayer ammer I can't remember the last
time she visited the old grave very well
I'll suggest it
man
sad we're going to have a sad
confrontation hak
[Music]
mighty mid where are you oh started ra
books that don't have any pictures
in wait how do I get there again
she's right there
uh
[Music]
entrance here yeah here the other side
and then
around see I'll come up with somewh
soon all right Clive what do you want
she also is lurking in the shadows and I
thought you might like to come with me
sorry I'm too busy for all that right
now got to get this this thermal
displacement stack
sorted
thermal displacement stack here and this
is for a sheep only the fastest finest
ship the world has ever
seen the enterprise
Enterprise me and my dad designed it
together where other vessels rely on the
fickle winds to drive them through the
water our is fitted with Mythril engines
the front is sick and those things have
got more push than a behemoth in a bad
mood and more heat than all the hells
put together which is where the stack
comes in I may have already talked some
tight Li ships into putting the hole
together for me in a little dockyard in
Cana but the Stack's a bit more involved
so I'm building it here thing is it's so
involved that I'm running behind and
it's starting to hold things up over at
the ship so you need something from me
I'll come and see my dad though when I'm
done
whenever that
is is there anything I can do to help
good old Clive our open you'd say that
first things first I need some parts
meing the sack will be made up of three
major components uhhuh there's the plate
in here that channels hot Vapors away
from the
engine the helm over the top that
disperses all that heat into the air air
and the sh in around the sides that
stops the rest of the ship from going up
in Flames
h a full suit of armor then probably
best to take it one piece at a time then
you'll need to start with the plate in
everything else fits onto it how the
[\h__\h] do I do that designs and the list
of materials here show these to Black
Thorn he'll know what to do
what where where do I suddenly have this
skill look you don't need to H
I just fetch it from people
again black of course
yes black form please help me think mid
might need some help why don't they just
communicate directly
[Music]
huh she has a person who was yeah yeah
literally like why can't
she
go to Black for and let me do my
important
things it's okay it's okay but I thought
we were done with fetch quests
man poy walki not hanging out with
anyone maybe people don't want to cuddle
with him anymore now that he looks
Funky
Man feels bad
man black Thor how with it it's forit
this might going then she said
you we don't need to hear this
right well I don't know what the hell
you and I'll need help get gavan in here
will you all right gavardo can I just
yell really
loud oh okay thank God they came on
their
own so mids roped us all in here again
and she
typical still if that's what it takes to
get her to visit sidr and uh what is it
take a look at this it's this plate in
that mean which is now there's a special
kind of sand I'm after that you can only
find out in the Vel Croy St as for the
rest of the staff my usual Supply should
have it in stock well we'll get it done
quicker one of us should probably give
you an handcut in the sand and the other
can go and get the rest from this
supplier right then we go sand we'll
make your minds
me and gav go
sand seems like
it wait
what
no what do I have to tell him where I'm
going you going after the which one of
these two
oh OT could come with me
too maybe I should go with OT cuz I
don't think we've seen much of him in
battle but
G gav
okay gav you're with
me sorry all right then it's fate we're
destined to be where do we find this
Stardust stuff there's a river that runs
through the southern reaches of the
velcro Southern reaches of the
velcro I'll go and Scout welcome see
about hiring us a wagon to bring the
stuff back too re Rew welcome while
you're off welcome back you too eh
please
[Music]
me you just like his
accon no that's not really it but you
know he always wants to join me and help
me do things but then I always leave him
behind at some point feel feels kind of
bad he wants to be part of the
action his hair no I do not like his
hair it looks dumb to have like four
tiny
braids at the back of your
head where is
he wait why is he not with
me looks like I found the
river where's G yeah where is he there
already or
what
fly
Ambrosia I don't really care about that
cuz I don't play uh Final Fantasy 14 I
used to for a while it's been a while
sorry to keep you g you have the same
exact hairsty really dis and I reckon
Round Here is our best bet if we want to
gra have to open the braids and then you
then you don't have it
anymore don't know what black Thorns
planning to do with it though not over
in dal and they seem to think it was
worthless but if Stardust is what black
Thor wants Stardust is what he'll get
there's plenty of the stuff lying about
just begging to be
bagged then let's get ding shall we it's
not four it's free we shall
Ria and lopsided only towards the left
side that's you know interesting
interesting
lizard little small itty bitty
wizard lizard in uu language is Wizard
so are Wizards just uu
lizard I can't collect it when I'm so
[Music]
fast so this is
Stardust it just look like black sand to
me need
[Music]
more you missed the Titan fight it was
very long but first
try maybe the part where I was saying oh
this is too easy maybe it was so easy
because like you it's just a really long
fight
and then you have to balance difficulty
maybe they did it on purpose like
that cuz later there was some some parts
that were a little bit more difficult
for
me but overall like we didn't die I
didn't use all the potions
either
so no problemo where's the last little
bit of
Stardust
uh ah
there
chill okay that should be enough for
now let's see how G's getting
on thank you guys I was
gaming
to what you doing
G you finished finished how much did you
get plenty
enough I
hope I
hope getting losing confidence while
saying
that that
Mighty ah I have fre
dmss
feels like ages since we had the chance
to talk you know man man like it does
doesn't
it back when you first took Sid's name
we were talking all the time working out
what to do in
that there was a lot to work out and
there still
is those shoulders are yours starting to
feel the strain hardly ever see around
the Hideway nowadays always on some some
errand or other they do hurt more than
can't take a day off you know well says
the man who spends most of his time
Behind Enemy Lines only cuz you keep
sending me
there I know I can count on you gav oh
likewise
kiss no okay so you keep sending me
wherever you need to and I'll keep
[Music]
going
safe in the knowledge that I have a home
to come back to this person is still
called Mario's entire
family thank
[Music]
you right that's enough soy shade for
one day we'd better get this lot back to
Blackthorne before he slings his hammer
at someone lad you go on ahead and try
to get some rest once you're there oh I
plan to believe you me after Black Thorn
gets what he needs of course also we
would have had bonding time with Oto
otherwise then I think it was more
fitting to do it with G OT is nice too
but ready to go home boy wasn't even
about fighting huh but still I prefer
the the bond between gav and um
Clive
gav man I love this [\h__\h] water so
much I love it oh wait so we go back
right like I can just
teleport
soon soon males not not so soon first
Japan then
males let's hope this is all black Thor
needs that sounds like a flag that he's
going to ask for
[Music]
more first taxes oh c the [\h__\h] actually
like I'm so nervous cuz at the moment I
don't have enough money to pay next
month's taxes the last 2023 payment I
was like how
calculating starting to panic cuz it's
really important um how much I get at
the end of this month maybe it's I guess
I won't know until the
31st we will see we'll see if I can pay
my taxes if not then I'm [\h__\h] woohoo
let's go I'll figure it out Black Thorn
somewhere or another got everything you
need yeah yeah I do cheers for the
Stardust should be enough to be getting
on
with we should go out on maneuvers
together more often sure you're beats
sneaking around on your Tod all the time
H
yeah I don't mind make a start I'm
putting this firm all plainting together
then it'll take some time mind so if
you've got other things to be getting on
with I could do without you breathing
down my neck thank you thank you black
I'll let mid no constructions underway
okay can I send her SMS text message
Maybe please letting off steam
one thank God I don't have to worry supp
we' better be getting back to work too
tax give us a sh if you need anything I
miss those times too where it just
happened
automatically you can stream in person
right no probably no let's go people Tex
no no no it would be way late anyway cuz
like YouTube takes time
to like process all of this so whatever
you're sing now I'm not getting it at
the end of this month but thank
you thank you you're just making my
taxes more
though mid hasn't been the more I get
the more I
pay man there's no way out of this
except of except just stop earning money
started reading books that don't have
any pictures in I just I just got to
refuse my
salary I'm good I'm going to do this for
free now if I don't call up
soon you'll be pleased to hear that
black Thorns started work on plating
forever excellent one down two to go so
what's next the Helm of course for this
we'll be repurposing Fallen SC scrap
Salvage from the
ruins I thought that material was Orit
impossible to work put the red ah but we
don't have to in three
years just so happens there's one
particular ruin that's broken into
exactly the right shape and size pieces
for what we need oh
really there we give you all
details what's her name what's her name
what's her name
right do we have a name yeah
Helena wow wow wow wow wow oh Sid is
this about the
helm uh yes mid said I should speak with
say yes I'll show you the plans then
here you see the mithil engine in which
mithil is burned to generate heat that
heat is then harness to produce motive
Force yes excess heat is dealt with by
means of the ther displacement stack
which disperses it into the surrounding
oh my God were we to in other words the
react this is where our experiments and
not only that that why if sea or
rainwater you can stop that mid said we
might be able to use parts of a fallen
ruin where would I find it did he did he
actually cut her off like saying you can
stop there understand cuz he really
understands or do you think he really
wanted her to stop cuz he does not
understand ah yes it's in lett's pass
near lost wi the thing is well I
probably should have arranged to have
the pieces we need brought here sooner
you see a said it's no longer a matter
of just walking in and taking them
it's going to be considerably more
dangerous than
that I see I and I suppose I'd better
deal with this unwanted visitor for you
what's happening would that
help oh very much did he bit his tongue
s when speaking team and head there
right away we'll meet you outside the
ruins so
sudden suddenly he
like
snake as as
fear yes think mid might need some help
Tiding but other words he
[Music]
nails
okay so what are we doing oh yeah we're
leaving okay we're traveling
far to Lost
wi to get something that I not quite
aware of but it doesn't matter I'll just
follow the quest
sign good day to you good day to you can
I get any closer than this
no oh no lost wing don't I also get lost
in lost wing yeah that's why it's called
lost wing there is no way that you can
reach the goal just by going straight
towards it you have to
find the way but actually uh oh that's
actually uh might be the correct
way went to the dentist before the
session he might have yeah sounds like
it a [\h__\h] this was a dead
end hi remember this place oh we have to
go up to the second level
no godam you're quite talented with
that you're quite talented with that Rod
of yours
wow you don't even
know you have no idea me
lady okay now now
we're now we're we
[Music]
rolling my
trip oh
man hi good girl girl she's a girl
fer
potion
hey I already had oh all the big all the
small
potions two kill that's
[Music]
nothing so how are you guys doing on
this lovely
day by the way time to
fight I had a good breakfast
again so
that's pretty much all I did before the
stream oopsie you hungry good but
cursing YouTube is it still so bad
money you wiped at 3% on a big bus in
world of rock
[Music]
no very sore from
walking you got eliminated in from
Worlds what what worlds where in this
world the Earth you got eliminated what
why did I not hear about
this why did we get eliminated um thanks
so much for coming the uh ruins are just
over there as is the creature of
course League of
Legends think of
[Music]
Legends
anybody H
creature a this thing again this must be
our
unwanted all
righty get
him get him oh oh yeah this how does
this stuff work
again how oh over here money what is
this again I can't go
on what I was supposed to go out of
that wait
what Auto
safe the pieces we need are in the ruins
just over there
what how low was my HP or is that just
kills
everybody
I didn't expect one shot
either oh my HP was
full go to this one
sick okay I left the
circle
SI nice try
right it's not it's a heavy enemy
supposedly hey you're a fine Hound stop
it
now oh damn
okay he gets me every time he dies get
him these things are so
slow kill
oh take
[Music]
down go go go go go go go go go go go
go a bit more come on yeah that's what I
like
see we're going to do the circle again
after that are
we yeah uh okay okay I left it I left
it
woohoo that is powerful
man nice try oh
[\h__\h]
bastard nice try a double
dodge
go oh thank God I got
[Music]
it and the big stagger
get kill
kill I'm not
[Laughter]
done okay well you took Revenge from
that one
de that was not cool flip the table yeah
this is table flipping
move you shouldn't have any trouble now
indeed did I why did I not see it
before table
flip eye of the warrior oh increases
strength tonic duration no thanks I
wonder if I should keep the necklace
that I have now for until the rest of
the game you guys did say it's the best
one in the
[Music]
game does seem like a
good necklace to have for a long
time you did you just kept
it yeah cuz like the others they're nice
for like certain upgrades for certain
attacks but this just helps in general
so till the final battle
uhuh I see okay for now we're good just
sticking with what we have
[Music]
then a p check who I didn't check for a
while oh thanks for reminding me I have
3,300 oh
okay oh I can upgrade
this increases range and number of hits
number of hits this is I thought it was
just a oh more like of these walls
maybe should we flip it even
harder or the super move super move is
this a super move oh which one's the
super
[Music]
move well
now what else could we
upgrade ignition no not
enough maybe I'll save again
[Music]
but I can upgrade the limit too my
limit what's my limit where's my limit
what do you
mean
oh I never use a stor
pun I could reset
this I never kick off
enemies do I okay it's just 15 points
but half for 15 points maybe I'll
accidentally do it at some
point
break let me
break what
what
[Music]
this oh this one
oh well it takes 6,000 H 6 what am I
saying 1,000 so need a bit more okay
then I'll I'll save for that now
then saving is good we need patience to
save for bigger
[Music]
attacks think mid might need some my
eyes are getting kind of tired right now
it's only been two and a 2 hours and 40
minutes but I feel like cuz these long
ass fights really feel like I stream for
hours yeah I wanted it short today but
not this short so we're going we're
still going going we're still
going
mid excellent and just right right the
shielding how so the plating is enough
to stop the engines going pop but which
is a prison I thought the helmet honey
well if I I know whose counsel I would
seek I'm not listening to I've the
detail can you this it's no story it's
just I need this because blah blah blah
blah blah blah blah
blah
[Music]
you don't you're not mad at me guys
right nobody Minds it right thank
[Music]
you
good
[Music]
fantasy techno Babble
what the worst part of the game I don't
want to hate on Mid but the quests are
mid but it's not her fault like she's a
cute
character her quests to be made yeah
they make me fall
asleep hypocrates do you have a moment
for you Clive always well actually it's
for Mid this time could you take a look
at
this a baffling
diagram enjoy look at
[Music]
this shielding for a mythal
engine she has yeah we already saw this
I
see I wondered if you perhaps what do
you mean consider the lake we have made
our home M its blighted Waters eat away
far more quickly than fresh water or
even Brine and yet we have made a home
here we have but bardolf must varnish
every board twice over to keep it from
rotting and obelis complains that
without a constant supply
of pitch
pitch what I see I he does it again
Gregorian history maybe he do have a spe
Moon you it said to be able to resist
even the most ferocious Flames before
the drons tamed the worms and wyvn of
the realm Nobles would dor their castle
walls with it in order to guard against
dragon fire so if we could recreate it
it might I hear it every material or
other in order to provide even though
there was no s now I hear his everywhere
where it does bel material perhaps
bardol and obelis might be of assistance
Li I shall speak to them and see what
wisdom they might have to offer
you hereo now you be so kind as to
procure the necessary ingredients I
shall a knowledge of yet useful to we of
them thank you
hypocrates you're asking others to help
you perhaps I should
too you hear it now too
so you need a hand do you we
do I'll be heading to market for the
ingredients we need I could do some help
that's some company too now the other
can assist me in researching how best to
prepare the shielding itself these SES
he nailed
always well thank you I am
sure me
too I am sure
sm7
okay oh oh oh I have to choose
again shielding that guards against even
the most ferocious I'm I'm choosing so
Clive who will accompany you obviously
why would I choose tya or
t very
well so
then I have taken the liberty of
preparing a list White Chocobo
X pepo nuts he likes those nuts are you
sure this list is right everything on
here seems very edible or wrong I would
have thought the ingredients would
though these items may seem
mundane they have potent effects that
are rarely exploited effects for which
they were so much so in fact now of
course is that so I've been meaning to
visit I will we probably saved like 10
minutes of dialogue Now by skipping so
much might not be an exaggeration
[Music]
time is of the essence very valuable
resource is time now where's chill why
do I always lose them why don't we just
go together we love each other the is
anyone supposed to AF
that this
way C you not find a
those how goes the H for ingredients
that's bread uh just started she look
she's looking at basket of bread and
just like I do nuts amongst all these
stalls no why don't we split up and see
we'll take a couple of ingredients each
all right what am I looking for no how
about you look for the peepo nuts and
some garlic I'll find the other things
we
need nuts where was where where was she
seeing nuts
[Music]
where this
girl has been too
sheltered any friend of the inkeeper is
a friend of mine the garlic
please yes
garc gnarly
garlic why does he only have one garlic
to
sell guys need more garlic the best
anyone ever wants any more one of the
best ingredients for food
ever buy sell or be gone he has one
peepo
nut
I maybe you to if that's what you want
that's everything let's see how Jill's
getting on keep them PES nice and chill
I won't have use I got those nuts you
want to see them Jill did you find
everything I did
here giving her my
nuts and the
garlic garlic and peepo nuts perfect Now
All That Remains is for hypocrates to
somehow turn all this into what mid
need but before we head back would you
walk with me a while
yes
nobody will interrupt us here
right oh the Bread Basket she just
bought the whole
basket thank you for asking me to help
you today it makes a nice change it does
it's good to get away from all the
battle and bloodshed for once just being
here reminds me of from you were
children do you remember walking down
Market Street in rosali taking in the
sights and
smells how could I forget what with
toal's Antics remember how his nose
would prick up at the scent of sausages
racing away and we'd have to go running
after him did we tell
chill I don't remember telling
her huh Did we tell
her about
too yeah but
f when did we tell her when was this
conversation I don't think we told
her what it seems weird like like tole
is here at this point of the story you
can choose Jill to go with you like why
why would we not
bring up this
knowledge she might have noticed by
herself but I would like this this to be
talked about and not just like off
screen that's so so weird like it seems
so important I want to see her reaction
I want to hear her reaction no we did
not have her reaction for
sure that's that's so
weird toy
Wy maybe maybe they maybe they are still
planning on giving us the scene but
there seems to be a Hest
necessary lot amount of time in between
us telling
her wouldn't catch you now would we
boy is there anything you wanted to
buise yourself over here except the
truth it was yes well sort of spee Molly
in the kitchens told me about a place
that sells particularly good pies
thought you might like to share one with
me I would thank you
and I saw some
bread where's the
pie it's a lot of big white cobs like
the baker back in rosali used to
make what do you think I thought we
might get some soup to dip it in but
then I tried to slice the but dry cured
ham it was just dipp you right soup to
dip it in
sorry it's just you're right I really do
feel like a child again being here with
you we're adults though jel and you what
you know what adults do Clive
ke is it wrong of me to enjoy this
[Music]
no no
chill this is how life should
be and it's how our lives will be when
our work is finally done and we can live
on our own
terms I hope
so C thank you
Clive uh how dare they not make them
kiss
here well I suppose we better be getting
back I need to give these ingredients to
her and tire I'll see you at the hi take
care shut
up I thought there was an extra scene
that that felt
so suddenly like a different
vibe these little shits man they just
playing with me in my
heart well I'm playing with their
[Music]
game that was the perfect time like they
were having like this deep bonding
momentes is getting on with the Privacy
as much as they needed in a nice
scenery literally having a date picnic
date God damn
it if not now then
when how's work on the shielding
progressing
hypocrates well very well indeed and
thanks in no small part to your kind I
understand it might be because I was
just explaining to T this was my best go
about preparing the moono and now that
we have all the ingredients we may
begin you can count on me I've mixed
more than a few mysterious concoctions
in my
time I'm sure you have we didn't have to
take her what about the shielding itself
work is underway under the water
watchful eyes of bardolf and oelas
apparently it'll be ready soon thank you
all of
you right then Jill would you join me in
the infirmary many hands make of
course that was very NPC turn around
wait a moment start walking Clive thank
you it was nice
just being with you it was wasn't it oh
that
look it appears our work here
is a shame when both the shield followed
by perhaps someone leave it thank
you you
po all right back to Mid
I better go and give mid the good news
then yeah I'm on
it why want she be so far
away that's the shortest
[Music]
way outside here
maybe now I can buy the limit break oh
right
sounds good what does it
do adds
a Mastery as a
fourth wait so then I will be like that
longer oh
wow
[Music]
okay all
right the healing is um I asked this
before but you guys I said I only get
healed when I actually attack right it's
not like just me standing around while
having the limit break heals me right
but does it have to be just started
reading books that the
R2 hits think mid might need or can it
be a normal square triangle square
triangle square
triangle oh is also pass oh there was no
need oh okay don't never
mind
oh it heals more when
hitting oh maybe like the more damage I
do the more it
heals sorry to keep in a manner of speak
he's supervising the brilliant thank me
right then to
the
yep Flames
ultimate you know when I go into this I
thought I'd be making swords and same
whatever you call
her let me yeah I'm kind of over this
make the [\h__\h] ship
already sometime
later
MH
can I skip this
too it's finished is finally finished
yay [\h__\h] for that I'll be feeling my
hammer arm for weeks thank you Clive
Blackthorne everyone that's one down and
just three more to
go oh didn't I tell you the Enterprise
has four mythal engines and we'll be
needing a displacement stack for each I
what now mean now they've got a finish
one to work off my gang and G can build
the rest yeah they
better good luck to them right I'm off
to get
sling it's just an excuse for it to take
even
longer
okay and all the nameless NPCs they have
names but they still are like what's
your
name respectless what's the matter
respect no respect no respect nothing
just no respect
daydreaming are we going to the grave
now thinking about the Enterprise
sailing off Over the Horizon to Shores
unknown come on searching for a land
Untouched by the blight just like me and
my dad planned so if the worst came to
the worst and every scrap of soil in the
twins turned black we might still have a
chance that's what she was meant to be
you see one last chance just in case we
needed it but now she's so close to
being finished I've realized I don't
want her to be that what I don't want it
to be just a Lifeboat for us to cling to
if things get desperate what do you want
it to be I
want I want people to sail a border by
choice not from the lack of it in a
world where we're not just trying to
survive but where we can actually live
I'm working on that and I'll do
everything I can all right as soon as
the Enterprise is fit to sail I'm nor
yor s our plans I'm trust are you sure
about something tells me it's what my
dad would have wanted he'd be proud of
you
um you were going to visit his grave
weren't you yeah I
was and you can come too now that your
little project is finished little
right there's just one thing I need to
finish up first won't we em Mo all right
I'll let AO know you're coming meet us
in the mess when you're ready a I
captain
okay better be
quick make it quick M told me she was
building a ship
progress all right CLI we' finish
sending half the otherway troes in
across the twins as she no excuses not
not quite she said there was one final
thing she had to take care of I'm sure
she'll be finished soon enough she said
that in those words she yeah did yes CL
yeah were you born yesterday or
something there is no I guess she'll
probably be half way a Cana by now girl
M I might still be able to catch
her Mama
[Music]
Mia
M that the same Tom's
helped
bu over
have you seen M yep in a boat going that
way what way then I'm too
late you in a hurry at all are you no
I'm not too late I can teleport I
offered to take her across but she
wouldn't wait just paid for a dingy and
rode off I will slap her silly when I
see her again she said she'll be coming
to me but anyway I was on my way up to
see you got a letter for you oh Urgent
by the sound of it one of your uncle's
men said I was to hand it to you in
person post bleeding a thank you OAS
don't mention
itle apology letter from mid
unfortunately oh my dear boy my journey
to canver has been a resounding success
the friend our Manion not only agreed to
share the content so of his strong books
with us but is considerable knowledge of
the going on in the free cities by which
I learned of the Endeavors of a certain
young friend of yours though I for one
Believe Miss telemon's project to be
quite a valiant Enterprise I doubt the
Canarian authorities will take kindly to
the unauthorized use of their do yards
no matter how deserted and if rumor has
already reached my friend it may not be
long before the guild Masters are
wrapping it out or why am I why am
I mid mid mid
Midwestern what yeah
Texas which is why I pay you this note
I'm committed now I would like to borrow
your man G for moon or two that he might
keep a watch on those who might mean our
little Fellowship ill and warn us of any
impending attack I trust that you will
give this proposal your full
consideration trouble en
cver well I'll need someone to keep an
on
[Music]
M ke I'm sorry mid got us to do all the
dirty work and then just sailed off into
the sunset it
uh that way should I be shipping Gaff
and we can do about it now together next
time you plan on visiting Sid you might
want to Tire to something before you
suggest
it ah don't be so hard on her got to
admit the Dirty Work was kind of fun
everyone pitching in all that bollocks
just like when we built this place why
not you're right anyway we all set to
head to the old Hiway I could do with
getting to Cana pretty sharpish wouldn't
do to keep lord rosfield of the seven
High houses waiting now W it AG but
after he asked for me
personally will be leaving with me he's
40 will you mind the place while we're
gone you can count on me gav's 40 just
be sure we'll give Sid and the others
more G look like
40 oh by the way Jill will be joining us
too she's got some things to take care
of but she'll meet us there I hope she's
telling the truth at least
least they don't seem like they have
such a huge age gra I guess they do
what yeah it's time lapse but wait well
how old does that make
me we're going without
mid
[Music]
sand
see
[Music]
me well
Sid I remember what you told
me if no one is listening to what you
have to say you may as well not say it
h
but I will say this old friend he's
pretty Hugo CER is
gone his shadow looms over us no
longer it's a Pity the Phoenix can't be
in two places at
once if it had been with us maybe he
could have done something for the
Lost not even the Phoenix can bring
people back from the
dead life has a
beginning and an
end so we must live while we have the
chance you guys all don't
agree not as slaves to the
crystals but as free
[Music]
men slander may we join you
oh a a
hold a everybody's here
[Music]
sweet lady Karen what a pleasant
surprise they got the memo I thought to
drop by and see how you were all doing
before heading off to restock me
supplies
a I I feel the sense of community now
that's
nice
[Music]
a it wasn't the most scenic view back
then but it were never as bad as
this I
know a blind March is
on and
soon there will be no escaping sites
like
these so our mission remains
unchanged we cannot stop until every
mother crystal is gone and their thirst
for ether with
them the only one that remains in storm
is Drake's tail in the crystalline
Dominion our next Target we're going to
twins
side it's the capital of the Empire
these days I wouldn't like to think how
tightly guarded they've got the
place not that that'll stop you but we
do well to scout it out before you go
charging in we would indeed if you're
off to the Dominion you can take this
great lump with
you Goods oh I am sorry have you
forgotten you're the most Wanted Man in
the twins I thought you might like to
disguise yourselves as the attendance of
a traveling Trader assuming you've no
better ideas he's going to help me with
that you wanted to buy yourself some
tools didn't you well now's your
chance oh
he you're letting me go with them oh
than none stop that you Brit me bones
you great Galo
what the
hell there's a caravan that runs back
and forth between the Dominion and the B
laab
markets by the merchant Guild just show
them goss's Traders p and you'll be on
your
way it'll be a down site less risky than
foot in at the length of the crystal I
can't even listen he's so loud you Karen
and glad to have you with us G oh okay
then I'll get me things and I'll meet
you there see you down in
bckad get off me P
fingers Jill you're with me he going to
fight understood and gav already on my
way
Captain be careful AR I always hey
scouting
[Music]
did you see that s your prot is making a
proper little Outlaw of
himself okay Gap is like going that way
cuz he's going to scout
right but then the holdor guy who needs
to pick up some things before he goes
but why don't why why are we all going
Separate Ways
H I'm still snacking on
cucumbers I thought I I should probably
snack on something healthy at least
sometimes all right let's need
Clift yeah a little bit of salt just a
little
[Music]
bit Eastern
Dalia
you eat cucumbers with yogurt
[Music]
oh not something I would eat with yogurt
but I can see how it could
work it's almost sour
[Music]
cream
onward we go forward you feeling better
thanks to
I'm glad to hear it and to help can use
J boy yeah are we going to talk about
tole or what
Jill yeah I guess not
okay this used to be a trade route for
Merchants Crossing the scar till the
Republic laid a new road wide enough to
let wagons pass and all official traffic
moved there leaving this one for those
living at outside the law
indeed I doubt we'll be the only Outlaws
on the trail
today a this is a really cool view like
having so many layers of things that's
in the that in the back is Drake's Fang
right oh what's left of
it it's really nice I can see so
far
[Music]
what do you
think how nice I have to fight this of
their own far
from and if you ever want to see theay
the
kill this one easy
ow ow you know the bump that I
cut it's like really taking his damn
sweet time to
heal and it still
hurts this
uh it was a tiny cut
though
tiny how come it still
hurts
w
kill your
room all yours to no okay that's
it most annoying get
him can I turn it a little bit quieter
again
[Music]
thanks for the
greeting My Stream has been frozen for
10 minutes well that's not
normal oh
SHO yeah hey gr plny at
night um last night I even put a little
bit of like wound wound healing cream
but only a little bit I wanted to pet
smovie
obviously [\h__\h] my combo aren't
working that's
better
why yeah free goes GES gag gagag keep it
covered or open for the first few hours
or like the first night I kept it uh
with a bandid we've done the Republic of
service but the last two days I kept it
open cuz I thought it heals faster that
way but it's not even like ow ow ow ow
it's like
still kind of like there's an opening
still so I probably should put a bandid
on again I guess I'm somehow just like
preventing it from healing properly
because I I use my Thum a lot I
guess it's annoying it hurts why do [\h__\h]
does it
hurt I see the DX lag behind R area when
it comes to bridge building the Fallen
ruin should hold at least you were
proven wrong 5 minutes later oh man the
path continues on the other
side yeah today is really not the day
huh for
YouTube hopefully it will get better
until family
fud I'll have to wake up so early for
that it starts at 6: a.m. for
me nice it hit them
all starts at 6: a.m. but you know if
you consider prep and the fact that it's
a big collab I should
probably start being on standby and
preparing at
5:30
yeah I think my stream will end early
today I still have to make the thumbnail
but that's not a big issue but yeah got
to I want I don't want to be too sleepy
6 hours of sleep would be
nice
oo so this is a
meus the land of the
Gods it's even more impressive than I
imagined I remember being captivated by
the story as a
child long long
ago man was overcome by
avarice and challenged the Gods in a bit
to in their
power a final battle took place here at
these
Falls or so the
goes good that we if anyone ever manages
to Plum those
deps perhaps we'll learn if there's any
truth to the
tale that the gods emerged
Victorious and punished man for his
Defiance by visiting upon
him two
curses what are they Domin in
Paris tell the
truth I always thought it strange that
the dominants and their icons were
deemed a
curse back
home the dominant inherited the
throne they were admired and
exalted not spurned mhm whenever I got
to that part of the story I always
assumed there must be something I'd
misunderstood you had a lot of story
books didn't you in your room I
mean when we were
young the old Legends were always my
favorites epic battles between Gods and
Men father encouraged me to read as much
as I
could he thought it good for my
education H you really were a boy like
any other weren't
you what do you think he
was just look at this
place
it's enough to make you believe the
Legends are
true I
know it's completely dead now man what
the
[\h__\h] we're not far from
Bad the road will be busier up ahead and
we'll have to keep our wits about us
I'll I'll probably just uh do one or two
more hours
anyway I would end it now because of all
the lag but I do need to get progress in
something
wrong so
nothing it's
nothing we're close to a good stopping
point oh okay they they always have like
good stopping points at the best timings
for me it
seems exactly when I need them
I see the reports are true father oo you
have surrendered the throne to
Olivier I
have emperor Olivier shall rebuild the
holy Empire of
sambre how is he to rule an Empire he is
but a boy I shall advise him until comes
of age father please or for as long as I
am
able the Empire we seek to build needs
Young Blood to rule it and I can think
of none better suited to the
task there is other news
Dion Hugo kka is dead and Drake's Fang
destroyed the pillars of the Republic
have
fallen a long the Imperial Banner shall
fly over every city in
storm and then
valesia all shall bow before their
Emperor father these are the words of a
tyrant they are the words of a
God the emperor whom I gladly
serve great Greer made
flesh ads so
good oh that's
something return to your Camp Dion and
ready your
forces it is time to show the
world the true power of SRE I love what
they did with the painting there the
design of this Hall is really
father
noise I find you much
changed I wonder who drew it is this is
truly the path you wish to
tread or are these the Ambitions of
another of Ultima
perhaps what nonsense is this
more I speak my mind and my mind
only though I do owe Annabella thanks
for reminding me of certain
truths regarding ing the nature of
nations of
rulers and of the
Divine
Exquisite you would trust the words of
this
traitorous she betrayed her country she
slew her husband you have ever been an
invaluable servant to SRE Prince
Dion I trust you will continue to serve
your emperor in the wars to come the
caner silence insolent
wretch you will bend the knee all else
is
heresy
Z forgive me this audience is
over come your Radiance the Rena
Syndicate awaits your pleasure oh not
another meeting with silly old men he
can speak they're so
boring well when he speaks he seems
pretty normal I'm hungry father can't we
have luncheon
instead H you can talk he's not
completely druged pain you that you will
not inherit your father's Throne
interesting I have suffered
worse count your blessings Dion for a
baseball born child to be chosen by
bahamat is Miracle enough you have risen
high on his wings but you shall rise no
higher lest your impure blood stain the
throne what do you know of my
blood is he a
bastard Bach this
beach we must destroy her
soon but she might just to the northy we
just need to hug the
coast okay wait what can we go down
there no right have to go ah yes oh choa
Cho come on to
time
the corners are really bad with this
thing left or
right just enemies is there a
chest no all
right I'm out of
here infiltrating the Dominion won't be
easy with the Imperials on high alert no
his Radiance has lost one Capital
already we can be sure Sylvester will do
everything in his power to hold on to
twins side his troops are well trained
and increasingly battle hardened but
it's not as if we can wait for the siege
to
end
sheesh
sheesh look at this
water no wobbliness to be
seen she as
gorgeous so smooth so silky I want to
jump into it
to take a
dive oh by the way yesterday I after my
stream I kind of felt like playing
refugees so I tried against hard AI once
only once for the crystalline Dominion
because they don't know how to live
without the Crystal's
blessing uh I got to Imperial age uh but
then then you know I was a little bit
slow on creating my own Army and then I
seemingly had the wrong um units really
cuz I was like I didn't know yet what
they were going to bring cuz I was
playing on the arena map where there's
the the walls so you can't really Scout
what they're
making and then I had all these organ
guns you know I thought ah they're going
to do it just like just like in the
Stream with
Ellie but now there are no crystals here
they destroyed but you know supposed to
meet gos isn't it practice makes perfect
he said he'd wait for us here after
replenishing his supplies I dare say
he'll have finish by
now practice makes perfect and I was
without help
so I'll have to get through this on my
own a few
times I I didn't really think I would
make it um
anyway
yeah I tried my best
recreate what we had in our stream
though let me carry your goods I'm out
of my sight
WR I'm not giving up did you pause a lot
still a little bit yeah wouldn't say as
much as I from across the water come one
come all Feast your eyes good sir can I
interest you
in cuz I wanted to remember you know
what what would Ellie do how much for a
measly crust of bread you won't find any
cheaper not nowadays what would ell more
than welcome
to the Empire's unlawful and
illegitimate occupation of the
crystalline Dominion is still in effect
only those whose business in twins side
has been officially approved by the
Republican Army will be permitted to
cross the border all who seek entry at a
formal line and ready their documents
for
inspection it looks like we aren't the
only ones who are eager to
leave and they're checking
everyone I can't you make an not for the
likes of you we won't get through
without that
pass
let's go and find good shall
we understandable here somewhere as
sweet as
nectar need to have my immigration
documents ready oh hi
holder D there you are you made it C I'm
so sorry don't tell Nan will you did you
forget something SL down goods just tell
us what
happened it's we Traders pass it's gone
no we Cann ride the Caravan without it
we won't even be able to get through the
flipping checkpoint ridiculous hold do
you remember when you last saw it it was
in me pocket a minute ago then a b
bumped into me and yeah with such a
big big back surpr back on your back a
busy market like this is prime territory
for pig Pockets I can tell you it's
probably somewhere back we need to find
this the very very very bottom where we
even start of your backpack I know
you'll have to take out every single
thing no one knows more about what goes
on around ear than she does where do we
find her and then you look once she's
the find it you think oh it's not in my
back then's got a red chocolate B on it
no it is you look again time like maybe
even the third time you two go on ahead
I'm going to check all right maybe even
the fourth time but it's in there I'm
telling
you and then you feel out embar red
choco then red Cho and the other one are
purses you feel embarrassed when you
finally find
it a damn it it was in here after
all
[\h__\h] I got it I got it now
whoopsy
okay
bloody Crimson Caravans scooping up all
the best customers leave some for the
rest of
us Quest destination nearby oh
chest that just reminded
me there was a chest somewhere that I
saw and I couldn't open it and now I
don't know where it was
anymore no I missed out on one
chest I like saw it kind of in a
cutscene kind of
moment I don't think I ever opened it
[Music]
afterwards damn was a a
white not one of these chests that I
just opened it was a white whitish
chest if our new arrivals had brought
any oh yeah anyway this is a red CH ball
place looking to hire a coach it's 10
million for a two birer to the
crystalline Dominion million oh we're
not here for that then I B you good
day wait don't go ell he's me
made a Yol as I live and breathe gos
what are you doing back in
bad
I gather lady Karen didn't send
you she
did is that a
problem so what trouble have you got
yourself into this
time it's me Traders pass it got
stolen by little Ben of all the you're
the size of a
moral
honestly GS told us that you know the
markets well might you have an idea
which little B could have done this we
don't intend to punish them we just need
our pass back I want to punish them
spank with the sh
way I see we have to so neither of you
has a traitor's pass
either
not that anyone would take you for
Traders but I suppose that's why you
came to me a good
disguise at the moment now I can't say
for sure who took your pass but I
suspect I know why they did it let me
explain CU of what I just saw right they
need to get
through l
ever since the fist marched on the
Dominion the Republic has been clamping
down on any Commerce that might Aid the
Empire more than it does us which means
Traders passes have gone from being
merely a way of easing one's progress to
being essential if one wishes to cross
the border at all is it CH or
outstripping Supply they've become a
precious commodity leading some to seek
to acquire them by less than legitimate
means so the children are stealing
passes to sell on the black market Jun
yes and no like a chicken passes are
inscribed with the names of their owners
and yet none of the victim's names have
appeared on the register of those
passing through the
checkpoint that someone is doctoring the
stolen passes the same someone who is
encouraging the children to steal them
and the same someone who has good his
pass whoever they are they're ruining
the livelihoods of honest Merchants
which is why we've decided will you
stand with us you want to get your pass
back and we want to ensure that no more
are sto catch whoever's behind at all
and two birds shall be slain yeah no
problem is there any other way this is
kind of similar to won't let you Zin if
you're not with the car desert City's
problem it's that a I don't know try
swimming across the street but the
guards deed problem that we have to
solve before we can find people who took
the past move on I'll give up all hope
of entering the
Dominion
okay all right we'll help thank you
kindly um yeah but I don't know your
name Eloise at your service Eloise
Clive a pleasure doing business with you
Clive
is your nickname
Ellie I know many Ellies
now many many Ellies seal obtained a
crimson color from L the proprietor of
the furniture makers by the coach stop
is spearheading the search wear that and
he will know you for a friend I suggest
that you speak with him first the
furniture makers
and
actually was pretty 4K to Me Maybe not
to you guys but out of my sight wretch I
know you for a friend to me for
sure come on come on hope I can play
more AOE when I get some time but
currently I have no time for anything a
are you the furniture maker looking for
she told for one harder to not that
they'd be like the fish thank you
MH thank you dun speak with the
fishmonger all
right you won't find anything of this
quality in Twin you guys still streaming
it on Discord that's so sweet you should
come with me to the Dominion I hope
that's working out well she's asked me
to help is that
false
I want you know
what fish I want to eat fish on a stick
on a on a all right then just grilled on
the fire how hard can that be that was
like one of my favorite things to eat in
medieval
festivals come taste my peaches sweetest
NE excuse me do you mind if I ask you
something just normal fish on the sck
the
finest more children
doco where are the kids where are the
kids oh almost
here you just have turkey
legs turkey legs I had my first ever
turkey leg in uh Universal studiio Japan
remember and I was really not impressed
by
my did not like
it would have been better with sauce and
stuff cuz it was like just like the leg
it's kind of dry and a
lot very dry definitely need
sauce it just looked so
good and it had such a long line you
would think that it's because it's good
but I think all the people just line up
because they see the other people eating
it it looking great it looks delicious
so they line up for it they think oh
there's already align just like we
thought so you line up then you get it
and then I think probably a lot of
people were not so impressed by
it although I've noticed that in Japan
that's that then a lot of things she
must have been the refugee that normally
here I would eat with sauce are sold
with without sauce in Japan
like also with like U McDonald's or
Burger King or whatever
daddy so maybe they just like eating
things without sauce sometimes that Big
Fat donkey was easy pickings he wouldn't
have noticed if we robbed his boots off
him yeah wish we hadn't handed over the
past though could use one of those
things to get out of this dump chance to
be a fine thing the moment they found
out they to dring us up by our
guts would they now perhaps you'd like
to introduce us to these Charming
characters [\h__\h] we're in trouble now
what do we do what his this child's face
I'm off looks so old hza where are you
going why does he look so old so that
was hza eh right Jill you watch these
two I'm going after him all
right shape shifter
maybe maybe he's a hobbit he can't have
gone
far I need to find him before his
employers
[Music]
do is trying to blend in with the adults
maybe did you
see thank you than you I thought
so
hza ah there he is hiding in the shadow
lur working in the
shadows [\h__\h]
cornered it's all right hza I'm not
going to hurt you except for L jungler I
just want to ask you some
questions fine not like I've got a
choice I'm looking for the people who
are making you
steal call themselves The Car Stones
they said they give me good Gill if I
did what they told me I knew they were
bad but bir doesn't come for free didn't
come at all half the time before I
started Buzz for them you know if I
didn't do it they just pick on someone
else someone they could push around
easy
H you found him then Jill Eloise is
watching over them she sent GS and I to
look for
you I haven't got your pass anymore if
that's what you're after I gave it to
the car Stones dude whatever you do to
me I can't get it back great not that I
go against them anyway if it wenter for
their Gil me and my mates would have
starved understandable
toy
Wy have we been
noticed cowards oh you will not force
another child to oh no no no no that's
not what we're trying to do we're
not what is this handsome young
lad with good principles and ethics H
you're making a mist mistake we're on
the same side misunderstanding like hell
we
are that
bro where did you get
it must it
feel
gos what are you doing with these
people unless you're the ones my sister
was talking about your
sister ah
Eloise right both have black
hair
huh and
so the circle Eloise didn't tell us she
had a brother becomes a why would she
I'm just her back and a blade Theodore
at your service service sorry about
before Theodore what do you know of the
cast
stones ERS who have made bad their
hunting ground they prey on the
desperate stealing from those with Gil
I'd been
looking but it seems they've already
stooped even lower than I'd feared looks
like a good no he doesn't don't blame
him for what they've made him do if he
and his friends hadn't agreed to work
for the stone some other poor souls
would have nah on pain of death most
likely even with and my sisters asked
you to help but then we all want
them no he doesn't yes he does no he
doesn't yes he does no he doesn't yes he
does no he
doesn't we can go on and on and on and
on and on is
it
so what's the plan what else you get
your all right then all right all right
then all all
all hza where are they camped couldn't
if I want or to they always come to tell
I Tred following them once but they
spotted behind we'll try it this time
back down the road towards L's CLE mhm
okay let's
go looks like a younger CLI L's cleft to
the South past we could be related for
sure yeah both have a a nice scared
beard growth as
well let's go I wish I could run
faster daddy the resting to are so cute
we have to keep going this is like a cat
minion is our only chance as a Choco
ball I
know just
loafing loafing choco
ball
Chola
cute I'm sure since they eat choco BS
that they could make a out of it too
yeah
sounds brutal
but what I wanted to pick up the
item the way he pointed his finger at me
that's the one who's been sticking his
nose in our
business
fast any more of that the ring leaders
but at least we know we're on the right
track where was the item
there it's throughoute to point yeah but
remember the conversation we had about
me saying I do point at people you know
not out of
a mean intention or so no
just like you know oh you did that oh my
God yeah W good or something like
that I wish people weren't so sensitive
about it cuz it's in my just like built
into
my body
now I just do it can't help it we got
company that's the
lot aim
Doo
arise any more AOE
no over here it's
over get
him
H from far away to a stranger soldiers
well I I for me it's always the context
like why am I pointing at this
person like when I'm what if I'm
pointing at a far away stranger because
I'm telling my friend that oh I don't
know go go go there
because maybe there's something behind
the
stranger uh no it could be a good reason
I think it context is
important so if someone points at me but
the context is like friendly then I
don't
mind no problem point at me all you want
Point me out pointy
pointy the attention shall be
mine oh yeah yeah like oh look how what
cool clothes they're wearing but
normally I wouldn't like point at
someone some of our new recruits are
natural B fashion or whatever especially
the little ones cuz I guess I also don't
want somebody to be like well why are
they pointing at me are they making fun
of me or something like that sh them any
we're ready when you are oh
I'm cuab it can be confusing [\h__\h] it's
that God from bulad kill him kill them
all you don't know the intentions of the
person pointing at you so yeah
okay generally I would wouldn't really
do it anyway all yours
[Music]
[Applause]
to I still got it I still got
it I'm on fire
oh and that it just keeps on going it
just keeps on
going all yours
tole this that's it I was out of
attack get
him oh hey hey hey hey
yeah fine
H okay chill let R
ready this
one got it got it got it got
it
attack
ooh when she hits it she hits it
Wella
service and another one
and the Dodge is so
good oh yeah guys check Discord on on
kfb Discord they're like streaming My
Stream in case anybody of you guys are
having issues watching
it KB Discord more reason to join the
kfb Discord
yay and they say crime doesn't pay gold
chains Rings purses swag and Traders
passes have the names been
changed not yet I recognize some of them
no doubt gos is is somewhere among them
now I just need to sort through it all
and everything to the people it was
taken from we should go and give Eloise
the good news I shall
support I support the kfp Discord
growing
because then kfp community
grows does kfp community projects grow
and also if you're more as a fan of
something if you're more
involved in a fandom I feel like in many
cases not always but in many cases it
can make make you just feel even more of
a
fan of the
person make you feel more passionate
perhaps make you feel more like you want
to support this
person even more so yeah I feel like it
uh it might have the effect
of increasing
support like you're already a fan yeah
but if you join the Discord right
maybe maybe we can reach even higher
Heights that's that then notifications
to being notified about some cool stuff
going
on that you don't want to miss out on
hurry man I must leave for the Dominion
no join the kfb
Discord the hottest memes what do you
mean I jinxed
it oh the
stream did it cut
out on Discord too ah Clive how goes the
hunt quite the
opposite so it was the cast stones who
were behind it all Theo told me he'd
been on their Trail and their demise
solves three problems at a stroke that
of the pig Pockets I
own you are
to here Clive Goods is part thank
you do we need some
too I
will L I've asked our boys to carry the
rest of the goods
handsome of course I'll make some space
in the store
room jeans I expect you'll soon be on
your way then but it wouldn't do to
leave without introducing yourself
properly would it now jeans Sid
jeans jeans yeah jeans don't look so
shocked I don't understand as you now
know all too well we at the Crimson
Caravans are always happy to help those
in need for a small fee we will move
anything now it's a good stopping point
be that Goods to Market or bearers away
from it I was the first my sister helped
I had no idea it just and to wouldn't
you agree I would it seemed so what
would shut up I'm so tired of the
chitchat
today it's not
important thank you thank you sorry no
no no need for extra lore today what is
it El has friends in high places while I
have
Associates
thanks more I be with
pride well All That Remains is to wish
you a safe onward Journey gs's path
should secure you a place on the Caravan
but if you encounter any difficulties we
would be delighted to provide you with a
coach of our own course 9
million how much do I even have by now
how much money have I
accumulated 8 is that the money I have
85,000 yeah uh right then who the [\h__\h]
let's get this back pay 10 million who
has that
money
sheesh yeah I would like to do
longer but there's been endless
lag and I have to sleep
early
H
yeah I mean I'm not going to go to sleep
right the away it's it's only 700 p.m.
but at least I I have definitely the the
choice I can should should I read super
chats at least I mean there's barely
anything I think so it's going to be
fast FF going on Hiatus no no I'm still
playing next week no not next week but
next week I should get in like I still
don't know when I'm really leaving I've
I I'll get at least one if not two more
streams yeah I guess I'll keep it for
next time um so tomorrow we have Family
Feud or like today depending on your
time
zone
for yeah 6:00 a.m. my time is the family
field and then later in the day I guess
now I have time to make the schedule no
I don't think I would be done so
early but later in the day uh I'm also
streaming something
scary a game that I was is waiting to
play until Halloween
time can you
guess can you guess what it
is chicken feet
Yes I literally waited just for this
season Fatal Frame is the day
after the chicken
Kus it's funny though I think from what
I've seen it's quite funny huge giant
chicken chasing you that's pretty much
all there is right but we'll play it for
a little
bit yeah thanks for reminding
me okay I guess that's it I feel so
empty and
Hollow
can this really be the
end is this really the
end of today
stream did you re record the thing yes
but I have another thing to quickly
record uh once I'm
done all right level
31 we
are going to hopefully make more
progress
and finish the game sometime soon I
wonder how far I am guys who who has an
idea considering I'm not doing side
quests how much longer this will take
[Music]
me I'm 60% in yeah this is the fifth
stream I thought it was shorter than
this two long
I was hoping today would be kind of
long
damn free to four more
streams
free let's make it
free even free I don't know if I can
squeeze in free more cuz like we were we
decided next
week probably no Final Fantasy but now I
feel like I need
to H
it's too bad cuz I also have to schedule
Final Fantasy far in advance like
somewhat far in advance so it's not like
I can like decide spontaneously like oh
okay I don't feel so exhausted so I
shall play Final Fantasy today or
tomorrow I can't do
that I think you can finish in free
streams to c 7 to finish
huh where her streams is much longer
than
mine playing Callie's house now I'll try
to I I'll look again at like
my
um my uh
like the flights that I wanted to take
and I see I I'll check how how much I
can drag it out to go to
Japan it's just hard because uh I need
to have like dance lessons and stuff
when I'm in Japan but there's like not a
single one set in
stone yet like there's no date and time
for anything yet I'm still waiting for
uh my my staff
JMA uh and another manager to fixate
these things before that I wasn't going
to book the flight but like time is
taking and I don't really want to wait
much longer to book everything I also
noticed all the accommodations
accommodations that I um
saved to look at like 90% of them are
gone
now so
H 12 hours one more well I can do if I
if we don't have like family feud in the
morning then I could do like 12 hours
today
too but yeah
uh I guess I'll just have to book it
without
knowing when when I actually have dance
lessons I hope I hope it'll be enough
time though h
h two s hours should finish the game you
think so really what what that would
mean that I don't really think we're at
60% that should be more but we'll
see we'll see we'll see I just want to
schedule it I want to I want to finish
it before
Japan that would be great
yeah
YouTube why why why are you so weird on
a beautiful
Sunday I'm sorry guys it was like that
hope you guys whoever was like having
issues with it I hope you were able to
maybe check out the vaud hello vaud
Watchers thank you for coming back to
the VOD I appreciate
it
yeah and thanks to Discord people for
backing up all the ones who were
struggling a
[Music]
it in 10 hours actually in 10 hours the
collab uh the family food collab will be
on my channel so I'll see you guys there
hopefully and in Germany we say
Al I I know later on got a little bit
like tired and bored but I think we had
some nice talks anyway in the beginning
and
jorks so I had fun thanks for spending
time with me this
weekend until another week the end of
October is
near bye-bye vamos
vamos vamos
Amigos
[Music]
this smovie will be like Mommy you're
done so early today what's
up well yes well yes I
[Music]
am