[Music]
all
right free hot
dogs
Library quick exclamation point and set
now we
wait oh look who it is so you break the
sound barrier and rush over here for a
free hot dog but you won't even take a
second to look at my text wow I see how
it is oh well let me tell you better
anyway her name is Sophie and she's my
pet rock well what of my pet rocks i r
to class for sh and
tting say where's your pet rock don't
tell me you didn't bring
[Music]
one you sure know how to pick a class
schedule Iris I mean discreet
mathematics after statistical mechanics
what the heck was I
[Music]
thinking at least it's
over which question are you struggling
with
number five okay let's
see ah Su the that's simple enough it
means I like you I mean I don't like you
I mean I do like you but I don't like
you like that like you know like
[Music]
d