[Music]
Hmm,
I
don't
[Music]
Hmm
yeah
[Music]
Me
with Mushu
[Music]
Hmm
me
ha
[Music]
Hmm yeah
yeah
[Music]
Hmm
today
me
[Music]
Hmm
me
can you
DO
[Music]
Yeah
yeah
[Music]
Today,
Morny 2x, so
everyone is a chocolate, everyone
is [Music] Hi
-A  I've participated
in the past two competitions for small fish, and this is the meaning of my participation.So,
Horo Live Marika is great.I'll
be participating in small fish high again this year.Hello, I'm Melancholy.Thank you very much.So, let's
do it again today.Let's be
miserable.  Yes, I want to do
my best to win the small fish category for the third time in a row.
Hmm, it's a little bit, I got a little bit of a
small-sized crown that I got in town last year or two, but it's a used one.Ah, I wanted to bring it with me,
but I
can't find it.Hmm,
wow, I don't know
what will happen this year.I want to keep going.  I
think I
'll do my best to become a small fry in Hi-Kan.Thank
you in advance.My
goal is
not to be at the bottom.That's not
it.  I
think the signs are the most important thing, so I'm going to
do my best.
Well, well, well,
what's this about? The
dentists are all here. With 5 losses, it's going to
be fun to see what happens this year.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
[Music]
Puck's so hot, I gave him a
coke, so I gave him some coke. That's
good, right?  I
took a bow, watched everyone run,
and watched everyone run, and then I saw
someone throwing something and cracking it up, and I
thought, ``Oh, bookkeeping, that might be cool,'' but that person was really cool.  I want to see Fan 8 of that cool guy.2
Hmm, I thought I wanted to play Eccho-kun,
so I smelled it every time.The
items that come out are killer caps.  Come
on, it's
just a mushroom, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, I want to have a moon with 4 leaves, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, I
want to use 6 with pose water with chocolate.  - I
definitely
want to release it. Well,
now, well, it looks like it's about to start.
Hey, I'm looking forward to it.
Hiraa is not just a 2-Char strange killer.
Why don't you try using Chocho? His past
beliefs are
pretty cool. It's like it's your
first time, isn't it?
[Music]
Thank you for the song Sedan. Let's
aim for Soraman. I think we can aim for it and make it to the middle.
Maybe, just
maybe.  It's good that you were aiming like that.If you
can do it left and right, you'll see the cherry blossoms.That's right, it's
not a sweet world.Do you
understand?
This small fry isn't like
that.  There's
nothing like that.
[Music]
Ah,
let's get started.
oh,
ah. Let's go.  No. 1
Why are the small fry in the back the same as Manda?
Hey
[Music] That's
great!
It's a delicious hotbed car. Here it is. Mess
here.
Metty. I
took one.
Don't look at everyone, wait a minute,
wait a minute, everyone's fast, everyone's fast,
wait a minute,
I love you, I
took it after shaving it,
take it, air
[music] I
got it from a problem that wasn't there, I got it
stopped, it's a difficult empty space right now, hahaha, it's
valid in.  The coin totter who took it,
irradiated his feet
with oj rank, got in there and stood up
[Music] It looks like it's gone [Music]
The feature is the fight that the remedy person wants to make,
go and go.
Let's go to Isogo. It
was a winning course. Let's go to the cup.
Ana. If the
big bone shows a run, let it fall.
Typhoon. It's a
scary thing, and I learned a lot from parfaits. I
don't have a bite, but I have a lot of opinions. The
certificate is
hot. It
's a scrapped car. It's Hashimi
[  Music] I
got off the train and didn't fall even with this. Hey, I'm the
champion. Let's catch up with the song here.
Isuku
Royal Castle Listed Designer
Korokko  I
want you to come home with a heartbeat. I'm going to give you
five pairs of chocolates. I'm going to give you some flour. I
said kneaded sweets. Once I saw it, the direction changed
and the big reason was blood deficiency.
Use it quickly. Killer. Use killer.
First arrival, I
'll leave it to you in advance.
ku. That's where you can get the weapon you want.
Leafa Ido-cho is close to being released. It's
getting close. It's getting close. What do you mean?
Hey.
[Music]
Oh, well,
well, well, well, there
's more. There
's still more, so let's
use If.
Let's apply. This
is Mom's fourth case, so
what are you talking about?
[Music]
Alfin Pitch
What, what, what are you talking about?
I wonder if he's really saying it with his fingers.
[Music]
Air, mama, are you shy
? I wonder if that chocolate is shy.
[Music]
Everyone looks like chocolate. Hey, it
looks thin.  Is
n't it strange?
[Music] The
director wants to make them, but he can't
go, but he's nervous, and Koi is No. 2 Tokyo Daddy.
Even after Mr. Osha fell on Iran on the 3rd, the opponent
was also a strong defense team.  Please look at me, I'm
a bit horny and have good manners. 1st place tt tt dk I can do it,
I can do it, I can
do it. It's a victory day after finishing with Bankai Star.  I'm
saying the 5 zones, and today I'm talking about everyone,
and I'm going to put it in my thoughts.
4 e 4 I'm not at the bottom
Go
this
Use this
Ha ha ha I can
go I can go
here I'll come back and go 4
Saba Birki vodka peg ok, ok, ok,
there's a flower waiting for me, ok, ok, ok, ok, where is it
ok,
isn't
this the first time?  It must
have been the governor.
What happened in those 22 seconds?
Waiting for the song that just hatched, what happened to 11th place?
c
Peppin
Eh,
wait, wait,
wait, wait! Oh, I want to wake up
when Choco-sensei first collides head-on with the turtle.
Music. If you
take a photo of Koremasa just once, I
'll have a party where I'll reveal it. Leave it to me
for 50,000.
Let's do our best.
Oshio Kowase Star
Notebook has opened the library, so check it out.
It wasn't the last place, so it's the
second to last. It's a
great start.
Okay, this time, Totsuka is a little girl. I'm sorry that
everyone used it with Yakhon and my sister. Than
, I'm sorry that it's a little 1. I
made a nail
character. I'm the only one who has Trevor.  Don't
act like you're talking.Someone
said that if you take a photo, your taste will taste faster.  The
person I can see in front of me is still a little
reunited, but I'm not at the bottom. I
can still go on. I'm sure there's still a
difference between here and there.
Or should I go to the sea? I
don't understand this enzyme at all.  It's going
to fall. I wish I hadn't fallen through the snow,
but I'm still alive. Now, I'm
hiking here. I
don't know what Abadi's eyes are. It's
weird. It looks
like a house. It's divided into two.  I
want to make a transfer to say that I won't stand up.
What's
going on now? Everyone
shaves off all their six hairs now.
Here, the other person also smiles. I'm a big Yuki type.
Here,
here, I'm going to use Union Wai.  I'm going to have a good time
Sasa, my ex-husband has a problem and Iida's career as an experiment is
gone, so I'm going
somewhere, so wait a minute,
don't hit me, I'll give you a little bit of chocolate and this week I'll give you a certificate,
here, here, here, I'm
going to stop.
When it happens,
77 I'm fishing for a knot, and it's built right now. Feels
good, feels good. Yes, it's abandoned here.
Tunnel tunnel, oh, it's a
rocket. Oops, it's here.
Good a stop.
Isn't this the road?  I want you to think it's a terrible path, an umbrella path,
but there's a corner,
Lighter Coke, Wow, okay
[music]
and we'll meet again.  I
don't think you're talking about original food, but I don't think it's with daddy
or daddy.What are you talking about?
Chocolate is good, isn't it?
This is
not going to be a 3rd grade Nezugusa 5 loss championship.Chocolate
is super.  Well, the
long one will take first place here.Even
if it's low, I think I can
still make a reversal.Maybe I can go.I can
do it.It's okay.It's okay.
Check several places. That's the
difference between today's women. The
large
water generation
runs. I'm a
champion who loves things with drift pattern tuxedos.  It's
different, walls and sounds aren't the same thing. If I
play Touhou, the song I want to be friends with is
Nekomi Pochirin. I'm
already late. It's
Hiroboko and I can go with all my might.
Eh, a good example of instant escape, a
strong car,
here's the killer, y'all, y'all,
abayo, y'all, y'all, ano,
ana
dj ko,
that's how it's accomplished, here, here, here, the 3rd generation,
Toki 3rd generation, I can't get enough of you,
Onsho Teme  There are people in front of me. Yes, I can
do it here. It's okay to do this here and here. It's fine now. I
leave the drum. Everyone
agrees that it's not the best record.
This is good, but it's good.  It's
Arthur, if it's a problem, I can do this.
re answer.
Okay. Well, I'll use it. Who's going to record this?
[Music] I ca
n't see, I can't see, I can't see. I can't
see. It's the lighting tower that originally came up with cold protection.  It's
easier to see with Ikasumi so that I can't see it.
Even if I leave it a little bit, it's good to be a good place to go to
Pancho and the first thing,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, do
n't leave the chocolate behind, and I'll give you some chocolate gum. What's the wait for the store to open? What's going on right now? Hold on, hold on, Jaxa Lander, please surpass me. I can't think of anything.  Goto
Rariaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa it's a relief that the level is a dub
Wait a minute, wait a minute, that's
funny
Sweets
Everyone's going too fast Yeah, I
like that it's kind to beginners.
[Music] There's
still a lot more to it than if we win first place.
Eh, this is still a chocolate life.
This is a chocolate life.
Well, it's the final.  It's not like it's
not the final. It's okay if you take it all at once. I can't get excited about it. It's my first time
here.
Hey Kyoko. I hope the movie will be released today.
Why don't you dismount 3-wait a minute, the
pot will fall off,
say something about chocolate and change it,
baby,
if it's my rally, I'll go to the man, but
not in front of you, cad, chong,
what a bottom.  So it's not yellow. I
think Hiller should come out. I think I can
go on. Just let
me finish. Yes, I'm going to do this and that. It's going to be
a little different. Hey,
no.
If that was an immortal with a thin chassis, it
would have frozen if you could carry it around. Hino isn't a sly kid.
Hey, that's the cones with those sly abs.
Pyoko.
Ena on the side
with someone. Now,
take the left.
Nice nice.
Here, here, here, there's a movement, the
people who received it are still big
, but it's still bad gel.  I
think it's okay because I got hit by lightning, so I cut it off.
Sound symptom dehumidification. I'm getting
into the swamp here. I'm a little stuck, so I
drew a killer, so I released the chocolate power and prepared.
Now, there's a drop.
Land
is the current situation.
Hahaha, it's
coming blue.  Wow, it's
already the 3rd week of high school. I'm
going to see how much difference there is. There's
still a lot to be said for window chocolate.
Even if I haven't taken it yet.
If you don't do it differently, you'll be in the suburbs after chocolate, and you
won't be able to get to the bank. You can
take the item from the other person and it's okay.
After making it, go back and talk to the robot.
Well, at
least bring it back.
[Music]
Hey,
it's all over the place. There were two of them right now.
ua
arthur and day moon.
Choco is the most powerful. Even though he was Thunder, he's
like that. He's so good.
Choco,
Choco, he won't give up.
The end is like this. We'll
reach the goal. There's no demons. There's nothing in
favor of support. There's nothing wrong with that.  It's
good that there's a
final raise,
but the
final is dangerous.
5th goal tie place 5
[Applause]
takanome
ran 4 horror eggs Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
If you think it's not there or not, then everyone
will see it, but
if everyone can see it, then it's still okay.We can go as far as we can.There's still a
long time to go for both chocolate and chocolate.It's
not because there's no one yet, so don't buy it.
Gay, gay,
hanano Melon Melon
has come in and I'm being chased. Hey, wait a minute, I can
wait.
Say it's now, and
challenge me with a nice sticky bottom.
It's finally here, I'm here, I'm remembering Hiroko, a I'm still
going, I'm still going, I'm going to go, I'm
not a girl at your company. Before the training day, I was a
child of sunlight filtering through the leaves.
Even now, I'm still here.
No, everyone's like, oh, I'm not going on a trip
.  6th place 6th place 6th here This is
green tea for humans I
haven't heard that version there is no path a
No no no 0
I'm here
[Music]
Bunsei Koko Iki
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Well,
Tanaka, let's just
say, we're still at the bottom in March. We can
go, we can
go. Hey, it's good now, it's good, we're on our way. Iyo is on his way, it's finally hotbed girl. I do
n't like it when the caster restarts instead of a reunion.
This is
it.  There's still one of the times here, hmm,
no, I don't like it, put down the chocolate. The
Washer Scrivener is delicious.
Here we are in an unconstitutional state, and yesterday was also the American version.
As expected, yeah yeah
yeah ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Aaaah, the
tree has fallen, aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaahah
[Music] The
part cutter that ran away
Well, baaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Thank you very much for your support for the third year in a row this year as
well. See you all
at the awards ceremony. Next
year, I
hope you won't be a small fry.  I'd
like to do it.
Well, I tried my best. I won't be able to win the
seat of Dumber One. Ah,
akuru.
Everyone said Takko couldn't win.
To my mother, I
ask for your support even at home. That's aaah. Thank you for
your hard work.
Weather
Forty Shogo  Thank you for spreading the bridge!