hey had some nice Tunes coming from this
way that you Iris oh yeah I was just
practicing some singing really trying to
get that mermaid training going for the
summer how you figure that mermaids are
supposed to be excellent singers I was
reading a magazine about it a moment ago
and realized I'm totally posing like a
mermaid so why not sing a few songs as
well hm good point mind if I cut in for
a little bit of a sing song sure why not
we can make it a
duet W hey there little guy how'd you
get over here hey Eno what you got in
your hand there a little taco found his
way up the shore actually it looks like
he brought some friends wait a minute
minute don't to you don't think
something's drawing all the sea
creatures to the beach do you I think I
have quite possibly the best idea I've
had all summer a business proposition
something wrong Kiara yeah everything
all good over there oh everything's fine
over here no need to stop singing or
anything you tour are sounding great
idle training maybe we should join in
too wait but bear here probably to make
sure we don't work too hard on our
vacation you'll cut us a little stck if
you want to do a little work
right this St are going to be rolling in
the girls and their siren songs are
going to make us rich and then we can
all go on vacation together but Kiara
we're already on vacation it's not the
same
you'll help me set up the booth right
we're supposed to put you to work after
all
so that's the spirit shall we get
started
then hey I think the wildlife really
likes our singing Iris a I wanted to be
a mermaid this summer not a siren maybe
we should stop I will make you both all
you can eat tuu Yaki if you keep singing
oh okay in that case let the show go
on pass a seafood but I could definitely
go for another round of songs if you all
are
Keen ladies and gentlemen beach goers of
all ages KB's very first tacoyaki branch
is now open for business
[Music]
wow wonder where she got the ingredients
so fast hey you did you help her or
something I tried to stop her I really
did H it's suspicious isn't it nothing
better than the sight of happy beacho
customers on a hot summer day am I right
girls oh Kiara where's my promised Taco
Yaki coming right
J hey guys who what on Earth is
that is that a giant octopus are you
grab my sword will you we've got to
defend this beach sheesh wonder what
could possibly be making that thing so
mad Hey where's Ena look up there that
raging giant octopus has are in its
clutches don't worry about me guys it's
really okay it's actually kind of fun
being waved around like this hey you
you're going to help us save Ena right
yes that's my blade all right we'll
handle this from here hey guys wait a
minute I can help too and then we are
totally chopping up that thing and
making more tacky for the
mass all right you savage Beast how
about you
I've got customers to feed take
this I'll go grab Ena while it's
distracted come with I'll need all the
help I can
get we can't take much more of this
better make it quick you too I can do
this all day I am feeling a little Buzzy
so maybe you guys can get me down a
little sooner
[Music]
hey tacu maybe that's enough play for
today h what's that your friend got
turned into takoyaki so you're taking
Revenge
uh-oh what that's horrible aw I'm really
sorry to hear that Mr Taco we'll find
the culprit and make them pay just
please put our run
down yay the battle has been won now if
you'll excuse me I've got to go clean
something up really quickly
Kiara you're acting awfully
sus sus me what are you accusing me of
it was it was just good business
[Music]