[Music]
hmm
my
[Music]
me
do
[Music]
oopsie
ticket
i'm back
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you for the
warm welcome already oh my god it seems
like it's been
an eternity
since the last time i streamed
yeah
did you miss me
let's turn on some btm moon
[Music]
i'm home
i mean i wasn't gone that long wasn't
even the full week was almost a full
week my last stream was saturday
last week
um
and i still provided you guys with some
videos here and there
uh like i always do because
um first and foremost because
of the youtube algorithm
[Laughter]
but yeah
it gives me a nice
uh reason to an opportunity to
get some cool stuff done
uh so i hope you enjoyed the videos
especially the
uh the one from cup z the dead cup set
it was really cool i think um
uh i i always wanted to
like ask cop zed to do something
together with me
it was always an idea and uh actually
like a while ago i was like yo
uh
are you like available like when i need
something for like
vacations and stuff
and they were like yeah let's do it and
i was like yo actually now now i'm going
on a skiing vacation so
let's make something
and actually um
uh
no you know what i'll i'll keep some of
this talk for
my pokemon stream or whatever for the
rest of the week there won't be a
schedule but i think i'm gonna play
pokemon either tomorrow the day after
tomorrow
we'll see
uh today i'll tell you about my trip
[Music]
but
to be honest i mean
it was a scheme trip so it's not like
there are
there's so many ver
it's not like there's a huge variety of
things that i did
um and this time um i'm not gonna show
too many pictures either
uh
yeah but i write up some pictures and
a video or two
um but i just i i want to talk about my
experience today so as you know i went
skiing
[Music]
you'll find out you'll find out whether
or not i died or not the fact that i'm
here does not prove anything
because i'm a phoenix and i can revive
so even if i did die uh it's no surprise
that i'm still here
she always comes back she always comes
back oh yeah by the way
sorry for the membership scare please
everybody who thinks they have a
membership but looks at their account
now and doesn't see it
maybe check it out it should all be
automatically
reactivated but
uh
yeah whole life is now uh
something called uh
mcn i think that stands for
multi-channel network i think
something on youtube and thankfully it
happened when
i was gone so the the
membership disappearance
was not really an issue for us
uh but yeah
yeah yeah this is another good reason
why you guys should be on twitter
because like stuff like this
usually always
you only really get notified by it if
you
if you're on twitter so
yeah you got your emotes back
congratulations oh yeah i wanted to say
uh
uh before we get started
uh this cute
uh
wait
[Music]
uh
wait
wait cho
oh yeah this cute
scarf and cape
uh i had to put something on because i
felt like um
i'm still in the winter mood so i got
some free assets from someone called
burial
b-e-r-y-l
they make a lot of beta acids so just so
you know
thank you free assets let's go
good stuff looks so cozy love that scarf
i love scarves i love scarves
just today i bought a scarf
i found a new skype i have a lot of
scarves
[Music]
ho ho ho ho ho
willing chill to be honest um no
but uh winter clothing is so cozy i love
it
winter
although my favorite is um i think
not winter because then you have to like
depending on where you live but where i
live you have to get get so
many layers down you can't really it's
kind of tough to
look properly cute but if it's if it's
autumn then you don't need so many
layers but still you can totally be
fashionable and cute
while looking cozy as [\h__\h] with like a i
don't know a poncho or cute coat and
scarf and boots cute bootsies and and
and tights
wool tights and and a nice
thick
skirt stuff like that and a turtleneck
scarf
yes yes yes
sorry i love i i l-o-v-e
uh winter fashion
usual
can i can i dress you guys up i want to
put you i want to take you guys shopping
can can may i take my little chimpkins
out shopping
can i be your mommy for the day
[Music]
although to be honest i don't know [\h__\h]
about um
men's fashion
you guys don't really have that much
choice still yeah although
i mean
some people still manage to look super
fashionable
i respect that
shopping at the bus
that's so weird
um
[Music]
that was akb48 a really old song from
akb48
i'd wear polka dots for denja ah
gnarly
i haven't worn polka dots for a long
time though
i'm more of a uh what's it called
uh a type uh who likes uh what's it
called what's it called what's that
pattern called
called play yeah i like planes played
i like played a lot and that um
that
thousand bird pattern
you know what i mean it doesn't look
like a bird but i found out it's called
like i found it out not recently but i
know it's called like a thousand bird
pattern or something like that um
pounds tooth
oh is it only called that in japanese i
think it's something like sentori or or
something
let me look at a cheetah
pattern in japanese
what what what wolf tooth
houndstooth
hounds is that the same thing
it is
pounds two dogs
so to japanese people it looks like
burbs and to
uh
to
english-speaking people it looks like a
dog's
tooth
that's interesting ah thank you
[Music]
i'm sure that hanami would dress up
really cutely for me
[Music]
of course i've seen the new cow carrot
video i watched it
on my way home
with some good content to watch while i
was bored uh in the train
all right let's let me start let me
start my story i suppose um we're gonna
i'm gonna tell you about the story and
then afterwards we're gonna just gonna
do a chill super chat reading because i
don't want to fall behind right away
[Music]
yes
guys guys guys i've just arrived
i've just arrived
oh
so why do i even start uh i have a memo
okay
okay so
actually
um
you know how my my last trip was with
bff and bff can drive
bff can drive and bff has a
has a license and to the last vacation
we we drove did i tell you that
um i think i did but unfortunately for
this trip
none of us had a driving license or a
car
um
uh
yeah
why is my chat
broken let me refresh there you go
um
because i went with a different person
last night was bff and this time is rmt
the girl that i used to live together
with um especially before
going to japan and then for a little
while after coming back from japan is uh
when i lived with rmt we still call her
rmt even though we're not roommates them
anymore but
yeah yeah and we're very close and this
was actually our first trip she was the
one who went to
uh
uh greece with me
again
[Music]
however we both don't have a driving
license uh
and that was um
because of the amount of
stuff that we had to carry both of us
was
pretty uh
unfortunate
if at least one of us had a license but
not a car then we could have rented a
car but nope and we do not so
yeah yeah and both of us
uh
have our own ski equipment because i
bought ski equipment my own stuff like
all of it i bought the clothes i bought
the skis i bought the shoes everything
beforehand because i didn't want to rent
uh
it this time i wanted to have my own
staff so that it would also maybe
motivate me to go
skiing um more often
from then on yeah yeah
[Music]
hello
what's happening here
come back
and there it is are you back
[Music]
good job
ah welcome back
okay
so yeah uh we had a lot of oh my god so
much so much stuff uh i had a i had a
suitcase a tiny suitcase
um a tiny one yeah but like i had to
take a suitcase with me because i had to
bring some clothes
i missed the
message
what happened where did she go she got
like eaten up by my chat refreshing
what did she say
like late over there
ain't it i guess not that
[Music]
then you're next
next trip is with you
yo
i'm already excited
i i
i was like oh when i was on my way to
this trip i was like [\h__\h] why did i
choose a winter vacation i should have
gone to some beach paradise but oh well
uh that's next
let's go
yeah no i want to go to bali one day but
arena recently just went to bali so it
wouldn't make sense to bring her to bali
with me
i don't think i don't think it makes
sense uh so we're gonna go somewhere
else somewhere where it's i think the
first time for both of us
and we're still still in very early
stages of discussion but we're going to
make it happen arena right
yeah yeah a place that i always wanted
to go to i mean we can still change the
destination but at the moment i i have
an idea
hello verification yeah i'm gonna see
i'm gonna see reina for the first time
it's kind of like
kind of um
[Music]
it could end up being really awkward but
i i think we're both social
uh cute people uh we can we can make it
work but it's the first time we're gonna
meet and immediately be like together um
uh in a room for several nights so
yeah oh oh always wonder how that's
gonna work out but i'm sure
i'm sure
i'm sure we're gonna get along
[Laughter]
if not then uh some it's gonna be so
warm anyway that someone can probably
sleep on the balcony
i i i uh i can sleep on the couch
we can move the couch to the balcony or
so
anyway
that's for another time
um
ah answer another time
okay so we
was just getting my story started
[Music]
time to do our social link homework
before then
i'm already socially linked aren't we
now until now i feel like we always got
along well i mean it's always different
in rl as well i think but i think i
think being together in rl actually
makes some things
easier but
yeah we will see we'll see
oh is that a persona reference oh for
[\h__\h] sake i didn't get it
[\h__\h]
even
is coming at me with some references
that i don't understand man
man i only chat but now dana
i don't even understand
my
my kohl highs anymore
young people these days
goddammit young people and old people i
don't understand anyone it's like i
don't belong to any generation
damn it i need to play persona i guess
so
i i will do my persona homework
eventually
okay
okay so yeah yeah yeah yeah
uh
let's let's look at my
in my list okay so we have to go by
train and actually
um
uh
rmt
didn't uh
do the whole train ride with me i
actually had to get into the train on my
own but thankfully
uh
i had someone to help me carry my [\h__\h]
at least to the train
so it wasn't that bad actually it was
not that bad at all i did i had so much
stuff to carry but it ended up not being
that bad because like she helped me
carry it inside the train
um and then
that that was that was the girl who took
care of my kitty cats
so she helped me put it in the train and
train was pretty empty and that no
actually no the train was pretty busy
but i had a reserved seat so i chilled
in the train and i waited for
uh
rmt
and oh yeah i actually i got up really
early for this i took melatonin in the
night before
what free letter name will you give her
oh because bff rmt and
[Music]
i'll have to think about that one that's
that's a tough one
i haven't
ridden the train written in such a long
time
uh
damn
ah man
i think it worked well
um
cat caretaker
now i'll think about it
is that correct okay
i haven't ridden the train in a long
time especially not long distance like i
mean it wasn't that long distance it was
a it was a decent distance let's say
um but
normally recently i've always traveled
by airplane right and and and car
so
it's nice it was nice being on the train
again uh if only if only trains weren't
[\h__\h] expensive
um
[Music]
would not be applicable to that anyway
holy [\h__\h]
holy [\h__\h] train was nice though i saw
some nice sceneries
and
uh i think i played some pokemon uh
and yeah
yeah train more price in the airplane
yeah yeah more expensive here
oh i don't know if it's like this
everywhere but
um i can
uh
i can be fast i can do some worse faster
and cheaper than
if i go by airplane then if i go by
train
so anyway
[Music]
yeah so we arrived
in this
place
uh
we arrived somewhere where people go
skiing a
skiing area we have many of those in
austria austria has so many mountains
uh i don't know if you know about it but
austria is pretty famous for its
mountains a lot of people
in europe come to austria for skiing
vacations
[Music]
yeah we have alps of course uh and we
have a [\h__\h] ton of mountains that are
beautiful
too and really nice to
ski in yeah and and austrians like
of course everyone knows how to ski or
snowboard uh
it's like our national sport but it
legit is because like austria is like
we're so [\h__\h] at any
type of sports except for uh winter
sports you may have seen i've noticed
this on the side during my vacation that
an austrian has won the gold medal
in skiing once again during the winter
olympics that apparently happened while
i was gone
just once again the proof that we were
born for this we austrians
[Music]
so i saw
the winter olympics yeah was that fake
snow
huh
was that fake snow
i won't have that like because like if
the austrians train on real snow it's
like
skiing on fake snow it must feel
different
i'm sure i'm sure it must kind of feel
different apparently it was fake snow
i mean it makes sense if
if it's held in the country at a time
where there would be no snow it just
makes sense but
[Music]
real fake snow
your vacations are just to cover so you
can participate yes
[Music]
wait i wanna i don't wanna participate
as a skier though you know i wanna be a
torch i wanna be the torch the olympic
torch man
[Music]
so
yeah we arrived and we thankfully from
the
um directly from the station where we
got off
we got picked up by the by a hotel
shuttle
thankfully hallelujah and so the only
thing i really only had to carry it like
a few meters my stuff so
it's not that bad if we didn't have like
a shuttle and if i didn't have someone
help me bring it to the train station
then
would have been tough stream legs really
stream lagging
you meant to torch barrow the litch
maybe i can be both
good question i think originally i
wanted to be the torch bearer
uh noodle i'm it's not only about norms
it's really [\h__\h] tough to carry like
it's not about not that much about
strength but it's just so much to carry
like that huge the huge skis
and the the shoes are [\h__\h] huge too
and they have to be in this bag too
and then the
your own clothes in the suitcase and
stuff it's it is a lot of stuff
you're a you're up lagging what the hell
i'm literally streaming in europe
no
why
i did get a weird message from youtube
uh when i started streaming not about
the connection but about something
else so i'm a bit confused
[Music]
oh well i hope i hope it's gonna
get fixed if it's not lagging somewhere
else then maybe try a vpn i suppose
if that really helps that's so weird so
weird when it only lags in certain areas
is that because of youtube's server or
is that because of me because if it's
only in certain areas then it can't be
because of me can't it
if it's only in certain continents
[Music]
it must be our service
okay
i'm sorry about that i'm sorry i hope
you can still kind of listen
oh
[Music]
anyway okay continuing so we got picked
up and then uh we checked in and that
was something that happened on sunday
that's why i didn't stream on sunday uh
but um when you go skiing usually i mean
there are some
places where you can do night skiing but
usually the right time to ski is you
know
uh around
in in the in the late morning and then
until like the afternoon
so
yeah you should go skiing when the sun
is still out normally
so we we arrived like in the early
evening i think or i'm not sure anymore
uh and then um
we
basically we just unpacked a little bit
and
then i think we went directly for dinner
no
yes
no yes yes we went i think directly for
dinner
or you might have gone to
uh chill a little bit in the spa first
i'm not sure anymore my my brain is slow
i'm gonna show you a little bit of the
food that we had this time i'm not gonna
show any pictures of
the hotel
uh but i'm gonna show you pictures of
food
look at this
[Music]
oh that's [\h__\h] big
this was a starter
gohan gohan
gohan none of this is ice cream
actually so the green thing was like uh
actually it was kind of ice cream but it
was like a pesto like a chilled cool
cold pesto like frozen pesto really good
like it was like gelato
um and you would eat that with the
tomato and the mozzarella the one the
right stuff on the left side is
mozzarella it was such good mozzarella
mmm
yeah it was pester no spinach no no no
no
i was oh man that mozzarella
might have been the best mozzarella i've
ever eaten
that was a starter and then we had
um oh
surprisingly
i went for the for the main course i
went for the
i went for the
fish
choice
and honestly
no regret it was it was salmon
with a risotto underneath and
i don't
the green foam was something
fancy tasting i don't remember any i
don't remember what any of this tasted
like anymore but it was really good it
was really good
it was really good
the salmon was so
soft mmm
yeah no that was not pesto though i
forgot
the risotto was
perfect too
that was the main course in between
there was a soup but i didn't i i
declined the soup because i didn't like
it
didn't like the ingredients
ah that's the main is yes it was pretty
big it might look a little bit small but
that's because the the plate was huge
it was was pretty pink
and then all the dessert killed me on
that day the dessert [\h__\h] killed me
oh it was so good
that was
um
a chocolate
cake no it was not liquid inside but it
was kind of fudgy
um and
on the top we have cinnamon ice cream
and plums
i think that was those were plums
oh so good
[Music]
oh my god but that i think this was
this was this this might have been this
or or another day it was when i was like
i'm so full i'm so full
i feel like i need to lay an egg
i didn't though i did not like an egg
though
but
i ate so much man because they also they
had like
a lot of salad we had a lot of salad
the salad was so good too i didn't have
a photo of that though
yeah so anyway the first dinner was
actually the best one the other ones um
i have some photos
uh i didn't i don't i didn't prepare a
photo for everything um because you know
food is food
[Music]
but yeah this was the best one
uh the best dinner we had uh yeah
so
we got we went to sleep actually pretty
early i was able to sleep so early like
before midnight every day
actually pretty naturally like i was
watching arrested development a few epis
one or two or three episodes before
sleeping on my ipad and then i would uh
sleep pretty early and then we would we
would always wake up like uh like around
eight or something and go to the
breakfast breakfast was yummy i had
pancakes every morning
pancakes every morning oh yeah oh yeah
and for for the first dinner that's when
suddenly
they were sometimes playing some weird
songs but they suddenly played that
um
what was that what was that song again
the one of the saxophone i think i read
about it on twitter
but i forgot it's that sexy time song
they played some yeah careless whisper
they played some weird songs during
dinner i don't know if they realized how
how
memeable their song choices where
[Music]
um
oh and also they had like some really
good uh
non-alcoholic cocktails every day for me
really really yummy
so i really enjoyed those
there was a large large variety of
non-alcoholic drinks for me
yeah
okay so
this is where it starts the the first
morning
we we kind of knew ahead of time but the
first morning's weather was
the first day's weather was terrible for
skiing actually it became better and
better after each day
but yeah monday was
terrible for skiing
[Music]
which is why at breakfast you know i was
already like really really nervous that
i kept on saying rmt i don't
i'm too nervous i can't i can't i'm like
i'm like so scared to go skiing rmt
please uh
and then i mean we looked outside at
breakfast during during the breakfast we
looked outside the window and it scared
me even more because i saw the [\h__\h]
storm outside
it was
um snowing really heavily
uh it was really cloudy
um
you you could barely see [\h__\h] and the
wind was really really strong
but rmt was like you're gonna be fine
yeah you're gonna be fine we're gonna
make it don't worry
and then
it happens
we put on all our stuff all our skiing
stuff
and i'm still like the whole time in my
mind i'm like [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] i'm so scared
i'm so scared
and then and then we're ready to go
the moment we're putting on our ski
shoes
we're being told
that
due to the
bad weather
all of the
all of the skis uh
thingies are closed
the one that bring you up to the
the ski lifts don't want to bring you up
to the mountains
they were all closed
because of the weather
[Music]
my heart out
inside my mind i was like
[Music]
the gondolas they were all closed i was
like
[Music]
thank you i looked
it up
but honestly it really looked dangerous
and for some for an amateur like me i
was really worried about my safety so
yeah i felt like it was faint um
but
then we were told that
um in within like uh like not a big
distance can quickly get there there is
a there's a an easy simple slope
just one
one slope that's really not not nothing
exciting
um
blue blue slope
blue as and there's like colors that
say how difficult the slopes are blue is
the easiest kind of but then there's
like practice slopes that are even
flatter than that but anyway so yeah
there was one where it was not a gondola
but something where you like you you put
like something like a chair in between
your legs and it will it will like pull
you pull you to the top of the hill
[Music]
so we were like yeah well we're already
dressed and this is probably better
anyway to start somewhere simple for me
it's like a warm-up
so
yeah drag lift
so we went
there
um and i was already exhausted
on the way there because i had to walk
with that with those [\h__\h] shoes it
hurts so much because you can't really
like bend your knees much like your your
your legs and and then having to carry
those skis for [\h__\h] sake was so
exhausting and we kind of had to walk
like up the hill a lot
waddle waddle waddle wabble
exhausting oh my god so i we arrived
there and we got a little ticket and i
looked at it and i was like
well it's [\h__\h] stormy but
it looks like a manageable
hill i
suppose um
so um
we
huh
we then got ourselves dragged up
up the hill
and i was standing up there and there
were by the way there were quite a lot
of people skiing there anyway even
though the weather was really bad
there were still a lot of people there
especially a lot of children that came
like with their school's teacher like
they had ski in class or whatever
but now here it is i have a photo
it doesn't really look steep
and probably i mean it wasn't really
steep
but
it was
a little bit a little bit it just
unfolds it never looks that steep
um but it also makes you maybe see how
the weather was a little bit
okay yeah i mean it's all white so you
can't really see how steep it is
but look at this um
this one's at
slope um
you don't see the wind but the wind was
really strong
and the snow was really [\h__\h] strong
too part there were some moments where
the wind was like so strong it was
pushing me
and and yeah it was it was really really
bad you can't see the the back because
it was so
so cloudy um
[Music]
but
it was it was okay you know the
[Music]
the
the this hill i'm not even calling it a
mountain because it's like um very close
to the
to the what do you call it
uh the
valley i don't know
it looks so steepy right over are you
joking it doesn't it doesn't look steep
on the picture it was it was a little
bit steep though
um
but then so i was standing there
and i was
i was looking down there and i was i was
i was i was like
getting [\h__\h] ptsd
from my
[Music]
um
so
it didn't even look that bad but i just
i just couldn't get myself to just
go
i would i had had a trauma like for real
like i was so scared
i could just not go down there and the
kids kept on like going in front of me
and going down like swoosh and then they
get back
kept coming back up and they went down
again and swoosh and all that
and i couldn't i just couldn't i
couldn't i couldn't i just couldn't i
just couldn't bring myself to go down
there and and
[Music]
it was really bad and the weather didn't
make it any better because the weather
made it so scary you guys don't have any
idea i was like
the wind was like
for real i was so scared
i was
so scared
i wanted
[Music]
i was terrified
i had ptsd i i made up a word probably
not the first one to make it but
in in german
we uh phobia is for b
and it rhymes with sheep
which is ski we say she to ski we say
she
so i said i have a she for bee
yeah a phobia of skiing
i was really scared
[Music]
no really though so
um together with together with rmt i was
like apologizing a lot to her because
she's a really good skier she goes
skiing like every year several times
she's a pro
she goes to really difficult uh
difficult slopes but i was like i'm so
sorry you have to deal with this [\h__\h]
but she's she was like yeah well it's
okay i knew and then it's not like i can
go to any other slopes anyways it's the
only one that's open
[Music]
but we were standing up there together
for like 20 minutes
and i i
i couldn't bring myself to do it so she
was like yo should i maybe like go down
and ask if they have a private skiing
teacher like
um
like just anytime soon today and i was
like yeah
yeah i guess ask i guess i suppose so
she went down there and she didn't
it took quite a long time she didn't
come back for a while so i was like up
here
for like 40 minutes just standing there
having uh the kids the groups of kids
going up and down and up and down and up
and down and i was just standing there
40 minutes all alone
just couldn't make it down and then
eventually
she called me and she was like yo they
have a teacher
um
you want to do it it's like uh
it was pretty expensive like 145
or 50
uh
euro for two hours
um but it's like a private lesson and it
would be on an on a practice slope
somewhere like close by
um but it's for beginners and and i was
like okay but when and then it was like
in in two hours
or one and a half hours or so from from
now and i was like okay i mean sure but
like how the [\h__\h] am i gonna get down
here though
because the
the the dragging thingies they don't
bring you down they only take you up and
and there was like no way to get down
besides skiing unless you walk but it's
pretty far walking and and pretty steep
walking as well
um
so
um she i'm like okay well for now i
guess come back up
and we'll think about how to get down
let's tell them yeah we're taking the
lesson
um so she comes she comes back up
and
we're talking a little bit about how to
get me down because i'm just so scared i
cannot go down
no way
i just completely forgot the basics that
i learned when i was a child and okay
for everybody who doesn't know in my
whole life i went skiing two times
before this when i was a child with
school because like every school in
austria goes on a skiing trip eventually
uh and i learned it really fast back
then
i was actually like pretty good uh just
in in one week i was pretty good
um
and then the second time was years later
centuries later
uh with cali when we went to hokkaido
that was one year ago and i had an
accident there
um
that gave me [\h__\h] ptsd like so bad
like it really was bad i thought i was
gonna die
so then
she comes back up and we talk a little
bit and i'm like i can't i can't i can't
i can't
and then it happens
you know what happens
suddenly
a different ski teacher
comes up to me a really old guy he comes
up to us and he's like are you good you
okay
you you're scared and i'm like yeah [\h__\h]
you scared
and it's like a really old dude
he told us later he's uh 85 years old or
something like that 85 years old but
uh it was obvious that he he was like a
really good skier he told us like oh
i'm gonna help you it's okay i will
teach you you can learn it immediately
no don't worry about it
um
so
he like uh tells tells me that he's a
he's a teacher skate teacher and he's
been professionally skiing his whole
life
and he goes skating every day he looks
really fit yeah
and and he said that normally he
wouldn't be here but you know all the
other slopes are closed and he always
finds someone that's like uh terrified
and he then helps them he's like a
[\h__\h] angel like a hero comes out of
nowhere and then saves the the terrified
ptsd children
yeah
so the thing though like he he wanted to
see like what i can do but i was so
terrified i couldn't even go like a
meter down
no
so he
he was like
he held me like he
he had he there's this like teaching
stance
um
uh like you
i was like kind of next to him and he he
uh took my my my skiing sticks and i
would hold on to them and then like
there were several stances but like
sometimes he was like uh pulling me from
behind
uh
so that i would not go too far like he
was kind of controlling me
and my movement
yeah yeah that's how you teach teach
children from zero how to
how to ski
and i successfully
um
made it all the way down with his help
and uh it was terrifying anyway i was i
was uh
yelling anyway i was like
but by the body um
by by the time we made it down uh he
offered us that he would teach me for
full hour but i would only have to pay
like half the price so that was really
cool really cheap but i was like [\h__\h] if
if i had if we met this guy like a few
minutes earlier before the phone call
then i wouldn't have to organize that
other
teaching skiing teacher lesson thingy
so
on that day i had two different teachers
and two different lessons
so this dude it was actually
we had like an hour time so it was
actually kind of perfect to fill the
time
and yeah he started teaching me basics
and the first thing he did was
uh change my skis he suddenly was like
get out of your skis they're too long
for you too [\h__\h] long unbelievable
you can't ski in those and i'm like what
but i bought those they're super new and
super cute and and and the guy at the
store he was like yo those are okay for
you
and he was like no you're gonna you're
gonna wear mine now and i'm like what
what
although his his skis were like i think
like five centimeters shorter than mine
um
but but like
height wise he was
i think maybe just like
two centimeters or three centimeters
smaller than me
but yeah he had different skins that
were a bit shorter and he told me that
um long skis you can only handle them if
you're a good skier
if you start off you need to start with
really tiny skis
and then go bigger and bigger so this
wasn't even ideal but five centimeters
shorter would at least help a little bit
he said so it was funny
he told me to get out of his skis and i
he helped me get out of them and then he
changed the size of his skis of the shoe
thingy and he got me into his skis
and then he taught me some basics and i
actually
picked it up really really quickly with
his help
i was able to go down this hill
super
easily
in like 10 minutes
i
[Music]
the ones that i bought were like i think
150 centimeters
um
and his were like 145
so
10 minutes but not
no it doesn't take me 10 minutes to go
down i mean it took me 10 minutes to
like get back into it
yeah yeah yeah yeah it was so so helpful
but
he had a very intense
and
somewhat aggressive way of teaching like
he was super funny he kept on babbling
about random things in between like his
his wife
uh and and uh like how he picks up all
these uh people who look terrified and
he teaches them
he told us so many random stories in
between it was really funny um but he
was like all the time was yelling at me
like
[Music]
yeah i felt like i was in the military
but it was not like it was not like um
evil it was still very
helpful and kind but
he also praised me a lot though that i
was picking it up so quickly and then
i'm doing great yeah yeah
[Music]
of course he was teaching in german of
course
we speak german in austria um
yeah it was like a crash course yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah very much so
i'm so thankful to him like he was
amazing uh by the end of that i was like
yo
we could kind of cancel the other lesson
because like now i'm
i'm fine i'm kind of fine
yeah rmt was also like yo
you don't
you're fine now you're good now
so actually i have a video of him for
you guys
um he kept on telling us jokes and uh he
was like singing for us and and i asked
yo if you can't do all these things can
you like maybe also yodel
because i thought you guys would love to
see someone yodel someone austrian and
he was like of course i can yodel so he
yodeled for me you guys wanna hear him
yoda
you guys wanna hear him yodo
yes
i blurred the video though um
so that you don't see his face he said
that he's fine with being on youtube and
stuff though uh but just you know
just because i i blurred it uh wait if i
put it into obs now it might be a bit
loud in the beginning i'm going to turn
it down immediately uh no wait what if i
do it like
let's show it
okay okay that should not play um
[\h__\h]
ah it will it will probably be loud
at first
i'll immediately turn it down okay okay
okay
where is it huh i didn't see it
where the [\h__\h] was the audio
wait a second wait a second did you hear
something
i didn't hear anything
[Music]
did you hear that
but i wanna hear it too
i wanna hear it
too foreign
[Music]
oops oh well yeah he said um he said
that like oh man he had so many stories
he told me that like his uh
uh
he he uh did this professionally before
but then he also goes around singing uh
professionally
and uh
uh
yeah now he gives some private lessons
now and then and also his his wife got
sick at some point um so he had to make
more money uh so that's why he started
all the skiing lessons and all that uh
yeah and and because his wife got sick
he also changed like his diet so
uh
he actually
he he at one point he pulled out
something out of his uh jacket like a
bottle a reused plastic bottle where
obviously uh something else was inside
before like a like a cocktail sauce or
something like that um but what was
inside was like a green mix of of
something looked like a smoothie and i
was like what what is that and he starts
drinking it like like out of a baby
bottle
and he says it's uh oh is his it's his
lunch or so or his breakfast uh he uh
he every day he only eats raw vegetables
made into a smoothie like that
uh no he doesn't cook anything he only
eats raw
uh vegetables and fruit and all that
only raw because that makes him so
healthy
he said i gotta throw away my cooking
pot because uh cooking food is unhealthy
like i don't know
if there's anything legit about what he
said but he's 85 and he's super [\h__\h]
healthy and he looked like he was gonna
live until he's [\h__\h] 150 so i mean
somehow he it must be true somehow some
some part of that must be true
he's so healthy he goes skiing every day
he's so fit something must be true about
that
yeah
i mean i mean the reason why he why he
makes it into his movie is probably
because of his teeth
uh but yeah uh
i think i think at some point you just
can't eat solid food anymore but still
holy [\h__\h] man it was so healthy it's so
funny
but then
um after an hour i was like okay okay
okay thank you thank you thank you and
we paid him and he he gave us his uh
phone number and said like you'll call
me anytime and i'll give you more
lessons and i was like yo okay i think
i'll be fine though because i have
another lesson after this
uh and he was like okay okay but for now
you'll find also get different skis
because yours are way too long just just
make sure that you get different skis
um
and
actually that
that kind of disappoints me because like
yo i spent a lot of money to get my own
skiing equipment and then it turns out
that it's just not made for me people at
the store at those kind of stores they
they don't really
you would think they know their stuff
but they don't really know their stuff
they will sell you
anything
and say oh this will be fine but don't
trust them guys if you're ever gonna buy
your own skis
and you don't you're not a good skier
yet then you need to get really really
small ones ridiculously small ones
yeah
it's pretty disappointing but my plan is
to
uh
i guess get good so that one day i can
actually use my big ass skis
i just gotta get good uh so that it fits
and until then i will have to
rent smaller ones again
[Music]
so after this we went to a different
slope that was
way flatter than this it was like
ridiculous it was ridiculously flat and
but
on the way to that we
felt like i had to climb the [\h__\h]
mountain
we had to walk up a
[\h__\h] mountain
with our um ski shoes and our skis in
order to reach destination so we were
kind of late but we eventually arrived
and and oh my god
everybody thinks i'm [\h__\h] 13 or 14.
the the old dude that we met here the
teacher he thought i was a child and uh
the lady at the
at the counter where we got our tickets
for the actual
lesson for the next skiing lesson she
was she thought that rmt was my mom
she thought rmt was my mom
[Music]
and apparently was really shocked when
she found out i'm an eternal phoenix and
actually i'm old
[Laughter]
she was shook
i was i wasn't there at the time but rmt
told me that she had a freaking mental
breakdown about about the fact that i'm
not 13 years old
the thing is like she didn't even see
any of my face like i had a i had my
mask on and i was covered in the skiing
attire the only thing she saw was my
eyes
[Music]
and i'm not that small
not that small
well apparently i have this kind of baby
aura
about myself
i don't want to tell you
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] man
i think it's partially also when i don't
put on makeup i look a lot a lot younger
apparently which i don't get but okay
[Music]
aura yeah
uh yeah i guess i'm one year old
[Music]
well i will so we got up there and then
the moment i saw the ski teacher i was
like yo just so you know i'm not 13 okay
i'm not 13.
i'm probably older than you i i say
and yes he was he was he was much
younger than me
he was uh like five years younger than
me
not gonna say how much but you know
so then
um
uh we we started our lesson but it was
two hours and i learned much less than i
learned in the one hour with the other
teacher um that was a big difference in
teaching style there it was
[\h__\h] boring um
not only the slope but the teaching
style was really boring um
it was pretty bad not really worth it
and the thing is the weather got worse
and worse and worse and worse
um from the moment i arrived at that
slope
even though it was extremely flat it was
kind of difficult to ski anyway um
because i it got so white that i
couldn't see [\h__\h] like i legit couldn't
see [\h__\h] and i really started freezing
even though
even though the skiing attire was pretty
strong against wind and cold and all
that i ended up freezing
because of the wind it was so strong
yeah
i was i i was
um
i'll tell you something that the the old
teacher guys we have to give him a name
um
let's call him
yo mr yojo so mr yodel
uh told me
that uh the other the other ski um
teachers they don't teach you properly
and fast on purpose because they want
you to take more lessons there
and he said he doesn't do that he
teaches properly he teaches fast
and that's why people also come back to
him
but but when you take a skiing lesson
without knowing that you think this is
normal
yeah but they they do it on purpose they
teach you very slowly and then they
don't really help you much
[Music]
so yeah i really noticed that honestly
that that other lesson the two hour
lesson for 150 euro was so useless
uh it was a waste of time like oh my god
i didn't learn much there
and the slope was boring as [\h__\h] too
it was like so flat that sometimes i had
to like
swim you know do swimming movements in
order to like i had to walk with my skis
literally
the price is apparently i think pretty
normal
um for skiing lessons the price is
pretty normal
but it's just like they don't teach you
much
so
um
after that i had enough i was freezing
and i mean it was the other slips
weren't open anyway and it was about
time to go back to the hotel so we went
back to the hotel and we warmed up we
were both freezing i ate some i ate some
kaiserschmann
kind sister mine is a dessert an
austrian
dessert
that looks like that
um it doesn't look special but it's so
good i love it i love it although my mom
makes a better one than this one
my mom i don't know if you're watching
but mommy makes a way better kaiser
smart than this one i expected greatness
but
uh nothing nothing compared to my
mommy's kaiserschmein it's base it's not
scrambled eggs it's
it's like a fluffy pancake a fluffy fake
pancake scrambles scrambled pancakes
basically and you eat it either with um
apple
mousse
apple mousse
which is what i had on this side um or
you eat it with vegeta
which
[Music]
plum stuff applesauce yeah applesauce or
or plums um
pieces of plums
sauce
i don't know what to call inspection
[Music]
mousse
plum jam no not a jelly it's um
um like uh it still has a lot of pieces
of the fruit in it but anyway yeah uh
really yummy dessert so i ate that and
and we warmed up in the hotel and then i
went uh
and i went into the sauna i actually
went to the sauna voluntarily several
times
uh during this trip because
uh i didn't feel so embarrassed because
there were no people there it was super
empty all the time
so i'm kind of getting into sauna um
recently thanks to that other trip i had
with bff i found a liking
in going into the sauna as long as no
one else is in
there
if i can get a private
uh room
then i enjoy it yeah
yeah yeah very healthy
so i know
[Music]
yo
if i ever buy a house i'm going to get a
sauna installed i already thought about
it
so and then i had a massage i had a
massage basically every day
um
i will keep the story for another time
but the massage person was kind of weird
the lady was kind of weird but okay
um it was still relaxing so i had a
massage and then we went to dinner
um
dinner was for example a [\h__\h] amazing
pumpkin soup with pumpkin seeds mmm i
love pumpkins
uh or another thing was i don't have all
the courses but this was a huge
um
[Music]
uh not deer the big male deer
elk maybe no not elk
something like elk
venison
do you
no not dear
elf
elk must be elk
elk
[\h__\h] buck
something like that
[Music]
whatever it is um a
thick steak of a huge
[Music]
and those were
pears at the bottom
um
piers that wear in wine
so i didn't like that much it tasted
very strongly like red wine
and some potatoes on the side this was
okay the potatoes tasted kind of boring
i was okay
and then for dessert we had like
nothing too special was just a
red velvet cake mm-hmm
that ended the first day kind of we
didn't really do
anything after dinner i think we just
kind of
uh
went into a room and i took a shower and
yeah we chilled uh in bed
watching i was watching our wrestler's
development again
[Music]
let me look at my notes
uh
[Music]
actually rmt was so underwhelmed by the
that slope that i was practicing it you
know the flat slope i was underwhelmed
too but she went in into a random house
and just drank mulled wine there
apparently
if you go to a place like this
pretty much every house
you can walk in randomly and they will
serve you mulled wine apparently mulled
wine and punch and all that
apparently it's a thing
yeah like every
no i mean they're not random houses they
they maybe look like random houses but
like there's like restaurants uh like
alpine huts not only on the mountains
but also down there and they all will
serve you something nice yeah so she
suddenly disappeared she's she said that
oh she just walked into this place and
had some mild wine
nice isn't it yeah
and and i realized oh
wait
i fought the time to get mulled wine and
punch was over when the christmas
markets were done after christmas but i
realized that after after christmas
season
these kind of places are the only places
where you still get those christmas
drinks yeah those alpena huts they have
they have uh all the christmas drinks
ah
you can still get them there
yeah it gives you gives you this winter
feeling
[Music]
then
second kind of second day
uh
i decided we decided i decided that i
have extremely sore muscles
and i don't
want to go skiing today even though the
weather was much better but i also kind
of wanted to give rmt the chance to
not you know hang out so much with me
but like go to more difficult slopes
and she
you know she looked up a route a route
with like black
uh color uh slopes
difficult slopes and she went on the
tour yeah
and i instead went
into the sauna and into a pool and i did
a swim and i did a hot sweat
and all that
i still i still had my workout though i
swim a little bit but i swam a little
bit but with the
with the sore muscles man
oh
my body was hurting like
[Music]
the massage must have been helpful not
really because i kept on building up the
sore muscles
so yeah um
and then uh
actually rmt came back pretty early
so
uh we chilled together alone uh at the
pool
because everybody else was like out
skiing i guess
uh and then we we had some lunch at like
lunch it was kind of late lunch but
still
and what did we do
we didn't really we didn't really do
that much on that day
uh
you know we didn't really do that much
[Music]
i guess i planned for the for the
following day
and
oh yeah i made an appointment with that
i made an appointment with the mr yodel
for the following day
i said okay
i will go up with you uh to the top of
the mountains together
but i'm still kind of nervous about the
slopes up there even though they're
supposedly blue i still don't trust them
i would like to get some help again so i
i hired mr yodel again for an hour
yeah uh he was spontaneously available
thankfully
master yoda no he's mr yodel uh so we
planned for the following day and i was
just mostly chilled and then i had i had
a full body peeling not a massage in the
evening that was really relaxing
really nice
and yeah
appealing body peeling never had that
before
[Music]
yeah hi it's movie
you look tired
what's up
what's
[Music]
the cats missed me
body peeling that's like a oh it's like
a scrub with a scrub and uh
some kind of you know
mixture
that they put on on your body and they
rub it in and then you you shower it off
so
uh oh yeah and then she put some hot
stones on my
in my hands and
on my back
uh
no wait that was that was on the on the
last day on the last massage day i think
yeah oopsie that was not not on the
peeling day but i i did that too it does
look like magical stones doesn't don't
they
they have some
looks like they have some rooms on it
like so
your back looks like a tub
now i took this photo when she left the
room
it's not my back it's just a towel
[Music]
obviously
uh
look
one second let me take a
cough drop apparently my throat
really isn't doing well uh in this room
[Music]
wow
but during the vacation i really didn't
talk much so yeah it was mostly just
like doing sporty things so
um
it was a good rest for my voice as well
i would say
anyway day free last day we got a late
check out
so that we didn't have to stress out um
we went skiing on the last day as well
we woke up we got breakfast but be uh
rmt she's also kind of a bff so
rmt said she wants to go with the first
shuttle she wants to go with the first
shuttle to be um
there early she wanted to
make use of the fresh
slopes
before they are messed up
by hundreds and hundreds of people
skiing and making the mess it was like
are you
really they have to get up so early is
it really worth it
but she said it was really really worth
it because uh when when they're freshly
prepared
it's like a completely different feeling
um
fresh slopes she was really really
really excited about that
so she woke up early i kind of did too i
wanted to sleep longer but i couldn't i
said i was gonna like join her later
um
um i was gonna uh get there in time for
my lesson with the skiing teacher
because like i i felt like if uh if i
don't have him then i'm gonna be [\h__\h]
scared again and i'm gonna be [\h__\h]
lost again
on those slopes so i wanted to start
together with the mr yodel
so we met up
a little bit later
and uh
we took a gondola gondola
is that how you say it in english too
we took a gondola to the top
and it was
it was crazy because like when i was uh
at the bottom it was really really
really cloudy like uh it was hard to see
stuff
but
once you pass that point with the
gondola you go up the mountain it was so
sunny and clear and beautiful and
actually i took a photo while i was in
the gondola
um
you can see it very clearly here
oh look
you see that
that that thing you see at the bottom uh
was like uh
not the start of the gondola but like a
middle station
mountains
everything everywhere was so beautiful
but it was really cool like we were
going through this um what do you call
it mist
it's i think it's miss not clouds
um we're going through it like we
couldn't see much but then you would
like get out of that area and the whole
whole town the whole village at the
bottom all the houses were covered up
and you could not see them anymore
um
it was like
you weren't
you went for a portal
[Music]
um
yeah it was gorgeous it was really sunny
and actually this was the best day this
was the best day we had the best weather
it was actually pretty hot
uh there where on this one you still see
some clouds but on the other uh once we
reach the top there were like no clouds
the sky was so blue
it was beautiful mountains were white
sky was blue
yeah weather was nice no snowing um
so beautiful uh beautiful
sight
yeah it was hot in the snow yeah yeah
you we actually army said we should have
brought sunscreen because like when it's
that sunny when it's that good weather
then you actually need sunscreen it was
actually hot
up there
yeah that was gorgeous so uh
once i reached the top it looked uh like
this although i have to say
this is just a small part it was
actually a really really big
skiing area
um
and this was just a small part and it
really does not
do
it justice at all
um
but
this is kind of kind of what
one side looked like
um once you reach the top of the gondola
you can still uh you see some non
gondola like the the the the lifts that
where you sit in but have your skis like
dangling in the air
um
those take you to some other places
nearby
and yeah there's like a lot of people
skiing and uh
that way down
um if you go like down here to the left
uh that's that's the slope that we were
going down the most that's supposedly
blue but um there were still some steep
areas here and there especially like
just the first the first um
hill like immediately when you go down
here it was already pretty steep
and so i had some troubles there
but it's beautiful isn't it our
mountains we were up so high
we were up so high
it does look steep doesn't it but it got
a little bit flatter here and there but
there were like i think two or three
spots that were so steep that i had to
go really slowly and carefully
um cool view
yes pun intended it was beautiful it
this does not do it justice and what
looked really beautiful is when when we
went up the gondola
oh man everything looked beautiful but
like the the untouched snow
looked like [\h__\h] foam it looked so
soft i think you can see it a little bit
here as well if you look to the
to the back uh
do you see that
untouched snow like in the middle of the
screen for example
at the top
you see that oh
it looks a little soft looks like foam
yeah
but yeah the snow was pretty good on
that day uh but it's
yeah it's fascinating how throughout the
day
um
it really changes quickly the slopes
they get like
uh
kind of like
they get these these small
bumps
so yeah i understand rmt now why she
wanted to be there in the beginning once
the slope got those bumps here and there
it was a bit more difficult for me um
not no problem for rmt of course but for
a beginner like me
the bumps are in the way uh and i can't
i can't ski that easily anymore
[Music]
so anyway i got up here and i met up
with rmt and mr yodell
and
i had my skis on but of course the
moment he saw me he was like nope nope
you're getting out of this skis
immediately and he got me different skis
because he knows a lot of people here
[Music]
everybody knows him too
so he got me different skis so i i um
actually he kept on changing my skis
every time we got back up here after one
slope um
he was like okay this is still not good
enough i'm gonna give you even smaller
ones so we went from originally 150
to
the smallest ones that i had on that day
that i ended up with were
centimeter
skis which was so tiny they were like
baby skis but he said no this is normal
if you can't ski well
it doesn't matter how tall you are
you gotta you gotta start with the small
ski anybody can ski with small skis the
smaller they're easier
yeah i have a little comparison
[Music]
i have a little comparison
um
on the right
uh
this might not have even been the
smallest ones these were i think still a
bit bigger maybe 130 centimeters or
something
on the right is rmt
on the left is me with my baby ski
yeah uh but it didn't help it did help
it made a quite a difference
[Music]
okay
um
it was it was all in all it was um
pretty
exciting um
he was like drilling me again but this
time it was
it was like amazing because like
ah
i was like sliding skiing through those
mountains i had there were some amazing
views and if you have uh if you're
scared of heights then it's [\h__\h]
terrifying though
because uh yeah there were some really
steep
places
um
but yeah mountains everywhere
everywhere you look beautiful mountains
everyone was like swooshing through it
was nice really really really nice
yeah
it was so beautiful it was very very
different from you know the lame ass
slopes that you have like at the bottom
of the mountain you really gotta go go
all the way up and then slide through
the mountains it was actually possible
to go from the very top to the very
bottom you don't have to take the
gondola back but um and rmt did that on
the second day but i we didn't do it on
the third day uh because you know it
would have been pretty exhausting and
it's not only blue slopes if you want to
go from top to bottom
um yeah but
even though there were some steep
um
passages every now and then uh thanks to
my teacher uh
i i was able to mostly handle it okayish
i just went really slow uh and really
stupidly
awkwardly through those steep passages
but then uh i i switched through the
the somewhat okayish places
pretty smoothly
and
yeah it was fun and then uh when the
hour was over he actually also taught
rmt a little bit she was like yo he's
such a good teacher i want to learn
something from him too
so he was trying to
teach her
some some weird style of skiing
um he called it
camille
uh
come come here wait what's camille in
english again
camel
uh well i don't know if they would call
it the same in english
it's like when you go like
yeah
i don't know how to explain it
but it's like like
yes
[Music]
zigzag you're
really quickly really short
small movements no not slalom
that's bigger he was just like i don't
know it's kind of like
it just looked like they were messing
around though
um
and then after that we met up at an
alpine hut hut there were a lot of
alpine huts up there and we've like they
serve mostly like traditional austrian
food and yeah typical alpine food and so
we met up there i was alone there at
first see it kind of looks like this you
see like people sliding over there while
you're eating um it has like loud music
playing like austrian pop or german pop
music
um
alpine alpine
[Music]
maybe it's alpine
and i was waiting for them and they
eventually came and you know what i had
i had something that's called a
gum clearly
doesn't that look
cute
it's like a big fat
dumpling
um with uh what's morn what's moon again
uh
what's a black seven top cardigan
the lemons does have oranges
a poppy
poppy seeds on top and then inside is uh
what was it called
it's vanilla sauce around it but inside
was um
what's it called again um
come on
help me austrian scam noodle
gum canoe um
[Music]
no no this is stuff inside
it's not chocolate it's uh
not custard no
porvide yeah poor veteran let's pull me
there like
paul vida english
eh jam yeah but what kind of gem i think
it's um
i think it's
plum
but it doesn't taste like plum jam oh
wait
is a fruit spread prepared from the
prune plum unlike jam or marmalade and
unlike the german fla plumpery pouville
is prepared with uh without additional
sweeteners or gelling agents who feels
cooked for several hours in order to
achieve necessary sweetness
it tastes
it tastes very interesting
[Music]
it doesn't taste like you know typical
plum jam
um but it is something like that and
that's inside of it it's it's very very
filling it's very big
noodle
[Music]
i was eating that um in the fresh
uh weather ah
in the sun it was wonderful
and then later on uh actually
while i was eating they already arrived
but yeah rmt and the teacher arrived
um
and
he sang for us again do you want to see
he was so talkative and we
he was like you're gonna you're gonna
of course invite me for some mulled wine
ride and i was like
yes of course
this is how you get invited to some
drinks you just assume that someone is
going to invite you if you say it like
that then you're going to be invited
[Laughter]
it was very funny
so i ordered some mulled wine for him
and he he put like part of it in his
secret
secret um bottle that he had in his
jacket for later
okay it will be loud again for a moment
okay be careful
uh
he was getting totally
classic old man move
but he was so charming i could not
resist of course yeah he had a flask
yeah
no but he's not alcoholic at all he was
really just uh he seemed very healthy
a little bit of mulled wine and so if
you're if you're up in the mountains
it's a must
okay be careful it's gonna be a bit loud
okay wait wait wait wait i want to hear
too
uh this time no yodeling he sang for us
a song that he
uh uh
has written himself
supposedly to the weight
monitor
and output
i think like this
[Music]
[Laughter]
so sweet
yeah he writes some good lyrics man he
needs to teach me how to write lyrics
isn't he lovely he has like he showed me
like a little piece of paper where he
has written down notes to her mind
himself probably of all the songs that
he has and all the jokes that he has as
well he told me uh
he has a lot of um
stupid sexual humor uh jokes
[Laughter]
yeah um but it was very very very funny
um
[Laughter]
oh let's get him into
uh holo holy and star someday huh
he's a good candidate i would say
w1 he's so sweet
he's so sweet but it was like talking so
much
but yeah someone like this would be
perfect for youtuber because they
couldn't go on and on and on and on and
on but they might they might often
repeat themselves but they can still go
on and on and on
there was a lot of unnecessary
information as well he said i don't know
if you guys understand this is this a
common thing uh a common phrase to say
uh he said his wife has a
a white liver
do you understand what he's trying to
say because i did not
until he explained it is that's a common
saying
oh
no idea
uh
supposedly it means dad
[Music]
um
let's say how he said it uh
she wants to um
do
do it every day
[Music]
i don't know how that has anything to do
with
the liver but
[Music]
he said he has a tough time with her
because she wants to
do it every day
[Music]
he told me a lot of stories i can't i
can't help it i have to share it a
little bit
what a chat
ah
yeah it was it was funny oh man
yeah um
[Music]
oh yeah like when you go to an alpena
alpine hut like this
it was cool they had like a little
skiing parking lot not really though
it's just like
everybody just throw their skis on the
ground and their sticks they poked it
into the snow so everyone had their
skis out there and i was like
i thought i thought someone stole my
skis when we were done eating because i
was looking for them and i just could
not find them because there were so many
yeah but um
yeah
this is the only place where you can
just put stuff
outside somewhere on the ground in
austria and it will not get stolen i
mean it's not like austria is like
a place where
you're going to be so careful about
pickpocketing or whatever but i thought
it was
uh fascinating how nothing gets stolen
here you just put your i had my other
skiers my 150 centimeters um somewhere
leaned against a building
for the whole day
and i came back and they were still
there
yeah
it made me nervous it made me nervous
but uh it has been proved that it's safe
apparently nobody is interested in
stealing your skis
yeah that is nice yeah skiers are
generally good people
i mean no i wouldn't say so because like
literally every austrian person is a
skier
but when they're on the mountains they
turn into nice people i feel like
i feel like austrians we may have our in
different indifferences um and things
that we don't agree on and and we have
our [\h__\h] in our country as well but
once we're up in the mountain
we become one
we're like this is our home
this is this is how it felt like
everybody
felt like this is where we belong to
it's it's our home the mountains are our
home
the law of the ski slopes yeah
yeah suddenly it feels like all
differences aside i mean it's not like
everyone talks or never but just by
sliding side to side
uh
on those beautiful slopes and those
beautiful mountains that we austrians
are so proud of
feels like we all become one isn't that
beautiful unity uh within skiers yeah
um
[Music]
oh my god
oh dear
[Music]
not hold on there i mean when i'm when
i'm in a fast restaurant i also feel
like kind of united with the other
people who are there
especially if someone orders the same
burger as me and i'm like oh you're a
crispy chicken type of person as well
huh
i catch
[Music]
that um
obviously i only had an hour with the
ski teacher so there was still a lot of
time left um i told rmt to just uh go
go to a difficult slope and have fun and
i'll go to like a baby slope like a
practice slope
um it wasn't as flat as the one i had on
the first day but
um it was still pretty boring but i was
like i'm gonna i'm just gonna chill a
little bit here try to
practice a bit more
and i'll see you in like two hours or so
but she came back early and because she
came back early we did one more slope
together like like the proper one where
where we went down with the skiing
teacher originally like we went through
a blue slope the the one in the
beginning that i showed you with the
with the steep steep parts yeah
but but at that point there were so many
bumps here and there
it was really tough
but
i'm telling you now
we successfully ended the day
with no accident
throughout the whole vacation
and um
i actually also didn't really fall down
at any time
no accidents
nothing
[Music]
probably because i was so terrified from
my last accident that i was extra
careful but still
[Laughter]
yay
she
yeah and um i think i think i got it
back
i i got i got it back in my blood like i
i i i it's it's back
it's back
i'm not a skiing master yet but
um i'm motivated to go skiing again
sometime i'm not that scared anymore
and rmt also was like let's go again
sometime
i'm surprised she still wants to go with
me because like i'm really a baby
but we had fun and ah
yeah it was nice and and then it's a
it's a fun sport activity
that doesn't quite feel so much like
you're really doing sports you know you
it's just like you know like ice skating
[Music]
it's a fun sport
and i have my own skis now so i gotta
get goods to eventually be able to use
it
i'm not gonna buy smaller ski i think
i'm just gonna rent it whenever
necessary i suppose
um
yeah
uh
i will try i wanna buy another pair and
i don't think i can give back the ones i
have now
um
yeah i used it like once and if i
sell it like secondhand now i feel like
i won't get
the value
that it actually is worth so i'm just
going to keep it until i can use it
properly
um
i don't think i can
give them back i'll just i'm just uh
i just uh rent something smaller
whenever i need it
yeah so after that we took the gondola
back down
it was a beautiful view again
the the fog the mist at the bottom was
gone at that point
it was even clearer than before
and we enjoyed the view while we were
going down and and the mountains for one
last time
yeah
uh and then we made it back to the hotel
we got picked up by a shuttle we made it
back to the hotel and then we packed our
[\h__\h]
and then we took the train back home
it's this time it was pretty exhausting
though um with the skis it was
more exhausting than before but
uh it was okay it was okay i'm a little
bit disappointed that my skis are too
long that i didn't get proper
um
advice from the store clerk
that's a bit disappointing
selling skis to us kfb
now i'm gonna keep mine now
[Music]
yeah i'm gonna keep them
they're pretty i like the the way they
look so
i want to
become good enough that i'm worthy of uh
using them
um
it should be about your heart no
no
that's what the guy at the store said
too but no it's not about how tall you
are it's about how good you are at
skiing
if you're one meter 60 or whatever
that doesn't mean that you should wear a
ski that's 150 or 160 or whatever you
should wear ski that's according to your
skill
[Music]
it's about technique yeah
and the better you get the longer your
skis should get
you have more pros and cons for this
holiday well yeah so i i worked out a
lot i have a really really bad uh
muscle pain my my muscles are sore as
[\h__\h]
um but i worked out and i also woke up
early every morning i had a healthy
lifestyle i had healthy
okay not healthy breakfast but because i
ate pancakes with nutella every morning
but still um i had good food had a good
uh traveling companion i went to the
sauna i went to the pool
um i met a cool yodeling guy who was
like a
kind of like a legend it felt like he
was a legend like a like an urban legend
everybody knew him
like eventually um after after he left
he said
he before he left he said that if if he
leaves then um i can still keep the the
skis that he got for me i just have to
return them at the
at the gondola give it to one of the
staff people and say his name and they
will understand so i was like after he
left i went there and i was like uh i
got this i got these from from hahaha
and and they were like ah
yeah yeah yeah
i understand understand yeah yeah fang
sings
he knows everybody he keeps on like
taking skis from there they have some
skis that they give away i guess
didn't even have to pay for them for
renting them i was able to use them all
day
he's famous yeah
mr yodel say no more exactly
[Music]
he's a mountain legend yeah
he really is
the
the we talked a little bit about him
with that uh
with a
gondola guy
chicken attack chicken
yeah
kind of like him but an austrian version
so
that's um
that was my vocation uh as i said it's
really not that
not that much
dif
like
variety but yeah it was it was beautiful
and
my conclusion is that the
um
and rmt says the same
that the reason for the accident in
hokkaido
was
rmt says it's mostly because of the skis
because you know when you rent skis it
also could very well be that they're not
only the wrong size but they're also
just not that good quality not um they
didn't get a good service uh as in they
were not
um
had to say
what's the word um
the skis have to be like
uh
yeah bad maintenance probably
with these rented skis at like
like those big uh rental places
yeah not maintained properly and and um
i mean rmt didn't feel or see the snow
and she can she can pretty much handle
any snow
but i say
comparing those two situations of uh
skiing here
and skiing in hokkaido
i
must say that
the snow in hokkaido on that day on that
slope was [\h__\h]
so it was the skis and the snow and
yeah so unfortunate that it happened but
now i am better prepared for situations
like that
how about frank what's his story
frank is uh sitting on my shelf now um
i found a cute alpaca as you saw on
twitter and i i dragged him back home uh
he lives with me in my apartment now
frank lives with me
i have a new pet he's an alpaca an
alpine alpaca alpine cup
[Music]
oh from the alps
does he get along with the cats um i
have to put him on the top shelf
otherwise they try to smack him and give
him like a cat punch
they want to touch his hair because it's
so fluffy it's fur
[Music]
gotta be on the very top of the shelf so
that they don't reach him
i have some more like uh little stories
that uh or or things that i might
mention in the following streams but for
now generally that was my trip it was it
was cool it was a
very different trip very active it felt
so healthy to
like be moving my body so much even
though it was a pain yes holy [\h__\h] like
especially my legs like the
sheen binder what do you call what you
call the front part of your
uh lower legs
what do you call that
those were hurting so much because the
the the ski shoes they make you feel
really really um stiff the shins yeah
my shoes
oh man cramp alarm cramp alarm
a lot of pain in my body at the moment
especially in the train ride that was
painful
[Music]
but uh hopefully it gets back to normal
even though my normal state is already
pain
it's even more than usual now
yeah
i think i will
read super chats now cause i don't want
to stream for too long today
you'll see what i have uh
what i will stream to i think tomorrow
i'm actually gonna go to a doctor
um and i'm not sure yet when exactly i
can go
um and when i'll be back so it might be
another stream in the evening that's not
too long
i think pokemon will be on sunday
[Music]
i'm not sure yet what to play tomorrow
we'll see
no no no day off no no no no i just came
back
i'm just coming back
[Music]
okay okay so let's uh read super chats
let's go to uh
let's stay here
because i have my comfy clothing here
[Music]
i know
thank you for the membership and thank
you for all the super chats guys thank
you for welcoming me back
come back
[Music]
reading super chats now
okay let's put that here
[Music]
you guys should go skiing too
you should go too it's fun
it's exhausting but it's fun
[Music]
uh
actually the doctor that i'm going to
tomorrow is the fruit doctor
so um i'm not sure if he's gonna be
immediately
uh able to
like
you know do something like pull put a
camera down my nose like iris i actually
hope he's not going to because that
sounds terrifying
um but yeah i am going there
tomorrow and have a little chit chat
with
a doctor that my that bff recommends to
me
[Music]
um
i'm going to the product let's go
when skiing once it was okay huh if it
was just okay then you probably didn't
have that beautiful scenery that i had
[Music]
oh no i didn't talk with her about it
but
yeah uh i'm terrified if i have to get
uh a camera right down my nose i don't
want that but
yeah
uh
let's get healthy
i hope i hope there's nothing
wrong but we will see we'll see i'll let
you guys know probably
uh what he says i don't think he can
really say much at that point in the
first session but
let's see
[Music]
i will read the super chats from this
stream
and the lag
maybe because of the lag maybe i should
just read it tomorrow what do you think
i don't know how many is it
if you guys are still having issues with
the lag
is it enjoyable is it okay
it seems okay now
[Music]
no lag
no no lag
fine
what about what about the europeans
maybe they already left
or the european bros
[Music]
big lag
fine no lag you okay ah okay fix itself
when i refresh oh okay maybe try
refreshing whoever is still lagging
little lag still
gone so lagging
ah
no like on the phone
i got buffer stuff all for [\h__\h] sake
[Music]
huh
i i stopped reading at least a little
bit i don't wanna
get behind too much let's see how far we
get
uh
[Music]
okay
i think like you know how i said that
the snow was [\h__\h] there and the slope
was not good but i think you know we
went to the closest skiing area in
sapporo
to the closest to sapporo so i feel like
if you would go like more outside
of that area in hokkaido then i'm sure
hokkaido has amazing skiing places as
well so i don't want to say that
everywhere in hokkaido is bad uh
hokkaido has great mountains and great
snow supposedly from what i've heard
like i've i see i see a lot of people go
skiing uh to hokkaido even from like
overseas so there must be a reason why
they do it
[Music]
yeah it's also depending on the day and
the weather yeah yeah although the
weather was fine that day
it was [\h__\h] cold though oh man
oh i do have to say though i mean the
first day
because of the stormy weather
uh it was testing the limits of my
attire but generally um holy [\h__\h] i'm
surprised how how warming how
um
isolating this skiing attire is i did
not feel cold most of the time and
underneath i was really just wearing a
really thin skiing underwear which is
like a leggings and a
a pretty tight
shirt thingy
yeah i was doubting it but it worked
wonderfully
ice isolating i said isolating
[Music]
and do i mean insulating but it isolates
me from the cold no
yeah they call it skiing underwear but
it doesn't look like underwear it's like
it's like a leggings and and some tight
shirts
it's not that special actually
eh well done can a good fun that wasn't
supposed to be a pun
eh good point but it is insulated
well in german we say
it's a little
in german we say
so it's isolating in german
[Music]
it's like it's like trained and drilled
inside of your chicken brains when i say
and in german we say
you say auf wiedersehen no no no no
bye-bye yet no no no no no no don't
worry i'm here i'm here
i am here
i'm scrolling i'm very oh wait i need to
read them
apparently i need to read the super
chats from a monkey and uh
kfb hiring the videos as well
alright
[Music]
thank you for the pinky i got an email
saying i was really released i was
released from my contract willing to
resign but only with union protection
caps shift length
and immunity from the basement
well you've already been restored i
think you're already a member again and
i did not agree to this so
nothing has changed
i do not accept your terms and yet you
have accepted coming back to the
membership so i think we good
[Music]
yeah sorry everybody who was worried
about it it's all back to normal um
don't worry about it
[Music]
and now my watch begins it shall not end
until my death i shall take no other
oshie hold no salary no other restaurant
i shall wear cave uniform only and win
no race
i shall live and die at my post i'm the
sword in the kfp i am the watcher on the
fryer i am the food that is this uh game
of thrones reference and the food that
noah gains or a bible referee
but no against the oil the stuff that
brings out the meal the horn that wakes
the sleepers who doesn't order anything
the shield that guards the realms of kfb
[Music]
this is the night watch right
yo i love me a game of thrones reference
at least something that i can understand
i pledge my life and honor to kiana for
this phoenix and all the shifts to come
thank you skye beautiful did you watch
game of thrones skye
you watched it recently why did you
write that now
well well
winter winter is coming and uh
your watch
never ends welcome
thank you skye
[Music]
it's a night's watch yeah
nice pledge i feel
like you're a really really loyal
chicken i feel the passion
danke shin
james
[Music]
yeah did you guys like my monkey noises
i recorded that uh last minute uh on the
evening in the night before i left i had
so much to do
on the night before i left
so much to record and and do
but yeah i recorded
the harmonies for the song cover of ame
and i recorded
the monkey video
[Music]
after the last stream that i did uh i
think it was pokemon yeah
after that i still had recordings to do
but monkey noises i would say i totally
nailed them
[Music]
here
i think i think my monkey um
my monkey noises are
at least in the top three of my best
animal noises
[Music]
the thing is when i was recording that
i had a i think i had smoothie lying
next to me
and she was purring and chilling and i
was like smoothie i'm so sorry but i
need to make monkey noises now
i was trying to drag it out as long as i
could but i had to and then i started
you know doing my monkey noises
literally screaming at the top of my
lungs suddenly
and smoothie of course is disturbed by
it and runs away
i'm sorry smoothie
that must have been terrifying
suddenly my mommy turns into a monkey
sounds like a light novel title
[Music]
my mom suddenly turned into a monkey
what should i do
[Music]
thank you ever for the pinkie
uh you mean extinction dr helghas thank
you patrick and turkish and lord everton
at 17p32
anton m thank you for the red super chat
today i woke up and found out that i'm
not a chimpkin kfb doesn't exist and
chiara is a monkey the whole world just
collapsed on you
oh no
what's it called a mental no what's it
called again uh
what's it called
[Music]
what's the word existential crisis yeah
mental assault
are you okay i'm done it's so bad to
know it was just a bad dream it was just
a bad bad dream i also had some bad
dreams recently crazy dreams man
crazy dreams
i dreamt that i had no chickens around
me for like four days it was terrible
[Music]
terrible
go bananas
you're funny
[Music]
i was a lot on twitter this time i
suppose but
uh at least during skiing i was not on
twitter
i mean
okay sometimes in the breaks i was on
twitter but i was just so excited to
talk to you guys
and share stuff with you guys but i was
still able to um
you know
[Music]
turn off the brain a little bit every
now and then
[Music]
yeah
i need to sneeze
[Music]
aggressively sneezes
thank you i don't have a kiss for you
don't worry don't worry shh
good job kid
it's all good no panic just calm
only calm
[Music]
and we're done with the monkey super
chats gonna reach the kfp hiring super
chats now
no echo this time no no i didn't want to
move my hand
[Music]
it's sleepy time for me soon
jacob 47 out thank you
monkey dangerous
yes i can testify that kfb has a really
heartwarming working environment i mean
physically heartwarming especially when
we were testing the new chicken giblets
menu also you'll never feel lonely
because there are always other employees
with you in the bucket
yeah it's a very social place to work at
i suppose um
and uh
[Music]
[\h__\h] i really can't say anything about
healthiness
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
yeah uh
i'm having trouble uh
representing presenting it in a positive
light um
[Music]
well um
you know how son asana is good for your
heart
being fried in hot oil
is
two
because
you
um
[Music]
uh
it's yes
it's um
it will kill off
uh bacteria yes
and it will um it's appealing for your
skin because it uh gets rid of all the
old
skin cells
and um
yeah
your
your heartbeat being too fast will not
be an issue anymore
uh
yeah um
and the the bubbliness the bubbliness
will feel like a massage you know like
in a in a
in a you know in a what's it called
again [\h__\h] sake can't speak english
in a whirlpool like in the whirlpool
um
it's like massaging your whole body
so your muscles will feel very very soft
afterwards
very good if you
had some workout before uh and want to
get rid of your sore muscles
and like a jacuzzi
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
anyway um
um
anyway
thank you felix as always you are a
great example everyone should learn from
you how to be a good example of a
chicken
[Music]
translate for
we're done with kfb hiring
i hope you enjoyed the video guys the
script was actually um
written
by cub uh coupzette mostly i made some
small changes for sure and uh yeah but
most of the idea was from cub zed
thankfully i didn't really have i wasn't
i wasn't feeling inspired i couldn't
really think of
anything interesting uh but the hiring
idea was always like
an easy
and easy idea excuse me
[Music]
who said that
who's
really one wanna you're going into the
usual room
uh
six months
i saw that
you sound like a hater
you need to go to the usual room
the
extra usual room
[Music]
you need to be massaged
and bunked
strongly
i think i have to switch out your brain
while i'm at it
[Music]
no
sorry does not work here
no sorrys
no cause you ain't sorry i know it
can't fool me
[Music]
have fun in the extra usual room
ah
anyway yeah
i want to make more videos like that
whenever possible but it does it does
take some work for the team they built a
whole kfp building in minecraft
and yeah the whole editing um really
well done i really like the style of of
the videos that cub that creates i
really like it it's so funny um but
definitely gonna ask again if i go on
another vacation i'm gonna ask for
another
video and you guys were like wondering
if there's gonna be like a part two or
something originally it was now planned
to like make a part two of this
storyline but we could i suppose maybe
maybe we will maybe we will
or just something completely different
but
yeah
i really like those cute minecraft
animations it has such a uh
like a good comedic timing as well so
it's like
don't don't the speed is so fast i
really like it
yeah
all right let's read the super chats
from today
[Music]
yeah i missed you so much how was it but
first of all you need to tell me
first of all you need to tell me how
does it feel getting followed by your
own aussia that you're shocked did you
think about it all the time during the
rest of your vacation
well i was very very excited about it
and uh explained everything to rmt
uh why it was so exciting to me and who
the girl was and all that but i will
keep that story for another time for a
pokemon stream or whatever and to talk
about it in detail but yeah an idol that
i have been supporting for
over 10 years probably like i don't know
14 years or so by now
and
followed me back on twitter and i didn't
i don't know when it happened i just
realized during their vacation
so i don't know when it happened but it
happened and i freaked out
i freaked out
yeah
i'll talk more about it soon
jacob 47 out there skydiving looking for
the top down
really our uniforms disappeared and we
were nakey
just like that yeah the first
memberships the door to kfb was closed
and i almost lost my mind because i'm
still holding my salary and i wanted to
keep you
back i know everything sounds so crazy
right i totally didn't lose my mind but
you were back just in time here take
back my salary will come look well we'll
comment the comments like we've missed
you so much
oh
thank you
that sounds crazy indeed yeah um
it's not like i didn't warn you guys by
retweeting the thing on twitter but
uh chicken brains probably forgot all
about it immediately afterwards so
it's okay it's okay
it was bound to happen
[Music]
realistically speaking you guys should
have already forgotten about what
happened
on that day
on those days
[Music]
as if it didn't even happen but yeah i
fell back to normal
if anyone has some issues
let me know it should all be back to its
original state but yeah
everyone should have their badges that
they deserve for supporting me
looking beautiful everybody
in green and in their uniforms of course
if you have no membership you're looking
beautiful too
but i'm glad to see all the members all
the chickens again
glad to see you guys looking tasty as
always
we don't have pants you don't need pants
i don't need
you
i will give you pants if you chickens
learn to control your bladder
but until then
[Music]
pets backpacks
and no diet first oh you would look like
a baby but that would kind of be cute
diaper diaper chicken
dakuma dakuma
when i see diaper chicken
but
if if you wear a diaper i feel like it
will get in the way of laying the eggs
because i feel like it would it would
break the moment it would pop on you and
then it would all just be a [\h__\h] egg
mess down there in the diaper
all the egg yolks
[\h__\h] that sounds uncomfortable
we lay eggs i'm sure some of you lay
eggs maybe not all of you
[Music]
i don't tell
just to be clear i i only
sit on them
to uh
to make them
to keep them warm but i'm not i'm not
the layer
i'm the sitter
yeah exiter like a babysitter
i just i just i just adopt the eggs
[Music]
yes
do i look like a chicken tea do i look
like a [\h__\h] chicken to you
i'm not a chicken i don't like eggs how
many times do i have to tell you that
[Music]
okay everyone who says yes bond
mod mods ban them
[Music]
bomb mads them
band wants them it well mods banned them
[Music]
don't mock them don't mock them no don't
give them the power
no
[Music]
and ever arriving here with a pinky
welcome back boss had a good time since
we all took a vacation from membership
review and we'll have to reapply for kfb
can i request a title never had one
before and really can i apply for kfb
head chef i've been working hard on my
cooking skills i did see the video he
head chef no
sous chef
i don't think you're quite ready for
head chef yet and you know why
i think your burgers desperately needed
some lettuce inside
where the [\h__\h] are the veggies huh
just a few pickle slices you think that
will do it
no where the [\h__\h] are the veggies
where's the tomato slices where is this
let where's the lettuce i'm not gonna
eat a crispy chicken burger if there's
no lettuce in it it needs a lettuce
desperately
the crunchy fresh lettuce
the only thing that was in your burger
your burger was
okay i'm sure it was delicious but
visually it was a lacking color
it was um
70 bread and 30
meat
[Music]
lettuce goku
i think that will improve it a lot
[Music]
but besides that
it looked it looked great
[Laughter]
uh a big i know yeah a big piece of
chicken you need to bonk it a little bit
make it a small bag
so it would be too big for me and i
would need to um eat that with a fork i
think
that was a big
big slice of chicken
big [\h__\h] slice of chicken man
[Music]
number excuse me what
what
[Music]
sorry for having a lot of meat i'm not
blaming you we just need to cut your
ties up in more pieces not used the
whole time fine
[Music]
i don't know what the hell you guys are
talking about
[Music]
no no no no no no no we don't say that
here
i love burger king
i love burger king i love boogie i had
burger king yesterday on my way home
but honestly
every in my opinion every burger needs
lettuce
yeah
crunchy lettuce
[Music]
but yeah you can take the title of sous
chef
and maybe one day you'll be worthy of
becoming the head chef
mr cat's mixed dancing for the pinkie
good to have you back my crazy phoenix
boss crazy what's crazy about me
huh you more than earned that trip with
the amount of effort and passion you put
into all your work now time for a
tangent attempt after pokemon what are
some of other therapists you would be
down to stream
oh
well
we're gonna play yakuza afterwards i'm
still kind of
low-key really low-key somewhat
considering xenoblade maybe like not a
whole series i don't know
i don't know what to do about it
i kind of want to play it but i feel
like
it would be tough to stream it
um then i guess suppose i suppose you
guys wouldn't call it a jrpg but i do
wanna play um zelda games and i do
i do count it in that category
because it's a japanese long ass game
[Music]
uh yeah
um
other than that i have not thought that
much about it i i want i kind of want to
play tales of symphonia
too
uh because i have not played number two
yet i played number one when i was young
um but i feel like if i were to stream
number two then i also have to stream
number one but i i don't know that would
that sounds like a long ass commitment
um
but it's one of the very few tales of
games that i have yet to play um
so
i don't know if there's no not it's
coming out soon no it's really old it's
pretty old at this point
i wonder if
maybe
starting from number two would like
story wise not be too much of an issue
especially if i explain what happened in
number one
maybe we would be fine
and i think a lot of people played
sinfonia one anyway because it was a
really popular gamecube game back in the
day
a lot of people's first tales off game
so still thinking about that um
besides that
[Music]
nothing
two
i mean
breath of the wild too
it's not i know it's not a
proper rpg either but i still count it
as a series
uh
yeah
um
we'll have to think about it oh yeah
yeah some some zelda games yeah
[Music]
i'm not sure
i i've had some ideas but
um we'll go with the flow whatever
whatever comes up if something new comes
up yeah
final fantasy like if i ever get
permissions um i really want to play it
if once i get it you know i'll be
playing it whatever it is like every
single final fantasy game i have
i have not played them
and i'm waiting so that i can stream
them
[Music]
[\h__\h]
cables
um
[Music]
yeah one day
one [\h__\h] day
continuing uh hi heather thank you for
the red super chat
[Music]
m
thank you for um pinky welcome home
tantrum glad to have you back thanks for
the fun videos you prepared for us while
away congrats on 5 million views for
goodbye decoration and 2 million
[Music]
now that you're back let us discuss the
work and certain tackle you know what
yes
honestly that video i did not anticipate
what was going to happen but i guess the
the video kfb hiring video was kind of
foreshadowing i think we have to go to
war
but but but but but it
but it had to happen eventually and anna
the the the stuff that she has now is
her profile picture like is drawn by her
peppa and it looks beautiful looks
amazing so
it's understandable but
she didn't she didn't tell me
she didn't even tell me
it just happened
she could have warned me at least
and gave her a pass because it's [\h__\h]
gorgeous
i would have changed it too if hookah
papa provided me with stuff like that
but my heart is
broccolo coco
[Music]
i need to change it too now [\h__\h] i
forgot it's embarrassing to have it all
alone
well what do i change into i guess i i'm
changing it back to the one i
commissioned from akira
oh yeah
oh yeah i will do it
remind me if i don't do it after the
stream
[Music]
egg is broken heart is true yeah
i know
someone is
[Music]
she said sorry though she ain't sorry
but honestly holy [\h__\h] the new art that
she's using is amazing it's beautiful oh
my god
oh my god
and she said she thought that i would be
the first i thought so too that came out
of nowhere
i thought i would change it by the time
when i'm putting out the new song cover
with ahmed
i thought i thought that would be it i
thought i would change it first but then
it ended up being inna holy [\h__\h] that
was so unexpected
my
heart ah it hurts it hurts
it hurts
[Music]
maybe she always knew yeah
because she must have commissioned it
quite a while ago
yeah
we're in her back with a second yeah
we're just gonna just kind of make
another song cover with inna
and then get her to use a picture of us
together again
she said she always knew but she never
told me she could have told me
if she always knew why didn't she never
tell me
[Music]
you know your dark side is chilling
i mean
oh man
i still love you though eena
i still
i will always love you
[Music]
i'm not sad
not sad um
hi lin thank you for the pinky
uh oh my god huh
thank you shirt um welcome back tinto i
had to change my shift at work
so i'll be part of the vod gang in some
weekdays but i'm sure kfb will welcome
you with all the love you deserve i hope
you had a great time with rmt during the
trip love you there thank you thank you
yes um
thank you
um
yeah i had a
nice vacation
rmt was great
um
she's a pro skier so i couldn't quite
keep up with her
but you know it's nice being with her
[Music]
foundation pilot i'm back i'm back
huckle and thanks for the pinky i missed
you i missed you so much so so so so so
much i was eagerly waiting for your
return in front of the cafe building
day and night i failed to play tales of
berseria what
i'm sorry but uh you are looking
especially cute today
why did you did you download it did you
start playing it what
what why
you asking me for
for a recommendation then you don't even
play it
why
you're not listening to my orders then
that means usual room for you
you made me think
very seriously about what i would
recommend to you
i took it very seriously
you did not do it you did not do your
homework
usually
[Music]
and in the usual room you must play the
game
so you will be in the usual room for as
long as it takes you to play the game
and finish it
[Music]
it's pretty long so good luck
good punishment
so tyrannical yes i'm a tyrant
[Music]
[Laughter]
i make you play
good games as a punishment
oh
terrifying
tyson thank you for the pinky i'll
likely be lurking during the stream
during work so i'll go ahead and leave
my welcome back here it sounds like you
had a very well deserved great time
can't wait to hear the stories i'm sure
you've found some great food and random
craziness yeah the food was the food was
fine as i said the first date was
amazing the other ones were
that was okay it was okay it was okay it
was okay it was good it was good but the
the first dinner kind of raised my
expectations so high that i was a little
tiny a bit disappointed at the other
dinners that we had but they were so
good still good still very good
yeah
good is good good is good yeah yeah yeah
good food good food lots of food i will
always went to sleep with a full belly
yeah
with an egg in my stomach
[Music]
yeah
no i mean in the hotel not at the alpine
hut's in the ski slopes although that
was delicious i wanted to eat more at
the alpine huts
i want to eat everything on their menu
because they have like typical austrian
food and oh it's just
amazing
i wanna eat all of it
i'm getting really hungry by the way
well
well i had
i had uh
had breakfast and nothing else today
i don't think i'll read all of them but
i'll read a few more
and
red thank you for tuning in oh red happy
birthday
you're in your 20s now oh my god
congratulations
make the best out of it the 20s i think
are
times that you you have so many
opportunities so many chances so many
paths you can go
make the best out of it red or at least
try to
happy birthday
[Music]
you're welcome
celebration
horse examination looking for the top
dancing
[Music]
i did not try that yet but i don't think
many people are using it so it won't be
that effective i tried tensho before
though but a lot of other people use
tencho for something as well
because slavic fellow thank you for the
pinky welcome back to anchovy i'll miss
you greatly thank you i'm so happy you
guys missed me
let me see you guys too
oh it wasn't even that long guys but
thank you for waiting for me
thank you
thank you so much
[Music]
why are you using crabs
cancer crabs as the icon there
why
did you forget you were chicken
you were chicken you remember that right
you know it right it's a meal
crab rave
where where where is that from
where is that from
[Music]
and why why are you using that meme i
feel so stupid again
and
crab brave
is it new
three years ago craw brave 10 hours crab
rave noise storm oh my god
but why
[Music]
what is this eminem crap god
oh
oh wait
i might have chucked away i might have
seen it before because of a v2 blue
dancing to it
let me hear
huh
oh my god
i have heard of them
i didn't know it was a crab rave
i love crabs though they're cute
[Laughter]
what the [\h__\h] is this though
what is this
why why does this exist
why does it exist
oh my god
uh thank you for the fun shorts while
you're gone you're welcome this time i
only could do two i hope it was
okay um
yeah
at least something better than nothing
right
maybe maybe next time i can time it so
that i can release a song cover again
yeah
[Music]
more than okay
i think the
it made up the cubs that video made up
for the lack of other videos because
it's just so good
yeah
and also wait there's a bit more as i
think the last streaming vlog is messed
up it won't load hot oh someone already
told me about that i didn't get to check
it yet
what why
360p
why
let me see if it's like um
[Music]
uh
if it's
rendering for some reason
no
no no
[Music]
youtube videos missing quality options
on this browser youtubers are available
in many formats and qualities but some
browsers no that's not what it is
[Music]
why
says my browser is outdated no what the
it [\h__\h] so long it yeah i mean it's a
long stream so sometimes it really takes
a long time to process the chat but the
video is processed by that and actually
it says here in in the in the youtube
studio it says like uh quality of the
video sd okay and hd okay
like
the rendering of hd is finished let me
write this down
[Music]
hmm
um
[Music]
yeah
uh
it was working fine before i know when
it came like this uh-huh
yeah
i hope it gets fixed for the
watchers because 360p
[Music]
foreign
just like 2008 back then it was hd yo
yeah watch it on your phone and then
hold the phone really close to your
face and then it will feel like hd
but we'll figure we'll try uh to figure
it out and maybe fix it if it's possible
i don't know if it or if it's broken
forever i hope not
but that sucks thanks for letting me
know
[Music]
when you had to type in hd in the
address part to get hd [\h__\h] yeah that
was a thing
i think i remember but that's so long
ago
wait that was a thing wasn't it
you guys remember that you had to type
in hd into the youtube url
oh my god that's so long ago
remember when youtube still had a
messaging system sometimes i wish it
still had that you know how like you
were able to dm channels
[Music]
i wish it still had that because it
would make it easier to contact
um
like i don't know musicians for example
or people who don't have twitter
yeah
ah man
but also at the same time
yeah if if
there was no way to turning it off i
think so
you would not be able to not take any
dms
um
[Music]
continuing uh
doc joseph duncan for the pinky every
day you were gone there was some tweet
for me about skiing climbing mountains
riding alpacas laying eggs for too much
food
and monkey and caffeine interviews were
awesome too i just wanted to say thanks
tanja for checking in on those ah of
course of course i could not resist i
was actually on my phone too much i
think
but i don't know i was still like i was
still very um
um
happy i didn't feel burnt out before the
vacation so it was not about fixing
anything like that it was just about
yeah
having fun
now
i should have probably not been so much
on the phone but yeah i have a i have a
need to share
a break never hurts anyone unless it's
your neck but i didn't break anything
this time let's go
i didn't break anything i'm actually
surprised i did not really like
yeah i smooth yes sorry sorry sorry what
is it
do you hear her
[Music]
looking at me
[Applause]
this is all me now she stopped talking
the moment i started talking she's
listening
[Music]
she's so sweet we already had a lot of
cuddles to make up for the time i was
not here
of course i had to
give her
a lot of
cuddles
yeah
yeah i'm petting her with my feet right
now
[Music]
yeah yeah i don't know who's enjoying
this more my feet or the cat probably my
feet
[Music]
i see
you multitasking
[Music]
pbnk thanks for the pinky a long time no
see i felt your absence a lot i really
want to watch daystream but i can't
because i'm very sick so i replaced it
with the super chat recently i tried
epic battle fantasy 5 again and it was
so fun that i lost track of time so i
highly recommend it even you can't
stream even if you can't stream this
game i always want you to be happy and i
will respect and support any choice
thank you always for your existence
oh thank you that's so sweet wait let me
look it up i never heard of it before
epic battle fantasy five
oh
[Music]
that looks um
interesting
i think i used to play something like
this when i was younger
yeah
is that like a phone game no it's on
steam as well
cool
epic fantasy games are good really
yeah
you should play tails off froze area as
well
well thank you you're so sweet
it's so sweet thank you it used to be a
flash gaming that's what it looks like
[Music]
so pbnk since it was two pinkies you get
a kiss
[Music]
daddy [\h__\h] for your support i'm sorry
that you felt so lonely without me
but
i'm back now
oh
you can sleep in you all all of you
chimpkins can sleep in the same room
tonight with me
not on the bed you have to sleep in the
coops but i'll put them in my room
tonight
[Music]
okay
we can have a sleepover pajama party
with chimpkins
and my cats they might try to eat you um
so don't be surprised if you're missing
a leg on the
following morning
oh thanks movie just
farted
[Music]
[Laughter]
not that i heard it but
i think i smelled it
[Music]
maybe maybe she's trying to tell me that
she doesn't want chickens around
i just had her on my lap and then i let
her go
and then she
farted i think
no she really cats do fart it's true
kiwama doesn't
want one doesn't
no no no no
[Music]
silent but deadly no it's just a small
small fart
she's a small fart hey
don't don't make fun of her she's a cute
baby no one can resist her cuteness
no it's not that bad
oh you're gonna make her feel
embarrassed you left the room
[Music]
[Applause]
before andrey
beauford
[Music]
no
freeze the frog thank you for the pinky
hello and welcome back to angel i missed
you i got a birthday merch a few weeks
ago but this is my first chance to send
the super chat since then oh can i
please get a kfb employee number from
you to write on my ic card sticker oh
yeah yeah i know yours by heart
it's a four
five
one
thank you for buying my merchandise i'm
glad it arrived safely please take good
care of it wear your apron every day
when you go to work you can also wear it
privately if you want to
[Music]
thank you for your love and support
yeah
i'm honored thank you soon
i hope the slippers fit
if you got the slippers as well
they don't fit um
a lot of people but
if they don't fit then
yeah use them as oven mitts or something
[Music]
oh wait that wasn't supposed to get a
kiss but i guess you
you get it anyway because i'm feeling
uh
kind today slippers didn't fit but i
hung them with the tapestry oh
oh
i see i see i see well why not
then they will at least always be in a
good shape
and not fall apart
anytime soon
i'm feeling generous yeah
your plushies shipped ooh
exciting
daisy thank you for the red super chat
kiwawa yes that's me i'm back i was back
you're always on the telly again
he
[Music]
tell
me i want to tell you
quite on the telly
[Music]
put me on the telly put me on the tower
okay while we're on the telly
i think she's on the tower yes i'm on
the telly
wait wait i'm not really on the telly
wait
wait i'll be on the telly
i'm on this telly
and i'm on this deli
and i'm on
this telly
and i want this telling
[Music]
i'm on the telly
guys i'm on the telly
[Music]
let me out
let me know it's so tight in here oh my
god
oh my god oh there's no space in here
i don't want to be in delhi anymore i
went out of here
[Music]
i need more space i want out of this
telly
scary
so everything's so flat here
[Music]
let me out let me out let me out
i'll let myself out no i'll stay here
i'll stay
i just have to remind myself i'm also
i'm also here not on the telly i'm
everywhere
[Music]
the the kiawah on the italian is not the
real kiwawa
it's not the real one the real one is
here
[Music]
i'm also glad i'm back alive hell yeah
hi to that question for the red super
chat don't come until like thank you you
know everyone was saying it in german so
sweet
i am back
[Music]
yes i have made a titan did you miss me
you better have missed me
and thought about me 24 7.
you did didn't you
zimkin is on diaper now i sleep oh
[Music]
beans
i think the egg didn't really need one
but
egg is definitely baby so
just in case just for safety
you know that might actually help um if
you drop the egg the diaper
could possibly
uh take some of the bounce and protect
the egg
with its softness and fluffiness
changing dap is part of usual from duty
now perhaps yeah
that's so cute huh
oh baby bubble wobble jenkins
it's so cute we've been provided with
adorable chimpkins again
isn't that wonderful
[Music]
i got pushed up all the way back to the
top of the super chats bye
[Music]
where am i now
here okay
thank you daddy
i'm back thank you for waiting for me
and for coming back to see me when i'm
back dancing
keep on having this feeling that there's
a cat hair in my mouth
um
but like
where
[Music]
no
sorry i tried to get it out of there
and almost grew up
it's it's back i'm i'm back in the
apartment of the cat hairs
it's inevitable
[Music]
especially chunkers is losing so much
hair right now is incredible
[Music]
i know you you commissioned her it was
perfect i was like thinking is there
anything
anything with kiwawa and snow and
there's not much there's not much kiwawa
in snow attire in the snowy area
but this fan art i got
good use out of it so
thank you for commissioning it
maybe think ahead like that miss fist
you seem to be thinking ahead at all
times
so think ahead and think about my next
vacation in the maldives with retainer
[Music]
um maybe we need some kiwa dana swimsuit
fan art
[Music]
yes yes
yes
great idea
why the hell would you not want to see
that oh my god that would be i can
imagine that would be so hot
dana and me we both look amazing in
swimsuits
hot
hot bibs
wow
so hot that rainer might also turn into
a phoenix
imagining respectfully
[Music]
gonna thank you for the two pinkies we
missed you glad to have you back thank
you thank you
it feels great to be missed um
but i don't want you guys to feel sad so
i hope
i hope you didn't feel so sad thank you
daigana you get a kiss because it was
two pinkies
nice to be back and nice to be welcomed
so warmly by all of you thank you
from the bottom of my broken cocodo
brocodocolo
i'll try to put it back together with
hot glue afterwards
misty very much thank you
thank you i'm blessed to have such sweet
chickens as my friends
[Music]
as there's so far thank you
so much
for calling
counting chickens and images
[Music]
a little bit longer then but at least
it's there baby little little tank is an
[Music]
thank you for being there when i'm back
it's very reassuring to have all you all
of you guys here
thank you
for your kindness
and your patience
i'll be taking probably a lot of short
trips this year i hope that's okay with
you guys but
um yeah i want to make some memories i
want to see some cool places and it's
always good to have a
like a like a opportunity to
like you know relax and cool down
like this this job does get
kind of taxing on
is that the right word i think it is it
seems like that
on on mental health
sometimes um
it is very stressful and pressuring
uh
and uh yeah
it of course i mean there's more tough
jobs out there but
and some people might think we don't do
that much to
[Music]
make up for all these vacations but
um
yeah
not only for the sake of my mental
health but also you know like get
stories thanks to these trips and
especially if it's with other whole life
girls
then we can also bond over the memories
and i think that's everybody loves to
see whole live girls hanging out
together it's always
uh nice stories that come with that so
[Music]
yeah
and
i think that i
i just if i were to do it
like all my respect to the japanese
girls but i wish they would take more
vacations because i feel like just like
who powering through a whole year
without taking a vacation it's just not
what i'm used to i i
grew up in a culture where
taking
vacations is a given and is encouraged
in the workplace
so
yeah i think it's really necessary for
the
human or the phoenix body
to do that in order to also give back
the full power continuously i mean if
you're used to
um a culture where taking a vacation is
not normal
then
i'm sure you can handle that as well
like the japanese girls are doing it
amazingly like oh my god they
they don't
they don't lose energy they're always
getting hundred percent and it's amazing
to me i really really look up to them
i don't know how they do it
but i need my breaks
i need my vacations
not only for the sake of vacation as i
said but also for the sake of
content and entertaining as well
and
other than vacations i really don't go
out do i so
yeah need to touch some grass or some
snow in this case
[Music]
since i don't go out drinking or i don't
go out into the cinema or wherever
i don't do stuff at all
i'm always at home
hmm need some interaction and some
something to do sometimes man
don't really have a hobby either
so
yeah
it's kind of unhealthy
[Music]
don't get shy away from taking breaks i
will not
i will not i'm so much planned i wanna
go to so many places and i still wanna
do my food trip uh did i tell you that i
said rmt
rmt agreed to go with me on a food trip
yeah and then also army told me
auntie told me that she
kind of like booked something for i
think it was december or something
[Music]
um
where was that
i think
[Music]
so what was that again some european
country ah i think it was italy a place
in italy
um and she was like yo i just booked it
because it was chief uh i can still
cancel it oh yeah i booked it i was like
yo should i go with you she was like
yeah let's go
i can't 100 say yet that i can go in
december but for now
it's somewhere on my list
might be going to italy in december
[Music]
until then until
december
yeah
it will be the first time in a while
of me going to italy
i would love to see italy again
love your italian blast ah
thank you very much
i know my italian is
perfecto
perfect
[Music]
bellissimo
right yeah yeah
[Music]
h hell yeah
that's me when i move from the border
between austria and italia italy the
moment i cross the border i will turn
into chiara with ch
[Music]
anyway another irrational [\h__\h] thank
you for the pinky why do you
why don't you give yourself a nickname
like that
you need to be nicer to yourself
oi give yourself a nicer name
give yourself more credit yo
[Music]
hmm you should
i mean you can keep the name if you want
to but i feel like you should give
yourself a nicer name how about
how about another
amazing beautiful chicken
something like that you know something
more positive
oh
she's back i am back indeed
i'll down kitchen for welcoming me back
and your generous support thank you
another dedicated chicken oh yeah oh
yeah that sounds good
that sounds good too
[Music]
joseph danielson
for the red super chat
welcome back to intro thanks for the
videos they are so funny but we still
miss you and sorry tanjo i didn't hear
clearly where should we to attack i'm
ready
yeah
oh
[Music]
and actually the
um
it i i think it was not supposed to be
a
taco bell
that we are attacking after that video
i'm not sure though we we could still
change our mind we know we we all have
chicken brains even though i'm a phoenix
i have a chicken brain i kind of forgot
i forgot where we were supposed to go
but we can decide on a whim especially
now that you know
the thing happened
[Music]
nothing happened
with inna
we must show her
that can't be
it's not to mess with
not to be messed with
[Music]
can't be need to be respected
they think they can like
play around with us just because we're
chickens
[Music]
no no no no no
we are not born to be turned into
burgers we are born to be much much more
than that
we have a destiny and each one of us has
their own unique destiny
so stop [\h__\h] around with us we are
more than just married again i say we
not because i am a chicken but i
represent you guys
with all my health and i will i will i
will improve our reputation
i will do everything it takes
we are strong
we're independent we're unique we're
special we're beautiful
we're chickens but we've cried
[Music]
until no one is left out there who
speaks ill of a chicken
we are not just a food source
[Music]
no
fight for your honor
and i will fight for yours
[Music]
[Laughter]
beautiful beautiful beautiful
beautiful
the passion and the motivation in the
chat is inspiring
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank you soon everybody
[Music]
we're marching
tomorrow 5 a.m let's go
we need to attack before before the sun
goes up
[Music]
oh man oh man
thank you takasama 64.
i did not watch the nintendo direct yet
it was so late and i was pretty tired uh
yeah i might watch it after this stream
i think i will
i just saw something uh
about a fire emblem and i got bamboozled
because
apparently it's not a new fire emblem
it's just a
um
hyrule warriors kind of thing
that's that was uh
um
uh
anti-climatic
i'll i'll look it up afterwards doctor
zillow verifies seven documents
i hope you had a lot of fun it felt
really long without you i missed you so
much thank you you know what you should
do you and all the others when i say i
go skiing you guys should go skiing at
the same time and then it would feel
like we're skiing together
[Music]
is there any place you can go skiing at
in your area i wonder
next time when i say i go to the beach
you guys should go to the beach too
go swim swim chicken swim
become as duck
never seen snow before
well then it's a good good reason to go
see snow
[Music]
you can go snowboarding too of course
doesn't matter
no beach close by same for me
austria has no beach no i mean we have
well we have no ocean but
you could go to a beach of a of a
of a lake
there's some big lakes out there too
where you can go swimming or you can go
into a pool i mean
i mean there must be a pool in an indoor
pool even in in your place the way you
guys live come on come on no excuses
no excuses
[Music]
if q i'm gonna do a swim you do a swim
if you wanna do whiskey you do whiskey
you chickens
are born for greatness
you have to learn from your phoenix
empress
hmm
[Music]
i will show you what you can do
if i can ski then you can ski
i'm more for chicken than you guys are
somehow
i'm i was quite a chicken on on those
slopes
but
i still overcame my chickeness
and i went from top to the bottom of the
mountain
[Music]
duncan
i cannot yodel
uh unfortunately i want to learn it to
impress you guys
yeah
uh wait a second friends papa go papa
where did you go translate for me please
[Music]
no every austrian can ski or snowboard
but not every austrian can
uh yodel unfortunately
sorry i'm waiting to hear some late last
words for chinese new year because of
this year of the tiger
oh
okay i'm done reading for scheme stories
but ready for scheme let me let me uh
find a translation for that
translate
special
[Music]
i wish you good luck in the year of the
tiger this year a happy new year for the
tiger the tigers air is soaring the
tiger is blessed with wind the dragon is
alive and the tiger is full of life
the smile is always open everything goes
well and you love tiger oil
red envelope for you
i love tiger oil
oh lots of tigers there
thank you
i feel like
tigers
tigers are so powerful so i think
this year will be very very powerful for
kfp
and all of you too
all of you
outside of your kfb activities as well
[Music]
what's it sounded cool in the original
it looks cool it even looks cool yeah
down kenshin for your support hakutan
for the red envelope thank you and happy
new year to youtube
and i wish you all the success in this
year
wow thank you
gd donkey and ellie smith duncan turkey
jester duncan backbeat highway duncan
jackson fb thank you for the pinky
man i want to go skiing austria so bad
now glad you're home safe and sound so
thank you
well i i hope um
i was able to remind you guys
of the fact that austria
has beautiful
mountains i feel like
within europe it's something that
everybody knows
no we have beautiful mountains some
other countries in europe have beautiful
mountains too too but no don't forget
about austria's beautiful mountains
yeah i'm not up there that much but i i
am very much aware of it so you guys
don't forget about it either
and and the photos that i showed you
don't even do it justice i didn't show
you that many photos there's there's
there's many many more beautiful photos
of
mountains in austria
[Music]
the thing about austria is that we have
a lot of beautiful mountains and we have
a lot of beautiful lakes big big clear
gorgeous lakes in between mountains and
that kind of makes up for the lack of
oceans that we don't have
yeah
yeah the water and the air is also very
clean
[Music]
um
hell yeah we have mr yodel
he's worth a visit
if you if you go skiing where i went
skiing if you'll find out where the hell
that was
uh then you probably meet him
he goes skiing every day like holy [\h__\h]
i respect that
with 85 years going skiing every day i
really think he's gonna be alive like
until 130 years old or so
[Music]
it's probably like like a daily jog
instead of jogging because he lives at
the mountains he just goes skiing it's
just like
instead of putting on running shoes it
takes a bit more time to put on the
skiing shoes and the skis and all that
but
yeah
it's more fun probably than going
running
[Music]
hmm
he probably has the same kind of mindset
like
there's a lot of people who go running
every day but he just goes skiing every
day
[\h__\h] cool
yeah
damn damn
hey ramos dancing
for the pinky comes on
hi boss welcome back from the vacation
and playful and masochistic chimpkin but
i missed you a lot i think it's food
vacation instead of skiing was good
enough by the way master yodel who is he
he's singing well he skis while i'm
jealous yeah he is a legend he he is
quite the charmer
he's funny he's he's got it all
he must have have a crazy backstory he
did say that he had like uh he has a
[\h__\h] ton of trophies from skiing
i tried to look him up i didn't find
anything specific but yeah
um
still apparently
he's always been this active and
successful yeah
former olympian probably not but maybe
maybe could have been there in another
parallel world
yeah but it is very impressive i'm so
glad he found me
without him i would have been so lost
and
i don't think i would have learned much
in that other lesson
so yeah i'm so glad he picked me up what
an angel
maybe it was like you know how in in hot
deserts you have a fata morgana
like a i don't know what it's called in
english but like in like a you you uh
have crazy
um
uh
what's it called
[Music]
mirage marriage mirage
marriage
perhaps a hallucination yeah yeah yeah
but instead of the hot desert this was
in the
freaking snowstorm it was so snowy and
cold and stormy that i had a
hallucination of this
of this legendary
old yodel guy
he probably wasn't even real
yeah i had a cold stroke instead of a
heat stroke
it was actually me yodeling the whole
time exactly
and and that also means that
it's always i've always known how to ski
i just needed to find myself again
he was never there i taught myself on my
own again
he was real and he deserves the credit
uh grumble dog danke soon kara ganitar
dankeshun
if i could take other myth girls on a
ski vacation
so um i would love to give it another
try yes with kelly and the other girls
perhaps if they want to but i wonder um
i've never heard the other girls talking
about ever trying uh snow sports
i like skiing
i i guess
they probably
don't know how to ski you guys know have
they ever talked about it
the other myth girls
good at inna
i would love to flex my
skiing skills to them and look cool for
once
[Music]
emma can't ride a bike what i mean i
can't ride it well either but at least
to some extent i taught myself
but i'm pretty bad pretty bad at it too
[Music]
you know doesn't leave her house
probably no
whoo well maybe maybe we can do a winter
vacation someday
um
i want them to see some beautiful
mountains doesn't even have to be
australian mountains
maybe maybe the swiss alps or whatever
we can go there
and moon dog thank you
for the pinky welcome back cute phoenix
sounds like you had a fun trip
so good to hear i'm especially happy
that you have bloot collect when it
comes to skiing
you mean
because of my
accident in
japan
do it now and then you will be skiing of
great comfort eventually
[Music]
well blood killing means that
i suffered right
that's that's what you're trying to say
you did say you were feeling it
wait what exactly
the
i felt a lot of things while i was
skiing like pain but also fun
and inspiration
i
got i got the taste of skin yeah yeah i
guess oh wait i totally interpreted it
wrongly okay
oh
oh wait what the [\h__\h]
hope it was more fun than pain ah
[Music]
yes
uh
fool no i think there was more pain than
fun but
it's okay i'm not mad
don't regret it i don't regret it at all
it's just that holy [\h__\h] man
it was really [\h__\h] exhausting
but but in this case i'm i'm not i'm not
mad it's okay it's it's part of it it
belongs
uh to the experience um it had to be
painful no pain no gain haha yolo
right
i got a good workout hell yeah holy [\h__\h]
i got a workout worth of one month
running every day
now let's see if i can keep it up well i
i want to go skiing at least one more
time
this season
to make use of my skis that i probably
won't be using because i will use
somebody else's skins but yeah
um
rmt said so too we're gonna go skiing
one more time one more time
but i think the
season still continues for quite some
time so i think i still have some time
uh
i wonder what's the latest maybe april
not sure
but the mountains are
staying snowy for quite some time
[Music]
i am
thank you
[Music]
do you guys mind if i ended here i it's
where my list ends right now if i
refresh then there's gonna be more but
it's already getting late and i wanna
eat dinner before midnight
and not immediately ruin my sleep
schedule i
i'm gonna be honest i suspect that
because of streams i will ruin my sleep
schedule again but now you know i'm
capable of fixing it
[Music]
yeah but since i'm going to the doctor
tomorrow um
i want to be able to get up somewhat
early
today i woke up naturally at like uh 9
00 a.m
[Music]
so
currently my
sleep schedule is doing good
yeah
yeah a few days and fixing okay usual
room
you go to the usual room
one week
[Music]
you have to praise me
you guys gonna praise me
say good job quinoa
[Music]
i
i need crazy
i need to be praised
thank you
i think yeah if i want to don't it's not
it's not like i can't
fix it i just didn't have a proper
reason to fix it whenever it's necessary
i can wake up early but it's all it was
usually just like like one day at a time
i would have to get up early for maybe a
recording or something
and
yeah
and then the next day there's no reason
to wake up early so if you don't have a
reason then it just keeps on going back
to it
but this time i had several days in a
row where i had to get up early and uh
yeah
that definitely helps
ah
now i will not have a reason again
besides the doctor's appointments um but
yeah the one tomorrow i don't know when
my next one will be so
it's probably gonna go back to waking up
late staying up late
which which is i mean
in itself no problem
um
[Music]
but
if i need to fix it again i'm just going
to take the melatonin there were like a
[\h__\h] ton of pills in that one little box
so i have plenty
yeah that's how it works that's how it
works
i need a reason but if i don't have a
reason then i don't think i need to be
so hard on myself for
having a shitty sleep schedule i suppose
it's
nothing to nothing to be so
[Music]
mad about
why would i not be up for it
of course she is
oh yeah tomorrow by the way uh on the
official channel
and there's gonna be another video with
me bhutan senpai vata sampa and euv
going up
you might have seen me retweet it on
twitter let me show it on screen
um
yes
another video we recorded this on the
same day that's why it's uh the same
team again
i don't know why but they wanted us to
record two things so
this is one of the
uh two things that we recorded
another official appearance this time
it's about um japanese language
they're basically kind of
uh
trying to teach us stuff
but me and eofy obviously very good new
hunger will we understand what they're
trying to teach us or will we not we
will find out there's a little bit of a
preview on the official twitter
uh that you could already check out this
is coming out in
let me see what does youtube say it's
coming out in 12 hours
[Music]
yeah the preview is already funny
yeah
oh i'm winking
[Music]
do we look the same
i think we do i think that girl might be
me we look so similar oh my god
mouth to open up
[Music]
whatever
my hair is a bit different oh yeah i
have a different hairstyle right now hmm
so who's the real one who is the real
amir is
is she a
fake kiana
[Music]
more on that
japanese standard time 6 pm 11 february
on the whole live official channel
so and i will continue reading super
chats tomorrow and play some game i
don't know what maybe maybe um
maybe we could play paladins
[Music]
could be good for a shorter type of
stream
[Music]
i don't know what else i will think
about it
uh
because i think if i play a pokemon i
would start too late
hmm
[Music]
yoko
thank you
thank
oh thank you um
super mario 64.
anyway uh
thank you everybody for welcoming back
me
welcoming me back so kindly and waiting
for me and letting me do these kind of
things
letting me enjoy life
yeah but i'm of course very very happy
to be back with you guys
and uh we're gonna have
a fun rest of the week hopefully
um
and next week is valentine's day which
means the new song cover with amma is
coming up so soon wait what the [\h__\h]
it's a 10
oh yeah yeah
valentine's day is the 14th i'm planning
on putting it out a day before
so
also thank you for watching uh my music
videos on youtube as we have reached 5
million on [\h__\h] goodbye declaration 5
million what
and yeah in 2 million thank you guys for
the support
sunday
what's a sunday
what's your sunday
did i say
oh oh
12.
i suppose that would be sunday
[Music]
oh
maybe it will come out on sunday
maybe it will
also depends on if it gets finished
i still working on the music
[Music]
video i say who's making a video
i did say it but i
i don't think i said it yet
[Music]
[Laughter]
no i didn't say anything
[Music]
anyway
[Laughter]
[Music]
but you know i had to somehow top or or
like be on the at least at least on the
level of awesomeness of all the previous
uh
collabs uncover music videos that i did
i always try to make each and every
single one of them special
[Music]
and i am kind of trying also to top
myself with every one of them
yeah
[Music]
so
how can i possibly top
what we had before
look forward to it is it's coming soon
[Music]
okay i'll go uh
try to make some food now
and uh
try to get to sleep early and go to
doctor tomorrow and then after the
doctor's appointment it might be kind of
late but i'll put up the stream
reservation afterwards because i don't
know when exactly i will be able to
stream okay and in german we say i'll be
that thing thank you for coming
everybody
had a great time talking to you
thank you for being here for me always
thank you for your support and your love
i love all of you thank you so much
[Music]
my
let them know let it be known keep our
life back
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
you