foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
what's up
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah happy
birthday happy birthday to me
hey guys what's up thank you very much
for coming to my very first ever 3D live
concert I see all you deadbeats and chat
going wild right now what is up
and just like that
let's go through bye-bye
I'm kidding I'm kidding it's a joke it's
a joke now we're here to we're here to
celebrate why are we starting off in
this room I don't know maybe because I'm
nervous as hell and I want to talk to my
friends
I want to talk to my friends
because I'm nervous I'm so I'm so
nervous so I thought I thought why not
do a little fun game with my friends who
have been with me since the beginning
and afterward new friends too that I've
made along the way why don't we play a
game or something so I can calm down
before this big concert what do you guys
think is that okay
is that okay that beats
happy birthday Daddy calm down no no I
refuse
you watch yourself mister you watch your
foot
I'm looking at you won't you tell me to
calm down I'm too excited
dad needs a workout I do need to go back
to the gym but you know what after today
after today
I'm gonna be extra strong mukimuki yeah
especially after today's game today's
game is going to require some 3D
movement I thought hey why not we're 3D
today so let's let's do some things in
3D let's do some actions and maybe I
don't know have my friends try to guess
what I'm doing maybe that would be cool
so anyway that's what I thought so yeah
yeah yeah let's enjoy a game of Charades
Charades with my friends
and I have some friends from ID joining
and also a friend from JP we'll be here
as well so let's get the party started
let's start marimasu charades game
let's do it we've got two different
groups of people
so you guys know we had to split them up
too many cool friends so let's see if we
can get him in here yeah yeah yeah here
we go here we go here we go oh who's it
gonna be who's it gonna be
who's gonna be joining us by the way we
got the hashtag if you want it's right
here I want to see your screenshots
please show me your screenshots
[Music]
okay everyone come in from the first
group please come here
hello
I hear my friends
[Music]
no stop I'm embarrassed
you so cute
I have my friends here today we've got
Sana Iris Bay Ina and rulichan in group
number one hello guys
first so everybody
thank you I'm so happy
please first Chico show Kai
stop it stop yeah
man no you don't get to look
so cute
okay
she can't she can't
oh thank you thank you thank you thank
you thank you thank you
thank you
thank you that wasn't part of the Game
Boy that wasn't part of the game
before we start the game though can you
introduce yourselves please from Sana
Sana
ah yes it's sunny from honey live Ian
Council I am a Mia Khalid Mori Ben not
your space dude
thank you Sana you're so sweet how about
Iris
uh hiris it's Iris uh hello live Ian the
Project's help of V singer YouTuber and
I'm so excited for Kelly's 3D debut at
also from Kelly's um number one uh fan
in Japan hold on Amanda thank you
that makes sense if I could really
properly make a heart I would right now
but it's a little difficult anyway it
costs enough close enough close enough
you get the message thank you Iris how
about how about my little sister little
sis
what's up it's me but hey guys hi I have
infiltrated I am uh this is my big
sister guys it's her birthday and I
wanted to come say hi and yeah oh yeah
I'm from Holocaust I'm not leaving
without a signature okay okay you'll get
one oh you're still bringing us
oh my gosh you'll get one you silly
freaking red signature on my leg on my
leg please is that what you want you
want a signature
yes
[Music]
I love you Ina thank you for coming
today I'm so happy man you know I love
you dude gosh dang it when are we gonna
get on the same stage right
I want a bokoboko fate in the face
and then who do we have last we have my
favorite kohai
oh she's doing that
yeah
[Music]
from the secret society holocs
yeah
you are so cute every every day but you
are so cute more than usual ah do each
other
thank you so much
thank you for coming
yeah shall we start the game yeah let's
do it let's do it okay let's go first
word okay okay the audience the audience
can see and I can see but the girls
can't see the word okay so they're gonna
guess okay guess me okay right all right
here's number one let me see let's see
what it is oh
how am I supposed to okay hold on hold
on
once I pulled out the Naruto run you
guys knew
not ninja okay please remember okay now
next word let's go
let's go
oh no okay this is gonna be kind of hard
okay um oh dang it ah okay cartwheel
[Laughter]
um
singing opera singer hold on I'm trying
to find a way to surprise okay I hope I
don't get in trouble for this you're
gonna beat the out of me if I get
in trouble for this huh okay I'm trying
to
look at him here
[Laughter]
and I was like this isn't gonna work but
yeah nice job all right the last
question mark last question mark last
question maybe it's a question uh last
question it's supposed to be hard so
let's go here we go let's go
oh no help okay hold on
Circle
swimming or eating eating contests
[Music]
um
someone eating a large bowl of ramen
oh nice job I was worried about that one
I didn't know if you'd get the first
part but I think I Illustrated the the
large bowl with my impeccable 3D
tracking yeah
nice job you guys are smart dang I think
I think that's all wow
oh my gosh that's crazy you guys are
nuts dang we should do this more often
when everybody gets a chance to be in 3D
someday sure
charades party with everyone yeah
man you guys please please someday think
about how crazy that would be if if that
was what we did just now and it was so
hilarious imagine all of us together
yeah
okay
I promise oh it's like a thousand
needles oh wow oh that please don't hurt
yourself please
please don't anyway I'll see you guys
later thank you so much for coming
bye
oh man it's so nice to have my friends
but guess what they're not the only
guests that came today no no we have
several more guests that will be joining
us in the next group why don't you
ladies come on in
come here come here
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah yeah
yeah yeah oh my gosh whoa jump more okay
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
is giving me the good Idol advice she
knows what I need to be doing right now
sorry let me calm down yeah save your
energy your whole uh performance or
probably ahead of you right yes you are
right dang it there you go okay
there we go big breath big breath
breathing oh big breath
okay
we're fine we're fine now okay who do we
have here today oh my gosh some of my
favorites some of my favorite ladies in
the whole world oh my goodness thank you
so much for coming today we have both ID
and of course Ian myth being represented
here please introduce yourselves first
starting from Rayne my fishing buddy
Kelly's fishing buddy also a big fan
everybody's a fan
everybody suddenly well you guys have
always been supporting me so thanks I
appreciate it thank you my my sweet
fishing buddy love you so much Renee
dang and how about um how about
how about my Apex buddy for the the two
times I've ever played Apex
crazy Ollie did I do it correct
did it so well
you'll be senpies a wife slash daughter
slash mother-in-law our relationship is
a little bit of foggy here but get to be
here
huh
hold on I didn't get the memo would you
say wife
hmm you propose to me yeah but you
tricked me
you watch yourself next up we've got
hollow en's number one detective Amelia
ho Watson
hi Callie hello everybody I'm hello live
to Texas
I'm so proud of you you look so
beautiful happy birthday Watson thank
you so much I appreciate that oh man I'm
so glad I get to do 3D stuff you're also
doing really awesome 3D stuff too so I
hope we get to do some fun stuff in the
future I can't wait I can't wait let's
do it and we can't forget about
my idol Mentor apparently
attention
[Music]
Phoenix and kfpe owner takanashi Kiana
and I am apparently a pro for charades
because I got the the testing prompt uh
in within one second oh my gosh that is
true that is true in the in the
beginning there you immediately knew but
that was something that was something
that you like know well you knew that I
was pretending to be yeah but that was
that's not because of that I'm just
really good at charades I'll approach
it's also because you are just really
really good at showing those moves and
expressing yourself that's too much fun
I have too much fun in 3D it's like all
of a sudden I see myself like on the
screen and I'm like oh man I wanna I
won't jump I won't jump I'm gonna stay
calm
well Shall We Begin the game then let's
go
all right first word here we go
first word oh no how much okay here we
go
oh
baking
course right out you're right you're
here
playing the piano no xylophone no uh
what it's like you're you're tying your
hair and then you're eating cooking
cooking close making pizza making ramen
ah
um
making dough making bread
okay watch this first oh yes that's it
you got it once then you got it
Sushi mustard I'm the sushi master
I guess my I guess my sushi rolling
technique what did you tuck your hand
behind your head because I was you know
how Sushi chefs like maybe have like a
little cooking hat or bandana or
something
I don't know don't you chop the sushi
like this and you're making like
nothing
I don't know well at least at least
almond maybe that's just a very American
perspective but at least Watson got it
maybe that's why
anyway
oh thank goodness thank goodness I
thought that I was gonna lose that one
number two question number two let's go
all right oh boy oh this one's too easy
I can do this one okay
watch closely
oh
[Applause]
I'm talking about so easy all I have to
do was pull out the kick and be like
okay
[Music]
you do it with a lot more finesse than I
do but listen nice
look that's good oh thank you I'm gonna
try it again
thank you thank you
thank you yeah
you're giving us a lot today wow well I
don't really know what you mean by that
but anyway question number three
question number three the last most
difficult question here we go oh okay
no oh no
okay all right hold on okay
hold on
oh
Frank Cali Fink what oh
you're uh
I think
uh bad guy killing someone close you're
very close
um
killing someone yes
and somebody dated
oh no begging for mercy and died dying
uh well maybe if I can use my fingers
your fingers okay okay okay okay yeah a
tiny ball
what number is this
uh two no
yes one one one one guy stealing someone
number one
um
but what's specifically more about them
congratulations
this question I'm gonna kill them
I think I might lose this one guys
um a murderer
um
my friends please don't kill me
no life grip all my friends are alive
and I am dead
uh someone died someone someone died
I lost this one died by being stabbed to
death
that was too freaking specific okay the
answer was the first person to die in a
horror movie
how am I supposed to indicate that I'm
the first person that's difficult that's
hard
can you be so specific right I know but
you guys got it for the most part so you
guys did your best we all did our best
yeah
ah but you know what that was fun with
you guys honestly oh man I'm so glad we
got to play a little games together you
guys need to get over here too and do
some 3D with me okay
yeah
yeah I'm waiting for you doing your best
to do your best Callie I will I hope
so excited thank you I'm excited too
thanks for coming and making time for me
I know it's really early for some folks
here and really inconvenient timing so
thank you so much for being here to
support me and if you check out the
concerting us
we gotta be here it's a special event
yeah
[Music]
hey
yeah
it's my birthday thank you so much
everyone I'll see you guys soon then
okay okay
[Music]
thank you bye everyone
see you
there they go well I guess that that
means it's time for the singing portion
I did get to shake off some of the
nerves thanks to my friends because my
heart's been racing today but because I
got to talk to them and I know that
they're supporting me I feel good I feel
like we can put on a show and I'll do my
best it's my first time really doing
this like live so I'm trying not to run
out of energy I gotta take I gotta take
Kiara's Idol expertise to heart I should
know that too being a rapper as well but
you know I forget and plus you know the
the speakers
all the time anyway let's let's do a
show all right let's do a show you guys
I'll do my I'll do my best okay nervous
retired a little bit of both but also
ready to go let's do this okay
let's go to the stage
[Music]
foreign
it's awesome
[Music]
do you have an issue Limitless
hey guess what your old news done living
with your eyes
[Music]
foreign
thank you thank you everyone
thank you so much
yeah we can perform on the same stage
together
you're right before we invite
um you're a special day of course of
course thank you for coming here on my
special day and I loved making spiral
tones together with you sugoi
spiral tones right
song an all English song I wondered
[Laughter]
please of course
yes
let's do it yeah thank you and I always
support Holo Stars
[Music]
foreign
see you
guys freaking Senpai is so cool man what
a what a awesome dude and great musician
check out rika's stuff please
um check out rika's channel he does a
lot of music stuff I know that a lot of
my deadbeats love my music and stuff
like that that I make so I always have
my recommended musicians amongst the
hollow crew Enrique is definitely one of
them and check out the stars because
they're working super hard too
now then since we started off with a
guest song I figure
it's probably time for me to to take it
on my own but I need a little bit of
water this always happens and every show
I go to it's like every single song that
I do it's like in between I'm like okay
water water it's become a joke honestly
hold on
but you can't see it it's the mysterious
water bottle you can't see
all right oh by the way check out the
stage you see that cool skeleton
yeah this is my special Holo live made
to order Calliope Mori stage
um with my cool skeletons with the wings
designed after uh the year Mori album
art by Ray
check it check out my Geico satachi
my skeletons it's like you guys sitting
behind me supporting me couldn't have
skeleton back up dancers this time and
next time
you'll be watching anyway shall we go to
the next song Let's Do It the Grim
Reaper is a live streamer
[Music]
dead
Shuffle
[Music]
stories
and on the town again death in your
midst right behind you down below you
listen you got the gist stop nobody
realizing they don't recognize me fine
by me it's agonizing disguising live now
for casting only so long lasting rather
it's a matter of a right or wrong yeah
[Music]
hell of a show
uh
[Music]
hey
whatever
yeah yeah
the breath there man
foreign
let's go
oh yeah
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
oh no
camera
[Music]
moving on
hey thank you
thank you everyone
[Music]
yes welcome to my stage yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
and it came out with her new single
template and template was number one on
the charts and Wiki was number two so um
amazing so wonderful and uh
yes we have we have another song
actually that we wrote together except
this time it's uh it's a calliope Mori
featuring hoshimashi song Yes
um a brand new song and it's very
important because after we perform this
song there's a really really big enough
it's the one it's the announcement I
mentioned that's the biggest of my
entire life so please look forward to it
and it has something to do with the song
we're doing so we're gonna do our brand
new song yeah it's called capsule yes
capsule with c a calliope Su for
s-uh yes
so please enjoy yes let's check it out
check it out and thank you so much
Senpai coming to my birthday
yes join us
foreign
[Music]
we can't sleep
let's go
[Music]
you know
thank you
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
and excited thank you thank you so much
everyone yes uh the truth is
um I am now signed to Universal Music
um and I am doing I'm it's my major
debut I'm lost for words I like don't
know what to say
um this is like something I dreamed for
for such a long time
um
honestly I I dreamed of doing something
like this and um
yeah I'm not gonna I won't get emotional
right now
um we got a couple things to talk about
so but yes I am debuting from Universal
Music and I will also be doing um a solo
live show in July my first solo on a
real stage in front of a crowd in front
of all of you guys so let the deadbeat
Empire continue onward and um and
there's a new EP
uh major debut new EP called
shinigaminoto Shinigami note
shinigaminoto which is kind of a popular
it's like a play on words
um you'll see later when you read the
kanji but uh
thank you everyone
um who's been supporting me and um
and uh yeah I'm really excited to see
where this journey takes us but I
promise you guys that I'll still be me
I'll still be making the music I want to
make it's just it's going to be on a
larger scale I'm like shaking right now
I'm still gonna make the music that I
want to make and for for the world that
I want to see this is a little corny but
um anyway uh this is like the biggest
thing that's ever happened to me in my
life so and I wouldn't be here if if you
guys didn't love what I do so much and
support me
um and cheer for me and listen to my
music and thank you so much
yeah so I want to explain some things I
want to explain a little bit about the
EP and whatnot
so first we have of course capsule first
major single and guess what it's
featuring my beloved singing Senpai
hoshima chisoise who I respect and love
so much we love suicide Senpai and I
could not have chosen a better partner
to be involved in my first major single
from Universal Music
um and uh yeah it's actually premiering
after this show the MV YouTube Premiere
and digital release it's going to be 30
minutes not 30 minutes I'm more like
more like 25 uh from now on my channel
so please check it out capsule
um yeah let's go to the next slide
next we've got Shinigami notes
if if you check it out at the bottom
it's like you know Shinigami music note
get it right because uh music
um but then also Shinigami no Oto using
the kanji for sound which is kind of a
popular play on words in Japan so um
yeah my first major EP and we have the
art done by my fantastic Mama Yuki Sami
mama you can scan the QR code right now
to pre-order it's going to be released
on July 20th July 20th and that will
include capsule by the way capsule's art
was illustrated by nardak so let's give
a big UPS to nardack as well but if you
guys want to pre-order and I recommend
you pre-order because you get some cool
stuff you can scan the QR code right now
next slide
because if you order the first press
limited edition you get the lp sized set
which is a CD plus dvd plus extras it's
LP size but it's not a record it's just
like the size of a record but it's got
the CD in it
um the Shinigami note epcd as well as
five original uh LP size cover jackets
drawn by various artists you guys you
guys are gonna love these these pieces
these art pieces are so cool and then I
also will be doing an interview 30
minutes on DVD behind the scenes of the
creation of the EP and then also you get
a Crest badge honorary deadbeat Crest
badge
um so yeah that's that's pretty neat but
just so you guys know these are super
limited like we only have a certain
amount of them
um so if if you want it you may want to
try and grab it before it's gone uh
because these are not infinite um and
it's and we are never making them again
so uh you may want to grab these as soon
as possible if you're interested and
then we've got the standard version of
course including the same songs and then
we have bonus items depending on each
outlet that you use to buy the CD so
you'll see those items pretty soon
um when this when the EP comes out it's
available for pre-order everywhere but
uh you'll get little bonus items
depending on which store you buy from so
again scan the QR code if you're
interested
let's go to the next slide and finally
my first solo concert July 21st 2022 at
toyosu Pitt that's the day after the EP
drops
um I want to see you guys there more
information coming soon but save the
date and don't worry you guys if you're
overseas and you can't get to Japan no
worries because it will be streamed live
to you and you will be able to buy a
ticket for it so please don't worry
about that uh fans all over the world
you guys will get a chance to see it so
please anticipate it we're working very
hard on it and uh and yeah I hope you'll
have fun that's all you know this that's
all so um I figured the next song that I
would sing would be um
sort of a celebration of moving on to
the nest I wrote this song
um to kind of come to terms with me
moving on from Japan's underground rap
scene and embracing uh what I have found
here in Holo and things won't change
with me in terms of Holo I'll still
stream for you guys and and collab with
my friends and do music collabs with
them too but when it comes to my
original music Universal is going to be
a kind of
um with me throughout the journey so
don't worry I'm not leaving or anything
I'm still here but things may become a
little more focused on the music things
might change a little bit but again I
don't want you to worry I'm really
excited about this so let's rather try
and and celebrate together
looking towards a positive future with
the next song end of a life let's go
thank you
wait around
run right through
those nights I'll never find my way back
to you inside this Labyrinth of flights
there was Madness in the meaning never
lifeless we were screaming at the top of
our lungs to the numbness the city never
died
[Music]
but what's the root of it all I couldn't
say it used to jump in the fall
get off without complaint not a sound I
used to trying to find friends cause in
the end nobody sticks around it's when
you shoved yourself into a crowded place
that you turned around and found
yourself in love and outer space cue The
Reckless nights no strings laughing at
our own dreams just what the hell was so
funny up the wrong tree stumble used to
fall in Great Hearts amidst the concrete
jungle singing cause it felt right we
mix the on we in troubles rhyming artist
content and though it's history I can't
forget the time it's been convinced that
this could mean another end exist
between real and pretend a twisted Ultra
fiction where I miss my chest is not a
scent disappearing into the midst of
never happened this to me that I can
never
befriending
[Music]
without the directions
God but it won't stop the rain from
pouring
run right through
those nights
[Music]
there was Madness
between the soaring high rises left to
trail behind to find a Wasted Time Of
Our Lives silent singer overworked and
underpaid thinks and opposites the
confidence a lot that's where you're
laid yet author says not the Mist you
ought to be afraid stopping nothing
wrong and writing songs behind the
lonely shade is the world a sadder place
without the words that you conveyed when
the latter fell and shattered every bar
that we had played does it matter in the
end the sound diminished and decayed and
your friends retire to Fantasy you're
wishing they insane you don't get to say
I miss you you washed your Heroes Fade
Into the rear view mirror of the villain
you portrayed stop the pity party listen
you don't get to be dismayed you don't
get to be emotional
is
the life because you chose to make a
trade recollect the days you hoped and
you prayed for this what is there to
miss me
[Music]
oh my God
foreign
[Music]
thank you so much everyone
thank you
thank you oh my gosh all the hearts and
the claps in the chat I saw so many
people being so supportive in the chat
and you guys are amazing and I love you
guys so much thank you so much for being
my fans honestly it means the world to
me and um and I have some other things
to show you as well
um my birthday in March of course I made
goods for you guys I wanted to to make
some really cool merch for my birthday
as well for my amazing Deb beats so
let's go ahead and show them
all right first of all we've got a
beautiful illustration by nardack to uh
show off the release of my birthday
celebration March we've got a birthday
voice and four merch items we have a
deadbeat honorary sweater my favorite
wine glass for company wine and a so
gorgeous your eyes will melt out of your
skull on a live poster and a hollow
Classic on a live album vinyl and of
course if you buy everything together
you get a printed letter
animation
yeah so uh we have many many things here
um first of all we have a deadbeat
sweater I designed that skull I I made
that skull
um I I found a skull I looked at a skull
and I drew a skull and then I wrote
deadbeat over it um so hopefully you
feel cool and chill wearing this it's a
one size fits all very very big sweater
big comfy cozy sweater then we've got a
not a full wine glass with a little
gradation at the bottom you can enjoy
your combini wine with a little bit of
gold Mori encrusted on top of it so I
hope that you'll enjoy that and we have
a beautiful poster designed by Ray who
made my album jacket for unalive my
first solo album that includes uh the
altar version of Cali from the unalive
MV
um and it is super amazing it's the same
size as the your Mori one so it's super
big and it's going to look beautiful on
your wall so I hope you guys will get it
I'm looking forward to getting a bunch
of them and just putting them all over
my house then we also have the UN Alive
album vinyl right now it looks like it's
just front and back but it's actually a
six panel vinyl album so you fold it out
and you get to see all of Ray's
beautiful artwork in beautiful six panel
Glory so it's in the same format as the
year Mori album everything can be bought
individually this time
um and uh and yeah if you buy everything
together you get a special printed
letter from me with some choice words
from your boy and also a signature so
yeah here's the sweater check it out
front and back on the back you got my
little Calliope Mori logo Crest at the
top
um I I designed this this skull this
skull myself looking to the side over
there it's got a really cool neck
um let's go next
and then we've got my wine glass this is
really cool I can't wait to drink wine
out of this got my signature on it and
everything beautiful golden gradation at
the bottom it's really lovely uh next
we've got the poster check this art out
I die every time I look at it Rey's work
is just like a beautiful beautiful
painting uh so I hope you guys will
enjoy having this on your wall and next
uh is there a next got the yeah the
album that's right we've got the vinyl
and it includes every single track from
the album check it
um but like I said it's a six six panel
so you'll open it up and there will be
there will be more than just a front and
back and it's really cool you guys are
gonna love it so much
um so yeah that's all in terms of
merchandise please look forward to a
special letter from me uh it'll be a
printed letter from your boy to the
deadbeats who get the full set
um and so yeah look forward to that
please
please look forward to it um and yeah I
hope you guys enjoyed my birthday party
but I do have have one more song One
More song to sing to you guys a song
that's very close to my heart about the
world that we live in because from now
on I'm gonna be trying my best with
universal and really really gambaru from
here on out
um there's a world I want to see and um
and it's really beautiful but things
right now seem kind of dark and dreary
you know it really seems some days like
just the worst days are every day right
so um I would like to continue forward
um singing songs that have
um some kind of meaning to me whether
they be about enjoying yourself and just
having fun wacky and wild fun party
songs or songs about our world
um this song happens to be one of those
more emotional ones but let's keep
moving forward towards the world that we
want to see let's go scuffed up age
foreign
[Music]
why not give up and play the bad guy
please
[Music]
okay
it's not really surprising where are you
compromising the sun is rising a New
Horizon friendships
could I
just got this cynical mindsets why'd you
try why not give up and play the bad guy
Mommy
[Music]
believing in a world of hate is
the lights and sights and sounds of
treasures
[Music]
foreign
see you next time you
hear the rest more he's in the building
so you know you're already dead
[Music]
hi why are you still here why are you
still here go check out the capsule MV
it's happening in five minutes five
minutes on my channel go go go now go
watch the MV go watch the castle and V
goodness gracious bye go go go go go go
go why are you still here go