[Music]
the your o's waiting in the closet
tonight no way to stop she dead said I'm
giving you aight trick or Tre but now
we're all out of candy feeling just a
little sick this je ought to come in
handy I got a very just possess some
experiment bet a little dection it low
babies hiding behind your screen a a
spooky Halloween without some mythical
be that is
flashing look at those red
cheeks how
cute I'll fix that up drain all your
blood that's what you see
make o creats oh what a curs IFI stream
there's no bones your scream only show
you on Halloween are spooky or terrifi
SC your s Oh What A goty C night Mythic
witches with endless spice can escape
her Idol as might no care be Insight so
your souls will suff
bust a funky dance tonight what a spooky
scary sign hungry dinosaur just one tiny
bite please spook song If your praise
and sing not your wife I am a pumpkin
sing dong in the G will be if you're
looking for scream singing songs that
make you PE t y give you shers make you
shout just like that out ladies that is
what we're about