[Music]
hmm
do
[Music]
hmm
oh
[Music]
wow
oh
[Music]
me
wow
[Music]
oh
me
[Music]
down
me
[Music]
uh
oh
[Music]
hello my
my um
oh
[\h__\h] was the word
[Music]
hello my
bae
my bad boy yo
boy
[Music]
[\h__\h] i'm getting that spanish uh
um
pronunciation
[Music]
yes in italian it's polo not polio it's
written the same way but they say polo
not pollo maybe that is why i when i
read spanish i always pronounced it like
this before
[Laughter]
[Music]
my little chickens
uh hello
okay
[Music]
wait i need to
need to
get rid of the chair
what's that chair doing
which one is the right one
that one nice
mama
yes ah
mamma mia today i can finally use my
italian accent and nobody can say
nothing about it except the italians
[Laughter]
and then
the day has finally come
what a happy day what a wonderful happy
day
oh mamma mia
what a joyous occasion
but but
okay so
i think like
the italians
do not mind because i know many italians
and
they're good people and we're neighbors
yes they live next doors to me am i
gonna speak like those little streams
ah
they live next door to me yes sir
austria is next to
italia italia and uh yes
you need actually because of that
probably that was the reason that uh
that i
um had to learn
um
italiano
but
when i was in
in the
school uh yes i remember that one
yeah yeah yeah
lasko la scola yeah mm-hmm
[Music]
[Laughter]
uh what was it lo
[Music]
today eat
small snack
snack from a spontaneous
[Music]
[Laughter]
everybody where are my italians uh
where are my
italians
[Music]
you don't even need to tell me how to
say that i know how to say that
[Music]
oh my god
oh
hello
[Music]
oh mamma mia the little italiano that i
still remember i can finally use it
some of it at least
mamma mia hello pasta ravioli indeed
fantastic dance well thank you i would
say that at least i mean somewhere
somewhere a little bit
uh
yes
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
that's the first it just happened with
the flow
with the flow we go
mamma mia
shut up kiana just stop saying mamma mia
but at least okay unlike other people
when i think of italian language mamma
mia is not the only thing i can think of
okay
let me tell you my background on
italian language okay
um so
first of all okay
i need to slap myself can you talk
normal for once key i don't know nobody
can listen to the [\h__\h] all the time mama
me i mean i could but
uh maybe not the view is okay i talk
normal okay i try
so oh god i can't i can't ah especially
now with this music in the background
holy [\h__\h]
i looked up
italian it's italian italy on audio
stuff
had some good stuff there you want to
hear the italian accent oh mamma mia
bellissimo
good to hear that um you want me to use
the accent okay
okay
[Music]
no wait let me try to speak normal for
once mama mia
[Laughter]
so
[Music]
you know because italy is a neighboring
country
i keep on going there
um
um i don't know what's normal anymore
yeah yeah when i was younger
going on vacation
with my family with my mommy often we
went to italy several times um not only
because it was close but also my mom
really liked
italia
especially venezia
especially you know that that's a city
that is all on the water and they think
it's all okay
you need to be as chill as italian
people about it
um
[Music]
yeah
do you know any latin oh yeah i had to
study latin
in in the school i went to but then i
had so many issues with it after
studying it for one year i think or one
and a half years i dropped out of that
school and switched to a school where
latin was not necessary
because holy macaroni
uh that was that was a tough one
yeah but um uh anyway so we went to
italy often so my mom actually knew a
little bit
i think of basic i don't remember how
good she was but
as a child i remember
her
knowing at least at least some basic
words i think
i want to say she was
able to do
um
some kind of rev light conversation but
i don't know if my child brain is
remembering that wrong
but yeah i really really
uh went there often and and had some
other
um
i don't know reasons that maybe
influenced me like i really liked this
i think it's from italy right this
italian manga called
witch
you guys know it
w dot i dot t dot c dot h dot
yeah that was my favorite thing ever
back then it's like more like a comic i
guess but this is from italy
and um they sold it in in the austrian
supermarkets as well and i tried my best
to follow up on it as much as i could
ciao
thank you
yes which really famous
there it's it's it's
not continued though
is it is it still being like renewed and
stuff i wonder i feel like it ended um
they had like
um an anime too i think but i only this
is this isn't a time where actually
kibaba preferred to read over watching
something apparently because i i didn't
watch the anime
i think i only
read the comic um
what the [\h__\h] was that
i feel like i just saw a black frame for
a second was that my sixth gene
whoa what
unbelievable
2001 to 2012 you mean the anime
actually i would love to
watch the anime now
see how that turned out
um
oh yeah chunk is coming from me why why
why why no no no no mama mia trunk is
already gone before the stream chunkers
was like bonkers almost
um
um so yeah what was i saying yeah okay
so i like witch and uh i like going to
italy and um
um
years many years later
i went to a school
where
i had to study
italian
for the school
for
three years but only
two months per year which is stupid
because the thing is i went to that
school two months per year
uh for three years because it's a weird
system when you go to work for ten
months
and to school for two months it's a
special training apprenticeship that we
have here
yeah i told you guys about that before
mamma mia did you forget
is your brain spaghetti how did you drop
the spaghetti
yeah exactly my my argument was as well
how do you expect i mean i was the best
in class legit but i still told the
teacher you guys don't honestly expect
us to learn the language properly and
remember what we learned a year ago when
there's a year in between
each time we go back to school you don't
honestly expect us to remember anything
right
um
yeah so i'll say
the whole class really didn't like the
italian teacher that we had um she i
don't think she was italian but anyway
she was like
very strict
yeah
very strict but but oh well um i i still
did my best and i was apparently the
best in class which
doesn't really mean anything because i
was still shitty
i was best in class but that's only
because everyone else was so shitty so
that the the
the bar was really low
[Laughter]
yeah we take we take the
that little um award i suppose of being
number one
um i was the best of the worst exactly
but really like you can't teach someone
a language like that and i think even in
those two months
we only had italian once per week
for two months like how much are you
gonna learn
huh huh
and and i feel like the way they and
they told us the system was really bad
too like there was not really a good
pattern
to it so you know i was like teacher so
i taught myself
i told myself japanese you know and i'm
really good at the english tune i'm just
gonna say this is not how you learn the
language but you're aware of that aren't
you
now okay i wasn't like a [\h__\h] like that
but i was saying like
this is
this is that this is not a good way to
teach someone a language you shouldn't
be surprised that we're also [\h__\h] at it
but anyway
because of that i know some italian like
echola chiave camera numero
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
hotel vocabulary
oh wait why are you speaking german iris
iris no no no
this is
italiano
[Music]
secondhand piano no no no
piano second floor
piano means floor
in italian
[Music]
camera means room
and
echolakia means here's the key
so that here's the key to your room on
the second floor
yeah i mean hello i mean that's
something
very specific but
that's something and as a tourist
usable i would say
yeah
i think you want a second breakfast well
no problem with that
okay so everybody we are going to eat um
uh
we're going to eat
a
keep on forgetting that we're going to
eat la spontino from italia
and i already had a little sneak peek
into it and uh the italy snacks look
really really good
and um i know there's a lot of good
uh big
uh not a lot but there's definitely one
or two huge
um
snack companies that
come from italy
so
um
oh i'm excited
for
[Music]
[Laughter]
you guys know ferrero ever heard of
ferrero
they make so many snacks i love them all
mamma mia
all right so i have my gloves on and the
camera should be
in place so
please turn on the camera
um
behind the scenes chicken
[Music]
okay yeah bonkers kind of moved the
camera a little bit i see
uh
then let's adjust oh sure there we go
italia
in in german we say italian
and also uh
venetic venetic venetic okay now bonkers
is gone now all good don't worry about
it yes okay we should you should
probably not to see this you don't know
what you see but you should not look
here and let me
let ricardo
have a cut here okay so we're gonna
judge the italian snacks
how wonderful pelici mom
yeah i'm excited let's look at this
beautiful
scenery this is where we're going today
in our minds actually oh that is
beautiful
um
not sure
my mom went to
vinicia several times i don't know if i
joined her maybe i joined her once but
it's a long time ago so i wouldn't
remember much
so we are of course as always we have
our little booklet
uh i'm gonna start reading to you some
of the things uh that are
sure
in here and meanwhile don't look at the
snacks
and just some of the things not
everything
just just so you learn a little bit
about italy beforehand
and ciao okay so the capital of italia
is the beautiful beautiful home
home uh wait what what was the english
for that
[Music]
[Laughter]
sometimes things are too close
oh yeah yeah
and they speak italiano of course and
the inhabitants are 5 59.5 million oh my
god kfp chickens in italy
make five more million chickens and
you'll be at 60 million round that [\h__\h]
up
59.5 million that's boring let's make it
60 million go go go go go go 5 million
that's not too much you can do it come
on
[Laughter]
and then use url
thankfully and typically italian it says
is pizza pasta
[Music]
ro
rome
[Music]
sphinx and vespas
you guys call it vespas too you know
those bloomberg machines
there's
machines on two legs
the fancy ones
[Music]
yeah it's like a bike yeah
[Laughter]
oh i should get one
okay flip the page is this this one page
i never know
i think so okay
now here we have
a fun fact
with takanasi kiaras like fun flags of
sheldon koopa and amy farafala
about countries aka
italia so
oh oh yeah did you know that the
shape of italy reminds you of the shape
of a boot yes
yeah yeah
it's in the south of europe therefore
pretty warm a lot of nature um in in the
north it's a little bit more um chill
and cool because you'll also find the
alps there partially um
you'll also find a lot of the alps in
austria though
where yum yum yeah in the south you'll
have a lot of amazing trees like olive
trees and other trees that i don't know
how to translate
uh
and no no
and pizza
is one of the words
that all
are understood all over the world one of
the few words yeah
indeed
um
someone called alessandro volta
created the first batteries oh
we have to thank an italian guy for that
let's see let's see
um
an average italian person eats 26
kilograms of pasta in one year is that a
lot i don't know honestly
is that a lot 26 kilograms of pasta
that's only the pasta i suppose only the
noodles without the sauce
is that a lot
it is a lot
only yeah maybe it's actually
surprisingly not so much i don't know
i'm not sure
one month worth
i mean this is average so
yeah
i mean i mean maybe that is surprisingly
low and and telling you that italians
don't only eat pasta
so i think that's a good lesson to learn
um
oh there's a there's a um a fountain
called trevi fountain in rome
which
um
daily
is being blessed with
about 300 coins per day
like people throw in 300 coins per day
into that fontana di trevia
fontana de trevi
i see i work near there oh cool well
maybe one day i'll throw in a coin if
you work near there do you throw in a
coin every day
do you guys have this this culture of
throwing in coins and fountains all over
the world
because we have it here in austria too
but i mean i don't i haven't really done
that in many many many many many many
years
[Music]
yeah yeah
no
yes that's a thing in america too same
when you say
not here in thailand it's a thing in the
usa
mostly yes that's a littering problem
i think if it was really that much of a
littering problem at least it's
contained in the fountain you can always
clean it up if it was much of a
littering problem i think the people of
the city would put like like signs in
front of the fountains
and say don't don't drop in your [\h__\h]
coins but i think
somewhere at some point when the
fountains are getting cleaned out they
can at least see that some kind of
donation to the city
and probably yeah take it use it for the
cleaning funds probably it will be used
up all for that
but i mean it's basically a donation to
the city because i mean who else is
taking the money out of the fountain
i've never thought even thought about
taking putting my hand into one of those
fountains and just taking a coin but
has anyone ever done that into the chat
[Laughter]
the cost of sorting oh yeah because it's
probably might be a lot of different um
currencies because of the tourists being
the mostly mostly the ones who throw in
the coins and
as a kid you did it i think as a kid i
did uh but you need that you need that
pocket money when your mommy doesn't
give it to you
yeah which is five euros per week
i can't buy enough
spontino's
from that snacks
but i mean
i don't know it's i never thought about
this that deeply but it's good to think
that
the city kind of receives at least
something from it
it's basically a donation bucket
yeah um the next fun fact is the story
of pinocchio
uh was
it doesn't say originally but i suppose
they're saying originally behind the
lines
uh in between the lines uh the story of
pinocchio was originally maybe
originally a told in an italian
newspaper
or were published in an italian
but i don't know the original is added
by me
i don't know
and
what
in italy
a guy
let his cat
inherit about 10 million euros
first of all can i be the cat and second
of all
if i had 10 million euros
[Music]
would i do okay i am a cat lady yes but
i don't think i would give 10 million
euros to my cat
aristocats
grandissimo
wow
wow who the [\h__\h] was that well he must
have been so lonely
it had no one else
probably no relatives alive anymore
and and the only
thing or something that loved him and
gave him love was his kitty cat
wow but what did the cat do with all
that money
i wanted it like what what
i need to know more about this story
i heard about that story really it's the
first time i hear about it
italian
is
[Music]
my it's again
that's amazing diamond plated litter box
[Music]
no it wouldn't be one of those little
boxes anymore it would be one of those
little robots that spin
you know
[Music]
i
what it would be oh my god how do i even
say that number
yen
oh my god
1 billion
1.4 billion yen oh my god
the litter itself is full of diamonds
yeah the cat is [\h__\h] diamonds too
anyway like literally uh there's uh
there's a little map
more or less of must-see
must see places the first one is rome
yes i have actually
never been to rome i've been to many
places in italy but usually you know
just like to the beach
and um
mostly it was also close to austria so
more like um often more to the north
i should visit rome yeah
it says
of course we start with the
eternal city
[Music]
even back in the times when it was
called imperium romanum
this city was considered as very
influential because from here on
uh in the antique
the roman empire uh
took over half of europe
look are you listen are you appreciating
my speech translation while i'm
literally reading what i'm reading
um
today this big city
uh
is filled with impressive art
history
uh architecture and culture
and you should take a look at the
colosseum where back in the day
gladiators and wild animals
was fighting we're fighting against each
other or the fontana di trevi the most
famous fountain in the world
like i don't even know what it looks
like let me look it up now i'm curious
we're having a lot of chitchat today
before eating huh
uh which is good because uh we're not
talking
in the next couple streams because it's
all collabs i think
oh dad is the oh
oh i suppose i've probably seen it in
pictures before wow
[Music]
oh my god can i take a bath in that
i want to bathe
it there
the water actually looks
pretty
looks like a pool
i want the bait in the fontana
[Music]
you may not
want
wow i see a photo where there's also
like lines
several rows of people standing in front
of it like
you really have to squeeze yourself in
to throw a coin in there oh my god
wow
i guess i've never seen it before this
is in the room
never been to a room
oh wait the whole
like place in front of that building is
covered
okay
what these turns that jump into the
fountain and then complain when they get
arrested oh yeah i say i want to babe on
it but of course i would ask for
permission first and then not get it but
i wouldn't do such a thing you
understand right
yeah yeah yeah not very albanian ella
fontana okay okay i understand i'm not
allowed to take a bath in the in the
fontana okay
me me
anyway second stop would be venezuela
and i'm not gonna tell you everything
about it but um
yeah you know you know
the city with all the water and the
boats yeah
and another one they say is florence i
don't know what the english way of
florencia
how do you say florentina or flor flor
florence maybe florence not florence
okay fiorenza florence
italian is probably your fiance
and then english is probably florence
okay
uh oh my sixteen upgrade yeah i'm doing
fine it's just my
my upper arm is
just a little bit of a horse
armhort
[Music]
but besides that i'm all good i had a
um
a good day
i
went what did i do yeah i i i waited for
some
to receive some
furniture
uh
in the beginning of the day and then um
i i went to get my my 6g
then um i did a little bit of some more
small small shopping
and i got that
oh that amazing banana split frappuccino
from starbucks frappuccino is by the way
also an italian word chino anything with
chino is italian
no scooter writing this time no no
back to the good old uber
um
but yeah i had also also had a uh
for the first time in a long time i had
a
um
my beloved my beloved crispy chicken
from burger king i missed you my beloved
sorry i haven't eaten you for a long
long long long time
[Music]
yeah so anyway and the last city that
they recommend is uh verona
which is like kind of like a middle-aged
city
with lots of small streets
uh
[Music]
yeah yeah i don't really know much about
this city
wonderful but i guess i've heard the
name before and now finally
finally hello let's eat the
[Music]
uh once again
we have some potato chips that we start
off with what is this pasta tina pepe
[Music]
uh what is what are those little
red is that pepper
pepper and
lime on the pepperoni
[Music]
oh what the hell is that the good
question lime and pepper
rose pepper oh
wait i'm not really in the mood for
um
for
potato chips right now but okay let's
eat them uh the brand i've never seen
the brand before but it sounds like a
italian brand
italian company probably right i mean i
don't i don't doubt that we have issues
finding brands to put in the italian
books i'm sure there's more than enough
yes okay
are you gonna see fonts don't look
don't look at my fancies
don't look okay
oh
oh oh
okay okay i'm getting excited about this
bontino sorry
hi by the way hi
i'm back with my white gloves
hopefully not too many cat hairs on it
sorry sorry it smelled good i'm gonna
dip dip into it
uh
yes
itadakimasu
wow
[Music]
that is a
hmm
remember the spain
um chips where i said that they taste
very
what's the word what was the word
rustical
what did i say what did i say
[Music]
that the spanish ones went with the ham
and there was yeah rustic
um
now this this is the opposite these
chips surprisingly taste kind of
refreshing
refreshing but like
i'm not sure like it's not it's not bad
but i'm not sure if this really fits as
a chip's flavor
i mean i would eat it because i like the
i like the the the thinness and the
texture of the potato chips
um
let me eat some more
yeah it's a bit strange
i mean obviously they wanted to put a
special flavor in there and this is very
special
um
[Music]
thanks for the membership
hmm
[Music]
it's kind of weird
the lime the lime is just
very strong
and fresh but like
it's a weird choice of taste to put on
potato chips you know what i mean
[Laughter]
lime and pepper is theojo no standards
what does that mean
you join our standards you like it do
italian people really like lime pepper
potato chips
[Music]
they're unusual in my opinion yeah
yeah yeah no it's not sour no not at all
but
see
see ya
what okay hmm
well
is it like sea salt and vinegar no
no
but anyway i mean
how much are we gonna give this
gonna be honest it's a very
odd flavor um i'm gonna give it a
six out of ten we're starting low but
i'm sure that everything else will be
amazing
[Music]
i can count
i want to get to know an italian vetu i
wonder if there are
any anyone's
[Music]
there's a drink here let's ask usho this
is a in a weird packaging again but okay
uh i think this is the drink right yeah
yeah
um
i still let's go italians you guys just
get me
italians mama mia we love we love iced
tea don't we but it's so it's like a
yogurt uh um
packaging like i i wait maybe it is no
it's not yogurt but you put the straw
there on that circle
[Laughter]
[Music]
peach um tea i should put this into the
fridge but you know we gotta taste test
it so then i can put it in there
afterwards wait where is the
gusta where is the
[Music]
where is this trail
italians do you didn't know this one
where is
where's the straw
or am i
huh why is this in the box
[Music]
this thing is a straw
[Laughter]
okay okay okay okay
how do they how do they sell it though
like wouldn't normally something like
this be like attached with some glue or
something
um
oh okay
i mean you honestly can't go wrong with
icy but let me look at the expiration
date
okay we're good 20 23 very good
now i just have to open this
straw thingy somehow
there we go
very hard to do [\h__\h] with uh
with um gloves as always but okay
now right in the middle there we go
bulls eye wow sasuke
let's drink
[Music]
oh man i love iced tea so much
thank you italia for putting the best
drink my favorite drink into the snack
box
i appreciate it 10 out of 10 10 out of
the edgy sodium
number i knew it before i drank it i
mean i mean i mean
yes i stay mama mia
[Music]
yeah
it should have been a bigger bigger one
though a whole bottle please
okay
uh what is this there's many what is
this why is there so many why do you
give me the same thing over and over
again was there a bug or something we
have four of them i think
no we have five wait what
no what one
did was there like a bug which is it one
two
three four five
six six six
what what about all the other things
they're in there too though right
what
what is this why why is it worth putting
six of them in there no come look come
on
barretta
uh-huh
you know that the fonts and the the
graphic design
that italy uses for stack snacks
feels really familiar because um they
all seem to have like the same vibe
maybe they want you to share maybe
okay
i mean hopefully this is good because
then i can eat all of the other ones
yeah but this is good that there's like
they're at least separately packaged so
you know with with these um
snack reviews i open up so many things
just take a bite and then some of them i
just don't want to eat all the same day
you know so i have to throw away a lot
of things often um but when they're
separately packaged like this then i can
keep some for another time okay let me
eat this
quack
[Music]
so
inside we have
a kind of uneven
chocolate bar
somewhat flat
i will bite into it right now
[Music]
mm-hmm
it's okay
it's pretty good
it's chocolate and and a cookie
and some nuts
is it nuts i don't know
or just more cookie
cookies
milk chocolate by the way
[Music]
it's just
normal
i think i would like it even more if um
if there was some like a layer of milk
in it or so no
[Music]
but not bad so i'm gonna give it a
i'm gonna do it
go to snacks mama mia
which one is good or maybe this
maybe this looks like a christmas cookie
[Music]
i will eat this it's called
a bon pong
pot
oh let's go
you guys know plan this deal this will
be a good good one good yes
wait what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] false advertisement
actually
i saw this originally
on the website too and i was looking
forward to this because i was like what
the [\h__\h] is this is this a japan box um
look
the drink here
the drink was supposed to be something
with pokemon on it
but they sent me a normal version
where's the pokemon
where is the pokemon
pokemon
score bunny where's my score bunny
outrage mamma mia
okay let me eat the chocolate
oh mama mia cute
[Music]
uh
mamma mia
[Music]
look at these little little round babies
oh cute
okay
uh you turn them around and they look
this beautiful oh
wow
karino
jocotino
[Music]
okay
i'm gonna eat now
[Music]
oh
yeah
it almost tastes like there's like a
cream inside that almost tastes like
nutella
very chocolatey
[Music]
so the bottom is very crunchy and
there's a soft cream inside and then the
top layer is like a hard chocolate
in the whole wide world from italy
nutella
and let me eat the last bite one moment
no more
[Laughter]
wow
wow my whole mouth is chocolate now
[Music]
yes i have water let me drink the
water oh
[Music]
okay
cool i have one more i'm gonna eat that
one later
oh my god we're speeding through them i
need a speeding ticket
let's take the one that you don't see
but it's a snack that like the whole
font and all that looks so familiar from
different snacks like kinder bueno uh
but this one i've never eaten before
i've never seen before but it's orange
and oh my god it's gonna be so good wow
love fiesta classical
[Music]
i am about to cry probably because it's
gonna be so good and i'm gonna be so sad
that they don't sell us here in austria
for some reason even though they sell so
many other things from ferreira but why
not these the mamma mia is orange i love
orange with chocolate combined don't you
get me guys do you understand
[Laughter]
[Music]
did you see that video oh my god we need
to talk about this too but um
did you see my who
calm down
okay
let me show you this
a little advertisement in the middle of
the stream
whole life production x valkyrie real
query ralph yuri need to learn how to
pronounce the valkyrie connector
um
i was waiting to tell you about this
today
uh i am one of the four chosen people
to be actually for once
put into the game it's not only that
we're advertising it as a sponsored
stream you know playing a game like we
usually do in these terms
but
they actually like designed those
characters and implemented us into the
games into the game maybe some of you
saw already um apparently there's
advertisements going around on youtube
like videos as an ad
um where you already see a preview of
the the 3d models like there's a there's
a chibi 3d model of each of us in that
design
fighting yeah i don't think they
officially showed it off yet but it's
already in advertisements and it's so
cute so cute
so we're actually in the game which is
why this was so exciting for me and it's
been in the works for a long long time
already
um
with other like gotcha games or whatever
these phone games or so that we have
advertised in the past um
you know it's fun to advertise them but
it's like so much more special when they
actually put the effort in and are
interested so much that they want to put
you into the game so this is for me
really really really really really
special
um and uh you see the
on my weekly schedule
have you seen it i uploaded it yesterday
haven't streamed since so
maybe some of you haven't seen it yet
um i mean let me put it up
no no we're not done yet by the way
with eating i just want to tell you guys
about this
um so here we have uh on friday
yeah it's uh 2 a.m for me but
this was um it was even like
like this or at six a.m or so and i was
like
uh
probably better to stay up later for me
more realistic than getting up early so
i was like okay let's do it at 2am
but collab with inna is on my channel we
are doing um
i guess we're playing a game like i
don't know much yet about like how it's
gonna work to be honest but um me and
ina are doing it on my channel i'm
hosting it i was chosen to host it and
honestly i'm like why why why why why me
why me i'm like a nervous mama mia
i'm nervous
yeah
no i wrote it like this because i i
didn't want to ride like plus one day
because there was no space okay just you
know you understand you guys are
intelligent chickens right
you can uh imagine that 26 means 24 plus
two
hmm not the first time you've seen this
huh
[Music]
i wanted to still put it on the same day
actually that was the real reason
actually yeah because i didn't want to
didn't want to put it on the saturday
for me it's basically still friday and
for est as well so yeah anyway
that's happening and from why i came to
this uh uh farts now thought process let
me help you out there with that uh on
the valkyrie connect twitter they
released videos of each of us
um this was the video that i was having
trouble with the other day
um and the one that i took on
on that day remember that one was
actually um deemed
ng because like
didn't follow
the rhythm but it was really difficult
so then they provided me with a better
guide
and then i was actually able to take it
properly anyway so in the one that la
fordasa took
she said her first impression of me
in one word was orange okay so this is
this is why we're here
this this is
the connection that i've made
[Laughter]
anyway this is really exciting let me
let me keep this up on the screen
because i'm so excited to be part of
this group of four people chosen to be
implemented into a game i think this is
okay correct me if i'm wrong but is this
isn't this the first time
isn't this the first one the first time
no
no i mean me not not whole life me
chiwawa
for kiwawa yes i mean for kiwawa
yeah oh mamma mia
[Music]
they just had my song but i was not
really like in the game
this is the first time
that's so exciting guys
yeah yeah yeah yeah
i a sprite yeah but you know i mean here
we have like
everything like a different outfit and
then turned into 3d
and wow
maybe even voice
and there's something one more thing
that's really special about this
uh that i can't say yet
i can't say yet but
[Music]
there's something i'm really looking
forward to
this this is getting even more
interesting so um
at least for for the for the
participants ina piccolos and me
uh oh no no just for us not not so much
for you guys
so more of a personal thing um
anyway
let us continue i want to eat this now
let's eat this
for more uh on this you will probably
find out on the friday stream with inna
on my channel
yeah cliffhanger
it's just for me but my own happiness
oh mama me
mamma mia this uh expiration date this
month mamma mia you're cutting it close
mamma mia
okay end of this month
well i am here now to eat it now
okay let's eat that easter
oh it looks uh
like someone already sat on it mama mia
it has been mistreated a little bit but
it's okay i will still love you
[Music]
oh
yeah i taste the alcohol a little bit
like really really really really really
really slight
okay now the aftertaste
is a bit stronger maybe that's why
they don't sell it in austria
it's more something that the italians uh
appreciate
[Music]
because i am really really sensitive
when it comes to
um
alcohol taste
it has a little bit of this like burning
sensation
[Music]
oof
that kind of ruins it for me
without that it would have been amazing
because the choc i was wondering where
the orange taste will be
if it's gonna be like in that cream in
between but no
it's uh in the chocolate and i like that
i really like when when the when milk or
dark chocolate has a slight taste of
orange and it has that in this case but
oh
yeah the the alcohol really unnecessary
for me it's getting pretty strong
my whole mouth feels like it's warming
up
[Laughter]
mamma mia mamma mia italians why you
like alcohol so much mamma mia
let me drink the iced tea
i'm getting drunk
yeah maybe that's why it's it wasn't
popular popular enough to leave italy
and come to
austria and germany and so on to the
supermarkets maybe that's it
not because it alcohol is not allowed
but because it probably
isn't so much for the general
children
uh
consumers um
ah
well
if there wasn't the alcohol i would give
it the edgy
10 out of 10 but they all go home
sorry mama mia you guys know me
i don't like the alcohol
i will try to not lower the rating too
much just because of that so let's say
unodor
okay
i don't want to be too too strict
i don't want to be too strict
but that's me being kind of kind
besides that it would have been so good
because i i love a nice biscuit snack
with the orange chocolate that's like
such a great combination
okay excuse me
it's okay
it's okay no
problem
yeah yeah all right next
snack what is this oh what is this a
cute thing
there's a
weird squirrel thingy
on it no no it's not that's not a
squirrel what is it is that a squirrel
no it's a beaver wait it's a beaver i
think because of the teeth and the
tail
never seen it
it's a beaver when are we getting a
beaver youtuber with um teeth sticking
out like that
never seen well yeah this seems like a
more um underground snack uh
it seems to be oh like those puppy race
pups race race pups isn't this race
buffs or rice puffs
what are reese puffs are reese puffs
rice puffs but this raised my face pops
inside
[Laughter]
them
raised belts
you guys you guys did that to me i
didn't even know the meme and i just
sang it normally in my karaoke and then
you guys are like wait
you don't want to beat him i'll put him
up just while i'm just trying to sing a
maroon 5 song and everyone in the chat
is like
[Music]
[Laughter]
ah someone open up this for me mama me i
can't know ah i did oh
oh wow
wow oh
manny
oh something fell off but manny race
puffs
oh that's the back side
the front side looks normal in the
backside
night and day
i'm telling ya
this is what you call get more
we got boy but we're chocolate
wow
[Music]
you know those um
those
um those rice
rice uh reese puff rice puff waffles
with the chocolate a really thin layer
of chocolate on top of it
you know those
you know there the chocolate versus
rice puffs a balance
is like
chocolate is like
10 to 20
now here
now here is the other way around
and not so much i mean you look at it
and you see so many rice puffs but once
you put it um in your mouth and taste it
it feels like the chocolate there's like
so much chocolate like i said it's one
of those rice puff waffle thingies rice
krispies but with a lot more chocolate
like okay it may not even look like that
like it's that much but the chocolate is
definitely
overpowering while you still have the
puffiness
of the reese pastries pastries puffs
it feels like the opposite yeah
but it still has that crispiness and the
chocolate taste is really good too so i
will give this uh una do it
um
[Music]
7.5 out of 10
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you for being here mamma mia my
dad hope you don't hate me yet
for acting like this
but i love you
i love italia
i love you guys thank you for existing
you guys are so cool i want to go to
italy again
i'm enjoying the iced tea
mamma mia the iced tea i love it so much
got felicity
shut up
these are not minky mouse gloves what
the [\h__\h]
ah but they honestly they're not very um
my fingers look like sausages in them
they're not very
flattering
okay i'm telling you my hands are not
that sausaging like what is these
they're pretty thin but still like the
way they are um
soon sewn together makes it look like i
have sausage fingers sometimes fingers i
would eat them up eat them up eat them
up if i had those fingers
worst thing
[Laughter]
what the [\h__\h]
i was about is say that those are
[\h__\h] ps5 buttons and this is ps5
limited edition the game girl of ian
i'm gaming even when i eat chocolate ps5
i can't eat this this is too special
this is so cool
do you know the snack my italian friends
you know
i mean the snack not the limited edition
just the ringo ring
is this a well known
yes
i prefer the vanilla version uh-huh
italian oreos ooh
well are they normally just flat
instead of having the the the buttons on
it are they just flat or do they have
something
[Music]
wait wait a second they robbed me of the
pokemon ice tea
but
um
see here i see the original they they at
least gave me a special version of this
originally apparently it was supposed to
be a different one and it just has an r
yeah as you guys say it has an r on it
normally
but i got the special one to make up for
the lack of pokemon okay okay okay okay
okay now we're talking you're making up
for
some
lacking of special stuff okay okay okay
well let me eat this wow i'm not
sponsored by ps5 yet
but
wow
double double c is how do you pronounce
c again
[Music]
[\h__\h]
huh
which one
which one was you say that was right but
[Music]
[\h__\h] you
and if there was some italian text here
[Music]
i think that means uh so much a free
three times the fun or enjoyment in one
single
uh
you know the other one means like
something like
yep
never mind i'm not gonna translate the
second
sentence because because i don't have
time for this
i'm not on translator duty oh no it's
broken a little bit oh no
i'm so sorry i'm so obnoxious of my
italian accent
[Music]
um
there's some
crack in the x
the the o is okay but the back the the
back one is also a little bit broken
[Music]
what no the hole was not okay because
the o
also has a
little bit of
oh no moment
they're all broken
now that i look at them they're all
broken
maybe that's why i got these
just kidding
okay
smell is oh
wait that seems familiar i've had that
smells like a different snack that i had
in austria before
okay
hmm
[Music]
yeah yeah okay okay i i taste the cacao
very good
[Music]
they're always broken
really good yeah it reminds me of oreos
indeed oh there's some cat hair
um
[Music]
yeah there's um there's like um a normal
biscuit uh and then there's some
chocolate
glue inside and then there's a cacao
flavored biscuit on top
yummy they're pretty good yeah i like
the taste um
i wish i could remember what other
cookie that was i had before that kind
of um tastes like this am i thinking of
oreos i don't think so not necessarily
you win the prize if you find a full not
broken pack really oh my god oh i need
to go on a on a quest on a search for
the non-broken wrinkles cookies
i'm gonna give this a oh no
no no no
[Music]
i'm having every time i do these snack
box reviews i stress myself to eat fast
and munch fast and but still talk
because i hate silence awkward silence
so i
i always get problems breathing
oh man
okay next time
i want this one because it's milka
colored it's milka color it's the same
company yes
i love milka um
this is
ah those cookies we have them in austria
but i don't think i've ah
maybe i've tried them before
uh
oh i don't quite remember but i think
yeah they're they're they're decent yeah
yeah
everything milka does is good i love
milka
um
i love milka
this seems to be kind of a uh what's
half a
cereal cookie with um a very
thin layer of milk chocolate milk
yes okay let's dig in
yeah i mean it may be a swiss company
but i feel like milka we're sharing that
in europe okay every country in europe
loves milk and chocolate okay so there
is
um three
three
cookies in there
i'm gonna be honest
like cereal cookies and stuff like that
anything with just normal cereals like
like i don't know porridge for example
it's not really my favorite thing but at
least it's covered in chocolate so
[Music]
take a bite out of all of them at once
what you do not
[Music]
even makes me like the things that i
don't like
oh yeah
[Music]
so you cut up
yeah
yeah yeah
[Music]
as i said i don't like cereals that much
but milka just you you can't go wrong
with milka so i'll give it up we're
gonna do
[Music]
um
milka always hates yeah i know milka
isn't
uh italian but also like if i were to
put together an austrian snack books
i would really have to force myself to
not put milka in it because if you grow
up in austria
and this is why i partially understand
putting things into a snack box that are
not originally from that country this
one i get it because
i grow up
with milk i grew i grew up with milk
eating milk or chocolate all the time
for me
it is
very much austrian chocolate even though
it's not originally from austria but
like huh
[Music]
i think every child in austria
connects
milka with their childhood is one of the
most popular chocolates here you see
many many many many layers of shelves
with milk and chocolate like all kinds
of i don't know about america do you
guys have milk or chocolate
there or is it like
well known
because we have so many different
versions of mecha chocolate on our
shelves in the supermarkets
kinder as well
kinder chocolate as well
rita spot too and lind as well but but
lint is more like i don't know a bit
more expensive than milka this is also a
thing why it's so popular with children
because it's more cheap
[Music]
never seen it no
not really
mamma mia
that's illegal
i guess it's more of a european thing
yeah because i i don't really remember
seeing much of it in in japan too when i
lived in japan i really wanted to eat
milk or chocolate but i could well
barely find anything
the only only
spot in in a store that sells
like overseas snacks
yeah anyway that was a good one
let's eat this one because we've been
looking at it for a while
interesting
it looks like sour candy
and uh
some of them are like green orange oh my
wait they look like candy corn a little
bit
wait is that what they're trying to make
it look like the candy corn
don't have candy corn in austria
never seen her before
oh you're like fratella
virgin nutella
no
okay i'm
opening it in
in
in a weird way
okay
oh the smell is good
i'm gonna go for the the orange green
one
come on come on okay so this
very squishy
[Music]
wow
what is so
how do i describe this
it's so squishy
and fruity
[Music]
it's not really that that's um
sour
it's like marshmallow texture yeah
whoa
hmm
[Music]
all that sugar oh my god oh my god it's
eating me up
you know what else is squishy and fruity
try saying it out loud say it
what else is squishy and fruity
what are you trying to say
hmm
[Music]
i'm guessing you want to say me but i
don't really understand how i'm squishy
and fruity
[Music]
i don't i don't get it
explain yourself
where did you go where did you go bottom
fragger
[Music]
are you hiding in the user room
i
see
okay okay i'll give this one
i tell you guys this every time like
these kind of uh sweets
the
what do you call these
non-chocolate
sweets i don't really buy much i used to
like them as a child more nowadays i
don't really eat that much but but okay
i wouldn't buy it anymore but i will i
will give it a fair and square
uh
um
rating
caramel gummies yeah i'm talking about
gummies
gummy sweets
[Music]
because it's pretty damn good
even if i wouldn't buy it i was just so
damn good
yeah
oh apparently there was a chance that i
would get like a yogurt version
i think
no like a koala version
i want the corner version
there's a gelatin
gelatin free koala version that you can
get maybe by chance
[Music]
but there are no koalas in austria so
maybe that's why i didn't get it
in australia version
okay there's not much left actually up
is that the last one
that's the last thing
oh no it's the last thing mamma mia it's
uh
fancies you guys have been eyeing them
for a while i know i know i know
what are these potentials
they feel
the whole package feels very
full
uh what is this
i don't know what this is but apparently
it's very well known
finale the final snack it's the finals
[Laughter]
[Music]
cheese chips
i tried to smell the bag and
my [\h__\h]
is very strong mamma mia
oh my god i keep on smelling it's just
so strong
so holy [\h__\h] but i have to say the
volume wow they're not joking they're
like the whole bag is filled up to the
very very very maximum
[Music]
mate
okay
i've said this in previous reviews
cheese snacks are not my favorite but
you guys love the the fancies apparently
so it says something like these
looks puffy
huh
[Music]
oh my god it tastes like those
cheese balls
and it and the texture is the same it's
just not round it's just
in this shape
the more you eat the better they get
it tastes like those cheese balls
remember to lick your fingers i can't
i'm not gonna lick my glove
okay the smell
is i think stronger than the taste
[Music]
i'm gonna eat one more
huh
it's cheese cheese balls
oh my god no yeah okay the second one i
like more than the first one
oh oh
oh mama mia maybe i like the third one
even more let me try another one
it does get better
[Music]
and so it begins
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
oh okay
wow you have got the
or don't look at this advertisement no
no don't don't dare look at it i'm not
being sponsored so we're not we're not
advertising anything here
no no
no no no no no
no don't don't look at it
only look at it if i'm sponsored
[Laughter]
but wait i have to read read to you now
because we have a quiz italiano
my friends are you ready for the quiz
let me put my my my censorship
[Music]
[Laughter]
this drive is so tiny i get such little
tiny sips
do you hear that sounds
this is
[Music]
la piccolo quiz
piccolo la quiz piccola piccola queen
[Music]
okay
okay sometimes i have to say sometimes
the recipes that they put at the end on
the last page are kind of questionable
like
really is this this you have a chance to
put something
on the last page a recipe and this is
what you do but okay this one i agree
i guess
before i tell you the quiz you want to
know what the
what the
uh
recipe is
you might want to try making these one
day
amaretti
[Music]
that's a good recipe to put in there i
would say yeah marathi cookies i like
them
have you guys had them before
[Music]
where's the pesky recipe what the peach
recipe how to make a peach uh get a
garden number one put peach
pit into earth and then wait just wait
good luck that's your recipe lasagna
recipe and they knew that i don't need
it because i'm the master of lasagna
they're almond flavored yeah i love
almonds
[Music]
they're kind of like a dry cookie i
really like it but any cookie is kind of
surprising no not necessarily i don't
like these cookies i haven't eaten them
in a long time
okay question
we need quiz music
and quiz lights you know like um do you
know um the the tv show that's like who
will you become a millionaire uh i used
to love watching that when i was younger
and i was telling myself one day i'll be
on that show and become rich because
even if you drop out very early like
after the fifth question and i was like
oh come on i can get five questions
correctly then you still get like what
ten thousand and i was like holy [\h__\h]
i'm [\h__\h] rich if i have ten thousand
uh bucks in my bank account hello
i mean
i mean that's
more than
the average person has in their bank
account so i mean
yeah i wanted to be on that show one day
who wants to be a millionaire yeah there
is a german there was actually uh there
was two
there were two of those in german tv i
think
there was like a more of a german one
and more of a one that's more
i think maybe more austrian
[Music]
have you seen inflation numbers
now
what what but still
what gary scotty in whole alive what are
you talking about gary's uh is that the
millionaire the who will be millionaire
guy
uh in italy
you have a show like that and that's the
the mc the host or so
that's
gary scotty
[Music]
oops
what is that
italian television presenter uh-huh
what former member of the italian
parliament television presenter and
actor marijuana so he did everything
basically
why do you are you guys asking for him
to join whole life
why because he does everything
i don't know by that logic we could have
all kinds of people in the whole life
[Laughter]
[Music]
in whole talk i should interview him
italian kunta
don't even get me started
okay
uh i need to i need to write the quiz
for you guys first question are you
ready
uh
oh
uh oh dear
uh
one italian
i'm writing the answers first
what
i feel awkward for even writing this
down gets rid of
the what do you even call it an english
again
oh i don't i don't even want to write
this
let me
write okay
you guys are confused aren't you
what are these answers
uh
okay so here are the answers italians
can you guess the question wait uh wait
wait wait
wait damn it
ah ah [\h__\h] this one is too long
um
[Music]
uh
uh how do i
it's too long the answer is too long
okay well let's do it like this
okay the question is
uh uh
at what event
[Music]
is the
colosseum in rome being lit up for 48
hours
brightly
i'm questioning the choices of answers
here
[Laughter]
okay okay i would say probably two when
italy becomes world champion they don't
say what but they probably mean like
soccer
champion
probably i would say it's that
world champion with what exactly a good
question but maybe it's anything maybe
it is world champion at anything really
what i would say is soccer in general oh
well
um the answer is
what
[Music]
the answer is b
what
when
a country
anywhere in the world
gets rid of the
r.i.p penalty
the italian cluster how often does that
yeah how nowadays how often does that
happen nowadays
why is why is italy celebrating that
why is it what
what
that's nice like yeah
why are they celebrating
because the colosseum maybe was a place
where people died often back in the day
when they had uh
the gladiators fight against
animals
or the other way or or glad
normal people versus gladiators and
normal people versus animal animals was
that the thing
but that's still weird
uh but okay you do you
that was
there even there's not many italians in
the chat or
because you know the app most of the
people voted for world champion which
was what i thought was was gonna be it
too
or even italians don't really know the
answer to this
like the average italian
okay well
interesting
i would think whenever they become world
champion or even my second answer would
have been when the italian president
dies that would that would have been my
second answer but okay well that's a
weird question okay a weird thing i'm
i'm gonna have to look that up later
um
second question
[Music]
okay
um
underwear
guess what the question is this time
hat
socks this is fun you guys can guess the
question first
and don't listen listen don't vote
what does an italian
wear on new year's eve in the color red
because it's it
apparently gives you luck
i would say underwear though
underwear probably huh
red underwear for new years
or socks
not not a hat
red underwear probably
and then they're gonna show it to their
to the new year's case person
afterwards not unprompted of course but
you know red underwear can be very very
sexy
yes right so
it's not only for getting good luck for
the coming year but maybe it's for
getting lucky on them
be prepared
that seems very italian to me like uh
you need to be prepared okay the answer
is yes underwear
ah
bellissimo okay
i can barely see more wonderful
uh
wow okay next question
next question is one for
144 million
um
one
point four
[Music]
a fountain
wait a second what what's
in
english billion
but we have a billion and
we do have billion in
in germany
okay
billion million is billion oh
okay um
or 14 billion
so many numbers
okay
the question
is how many
espressos is [\h__\h]
are being drunk in italy per
year
oh my god those are big numbers
i will say 1.4
but that's a lot that's
that's a lot
well let me let me look up first
how many
inhabit heads does why do i ride like
this i could just look up italy and it
will probably show me uh does italy have
59 59 59.10 million
59.10
uh-huh
if every
one of them
sips one espresso per morning
for
uh one whole every day in one whole year
well i can't do that math right now
well okay i'll just say 1.4 billion
let's see if we're lucky
[Music]
[Laughter]
what's wrong with me today
14 billion and they only
have
almost 60 million people in italy in the
population
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
yeah i mean they love they love coffee
but wow especially espresso wow
damn i mean i don't even drink coffee
okay
next question
what
up do i really have to type all of this
out
and that's not even i think that one has
an english version program
uh-huh i'm gonna type all of this
okay you guys the next poll will be
no poll i just ask you
in which italian region
uh is the garda
lake
it's always so confusing because um in
german lake is c
c
which sounds so similar to c
but c in english is ocean so i always
have to you know
concentrate you guys you guys say
lombardia this is probably correct the
answers would have been here something
like a in
real
don't know what that is in english
uh or be entrentino venezia and
lombardai or c in pmo emilia romagna and
ligurian
yeah but it seems to be lombardia
uh yes correct
uh okay now the next question i will
type down again
uh oh you thought we're gonna learn some
italiano
[Music]
can you
um
okay the question is
the question is what do you call the
summer vacation the holidays in which
many big companies close
okay let me let me tell you
my italian skills
say
fair ago
[Laughter]
because
it is being currently voted at 75 oh
it's going down sixty one percent what's
going on
i say fair ago
[Laughter]
because obviously i speak
um
italian yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah thumbs
what is the answer it must be fair ago
um question number five see okay
[Music]
okay
one more one last question
i'm not cheating
you guys know nothing about italy that's
not true so far we always win we have
always won the answers oh no that's not
true the first one what the [\h__\h] was
with that huh why did you guys not know
the answer
[Music]
okay
um
next question
chanel
[Music]
chanel because that sounds very french
to me and the rest sounds
italian to me the question is which one
is not
an italian brand
it must be chanel chanel is french right
but moschino is italian versace sounds
italian to me too
that's chanel i mean come on
baby boppity booby doo boo
it is chanel
i know everything we don't even have to
leave this poll up for too long we all
know the answer
sorry guys i'm impatient i only gave you
like 10 seconds to vote
yes
easy peasy
let me clap for you
okay
now
that was it
that was it ah fun i love i love these
snack box reviews thank you everybody
once again for joining uh me in one of
these snack box reviews i actually don't
know what the next one will be
um the next one will be in june but i i
don't know what's coming this time
looking forward to it though
i won't i can tell you let me
[Music]
let me look it up
well let's see what's the next
um the next one
i'll show you we'll show you so
[Music]
it doesn't say yet i think
i don't think it's on here
it's going backwards we're in october
september
august august 2021 was japan yo
what's
k-a-n-n-2022 what month is that is this
website drunk
[Music]
okay i'm not sure
i'm not sure but that month doesn't
exist in german language so
what
i had too much alcoholic chocolate
now let's be honest and unspirit let's
be real that probably did absolutely
nothing to me um but
but uh i always act drunk
now i i i have had many occasions where
someone would ask me you were you drunk
just because i was a little bit
energetic but i don't drink alcohol so
people who know me would never ask me
that
i think the website is drunk yeah
absolutely smashed the website is
smashed
[Music]
anyway thank you everybody and we're
gonna read super chats um but i want to
say thank you for
coming everybody especially the italians
it's always nice to have
people representing the country uh of
where the snacks are from
in the audience if you missed some part
go back to the beginning in the archive
later and check out my other reactions
to the snacks
and and yeah hopefully um you know you
guys are my neighbors so hopefully we'll
be able to visit italy again sometime
um maybe um maybe in the winter maybe
i'll go to
rome
because i've never been to rome hmm
i think in the wintertime it would be
nice where it's more chill yeah i'm
already i mean i've been to italy in the
in the summer months many times so
maybe it's time to go there
for a reason that's not going to the
beach yeah
let's go to rome
um oh yeah luka i want to go to lucca
yeah yeah for the
uh event for the anime convention look
look at comics um
yeah
all roads lead to rome i suppose so i'm
just gonna follow the road
yeah
milano games week
oh no no fashionista chihuahua goes to
milano fashion week
no i'll go to both i'm a gamer and i'm a
fashionista i have to be represented at
both of them
hmm
[Music]
um but we're gonna i think we're just
gonna stay
here on the screen because i'm lazy let
me turn off the
the camera here love love love love love
love thank you everybody
um
turning off the camera i'm gonna just
put my schedule on here i guess
tomorrow is another day off i have some
more appointments tomorrow
and then on on thursday we have kiwi
with
me
it's the week before my vacation
um
so i also have many appointments to
squeeze into this week
and
um so there's not so much going on it
seems also i've been doing a lot of
collabs for some reason last week and
this week
uh i don't know how that happened
um
but yeah on on sunday i'm hoping to just
do some kind of maybe karaoke or talking
stream before the vacation not too long
because not much time have to pack my
things and all that
um
but yeah
maybe during the vacation i'll be able
to stream i will try definitely
but just in case
that it doesn't go well and i can't
stream much during the vacation now i
still want to still want to
do as much as possible this week as well
[Music]
i'm not gonna jet win no no no no no no
cause i'm not leaving yet on a deadline
thank you guys thank you guys no no i
will stream oh and there's gonna be
um
at least i have at least two videos
prepared
i want to prepare a third one but i
can't think like i wanna i wanna um do
like a little
little um how to say
a little
skit
uh with a background that i have
prepared but i can't think of anything
is there any kfp who wants to help me
write a script a short one
who thinks they're funny
who thinks they're funny and can help me
yeah you all are not funny i'm the
funniest here
just kidding
not me oh wow you guys have no
confidence what's up with that where's
your confidence but yeah i'm the
comedian
[Applause]
yeah
you think pudding is funny
[Music]
[Laughter]
well
maybe maybe if i have a lot of choices
[Music]
oh my god
i'm so
i think it's the banana split that i had
today oh the banana split frappuccino
and uh yeah i had a had a decent day
i mean i woke up after a pretty bad
nightmare
you know when i dreamed
it probably doesn't sound so bad to you
guys but
it was pretty dramatic in my dream
i had a dream that my my twitter and my
discord got hacked
and taken over
um
which is pretty bad for like terms of
you know
accompanying you secrets and [\h__\h] like
that being like i mean discord is yummy
and um
then then i i because of the hacking i
don't know the hackers
came to my apartment and i tried to i
tried to burn them like suddenly i had
the ability not suddenly i always had an
ability obviously but i was like fire so
i made the floor go up in flames and
they fell into a hole um of
you know what i created
so i worked the first time but then more
and more came and then suddenly my fire
magic skill didn't work anymore and i
was getting
really really scared um
yeah
it's like why did it work the first time
when is it not working anymore where's
my magic
and i was worried about getting really
really really
uh
scolded by my
management
but like what can i do
what can i do about that
no not my fault
ah yeah it was really stressful
really scary
okay if i think about it now i guess i
had scarier dreams
before but still it was very scary for
me
yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
because i mean it sounds like something
that could happen in real life you know
it's too tutorialistic
yeah
and that's really scary
[Music]
i created a hell hole in my apartment
[Laughter]
no it's not so much about being scolded
but like um
probably another fear was being fired
high fire um
for
creating this trouble
in the first place oh man so scary
oh well well oh well
all is good
all is safe
all this secure
eh
it's a touristic chocolate in
switzerland
what but it's so good
i guess you guys are more into lint huh
or other chocolates yeah that's
surprising because we love milka in
every other country in europe i think
but you don't like it much in
in switzerland where it's from
that is surprising
i love milka
i love everything that milka creates
[Music]
they could sponsor me honestly
okay
okay let's open up the super tacos
i have to cook after
um this stream
i don't want to end too late
oh i have a different italian
background music
or the super testy
[Music]
isn't this nice
beautiful
okay i'm going to read subjects from
today only because i think i'm caught up
um
last schedule before going on vacation
with elena i'm getting really nervous
about it doing some last minute
preparations
um
actually yesterday i realized that the
transfer
to the hotel because they have like the
maldives are like a million
little okay thousands little islands
um so once you arrive on the main
airport you have to go with like either
a seaplane
or
a combination of a plane and a boat i
think you have to go to the to your
destination so
um i realized okay i should probably get
to organize that tell them when we're
arriving so i told them
and the i was holy [\h__\h] she's so
expensive
the [\h__\h] seaplane
it's more expensive than my actual
flight
i think
that my actual flight to the maldives is
cheaper than the seaplane from the
motives to the island
i'm like what the [\h__\h] is up with that
yeah
i mean what choice do we have
because like maybe there is any any like
a different option but
i don't know [\h__\h] about the motives um i
was discussing with dana like
should we just
should we just go with it
i don't know it's too it's too
complicated at this point i have so many
other things to keep track of
um so i don't want to think about it
yeah we're just gonna
take the
stupid seaplane
yeah
you're both birds just fly i wish we
could do that planning for the strip
sounds stressful it is because like i'm
also worried about the weather
um
this week is still fine
but of course best timing
apparently next week is gonna start like
every day is rain
every day but
one day stronger one day less
strong
so i'm hoping
it's still gonna be hot though
it's still gonna be hot
really hot
so i think we can still swim a little
bit but there might be one or two days
where it's really gonna be
stormy um i'm worried about it but the
the weather report might still change
you know it's still a little bit early
to say
sometimes even the rental report on one
day before is really inaccurate so i'm
not giving up yet i'm still i'm still
hoping for
at least one one sunny day or like even
when it rains a little bit if it's just
a little bit like who cares you're going
into the water you're gonna be wet
anyway
hmm
i i hope so i'm what kind of [\h__\h] i
ah we should have gone like one week
earlier
yeah
now apparently it starts exactly the
rain region starts exactly with when
we're arriving
uh
i didn't expect that
um
[Music]
man it's a really expensive vacation i
don't want to be [\h__\h] up by raining
old [\h__\h] day and us having to stay
inside all day you know what i mean
that's
oh my god i'm gonna be like
such a waste
but
hopefully
i mean if it's raining we can still
maybe go diving for example probably
right
and i mean
as long as it starts storming
um
you know
we'll have to make the best out of it
and
uh
yeah
diving while raining is a bad idea is
that so i've never been diving
or snorkeling
um
yeah okay well i'll definitely bring my
switch
i will be playing switch all day maybe
ah so [\h__\h] man
i'm sorry i don't wanna i don't wanna be
already
like
thinking negatively about it i still
wanna be looking positively
forward to the vacation
i don't want to think too much about
that it could end up being bad so let's
let's be positive i don't know i don't
want i look forward to this so much and
uh
i don't want it to be a waste so
let's be optimistic okay
let's not think about it even when there
will be the one one thing i'm also kind
of
like worried about that it's like you
know i kind of invited reina this was
kind of my idea
so
for the sake of you know reyna enjoying
it as well i don't want her to be like
disappointed because it was my idea you
know i i would feel guilty
if elena was feeling disappointed about
it
i just feel like it was my fault
so
um
[Music]
i hope we can um have a good time
yeah
maybe we should tell them that we're on
a honeymoon too
to give get some free stuff
to get some special treatment
should we tell them that like everyone
goes there on the honeymoon we should
tell them that we're on the honeymoon
but oh i already told them that we're
arriving in
separate
planes
maybe that's a little bit sus hmm
[Music]
we had an online wedding okay
this is the first time we're meeting
okay it's an arranged wedding that's
still that's still a normal thing in
some cultures okay
[Music]
oh rings oh i'm just gonna buy some
cheap cheap couple rings yeah
when you call her can you also ask for
it to not rain or is she only available
to make available to make it ring
please
[Music]
i need your help
if she's only
the one who makes it rain maybe she has
a friend who
like a sun shaman you know
maybe she has a sun shaman
[Music]
get rid of the rain and html there's no
html bothering me only the rain
the main job is stop running really
let's ask her to move it somewhere else
yeah it's just even a neighboring island
as long it can still stay in the
maldives as long as it's not on on our
island
[Music]
well i
i looked up the weather for the maldives
but i wonder like
if there's any difference depending on
which island i'll be on
if that makes any difference like how
far spread apart are the islands anyway
or is just the whole area [\h__\h] i
wonder
hmm
[Music]
maybe
maybe just my island has good weather
because i mean the phoenix is coming
there symbol of sun i am i am
mostly
which means i bring good weather mostly
yes yes
um
i bring sun
i will
at least it's not gonna be cold that's
that's
one thing that
at least is a relief i guess
yeah
i was looking forward to it so much
[Applause]
no it's gonna be okay it's gonna be okay
it's gonna be okay it's gonna be okay
it's gonna be um fun and we're gonna
swim and and and we're gonna take cute
pictures and and we're gonna play and
eat and yeah we're gonna bond
yeah
yes okay
positive thinking positive thinking
and you know what we're both gamers so
it will be fun even if we
just chill all the time
um looking at the rain
and uh playing switch
because
if i think about it even on my in my
vacation to greece for example
how much time did i actually actively
spend in the water not that much
most of the time
me and uh rmt were chilling on the beach
just chilling enjoying the the warmth
and the sound of the ocean
[Music]
so i think i think that's the same for
many people like if you go to a beach
vacation how much time do you actually
spend in the water huh
not that much most of the time you go in
for like 10 minutes
and you split slush a little bit and
then you go back to your your seat and
just
yeah right okay positive thinking
positive thinking positive thinking
positive thinking
it's still fun yeah i want i want to
like i looked up some videos i think
it's like as long as it's just raining
it's like whatever
um
i should ask the hotel
if it's like
rainy season if people still normally go
swimming if it's okay if it was it's
fine
um no
i'm also worried about like
ah did you guys hear anything about
aina like
did she say anything on stream about you
know
bringing me a present or so because i
talked about it a while ago
i was like
they didn't have the necklace or maybe
she heard that and then was like oh i
gotta bring her a present but now now i
feel like what if she brings it brings
me really expensive present and i just
bring her a really cheap one
then
mine would be so disappointing
you guys
do you guys know something
can't say anything you know something
isn't it
is it expensive
how much do i have to spend to be on the
same level
don't tell there is something
[Music]
just tell me link
what level is it like
do you guys know
four months sell like from what my
salary or your selling
huh
no nothing about a gift
what
one nutella jar
wrap yourself in ribbons you're such a
little [\h__\h]
ah don't you i don't wanna
i was thinking
four weeks already
i have one idea but
if i give her that and she gives me
something really expensive then i'll
feel like an idiot
she's not going crazy really really
really
hmm
[Music]
tomorrow tomorrow um i'll spend some of
my free time
getting a gift for or many gifts many
gifts for lena
uh uh
the [\h__\h] the [\h__\h] that counts well i
mean i guess so like like elena could
probably buy herself anything that she
wanted to so it's not like it has to be
something expensive
[Music]
you don't recall you're saying anything
specific
[Music]
okay i'll think tomorrow
maybe i'll give her um turkey seasoning
nevermind
[Music]
i wonder like i have some ideas but i
want something more personal what's
personal between me and elena
a dog because we played
frogs
i should give her a dog she has
she has no dogs as far as i know
how about i give her a dog
a dog with
no butt but two faces
can i find that
[Music]
bird feet
something bird related yeah something
with feathers because we both have
feathers
uh as our one of our you know
marks
symbols
hmm
we both have feathers in our hair
yeah
but yeah i also wanted to give her
something specific from austria
something
kind of like souvenir touristy
[Music]
okay
and one of my phoenix sweaters
[Music]
oh
crayons
my god
i need
[Music]
[Laughter]
no i'm not getting your crayons
damn getting your name is something that
i don't even own myself
hmm
[Music]
you love the crayons
[Laughter]
is your brain okay today are you
overheating
you know well i'm a phoenix you know i
need to put my head into the toilet seat
again
like i did back when i was a child you
know
my head is on fire
can't you see
oh man oh man don't tell don't tell
elena though
some of you might have an idea what i'm
doing now don't tell her
i mean it might be a little bit obvious
if you think about it
but don't tell her
i already asked her about your
measurements
and so she she will probably think i'll
buy i'm buying her something that you
can wear
well i'm gonna try i don't know if i i
don't even know where to go to buy
something like that you don't even know
where to go
oh well anyway okay let's read the super
chats
you know who you are
and pepsi dangerous and pets and violent
evil god and what is that perfect
picture is that me
it's not me
what the [\h__\h] is that
who is that it's like orange hair but
it's not me
what is that violet never got in
who is that
you changed your picture again he's not
here
you have to explain yourself it looks
like some
some kind of anime game or or anime
[Music]
ah you're here it's called nino who is
that
nina and i look for nino i just find
[Music]
something called el el nino
yeah it looks like love live or
something like that
[Music]
quint essential quintuplets aha
so some anime right
quinn quint quinn
a bad chick oh she looks so different in
your picture because she's wearing a
swimsuit
a dead chick okay so you're not even wow
you're not even into youtubers anymore
at this point you're just putting
a random anime girl into your orange now
wow
it's not okay you're straying away too
far i'm
afraid to lose you
mr casper's duncan thank you yeah the
the lineup for this
you know with inna and pekora i mean
sorry lapras but i'm especially happy
about being in this with vena and pekuda
i mean you know i'm
me and eno are like buddies buddies
bunnies and pick whatever senpai is like
it's my an honor for me to be
um in there with her
so wow
wow i don't i don't understand like why
i was chosen for this and i'm the host i
feel like
i know why
[Laughter]
but i'm very happy about it
i'm like i'm gonna be part of the game
forever people
who gets my character will have the
character forever
that's so cool
[Music]
ah it's so cool to have like a special
outfit for this case you know not just
default
um
[Music]
i don't know much about how you can get
us i think they said something like you
can get us for free
uh i think you have to play
certain
like missions or something
i think
yeah apparently it's a free event
but
the more you play
the more happy things will happen i
think
so please um i'm gonna start playing it
too on this occasion
let's play it together
and
kakun danishan for the pinky i said
goodbye singing is my favorite but after
streaming cinderella for so long it
finally became my all-time favorite
roomie
it's so amazing the fast singing the mv
cute voice your random chew the beat
absolute best cover ever use awesome
singer and best girl thank you
i really like the remix but for me
personally it's not definitely not my my
favorite of my covers like
um
i could have done better
or like
you guys know i was kind of unhappy with
the sound i guess
of my voice
i don't know what would be my favorite
of my colors
maybe
ai kotoba or goodbye singing
one of those not only because of the
video but also because of the song and
the mixing and everything
um
i think one of those two yeah for me i
see i see your ear is a great one too
if you fix the audio problem what audio
problem
i love goodbye singing them all thank
you
goodbye singing
like my king cover is the best thank you
thank you
vampire was good too i think so too then
the video might be more focused on you
know
um
type the typography
um not so much going on there but the
song me singing vampire i think it was
pretty good
do you mean to have the best video
dreaming too too special because of the
video yeah the 3d
video
with the special models i put a lot of
uh
budget into it
because i wanted it to be special
i'm glad some people mentioned that one
thank you thank you thank you
oh the acoustics
oh actually i had
um
gojo
who was the mixer of cinderella makes
something
else for me recently
my
new
original song
and that one
um sounded really good to me
uh
kind of
made it sound on my request a bit
fitting to the genre i think
um but i was really happy i'm actually
probably not even going to get anything
fixed maybe one small thing but um
i'm actually really happy with it so i
don't know what what my the problem was
before but the next one i'm really happy
i'm satisfied on the first time i heard
it i was like wow
wow and then the second time i was like
wow and then i was listening to it a lot
yesterday and i was still like wow
[Music]
looking forward to you guys finally
hearing it i think it will be released
after the maldives because i want to be
there to properly celebrate it
[Music]
me
i have a head start on streaming the
song of course i always do
yeah fast phoenix
john bieber duncan
happy birthday
oh it's your perfect on me but
congratulations
happy birthday
[Music]
you can have all the leftover snacks
sorry i already
i already munched on some of them
oh
john weaver are you coming to dokomi
out of interest
just curing it because i see
euros so i think
no
wow okay
i mean i don't want to kill you
that's unfortunate busy busy with theses
oh what university
oh that's sad
maybe another time
oh
well good luck with that
and happy birthday
thank you
[Music]
oh oh birthday yesterday oh happy
birthday birthday okay mike
so many birthdays always oh man so
exciting
you know what birthday is during the
maldives in our birthday
[Music]
me and reina gonna try to call in and i
don't really know what time it will be
when inna is streaming
what's the time difference mall
this website
right now it's
1 42
a.m
so that's uh three hours only what the
[\h__\h]
it's so far away and it's only three
hours time this time difference
three hours
ooh i think it when inna is streaming it
will be a very very very early morning
for us because i think i saw when she's
doing um the birthday stream
i think that will be very early early
morning but yeah i think we'll we'll
call in if we have internet
together we'll do a double calling
yeah jet lag not that bad
crazy free always what sofa away
from where i live
it's uh surprising
it was weird
i would have thought it would be much
more
it feels so far away
three hours from where i am
now it's maldives one time i think so
but most countries are
most unless it's an insanely big
country
[Music]
and then there's insanely big countries
who still only have one time zone which
is also weird
[Music]
so yeah jet lag might not be so bad
that's good i guess
thank you for the painting there's a
nasty rumor going around potential
they say your favorite food is fried
pork and that could be chicken
who the [\h__\h] said that
you're not abandoning us for the other
white meat are you tenjoy you're not
frying up hot dogs behind your backs are
you it's is that really a rumor like
where
look what the [\h__\h] is that rumor
huh
you mean i did
[Music]
oh
oh the video
the the promotional valkyrie connect
video on twitter i said my favorite food
was hirakatsu
[Music]
what wouldn't it be
more like wouldn't it be better for you
guys if my favorite food was not chicken
like you guys are obviously my favorite
animal
but to eat you know
[Music]
now generally i always prefer chicken
over pork
generally yes
but hirakatsu have you guys ever had
hira or tonkatsu i mean if you will if
you have it then you'll understand
you're not being abandoned no no no no
no
now you want to be eating umbrellas you
guys are [\h__\h] unbelievable i'm i'm
getting
i'm losing my [\h__\h] patience with you
guys
now you're like please eat me
why would you abandon this and then when
it's about eating you guys and frying
you guys you're like oh my god you're so
evil oh look good wow holy [\h__\h] can't be
so scary
you guys are such little shits
the [\h__\h] duality
oh my god
how do i
[\h__\h] decide just choose one side do
you want to be happy about it or do you
want to be scared about it i mean i
would be i would prefer you guys being
happy about it
you know i just said hirakatsu because
if i said fried chicken you guys would
be like oh my gosh
save us from our destiny so because i
didn't want you guys to freak out i said
of course my first choice would be
chicken
pho is a loose with you guys yeah and i
can't i can't win them you guys
you've changed excuse me
i love chimken nuggets
get yourself in chimken nugget shape and
i will
i will always
push away that hirakatsu
i'll always go for you if you're chimney
chicken
as well
i really like that one too
[Music]
i got in the bucket for this
what do you mean
[Music]
final snack for me is gonna be
that might be true
[Music]
get in the bucket cindy i became a
bucket for a reason well okay
but don't you co they're complaining to
me ever again when i talk about chickens
when i talk about frying and eating
chickens again
[Music]
you guys are so complicated
am i [\h__\h] ever lavina what
are you also skater boy by any chance
is your hobby skating
[Laughter]
you just want attention
oh cute
yeah you have a weird character
development so weird that it changes
every [\h__\h] day
you guys have mood swings
you should get that checked out
[Music]
no
yeah find a chef friend to cook the
whole menu for me oh my god
gotta call up monica gala
[Music]
monika
okay
anyway that was funny for a long
i didn't know what the hell you were
talking about
because pork really normally i wouldn't
go for pork but
hidaka is a whole different story
i can take out my gloves now can't i
yay
take off those gloves let's go
stripping
on stream
wow
[Music]
gloves
we want the naked you be you bees
[Music]
slap the chat with the gloves
you wouldn't see you wouldn't see it
anyway trevor g thanks for the pinky
with ch of course i may or may not have
fallen asleep midway for the last window
extreme due to being too comfy in my
nest to have you beautiful chirping in
my ears but i wanted to know wanted you
to know i called you a lunatic entirely
out of love nah you who do
who else is crazy enough to adopt over a
million chickens and say their only
child is kobold
well
okay sorry i i i seem to have forgotten
about a million chickens yes that's true
um
you guys are my children too but not all
of you seem to like that thought so
hmm
we became a stranger no no no no just
got your hoodie
nice thanks for getting it
hope that it makes you happy for a long
long long long time
i have to i have to pay child support
why would i be paying child support
wouldn't the non-existent other parents
be paying the child support to me
because i'm taking care of you guys
wouldn't the country be paying me child
support why do i have to pay chance but
that makes no sense i'm taking care of
you guys
no no no that's not how it works
i know it from my own mom
[Music]
uh
wavin today
in the next
hours
attain the measurements
[Music]
oh my god am i really doing this
am i really doing this
[Music]
hmm
ah
the thing i'm so shocked about i can't
even say
no no she didn't send me the
measurements
[Laughter]
oh
hmm
what
[Music]
she just beat elder ring really well
bam
[Music]
okay
okay okay
curiosity is killing you sorry i can't
tell you
i can't tell you it's the secret
[Music]
thank you for the pinky tomorrow is your
birthday oh my god
i've been saying happy birthday so often
today tomorrow's my birthday so i
figured out i figured i'd send this in
today maybe i should save this to roll
for you and valkyrie connect but i trust
my luck
well i mean so from what i know we're
kind of free so maybe you don't have to
spend too much anyway i'm not sure how
the system works yet but uh good luck to
you thank you for planning on getting me
oh i'm excited you guys can actually
play
with me in a game oh god
and i look pretty strong too with my
fire
so cool but anyway happy early birthday
thank you for
being with me for being with kfp thank
you for being
a chicken
you're beautiful beautiful chicken so
glad to have you
stay the way you are okay
thank you soon and i wish you all the
best yeah
became a creed thank you soon
captain meow thank you for the ride
super chat oh hi today i'm officially a
bucket
thank you for bringing me joy and
helping me go through many hard times
alone in germany oh in the past year you
motivated me to study harder in german
in my master degree degree see you in
dokomi by the way can i have an employee
number yes
oh
wait did i i may have forgotten i don't
know if you told me before but i may
have forgotten that you're in germany
because of your donation currency oh i
didn't realize or i just forgot
i may have forgotten sorry in that case
but
yeah
well that's great then yeah then you can
be a dog
[Music]
oh you are in germany
well how long i wonder
for your master degree
jim how long does that take
university can
take
like three years to 10 years or 20 years
even if you if you take your time right
hmm eight months what
huh you only need eight months
for master degree are you [\h__\h] genius
or what
two years for master degree ah and you
have eight months left
[Music]
like what you it's always one to two
years
can't it take longer if you're lazy and
and stupid
oh you're here just for eight months oh
and then you
go back
oh
you can't right yeah
from what i i know i know some people
who take really a long time with
university and
nothing's happening
many years later oh you're still in
university huh like for me like i don't
know much about university because i
haven't gone to university
but
it's interesting to see how some some of
my friends are
in university for forever like
why don't you ever leave in university
dude
[Music]
but i mean take your time like i mean
there can be several reasons why you
need more time and even if it's not just
that you're busy but if even if it's
just that you just can't grasp the
[\h__\h] material
like i'm not gonna blame you for that
like i'm
i wouldn't i would probably have a
really hard time in university too
[Music]
well i can imagine some some of the
things you study there can be very very
very very very difficult so i'm not
gonna blame you guys sorry for making a
little bit of fun about you but
final final
hmm
and final captain meow allen scott
yeah and congratulations on becoming a
bucket and see you at taco bell
yeah yeah yeah
your employee number i forgot and okay
i'll say it in german let's see if you
can
understand
[Music]
that
from vonsvanzik
let's test your german skills
to get it on what chat is telling you
anyway
[Music]
you almost got it
three two five
and a kiss
i love your italian accent really
looking forward to hearing lots today
much love from your downstairs neighbors
and bon appetito oh
i'm so happy to have
viewers all over europe really it makes
me so happy because
you know we really don't have that many
um
that much of a fan base in in europe and
whole life so i feel like me just being
based here and streaming in
european hours i'm single-handedly
you know
it might not be much but i'm
single-handedly creating a european fan
base
somehow
so
what i'm based what did i say
what did i say
i'm carrying the whole continent yeah
and um
i hope i hope that we can
um
make the fan base grow bigger and bigger
and bigger
in europe i don't remember saying that
but i guess i did
and someone has to do it
[Music]
oh did you see pewdiepie went to japan
finally
so random but i was thinking about
you know
what if i wasn't in europe but in japan
[Music]
pewdiepie finally made it yeah
does he even speak japanese i feel like
in all that time that he
had where he was waiting to get to japan
he could have studied japanese does he
speak
any
japanese
like any
[Music]
he's going to be on oh
hmm they tried studying
i mean if they really want to live in
japan that much i wish them good luck
because um
you won't get that far in japan without
speaking japanese
unless you stay in a little bubble of
foreign friends only
but even then like you're gonna have
some troubles because um
english doesn't get you very far in
japan
oh yeah i know matsia is italian yeah
um
that's that's good for them finally i
heard that i mean i don't really follow
pewdiepie but i heard that he was uh
applying or have having someone apply
for him for a long long long long long
long time
uh renting or buying an office
in japan as well and all that
but yeah in general things have been
looking
more
positive recently
um but guys i'm just gonna say even when
the news say something like oh tourists
can now enter japan
it's usually
it's not that easy yet okay as far as i
know it's currently just being like
groups
in a test phase
phase um but it's still getting better
definitely the fact the simple fact that
they are starting with some tourist
groups in in tours
um
like uh organized tours is at least a
start okay
yeah
it's not fully open yet though
and but it's looking positive
[Music]
so
yeah slowly slowly slowly but surely
[Music]
yeah soon we can i think at this point
we can at least finally say that this
year it's happening uh hololive myth
meeting up in japan
we're closer than ever yes
that is true i'm looking forward to it
[Music]
i mean
you know in order to get all of us there
certain requirements have to be met and
um
certain things have to be planned out
very very carefully
uh like schedules
um
in
like you know because we obviously want
to have like 3d stuff together so studio
schedules and we have to find
a place to live where we can also stream
so you know it will take
some time
to make all things work
properly
but
i'm
looking forward to it
maybe maybe maybe maybe even before that
maybe i'll just go on a quick trip as a
tourist
if
if japan lets me
if it still takes a bit longer to go
there with myth then there's even a
slight chance that
um in the meantime i'll i'll go back i
go there as a tourist
i might actually do that then
and in the very i can tell you in the
very moment they really open up the
borders i'm booking my flight
hmm
would you have a move back um no so
um no um i've lived in japan before in
total three years but like kind of
separately
and
um the last time i lived in japan with
my one year visa
was kind of for me
um a way of closing a certain chapter
and
[Music]
as much as i used to dream about
living in japan
when i was a bit younger
at the moment i'm i'm seeing
myself my future more in europe than i
see it in japan
um
for many reasons
just like simply the fact that it's
easier for me to live in
in austria and i have my friends here um
i
love japan and i will visit it every
[\h__\h] year if i can
but
living there is
difficult first of all very difficult
unless like i don't know
like even getting a working visa is
difficult the only easy way to live in
japan is if you get married
and no plans on that so
yeah
um
[Music]
also i have my cats and i don't want to
have them
travel
a long distance flight
if unless it's really really necessary
but
at this moment i'm
kind of happy
in the place where i am
now in europe
and
i can travel
wherever i want and i want to enjoy that
for a while just traveling
wouldn't you be able to get a work visa
if you wanted to i'm telling you guys
japan is so difficult to get a working
visa how many times i have to tell you
guys
it's really not that easy
you can't just be like oh
i want to go live in japan and i mean i
don't know whatever i'll just do
whatever that doesn't work
and and let's say
i don't know you want to just be a
waitress or something you won't get a
visa for that you will not get a visa
for that you need okay let me tell you
for a basic working
visa i have done my research on this for
many years
but there's many different categories
but for a basic working visa you either
need a university degree
of something and then have to work
something in that category or you need
10 years of experience
in a row
in one job
one category of job
and
i don't have either of those
besides that your other choices are
being like some kind of
specialist
like olympic whatever or
i don't know you make spaceships or
something
be some kind of crazy specialist in some
crazy special job
or the other easy thing that i still
won't do because i don't want to be a
teacher is being an english teacher
that's the one easy for somewhat easy
job that you can get in japan but even
for that you actually do need some kind
of degree and i don't have a [\h__\h]
degree and even if i would try where to
try to get something like that out of
nowhere now i would have to go to
[\h__\h] university and it would have
[\h__\h] up time for that i don't have
time for that i don't want to be a
teacher so what the [\h__\h]
yeah uh
i've been on
a
working visa in japan before um that was
a special one too
but that one was organized
that's something you need to have a
company that backs you up for and and
gets goes for all the travel to get that
for you but even then it's it's not like
something anyone can get um
that visa was difficult
and had more than enough trouble with
the
with getting it
anyway and and renewing it but you need
a company to back you up and then bring
you to japan and and sponsor you and
visa
but they can't just do it for any kind
of job you know what i mean it has to be
something special
and um
yeah
yeah and the last year that i spent in
japan was with a working holiday visa
which is a once in a lifetime visa you
can only use it once until a certain age
and not every country has that kind of
deal with japan but mine had it luckily
so i was able to go there for one year
and i was able to do anything i wanted
in that one year but then [\h__\h] cool
nah
showed up and said [\h__\h] you kiwawa you
came here to use up that
once-in-a-lifetime visa oh oh [\h__\h] you
you're you're not gonna be able to do
anything because you know what
uh-huh
you just stay in that little tiny bed in
your little tiny one-room apartment
where that you
rented because you were hopeful to do so
many things while you're in japan so
that you're not going to spend time in
the apartment anyway but you just stay
there and watch vegetables all day and
become really depressed
instead of instead of actually enjoying
japan yeah yeah you just become
depressed so espresso that's what you
deserve you have a [\h__\h] you
and then bam whole live auditions in
your face save your life let's go
change your life for the better do
what you always wanted to do use your
talents stay at home while working and
and and and yeah
yeah maybe maybe still not really uh
you know logical to be in japan because
you didn't need to be in japan for that
but whatever at least at least i could
meet some of my co-workers
anyway so um yeah at least something
good happened but uh my one once in a
lifetime visa was absolutely wasted
absolutely wasted write a book i should
i should let me write right now
[Music]
[Laughter]
sorry um
so yeah um it's not that easy and when
people
ask me why did you leave japan well uh
listen it was not a choice ahead
actually um
also because of the whole sifing
situation and me hoping to
have my 3dw
while i still was in japan
um
i was hoping to like somehow extend it
so
um
and i couldn't extend the working
holiday visa but i asked if
maybe
with the help of
hololeibu
maybe i could
you know extend it but
like you know get a different visa but
uh
that didn't happen
so
i did go home and
in the end i think it was the best
choice because even if we would have
extended it let's say for three months
or six months well look where we are now
i still didn't have my 3dw and it's been
over a year so
so
[Music]
yeah
it's good that i went home
no it's not not really about them not
covering it it's just also about like
if it's even
possible
but i don't know whatever it's a
complicated you know visa stuff is
complicated
um
but
yeah
you know maybe you guys don't maybe many
people don't quite understand it because
the visa
laws are just way more
simple in whatever country you are in
and honestly for austrians i think it's
really
easy to get into austria
and get a working visa in austria and
all that i think it's really simple
japan is just very special
you guys don't understand
japan is very
very difficult to get ibiza in
it's very different from other countries
[Music]
so why the [\h__\h] are we tangenting into
this
uh optimus prime don question
mary pippen
thank you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
please look forward to it and support
this
collaboration with valkyrie connect
it's a very special one
[Music]
is that lu or eo
what does it say
[Music]
does this mean
you're trying to make me say i love
owl's owls are the best
oh
is this trevor jean
honestly that profile picture how could
i not love owls with that
is an owl with a pizza slice
in its mouth
you're so cute
owls are [\h__\h] cute i love owls i love
them if only they were like
like
a normal pet to keep
i would totally keep it
totally get one of those cute oh you can
you know those tiny baby house oh my god
so cute
uh every owl is so cute i've been to an
owl cafe in in tokyo before
but
i felt kind of sorry for the owls
because it was such a tiny tiny tiny
tiny tiny room
um
there's alcohol yeah yeah several ones
but the one i went to was an akihabara
it was so [\h__\h] tiny
it was cute to see the owls but
the room i don't know man
they have such long hidden legs
cute
yeah
you have to push it out with a broom
once it wouldn't leave my points so cute
oh my god it's so cute
everything is tiny and talking well
exactly that's why i just feel like it's
a weird choice to
have an owl cafe if you don't have the
space for it but
yeah
hopefully there's some bigger places i
would hope that there's some bigger
places
sometimes you would see the alcafe
workers
outside with an owl
on a leash on their arm
trying to get in customers you know
advertising
that's that's
probably their only way to see
get some outside time
like some some more space for ones
walking the owl basically yeah
um
i don't know i don't know how owls are
supposed to be kept but that just i
don't know felt kind of wrong
but i love owls so god
ravioli foundation tony bro tony bones
duncan
what
what what what what
hi kiana today at work
i learned about tiny rose-colored
glasses
made specifically for chickens so they
cannot see blood
since the sight can cause them to enter
a murderous slash cannibalistic blood
frenzy isn't that cool
what
you mean those
[Laughter]
that's why i always felt different when
i put on these glasses
i always felt when i put these on
something feels different
feel more sweet and kind and gentle when
i put on these glasses
[Music]
but wait what
[Laughter]
what
but who puts glasses on a chicken
let me google that
[Music]
rose colored glasses for chickens
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
why did they put red sunglasses the
inside was simple the side of red
colored blood intensified the pecking
inspecting chickens the red eyeglasses
tricked the chicken from seeing the red
color of the blood thus reducing packing
and even cannibalism
[Music]
okay
um
what
but i've never seen that before like who
actually does that
oh my god
what the actual [\h__\h]
why do they look so stylish
what the [\h__\h]
do we need to get these for all my
employees
it's kind of dark
prevent packing
stop cannibalism
what
this is real
of national's new anti-picks
is this for is this real
white is contribution to the poultry
world amongst the new epoch in the
control
of the vicious practice of pick out
cannibalism
[Music]
chatter above me is looking kind of
tasty oh they are light
and and
anti-depict the simplicity itself with
what
[Music]
a bird is rendered colorblind by this
red celloid shields cannot detect raw
flesh or blood when head is lowered from
feeding etc the pendulum type shields
swing forward providing clear
unobstructed vision of objects of the
crowd
oh my god what a deal
100 glasses for three dollars
[Music]
1000 glasses for 27
is this a jork
is this a satire
i'm i'm so confused
but it sounds like a good investment
did did hook a papa
knowingly
give me these pink glasses
did he try to
control my urges
did i just hear a cat
chunky monkey
he's just sitting behind me
sitting up and meowing at me
you want some snacks donkey monkey
chunky
i'm gonna get you
i'm gonna get you i'm gonna eat you up
i'm gonna hit you up i'm gonna eat you
up
[Music]
she ran away but she got stuck
in some narrow corner
i have her i have her i have her
donkey monkey
[Music]
yeah
he's making uh
dove noises
yeah
yeah this is a baby
who's a baby you're a baby
[Music]
who's a baby mommy is still streaming
you guys need to let mommy stream
okay
i haven't even streamed that long
today it's only been three hours
i need to end it soon though i need to
cook okay
oh god let's let's pace it up a little
bit shall we
turn
[Music]
it's only in korean they'll be
translated
i woke up at 3 am to watch kiana's
broadcast please understand even if i
can't chat because i don't have enough
days to subscribe oh
i will enjoy the review of italian
snacks oh sorry i thought two weeks was
like you know generally enough for
most of you
but thank you for watching anyway i'm
actually sorry me i'm there
i'm sorry we can't communicate oh no
sorry please understand
but you seem to be fine and very sweet
and understanding
[Music]
thank you
yeah apparently you can still super chat
oh
there's a certain bonkers
invading the snack box right now
good then the camera is off
[Music]
you know at this point i should just
show you because like you already saw
bonkers
uh what i want i want
we need some kind of boundaries
right red bunkers
no uh she's she's um
rubbing her
her chin against the snack box enjoying
the
the nice cardboard
don't you love that cardboard
oh yeah
and cram
[Music]
sounds like a cute japanese name yeah
anything with cool at the end it's
usually a cute japanese name yeah but
don't make never heard before
it was a typo i think
time to thank you also for a red super
chat
[Music]
oh yeah italians like to kiss on the
cheeks a lot don't they i mean austrians
too
as a greeting
but
i think italians do it even more
um i don't really
like doing it and it intimidates me and
i'm
don't please no to too close to close
too intimate
i don't really like it to be honest
um
yeah i usually always try to
uh
um avoid it but especially now with the
whole
you know the sea thing
i think most people don't even shake
hands anymore
so
i like shaking hands but
you know gonna keep some distance
[Music]
if you try to do something like that in
northern germany you'll get hit really
i go for fist bump only now someone gave
me a fist bump today
i was so confused but i think
um
that person was probably a little bit um
confused too
sick
yeah i was just standing waiting for my
uber
and someone walked a girl walked up to
me
then waited a few seconds
while like showing me her fist
and i was like eh
[Music]
you really want me to stump you randomly
and then i
i realized
okay
i mean i guess it's okay
no no i don't think she knew no um i
don't know how to say but i think uh
um
[Music]
i don't know how to say it i don't want
to say anything
offensive but then i gave her a fist
bump and she was really happy about it
and she was like yeah finally and then
she just walked away
um
she was cute though she had a cute
backpack hmm
an extrovert
i mean i guess
those extra words are so [\h__\h] weird
man
[Laughter]
those extroverts
ah i don't know how to deal with them
oh the other day an extrovert wanted to
convince me that they were an introvert
and i was like nope
you are so obviously an extrovert but
they these extroverts they try to they
try to like you know be special by
saying oh i'm such an introvert you know
but they're like really such a [\h__\h]
extrovert
they were like um but i need you know
any time for myself once every like
once in a month you know like
i i can't be with someone like every day
and i'm like dude that's normal
what one once a month i need for me
maximum of meeting someone
is once a month
[Music]
you are
you are an extrovert
[Music]
ah man
yeah they don't understand
what an intro yeah it's like a trend
they wanna they want to be cool by being
an introvert but that it's not that cool
i think there's a misunderstanding there
and you don't quite understand what an
introvert is
the same time next month
yeah once them up i mean a month goes by
so fast too honestly
meeting once in a month with someone
sometimes i don't even meet people like
like my my best friends
i haven't met rmt who is one of my best
friends
in
months like since the the skiing trip
yeah
i don't meet people
and i'm happy with it like even if i
don't meet them
doesn't mean that we're not friends
even if we don't write on on messenger
and whatever either doesn't mean that
we're not friends i still love them the
same way
um
no we don't call either we don't chat
but like i'm i've been like this for a
long time i don't chat with my i don't
chat or talk or call or meet with my
friends that often
[Music]
exactly exactly you guys get me
sounds more busy than an introvert no
but even when i wasn't
even when i wasn't as busy as i was now
so before her life
i still
didn't really
feel the need to
meet my friends that much
like conventions anime conventions were
basically
most of the time the only
occasion when i would meet friends hmm
anyway i need to read the super chats
rebecca duncan
oh
wings no wings i wasn't into wings like
i liked which more for me winx was like
too much like
i didn't like their visuals and
and it was too
ew
yeah emma i'm a witch kind of person
wings was too hard to say like too
flashy and like
black
which was the cool stuff yeah yeah yeah
wings felt like they were trying to
recreate witch
but
it was too
too girly
too cutesy
but also like
not cutesy but it was like you know the
outfits they look like to me they look
just
like those edgy um
tick tock and instagram girls nowadays
yeah
the way i felt about wings back then is
is how
tick-tock and instagram girls look to me
now
like um yeah like e-girls
like they're nice to look at maybe but
it's just it's just not my world you
know not not my world
it feels like
i don't belong there um
too
how to say
what the mainstream
girl aspires to be now oh no i can't
describe it's difficult to describe
it doesn't feel genuine maybe but
honestly like i didn't give wings much
of a chance
anyway so it may have been great
honestly
but for me i was just too much into
which
have to go thanks for watching thank you
we're done soon anyway i have to hurry
brandon thank you soon
thank you for the super chat you're
basically yeah throwing a coin into my
fountain
dame got guys singles
happy birthday wait wait wait i'm glad i
noticed because you know
it's not a red or pink so i'm sorry if i
ever
um
read over
someone's birthday message
uh
because they're not a pinky or a red one
sorry if that ever happens i try to see
everything i try to always have an eye
even on the messages that i don't read
so that i don't miss anything like that
but in any case happy perfect thing i
wasn't glad i noticed wish you all the
best
thank you for supporting me too
yeah
17 years why since you last visited
daisy
check it's
if you like the pgm i'm happy to hear
it's always fun to
find fitting btms harbor line thanks for
the pinky how goes it boss lady i just
bought myself a new phone today for
super cheap i had 50 left over which i
put into this pinky
you bought a cheekbone what did you get
everything on the screen looks so clear
wait you actually have a nose i thought
it was just an urban myth
what
[Applause]
i no i have a nose just an anime knows
man what i don't have is nostrils
i don't know how i even smell anything
at all maybe it's maybe i'm smelling it
for my eyes or something
man
you know as an anime girl over the
over the past
[Music]
how many times how many years has been
centuries
over the past centuries anime
people had to adapt
and therefore for the lack of having
nostrils they
adapted by having a
sense of smell for their eyes yeah yeah
evolution guys it's anime girl evolution
that means we have to smell somehow
yeah
happy for you getting a new phone though
um factor tech thank you for the rest of
the chat kick of the key is great to
observe other cultures with mama kiwawa
right
i always love the variety of streams you
have on offer you're always expanding
your horizons trying new things pushing
the envelope you're a great example for
his uh glory to kft
oh man that makes me really happy i feel
like i could do more always you know but
i'm just like
if you guys knew how [\h__\h] lazy i was
before whole life the amount of
work i put into all of this now is
absolutely astonishing to me
like
such a glow up oh my
god and even then i feel like
i probably
could do more but at the same time
i mean not every stream has to be
like hmm
i feel like my schedules are
good the way they are
and having like a special screen stream
sprinkled here and there every now and
then
but then even the streams that you may
not think or perceive as that special
are still mostly special to me like even
gaming streams like wind waker for me
that's really special
even if it's not like reinventing
someone something completely
new
that something like that is still
special to me
um
i can't have
a revolutionary stream every [\h__\h] day
right
yeah
yeah thank you guys
and thank you for the sweet message it
means a lot to me thank you
soon
thank you soon
[Music]
as our secret agent who was codenamed
bunkers showed successfully operational
results we raccoon decided to support
the reward accordingly consistently earn
the phoenix sancho's trust oh don't
worry i trust you raccoons
actually bonkers is
you know the
the snack box is currently on a really
small um
cat tree
um it's really small it's just like one
square
meter not even a square meter
i think and uh the box is on there and
the other half of that is currently
being occupied by bonkers
apparently she felt the need no she's
not in the box
she felt the need to just be right next
to the box partially
with her legs
um hanging off of the cat tree
i don't even see her let me look at you
[Music]
this is so cute you could try to get
into the box oh
she's stepping into the box get into the
box get into the box bonkers oh no now
she said
no she's oh you're so cute how are you
so cute she's going behind my monitor
now
she really likes that spot oh
there's like i have a movable scent
oh
[Music]
hello
oh no
you guys hear me
she disconnected my going saliva because
she's so chunky wonky
because
my my cables from the
go xlr go through underneath the
the
monitor that i have and she just sat on
top of it you know she's a bit heavy
[Laughter]
yeah she's hiding there she likes that
spot but um
i don't know how to describe that but i
have free monitors okay and um when i'm
working on my pc she really wants to be
close to me and she will choose to
forcefully squeeze herself even if there
is no space
um through the like the two left
monitors the middle and the left one
until i move my my cintiq which is on an
arm
to make space for her to squeeze through
she will forcefully
push through until i open the path for
her and then she'll sit behind the
monitor
[Music]
gamer
i started off with one monitor when i
started out in whole life i had only one
small monitor and i always thought that
was enough but for streaming it's not
it's definitely not then i got a second
monitor and i thought that was enough
but it was still
i needed that third monitor holy [\h__\h]
i have so many
things to look at and i wish i wish it
was more like i don't want to look
around so much like from left to right
and left to right i wish it was a there
was a way to make it more
compact i could probably have one above
um kelly has that like set up i think
she has two screens
for free wait does she have three but
she definitely doesn't have them from
left to right but she has them from up
to down
um but i'm i don't know i don't like
that either it's just uh
well now she has four oh my god
oh my god
i wish i had the room yeah it gets
really it gets really um
uh how to say i don't have space here
either anymore on my table the table is
too small for the monitors to be honest
um but finding a bigger table in this
this is the biggest i could find and i'm
not happy with it i want the bigger one
i had a really big one when i lived in
japan
it was a it was a corner table though
that was huge
i think i ended up giving the table to
gemma
yeah
because it was so new i bought it and
then i only used it for half a year or
something
and it was a huge huge nice table so
i gave it to genma hmm
yeah yeah i didn't want to just i don't
know throw it away
yeah thankfully i could give it to
someone
[Music]
you know hmm i need a bigger table
i made a bigger table
but then again
i don't wanna
i don't quite wanna use more space than
this like as i said i don't want to look
around so much i tried to keep
the chat
on the very
why am i even talking about this i need
to read the project but i'm trying to
keep the chat uh either in the middle
screen when i can right now during a
super chat rating or or i have it like
on the very border
[Music]
that is uh
next to the middle screen but on the
right screen you know what i mean anyway
who the [\h__\h] cares okay wow just shut up
just shut the [\h__\h] up
thank you um gentlemen
then i i i
talked about something completely
different but thank you
thanks for the thinking comments from
getting into a game changer thank you
it's really really really really special
to me
thank you i mean
i i don't really i don't really am i
never played the game but
i'm ready to get into it
just because we are in it now
yeah yeah yeah yeah
but the fact i kind of you know it's a
gotcha game but i i like the the style
of it the whole
um
how to describe it it has like this rpg
style to it
i really like that the fantasy rpg style
so
um
the pretty chibi models are pretty cute
too
[Music]
so i want to give it a chance
my following base yeah that's really
cool too
waiting for a referral link oh i asked
but i still haven't heard back from that
so there might just not be one but maybe
wait a little bit longer i'm gonna
follow up on that
[Music]
people
for referral links
[Music]
yeah i mean if you already did i think
already a lot of people did but
um i think it should be fine yeah
yeah yeah
don't worry even without a referral link
we are getting paid so don't worry about
it
[Music]
thank you
so sweet
thank you thank you
god see you
come for 69 thank you soon
lord emma thank you
[Music]
i understand everything you are greeting
me from the magical rome
thank you for watching my stream scott
and paul another italian one no no this
sounds more like boppidy boob
napoli pizza frittata pizza portafolio
baba gotcha pizza
[Laughter]
16 moms nice thank you 12 moms nice
thank you
oh you hold your chunky monkey
i saw her paw and her eyes underneath my
my monitor peeking through hello chunky
wonky i'm giving her some scratch
scratches
er
miss donkey shane i am flip channel
duncan
for tuna's twenty two down
thank you
uh
who's a cute baby
[Music]
wait you guys sent so many super chats
what the [\h__\h] man
[\h__\h]
as
[Music]
to say hi and super excited to see you
in the game i normally stay away from
gocha i mean gotcha because i always
tend to go crazy but if you're in it
let's go congrats on your first game
thank you
yes it's special cause i don't mind it i
understand you know if you especially if
you already play some other godzilla
games
then it's hard to start another one but
you might like it
who knows
i'm giving chunky won't give some squish
scratches so i sound more
distant maybe thank you mickey tunes
thank you let's go thank you for the
support
[Music]
mamma mia
there are so many super tempo
you need to chat thanks for the pinky
well if the weather is rainy and hot you
two will get all sweaty terrible
well
[Laughter]
i'm sure it will still be lovely it
won't be wasted there is so much to do
and the location is special no matter
what
i hope so
thank you
let's stand positive
optimistic yo
raikana thanks little pinky i'm sure you
will have fun as long as you guys are
together thank you
probably yeah
i just you know as i said probably one
one thing i'm most worried about is that
reina will feel disappointed
hmm
[Music]
is really enjoying
thank
you even wondering what the proper kp
employee uniform would look like what do
you mean you're already wearing it
don't we have perfect examples from
dakuma
but yeah all of the almo cat stuff or
birthday apron or whatever anything is
fine
anything that makes me
recognize you guys
yeah i know you mean irl
sire examination looking for the topic
[Music]
oh my god she's so soft holy [\h__\h]
so soft i love you chunky wonky
[Music]
lounge thank you for the pinky today
marks my one-year membership ooh for all
the great content you provide and i wish
you a safe trip and lots of fun with
rainy on your vacation thank you
also really looking forward to all the
upcoming music projects thank you
[Music]
i'm looking forward to it too yeah i'm
not getting excited hyped up and uh
besides the upcoming music project
there's one more thing
that i'm
hoping
to
get out there before dokomi
that i mentioned the other day too
let's see let's see let's see
[Music]
what your ears
what what what
aren't you used to my screams at this
point
or is it because trunker is just
lying on the cable and made a weird
noise
[Music]
thank you tealands thank you so much one
year membership wow
i hope you're not sick of me and please
continue
supporting me okay i will continue doing
my best then um and i also
will do my best to enjoy the most out of
the rainy vacation you
thank you patricia
maple leaf 2501 duncan advanced me
duncan oh my god i'm almost done oh my
god
[Music]
it's almost midnight guys i wanted to be
gone by now
brandon duncan
douglas jones thank you i'm done now
remember
oh
thank you
for watching me during your time at work
yeah okay i'm done i'll go cook now
hopefully my recipes are simple this
week i forgot what i
what i ordered
you know my my hello fresh stuff yo
i don't remember
thank you everybody for staying until
the end thank you
i appreciate it i'll see you guys
uh on thursday on my channel i think
because last time kiwi
was on mummy's channel right
so this time we're doing it on my
channel
all the collabs on my channel this week
yeah
thank you
thank you everybody love you guys
thank you for all the love and support
you give me
and for always being so supportive i
would say one of the reasons why i got
this
is because you guys are always so
supportive when i do
sponsored streams and all that
um
partially that was surely the reason
so thank you so much for opening up
pat's like that for me
you guys are amazing
now chunky wonky is getting impatient
though
i'm gonna go now
i know
how
[Music]
dad
chunky monkey
[Music]
here
wonky
i'm done
[Music]
mama mia i'll be there
ciao
[Music]
pizza pasta
um
[Music]
baby
wow
[Music]
just because you can rage doesn't mean
you're allowed to
[Music]
need to get my cats under control