[Music]
amazing I feel amazing and you guys need
to look forward for the upcoming
performance tonight
[Music]
yeah have fun and please enjoy tonight's
show as well
okay bye
yay I feel so
excited you know I feel like me and Kira
have a lot of things in common about
performance so singing and dancing we we
really love to doing that we really love
um performs and
also um I think we
have uh the
same taste of
genra so uh singing with her and dancing
with her in the same stage I feel really
really happy excited
and I can't wait to show you
guys hello so KY I hope you guys enjoy
uh our performance um I hope you guys
enjoy all the things in Cara's
anniversary and don't forget to always
support her Always by her
merch and reloop her
song bye-bye thank you
it's always a blast to be performing
with takanashi Kiara so I hope you'll be
looking forward to it as
well kfp I hope you're all ready to have
the night of your
lives thank you so much for coming out
today everyone and don't forget to cheer
extra loud for the birthday girl Kiara
happy birthday Kiara and uh for now kfp
bye-bye
[Music]
beauty
hello please enjoy please look we yay
yay
[Music]
byebye how am I feeling about my
upcoming performance tonight oh I
believe we have cooked so hard and yeah
how much can I
say well I do believe and I do sincerely
hope you guys are going to enjoy it
because me I I have a really good
feeling about this all right I'm so so
happy can you say something to the
viewers of our channels
please h i wonder I wonder what you know
you guys you guys need to you guys need
to keep treating Kiara right okay keep
treating her right cuz you know she
deserves it and it's it's her party
night today so you guys better shower
her with lots of love okay we're here to
celebrate as well but ultimately yeah
celebrate for her it's her day let's
freaking
go all right bye-bye hope you guys
enjoy today live so I'm very
nervous I practice her so that I could
give a performance that I would not be
inance to stand next to K Senai
to but I'm happy to be a guest perform
at uh k for wonderful live show so we
will bring our best singing and dancing
please enjoy the
[Music]
show I'm super nervous and excited to
perform with Kiara our performance is
going to be
mindblowing kiar is amazing and you guys
are lucky to have her as your
telf thank you so much by r
oh you know I'm just so excited I
invited all my friends to dance and
perform with me today and I practiced so
hard spilled so much sweat sweaty
spaghetti you know um but I think the
result will be really Exquisite Divine
perhaps oh yeah um of course
subscribe like leave a comment of that
make sure to share it with your friends
wink yay bye-bye enjoy the show
everybody bye
[Music]
I can hear it
clearly
[Music]
for I will to keep on fighting till G
no I
[Music]
don't break I will never give up don't
break
[Music]
[Applause]
Tru bre up day I've been trying to find
my
destiny but I keep pushing and pulling
me
after if I go around what awaits me in
the
dark could you tell me please where I
need to go
[Music]
tell me I can hear it tell me
blazing Flames show me that Lance and in
the next I promise I will find you
[Music]
KY yeah we're so back welcome to my
fourth year anniversary Fredy live yay
that was hot to R remix the first time I
ever performed this version of it did
you like The Comeback of the Kik cake
yeah well well well let me take you
through the stage a little bit this is
our new stage it looks so luxurious and
beautiful wow so shiny I know well H we
also have a very or I have a very
special surprise for you guys at the end
of this live the last song H what could
it be it will still stay a surprise but
please still stay until the very end and
we have many guests too that you may
already have seen or heard about so look
forward to them yeah the next song will
be a cover song from K not my song even
though you know similar vibe to my
original songs so please
enjoy nice
type
[Music]
yeah it's getting dark here your back
pay attention now a demon
toose now watching teasing make it so
easy
[Music]
baby take
control
easy satisfy hunger got you l l down
still begging for more you
[Music]
got try if you I'll let you come ins my
mind hold it down and let's go all you
look so nervous what's wrong don't be
got you on your knees i' never claim to
be a
nice intentionally innocent to you
you're looking for help ain't no use boy
you should have know once I'm down I'm
moving on when look into my eyes you're
a you're m forever I no it only takes a
minute to get you all addicted can never
get enough no no no begging for
more alone no CL what you got yourself
into at all
escalated
boy try if you I let you come inside my
mind hold it down and let's go all night
oh you look so nervous what's wrong
don't be polite got on your knees I
never GL to be the
nice I'm not the
nice got you like
that I'm not the nice now
ever claim to be the
nice I miss
you want to ad but I do always been
close but far away you go but down you
stay yeah that's always been you I guess
we are different after all but it's
shocking how far apart we grew so I CAU
all the ties to play it safe but you
like playing games it's always been a
you and somehow you still
here this feeling could kill
me somebody still here
and this might take me out take me down
take
meart oh I got it back got attached my
imagination brings me right back to you
always want it all when I fall I fall
hard baby tell me why tell me why tell
me why that's the heart break a break
ah tell me why a heart break the Stars
fake oh baby tell me why tell me
why it's kind of painful to tell the
truth I should cry it out but I don't
usually do some don't change though I
make them if I could cuz I don't feel
human I wonder if you would and it's not
even fair that you're happy with her and
you're so unaware maybe that's why it
hurts the world stops and the clock
keeps taking all
night oh I got it back got toach my
imagination brings me right back to you
always want it all when I fall I fall
hard old baby tell me why tell me why
tell me why do a hard
why won't you let me
go I really want to be alone
right delete my number from your phone I
want to be alone but somehow you're
still
[Music]
here
ooh yeah yeah some you're still
here and this might take me out take me
down take me aart
oh I got it bad got attached my
imagination brings me right back to you
always want it all when I fall I fall
hard oh baby tell me why tell me
why oh I got it back I got iTouch my
imagination brings me right back to you
oh I know that I hard oh baby tell me
why tell me why tell me why a hug break
a hug break a
hug tell me why does a heart break the
Stars fade oh baby tell me why tell me
why
[Music]
oh baby tell me why
me we can't wait to
talk thank you so much for inviting me
of course it's such a rare du I know
right we have to do it I think this is
the first time we we sang in DS together
like just the two of us did you like it
did you guys like it okay what you to
doce yourself then hiis it's Iris from H
live English promise yeah I and I am
just so so happy me because I've been I
think I've been here in the whole life
for like over 3 years and I just can't
believe this is our first time yeah
sorry to keep you waiting yeah yeah know
I know it's it's very special so yeah it
was a really special song too right yeah
why does a heartbreak right why does a
heartbreak Iris uh I mean technically
I've never been heartbroken ever in my
life no what about B well I mean I might
have broken her heart but I've never
been broken really well I mean honestly
when we were doing this dance move this
one I was
like I smell B on you
liar last time no no I was alone last
night what you talking about she's lying
she's lying she's a she's a fat liar
right now was it the night before before
no no no if you see I wash my hair every
day it's more like your whole
body exudes okay
wow well let me let me take a sniff at
your
hair M oh that smells nice it smells a
little bit like a nice smelling Crow oh
Crow cron too CR is not a crow no no I'm
thinking Some Like The NIS
Nissa well I mean okay honestly that
could be because me and Nissa I thought
we had you know something because she I
felt like she CH me you do have
something thank you but I got a little
bit confused because a while ago at the
New York concert she was kissed okay she
didn't kiss her she was kissed
by so now I'm really confused because I
know she loves yod and like where do I
stand with her I'm so confused no you
guys just take your relationship as
especially when it comes to kissing and
stuff more personal not like in private
I'm assuming right I don't really know
about that did you guys like did you
guys like take a shower together no no
okay we were in swimsuits I think we
were in swimsuits okay okay okay okay I
think I'll clear it up with her because
the song after this I think I sense her
presence oh yeah maybe you should talk
to her a bit if you're worried you know
she's an Aris though so you know I'm
sure we go on a like couple
date no no not a couple date just it's
just a group of friends what are you
talking about it's just a group of
friends well done are you guys ready for
the next song I am so excited to see
that thank you all right you watch on
the sidelines see you guys next time
thank you
[Music]
I don't want the handbags the money or
the diamond rings cuz guys like you they
all don't care about the little
[Music]
things on and I'm never ever turning
back around around around again now I'll
go higher and I'll go higher and you
couldn't take me down if you
[Music]
tried now I can finally open my
eyes I'll get you
[Music]
I'm
all oops deleted your number all of my
friends used to warn me about you baby I
that I couldn't without you I got
[Music]
I I don't want that BS the money on the
diamond rings like you they all about
the little things
[Music]
[Applause]
every turning back around around around
again now I'll go higher and I'll go
higher and you couldn't take me down if
you tried
[Music]
now I
can
[Music]
eyes
[Applause]
all all
the the
[Music]
Heart Break
it's you
ready my
[Music]
now I can finally open my
eyes get out of my I'll get you get
[Music]
get my Bo I'll get you get you get you
cuz I'm fine I'm all right me I
[Music]
up
for
[Music]
next
for
[Music]
foree fore
over here the
[Music]
goodmy
over down Lely
[Music]
[Applause]
HEK
welcome introduction
please hello my name
[Music]
is hi we sang beat eater together I'm so
happy because I really really love this
song and when I chose it I thought I
need someone who can dance really well
which
is but then I I after like I already
chose you I realized when I was looking
up beat on YouTube I found your cover I
was like she's saying it
already so very very pop and cool so I
live it thank you today yeah thank
you
thank it was a very like dance focused
song so I wonder what dance move was
difficult for
[Music]
you so w so
very actually I also just like today I
finally understood
like rehear together
let's this
way for me there's like you know when I
overthink overthinking then I like
forget how to do the simplest things
even though I know that I know it so
there was this one move you like step
forward and when you step you like kick
the other leg back right and then you
put it to the front and we add the hand
right so it's like this but I over think
and I like
stumble kick
[Music]
wave
more so I had to do it 100 times so that
I stop overthinking oh my
goding so hard you
know so together practice together very
yes
[Music]
let's do it again sometime yes let's
singinging together yes also it very
nice
English
practice okay so with that we move on to
the next song and the next guest who
could it be bye bye guys see you next
time byebye next
[Music]
foree
fore fore
[Music]
for
spee
[Music]
St for
tanky
[Music]
styley St
good morning we're on stage why did we
fall asleep oh it's such a chill
song how are
you
hello maybe you you should introduce
yourself myself oh hi
hi you is from Hall of English
hello yay okay I know it's comfortable
on the floor you love the floor five
more minutes special floor right floor
rating good floor a solid 8.37 oh that's
pretty good but we got to leave the
floor
now guys it's been so long since we
released this as a song cover and we
finally upon popular theand performed it
how long has it been like 3 years three
three years something yeah have you guys
listened to it before or are you a
newcomer and you never heard it before
in that case what should they do you
know listen to it listen to it yeah but
it's like pretty far down so you got to
go to the videos and the most popular
cuz it's really popular y thank you
Tak
Tak thank you for giving us love yeah
thanks for inviting you oh of course
it's so fun with you oh yeah we had to
you know this special dance yeah we're
speaking with fun we have this guys
dance with
us like robot St yeah robot kind of it's
like ah whatever whatever whatever yeah
that's fine so actually this stage is
like pretty like epic and Godlike isn't
it oh I feel like a goddess so far the
songs haven't quite fit the theme but
now in the second part of this there's
going to be more guests more songs and
they all going to fit the Bible they're
going to be Godlike
and so I'm kind of
nervous you can't wait well can you give
me some kind of like motivation call
please no not whatever whatever okay
well just just just this time okay okay
you're going to join me on the H
everyone will join me on the oh okay on
the o okay sounds good here we
go
[Music]
f never heard that before okay okay
thank you bye next song
[Music]
oh please don't let me die waiting for
your
touch no don't give up on life
[Music]
I wish I was there oh please don't let
me die waiting for
[Music]
no don't give up on life
this must need for now I feel all
my time is spinning
around your de black eyes I forg what
time it
is and our memories are G
[Music]
I have a hair oh never close your eyes
searching
for we so let us Ry
again from the very first
[Music]
time see
again Bing
in bing
out Bing
[Music]
I was over
there you could
no don't give up on
[Music]
life
I and will die waiting for a
new and where start waiting for New Day
me oh please don't let me
down
he not
[Music]
oh
know
[Music]
fore
fore it's
[Music]
foree spee
for
[Music]
h
[Applause]
[Music]
speee
the
[Music]
foree
spee fore
[Music]
like a BL man to and fairness
spee been for
[Music]
the
is
is is
[Music]
like a BL to and fair
me
[Music]
I love fin
yay wow was that epic or what blooming
cons I think is a song that many people
wanted me to do for a long time I
finally did it wow German song on my
life what who would believe it but this
Vibe was I think really epic and amazing
thanks for singing with me everybody by
the way yeah but I have to kind of ruin
the vibe now because I'm going to
advertise to you my merchandise it I've
been here for over four years now and I
know my anniversary is a few weeks ago
but this got delayed actually you know
we're a little bit past anniversary now
but I haven't shown you my solo
Anniversary merchandise yet so here we
go it is
[Music]
time oh what is this yes my merchandise
is once again kind of kitchen themed now
let's start with number one the plate
t o oh oh isn't it nice this is like the
main illustration with you know a little
cute new outfit it's like kind of like a
apron or like waitress outfit I really
like it it's so cute and you can eat all
kinds of stuff on it you can eat pasta
or you can eat a burger or some fries or
a steak yes and or maybe some fried eggs
but if you're not really a fried egg
kind of person we would go to next the
egg cup yes we have an egg cup where you
put in your favorite boiled egg how many
minutes guys one two what's your
favorite like I don't know how to say it
well I like it like maybe six seven
minutes but of course just like that
that's not enough we need some salt
there and maybe even some pepper do you
put pepper on it I don't but for that I
got you covered we have salt and pepper
shakers oh what so cute they are in the
shape of an egg but they're wearing the
uniform what the heeg get to word the
uniform that's new but yeah it's really
cute uh it's your choice in which one
you put salt and pepper I think but I
think there's a more common way to do it
it's different with how many holes it
has isn't it cute and last but not least
another kitchen theme thing would be D
the glass yes we have a glass yes
wonderful finally a glass don't break it
be careful with it but in case you break
it maybe get some more maybe get some
more of the plate too might as well
right and after the glass we have one
more thing a BL pack yeah I wrote the
script and I tried my best I was riding
it on the airplane and the situation is
As on an airplane so I was like don't
worry it's not a situation that really
happened to me but maybe maybe in your
brain it really happened just like for
me I spilled like some tomato juice and
so on on you so isn't that kind of spicy
it might be it might just be besides
that we have for full set an A5 clear
file which has the main illustration on
it which I would love to have that so
make sure to get the full set to support
me I would appreciate it and now we're
getting into the last face guys don't
you want to hear some Chima again h I
got you covered last song Everybody are
you
ready
[Music]
o oh no fell into the Abus unknown left
me bleeding heartless all alone he he no
control don't you dare
apologize turn my back and F the cold KN
listen up cuz here some
advice you're out the time we out the
line it's taking over like Renegade I
for night I'll make you
cry tearing it down just when I calling
[Music]
me taking the crown now you calling me
King you going to hear him
[Music]
sing don't back it up don't back it up
keep that aim I got thoughts that will
drive you insane come over if you like
we'll have a lot of fun but I got a lot
of B I do what I want make sure you
don't forget it an Army on my back say
I'm sick I'm just sadistic not living in
aive in the line I want to see the way
you
bleed it's taking over like a renegade I
for and I'll make you
cry tearing it down
just keep calling me
[Music]
taking the crown now you're calling me
King you going to hear him
[Music]
sing I want it all so give me some more
flame bur me up down into my core oh you
wish I'd stay down but then I just
rise you're not my
enemy baby
D to me hear my voes screaming out loud
no doubt
[Music]
yeah tearing it
down call me
[Music]
taking the crown now you're calling me
King you going to hear him sing
[Music]
that was fun to do that
again did you press
four thank you so with the next song
it'll actually be the last song but this
one is a very special one because For
the First Time Ever you will hear my
next song Mirage and for this one what's
really special is for the first time
ever I'm bringing in some back up
dancers back dancers who are going to
join me so please enjoy and afterwards
the MV will be released so hopefully if
everything goes according to plan so
please make sure to check that out too
and support my new song m
[Music]
yeah
mirle going under confused Obsession I
still wonder if I was made for you if I
could only
see oh please I make me up a new so not
calulated perfectly for you pretending
like it's all for me don't think so
[Music]
life they got yet I'm asking you never
see what I want what I need oh do you oh
do
you through that you pursue but
now you saw me on a mirage i k you up
into shred I don't even know what to do
with this
be good lart my
[Music]
Mir do
anything but I be the king and queen of
[Music]
new see I'm you you're all me it seems
like everyone wants it all around
running around on and on like keeping me
captive escaped my way say I'm way too
FTI out I'm just your perfect ID break
me shake
me you'll never see what I want what I
need oh do you oh do
you follow through like
you
now you me on I you shred I don't even
know what to do with this
m it be good play you part my
[Music]
miring and on and on
me heart
me you make me fall in
[Music]
love hey
no you saw me on a i you shreds I don't
even know what to do with this
man play
part the last and on and on this me I'm
lost to hard me
[Music]
right
o
[Music]
yeah e