n
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
a
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
a
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
am
[Applause]
h h
[Music]
[Applause]
w
n
[Music]
[Applause]
hair in my
[Music]
mouth
look oh my God it's so
much oh it's so much stuff
[Music]
K maybe the mask a little bit lower
sorry nothing changed it's just
me oh
[Music]
oh oh I look so
funny uh yeah unfortunately I can't
exactly pin the hand to my hand
there uh because the focus like the the
main point is like in the middle of the
object and the hand is not in the middle
of the object ah almost
perfect but if I look this way you won't
really
tell or if I just I can just put my hand
down I guess that's almost
perfect that's I mean yeah it's fine
but then I guess I can put it a little
bit
more we are we striving for
Perfection aren't
we like like
here
yeah
Perfection Almost
[Music]
Heaven West Virginia vest vest
Virginia okay I feel pretty
perfect wa in the
trash they call me the destroyer of of
gumy bacos of trash cans they call my
ass the trash compactor well well well
look at you now I am in the trash
what does that mean
huh small small thief in the big trash
small thief in the big
trash wa in the dumpster I'm dumpster
diving whoa dumpster
[Music]
diving dumpster
diving dump it just don't don't even say
anything it's not about
that wait kind of want to
start where am I
[\h__\h]
restart
no okay
[Laughter]
I dumpster Drive let's
go you okay nice I just wanted to do
that just wanted to do
that so whenever it gets scary I can
hide in
here
nice 10 out the 10 animation thank you
this is um old aets from last time I
played uh Thief simulator one and ever
since Thief Simulator 2 has come out uh
apparently at the end of 2023 what the
[\h__\h] did you guys not tell me about it
you probably
did you probably
did did you it's a
sequel and apparently it's a good so we
shall put it to the test for a little
bit of streaming fun but uh
before before I start
little memo
memoro
um
KY oh by the way thank you for those 20
memberships
OMG OMG that's so much thank you a
sequel I don't know would you even call
it a sequel it's just the same game play
right over and over over but anyway
here's the schedule for this week
yesterday was my day off I had a lot of
stuff to record a lot of stuff to do and
then now we're playing fif simulator
tomorrow I think I have
decided for sure for real for real to
switch Friday with
Wednesday if that's
okay um
because it might get way too tight on
Friday for
me um so we're going to do that a bit
earlier than
expected
yeah but apparently some of you guys
uh don't care so that's nice and then
Thursday is just another rest day
because I'll be
busy and Friday will then be members
only chatting most likely just chitt
chitty chatty
chatty I have some things to say to my
members that are on my COC do
um I need to Yap um release some
important
yapping and then and then we have uh
finally uh girl talk for real for real
and then Sunday I'll be gone uh Sunday
and Monday I'll be
gone okay I'm going on a little
trip yes uh one night two days trip I
have a business to take care
of yes yes so does I cannot stream and
does everybody everything else is like
preparation for that like yeah so me me
me me me yes let let get
loose should we play it I'm not going to
play it in full screen because I'm
already taking up so much
screen oh and yeah oh I by the way I
recorded some motion I got it to
work recorded some motion uh I don't
know what it looks like yet I only
recorded the motion I didn't really I
need chagy
to see you know how it looks like I
don't know if it will look good but
um the issue that I had it was just um
in this case it was just my fault uh I
did some
oopsie um but it's like one of those
things like have you tried turning it
off and on again I mean it's something
like that something as simple
but in some way I was glad that
um that you know I was I was like trying
to troubleshoot with goo staff theyve
been so helpful thank you for the
memberships and then goo staff was like
what the [\h__\h] like I was sending uh
samples of what's happening with my with
my motion with my motion yeah I was
sending
that video of screen caps of my motion
sorry motion
and and um and go staff was like what
the [\h__\h] I don't know why this is
happening to you but I would look into
it and we were like you know discussing
what it could be what it could be trying
this and that and then it was just
having the right leg tracker on the left
leg and the other way around but I was
personally happy that I that was not one
of the suggestions because they just
didn't think I was that stupid I
suppose which I will take as a
compliment but it made it even more
embarrassing but it's a compliment to me
that you didn't think that it could be
that simple of just having one track on
the other
leg you know what I mean it's a
compliment
okay okay enough of that enough of
[Music]
that
uh
Play No but I still have other problems
that are you know currently
unsolvable and that I don't think it's a
simple Pro you know the retargeting
problem you know not so simple I cannot
fix this
problem
anyway from Euro Truck Simulator to fief
Simulator 2 what Euro Truck Simulator 2
as well right to the other one wait
you're too big
[Music]
careful careful
careful a thief must know how to be
careful something like
this
okay are we good
I'm actually going to make my je little
B okay truck driver are they Fe by night
oh okay that is now Canon I I'm going to
say that is
Canon where's my mouse yeah where's
my I dare it
okay let's go do some fing I'm guessing
it's like the same as like before
Lear too much about getting caught
typical Thief experience everything is a
challenge but not hard attack anding ah
should have gotten my oh wait my
hand
oh my
no that's what I accidentally touched
okay yeah oh w w w w w it's dangling so
much easy to Bonk
people oh no wait it's dangling it's
dangling so
hard why why you dangle so
much where why what are you attached to
okay this is better no it's attached to
my hair okay okay okay okay sorry sorry
sorry sorry sorry sorry super wobbly
crowbar danger danger I'm just going to
go normal even though I would love to do
go I would love to go easy but for you
guys I'll do normal story mode free mode
no story whatever you want
uhuh there's a story
mode oh sorry you can't see me sorry
well you're not supposed to see me I'm a
thief I'm going to go to your home now
and steal your
panties it's normal that you can't see
me but I'm not happy with
this 2 days
earlier private
number
okay
okay SP wow wow it's so HD is this my
place oh I like how it's like in the
like perfectly in the corner nice
they're coming you have one minute oh
it's not my home he what no 1 minute do
I need to
leave who there cameras oh they really
coming can I jump out of the window oh
yes yes yes oh
[\h__\h] not
going enter the house through the window
what why you
there okay okay
left what through this what
ah didn't open that very quietly this is
like a tutorial but it's already really
stressful oh
OMG oh I was probably supposed to be
careful
there how do I
crouch crouch button is not on the usual
Crouch
[Music]
button see what
not B they don't they have doesn't this
dude have a
gun oh nice Crow Bar flashlight key to
the back may maybe I need this maybe I
need this turn off the light do I need
this wait why is it so not
here I'm scared how do I how do I even I
have guns
oh
yep am I going to kill him I'm going to
kill him maybe oh God he looks like a
burglar got
you
what what I was hoping he would just
faint why did they put the Crowbar there
if I'm not really supposed to use it
like that coming you have 1 minute what
1 minute what happens
[Music]
then what
happens okay so now I got here way
faster
flashlight useless crowbar if I not here
if I'm not supposed to use it then Che
the back he's behind the gate right he's
got a exclamation mark
over the [\h__\h] where where did I
go wait didn't I get a key to the back
it ah do do I run back here yeah
yeah made too
late a
[\h__\h] um oh he went
through well just in case I mean it
didn't work last time but yeah what the
[\h__\h] am I supposed to do
now what just
what
man ah M Mia this is not how it's
supposed to
go he's got a
gun yeah he didn't I guess he didn't
even see me it was too dark and all that
okay bad I better go fast one minute go
go go how do I have to look at this
first okay I don't care I already
know open open run run run
run I don't think I need these items but
maybe I can keep them for the
future oh my car my car my car Chad
stand on okay really
okay my car my car I hope it's my car or
maybe it's not my car cuz I'm a thief go
go I did
it I guned
it I fed I fed
[Music]
successfully
yeah what's this neighborhood called
madis something Madison Madison hello
all right so you're in some deep [\h__\h]
it's took long enough well you're my
friend and all I'll help you get out of
this mess but not for free you have a
whole criminal organization going after
you organiz what can be done let's say
you piss off a few people break into a
couple houses and then you get my help
how's that for starters do make 102 and
steal some [\h__\h] from there empty use
your crowbar to get inside okay we use
crowbar to get inside now
interesting oo that's 101 over there he
wants me to go to
102 look how beautiful this looks wait I
need to fix the
[Music]
chat what about
now what about now
H what about now
there we
go what's in this trash can I hide in
here no too small oh maybe I can hide
behind it like take the same
pose and become the
statue oh hello oh I have to lockpick it
but it was ringing somebody has to pick
it up an ATM in a location like this
what the
[\h__\h] there is the perfect trash
can that's me that's me that's going to
be
me yeah yeah yeah okay 101 is there why
is it not the closest
place 102
look
cute
a
aha excuse me sorry what aha she had a
real aha moment just
now
sorry where do I go
this looks really similar to the old
game I hear it
is what is this I can put a micro camera
inside interesting okay so the first
level has got to be really really really
easy cute to take out the Crowbar aha I
did with scrolling the mouse
wheel should I be really doing this in
broad daylight yeah maybe
oh she's holding something unusual oh
never mind she already put it back
oh is there a back
gate oh there's just Hedges [\h__\h] ton of
Hedges okay then we wait I'm not only
holding something unusual I'm probably
also dressed
unusually I probably should be here I
think they don't like it when
you're when you're like did you just
change hairstyles
H when you're not on uh on the sidewalk
okay use
use oh nice I guess we stay we keep it
open
Money nice random cash we like it
probably going to be easy this one I
don't think anybody's going to come and
bother us let's take a frying
pan the wooden Decor you guys going to
buy that off of me right you guys are my
pawn shop oh you can hide under the
bed I don't know if I want to do that
because hiding under the
bed might get really uncomfortable when
that person does ends up sleeping there
or doing other bad
nanigans not my favorite place to hide
the best place to hide is after all the
trash
can anything important what is this
it hello
books oh oh what happened with the
shower curtain why is it like
this why is it so
stiff oh American
bathtubs they're so low I don't get it
they're so low I I think I talked about
this before but
oh let's take
this American bathtubs and Japanese
bathtubs and Western bathtubs are all
like kind of
different like I just heard
something okay I need to bring
this okay to my
car all right let's go
easy yay well I'm already several met
away and the law the book of laws says
where once you're 10 m away from the
property where you just stole things
from nobody can say anything about it
so is mine now finders keep
it
yay fief FM should I turn this off is
this
copyright doesn't sound like it where do
I go is the S on the map maybe
my wait still enough to level up but
wait did it even
count did do the EXP not just count once
you go
back wait the
SS still
more what what
what guess it wasn't enough am I going
to get fined for parking
really hopefully not what how many XP do
I
have
H where is does it
say I guess I'll just oh there we go
oh very nice time to sell this stuff so
you can pay me brother drive to Crazy
Joe's Pawn Shop He's My Pal okay he in
the same neighborhood numberers
115 ooh wine might be good frying pan
all right all right all
right
oh that's a typical Sims
uh
whistle nobody there
bamboozle I love how Sims whistle all
the time let's
go perfect they have nothing left in
their home I'm a raccoon now maybe maybe
always have been e it looks like a
fif dressed in all
black dude what are you doing there
you're kind of
suspicious there can only be one thief
in this
neighborhood oh is this the pawn
shop looks like it doesn't it okay let's
park
then does it just register or do I have
to like put the bring the painting with
my own
hands
inside what do you
think oh nice car damn they got some
cool nice cars
now
M great paring thank you not bad right
oh oh perfect parking and this is
actually quite the quite the Masterpiece
merry freaking Christmas what Merry
Christmas welcome to Crazy Jo I buy
everything well almost Stone things are
preferable to sell big items just Dro
them on the floor and talk to me oh I do
have to bring them over huh free time
surprise today's hot
item an
iPad
oh here take this I talk to you now do
you have the painting
Yes 120
bucks
12 15 20 nice ooh 30 for the China BAS
you like the thumbnail thank you
Christina drew the
artwork 20 120 35 ooh the wine is good
okay so the the white china vase I'm
going to remember and wine do it for the
vine pretty good oh this looks like a
like in this scale it looks like a
really really small like children's
swing
okay sell all should be good
money I want it on black Bay wait wait
wait wait I should have no sold it
should I have ah to I just realized
there were several ones [\h__\h] that was an
issue too like last time I played this
the first one I don't I only realized
until later that these were like wanted
things oh well we're still in the
beginning we still have chances of
getting all these things but at least
they show it there that's
it'll be rent for your new Hideout I
need something from 104 and to break in
there we need a drone Dr the guy 103
ordered a drone so I steal drone from
103 we have to find out when he goes to
work learn how to Mark people we
ah okay where do I learn the marking
skill do I just go there 103 wait what
104 has the Drone or 103 has the Drone
10 103 has the Drone right
hello who are
you I have the lockpick to get in who
are
you he's just staring at his black
laptop there's nothing on the screen
he's just sitting
there 103 has the Drone 104 I steal from
Once I have the Drone you you're saying
that wrong spicy chicken butt because in
the end I'm also stealing from
103 I'm going to be stealing from 103
okay here we go
ikim beep F
FM wait what was that what was that
radio meme you guys kept on like showing
me on the on the Twitter tag two people
two people brought it
up I could recreate that uh where did I
go one
of three four
this is 102 I need to listen to the OG
so I know what tone it
is W you're listening to W
radio uh 11 15 no no no no no no no no
what where where is the
right
woohoo oh
welcome to VA
radio you're listening
to you are listening to F
102.3 or 102.3 EV where we only play F
tunes and only F Tunes is not your
grandma station
love brush I feel it every every day
that's too loud
oh it's loud by default you just have to
um you know raise skill level of your
ears okay here's 103 was I supposed to
take the Drone from 103 H he just left
wait wait we have to mark
him how to Mark hello is your name Mark
oh oh ah he
left what do you think was his name mark
was he a
mark
[\h__\h] how do I what maybe it wasn't ah
open the skill
tabuh best radio
station W
radio but I probably need to pass time
to have him come back
learn marking SK oh wait new tutorial
skills T ah in your inventory you can
select the skills tab to acquire new
abilities you have to level up to get
new points you can use to level up still
as many things as you can
mhm skills
tab okay is this barking M
Mark I can mark all the marks in the
world any marks in the chat I'm marking
you
you yes yes learn what's next
lockpicking
o I hope we can unlock the lockpicking
I'm going to lockpick the lockpicking
skin somewhere visible at 300 p.m. 1500
Military Time wait it out in the parking
lot and then go to the spot I marked for
you okay is it 103 or
104 I keep on forgetting but I have to
wait but the the Mark I don't see the
Mark or is it the S that's probably that
but 300 p.m. is a long time to
go is it one over okay I'm supposed to
wait
here
ah and now we
wait why can't I just not just go in now
I probably could but they want me to
mark there's a break
there all
right I shall pass some
time oh I know I know I can
read uh 15
o sleep until oh I don't think we were
able to like adjust this so nicely
good
sleep oh 1 hour is 1 minute oh
dear okay here we
go the irony of me leaving my car open
when somebody could totally feed my car
when I do that but I guess nobody's
going to do that they should uh invent
Arma in this
game and have my car
fed okay I'm ready how do I Mark just
click on them probably when it happens
is this
Mark no no he's not coming this way
Mark
oh [\h__\h]
oops that wasn't on purpose H
Mark
Mark Mark is it you mark hello
Mark no what I think he just came
out I just heard a sound ah
Mark have you got eyes on him Mar his
ass so we know when he's out I Mar I
marked his back not his ass
unfortunately all right now do some
planning you'll see his next
destinations it's a very handy skill how
do I know this how do I have this
knowledge see that saved you the need of
going through the journal my sources say
he leaves the house at 5:00 p.m. there's
a problem though uhhuh you can't break
in with the Crowbar because the guy has
a sound alarm trigger I jump from here
lock picking oh drive to your new
Hideout and check the computer I have a
task for you which will gain you some
more experience oh okay but does this
mean
15 3:00 p.m. to 4:00 p.m. he's between
the time he's going to leave cuz he said
at 5:00 p.m. he's gone oh ah
uhhuh well he he's doing something in
there during this time and then he's
going to leave 300 p.m. to 400 p.m. is
when he's doing some weird F fumbling on
the ground
okay all right all right all right all
right r r r r r
r we're going to go to my new totally
super fancy hideout
but first we must listen to the wah
radio we're only the best tracks are
being played at all
times only your favorites here at wa FM
listen to it while you're driving listen
to it while you're cooking listen to it
while you're
sleeping only the best sounds on Wawa FM
uh where is my Hideout they're not
showing
it I'm just GNA drive here drive out of
the area yeah okay
okay yeah oh good radio good radio FM I
could only afford once no I have more
but it's only fitting one for now I
think or hello ain't this house nice
just pay me the rent weekly and you're
fine get some cash you can do repairs on
house renovator yo go to the computer I
have to show you around in your new
world house renovating
simulator yo if you guys remember last
time in fee simulator 1 our Hideout was
just like a garage now we got an actual
cute looking nice little house honestly
like this is so American to me I would
love to have something like this all the
lights up here and this like
what porch front porch you can put a
little a little bench here
a this so
[Music]
cute and it's so spacious too and we
have like garden and is that a huge dog
house or is it house for future
children I'm going to keep my future
children in here maybe like enough space
for
five what would you
say I think that's fitting or I'll make
a a cat house out of it
yeah nice bench
swing oh a
workbench
wow wao
electricity
box it's
going uhhuh wao look at the sky it's
burning wo oh oh oh I switched suddenly
to uh
blue okay okay okay gas gas gas
gas okay well uh yeah the floor boards
missing here and there needs needs some
some
fixing ah
okay I have a feeling that he stole his
house
oh a nice plate of grilled Meats and
veggies how the hell did you get this
kind of like Grill like pattern in in a
in a frying pan like
that not realistic if you ask me you got
to you got to put that on the
grill to make it look like
that oh oh oh learn pick pocketing
skills to practice at at a body like
this how how is that going to work
how is that going to
work
oh well this this part of the house
doesn't look so bad the kitchen is uh
too
tiny for the size of the house let's be
honest like there's no working space
pretty
much kind of sad could have used more of
the
space
w that looks not bad either
cute I like this table that is obviously
for
Ika oh oh I have C I have safety
cameras or just
one nice though oh that looks so cozy
actually looks like a like an air
mattress actually it looks really
cozy yeah the PC is high high not high
end but
looks modern I mean look at that screen
it's really
thin okay check out Ste gain experience
better tools will become available to
you okay steel gear on Rob tips you can
buy information about houses loot
location security tenant routines Etc
all information about 102 free of
charge we'll get 102 free of
charge did we
but we already robbed one or two but I
guess we can go back bye bye bye bye
black you can sell items you stole
through there they sometimes offer much
better prices than the pawn shop it's
always empty yeah okay always empty
bathroom window open broken fence behind
the home alarm on
draw thank God I didn't I didn't open
that oh dear oh takak chan oh you can't
see it oh my
my trash thing is perfectly hiding my uh
steam
name
nice hey it's already hiding it you
don't have to ride it out the the whole
thing on in the chat now just because
you know it already you little [\h__\h] hell
neighbor like I said before you need
more experience before you can learn
lockpicking accept the job at
102 oh yeah gladly get the hang of it
you can browse other websites there are
plenty but not crucial for us now get
off the PC when you're ready plant
evidence I I have some plant
evidence when you steal things and
complete jobs you get experience with
enough experience you can learn
new picking which is needed to break
into
103 get to 102 and complete the job you
just accepted should be rather easy
wait I always forget this is evidence
that there is plant okay smash a few
things is a task
okay uh uh complete the task smash a few
things okay let's go back to one2 where
nobody will ever disturb us let's
go Madison
Street well timed yeah
totally after you hack an ATM it will be
locked out for a week w
Dave speaking have you checked stolen
rewards you can receive nice perks if
you complete where is there well on the
map there's a sign can you see it it's a
sign for uh a shovel here right
here do I have to dig can I
dig I want to
dig the driving is really smooth look
it's smoother than in the previous
game but never really was an issue I
think and
102 I think when your car stands like
randomly around they get angry at
you so I better leave it
here your driving is just that good now
must be the driving pretty much blind
while singing practice
oh I yeah
crowbar here we go it's
open dinner is served is there something
here to
destroy
money what what was that star sign do I
smash this oh oh no I feel so bad what
did that chair ever do to
me you here
H what did the chair do to me key okay
let's remember to not open the chest uh
next to the bed like this here right
there's an alarm
here oh wait it do they mean oh
oh it just means the alarm clock is on
the
drawer oh but you guys misunderstood as
well I thought it meant I can't open
this Donuts ooh yummy well then I I
think I'll probably be able to sell that
and this e table lamp you mean
Ika
okay something here no okay smash
let's smash
this scandalous ooh wine is good to
sell you think I might need the pot what
do you think probably need
everything oh oh it's
behind I'll take it can I carry this
much
yeah yeah we could it's going to get
annoying later when I have to carry
things to the car and then come back
very
dangerous who whoa whoa who what do we
smash a the the the Stars disappear when
I get too close and then I'm
confused what who called him that thing
is next door called the cops hide in the
dumpster or
something
offic you think they saw
meop right now
did you see him did you see
him okay I'm just going to I'm just
going to run for
it I hope he's not behind
me oh he's running after
me I'm being
shot y
b cops are L to the location but what if
I leave the
location holy
[\h__\h] holy
[\h__\h] what
unavailable it's like GTA I'm losing the
star
okay oh my
god oh that was kind of scary I know I
I'm already a
dumpster this works I I I didn't want to
look around too
much he was shooting me I'm just a
little small
fief they nerfed leaving the town oh
they totally did it would be really
funny if you got caught escapes trained
Assassins but he can't escape a
policeman who ate a donut crime scene
time to learn lockpicking you still
somehow don't have he also from
102 I can pet the cat I can pet the
[Music]
cat okay what did what was he saying I
was a little bit distracted but uh let
me check a black
Bay
first before I can do that here right
yeah yeah yeah yeah black
Bay
uh I need I need the second tea as
well toaster knife
holder I need another frying pan and a
teapot oh dear
okay there's no like single
items
uh bi boo
statue self-made
gun okay then yeah I can't sell anything
yet the items aren't
single
oh that's
already one way they one uped
me oh what the hell why is it so dirty
ew why does the PC look so good but the
bathroom
the I mean I think that's like kind of
dirt just from being old so you can
probably remove it
somehow but yeah what's with this music
you don't like it this my
house a man lives there that's me I live
here I live here
now okay what did he say I should go to
uh ah wait learn the lockpicking
skill sure easy
enough call me I knew I knew it brother
take out your phone and order a nice
basic lockpicking tool you can buy it at
your PC too but it' be a wasted time to
drive there oh he doesn't realize I'm
actually at
home uh oh I can buy what
[Music]
where H buy a basic lock picking
tool what
where F Well I will uh Buy on the
computer even though he says maybe I
don't need to basic lockpicking tool
there okay okay
okay what else do we have in the future
500 for micro camera
noisy walkie-talkie dog meat oh is there
going to be dogs that we'll have to like
distract
oh
doggles ooh they're going to get us in
trouble why do only some of them show
price I guess they don't want me to buy
it yet they don't want me to
like get like a [\h__\h] ton of money early
on and then buy this so
really Bow Bow Bow Bow Bow 500 for a
shovel yeah what the [\h__\h] but then we
can shovel dig dig dig in those uh spots
I already saw like two or so there's one
in my backyard
too oh so you have the tool you can
practice on a lock in 102 if you want is
always good okay break into 103 and
steal the Drone it's big so you can't
miss it just make sure to check your
journal and see when the guy is out
uh-huh practice at 102 maybe and steal
uh burlar awareness day and Ste at
103 but I want to go to the pawn shop
first I need to sell oh but then ah I
don't really remember ah I should have
put my stuff there I don't really
remember what and shin I need forit
money
black make sure to check should I go
back and just leave all the things that
I requested a black Bay in my
home
maybe ah it's pointed out in oh you're
right okay okay never mind okay thank
you thank you for reminding me small
brain only few brain cells I
has okay pawn shop was at the PE or is
that a parking spot normally that means
parking spot I think oh yeah it's just a
parking
spot
uh oh oh so ooh nice restaurant over
there can we can we f it as
well where is
what is this the pawn
shop look for the dollar
sign okay those are just normal
s's but I was there
before is
this no looks
different there's a playground here no
no that's a
station I was born to
Fe I like that you guys all use the same
way of
writing
Thief makes me feel connected to you huh
where is this is this the porn a
[Music]
porn how are the theves doing on with
Thief is this the porn chop to steal to
no wait I think I see it
what do I is this the porn shop this is
the porn
shop
uh that's exactly what I
meant
[Music]
yeah it's embarrassing
yeahi hey what's up okay wanted wanted
not wanted wanted okay
I'll sell you only that
Goodbye Oh there's a door open
here okay
one2 for lockpicking practice and
103 for wait I still have so much stuff
can I put the stuff in my car like
generally like even the smaller things
then I don't want to have it in my
backpack it's already taking up so much
space ah there we go I no not this one
one this this
this and no okay good wait no I'm
staying uh no I'm going
in well the porn shop could very well
also be selling some
porn stolen
porn yeah
that [\h__\h] turns me on as a
thief uh where do I where is
here check the calendar on your phone to
see if any event is coming up maybe
people will leave the house for some
weird Festival oh
reallying wait burglar awareness day
does that mean nobody's at home no I
guess everybody's at home except for
102 okay it's like 10
a.m. soop just get
out everyone's
aware yeah but even if you're aware of
something doesn't mean that you're
necessarily going to do anything about
it
right so we go in here
again oh oopsie
oh oh I opened the door
normally this is cute
okay
oh ah it's just a random lock on a table
for me to
lockpick oh remember how I struggled
with this but then I figured it out and
then it was okay uh how does this work
how does this work again my cables are
all over
me um wait I only have one Lockpick
amount I can only pick once and then I
have to buy a new one or what 50 bucks
for nothing how does this work I like
turn it a little bit right what this
what's the D ah
huh
ah did I just first try
it did that work if did did it
work or was that it
I think that means it worked
right hello do you have a frying
pan oh he's not stalking back up again
what's gone is gone a toaster why did I
not look there
before nice cutting
board okay okay the toaster is
good Freddy box for
[Applause]
free ah man I love my
job a freaking
radio oh yeah oh yeah always check
what's in the
closets okay I think can I take dis now
can I take this
no
okay have I outfeed
myself think I checked here before what
about
here what could be in here no okay
nothing interesting and
here not even free
money
what o I can open this up huh
oh how did
this how how was this hole created in
the first place okay we have passed time
pretty
nicely I'm going to don't don't mind
me don't mind me let me have my crowbar
what's unusual about this in this day
and age crowbars should be you know
objects that are welcome in any
neighborhood
n know my should have familiarized you
with
it okay my lockpicking tool still exists
so I don't understand the onetime use
thing I don't even know if that worked
at all or not but
anyway uh
okay he
oh Mark how are you doing mark
Mark aha I see you're still going to
stay in here for a little while huh
you're just wasting your time wait his
name is
Gustavo false in false house I'm looking
for Mark Mark are you here
hello yeah uh
ooh Why is what's this red light where
is it coming
from oh there it is can I Mark the
camera but it's not at the door what
what's even the
point I guess it's just a red like this
to show me what it captures IRL it
wouldn't be red like this see like no
I'm I'm sure it brings good money
right
oh or is he
leaving no not yet it's uh uh 2:00
p.m.
mhm I know everything about
you you're just rivering away on your
couch all
day what's the
star destroy the window is that a a task
but that's probably going
to oh I need a oh okay now that's just
here so I can practice safe cracking one
day probably this is just a tutorial
house all
Vines huh
hes I'm pressing
e doesn't work maybe I need to learn how
to
climb H I would love to take the entire
safe it looks kind of heavy safes
are probably really heavy wait I can't
use e here either so what I
just hidden item found I just got 100
bucks what detection this my house this
is my house have you seen anyone walk in
or out here out of this house besides me
no it's my house it's my house it's my
house okay he's doing the the weird
thing on the ground
now is he like tying his
shoes is that supposed to be tying his
shoes yeah I wonder what I'm dressed
like I can't possibly be dressed like a
thief that would be the end of
[Music]
me okay oh oh never
mind he's tying his other
shoe you got it bro need some
help I can help you with your shoes in
exchange for
oh what is he doing I know maybe he's
like supposedly doing something by the
the
Shelf he just dropping a lot of things
I'm dropping my marbles let me pick them
all up again 1 2 three 4 5 six
seven I ah one more to nine 10 I got him
I got him I got him I got them all oh
wait I dropped them all again 1 2 three
4 five 6 7 8 9 10 11 12
13 okay okay oh wa I dropped him again
oh 1 two three four five six seven ah
these MERS one two three four five six
7even 8 9 10 a [\h__\h] this [\h__\h] I keep on
losing count 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11
12 these
mares 1 2 3 4 6
8 my man do you need help with your
marbles oh he dropped them again he
thought he was oh he's got his marbles
he's leaving with his marbles okay how
do I
enter says break in so maybe just
through the front
door okay he's
gone but he's only gone for a few
hours ah
oh I was supposed to use the
lockpick
oh sorry I wasn't
thinking trash
[Music]
can God damn
it that's why I learned it I know but I
thought maybe I have to use it on
something else maybe maybe a safe or a
door inside should probably put away my
crowbar I'm not I'm not holding anything
in particular I I I I'm sorry I'm
sorry oh I'm losing I'm losing it I'm
losing
it okay then then we still have time
okay let's
go is this house
right yeah okay one more try Poli Vamos
a it's open
oh see okay I thought maybe like for
this
uh how does it
work ah do you go like
diagonally with what am I supposed to
steal the Drone
right well the Drone is probably not
here but I need the frying
pan thanks nice
than
goodness okay just got to keep an eye on
the time oh I can hide in
here drone do
oh also Oh I thought I could take
something who whoa that's a big
boy oh table lamp I take I take the
Drone I probably have to carry with my
hands is this wait there's a key a key
to his home so I don't have
to break in anymore I see that as an
open
invitation right we're besties now I
have your key that means we're
besties oh I was able to just put it in
my bag nice you got it cool you need to
upgrade it so it can disable cameras
there's a camera at the entrance to
104 sell some Loot and check out drone
Tech on your computer take your
time all right I'm taking my
time nice always look for every single
one of them guys you see you will be
rewarded what is
this what is
this power switch oh no
oh oh good stuff head statue and the the
nice the nice
vase oh and the robit one all
righty I'm quite happy with my
loot just going to just going to SK
outle let's run oh is that the break a
box
ah I got a good amount of stuff yeah
nice
haul maybe I should do a little haul
fief haul video wait are
there not that I want to support
thiefing or so but are there Thief hauls
on
YouTube that be so funny kind of in a
way like this is what I stole so this is
what I stole today at 103 that stupid
idiot called Mark I I totally got like
everything that is dear to him I got
this super cute little uh V I'm going to
put my stolen flowers in there as well
yeah sto them from his
[Laughter]
[Music]
backyard yeah you you would hope that
doesn't exist but I mean actually maybe
you would hope that it exist exist
because then you can report them and
maybe maybe somebody could get their
stuff
back if if a fief is that stupid to make
a video like that then they shall be
rewarded by getting
caught uh wait sorry small brain why did
I go here I should have gone to the um
pawn shop but I have the wine
set
yo nice to so I'm not selling that again
huh o I got both lamps and I still need
like a normal radio oh where was
that no huh
oh never mind what did I
see oh so much
stuff
valuables got nothing wait really what
about that other head wasn't golden but
Rock statue orange vase ah China vase
head statue we need a small vase ah that
one I sold before but they don't stock
the house back up maybe it's in
101 just do an off collab and use some
of the girls stuff for fif fall
stream but then what how how I like the
idea to just fief from
oh
no could could I make this into a
stream like staying over at a member's
place and
then taking something from them
obviously giving it back
but how
I have to think about this
one oh my God I'm going to get fired for
stealing from my
[Music]
co-workers okay okay okay we're going to
go to the pawn shop what do you mean
that's
illegal just let me have my
fun uh if I want to sell stuff do I have
to put it in my
bag
probably it' be like a little exposive
thing you try to steal an
item reverse reverse be but like like I
don't know that's what's so sneaky about
it I it's so easy expose them well then
I definitely want to get their
permission beforehand because you
know hey I'm going to steal this from
you and then expose you is that
okay cuz otherwise you know it's private
stuff um but we could make it into a
dramatic
thing man we always got the best ideas
usually they come from me but this one
this one I'll I'll credits to you guys
although it was kind of inspired by
something I said
oh piggy
bank right the piggy bank
incident I need to find the pawn shop
again that takes highest amount of
concentration I think it's somewhere
here
is
no I'm not stealing your ideas it's it's
it's
mine oh okay my bag is
full hello are you open at this time of
day well well that's just
crazy what my full bag I know okay sell
sell and
sell and sell the rest I keep thank you
toaster oh I need all of this [\h__\h]
let put it back into the
car here here here here here here
okay
M when I sell something on black Bay
does it consider the things I have in my
car I think it does cuz does it does it
does
it storage home too
[Music]
yeah I wonder if it is that anyway how
are theie do go home buy a wait I need
to buy something uh buy a camera disable
modu module on drone tech oh for that I
have to go home God damn
it I didn't read it but okay well before
we
go will 101 become a mission at some
point Jefferson suggested level five
I'm level three oh this is like more of
a I thought it would be even easier than
the abandoned
house
huh local
junkyard can I check the local junkyard
it doesn't say anything about the
level you're lagging if you're lagging
you might want to close the chat seems
to be an issue recently
hello is this a local
junkyard oh uh wait no no that was
something else that was somewhere over
there I think
so I probably can't get in that easily
can
I a lockpicking level two
necessary oh
oh o oh someone's in
there well
okay please don't drive against my door
careful
careful excuse
me you are awfully close to my car I'm
going to call the police on you I'm
going to film this incident I'm going to
put it up on on
Facebook and then you're going to be
filming me back while I'm filming you
you oh it's so funny when when you're
like facing a Karen I mean I never had
this happen to me I just watch videos of
it but when you're facing a Karen and
you start filming the incident because
it's just crazy and you need proof and
then a Karen films you
back but the thing is they're like
complaining about being filmed and then
they just film you back but then I think
they have a right to film you back
totally like even if their main
complaint is you filming them like how
dare you film me you're not allowed to
film me W how dare you film me you
little [\h__\h] but then yeah I I I get them
wanting to film you back as a payback as
a
protection that makes
sense but usually it's just the most
ridiculous situations I love watching
those kind of videos Karen
compilations okay what camera disable
module uh no not
here still
here so I didn't read I didn't read
properly a drone Tech
maybe yeah 300
bucks shees battery module speed module
can I actually control this
thing great stuff now you can disable a
camera with your drone it'll come in
handy a lot buy all information about
104 on Rob tips so there are no
surprises I won't hold your hand for
much
longer 104 he's going to stop holding my
hand guys will you hold my hand then two
cameras one at the front gate and the
other one at the back the side window is
open tenants routines have been revealed
where to
whom oh oh to
okay I guess I just I'm just going to be
able to see it now PC unit in the main
room receiver in the storage
area headphones I can't remember all of
this main room storage area metal cabin
I'll just find it on my own don't worry
okay but the cameras are important front
gate and on the
back so two guys at 104 but they both
leave at a certain time should check it
out in your Journal oh no go there
disable the camera at the entrance with
your drone and I'll call you about your
next step okay just at the
entrance you just just want me to do it
at the end wait huh 104 the local
junkyard need to you don't need to
remember game we'll show them again
okay there
is no time window where
both no wait I know ah okay from
Midnight
to what was it like 3 it starts it
ends at 3:00 a.m. 3 hours and then 1
hour over here midnight to 3:00 a.m.
okay now it's
4 we got to pass some time again uh let
me see let me break bring my things into
my home storage then taking a peek at
work when you're not supposed
to taking taking a little
peek maybe I should hide and you should
hide too we should hide together in here
you and me then nobody will know
[Music]
sh everybody
hide
Ste are they watching are they
watching sneaky NY n n n n NY sneaking
like a
snake stealth
1,000 minimum
1,000 okay where do I where can I put
this in
here nice
okayy NY sneaking like a
snake um madon what is this sign it's
the police out now what was that always
there sneaky
n sne just for
you how's it still burglar awareness day
is it does that mean like burglar
awareness day every day oh that's so
nice of them I'm so glad that people are
so aware of
Me no they're not aware of me I'm a
thief not a
burglar big
difference where's
104 I saw right there no that's 100 that
is not the local track a
place 104 there's 103 over there maybe
around the
corner ah ah here it is is this is this
how they number houses in America for
real because it feels like there is no
good
system no okay do you have a better
system I think for example in Japan I
noticed it's really oh I don't even know
how post PE post office people get
things to people at all I don't know how
they even do it wait Did I need to bring
my drone no okay it's in
there somehow
it's
worse how do I ge whoa can
I disabling it now is maybe a is that
too
early ooh intuitive
controls should I be doing this now
while they're still there probably fine
right oh
I lost the
Drone there's a cardboard box with my
stuff inside workers were supposed to
send it to me but it's still there it's
heavy so put it in your truck and bring
it
home I was too far from
me okay uh he needs stuff that's in in
here okay wait why is it not the time
that I thought
ah I thought I was I slept until
midnight
that didn't
work oh I pressed go back I'm so
dumb get a drone immedately loses it
isn't realistic I guess so I never used
a drone before I mean it's probably not
much different from like a like a what
do you call like these little cars that
you control with like a controller
remote control remote cars remote
whatever oh where do I enter is it just
open oh dude oh yeah okay wait dude is
still there wanted is that
me wait that's me a slim tall white male
wearing a beret in a Lea jacket with
seen breaking into
houses that's me oh one more poster
remaining I wonder where it is that's
me okay two Camas
one should I uh wait uh
g g g g g that's probably too
[Music]
far how do I get
lower if this is higher [\h__\h]
I don't know [\h__\h] I got to go it's
time hey it's
time as Mariah caree
says okay nobody should be inside
now let me in wait uh window side window
open Where's where where is the
window did you guys see a window
what there's just
a really thick
wall it's already
one
this go faster my
God uh [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] ah I lost
it it shouldn't have been smashing it
what ah I got no
time ah two 2
hours uh uh
window okay I got a I got I got a
receiver what am I supposed to get
receiver I got saer PC unit and wait
does he need
this is this what he
needs whoa whoa whoa what what PC unit
in the main storage
room
this open open
a good that you can throw PCS in this
game uh headphones and metal cabinet
what hour where where the headphones
what the [\h__\h] speaker uh I guess I can
come back
here scanner so much stuff where the
[\h__\h]
H one ah I want
to metal metal maybe maybe this is meant
with metal cabinet but it's got to be at
the bottom cuz I can't see
nice cash
no
no regular wallet where the [\h__\h]
what just going to take this
all ah ah ah ah
ah I'm going to I'm going to I'm going
to I'm going to I'm going to take this
uh
uh yeah where's my don't don't even look
don't even say anything don't even
dare I'm going to have to leave those
things
behind is it in is
in but are they I think they're just
going to either be like put back into
place
or okay yeah or or they're going to stay
there until next time
the Box yeah it's okay I'm going to come
again
or what do you think can I tant found
tenant found an Open
Door tenant found an Open
Door tenant found an open door door with
you
found an open
door
door I'm coming back don't worry I'll be
back
um
well
but what those things were just tasks
but I don't need to sell it to a
particular place right
I can sell them wherever I want to right
this is black Bay black Bay black Bay
regular World
also keep
ah is the PC properly placed yeah okay
well the computer these big items I'm
guessing I can't sell those in Black Bay
right cuz like
how how
that's too dark but that's
normal that is normal in fifth game but
I can
try make it a bit
wider
oh
brightness on night
brightness better
right there's particular night
brightness I think I'm going to go to
the pawn
shop am I going to or just like stay and
wait for the next
timing Dave speaking have you checked
stolen rewards you can receive nice
perks if you complete certain tasks
there's an s on my
car oh nice
car the thing is on
again okay let's pass
time let's go back in time no actually
let's start from here it's too stressful
ah
[\h__\h]
sleep better much better
okay if I Could Turn Back Time
then I would go to
sleep
okay
drone my baby
drone
oh got to be
careful R but then how do I go
lower enter
no
oh oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
can we get much lower maybe just let me
try one more time if I just start at
this height and don't go in lower higher
at all I
can't ah left shift
ah oh
I think I cannot act deactivate this one
ah H oh
well it is time oh Z oh is it like one
per
night but when I want to be a monkey
it's hard to be a monkey
hello how's the guying
gang this
window
uh so did they put things back yeah seal
the card there's not even is there even
anything in here why are we stealing the
cardboard box Just For
Shenanigans H I know
do they have a flashlight yeah but I
don't need
it the mouse might be a set with
something okay these uh headphones I'm
still looking for ooh a multimeter what
is that is that for ghost
hunting
[Music]
calculator toaster another one I
probably don't need another
one headphones in the the metal
cabinet am I misunderstanding this this
is a metal cabinet
no maybe a different
one why would it be here that's not
metal
anyway the thing on the ground now this
is this is a safe this one I can't open
I think cuz right or maybe maybe I can
oh okay I thought it was a
safe I don't think it's a safe
anymore okay I'm kind of done
oh where did this money come from and
the radio
set
okay okay I'm ready to go I think I have
it all loot side yep yep got to get the
books wasn't there something else I
threw outside wasn't there free things I
threw
outside oh maybe there's something
around here
too just a
[Music]
box oh oh oh you meant to crawl bar I
thought you meant the Box yeah there's
nothing unusable about the cardboard box
right oh bring it home okay bring it
home it's just a box
yeah what would be so weird about me
carrying a box is obviously the
Crowbar just a box
move I'm just a box just a box just a
trash can just a box ah
Moy okay I assume you have the box and
it didn't fall out of your trunk it like
a normal man does with a knife what's
inside must remain a mystery s to me via
once you have
it oh well can't take
it wait does he mean it really open it
with a knife or is that just
like
huh open it with a
knife what can I just uh
huh
what maybe here no h
huh how do I open
it
oh
H I have to buy a knife
or knife there's a there's obviously
this thing here but I can't pick it
up can I what
how do I open the box got the diamond
icon ah ah ah oopsie okay okay okay ah
here is this like the inspection
area uhhuh uh-huh and then
what oh where did that knife suddenly
come from what's in there black package
that that doesn't really reveal to me
what what it is but okay send the
condence Via black Bay ah send it via
black
Bay wow
[Music]
magic send a black B
ohuh oh he is the commissioner for this
one okay can I give
anything ah oh
woohoo a full PC set let's go I got a
scanner I need a drawing tablet maybe I
can give them my
own just helping
out where my help is
needed I still need the freaking small
vase will I forever regret selling my
first
loot great you're really helping me
right now I'll make sure to repay that
there's a few more things though h I
need you to plant a certain package at
110 in the bedroom be careful though you
can't be seen by the guy a certain
package in a bedroom needs to be
planted what what could it
be freaking
bomb May did you give me the
package how am I just going to
what let me check also black
stuff so it did show that I have the
scanner so I think having it in my car
is
okay in
theory okay but I want to sell some of
these things and some of these things
I'm going to put back into the
home so scanner the wallet and a
multimeter
nice nice look at my nice
loot Free
[Music]
Fall welcome to the fif Hall of
[Applause]
Fame thank you thank you thank you thank
you thank you yeah yeah you like that
one okay um
[Music]
um where was I going to go to the pawn
shop where is the pawn
shop you don't have to cheer alone any
you were never alone everybody in the
chat is audibly cheering at all
times you just have to imagine it well
well that's just crazy
oh you want the teapot huh I can give
you an alarm clock for 40 a you found
damaged for 100
nice calculator Robert
wine radio set keyboard for 30 toaster
for 40 speaker for 15 that's a funky
speaker receiver for 75 and high
what
he what kind of headphones are these
what are
those
sick sick and
tight I love my
job no more H life fing all day
24/7 mm
Mark Mark what are you doing Mark be
careful H uh one 11 10 11 one
one0 do not
here
probably around the
corner my wife stole it's nice and shiny
have you been on dark 105 wait did I
make sure check it out 106
107 it bothers me that I'm not thiefing
in the order of the
numbers that's
ridiculous there it is right that's so
ridiculous thank you I I'm saying the
same thing thank you for
understanding
okay uh we don't know yet right we need
to mark
Mr Mark are you in
here may
I oh you look suspicious to me cuz of
how you walk never
mind I guess he's homeless or
so but he still walks weirdly you think
that's Mark oh oh Mark Mark Mark Mark
Mark Mark I couldn't Mark him
Mark
[\h__\h]
oh he h
me just a bush just a bush oh no oh
no
I what where did he go I thought he'd
totally come here
agility
agility ah ah ah it's
[Applause]
[Music]
close trash trash trash if they see me
they can shoot at me now they weren't
able to shoot at me like in the last
last
game I can't even I don't I need a back
mirror I need to see if there's still
behind me if I need to be
stressing I'm being chased it says oh
there there's something good come on
come
compromised
really what why
why why
why why what what there was no one
around ah I'm
okay I'm blocking the
way I had some business to do oh hi Poli
vamos
Amigos what because of my car well I had
to get back to it didn't I wait why are
we why what because of the car
on the wa let me ah really cuz of the
car I have a simple solution for
that I'm just going to drive I'm just
going to drive away okay be take down
gun be why are they so what if I'm
illegally parking just give me a ticket
or toe on my
truck no need to get so aggressive be
[Music]
okay okay okay okay okay okay he walks
like a chicken on
with oh okay okay escaping is pretty
easy
actually oh my God punishable by
execution ex execution of
me please please
no okay so I I don't know how all of
this just happened that was oh wait I
shouldn't Park
here what have we just
learned um there's a parking space
there
execution
oh sorry I did that for you guys that's
why I was a little bit late
[Laughter]
uh how how did all of this
happen I just wanted to Mark him and
then I went into his backyard okay well
I guess
maybe you
know there we
go finally is he what leaving at 1 no he
just be in the front
garden and I'll be watching
him and judging him
suspicious package inside them oh wait
he won't is the green part when he's
gone I think
so then he won't be gone for a
while is he going to react that I'm when
I'm standing here
no I'm is his name mark no at Le Leo
[\h__\h] from one for moment I thought it
was actually Mark no that's your house
no no no this is Leo's house don't don't
worry
so every step you take I every move you
make I'll be watching
you Every Breath You
[Music]
Take
every every plant you
take every dream you dream every food
you make
I'll be watching
you I sang that in Koka before for you
guys I
think why why the point there's no point
in marking him now right I already know
what he's doing at this time of the
[Music]
day this one is archived yeah
wait I need a new crowbar how am I going
to get in otherwise I have no fing
tool how do I buy from here he said I
could buy from here right wait have a
depth of four 500 oh my
God what do
I what is
this can I you have a shop on your phone
am I
blind
huh well there a skill
tree I could unlock something new I
think pick pocket pick pocket every
person find out what they hide in their
jeans let's
go you can open the phone while
outside
ahuh oh they did not really teach me
about this she just said oh yeah you can
buy it from your phone but
how uh navigate
oh quick
buy ah oh but I can't buy a crowbar what
it's more expensive on here wasn't it 50
bucks
originally e to you too
lady I guess this is realistic oh wait
did I just say there's no crowbar am I
[\h__\h] blind it's 100
bucks oh
my yeah it's more expensive like this
cuz I'm getting it immediately without
going somewhere else with it I guess
makes
sense this pig pocke thing how does that
work is there a chance for me to fail I
think I can practice it so that must
mean oh nice
shortcut since I can practice it that
must
mean
that I can also fail there's a right way
to do
it it's like a fishing mini game oh that
sounds
fun fif universe
what the [\h__\h] yeah how much do a kill
bar cost IRL I never tried buying
one
obviously cuz I fed
them I just I just take them oh there's
a brick
here what if I
just maybe not
now but good to
know brick has been
acknowledged brick and Mark
I know everything about
you he's leaving
soon he's in the back
Garden want to try pick [\h__\h] but but
what if I fail do you even have
pockets hi well probably shouldn't do it
while you're looking at me
ridiculous I shouldn't do it but when
he's about to leave I'll risk it again
some another time 10 10
bucks 10 to
50 50 to 100 for a good one there's bad
ones maybe like miniature
crowbars and big size crowbars do is
there different sizes in
crowbars what do you normally use them
for I guess for opening doors and maybe
also for cars opening opening anything
there is there different sizes can I
have a pink one or I got a normal one
and then I bedazzle it oh
hi goodbye oh he's also listening to waa
radio okay here we go we don't have that
much
time
okay uh uh God damn it what
ooh I get it it would be nice to find a
key first try
[Music]
ooh Daily
News headphones no name okay that's not
what I'm here for uh we need to plant uh
at least something oh China
face wa wait wait let's go to the bed
bed bed bedroom
first plant the package inside the home
oh no wait it wasn't in the bedroom why
did I think it was in the bedroom it's
here or downstairs downstairs
downstairs you have a
downstairs
H
what h no maybe it is in the
bedroom uh-oh uh-oh
uh-oh here
here huh thank you two more things kind
sir I need a photo of the kitchen in 105
okay well let me am I in 105 no right
I'm in one one one one one 110 one 110
okay let me just take this
TV nice
loot are you also playing a game right
now and you're on the same level he yo
he yo
so I didn't have much time left but I I
brought something good I think TV is
good TV is probably also desired on
black
Bay headphones headphones
also okay nice then I'm going to go to
105 in one go hopefully I'll get right
in a nice little T did we have a TV in
our home in our little ah
[\h__\h] our little
Hot 105 105 what did he say what a
complete photograph kitchen
okay yeah 33 bucks it's okay it's not
too much wait that's
106 I 105 is over
there hey it's not the right restaurant
is it my wife bracelet it's nice and
shiny oh I feel bad as a store not a
restaurant no I don't want to
no I I want to support local businesses
not hurt them but the doors are open so
maybe I don't even have to act like a
[Music]
thief can I just walk in
I
guess are you leaving oh you're
leaving there's a dog in
here
huh oh is this
some is someone coming
out oh hello
Mark what's up Mark
oh no answer wait let me follow uh what
do you mean what do you mean what do you
mean what do you mean I I I I I'm just a
customer what happened
what what happens when I go to
[Music]
jail what what happens when I go to
jail do I lose all my money what about
the
[Music]
TV or should I load safe but is there
auto
save build
character you have to pay to get out or
break out
I'm a
jailbird let's see what happens in jail
law breaker I got a law breaker
achievement oh no I need law
oh I still have my money so I probably
still have my TV bailout 500 oh
wow hey I've been there too I left a
crowbar to make your life easy oh those
don't let love bastards can go [\h__\h]
themselves oh and you could get my
package from Madison 42318 it won't be
of any use to me what was that
mean what does that mean M who's Madison
isn't that the
street what's this
code maybe it's a secret code that you
only know if you're like a
badass oh oh
cool and we get a new crowbar why I buy
mine for 100 bucks and I can't get one
for
free so
now what I got to do is be super
stealthy can I mark you no okay but you
don't even look like a guard are you
saying you're a
guard do you want to make me move
on are there
I have people up there but I can't mark
them maybe only once I'm like out of the
door you think I'll get caught he's
standing
there
menacingly that's so scary he's looking
at
me not anymore
go away oh he went
[Music]
away what can I not go to jail from
jail what what what what's my
save I guess crowbars are a little bit
too
loud oh okay but so I I'll get several
tries I guess okay
are he's sitting
there ah damn
it ah he
left maybe if I stop hearing his
footsteps get the hell out of
here get the hell out of
here what
what
what am I
considered free to
go
um well if you guys ever need to like
you know this corner is
op uh so can I do I need to be St hey
still am I free to go sir officer get
down wait wait wait wait wait okay okay
okay
[Music]
okay get the hell out of here
it's the wrong cell
dude what what what's going
on okay so I'm still considered to be in
jail I still need to get out
stealthily but this corner is
op oh
dear but Wonder as long as I'm in within
the boundaries of the cell if they
wouldn't care was I out of the cell like
one step out of the cell when he just
caught me last
time the power of a dark corner I can't
believe you found
this works IRL to totally got to test it
out next time you're in
jail oh maybe ask Advent they probably
know Adam probably
knows okay move move move move do I go
left or right
guys uh maybe
left
oh I found a nice
statue okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay
okay oh is this the accident what oh
there's so
many
visitors [\h__\h] exit
exit
exit is it this
way I need an exit
key
what this is like like a different game
now guys
but there's no one in here is
there any a key I can steal from here
too wait we can have an insane Hall in
here
ooh
oh don't come
in okay okay okay okay okay okay okay I
wonder if there's anybody ever coming in
here
[Music]
oh I can hide
in I heard a a
groan oh God this
is
laptop what
laptop this is making me go doky
dokie I don't know where the I guess
it's there but I need a key but like
this place is
huge do you stay
calm if it doesn't work
out this
time I will just bail myself
out okay I don't think people ever come
in here
good to know and I don't think there's a
key in
[Music]
here what about
here oh it's so empty guys you shouldn't
leave everything so empty
people people
doco it's not safe nobody's
working oh
sexy sexy a little laptop M we like it
we like to see
it what's in here what's this what's
this what's this Corridor this is where
the police people change and go from
normal person to police person ooh
money I hear
footsteps
uh-oh y y guys we're not
look you think I have to pick B in the
guard ooh but I don't even have I don't
even I never tried that out
before Oh no
can you guys look up if that's what I
have to do or if it is in a specific
locasion can I
just what he was in the
dark
no okay I think like I'll need to like
learn how to do this
properly otherwise oh it costs
money
otherwise like I think this is still too
too high level for
me part of the plan go to jail steal
from jail bamboozle they'll never expect
that somebody steals from jail but
there's a lot to take from here you'll
probably end up like getting a bigger um
backpack and stuff and then you can take
everything with you or you just go here
several times I guess um
M wait a
second I can Mark
him
okay well I was actually going to try
pickpocketing
him if he doesn't look can I I'll slam
you
no when did he turn around because he
was about to turn around or did he turn
around because of me hearing
me freeze hands up freeze get down on
the ground now get on your knees hands
up arms up in the air where I can see
them are you stuck here well
oh I want to try pickpocketing one of
them maybe they have a
key why let me take a step back and go
into my corner okay I'll go into my
corner and reflect on my actions don't
worry oh he probably has it
I mean I'm I'm just in my corner I'm in
my corner I'm being a good girl a good
good thief in my
corner
okay I always have to open this
otherwise I don't I don't think the game
recognizes that I have H wait let me
Mark you
[Music]
hello yes tenant was disturb yes I yes
you're disturbing me can you please give
me my privacy
he's looking at
[Laughter]
me but they're not marked as people
they're marked as out of house and
ground oh is he leaving does that mean
he's leaving
now
H oh oh yeah he left okay this dude
is
staying
H now he's leaving he's going around the
corner maybe wait what do I spy with my
little
eye a
picture Easter egg I was caught
by two of them now they're multiplying
no I was about to go to my corner I
swear I swear I swear I'm not doing
anything
suspicious oh wait come back come back I
need to Mark
you why do I
scream why do I even scream I don't
understand
[Laughter]
myself oh man
oh
wait wait I so I I can't I don't think I
can mark them while the door is
closed get the hell out of here no no no
no no
no no no no no no no nice where's the
other one
there
nice
nice best choice after finishing today's
study oh thank you for watching
on okay I want to go there again why did
it fail last time cuz of was it a sound
I made or were they just there I
forgot ah the camera [\h__\h] wait I have my
drone can I use my drone in
here no okay
you can go
now you can go now and it's
okay it's
okay I won't do anything trust me
thanks where's
ah Maybe
o oh it turns though it
turns but I think the keys in there can
you see that I think the key is
there I was
caught I found another op corner
stupid camera I hate you how do I turn
it off ah okay I can mark the area like
this
oh oh
oh okay I see oh but this area mhm
mhm there's a little bit of a strip of
no Red light over
there but then how am I going to get I
mean even if I get caught I have time to
quickly run into the corner
maybe
[\h__\h]
oh what's
here another camera by the
way I didn't realize there were cameras
at all
before okay so like when
here I could
possibly go
there can you crawl under the table I
wonder I think
not my
D let's
go oh it's just cash ah wait what's
that a USB f [\h__\h] flash
drive you that was not what I thought it
[Music]
was is he
coming a I should try a
pickpocket and then if it fails then
whatever check the other room a yeah did
you guys look up if the key is like on
the people or if I can take it from some
table desk or
so Mr Marell are you saying that because
you looked it up is it is it up
there they should have the
keys ah you saw it on a room maybe
there's several options then you saw it
on a room desk for real you can pick
pocket it okay okay but how do I never I
never tried it before they should
probably not be looking at me right only
I had a
Gun there's also a set of keys there's
multip
okay
H okay I'll
try checking
the I checking the
tables remember when they gave you a
dummy yeah but like I didn't get time
time to do that yet
man
man I think soon that other guy is going
to come
back
but I guess one of them is going to
leave
too there's another
floor no one here right now camera no
camera and another
floor whoa how do I turn on my
light uh how do
I or maybe I don't have one
now o laptop key is that a key Police ex
keute oh my God is he going to turn on
the lights when he comes here oh God
no he he's not entering he's not
entering where is
he are you coming in here or is that
below oh
God what does that line mean no he's
going down
right ah
ah he's going down right yeah
yeah I have the
key okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay
okay now I need to find the exit
again but there was an exit uh sign oh
my God if I'm going to make this well
now I know a location of a key so yeah I
need to steal some
stuff I have a
laptop uh that might be really
heavy careful maybe there's cameras
also shouldn't there be two more people
maybe they're also gone right
now oh that's the
exit should I just
go why is there no cameras
here okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay yeah but I don't have much
time the other dude is coming back
[Music]
kind of kind of want to go into the
locker place again but I don't I don't
remember I don't remember oh let me take
that sneaky nyyy nyyy sneaky sneaking
like a
stick I just I'm just going to take the
these
things and I'm going to
go I'm too scared I might come back one
day one of those
days ah wait no I want to steal more
things no I want to steal more
things
this and
this and oh there's another key
here oh my God
I'm
Kiana the owner of the
keys protector of the
doors breaker of the
chains thief of the
city I made
it yo I press breaked oh my
God I did
it
yo amazing I feel like that's like next
level thiefing that's I can skip
everything else
now what can they do to me hi little
kitty cat what can they do to me now
that I know how to get out of
jail do I still have the other key I
wonder I should I should I might but but
they might take it away from will
they I have two of them will they always
work
now oh I'm ready for Fe simulator free
that's right I'm going to sell my stuff
in the porn shop
now my porn shop brings all the thieves
to the yard and they want to sell it off
me they bring all the trash to me and it
looks like I'm the best
Thief porn
chop I maybe that's a song for next uh
truck
stream where are we going where is it
[Laughter]
here oh I still have the TV I still have
the
TV I just paid rent oh [\h__\h] how much was
it oh I think that was a
lot how much
H oh oh wait I have two things in
there do you need this sir well well
that's just
crazy he likes
it could use that 220 yeah 50 150 100 30
80 and have three of them um all all
let's
[Music]
go St STS St St
STS they didn't even take that as
evidence why not unch no no no I don't
think that makes sense yeah I'm out of
jail who would have known jail is so
profitable I might want to go back
honestly there's still so much feing
potential so much feing potential y'all
where do I have this computer from
guys take it
500 why do I have this did I just forget
it in my truck from like ages
ago hey
yo oh
Ked Snee oh was like whose car is this
my
car okay what were we doing we wanted to
photograph uh photograph photograph a
kitchen back to my main
activity uh at the restaurant
place
uh for like
how how do I even do
[Music]
that oh here it is here it is let's try
not to land in jail are you sure maybe
we should sounds like
fun
sneakier thanks for the membership I
guess we going to be sneakier but I
thought we didn't have to be
sneaky photograph the
kitchen so this is a
store and I'm am guessing I'm not
allowed to enter these
doors how do I takes the photo I guess I
have to be there when they're not
there it can't be that difficult when
it's still in the beginning of the game
maybe I can take through a
window the
photo ah uhuh wait a second lockpicking
level
two I need like 10 more
exp
oh I heard s
door huh
what she doing
doggo doggo friendly
now cute can I pet the dog hi is it a oh
is this German Shepherd
dog I cannot pet this dog so sad okay
dog is in the front garden while this
dude
is uh doing
stuff for 1 hour in there what the [\h__\h]
how do I do
this I open
[Music]
oh what is the the other person
who okay maybe I'll try he's sitting
there I I'd like to
try go through this door but I have too
low lockpicking skill I got to steal
something what if I steal the
dog
oh
what what's that is that supposed to be
a hot tub
or out of wood it looks so
cool try the crowbot yeah when doubted I
guess it's time for the Crowbar but
that's so loud that's the problem it
will 100% alert
him or the
dog I got to wait for
[Music]
H well the thing is if I had a better
exit route I wouldn't mind doing it even
if I make him hear it cuz I could just
run away but the dog would probably meet
me here in the middle
o can
I
aha he had an aha
moment ah he's doing stuff again M don't
risk it I don't think yeah let's just
get a level
up uh where do we want to enter we could
go in here
again there's oh there's a 1 hour time
window in a moment where I can
enter
mhm what was it uh left
shift
okay in broad daylight yeah [\h__\h] fake
people that graffiti looks kind of fancy
like that that font and the
brightness looks like it's a a stylistic
choice all right all right all right uh
uh they're about to
leave come
on come on dude
1 hour I feel like I stole a lot of
things already
but maybe there's something in the
backyard I can check one day I'll be
able to enter this
thing hurry
up he's about
to come over
here so far I got to say it's um
definitely like pretty Sim SAR to fif
simulator 1 but uh it's like a little
bit
nicer but not a big difference for me so
far got to say not very obvious
difference yeah it's basically same
game it's just maybe nicer graphics and
a few like quality of life
changes one guy you think one single guy
made
it uh
wait I
I'm I got to be
fast is there anything
here this makes me so nervous it's
already it's they're already coming back
basically
ah ah
ah ah they don't even I took everything
already keyboard speak okay I'm
out I'm
out
quick no can I hide is there a secret
Corner again oh it's so over it's so
over it's so over so over stop right now
enough for this jail is it jail
time I'm going to go to jail again I
wonder if it changes can I still use the
same key oh my bag
is
full ah I don't have the
key now I do have the key
what why are they so
stupid and another crowbar why are they
so
stupid Oh I think there's different
staff I heard a lady voice or is just
because I'm here at a different time
maybe cuz otherwise I guess I wouldn't
have
oh went into the wrong
cell IO otherwise I wouldn't have uh
already
the the
markings I I couldn't Mark her damn it
[\h__\h] it's a
lady what Happ please come
over damn
it I want to Mark
her [\h__\h] come
on if I stand here it's okay maybe stop
it now what I'm in my cell
oh I guess as soon as as a cell door is
open it's like yo you are actively
breaking out you little
[\h__\h] why do they always look over there
in the neighbor
cell oh these people are so
stupid so
funny okay
a damn
it okay well let's
see
ooh
projector going to project all my
problems onto you and all my
feelings
oh huh
stop it now
what what you going to do what you going
to do about it ehuh you got a problem
you want to do something about it well I
don't think you can do
anything there we go we got the fourth
person they can't do [\h__\h]
NY oh oh was it just a natural aha I
thought he found me never
mind but the footsteps I hear many
footsteps what should I going there is
maybe
dangerous oh wait the the the figure I
guess I didn't take it last
time bucks like I took it once but then
I guess I got caught
level
up
[Music]
uh let me get my skill if I get caught
then I'll have to probably do this
again lock picking level two is there
someone there can I go cuz my problem is
now only have this one person marked
I'm sure there's more
people oh
dear okay there's at least two people in
here is there anything to get from the
other
cells what the [\h__\h] why is an iPad in
here not going to get it though I would
have to buy a pick oh
[Music]
money
go
okay
um okay is that the guy I have
marked all right this is so fun guys I'm
doing stealth I'm in here it's heavy I'm
in here fing again I'm already full ah
cuz I had like stuff from the other fing
activities maybe let's let's go to the
the the the things that there's money
over
there if it's still the
same then there should be some
money
yeah somebody here
no okay I like this jail
section it ain't bad it ain't bad you
just have to not get caught where's the
exit are they in there yeah I think
so
uh-oh footstep
be
uh-oh where are
they they usually they don't go in
here I
think okay she sits
[Music]
ah she's leaving I think is she going to
leave no wait is he leaving somebody's
leaving soon I think
him maybe I don't know what that means
there's a green part I think the exit is
there they stealing from the cops again
they have not learned their lesson how
do I wait I don't think now the exit is
not here I think I'm somewhere else
uh I'll find my
way it's that way maybe over there I
think can you Ste the paintings I
wonder oh
oh oh she's leaving I think she's
leaving do we hear door noise when she
leaves oh she's leaving that's what the
doors okay I'm also going to head out
now and thanks guys have a nice day um
I'll bring donuts next time all
right thanks
for being so kind to
me you guys are so
welcoming so
nice thanks for giving me you know a
nice place to sleep warm
War a lot of presents feels like
Christmas every time I'm here you guys
are the
best I made it again second
jailbreak I'm not scared of the cops
anymore I got this down I feel like
normally this should be like really
something you want to avoid but oh no
issue for
me here another scanner but I think they
probably only need one for black Bay I'm
going to keep it in here though for now
all right we got some stuff to sell got
to go to the porn
shop yeah they just reward me with more
loot they should they should like yeah
make this more
challenging it didn't even change from
last time and I even got to keep the
keysy it's they should have at least
changed the lucks the when when there's
jail
breakouts do they never change the
locks I got my level up now too but I
got to be honest I'm a little bit scared
I want to sell the things
first don't want to go with all this all
this luggage into the jail
againa of the
U log changes aren't in the budget no
for real though do they not I guess I
guess normally in jail or I guess that's
more like a police station right not
real jail I I've never been to like but
there's like jail at a police station
and there's
jail in jail right was that police
station jail how you
doing ooh 30 15 60
nice jail versus prison yeah I wonder if
we have the same thing the same system
in Austria cuz I always just see that in
America like people on TV
shows
uh end up in jail and then they get
bailed out and then it's all
cool you don't know yeah I don't really
know I mean I never been I'm not I mean
I may be showing some really serious
hardcore thiefing skills here but IRL
I'm I actually am a law abiding citizen
I got to go to I know it's kind of
boring kind of
lame half 10 versus kangus half
US is that a
thing anyway what am I going to do I
okay let's let's let's uh let's see I'm
going to
buy
um what is it P do I have to get out of
my car for the phone
yeah I think so uh okay let me get the
to the closest park
actually let
me let me get my my my
package my parcel my present from my
friend my jail
friend what is it going to be do I have
to remember oh [\h__\h] guys
is it Somewhere In My
Memory did I pick up the the
paper I didn't think I'd have to
remember 42 I love
you you saw the number too often how you
actually remembered it this is just like
in the post
office ooh 101
key a 107 key that's it I think
yeah hey 101 key over there I didn't
enter that place before 107 I also
didn't enter yet I
think oh I'm not going there yet though
cuz uh I'm going to go there when the
game wants me to go there but then I'll
have an easy way
in nice appreciated thanks
buddy uh we got to go to the restaurant
now it's so nice that I can keep all my
things when I go to jail
they don't take any of my
belongings but I was I was going to say
originally so if there's a breakout in
the in the police
prison do
they do they
change is there ever I feel like it
might be more is it more
diff do they change locks is what I
wonder
it's probably it's not an issue of
changing locks usually probably it's
they broke out in a different
way you think they'd have
to okay I'm kind of stuck with this task
here as you can
tell uh currently there's one person out
of
house this dude is in his work the the
dog is probably inside as well which
means I can go and maybe on the other
side open the gate unless the dog is
there no I don't think
so oh I have to buy I have to buy the
lockpick [\h__\h] [\h__\h] I was going to buy
the
lockpick oh is he
leaving please don't go around the
corner oh no am I allowed to be here no
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] I I I have an easy
time in jail now but I really don't want
to no no no no no it's probably
compromised offic on the
oh hi oh what where the hell is he you
didn't see me go
in
N remember previously where he was
compromised and I looked behind me and
there was literally no one
there
NY Skyrim
guard I can imagine even though I didn't
play
it okay so at night I'm not allowed to
be on this property I guess oh he's uh
sitting oh
what you doing what you doing buddy let
me
in let me in share share your story with
me ooh the kitchen is on the second
floor when the [\h__\h] how the [\h__\h]
what he's going up now he's going to
sleep now blue is
sleeping maybe now is the time
now is the
time oh this door stays
open oh that's not very smart of you
guys oh but they take out away oh no
actually there's some product there
toilet paper wait wait so
uh
uh quick
buy wait there's oh wait lockpick and
Lockpick to what does that
mean
uh how the [\h__\h] does this work
again ah Tippy
tappy [\h__\h] how does this
work why is this not stay
ah do I have to I have to click it in in
place ah okay
okay it's so
shiny oh
easy
easy what the [\h__\h] so
dirty sheesh I probably can't put that
in my
backpack oh that's
heavy what if the dog is just suddenly
there where does the dog
sleep outside or with him on the bed
or wonder
wall
dog no dog what the [\h__\h] was why is it
so dirty in
here okay second floor take a photo
probably with my phone okay okay damn
this was high
effort is that good enough oh yes don't
call me now you idiot we're going to do
something crazy but first you need to
learn how to use lockpicks I already
know do some jobs steal some more
lockpicks once you myself I've been to
jail three times since our last call
I've been through a lot of stuff but I'm
an absolute Pro
Now where's his dog I guess the dog does
sleep
outside damn I'm such a pro now I don't
need your advice anymore I'm way past
that is he going to wake up soon no
nice okay let's take
something let's maybe let's take this oh
I can put it in my
backpack all right it's full I I'm
leaving
sick should I relock the
door nah what's the point of relocking
it so I guess while I'm still in the
house in case I'm still in the house and
they wake up and walk around if the door
was uh open then they would alarm aler
alert probably and but if I'm already
out then I think it doesn't
matter yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo I did
it once again Oops I did it again I
stole all your stuff and you're not
going to get it back ever again I don't
know I [\h__\h] up the
Melody I should know oops I'm
again what how does it go
on actually maybe wait let me go to the
porn
shop excellent fing
right well it's difficult because he the
house does doesn't seem to ever be
empty that is the
challenge and there's a dog but we
didn't even need to use dog meat or
anything well I guess when they're not
out of their home ever then the best
thing is just to go in while they're
sleeping only problem is you can't go in
when
um when they're uh you can't go into the
bedroom then if they have anything cool
there how you doing how you doing here's
a cast register that's it that's all I
got the other stuff is all oh okay I
should check at
um black black Bay at
home if I have some full sets
now and maybe buy some more lockpicks
and stuff but now so I guess I don't
necessarily
need the basic lockpicking sets anymore
at this point I wonder if I still need
them or if I can always just use the the
the big boys thanks for the membership
welcome what do you mean you're
professional at this as a Brazilian at
at lock
picking excuse
me you're doing me a
concern okay black bear do I have
something no no full sets I have a
scanner need a drawing
tablet oh acoustic guitar I has I need a
blue guitar and a black guitar oh all
these sets are going to take a
while regular wallet Lea wallet black
leather
wallet o China V headset ah hey is there
any later houses that have like the the
first cheap ass vase that I got in the
first house or is the first house ever
going to like
restock what do I
do I
need also I need a knife
holder two knife holders I need to set
twice getting all the sets will take a
while there's a whole new zone of houses
M there's going to got to be another one
yeah there has to
be hopefully hopefully I made the same
mistake just like back when
oh there's a skill book in 110 111 and I
think what do you mean you think 106
worth checking them out reading makes
you smart to
say don't talk to me about
reading smart baby smarter smarter baby
smarter
yeah I'm going to
buy and buy and buy
and just in case
bye hope it doesn't go stinky
stinky
okay um learn lockpicking too and buy
free oh okay free
lockpicks uh should be my third now
yeah test I don't need to test it I
already know how it works try a test
lockpick at your hideout because you're
going to jail I'm not kidding I'll
explain once you practice I you're going
to jail I was already there don't make
me go to jail now I already been there
three
times Well I waste of my
time H it ah
[\h__\h]
[Music]
speed all he's not watching my stream
onps it's a police station which you
will visit why I shall explain are you
saying I'm entering from the from the
outside to the inside this time and not
going from the inside to the
outside no
what I I have a shortcut just get
caught is he for
real okay uh info on on what was the
police station 106 or and what was
it some police
station there it is
116 what he wants me to buy the info
it's going to get expensive but I
actually have a lot of money now two
police two security all armed the
C security panel isn't a conference room
exit door yeah I already know a lot of
keys
places ten routines have been revealed
woohoo R woohoo decent SSD in the boss
room oh boss
room going to have a boss
fight iMac in the office on floor too
what do you want which one my associate
who's also a thief was caught and is
currently stuck in ja what you'll go
there break out break her out and Escape
together if you manage to do that I will
do anything to help you it's a promise
so do something stupid and get caught oh
you want oh you do want me to get caught
I'm not entering from the outside okay I
mean okay he wants me to get caught H
come up the
[Music]
he said I'll do
anything
anything when somebody says they will do
anything in Japanese Japanese people
will be all over the chat and be like oh
c I almost jumped on you they'll be like
did you just say did you just say that
you do
anything that's what you said right cat
I'm just going to follow the cat
now I go sneaky NY nyyy NY NY NY
sneaking like a
cat meow meow meow meow meow meow meow
meow I love my
cats I would was um chasing chunky wonky
around today it's so cute cuz like
she'll go like and like she'll she'll
run and then then she'll stop in a in a
in a position she like she'll be
like you know what I mean and then I
then I run towards her and or make like
a like a sudden movement and then she'll
be like and then she'll run away again
and like go like she's so cute so funny
she's so funny she's so happy and she
zooms around my whole place she's like
whoosh
whoosh so excited to be chased yeah she
had the Zoomies a little bit a little
bit so cute all right let's get caught
guys wait what what do I have in my
inventory what's with these
laptops they weren't an option to sell
were
they cuz I didn't see
them or are they in my car
no I'm just going to try to put them in
my
thing oh maybe I have to unlock them
before I sell
them
probably that's why I couldn't sell
them I'm going to learn the hacking
skill I
think haven't s the the guitar yeah e
what's with the guitar where is the
guitar is is it in my
inventory but they I was at the porn
chop cor is that a Cory
no forgot you want to get get chased by
me R did Che out ROV if your house is
looking awful it's a good ide what could
you do to get chased by me I guess you
also got to th something from me
then I chase you I'll chase you and then
I'll fry you no mercy no thiefing from
the thief of all
thiefs so what's
up what's with the guitar was I blind hi
there no there's no guitar in
here there's no there's no guitar here
either I guess did I sell it did I put
it in my closet is it here is it in my
box it's in my box yeah okay we're just
waiting
to yeah do something fun with that he
wants me to get caught and then go to
jail H but I don't want to get caught on
purpose that sounds
stupid where could
I what I don't I want to no I don't want
to get purposely caught we'll just steal
a little bit and see if we accidentally
get
caught hello do
do dougle where' dougle go dougle in
back
guen oh could throw him some
meat you could drive there can I
I want to learn uh
climbing
Hi H well probably should do it at
night would be stupid
otherwise what time does he go to
sleep uh
what what time is that I can't check it
can I cuz I didn't buy the info or wait
do I have the
info what's this
105 I can check it
John sleeping what
John ah
John John probably doesn't live here
only Leo lives here and he goes to to
bed at 11:00
p.m. we still don't know what he's doing
here we remain a
secret steal dog no no I don't want to
steal his dog no that's so mean that's
so rude you can't just steal someone's
dog
no I would kill you if you stole my cat
so
that's not
cool if I lost my cat or so either by
just them running away my cats
or or them being actually stolen or them
just dying early earlier than they
should you know I
would I I don't think I could function
do I want to enter from
here no let's just enter for here
again okay is there something to steal
here
no no what is this room oh basic
okay
[\h__\h]
ah honestly I I I totally understand how
to pick a lock now this game is very
educational no more Wi-Fi for you a
cracked vase oh my God absolutely
cracked I already checked in here I
don't think there's anything oh the the
drawing tablet let's
go oh
yeah
nice uh here's where he sleeps
right can take the
phone no Wi-fi no phone what is he going
to do the knife holder we also
need smartphone nice not even
broken
hey a sauce pan I'll take it I'll take
it
all Bring It On ooh a mixer
sexy yeah nice haul that's going to be a
nice haul video that's going to be like
100k views
at
least okay I got it is that oh okay
Robert one I don't think I oh what
second one I don't think I need to sell
that at black Bay
anymore okay I'm pretty darn good huh do
both of these doors lead to his this
bedroom or is that is this the
bathroom no oh [\h__\h] is it too dangerous
to
enter the small the
small yo yo I'm supposed to collect I'm
I'm an art and U all kinds of item
collector not a
thief don't call me that that is not
sophisticated
enough I need to add these things to my
art
collection I carry too much oh that's
why I can't run oh thank God she didn't
look my
way let's
go yeah if I if I if Thief steals art
then Thief is just art collector am I
right or am I right need need need need
need need need nice oh my God we got so
much new blackb
of
amazing
[Music]
yo careful there little boy you
shouldn't be out at this time of the
night 2 a.m. be like a million do at
least 2 a.m. I'm going to call the
police on you I guess it is oh hey did
you notice we didn't get
caught does that hold up in court we
we'll see I mean does it have to hold up
in court when I can already Escape uh
police so easily
H sell 50 35
35 15
yay let's
go this is lock picking wa and today I'm
going to demonstrate how to pick this
virtual Master
Lock wow in the comments it's going to
be like wow Tak thank you so much for
teaching how to pick a lock I've learned
so much from you you changed my life you
saved me that one night when I was stuck
in the
closet you you help
me you turn my life all around what
would I be without you life changing
moments for real for
real catch hair what the
[\h__\h] oh wait why am I here yeah never
mind sorry
brain all right
yo let's go why was that twice there
okay I need another
teapot oh I can just there it is again I
can just get the same set and Sell It
Again interesting we need a toaster and
have a toaster ooh we need two more
toasters
okay big money 400 bucks for the drawing
tablet let a scanner let's
go Ooh So
[Music]
Exciting we need these iMac things
didn't he say there's an iMac oh huh
where did I see an
iMac 200 there we go finally that set is
complete in jail right was it the one in
the in the cell or was it just like
randomly like on a
table I need iMac iMac keyboard and iMac
Mouse for
4,000 and that would be too easy if it's
just there in
the on the table oh it was in a Cell
okay but I think it was
only tablet
and that's not I don't know if that's
the same thing no it's not this is the
the whole
computer yeah that would be something
else I guess USA President's phone wait
wait wait do you break in to the White
House at some
point or the
home Mar maralago or
so but that's the previous
one does it count if it's from an ex
president
H oh
well
okay you know
what my car is so full what the
[\h__\h] why is so
full what let me bring it in I probably
don't need two of those headphones
but H wait let me check again if I can
sell those or if if it did register that
it's in my
car I
think as long as it's in the
car or in the closet it's okay okay
break into the White House I you going
to do
that secret
documents remember to leave all the
faucets on is that like a previous
incident or
what why are you saying I should do that
oh there's another Cat Here in My Water
all right let me drink my ice tea
instead Home Alone reference
ah I guess it is break it to the white
house and home alone
right wait when did I
H there's several Home Alone movies
right I surely watched the first one I
don't know if I I probably watched at
least the second
one I don't recall an incident where
they left the faucets
running um yeah I don't I don't there's
something about you know purposefully
getting caught as a professional Thief
that just doesn't sit right with
me it's just I just want it to happen
naturally ah damn it why why do I have
such an issue with
that man it really bothers
me it really bothers me
[Music]
all right let's try
something if I get caught I get caught
if I don't get caught then my pride is
stronger than
ever what time is it 7
a.m.
hello well
okay no bring me are you going to
h no bring me to the police station
please
hello radio want to chill listen to us
then what are you tired of music that
makes
you yeah but he should call a cop be
listening everyone
[Music]
n God damn
it hello
call the police please I don't want to
waste one of my lockpicks on you yeah
hear me hear
me witness
me witness me hey you call the police
maybe are you going to run away is that
how you do
it is that the way you do
it h I'm
ready police you might want to question
why I want to be uh caught
you might want to question
that what do I have in mind what's my
plan yo okay so there's apparently a
friend oh right there okay okay no
problem I I have I have all the tricks I
have all the tips and tricks at this
point leave it to me iMac in the office
on floor two decent SSD in the bathroom
is it a must to get those I think the
only must is to get the associate
associate I I'm going to assume
that wait do I just have to open the
door for her or does she like follow
me after I open and then I have to bring
her out safely like an escort
Mission
or do I just open the door and then she
leaves on her
own because then that's important
because I might just go get the loot
first if I have to lead her
out she follows me no way
oh that's annoying Then I then I would
get the loot first or just another time
cuz I guess these are just tips for
another time I don't have to do it
now I wonder if the iMac comes with all
the other
stuff hi what's up how you doing I'm
back again I'll back again and this time
I'm not breaking out alone no no no this
time I'm breaking out with my
friends was a friend that I didn't know
I
had o now I have all the all the
thingies so red means that they're here
so now there's free
people
right anyway oh
are he's going to sit there now for
real it's kind of a bad
time yeah I'm stealing your
inmate I'm stealing my
inmate yeah this makes it very very
difficult but he's just going to sit
here for 1 hour
okay how you doing over there don't
worry I'm going to get you
out I'm going get ooh was it always 950
wasn't it 500 last time
damn it's got more
expensive it's interesting how the story
needs you to get
here uh so early I thought this was more
a late game kind of thing getting like
actually out of the cell by breaking
out
damn it was less
huh that's okay though because the game
wants
me to break out we're going to make it
break
it
[Music]
unfor watch
me watch me now do I still have a
key yeah
yes I'm so overprepared I don't even
need to look for the keys anymore and I
kind of know where the exit is it's so
easy to find it
too how long is this 1
hour weren't you going to
leave dude oh
oh no there he he there he
goes so is anybody else coming down here
I hope
not I has to pick the
lock oh is he coming down oh he's coming
down oh no okay
uh y yeah I'm so
criminal help
I'm such a smooth
criminal oh hi oh are you in or out
you're in okay you're out okay uh [\h__\h]
this is oh God this
is oh man I don't know I don't know if I
can I don't know if I can do it with
you
ah my do we show up
mukashi he's
here oh
[\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] come here Lady Lady
Lady oh come here that's awful come here
okay wait where are we go they're
staying they're somewhat staying ah
a oh this is so difficult a he's
standing right
there yeah but you have to like lead her
around the corner she's not like going
there on her
own
girl what's his
plan okay what's your
plan uh okay
and
yours oh man hard to
tell hard to tell this court Mission the
worst thing guess you should just charge
out the door and take the IMAX over yeah
that's the plan I don't want to take
anything now um
but okay uh they're switching or she's
not
coming okay okay
okay that's
good that's is very good I think I'm
ready to
[Music]
go wow I think I I might take
Commissions in the
future breakout
commissions if you guys need me call
me oh it doesn't matter they see her oh
really that makes it easier Oh I thought
she could like mess it up for us y'all I
[\h__\h] did it wow h no
yeah
she as a way to say things she's going
to steal with you if you call her up oh
really might help you in many ways what
so to work my magic I need a briefcase
from 108 it contains info about
Lombard's Rivals if we send it to the
Lombardy boss he might rethink killing
you hell he might even think you're
useful now what a way to turn things
around get me that briefcase
Pronto uh no I think we'll call it a day
for today cuz it's been three and a half
hours and we read some super chats so so
supposed to be a shortage stream and
then I got to cook some f let her cook
but that was a lot of fun I see I see I
see some improvements yeah I mean not
like crazy like I'm not that there were
crazy improvements necessary you know
but I like it yeah yeah and it gave me a
good reason to play this game again just
because there's a new one candy cat I'm
so happy that the protagonist has like a
cat although it might be a straight
cat but it makes me happy that we we
seemingly are in character a cat
person yeah so true that was fun
yay tunnel
so
tomorrow uh I'll
be did it safe I think
so tomorrow I'll
be yeah okay I'll be playing from 400
p.m. Wawa time onwards
Yakuza uh hopefully we'll finish it
don't worry I I I can play 10 hours if I
have
to it's going to be fine
the Intel I have gathered says that
we're going to be
fine thanks for thank you I want to stay
in my box I wonder do I have a fitting
background for
this what if I break into girls talk
room at
night what if I break it
skin wait where's
my where is
it I copied
it there it
is I'm going to break in with the trash
can
[Music]
should I get rid of the table for
this this is so stupid why
why well just a box or uh just a trash
can
basically you
know just normal sneaky stuff I'm on a
Mission and it's a sneaky
[Music]
Mission I'm
here have you noticed that I'm pretty
NY have you
noticed
hi I I have broken into my own
room then naked Bandit n like a snake
snake
n n n n n n NY NY NY NY like a
snake less clothes less noise
yeah I guess so that is
smart did you lose the key yeah I lost
my
keys all the
irony has all the keys to everything
else but not my own
Keys the last you wear the sneaker you
are everybody take that as a lesson As A
Life
Lesson there's a valuable accent suit to
steal in
that
yeah and it is it is even a little bit
sweaty sweaty sweaty sweaty sweaty
sweaty sweaty sweaty sweaty sweaty like
wah wa
[Music]
okay uh then let me close the
game and then we're going to see where
we left off last time and I'm going to
turn on some
bgm it's fun I like these kind of sneaky
games as you may know I always like the
sneaky parts of other games too so this
is kind of my jam and I feel like last
time I played this game I was a bit more
freaked out but um maybe that was also
just because I was in the higher levels
and then it gets like way more difficult
you guys are already saying back then I
should play
Hitman in terms of games I now that
we're finishing Yakuza for real for real
this
week uh I was thinking about what to
play next and I don't know it's
either the Witcher
which makes sense cuz I just um still
have it on my
brain uh cuz I just watched the whole
show um but then the one thought I have
is it's kind of stupid like unnecessary
like I don't have to like pay attention
to that but just thinking because fauna
just started it it's like why why have
two of these playthroughs running
simultaneous it makes sense when a game
just comes out just releases and then
people are playing it because of the
release hype but you know what I mean I
just feel like a little bit like why why
would I isn't that like too
much but but uh yeah it makes sense cuz
I just watched it and I have it fresh on
my brain but I could also just wait and
you know fill my brain with even more
Witcher by reading SL listening to the
book but then the other option listen
listen
yeah maybe you guys are not watching
hers so you can watch mine that would be
ideal um stream snipe the game overview
no I I think she probably always wanted
to play it but uh it is the I do think
she had the idea in um like uh what's
the word set into her brain by the
incident of me gifting it to Cali and
then getting the PC permissions uh for
us yeah um otherwise yeah it would be
weird cuz that was all at the same time
and she called in right after uh I
called cie at that
stream the timing is too
good um but it's okay so either that or
my other idea would
be um
and you guys probably will like this
idea
uh uh uh
fallout
uh Las
Vegas my mom wants me to play this
and and the thing is that there's the
show going on right now so it's still
fresh so it would make sense to play it
now and we do have perms for it right
because am I played it before a long
time ago I don't really know what kind
of game it is to be honest I don't know
if it's a game that I would like what do
you think yeah I know I'm tweet that she
wants to get into it again
mhm listen to justce
once it is an
RPG H you might like it just try it out
there's a cute lady at least on the on
the promotional picture uh she seems to
be like the main lady do we play a lady
in the game please say
yes who is that lady in the blue suit H
oh I can make my own
character
oh
oh M
interesting interesting you make your
own is it a long let me look it let me
look it up
uh fall
outl I wanted to say fall guys I was so
confused I had to think about
it uh game H New Vegas not
last New Vegas same thing uh very long
oh God length
longer wait it says 27 that's not long
for me I'm currently playing Yakuza
which has already taken more than 50
hours I think for me this is not this is
not long for me 27 hours in game length
if you're a gamer that strives to see
all aspects of the game oh oh well then
you are likely to spend 132 what the
[\h__\h] is this difference 27 hours versus
132 oh my God I don't think I've ever
seen such a
contrast in the time it takes not
accurate at all New Vegas would be a
game you play through and come back
occasionally rather than playing
nonh okay so like like how Amit plays
like Skyrim and stuff like that or
Oblivion was it just like an okay I
think I don't mind seeing it like that
like not playing it every week just like
maybe the first three weeks or so I play
it every week and then it becomes more
like uh every once in a while every two
or three or four or five weeks
H and yeah just like whenever but is it
not like with the story doesn't not feel
like when there's too much time in
between is it not like I forget
everything and it's like lame for the
audience too cuz they also forgot
everything no
really not at
all the quest are very episodic
organized around the the towns you visit
oh so that works well no you probably
won't forget everything
oh the main story is the weakest
part I might have
[Music]
to we're talking
about Fallout right now right The
Witcher free
length oh this one's kind of longer but
I mean depends on how you see it 56
hours
56 hours oh oh if you're a gamer that
Stripes to see all aspects of the game
you like to spend around
190 one 190 hours
okay
wow in what world apparently in the
speedrunning
world is also sidetracked fil G damn Alo
both of
[Music]
them so you guys seem to really like the
The Fallout idea but you also like The
Witcher idea so I I don't really know
like this would be more fitting for now
because the show is popular right
now and I'm not rushing to play Witcher
you know I I would have liked to play it
right away after I finish the show
but this makes more sense if you think
about what's hype I guess I guess start
a
poll uh what's
next um The Witcher free
or with Fallout I would be on the side
watching the show I wonder if it's a
spoiler I fall at New
Vegas there you go vote vote democracy
democracy
YooHoo eventually I want to play both so
you
know and I mean if if if f out is like a
game that you play every once in a while
not in one go maybe we can play
both I don't
know oh it's not a competition huh
73% show doesn't spoil it okay
cool good to know have you guys watched
it it keeps on getting like in my
recommendations when I open my smart TV
when I turn it on is great yeah no no
50/50 split this is a good
split
damn H
interesting interesting my mom like we
talked about games you know she she was
like oh after you finish Yakuza what are
you going to play next and I'm
like maybe The Witcher and she was like
saying ah The Witcher like she she likes
The Witcher but also not like she said
she tried playing it I don't know which
one but she said
that it's kind of
depressing she said that in every town
you go you have to like work really hard
to make them like you but it's
depressing because they're all [\h__\h]
rude to you uh and rejecting
right apparently is super dark so that's
why she didn't couldn't enjoy it she
said and she said I should
play
Fallout New Vegas and then I was like
well yeah actually that's not even such
a bad
idea yeah she still mentioned Mass
Effect but she knows she knows she knows
Mass Effect is you know just a joke at
this
[Music]
point Fallout is not less dark or
depressing oh that's actually true in
all free games what free games what the
other one people free and distrust
witchers Oh you mean all free Witcher
games oh okay
oh yeah I mean I I get it because um I I
can imagine because I that was kind of
shown in the Netflix show as well when
geralt especially in the beginning not
so much like honestly it was really only
shown once or twice I would
say he walks into little village
everybody is like mean and hates him but
probably way more so in the game I can
imagine Fallout is dark sometimes but
also goofy fall has a lot of humor in
the dark setting M postapocalyptic
everything sucks but it's also wacky
let's go your heard is getting more
seasons yes I heard and I
mean I know I'm personally also gonna
feel weird about watching it and having
the main actor replaced
but the main actor the new one what's
his name again it's a famous one right
[Music]
um new actor I feel like his face
structure is similarish so with good
makeup they can and the wig and
everything they can make him look
somewhat similar and then maybe it's the
LI Liam Hemsworth then it's maybe not
like too bothering but obviously it's
weird it's just going to be weird
have a different dude there I will admit
I'll have to see how that feels I hate
when main actor switches
yeah but I will watch it
anyway cuz even if it's different from
the books I just enjoy that kind of
fantasy setting you
know I'll say like other shows other
fantasy shows that I watched are
better uh other I like more just because
of plot reasons I don't like the plot
and like the characters as much
TB and even when we talk about fantasy
there's something about just
like
like some parts are still like
like a stretch like chal in my opinion
it's like weird weird
script um it's like it's like I don't
know it's not serious enough or so I I
don't know describe it it's
just I think sometimes the
characters dialogues and actions are
just weird I can't explain it so it's
not perfect I don't like it that much
but I still enjoy any kind of show that
has a setting like this yeah it feels a
bit off to me what's the Super Chat
since everyone wants to play Mass Effect
you can play it right now for the Super
Chat choose an option red blue green or
tell the child to stop yapping ahuh that
must be some references
I guess we're choosing pink cuz it's a
pink super chat but there's no pink
Choice that's cuz it's bad no but people
like the first season and even the
second season still but even there I
already felt that
way like this is not perfect it's good
but it's not
perfect you
know it's a master spoiler oh oh it's
okay I'm probably never going to play
it but yeah
anyway we'll see you
know I think a lot of people know Henry
Caville from other
shows uh what was it again what's his
most famous thing that everybody knows I
know him from the tutors you
know I know him from the
tuts you know him a super ah yeah okay
most people know him a super what he was
super
Superman what that's
him damn he's like a shape
shifter oh wow oh okay oh well he looked
very different on that picture but on
this other picture it looks more like
him but
still wow like in it I told you how when
I started watching The Witcher I did not
recognize him even though I I saw his
face a lot on the tutors for several
actors uh Seasons I read the word actor
while I was saying
for several
seasons and I didn't recognize him for a
long time probably also cuz the voice
was different
too
but like comparing him in the tutors and
in The Witcher and in the
Superman he looks different wait this is
not Henry this is Tom
caval is this his
brother wait are you guys sure that
Henry Kev played it this says Tom
Cav wait is this his
brother maybe that's why he didn't look
like him to
me
what does he have a brother you guys
said you know him from
Superman are you
sure it says
Ah Tom caval cast as The Witcher and it
shows a picture of him next to
geralt Su super what what did they just
mistake his
name who the [\h__\h] is Tom
caval they even wrote it with one
L look up Man of Steel Man of
Steel is that Henry or this Tom dude
what I don't get it he does look kind of
like Henry but as I said it doesn't look
like him that much that's why I'm
confused
Man of Steel Henry Caville that that's
what it says on the on the poster is
that really
him the more I look at him the less he
looks like him to
me damn he's such a shape
shifter are you sure does he not have
like a brother who's called Tom and he
played Superman and y'all have been
gaslighted
I guess this website what let me look at
this article why the [\h__\h] did you write
Tom
cille
uh there it
is ah wait it was
fixed Tom Tom Tom I swear it says Tom
over
here show you
but when I click the article and
actually read
it then it says
Henry here Tom Cav caval cast as The
Witcher that confused me that was like
the first thing I saw
H funny
anyway he still looks so
different I would have actually believed
you if you said he had a brother that
was called Tom
because he does look
different that's AI stuff
what how
what just yeah it's just a bad website
but the article changed it
anyway I'm not trying to Gaslight you no
maybe you have been
gaslit is Superman's real person like
the character is is is that character
called Tom by any
chance surely the civilian behind it oh
is Clark K Clark
Clark Clark is such Clark is such a
funny name
Clark
Clark Clark Clark sorry to all the
Clarks in here sounds funny so gnarly
Clark Clark
Clark
Clark Clark Clark Clark I sound like a
like a proger so Clark Clark Clark CL
like
um like some animal Clark Clark
Clark Clark clar clar CL clar Clark clar
Clark sorry is there a single Clark in
here like a single one or two or three
I'm so sorry I'm so sorry I'm so sorry
I'm so sorry it sounded so funny to me
like a seagull
yeah not
anymore wouldn't you agree it sounds
funny his name is from the 1930s well
are you saying the name is not really
like a thing anymore so what it's so
funny it was funny back then
already oh by the way just because I
just saw it in hyzer uh the reason I'm
not playing the OE game this week after
alls because she told me to maybe wait
because uh the version currently is a
little bit scuffed and they're going to
put out a patch and she can't say for
sure when but hopefully by the by next
week it should be
there so that's what I'm waiting for oh
what you waiting what you wait okay ifp
be like what you waiting what you
waiting what you waiting what you
waiting for
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you do you know this
song might be so old some people don't
know
it
oh thank you delar you saying that in
the Super Chat makes me think you might
that might be your
name um I think I have to read part six
of like a dragon
I
think I think I'm caught up with members
and the next one would be that one I
think
okay
um this
one where son he joined us
spoiler they oh yeah and
music um
music
music your name is D
yeah you know what I
[Music]
mean you like jazz
do
you
dabble
yes is this
Jazz be nice
be do you a thank you for 800,000 views
[Music]
onim thank you very much
appreciate
[Music]
[Applause]
it yeah 1 million
soon soon soon
soon yeah thank you so much let's
go okay I'm
ready I'm so
ready soring well yeah my baby my child
I'm um I'm giving it milk every day that
reminds me that what's funny so okay um
you may have seen on on
Twitter uh that I've been interacting
with a
viewer who said oh I can't be I couldn't
be at the stream really because my dogle
had
babies and they're so small and I have
to take care of them and then I was like
oh my God show pictures and then and
then we saw pictures yeah J cow puppies
and some of the dogos have a cow pattern
you know the typical black and white and
I was like oh my God it's a baby cow and
then I did that joke like three times by
now
and I'm being really three times now and
on I think the second time or so I saw
several
replies that seem very seriously
concerned seem to be believing that I
really believe it's a baby cow and they
were like it's just K dot dot cows
aren't as small as a baby or something
like that stuff like that like a few
people actually thought I was serious I
think I'm just doing a little
bit you
know I was thinking if I should point it
out to them but there were several of
them and I didn't want to bother with
it teacup cow yeah totally
[Music]
yeah of course I
know of course I know I'm making a
jerk how is it not obvious but it's
funny to me that some people believe
[Music]
it
vexo
VPO V Expo invited me to boo at their
convention but the plane ticket to the
UK from Singapore where I live is too
expensive and I can't go
so what are you saying you're offering
the booth to
me
uh the
UK can't
go
damn maybe you can have someone
else uh like some if you want now maybe
you can have
kfp uh handle your booth and you can
sell things from home I don't know I
mean some people do that right they have
a booth but they're not even there
they're not even in the country they
just have someone else had if you want
to but
like yeah make some extra money I'm sure
there's some
UK kfp who might even want to help out
with that for a free ticket into the
convention
[Music]
yeah as I said I hope they grow big and
tall and then invite the
lawa speaking of invite the lawa I
cannot give any details but I got some
really cool
thing
and by management told to me for you
know
future and de and I'm like wa that's
cool a really really
nice opportunity
so you won't know for a
while
but it's nice you're going to know I
think when it
[Music]
happens W wa
wa W yay
[Music]
the teas drip looking forward to
whenever have hey when you're fast
typing that
message no it's
[Music]
exciting how much is the merch going to
me uh no comment if there I don't know
who knows what it is who knows who
knows no no k solo life I'd really love
to have a wawa solo life still at some
point but for now I don't know
convention appearance is is
like the closest thing to
[Music]
it yeah okay so here we go I'm going to
read some super chats Super
Chat uh oh do you guys want to be
captured
do you want to be on
[Music]
screen
sorry you are not available at this
moment just kidding there you
are
oh hello there you
[Music]
are capture the moment
okay here we go you want to end the
dumpster
come go go where you belong in the trash
in with you no more out for you unless
you learn how to break out out but I'm
going to Bunk you bunk every time every
time you want to try and go
out oh oh oh oh B oh down down with
you stay
stay Super Chat Super
Chat oh oh [\h__\h] stay you little
[\h__\h] what did I say
oh a bunk a bunk get down get down get
down and stay
[Music]
down I swear to God I'm going to delete
you from my OBS scene if you try that
again get it okay you good
[Music]
ah I can't reach up there oh you fast
boy ah [\h__\h] I missed it now you're up
there in the ceiling and I can't reach
[Music]
you no
no
no okay enough shenanigans
[Music]
enough enough
enough too fast
cute no God please
[Music]
no wait did I not read this before it
sounds very
familiar or it was already in in the
Stream
maybe spank thank you for the right
Super Chat okay yes Callie got to me
about my
name I've removed my beloved Anheim to
make my name easier for
you
what it was not difficult not that I
care or anything oh oh because oh it was
spank kfp beheim
but I would whatever it is I I can just
choose to read spankenheimer
[Music]
in my
brain I want to see the moment where she
has scolded you about your name I need a
time stamp please thank you Callie
hasn't even noticed yet see I IMM
complely acknowledge your guys' name
changes I do it right
[Music]
away
whatever
whatever thank you sp
I Jimmy weep should D oh my God I read
you had a stroke I hope you're okay like
I only see it
people getting strokes and movies and it
scares me I hope you're okay please take
care of
yourself
Thomas
again how there you go I agree with you
El Jimmy weep shooter D Marcus Menace
say
d I'm very observant no I'm
just I'm just you know
always always on
Twitter not a good username
[Music]
Lord Randy RJ Kafka on
theen aalon Space wonderful
D thank
you thank you I appreciate that Wing CV
Dan tip to roll your
ARS oh thank you for the
[Music]
raid hello
rers by the way it's one week left on
froggy waa merch I just had the window
open so I saw it but I I want to show
you the pictures but I I can't because I
still want to fix one thing but it's
probably too late to fix it anyway so
might just have to go with it I'm just
waiting for one last reply maybe I can
show you the pictures
tomorrow anyway uh so tips to roll your
RS press the front of the tongue not
just the tip of your tongue and you
don't need to press that hard to the
roof of the mouth and then exhale like
you want to push the tongue down aim to
[Music]
vibrate I feel like your explanation is
really
[Music]
good but it's not going to work for
me I can do the German uh R but uh
Japanese R that's what you're trying to
explain
[Music]
right that was not
it co
[Music]
co
no no
tip of the tongue right behind the top
[Music]
teeth I'm trying to say like
like P says it for
example like for example Yakuza also use
this like Japanese strong r a lot like
you can say or you can
[Music]
say there must there has to be less r l
no
[Music]
[Applause]
but it's not
just it's
um I don't know I can't even tell the
difference right now
[Music]
anymore no that's just normal
arm I can't I can't waste my time with
this right now
[Music]
I moving
on that was close though
[Music]
yeah k k
you py D don't watch wi's new Vlog for
the love of God so
actually ever since you wrote that py I
had that in the back of my
mind and then I looked it up uh and he
had two new Vlogs one was the
underground like whole life Club
thingy which I'm pretty sure it's not
like always a whole life Club it was
just that one night um but the other one
was the Expo thingy and you saying for
the love of God don't like don't watch
it made me
think uh there must be something in
there that I should
see I watched it though and they did not
play a single kiata song in the club
they played a Million songs and at least
judging by the footage I can't believe
that they didn't play do you or SP
[Music]
what like I mean they played they played
like like original songs from like every
member but maybe maybe cuz it was
already going on when he entered the
club maybe it was like before he entered
or
so I was so bummed oh you were there too
in that club so while you were there
they also didn't play a wa song I wonder
if it could have been requested or
so H but I just thought H it's like you
know my songs would be perfect for
this so I I I went for the whole video
and I was waiting and waiting and then
at some point I was skipping and
skipping looking for my songs and no I
thought there was a reason for why you
wrote that in in the Super Chat and I
thought the reason was because because
they played my song and then maybe in
the footage I can see kfp go absolutely
insane and I wasn't supposed to see
that but no the reason is they didn't
play my
song but it's still cute because I still
saw some
kfps actually I saw a lot of kfps in the
club which is exactly why they should
have played one of my songs there were
so many C Fe there was a lot of orange
there and they were all like kind of
together in a group standing in a group
together so it's like an orange
[Music]
blob yeah I I saw you too in the
club you know you know what you do in
the
club you get
[Music]
L she hit theow got to get
low you stand on the side yeah that too
I would probably stand on the side and
the Rebox with the
[Music]
strap give that big booty a
slap apple bottom jeans and the reuck
with the
the whole club looking at
her she hit the
flo you didn't wear orange because you
had to you just arrived and oh but you
were in the club don't worry you were
plenty um showing the kfp aura even
without wearing orange
[Music]
okay still still good content by the way
anyway even if there's no wawa song
those videos are so
good it's such a nice perspective I was
even thinking of doing like a
little like watchalong uh video like
reaction video just just this once
because you know they they are pretty
wholesome and moving to see this kind of
point of view and see kfp interacting
and all that just you know it moves
[Music]
me I thought maybe that would be a nice
reaction but in the end they didn't have
my song in it in it if if it had my
song but then also the the other one I
watched the other one too the Expo one
M that one was wholesome
[Music]
too thanks for the r chat we are not a
cult K is just an organization with a
figure at the head woried in a Divine
fashion and for whose happiness and full
stomach the members of the organization
are willing to sacrifice with the
promise of being reborn moments later
whatever we are we are already million
times better than
Pana
[Music]
right we should go up against them we
should challenge
[Music]
them yeah
agreed thank you
L we're the better calls
47 golden
K Lord Michael H
[Music]
Michael what what are you trying to say
k has no drink Lings or Bingo
remember could do yet
what what is this what is this hint is
it a hint that Kido
[Music]
dies oh
is was it hint that they
never like
merge
ahuh uhhuh oh it's a hint that they
split in the first
place cuz first they were together I
guess were they together did we have k
and ichun together we did right in the
[Music]
beginning there
D you're welcome Michel D Michael Ed Dan
flight flight of
fancy D Jim j d Michael H DW D J Monkey
D Sky D Cruz D J dang Louis M dangan
dang Michael H dang for several stickers
thank you oh my god Michael H was
spamming super chats H
Moon you did take P twice of a group of
K yeah I'm sure you looked funny in
there it already looks funny on girls I
think it looks even funnier on
[Music]
[Applause]
guys man in some okay there's some ponut
I don't know if I told you this already
but there's generally so recap recap
there's no boys allowed generally not at
least not on their own in the pruna
area area don't hey you want to hear
this trust
me uh so there's no voice allowed you
usually should go I mean probably if
even if you go in there especially as a
foreigner they're probably not going to
say
anything but generally it's like kind of
a rule maybe times have changed maybe
it's not the same anymore but I think
it's kind of an Unwritten rule even I
don't know um also maybe it's more more
stricter in other places but anyway so
so but one thing that is allowed is like
you can go as a boy H with a girl like a
couple or so you know or like friend
group and when you do that and say some
some po machines that have a mode for
like couple pictures or so where there's
like a girl and a boy taking pictures
together um is there like a reason about
it probably like incidents in the past
because that's just a popular place for
girls to gather so you know uh incidents
or just even like PE like guys going
there to pick up girls just getting too
much and being annoying as
[\h__\h] could be I don't really know what
caused it but it's just you know kind of
a thing but anyway so you can go there
as a but and there some there's like
some machines that do like a a boy
mode you can like choose either it's
girl girl or it's girl boy and then you
can choose the girl boy one and then
stand where they want you to stand as
the boy so that they like edit your face
more
suitably AKA they just like make your
eyes less big probably and your face
maybe a little bit less small stuff like
that but I think they hard to find cuz I
don't think you can really for most of
them you probably wouldn't know unless
you go in if they have a mode like that
or not might be hard to find anyway I'm
done okay I'm
done don't worry I'm
done hey you're going to look pretty in
the boy mode or even with no mold at all
you don't need that in the first
[Music]
place H that was it I mean I could go on
but it look silly but it was fun I can
imagine
yeah and you have a nice
Memoir cuz they're not just boring photo
booth pictures they're
fun they're
fun bit too short please
continue
wow no no no no oh bad bad waa
bad don't challenge
[Music]
me
no
booa BBA hot Domingo D Michael h
d d Deon bear D offer dag Channel D I
got to send chagy Channel my motion
oh my God it's almost
midnight
no
no please yeah
okay I also have a meeting before the
stream tomorrow but it shouldn't be
longer than an hour um I think I should
be fine uh I do want to
play I know I I know it's like but I
will play Yakuza before the stream a
little bit I'll do the dungeon um I
think if I do the dungeon I'll be fine
mostly for everything
else C cind why why has no one drawn me
in Cinderella dress until now what the
hell I'm always like ah it's midnight I
got to go I'm always like
this it's so
obvious nobody notices boo 73 D Michael
H D egg bir D J SW d py d and Michael h
d and moonat again thank you
soon oh yeah I even did a cover the
Cinderella yeah the Club remix I love
that
one did I where's the where did the
window
[Music]
go okay can I read one more what do you
think I can probably speed run one
[Music]
more who who who where am I where am I
where am
I here ooh your
truck actually has a lot so that one
probably not that one also not okay
let's read let's read part eight
quickly the others I will read next time
oh wait that's the wrong one part eight
is this I made new fum sorry it took me
a while but they look so nice
now
yeah for tomorrow it's the finale so
maybe I'll make
a even before maybe I'll make like a
finale thumbnail don't I don't know what
to put in
it skip part yeah well we're skipping
part seven for
[Music]
now yeah don't worry about it don't it's
it's I have a system I have a system
although wow there's a lot of pinkies in
here actually
surprisingly py d space waterful Dan
space water Dan thank
you oh don't worry you're
welcome I'm glad I could make you feel
better about it Jacob 47 danush golden I
Dan for free oranges that's like a
pinky the talk about education hit close
to home so I'd like to share I completed
a bachelor's degree in Psychology years
back wow do can I do you want to be my
psychologist but ended up not pursuing a
master's degree in forensic psychology
when I realized how many years it would
take ooh wait do you need both of these
degrees to do it as a
job I would have to not only study
advanced psychology courses but also
learn the court system oh wait forensic
psych that's like I see that's like more
for like court
cases
for psychol geologically analyzing
criminals or I was burnt out from
studying honestly but I honest
understandable but I don't consider the
four years a waste I have a degree in my
experiences which provided a proofed
that I can get good grades if I apply
myself my messages my message to all kfp
with similar stories is that your
efforts always matter it's not a waste
even if you decide to quit no matter
your age or your situation it's never
too late to try something new there are
many paths in life both in and out of
school there's no shame in experimenting
until you find what works for you
exactly a master's degree is generally
considered a bare
minimum what what does the bachelor
degree do then does the bachelor degree
just allow you to get master's degree is
that like step
one why can't you just go straight to
the Master's Degree then just skip
that DN this kind of stuff I don't
really understand it
but sounds like a pain in the
ass it just allows you to get a a
master's Masters is to get hired
Bachelors to work
what ah
what same thing in the
end damn well for stuff like
psychology I get it I don't want to like
there's certain jobs that you could
totally do without all the education
that maybe they say you need to do like
people can do certain jobs without going
for a
special University or whatever you know
right
like I don't know whatever hotel
management you can you can like study
that [\h__\h] or you can just yeah
practically learn it while doing it but
psychology I I wouldn't want to like go
to a psychologist who doesn't actually
have all those degrees if I think about
it
like like you just like like what so
that one I I understand same with like
doctors I'm not going to trust you as a
doctor if you don't have all that
experience in studying this
[\h__\h] like even even then doctors still
sometimes make mistakes because they're
human you know just like sometimes you
just you know but even on that level
making mistakes still is a thing so
you'd want to be as educated as
possible I have Web MD
memorized
same yeah other things are like whatever
I I would say like don't waste your time
even just try to get the job without uh
studying if if that's
possible for
me that was possible too like more or
less like no like I the thing I did I
went to a hotel school right right and
then worked at a hotel but there's like
you can study that in University too I
had colleagues who kind of studied that
in college or
whatever but I kind of took the short oh
actually they were working in the hotel
like part-time I think while doing
University for this kind of thing hotel
management or
so but I could have somehow done that
myself
too h
yeah trade
school trade school good
enough also like simply like art for
example people like go to Art School
whatever like
me
um but and graphic design graphic
design you can learn that you can study
that but you don't have to at all I
think that's like a great example
there's so many great artists and great
graphic designers who are completely
self-taught just because it was their
their hobby so H that's another example
of it not being necessary
to you know go through all of that pain
because then often it doesn't give you
an advantage often right doesn't even
give you that advantage that you would
have hoped
[Music]
for yeah anyway where was I um Santiago
Martin thank you for the red chat a
letter to my kfp comrades first week of
the month on the usual room even when
I'm already been here time ago the
punishment become a hell they sit me on
the chair and loop
the yeah they press four I guess on the
Chima video clip the entire day Nissa
was there too I think because she wanted
it though to be
honest Nissa just hanging out watching
the endless loop of
four pressing
four h well how are you not enjoying
that I thought that's really
enjoyable that's supposed to be a little
bit of a stress relief
actually man
[Music]
anyway enjoy your time in the usual
room with the pinky W I'm adopting a
kitten next
[Music]
week tell me more
but don't have a name for her any ideas
she's a long-haired Tabby and white with
beautiful eyes also my guil just got
Cutting Edge in World of Warcraft again
what does that mean please praise me I
don't know if I can praise you for
something I don't
understand is it a
cow no it's a
tabby sandp yes she's asleeping you head
a kittens will do that
[Music]
Dage cat girl right yeah
Tabby she doesn't have a name yet right
or did you name her by now did you not
have patience anymore oh
[Music]
oops call her cat girl
I are you dead name what if I say a
different name now you're going to
change it is is Shelly
temporary Shell's kind of
cute Shell's
[Music]
okay but if you still want a different
let me know but then i' appreciate a
picture to get my inspiration
[Music]
going sh's
cute pretty
cute even if you don't need a name send
me a picture
anyway chasb
D the einander
D and naan cotton thanks for the pinky
wait are you not supposed to give pep
talks with a crowbar that explains why
mine never works
actually kind of suitable Super Chat for
today no I think you saw a proper usage
of a crowbar
today destruction and pain infliction
okay
Nathan now you know R up for D Jackson
FB
[Music]
Dan HL Dan thank you a I hope you feel
better you must be
happy watch watch a every day all day
watch
watch what # you only
love watch
[Music]
only ah watch only Ki not woke woke
watch only Ki every day there you go I
forgot it I forgot it no we must say it
more often
I'm bonking myself it
hurts J spanking hi thanks the pinky we
were supposed to be standing during the
streams wait I read this I think when
you first sent
it confusing me but I don't think I read
the whole super chats not all of them
just
[Music]
this standing is healthy I guess but no
please have a seat so that your cat can
properly sit on you that's just that's
the bare minimum as a cat owner you know
it you know you know you have to be the
chair become one with a chair Unity chat
Cruz Michael
hson thank you for the pinky AG torture
doll
fund maybe
tomorrow we will be able
to torture
him but I have a
feeling that we're we're going to have a
boss fight and then we're going to have
like a emotional moment where Ichibon
and a are going to talk it out kind of
and then it's all
okay probably going to be like oh we're
actually so
similar oh my God I'm so sorry I was
such a piece of
[\h__\h] probably we'll see and then nak
kiss no please
no I don't know we're too nice that's
like maybe one thing about Yakuza I've
noticed like in the
end like it's a dorky game and it's a
badass game but the badass gets kind of
undermined by all the times we let
shitty people get away I understand of
killing
people uh that's fine but we could still
like not let them get away in other ways
I
[Music]
think the game just like forcefully
always brings them back we could like
blackmail them for example I mean you
can blackmail evil people who will
otherwise just do more more more evil
right at least we're not killing
them you know I don't know just it's
just like a little bit too soft
always and then we can't kill kill the
evil people but then they kill the nice
Side characters that we have on our side
just with no consideration nothing they
just suddenly walk in and PE PE Pew and
dead what they have absolutely no mercy
towards the good people that's the irony
of it but then the evil people we let
them go all the time and a lot of them
don't even redeem themselves they stay
evil and then they come again and we
fight again and so on
[Music]
yeah you would think you would think
rise of free that what we do kills them
but apparently it
doesn't you would not be able to handle
American comic books why do they also
always get
away like with a like we've seen him do
the craziest [\h__\h] and he was just like
genuinely evil I don't know how that's
excusable at least he's got to go to
jail
at the very least he's going to go to
jail we'll see we'll see I guess
[Music]
pyro and thank you for the red super CH
again
[Music]
I shouldn't make these loud noises when
I'm in here feing
around
BOS
[Music]
elos tenants have been
alarmed okay I'm going to skattle
[Music]
oh don't worry about the police I know
how to get out
now I'm so sneaky I'm just so sneaky
like
that all right guys in German we say say
tomorrow for
Yakuza never mind they dropped Yakuza so
confusing I'm so used to saying Yakuza
it's like a dragon now
officially
h
Huh how will I ever get used to
[Music]
that see you tomorrow tomorrow I'm
probably going to put up the reservation
after I get up
two yeah they dropped it I think it was
still yeah it was Yakuza like a dragon
for the first one but now it's like a
dragon infinite
wealth it's not there anymore even as a
sight title no
no is still Yakuza in our hearts it's
Yakuza in our hearts and Yakuza in our
face cuz we're going to smash them and
they're going to smash us so kill let's
go
[Music]
even though it's in the middle of the
week I hope you guys will come and Stand
By Me for a hopefully very exciting
[Music]
finale oh [\h__\h] TS have been alerted and
it's selfie doesn't I got to go
actually come with
me oh [\h__\h] what what
what where's it where's the door here
okay close
close close it
sh
[Music]