thank you
foreign
hiya Darlings this is hello live English
advents devilish Diva the one and only
narissa Raven craft welcome one welcome
all as today we hop into the world of
Terraria or Terraria however you want to
say it it's up to personal preference I
loaded in the world and I've been hiding
underground because I didn't want to
actually start playing
[Laughter]
um
so my my guide guys just
um been killing things
what a good guy he's like you you hit
Underground
you hit underground and here I am
actually putting in the work
uh yeah I'm in the pit just to protect
myself
how are you guys doing you are listening
to bee boo I I was listening to bee boo
but since I have to stream I can no
longer listen to bibu sadly
my my day is ruined but
um welcome
to Terraria uh for those of you who
don't know this game is sort of similar
to Minecraft
uh it's it's it's similar in the sense
that they're both kind of like Adventure
esque games I'm just gonna get right
into playing while I talk I hope that's
okay with everybody
um
I've played Terraria before uh I've beat
hard mode Terraria before with friends
but this is my first time playing Alone
um
I'm in a VC it is open uh for any of the
girls to join if they would like I don't
think anyone will today because it's
kind of short notice but I am planning
to make this a series where any of the
hello live girls are welcome to join if
they would like to try Terraria today
we're mostly going to be focused on uh
exploring the world seeing what we've
kind of got
um as well as just you know uh starting
to build a house and get NPCs and stuff
so today is going to be pretty basic
don't expect any boss fights we're just
basically going to be having fun
at the start of the game
um I picked the mid-sized map
um because I I figured I'd probably
mostly be playing alone to be honest
um
so uh that way it's not the smallest one
but it's it should be a good size for a
few a few people
yeah large is too large I have that
feeling too unless you're gonna get a
really dedicated team
hey man how's it going why are you
talking to me
I'm not going to talk to you sir
please
what evil we got we got the corruption
um we'll run across and I'll show you
everything
um I haven't actually looked at much in
this world because I literally just
built myself a whole underground and
that's been where I'm at today
oh look at the cute little bunny
um
oh I'm ruining the bird's tree
uh but yeah I really like Terraria I
think it's really fun uh
personally I I think I I like it just as
much if not a little more than Minecraft
if I'm being honest
um mostly because uh I get lost so
easily in Minecraft
meanwhile in Terraria
um
I it's so nice you can see everything
you have a map that automatically gets
made for you I do enjoy stardew as well
but a very different but very different
kind of game but yeah I enjoy Terraria a
lot so I'm really excited to be playing
it for all of you on stream
no
can I kill it on accident
um we'll start I I just want to get
materials for a house first as you can
see from my guide killing a ton of
things I have like random stuff in my
inventory
yeah I really like Terraria again no
promises that anyone will actually play
with me
but it would be cool it would be cool it
would be cool if I could rope maybe some
of the other girls at least some of the
Advent girls in on on the shenanigans I
think that would be a lot of fun
where are you
um the class I'll probably end up going
for is either the magic class or
Summoner currently I did Magic before
um and I like it which is my issue so
I'm like I want to do it again but I
really want to try Summoner because it
seems really op
so that's that's our plan for this this
run through again just building a base
today exploring the world
um
I want to build a base before it gets
too dark
uh I don't remember all the requirements
because it's been a while um I think I'm
just on normal mode
um so don't expect things I mean
eventually we'll unlock hard mode anyway
so
it'll be fun
we should hopefully almost have enough
enough
trees cut down oh wow a desert biome
yeah someone are from what I was
researching seems rough early but
obviously gets more op the further you
go so
yeah
there's a vulture I don't want to touch
him he's a mean guy
he's not very nice I know him
I have a family he doesn't appreciate
that that I I have a family he'll kill
me anyway
sorry slimes
not yet okay let's start by going this
way first
konnichiwa
Ohio gozaimasu uh
nihonjin
um
Bros JP Bros
good morning you know
this is where I spawned in but oddly
this feels like a good place to start a
home so where's all my wood that I've
just dropped
um I don't remember how to use things
because it's been it's been a while
first I want a workbench
give it to me thank you
um I'm gonna need
I think
[Music]
wait I need to stop focusing on building
I don't have a house yet so I'm not safe
from random attacks
I'm gonna die early on
it's okay it's daijo boo
okay so
um I'm not certain how I want to build
my base 100 yet but
for now
we just need a base right it doesn't
need to be anything fancy
we can always expand it later to have
rooms and I'll probably even do that
today
um
solely for uh
oh no I made a mistake
okay
let's
this way
please
uh if I remember correctly I've gotta
actually make a proper housing
or else I'll get canceled by the people
who eventually
move in and they won't move in because
they'll be like oh this housing sucks
so
I will try to build sufficient housing I
will not skimp
can you move
man what's wrong with you
he's like I don't want you to build a
house actually
oops you know it's probably fine I think
that should still count right it'd be
dumb if it didn't
[Music]
um
uh okay
so
I need walls
ah yes wood breastplate perfect
I need a chair I need a table
I did not take the table I need two
doors
and I need wood walls I don't know how
many I'm going to need so I'm just gonna
grab a bunch and call it a day
please fill the dirt holes trust me
we're going to be going down there later
trust trust the process
um I have an obsession with digging
underground okay
so we're actually going to dig down
there which is why I didn't do that
okay there we go
nice
now we've got to fill in walls
thank God for whatever this setting is
that lets me do it super fast very nice
hopefully I got enough walls but I have
a feeling I didn't
yeah we're gonna have to dig a
hellevator but first I need to get
enough stuff so we can get back up
successfully
we don't have to worry about that quite
yet though
not a big deal
oh no I I like I like when the cursor
does that I I don't want to turn it off
it's my crutch
Perfect all right and now we can just
Place some torches
uh and now we've got our first nice
little house I believe it is equip with
enough stuff maybe once I place the
chair in the table actually not yet
um
perfect this this I'm not a hobo I have
a real house
first base let's go so
um
now comes the hard part of this in which
uh I am actually going to destroy the
support for my house uh don't ask why
it doesn't matter it doesn't matter I
just simply I don't want there to be any
dirt under my house
it disturbs me it upsets me to have dirt
under my house who would want dirt
underneath their house not me
not nerissa ravencroft
um don't worry we will obviously do
something about this uh in a bit but
just just trust trust the process for
now if I can get up
there we go
um okay let's go ahead I need
a few of you
okay we got someone platforms
now we can platform it
rope perfect
all right we're starting
so yeah again hopefully the game sound
is loud enough I have a pretty quiet for
me but it looks like it's pretty loud
for you guys please let me know if it's
too quiet or too loud
I will adjust it as need be
but I imagine the sound is probably good
I I tested it beforehand so
should be fine
yeah so again our goal mostly is going
to be to begin building a base
um
we need to get NPCs oh whenever I think
about this game I feel like getting NPCs
and digging downward is like my main
priorities
so that's what we're going to be doing
today honestly
we're gonna build a few rooms and then
we will just go downwards eternally
until the end of time
it can build vents
it came from local
and thank you
I love fuamoko
I love Bijou I love shiori I miss shiori
sure please come back
yeah there's there's some slimes in my
house it's okay
the what are they gonna do they're in my
house but like what are they gonna do
about that you know
they're just kind of they're just kind
of stuck
now we just think I need one more layer
I'm not sure
it's been a while since I've played
Terraria
oh but it's so nice I missed this game
DVR on no it shouldn't be
why
I'll check real quick
uno momento
um
oh it is
oopsie well now it should be fixed I
turned it off hopefully it didn't seem
to end stream so thank you uh for
noticing that I don't know what DVR is
but I know I'm supposed to have it off
so good Keen Eye
good good eye there I appreciate that
pun no I'm I don't know what that I
don't know I know what that means but I
don't even know what that means you
can't just call me pawn
three
one two three
and do I need to go one layer deeper I
think so
I do love ponkatsu
wait
tonkatsu with a D
same difference they're not it's not the
same thing but just pretend for me
but for for me
for me uh donkatsu Korean Korean version
of tonkatsu
or it's they're not the same thing
they're not the same thing I don't think
because but it's they're they're
different they're different things but
it's it's okay you don't need to
you don't need to understand
it's fine
Korean huh
I love Korean food
is uh
funkatsu and
Don katsu is uh
Korean it's different I don't I don't
know what else to say
why do I feel like this is wrong why do
I feel like I I'm doing something
incorrectly because I am you know is the
real answer to that question actually
um it's because I didn't you know it's
this is what I get for not playing for a
long time
you forget the controls
you forget how to do things
pubg no thank you
uh to be honest I don't really like
because I'm not good at first person
shooters
I know some people were apparently uh
impressed with my my gameplay
which I have to say thank you
don't don't expect me to play those
types of games often
they're not I don't have the most fun
with them I suppose yeah we're not not
knocking the dust off we're remembering
how to play
and again we're probably gonna build
more rooms so I'm just gonna leave that
as is
hey
perfect
got some got some stuff the the stuff
you know
essential you need you need this stuff
you need the things
the things to to do the things into I
don't know how to describe anything that
happens in Terraria to be honest but
it's such a fun experience
oh what was that that just happened
um
why is he not he's like resting and I'm
like hello sir I'm trying to build our
Fortress
and you're just sitting there as if I
don't exist
uh how how
dare you honestly
he won't even close the door what's
wrong with you what's his name
Brandon
yeah NPCs don't like to do anything ever
actually
it's not just a night thing they're just
lazy
I'll leave Brandon alone I refuse
actually
that should be enough for the wall
[Music]
um
I'm gonna need I'm just gonna get
four doors I'm scared
um
[Music]
I just built the wrong thing can I break
that apart I don't know I'll just keep
them it's fine it's the aesthetic the
aesthetic you know
oh God already already making rookie
errors
how lame is that
can y'all stay out I'm just trying to
thank you
I'm just I'm just doing what needs to be
done
why did it break
did I hit control at some point
why when it auto place the walls anymore
what did I do when did I break
hello
[Music]
I I I am pressing control repeatedly I
want to get that star though
oop I literally just ran into that it's
fine
come here
a demon demon eye
I don't feel like killing you
oh
Oh indeed
it was working and until it wasn't
oh it only works if there aren't already
walls
uh are you sure about that because we
just didn't we just do it after I'd
already built walls up there
any kind of wall on the way if you don't
bring anything and
I see I'm confused but that's okay
I'll figure it out eventually
either way we'll finish off these houses
for now
um I could probably make three they're
not gonna be even
but that's okay
they don't need to be even
uh we can show blatant favoritism
to this middle room apparently
okay torches
um
can you use platforms instead of Dora
say they don't open close them eh no I
want doors
I'm pretty sure you need doors to have
them be like considered like actual like
housing
I don't think you can just like
cheat the system like that
you know what I mean
[Music]
these guys
okay
you can use platform for doors
that's so strange I've never heard of
that before
since when
since when is is that a thing that you
can do
um
foreign
okay wait I'm just uh I'm set I'm
setting up some stuff real quick
one moment I I closed I closed the tab
that I needed okay
platforms count as doors how do you're
talking about this wood platform yes
how
well it doesn't matter
you closed this didn't you you're right
I closed the chat on accident how did
you know
um
well that's so odd
that is so odd I didn't know that that
was a thing
kind of crazy but that's okay
we don't have any weapons yet so we need
to go find some
uh
losers
me about to die to monsters because I
have no hearts
it's fine
look at all these body parts in this
place that I just put together
isn't isn't that sound
okay
I need to get things that oh wow there's
a lot a lot of fallen stars
I need to stop jumping
yeah easy easy money for real
the day is almost here we might as well
wait so we can go ahead and build our
beloved hellevator
because that's that's really what we
want and now I'm not going to actually
build a traditional elevator to be
honest today I simply want to dig
uh I just want to dig you know I want to
dig we will also explore the map maybe
after we dig a little bit
have you eaten of course it's late I've
already eaten everything I'm going to
eat today
I had I had fresh peaches as well so
that was very nice
um
I love to eat a peach
those guys won't leave me alone he won't
do anything
just kind of chilling
uh this is normal mode
I figured I wanted it wanted to keep it
simple you know not too hard yeah diggy
diggy hell hole exactly
all right
um
so this is how big the map is this is
all that we've explored we have a long
way to go down we have quite a ways to
go up and we have both all the ways to
go to the sides
but for now we have one way we want to
go and that's down word
but like a little bit sideways
we can build a proper elevator later but
I want to wait until I have like Vines
and stuff
here we go
yeah we're rich guys
now he's waking up and he's like oh I
guess I should go do things um
oh I also want to see what
uh you know I accidentally built these
so I might as well place them
in some of these rooms for me shouldn't
I
on both sides
no matter where you come in
I just want to see what I need to build
torches I don't even think I actually
need to be in here to build torches
[Music]
oops
I am not smart that was a dumb a dumb
thing to do okay
I'm gonna build as many torches as I can
well I run out of gel
perfect
we are all torched up we've got some
tiki torches too
I can't jump high yet I'm not used to
this
um we'll just we'll place
where did they there
place our five key torches
I guess we can't place them there
I guess they have to go
inside they're they're oh they're a
decorative oh they're a decorative room
item I understand
I get it now
I'm I'm I don't understand but I
understand
okay back to digging we need to go find
some good minerals
because the ax I have is bad
[Music]
sucks
it's the worst it's the worst thing I've
ever had to experience
you can place them outside it's okay
we'll do it later
it's not a big deal
not a big deal
yeah we're looking for bee boo
we will find her
one way or another
yeah where's Kyla Senpai when I need her
I love
me dude I hope I have Platinum I'm very
curious to see what kind of um
what kind of minerals because I know
some of them are randomly generated
Going Underground I don't need
I don't need to cut down trees yeah
definitely gold right
yeah escalator
look we gotta get to hell because we
have a boss that we have to fight down
there eventually but we're not gonna
fight the Wall of Flesh quite yet
ah we've got our first Humphrey the
merchant fantastic
now we can buy stuff
and we should have two other NPCs come
in since we built two other rooms
the Wall of Flesh yeah you know the Wall
of Flesh
surely
you've you know you know Terraria yeah
the Wall of Flesh no
look at all this progress
we're down so far
we we gotta dig
ging is a requirement
uh
what if I don't know Terraria that's
okay
admittedly I I beat it before but I I
don't really know what I'm doing on my
own
so it'll kind of Be Like Us figuring out
together
and I I've I've done a bit of research
so I can hopefully be decent
a decent guide
yeah I'm trying to get back home right
now actually is what's happening
totally 100 percent
now would we make it to Hell very fast
if we just dug straight down yes and
that would be great because we would get
a hellevator but however our purpose
right now is not to get a hellevator no
no or purpose
is to dig and find oars and stuff our
goal we are here to build
so yes we are indeed digging for days
give me one sec I don't know why I
really want to suck on a candy yeah
we're gonna gather resources first again
today is about exploring the map
starting to dig down starting to figure
out how to get to hell that sounds awful
um yeah I guess I'm a dwarf and I'm
digging a hole
Diggy
pretend you didn't hear that
just pretend I didn't say that
foreign
candy
but I've tricked my not even tricked I
think they're pretty good but uh some
people might think I've tricked myself
into thinking that they taste good
yeah we need we need Rock we need Stone
we need we need replacements
for the things we currently have because
we can't dig very fast we dig very slow
with this equipment
and that's okay you know everybody's got
to start somewhere and I think that's
the fun of both Terraria and Minecraft
to be honest let me reposition myself
I'm also going to reposition my model
she like is not looking
where I want her to look
I feel like I'm looking over here half
the time so
it's fine
guys stop I'm sorry
I'm sorry please forgive me
okay look we're so far we've made so
much progress you guys
I'm surprised we haven't run into
anything yet
oh also I know some people pointed this
out already thank you guys for already
uh what a fourth of a million views 250k
on on Kami Point uh that's crazy it's
only been up for like 24 hours you guys
are wild
thank you so much I appreciate that
support thank you guys for streaming and
please continue to stream a lot I worked
very hard on it
I'm very I'm very proud of it
when am I gonna come across some biomes
thank you thank you guys
[Music]
this is this is so fun am I just
building a way down yes am I having a
good time
yes
for me uh I'll log on to Terraria
honestly and I'll just start digging
I just like to dig okay
but I'm I'm hoping to run naturally into
a biome
hopefully before too long uh or not even
necessarily uh oh oh we got Noir
let's see there's gotta be more look at
that we've got lead
I don't think lead is a fantastic ore or
anything but
better than nothing
better better than nothing
I'm just gonna go this way for a little
bit see if there's anything else
I'm pretty sure lead is still better
than what I have now
so I really can't complain at all
okay downward we continue we continue
our descent
lead equals iron and Terraria okay
lead is your yeah yeah so it's it's
better it's better than my copper
that is a good sign for hardbone hard
Mort or yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah look I just really want
Platinum
I'll be really happy if the game gives
me Platinum
I hope I hope I get platinum
I'd be very pleased pleased as a peach
but you should but here I already
explained I'm not digging a hellevator
I'm looking I'm looking for biomes and I
want to be able to get back up easily
so rather than prioritizing getting down
quickly
I'm trying I'm trying to actually like
get
like a a quick way down and hopefully
find uh biome entrances
so that that's why we're not digging
straight down I I'm not trying to get to
hell right now I'm just sticking why not
use ropes because I don't have any right
now and I'd rather not buy them
later
that that is for later to cook we're not
going to hell
we're not going to hell you guys
we we are going to we're looking for
biomes so this is fine if anything it's
better to do it this way
foreign
open world basically any of the hollow
live girls are allowed to join
and play along our joint voice chat as I
already mentioned no one probably will
today and that's okay
um but just so everyone's aware it'll
probably just be me today kind of like
setting up the world getting things
started
gotta kill the slime
thank you
and not just the end for now it's just
Ian
um eventually hopefully I'll be able to
include ID too
I would like I would like to play with
ID because I feel like
Kyla kylo would get a kick out of this
game if she hasn't played it before
with how much she likes Minecraft
I feel like she'd really dig Terraria
perfect
just need a straight straight way down
I do say you know quite often do you
have a problem with that
yeah no I I am also the type who enjoys
Excavating the entire map so like I get
it you know
I understand the appeal the same like
there's something about this that is so
exciting to me because there's there's
nothing there's nothing you can't see
anything it's all black you you need to
uncover the map and therefore you have
to excavate the whole entire ground or
else you'll never know where everything
is you know
uh it's it's how it it's how it be
in these sorts of games and that's okay
and if anything I think that's great
yeah we're looking for bee boo
bee boo where are you
where is she I wish I had um
I wish I had explosives I don't know if
that I don't think there's no there's
bombs there's bombs
I don't use those though I like to dig
organically people where are you please
Queen
um
were any of you watching her karaoke
it was very good
up there's uh some water area over there
revealing its secrets to me
we will build a tiny way in here
an attempt to go down
now follow the singing We're looking
we're looking for bibu
there's Dynamo oh yeah I figured but I
haven't I don't remember if I used it
before
yeah I know she's really good
I love biboo
is is nice to hear her uh sing I'm
excited for her to do her first karaoke
like this I hope she's having a good
time more than anything okay we found
something
it's not a unique biome but that's okay
we're trying to get over here so we'll
keep going
yeah we're looking we're looking for the
caves this is what we're digging for
this is the reason we're not digging
straight down
ideally I'd like to find some chests
that I can take back with me
um
oh
I forgot you can't really like swim
properly in Terraria
okay
just gotta you know make a little
stairway make this safe
for me
because God knows I I need it I need it
to be safe or I won't be able to get up
I don't think there's anything up here
there is a little cave
nice
loading
stream dying my connection's good
I think it might be YouTube
very stuttery that's not good
I'm looking and it says my connection is
great
YouTube problems man
so try refreshing if you're still having
issues a lot of people are saying it's
good now
yeah terrarium
Terraria is a good game
terraria's in my opinion underrated I
feel like a lot of people really like it
but I feel like I don't hear people talk
about it as much as like other similar
type games
you know what I mean
so I want I want more people to
experience it
it is amazing
and again I prefer I prefer this map
because look I can I can see exactly
where I am and how to get back to where
I was
and for me that that's great for me I
really appreciate that aspect
I really feel like that helps me
to be able to get places you know
um I need to keep digging but I just uh
was checking real quick my manager sent
me a message I was worried I somehow
said something bad and I was like what
did I say I've said so much and never
gotten in trouble yet but it was all
fine
why are we digging here don't ask don't
don't question what I'm doing I just
I want to be able to see everything
you know
in this general area
because I'm I'm just I'm just like weird
like that
it's a it's a thing
it's a it's a nervous it's a nervous
Terraria thing
I'm like what if I'm missing some really
good oars that are right there because
they can't see them
um
well if there's
a cave here I'm inclined to believe
there's probably caves around here
which means maybe if we go straight
we might find something
probably not but we're gonna look anyway
there's a cave downward
[Music]
now we've just oh
I made that deep enough oh look at that
more copper
yeah I need to find the B I think I need
to do something with a B
for the Summoner class
I think
yeah I love the mushroom biomes
I want to build a mushroom house so
we've got to find them
we dig
oh how am I gonna get back up
my one my one issue
the one thing I didn't think about
How can I
how can I return
I don't have my Advanced jumping
technology yet
[Music]
I need to be mindful of that that fact
kind of curious to keep digging downward
uh why do I only have 16 I thought I
built more of these that's okay oh I see
something
come on I'm not afraid of you
poor jellyfish it literally didn't do
anything to me
and here I am causing it problems
uh I haven't found a jungle biome yet we
pretty much just started so I'm I'm
pretty much just in this world now
we haven't done anything
we've literally done nothing yet
[Music]
um
this is inconvenient because I can't see
which is not great
zombie you're killing me
why would you do something like that
I just want to dig let me Dig Down
hey draining some of the water that'll
make this easier that means we're right
at the top of it
but we don't want to fall in
perfect
okay that's probably good for right here
a bit too many that's okay
we'll continue we'll continue down this
way it doesn't seem like there's much
much interesting going on there and
that's okay
uh we're on normal difficulty
I will I will say one more time where
normal difficulty we're on the
medium-sized world
there's a Discord it's it's the the
hollow live Discord so the girls can
join not you guys sorry
I don't know if anyone uh will today
um I think I've already said that again
but no one no one's probably going to
join today just because we're mostly
just setting up
setting up the gameplay
hidden I don't know how to make pins man
manager
please
so yeah mostly setting up digging down
starting to explore the world a little
bit and chatting with you guys yeah I'm
alone right now no one wanted to hang
out with me
she already left on vacation just to
avoid me
just to avoid this collab veju viju's
having a car okay already streamed and
I'm sure is quite tired and wants to
rest
there's other collaborations going on
everyone's busy doing amazing things
yeah no someone needs to teach me how to
pin for real for real
I don't know why because I've I've been
able to pin things before but I got uh I
think hyper chat extension and now when
I hover over the text like I used to be
able to it doesn't give me the option
and I'm like what's going on
oh what changed
um
come here
you weird plant Zombie Thing
here we go
um we'll get things from killing things
of course and that's nice
so we might as well not ignore
everything
perfect
back
downward
as we ought to be
oh wait yeah I can't equip the shackle
huh
um I forget what slot it goes in right
here yeah
perfect
we are gaming
I do really like power washed simulator
and thank you for the akasupa I I love
power wash so much
uh power wash is one of my favorite
games actually so I'm really excited to
uh play it with bae uh next week if you
guys saw my schedule
uh uh I I pasted it already
this looks like an or I can I can mine
and we're going to be doing our first
collab tomorrow I have my first collab
ever with Kiowa
tungsten I forget where does tungsten
it's not a great ore is it I don't think
it is I think it's pretty weak actually
I can just tear this down okay that
works
get the tungsten anyway
ah silver equivalent okay
I will try to remember that I'm putting
it in the piggy bank that is my brain
okay
uh tungsten's better uh silver tier so
it's better than iron
which is lead
how do you get down here go bug somebody
else I'm not having luck usually I feel
like when I dig down I run into things
pretty quick and I just kind of run into
biomes and stuff
but I'm not having much luck right now
huh
that's okay though
I hope you have Platinum I feel like I'm
not going to
I feel like just simply due to the fact
that I want to have it I'm not going to
sometimes it's how the cookie crumbles
I need this water to dissipate
out of my way
I need to build a path downward which
means I need you to get drained
away from me
how to breathe I see a pot that gives me
hope that we're getting close to
something I don't know what
um
I didn't need to use wood for that all
right I I made a mistake
and that's okay
happy happy accidents you know as they
say
um I'm looking forward to eventually
unlocking hard modes
um I think that'll be pretty pretty fun
uh pretty pretty fun first dream
but not not today obviously we just
started we have a lot to do
probably probably
look we're on to something okay let's
drain this
I'm gonna place a torch because it's
getting too dark ah
kill this little guy
kill this big guy
come on
it's time for death
I don't do very much damage I should
like go back and like build a weapon or
something
but I want to find something
two
oh I'm gonna freaking die
come on
we got a traveling Merchant he won't
stay though because he only travels come
on
get down
please oh thank you
I thought it was going to die you guys I
was like this is it already
yeah one heart and a dream exactly
we're we're doing it we're doing a
jailbirth
that's what I get for having the worst
weapon
not me let's go explore with the default
huh onward
okay
there we go
we're spreading the water out making it
a little less
but that gives me hope that around here
there's probably multiple a lot of
biomes that we can explore
which is fantastic news
if you ask me wood sword
uh don't ask me questions I don't have
answers we have a Nimble copper short
sword
not not a wood sword just a
something that's are arguably probably
worse
somehow
good enough
Hannah the die Trader has arrived
oh hell yeah
look at all the digging we were just
saved
I like I like doing it this way before
just going straight into a hellevator
because I'm not trying to speedrun
anything you know we're taking our time
taking our time with the game
it doesn't need to be it doesn't need to
be crazy it doesn't need to be fast
um because that's not the point of
Terraria the point of Terraria is to
take like a madman
oh I fell down somewhere
nice okay we're on to something
we're getting somewhere I like this I
like this a lot oh oh oh do you see that
down there
do you see this
look at that oh my God we are so in
okay
gold chest
um
Loot and then I want the chest give me
the chest
uh give me can I get this I can okay
perfect
um I think this is pretty small house
sadly
I don't think there's anything else in
here for me
we have we're doing it
what kind of boots did I get
um good we got Hasty Hermes boots boots
boots boots boots boots
am I putting them in the wrong place
how do I equip my boots again pants
accessory it's an accessory yes
I think boots should have their own slot
boots are a requirement not a not a
suggestion
okay
I'm just building the most accursed
stairs ever
because I like to do things the wrong
way
found some more lead which is pretty
good
let me up
please
what's in my way
moving over too quickly I see
it's gonna go up any higher
I have a feeling probably not oh I'm
just making I'm fumbling you guys it's
because I'm so nervous because you guys
are here and you're like watching me you
know how hard you make things it makes
me so nervous
I'm sorry
a good good thing I've got butt Wings
right
hmm
that leads me to believe that there will
be more over here too though
that makes me want to dig straight over
you know what I mean
you feel me
skill issue
you're a skill you're right I do have a
I I am the skill issue oh look see a
little a little cave I don't care if
it's little it's a discovery
a discovery nonetheless
and that is the joy of digging holes
thank you for coming to my TED talk I'm
here all night
well let me finish this I don't remember
what I was saying I'm sorry I had
distracted myself
okay
I don't think we need to go up there we
can later maybe
but it's probably not too interesting
for now
I need to get I need to get the cloud in
a jar so I can move faster what is that
I have no idea
it didn't tell me anything
are we foamoco today
yeah fall down good luck try just try to
get back up
good luck with that
have fun being stuck idiot slimes
and I don't think we got a raid did we
did we
hello are we just bow bowing or was
there a rate I'm pretty sure they ended
stream and ready to be bee boo so unless
bibu is rating me I I don't think so
and look again that saved us so much
time yeah we're just bow bowing that's
what I thought
muster healing potion very nice
um we're also hoping to obviously find
some hearts
that would be really nice
oh the
demolitionist has arrived
see that's why we build houses we'll
we'll probably need and want to build a
lot more I think there's what like
something like 28 20 something NPCs
I don't remember the exact number but
there's quite a few
28 20 something can we get a Kaka
I don't sound as good as kiwawa because
I'm not a crow I'm a raven
yeah give me give me the cause give me
the oops and the cause chat
oh look at that I'm gonna destroy that
I'm so big brain uh
we're coming to the biomes and have
nothing
I don't mean literally have nothing but
are just a little more complicated
um
easy transportation
it's very important
who doesn't like to easily be able to
get around you know
and that way if I can convince anyone to
play with me they can come down here and
be like oh it's so easy it's so
navigatable it's so it's so fun because
I don't have to worry too much
that's that's the real plan here guys
we're making we're making a fun a fun a
fun way to play I think yeah we found
bibo you guys
amethyst I don't think Bieber was
technically I don't know what kind of
gem she actually is she's a biboo gem
um let me quick look at something real
quick
um
okay
so we got Hermes boots
we've got uh
we're not doing too bad we're not doing
too bad considering we literally just
turned on the game basically
come on
funny I'm gonna die to slimes
I can already feel it
[Music]
come on
you'll never take me alive
I guess we could go up sometime soon and
see what time of day it is and maybe
maybe try to
you know
um build a different weapon
I actually don't know how to build
weapons I've got to be honest I don't
know what the hell I'm doing
I have no idea what's happening
[Music]
yeah Terraria music is so good
I love Terraria Music Man
okay another way down
let's explore ikima show
yeah we need a furnace we need an anvil
that is correct and we probably have
everything no there's something more
down here I need to know
we're getting into different biome
territory
I'm sorry I'm too excited I can't stop
we gotta dig
we we gotta dig it
you guys understand don't you when you
find something exciting in a game and
you're like
it's over for me
okay oh
um I'm gonna make easy to get up there
we go
perfect okay downward
let's dig look at that the color's
changing
I can see something glowing down there
I'm so excited
we need to dig you guys don't understand
we have to dig
yeah we gotta diggy diggy the whole
I'm digging a hole
I bet there's not gonna be anything down
there it's gonna be so funny it's just
gonna be like one little one little
whole room
yet here I am being so excited for it
just because it's glowing a little
I love to dig digging is the best
digging is the most yes it is it is a
reference yeah
you are correct on what I am referencing
sorry I should place a light oh I placed
it in the wrong place again
I'm gonna just further create problems
for myself
my ability to see oh I can see another
cave okay we are so in we are so in this
we are in this this this tunnel cave
we're gonna have so many materials you
guys
it's all just gonna be dirt and stone
but who cares
descending will be no problem
just gotta get through all this play
first
and around desert is extremely dangerous
early game it's fine
I've played I've played before I'm I'm
so good at Terraria
probably
hey give me give me what you got
okay
we gotta build stairs easy access
and then I see something blinking over
here
so we're gonna dig straight
thank you for reading hello everyone
Bebo please remember I have open voice
chat if you'd like to join you can play
Terraria if you want to mine but if you
want to take a break after your karaoke
I understand no pressure but if you want
to come talk to me for a little bit you
can feel free to hop into I love you
Bieber thank you for raiding
welcome Pebbles how are we doing today
Pebble raid I'm getting pelted by
Pebbles
I can't believe it
thank you for stopping by as you can see
we are playing Terraria today I will
give the quick rundown
as pinned in the comment as well uh we
are we're just
chilling okay
um we're chilling
we're chilling we are just trying to
kind of uh this is a new map
um this is all we've explored I haven't
even gone through the science
um yet which I will soon because oh oh
no not the worm
oh no I don't have the means to kill
this thing
we might need to run for it
that's okay
um but yeah we're exploring I wanted I
wanted to mine because mining is what I
like to do
um and I wanted I wanted to just get
started
um we've built uh housing already
so we do actually already have some
people moving in
which is nice
the thing's gonna kill me and I'm just
not caring at all because I'm like so
close
uh you know actually it's almost dead
and I've still got some health in me
it's fine
it's fine probably probably not but I'm
just gonna keep telling myself it's fine
there we go look at that killed it
without even trying
that is the big big brain plays here
oh gotta
kill the red slime
before it kills me
ow
a Calamity playthrough I'm not sure what
that is you're gonna have to enlighten
me
we're not playing on easy mode we're
playing on normal
I've already I've played it on normal
before and beat it on normal I didn't
want to go harder
um because that's not what we're here to
do to ooh Sapphire Platinum Ore
let's go
already got Platinum
that's amazing
okay very nice
I'm so glad I have Platinum I'm so glad
I came right over here it's a nice
little pocket too
so hippy hippie
okay
easy ways to get back up
make gotta make the gameplay accessible
can I not place underwater
that's okay I have a solution
I have a solution first I'm gonna get
the tungsten ore
and we're just gonna
jump
thank you
it's enough
we've done you've done well narissa
Terraria narissa we're gonna head back
up for now
yeah I need to I need to figure out how
to make my uh pickaxes stronger
um
okay
onward we go we continue our journey
I could probably make this
a little more
accessible
good
oh
this is fine
look at that oh no
I dropped into a hole I can't see
anything
I'm alone with the Slime who's going to
kill me
come here I'll kick your ass don't test
me
okay we found our first cave system
which is admittedly I'm pretty excited
about it
and oop I'm gonna die I'm gonna die to a
slime
get away from me monster
please I'm innocent I haven't done
anything
uh
okay it's almost dead it's almost dead
but it's this other one then going to
hop down is the real question
I feel like the answer is yes because
that would be my luck
to build some stairs up
the easy way out
and then we're just going to run to the
surface as fast as we can
um
but we've got to also make it easy to
get up so we have a bit of a ways to go
it's actually going to use the pickaxe
for fighting yeah it seems that way my
sword sucks man
this is the weakest sword I've ever had
in any video game ever
uh
oh look at this look at all these Vines
can I
how do I uh pick up the vines I want to
farm them
I don't remember what I need to use to
cut them down though
okay
um upward
let's go
how do I consume the fallen stars for my
Mana I forget
it's ammo material disappears after
sunrise
uh uh I need a book yeah how do I how do
I eat the star
how do I just eat it surely
oh I need to craft it okay okay okay
sorry it's been a while I know I've said
that already but it's been a while can
you tell can you tell now
oh another one
nice
okay so we need a furnace
furnace furnace
I presume I'll be able to build it from
here
we also can get a chest but I already
have a gold chest so I don't need
another one quite yet
for furnace
okay what was the other thing we needed
what class are you playing currently we
just started so we're not playing any
specific but um
I I'm planning to do Summoner Anvil yes
thank you
nice okay
very good
okay
yes Summoner gang we go but I feel like
I'll probably end up going magic
um route
just because that's that's just you know
I feel like I'll probably
um you know
you can buy anvils I'd rather build it I
have the material so why not
[Music]
wear my oars
um
okay first
we've got some things for decoration so
firstly we have or did I oh I'm just
literally can't see
um look at that
look at that isn't that amazing
oh my God that's beautiful that's the
most wonderful thing I've ever seen so
what we're going to do is we're going to
dump all of our oars into here
um or all of our extra stuff for nelm
that we don't need
like wood
I I'm Gonna Keep My Wood on me actually
wood and dirt are always useful
gel you can go here
a wand I'll use that as my weapon seeds
copper ore
lead ore lens
day Bloom mushroom shackle
uh sure can cobweb
uh a blank root
uh
living wand is a tool oh my God okay
I'm just gonna get rid of that then
anyone joined yet no
no one wants to hang out with me that's
okay
Sapphire Platinum Ore that's what I'm
looking for Tungsten arm
s we've got bombs we've got amethyst
we've got blank root seeds I need to do
a better job I'm not doing a very good
job at all organizing this that's okay I
just need to get a general idea
um
sort
that's not how I wanted to sort it
can I sort it here
yes okay cool
so now I've got a good idea of what I've
got sword
seeds
somehow this is more confusing for me
somehow
sort
if I keep hitting sort does it keep
sorting them differently no it doesn't
it's just like we've already sorted it
what do you want from us
um I just want to separate the orb
we've already got Platinum
which means
I don't want silver coin I don't want
Copper Coin wait I can craft
that
huh
nice
okay
and we've got our first consumable
let's eat it
[Music]
perfect
look at that we are gaming for real for
real
I'm so sorry
why am I like the cringe master
um
lid acts is better than what I currently
have
so I want it
um we need to go back in and get our
other tungsten
we need
[Music]
why would anyone make platinum bricks
that's so crazy
I have embraced my cringe I am cringe so
I am free
[Music]
okay I do need to make it into bars
first
where's my
give me my tongue tungsten bars okay
um
[Music]
I don't think I have enough to really
make
really make if anything yeah I don't
have enough for anything
that's okay it's all right
we don't worry about stuff like this
we needn't worry because at least we're
cute right
I'm confusing myself
that's okay
all right
I want to build a regular chest
why can't I build a regular chest am I
confused am I blind
[Music]
I must be having a stroke I'll come back
later
um it's fine
oh I need iron okay I see that that
makes sense
iron makes sense
I guess I guess it makes sense
[Music]
okay
look at look at us look at look at how
far we've come isn't that amazing
surely now yes I can build a chest very
nice I can also build a trap door
but right now I just want a chest
idea
and in this one
um I'll put my extra stars for now
um let me take a sip of water while I'm
thinking about what I want to do
okay
hmm
[Music]
I want to place my oars in here
I want to make a collective so everyone
can get oars
from the same place you know what I mean
like if they need them they're like here
it's an ore tungsten bars
uh order this is technically the correct
order I don't remember how many there
are in this game
we'll do it like that for now it doesn't
need to look good
it just needs to it just needs to look
you know
I could probably put the other ores back
on
yeah I'm gonna explore the surface now
before we head back down
because that seems like a good a good
move
Papa
okay onward we go
so going to the left first I don't know
if we'll get all the way as far as we
need to go
first we have a desert biome
desert biomes are fun
oh out
it looks like there's a start to a
elevator
makes me curious
makes me excited waku waku
oh another one
not you
I don't want to fight
please keep running please please we
need to get away please
oh yeah see it's getting light up and
we've already come across
our first bit of corruption
which means I need to get the hell out
of here I'm gonna die so fast I'm like
about to die oh
can they get me underwater oh no they
can't that's so funny
[Music]
they can though I'm screwed man I'm
gonna die
not another one
just keep running it's fine
it's fine we got the Hermes boots
we've got the Hermes boots which means
if we just run it'll be okay
we're not strong enough yet we don't
have any armor
yeah oh is for right Is For Real
this is this is a premium Scooby-Doo
moment
hello little slime on a balloon
We're Not Dead
[Music]
I think this is as high as the ceiling
technically has to be I just made the
other ones a little extra spacious
because I'm so nice like that
so there we go a little a little
exploring to the side we will need to do
more later
I need Headroom for my horns you know
they bumped me up to like what 182
centimeters
kind of crazy
perfect
I actually wanted to go in the chest
thank you
[Music]
doors
doors are what I need one two three
one one
two three
[Music]
uh
one two three four
and then lots of walls
put an input to Quick move items
that's okay I didn't know
we we were digging we'll go back to
digging or maybe we'll go get some trees
again because I probably need
some more soon
tree tree stuffs
um
nice okay
we'll need to fix that
kind of need that
that would
but for now we're building
[Music]
we are building successfully
nope
I forget how to destroy the walls I
think I need to full on just
I need a hammer don't I yeah I need a
hammer
I don't have one on me we'll come back
and do it later we'll fix it later well
now I've annoyed myself actually wait
one sec
okay
[Laughter]
not the broken looking wood hate that
hate that appearance so much
bugs me to no end
I won't be having my my villager thing
houses looking like that
we are successfully building
the next bit of housing
we just need to put lights in it
and I think it'll be perfect perfect and
viable
broken wood
it's fine we're winning we're winning
guys chat please believe me
leave my hotel alone leave leave it
alone it's just it's just to get it fast
hmm
I'm doing my best please
I'm begging you be nice to me
look it doesn't matter it doesn't matter
where where they where they live okay it
doesn't matter
they have the opportunity
they have the opportunity to live
somewhere that's better than being
homeless
imagine imagine someone gives you a free
house are you really gonna complain
about that
Free Housing you don't even have to pay
for it I protect you I mean that's
basically you know that's yeah that's
already the our situation you live
outside I feed you I provide for you
my jailbirds
it's okay are you winning I'm trying
I'm trying to collect some wood before
the day ends
is that a fruit it is a grapefruit I
thought it was an orange
come here
come here you
I need to go back down to my mind and
find
decent weapons I need to find something
that is not what I currently have
so badly
and then we need to try and um
do literally anything
yeah this this was it was my decision to
play this game so I can't complain too
much
at the end of the day the suffering is
by my choice and I'm happy to suffer
because I like Terraria
it's it's just a little bit of suffering
at the beginning anyway you know
it gets easier as the game advances
until you turn on hard mode then it gets
hard again but that makes it fun you
know it's more of a challenge
everything everything scales with you
let's get back in here
um
quick stack
I'll add my grapefruit in there water
Leaf whatever that is
sounds like something I don't need
let me take more water I'm thorsty
I'm very thirsty
need bed can you build a bed I feel like
I've never built a bed in Terraria
um
okay let's
talk to the guy and you should stay
indoors at night it's very dangerous to
be wandering around in the dark
underground are crystal Hearts which can
be used to increase your max life you
can smash them with a pickaxe
thank you
okay
uh oh wait you know I was checking
something and then I didn't even check
the right thing
you'll ever get distracted when you're
doing something that's me
all the time
[Music]
yes
cool cool cool cool cool cool cool cool
cool cool cool cool cool
okay everything's all good okay
onward
um I guess we could wait here until day
time
if we really wanted to
that cute little owl oh my God
there now we can get on top of the house
let's just for now
I'm gonna get rid of this
this because I have a better one
and let's just move you know is it
dangerous because it's night absolutely
yes do I care no
we have fallen stars to collect
I need to up my Mana so I can be a good
Summoner
ugh
yeah until until we can start building
Summoner if I find magic weapons is
probably what I'll use for now
for anyone who missed that spiel
but I really want to I really want to
Summoner run
because I've never done it before
scared
because it's hard it's not easy
[Music]
come on come at me
maybe not I'm weak actually maybe go
find someone else to attack
not doing so hot
please
I need reinforcements please oh no
coming out at night was a mistake proven
100 I shouldn't have done it
but I think the nice thing about
Terraria is I'm pretty sure when you die
you don't lose your stuff right
you lose your coins
that's it you lose your coins but you
don't lose your stuff it's okay I didn't
lose that much
only one gold 42 silver I mean what did
I even have to begin with
plus I can just go pick it up
I don't think it's the same amount
though I don't remember
I don't remember how it works
Hey look
picked it all back up we're all good
got two fallen stars we've got a lot of
eyeballs who need destroying
I really don't feel like fighting these
things I don't really have a good weapon
yet which is a shame
look at how many there are I'm so
screwed
there I'm safe
filmcraft wooden swords I mean are
wooden swords better than the default
sword do you need bait no I'm okay but
if you'd like to pop in you're more than
welcome I think we'll need to add each
other on on
you know on Steam
yeah Cali I saw said that she might be
interested in joining so I was like oh
my God Calliope Senpai play Terraria
with me
wait I shouldn't say this while she's
here I sounds totally weird
but I feel like that's kind of
accidentally my branding
okay let's just run back home for now
we've we've killed enough
I don't feel like killing any more eyes
[Music]
I didn't see what you said one second
let me get my house
yeah we will go back to digging soon
I send you my steam please send me your
Steam account I will watch I will watch
for it I see it
okay give me one sec I want one moment I
gotta I gotta figure out how to work how
to work Steve
friends and friend ah hello
I hope I can be useful I don't know I
can be useful but I wanna try
it have you've played before right yes I
have I have three hours on this game
three hours this might be worse I know
the basics yeah no it's not bad okay I
sent you an invite to um be my friend
please be my friend okay yeah sounds fun
oh my God impromptu cool yeah yeah I
guess so I I kind of I had some stuff to
work on but
um I kind of don't really want to do it
so here I am yeah
you know same way well it's the way nice
to see you nice to talk to you this is
the first time we've ever like spoken
one-on-one I feel actually it is
actually let me turn on um tech oh she's
so cute cool I'll put on Do you have
yeah with my cowboy hat it comes on when
I speak yeah yeah okay a special feature
I like it I like it little little Ranger
cowboy
yeah
yeah it's the cowboy thing thanks all
right
let's go
give me
give me me waiting patiently all right
hold on join via steam I got it yes
incoming friend request no no no don't
don't you other people start sending me
friend requests right now because you
know I'm looking out for nurses yeah
guys stop it
all right well I found it thankfully and
yeah I accepted so let me see if I can
find you okay because I don't know if it
says it says in game let me just reopen
steam yeah I think that'll can I re can
I restart steam I don't know if I can
um all right don't you worry I'll come
to you okay I think I need to invite you
is the issue
um and there is a code as well you're so
good well extra safety I guess yeah I
just gotta make sure no one no one
weirdly is trying to like get in or
anything
um well I mean if I close steam it won't
close the game and the game Auto saves
so who who will it hurt you know if I
close the time
well I got the code thankfully so yeah
yeah you said you said you got it and
you added me so um let me
let me let me let me uh destroy the game
real quick
oops
waiting sorry I haven't done this before
um no no no it's okay I don't think
anything will show on screen that's not
supposed to but just want to be doubly
sure everyone said fingers crossed yeah
fingers fingers crossed
exactly okay let me uh quick restart
restart steam
um gotta open up my little task manager
all good I'm just here avoiding
responsibilities
all fine with me you I know what that's
like
okay
classic dad Behavior they're saying uh
but really uh to be honest I can't see
you avoiding responsibilities because
you produce stuff like crazy
yeah I mean the thing is my hobby so I
guess but that's fine sometimes you
gotta sit back and unwind with the
homies that's what I'm here to do so I
still don't see you for some reason so
let me give you my friend code and just
make sure
what if I accidentally added the wrong
person can you imagine that would be so
funny like I planned this yeah they're
like oh my God she's we just quick
change your account name quick
ly
all right here send send invite okay
perfect I got you I'm fine yes so
whoever else you added please remove
them all right time to get rid of them
oh no dang you
okay I'll load back up the game and then
I'll send you an invite
okay
sounds good it says you're online yay I
finally see you yeah I see you too oh my
God Maury Calliope my friend on Steam
yeah
I just I I don't do anything don't worry
about it but I do want to be helpful so
yeah so um you know if you need someone
to throw in front of enemies for a sec I
I can be that person for you
you need I mean I won't throw you I
would never I would never do that to you
um I like you I would never do that to
you oh you're all right too
I like you too wow you're so sweet okay
yeah
for me Calliope I even have a character
already nice then you'll already you'll
already be built up a bit won't you
a little bit you know as much as about
three hours can get you
yeah
okay invited me it's Terraria really is
that okay yeah she has work to do but I
guess I'll go it's okay it's for your
cute cool high so you can't say no right
that's a really good point actually yeah
management what are you gonna do about
it huh you're gonna tell her she can't
help me
precisely okay precisely let me see um
accepted an invitation okay yes I did
and then I will throw me I typed you the
password so okay
gotcha let's see uh join the game
with my character yes and then joining
okay I'm on my way oh my God I got the
password I have the password that none
of you have yes uh lost connection okay
oh you know what it's because I copy
pasted the wrong oh it happens just just
kidding I'm on my way sorry to interrupt
the flow no you're not my fine I'm happy
to have you interrupt the flow I was
just um doing whatever it is I do when I
stream why you got it why is it why does
it keep losing the connection that's so
weird maybe I'll manually type it in
okay let's see
join game you're playing on PC correct
yeah obviously yeah okay gotcha okay
should be fine then
joining and then found the server and I
need to put in the password yes
it's pretty it's pretty easy
got it
what why is it not allowing me to
connect no please it's weird let me odd
let me play with Maury Senpai game
what's wrong with you I found the server
it doesn't want to let me players
I don't want to do my responsibilities
let me close to already and open it
again okay
you can keep doing your thing oh yeah
yeah don't don't worry I'm uh I'm
killing slimes and uh cutting down trees
and not replanting them like a monster
no that's the that's the best way to do
it I know that's because it's time to
replant the trees don't tell fauna I
said this to you I won't I'll be sure
not to mention it
I don't want her to be crossed
across fauna when it comes to trees man
yeah
well I realized I have like 70 seeds so
now I'm just running and replanting them
which is probably not the best method
but who cares yeah exactly whatevs
let me see a fun game
maybe all right
[Music]
a very strange still not working
yeah I don't know it must be a me thing
it says incorrect hold on no it's the
correct password it's just that I can't
join I don't want to disturb the flow of
your game
all right it keeps losing the connection
so uh I guess maybe okay maybe others
will try and join a bit later and we'll
figure out because I don't want I don't
want you to have to stop what you're
doing but ah it's okay we can definitely
figure it out yeah thanks for popping
yeah for a bit I mean you're welcome to
stay in chat if you'd like to
is that okay yeah I don't care who who's
gonna stop us it's too late
good point okay well yes so you've
played Terraria for three hours what
what do you like about it
I like that it pixel art same pixel art
pixel art fan me too
yeah I think you know Minecraft is is
fine I have a bit of a I don't know I
think I prefer the way that Terraria is
to Minecraft to be honest it's a bit
small though everything's really small
so my my eyes kind of have to strain to
look at everything
no I actually uh feel the same way I
really I really like Minecraft still but
I feel like uh the thing that gets me
about it that makes me like kind of like
eh about it is that like it's so hard to
get everywhere it's so easy to like
forget where you are and like it's so
it's so sandbox that to me I end up
never doing anything important in
Minecraft and like just kind of wanting
to play on creative and build because
like I just want to build you know
um yeah as for like Terraria like I it
makes me want to play the plot you know
like I don't just want to hide inside
and sleep during the night so I can
avoid the monsters no no I'm like oh
yeah I gotta fight them
Ah that's so interesting that you prefer
the creative on Minecraft but you wanna
beat some people up in Terraria I just
want to dig in Terraria
I wonder how low you can go that's what
I've always wanted to find out oh well
you can go all the way to Hell literally
yeah we gotta do that I know no I'm I'm
I've been digging down right now but I'm
not getting super duper far um just
because I'm trying to find like biomes
and stuff so if anyone else wants to
play it's more like easy to get down
without just like falling down a hole
and then like dying from Fall damage ah
good point yes yes wow that's cool and
monsters spawn underground right yes
they do it's annoying
ah I still gotta fight him uh can I see
they want me to show you the map or do
you have my stream open by chance
I'm looking at it
um so I'm opening up the map to show you
the whole world I haven't explored at
all obviously even to the sides because
uh whoa the corruption but uh basically
once you get around like this point-ish
I think it becomes hell so I have a ways
to go and most people will build what
they call a hellevator where they'll
literally just build straight down to
get there as fast as possible oh my gosh
but how do you not die from Fall damage
um well it's more it's more about when
you're digging straight down it's fine
and you can um build things like vines
or like ropes and stuff so you can
actually like climb or um they're also
uh like wood platforms so you can place
those like I've been making stairs with
them
cool yeah I can see that yeah
wow good idea man I hate that this is
making me want to play it really bad I
am so sorry
don't be sorry I'm sure there's
something on my end I wonder if it's
because of location we're not in the
same part of the underworld you know oh
yeah that's a really good point I mean
it could be the case but let me see a
lost connection
us steam okay there are various factors
um Miss Master outdated game version
corrupt game files incompatible game
character and so forth do I need to be
playing like a hard mode character or
something we're not we're so we're not
playing hard mode we're just playing
normal and I don't think it should um
matter so hard mode you actually unlock
as you go in the game so the game kind
of starts out on an easier mode and then
like after you do certain things you you
have to like actually do things to
unlock hard mode it won't just like
forcibly give it to you so it's like
it's like an effort you know
ah okay it makes it it makes it fun
okay that's neat
um I feel like I'm okay thank goodness
because I was really I was really
nervous I was like if this is hard mode
I don't know no not yet
all right I'm gonna I'm gonna do I'm
gonna do some troubleshooting and I'll
try to join one more time but if not
then that's no problem I don't mind
chatting too yeah but I don't know pixel
art is like it's my kryptonite man I
could be working on the most important
thing in the world and then like a new
pixel art game comes out and I'm like oh
no yeah I'm in trouble I feel you I'm
like I'm weak so I admittedly uh I
really like um RPG Maker games that are
like oh they're so good
I saw you played Witch's House I
suggested it is I really like I really I
really like Witch's House uh it's so
much fun the story is so good too yeah
pretty good yeah I'm playing Mad Father
uh next Saturday too
that was probably one of the first games
I think that was the first game I played
on my channel ever really
back in the day good old dad is mad and
we don't know why you are down
so does that mean that you are the Mad
Father yeah see that was that was
another area
I think that was the secret Genesis of
the quote unquote dad joke yeah
as far as then not just my dad is the
queen of all YouTubers which is a great
manga that I recommend that you read
yeah it's a good one um what other oh do
you like stardew Valley I love stardew
Valley
oh are you excited for haunted
chocolatier oh my God I am yeah he did
waiting for it yeah I know same like I
can't wait I I need it out yesterday
huh
oh yeah but then of course would not get
um any work done so maybe for the better
it's not out yet well hey at least
you're a streamer so you can just you
know uh play it for Words
yeah that's true too
really yeah we're not allowed to play
stardew just because
reasons but that sounds maybe someday
maybe someday maybe someday yeah I
thought I saw Ina play it before so I'm
surprised
I think I'm pretty sure it would
probably have to be privated at that
point but yeah
yeah for shame but it'll be it'll be fun
to play with others yeah I'm not allowed
to say the reasons sorry Chad that's
okay
why perms are dumb it but all right
maybe I'll try this again
let me know if you need me to send
another invite
oh no worries that's all right I'll just
I'll just join you
I went ahead and I verified the game
five the Integrity of the game files
chat you know what that means I went
into the data and I verified them we'll
see
they want me to restart the server okay
I'll restart the game too one more time
because I I don't mind are you sure I
really don't want to be like me no like
for real I mean the whole point was so
maybe maybe people will play with me so
it makes me happy if we could maybe play
together even if it's only for a little
bit it'll make me a pretty pretty uh
pleased as a peach oh okay if it makes
you happy then I guess it can't be wrong
oh huh
is that people it is
it's going we're trying to we're trying
to see if we can find a good way to get
uh
caliope here to join aliope oh I still
gotta download it
you haven't downloaded it yet
no I'll download it right now oh no I
thought your karaoke was gonna be from
11 I was gonna go watch it
I just finished and then I had a little
break but I know I know erase that was
doing her thing and I wanted to come
play I want to play play with me I'll
give you the password and I'll send you
an invite okay okay give me one sec cool
uh where are you
and before people can't get I get in
either what should be like somehow an
issue on my side
okay I'm in the game right it's just the
base game right yeah yeah no no you
don't you don't need anything oh that's
a four pack never mind yeah yeah it's
just it's just a game okay let me send
these invites
um
invite
reading the name in the most cursed way
go minisari okay
[Music]
I know I know that he he
yeah I'll join in just a moment
[Music]
Calliope Maury
because you
oh I mind you
what you were you were in you were in
the game so I mind you there's there's
some purple gem so it's I don't know if
I want to play it no please
okay I sent uh you the invite and the
password so okay I'm installing the game
yes in the meantime I'll explore the
signs of the map while we see if Miss
Calliope can join yeah
I think we're at this game right no I
beat it before though
all the way through
Terraria yeah so I think I'm pretty
positive it lets you keep playing but
yeah there's like an end game stuff like
you can actually like finish it but
again like it can keep going after it
but like there's a final boss I mean
it's sort of like Minecraft in that way
but yeah you can keep fighting the Final
Bosses
cool yeah no bosses didn't even know the
game had bosses there's a lot of bosses
I played I played Starbound which is
why I think it's like the space version
but I've never played this one
yeah Starbound seems cool
all right it says joining just taking a
while okay nice nice we're getting
somewhere outside yeah I think that's a
good sign
all right connecting and then it's gonna
ask me for a password at least it's
taking time now yeah because that means
it's working
I have hope
I'm excited I want to go to hell
[Laughter]
so okay the nice thing about Terraria
when you die you don't lose any of your
items so you will lose your coins but
you won't lose anything in your
inventory so uh something that you could
do theoretically if you really wanted to
is you could place stuff elsewhere like
your coins before going and then you
could just literally dig straight down
to Hell it would still take a while but
like then you don't have to worry too
much about like losing all your stuff
kind of nice see
I see here that there's a tip that says
if you fall on a cloud don't worry you
won't hurt yourself can you go to the
sky yes there are sky islands
are you kidding me no
one piece yeah there's little there's
little houses too uh that you can Loot
and there's harpies in the sky so you
have to be you can go all the way to
space but you can't do much in space
you can get wings and fly as well so you
can like drift yourself slowly to the
ground
oh I might be a wild there's character
customizing yeah that's okay take your
time it's not it's not too too much
character customization but I feel you I
I had to do it all before a stream make
myself cute
you're always cute people
true it's not alive no I'm gonna die no
I can't do I can't do double praise
don't both of you don't do that I'm
gonna die
two two one-san types in chat
that are complimenting you what are you
gonna do
[Music]
it you're a good B week
I like that it's cute
I'm so sorry no I I'm very Focus right
now I'm getting making a cute character
hmm
I'm just gonna go ahead and join the
esteem because it's taking a while for
me to join so I'll just join game
select player joining
found okay passwords got it
um there's also different classes oh
caliopa joined welcome
okay give me one sec I found a ton of
ore
um but just get in the house and hide
for now if you'd like yeah I'm chilling
don't worry oh you got a cool chest yes
feel free to look at it all right I look
all up in there let's see oh
oh
nothing
what are you stealing
I see that there's some things here like
uh oh Hunter potion magic mirror
a magic mirror wait I had a
magic mirror
of magic mirror excuse me oh oh okay I
see you I see okay the nice thing about
the magic mirror I think you can use it
to teleport back uh to base at any time
so that's huge hi is it one youth hi I'm
here I'm always here why is my skin
orange I don't know
um they're not one use I'm pretty sure
you can use them endlessly so really yes
um wow I was holding on to that the
whole time yeah look at you um but
obviously it kind of sucks if you
accidentally use it
um oh yeah because you know it's far
away yeah when you're when you're
digging and you found like a really cool
place and then you made to click
something else but you accidentally
clicked this stupid mirror and then
you're like oh no
what do I do with this how do I play
stuff
um you should just be able to place it
click in place maybe it's a weapon stone
block
can I please that oh I did it yeah yeah
yeah I don't know what that is never
mind it looks like a block never mind
there it goes I don't know what Obelisk
does I just have it they're block do you
want to go down in the mines
yeah sure let's do it I have a copper
pickaxe perfect better than nothing
invite yes I can one sec I'll do that
for biboo and then we will uh or you can
just run down you'll be fine
also if you're having trouble joining um
you could also like join via steam
friend list that's how I joined oh yeah
just click join and then put in the
password
cool
and um it's not yeah
it was being weird at first when she
tried to join too
make sure you verify the Integrity of
your game files though I think if you
just downloaded terrari you're fine
I think this is where I'll password
required okay okay yes you got the pack
yes I said yeah you're in he's in boys
she's in
all right here
here we're we're down in the mines you
might not like that but feel free to
come down too if you'd like you should
be able to if you hit M you can see us
on the map
um you don't have it unlocked but as
soon as you see it it'll it'll update
the map for you
so and now you can just dig that's all
I'm doing cool how do I steal your stuff
um you can go on the chest and if you'd
like you can steal my stuff but I'd
really prefer if you didn't
I'll try I'll try to build I'll try to
I'll try to build weapons and stuff for
everyone okay later I'll leave your
stuff alone yes don't don't touch my
oars please they're precious
how dare you oh bunny you can kill it
no can I have it as a whip okay
uh me and then Cali are about to mine
some more
yeah sorry for what I'm about to do to
your rock brethren
torch is down by the way um so anything
you want to sit down
um you need to the issue is you can't
put them on the wall here so uh I'd
recommend pressing Ctrl and it'll pop up
this little yellow box
when you're trying to place things and
kind of like show you where it's going
to place
um but these you can only uh you can't
place like on the walls because there is
no wall behind us it's just open for
some reason yeah okay I understand it's
gonna kill me no don't dye the slime
[Laughter]
[Music]
people you're poor thing
yeah
our place our sweet baby
do you do you have torches or do you
like need some
probably want to make some I know that
you can craft in this game correct yeah
so click the escape button and there
will be your inventory will open up but
there will be this little thing on the
side as well that has all the things you
can craft all you do is Click them as
many times for as many as you want
um I see yes super easy got it um can
you pick me up I'm scared yes okay
Calliope you feel free to do whatever
you'd like down here I'm gonna go give
it to me
got this
bar unlocked
just let me ask I can make build some
stairs
stop Hammer time let's go loadout
yeah
okay um are you in the house just
chilling no
no epic battle
use use your pickaxe to fight them
I know you're a gamer yeah you've got
this you literally play Eldon ring yeah
slowly but surely I'm getting killed by
a slime tube
we're we're all like at our weakest
stage
camera mode
uh-oh upward settings be scary baby blue
I'm on my way
okay so help
I just hear you guys go oh yeah oh
that's all I hear
okay yeah okay you're you're helpful
naturally regenerate space bars
obviously jump so oh okay yeah
come with me short stuff
was there a flat chest option I could
only get boobs you have the option for
boobs period
well look look at my character she's got
she's like kind of sad it's kind of the
clothes you picked you show off okay
come here and then uh if you hit the the
down s you can come this way
I didn't make a lot of progress I was
trying to figure out the crafting stuff
on my own that's okay no problem
yeah and then we're just I don't think I
have any wood is the thing so oh yeah if
I should participate in this I don't
know how
you do you need something I only have a
copper accident no I didn't I this this
hurts to look at oh you oh you're the
game
okay uh I mean you heard it I gave you I
gave you something
so uh well we gotta suck it up man you
know we got we got we got stuff to do
here yeah look how yeah we have to get
to hell we have to bring Calliope home
oh I want to go to hell okay yeah
exactly so sacrifices must be made
exactly I'm not happy but I just want to
go on record I'm not happy about this
okay we understand
gotta be happy about it just gotta dig
um oh I threw some wood at you by the
way so you should you should have like
awesome thanks yeah okay I'll go ahead
and see what I can do about crafting
then this is so exciting 300. ah
oh I can craft torches now nice yeah
so I also have quite a few torches but
yeah
okay
so our goal is to make a path down that
is easily accessible that won't kill you
when you go down so
um so that way everyone can easily get
to Hell there are also bosses in this
game I think I already said that but um
we shouldn't run into any hopefully
um
what kind of sword do you got
um it's a massive copper short sword
it's nice nice copper I got a strawberry
short toy
copper great yeah
um Copper's not good we're looking for
better ores that's why we are mining
that's why we're in the mines it's okay
I'll get a torch in my hot bar okay
porch torch torch oh I have one too yeah
which torches torches torches there's
some tungsten ore up there tungsten is
the equivalent to iron
um nice so I think I think the the
superiority of oars is the same in this
game as it is in Minecraft but the issue
is or not the issue the difference is uh
every time you spawn into a world uh the
oars can be different there's something
down there or uh no silver sorry
tungsten is silver
OMG there so are totally slimes down
there don't worry
they're they're blue ones so they're
they're the weakest
yeah
yeah oh it's so dark
yep okay straight down or something
um let me build a way down don't be
crazy
people you're gonna die
are you gonna fight the the zombie
yourself
I'm gonna fight him oh
what's up
all right I can help
I don't think there's still a fire
[Laughter]
on my way
I got you I believe there's no Friendly
Fire we're fine yeah yeah no Friendly
Fire
oh God's depravity was ended by the
skeleton
magic mirror whoa you made it home and
if you just wait your huffle around to
leave gradually you know come back
yay okay we made it we made some
some progress can I build any weapons
early on with the stuff that I have can
I just I need something better than what
I have so I can better defend all these
cuties
yeah I want to help too oh wait
yeah
it takes you home when you need to go
home
um why do you have random prisoners in
your house they're not prisoners so
those people willingly moved in with me
okay so those people
um
I have moved in on purpose they they
want to live here and they will help you
so you can talk to them
um and they will they will do things for
you how do I
[Music]
okay uh I don't know what kind of
pickaxe you all have but I made you each
a slightly better one than the default
uh no it's not tungsten it's just lead
so if you have tungsten
yeah I can make a Tungsten pickaxe do it
oh we have the nurse nice
how do you craft stuff um so you can
come over to these things here and there
is an anvil and then there is the this
stove and then there is a little
crafting bench but oops sorry I picked
up your tungsten pickaxe okay did you
mean together
uh
[Music]
how do I I think I threw it to you do
you have a new pickaxe in your inventory
I have legs how do I eat stuff wait left
um so yeah
just throw things I'll eat stuff uh so
click click escape and then click on the
thing you don't want and then uh
literally bring it where you want to
throw it and then just throw it and oops
I accidentally gave you my ax could I
please have that okay sorry to steal the
rabbit
where's the good one
um
you should you should have a lot of I
threw like two pickaxes at you so you
should have multiple
I do
um okay
yeah yeah
look when you look at it it'll open up
your whole
um yes thank you that was my strong lead
ax uh how many other pickaxes do you
have people one I have a zealous sled
pickaxe okay throw
you should have that here here you go
for you oh
sorry no it's okay
no well are you you just gave me okay
wait I see it okay there
conversion complete okay perfect
all right I'm gonna open it I'm gonna go
ahead
lead sword uh can I build not a lead
sword can I build it with the superior
platinum or do I just not have enough
it's probably that I don't have enough
stuff
yeah I need Platinum bot yeah I found a
little bit
cool how do you interact with these
things
um
so you just click on them uh wait no no
you don't need to do anything as long as
you're standing in front of them and you
hit Escape it'll show you the unique
options of the stuff that you can build
with what you have in your inventory
yeah yeah I claimed this room I'm gonna
go claim a room you don't you don't uh
you can build your own room you don't
need to claim one
oh really yeah you can build your own
house so all of these rooms are actually
already claimed by these little NPCs
walking around how dare they I know it's
gonna be right here
so yeah
underground bunker I'm gonna build yeah
feel free too do whatever you like
that's the fun of Terraria you can just
do whatever I'll help you oh thanks
beaves look at them flirting already
right in front of my face
I'm too lazy to build a house for myself
can I just squat in one of your rooms
okay yeah yeah we can have a house
together if you want
I don't mind
okay I'm gonna run out of rope but
okay well
um make sure when you build build your
house
um that you uh you need to give a floor
and walls and doors or else it won't be
an actual house
right yeah game won't consider the house
yeah yeah
I need to get out of this hole I'm stuck
I think oh no we're all stuck sadly
beautiful all right yeah I love you know
what the zombies are ever gonna be able
to get in here
you'd like to think that but I have bad
news for you oh no come on man really
they will they will find ways I'm just
gonna okay
if I connect my home go ahead via
underground it's not my home it's every
it's the home base
so it is everyone's home
yeah
okay
understood
I'm gonna go expand my map oh I killed a
turtle oopsie oh I killed a bunny too
oh
it don't cry people
it's okay sometimes but there's blood
all over the bunny ah piano that's
brutal
it was it was an accident people please
trust me it was totally not on purpose
are you sure about that
um you can't swim in this game so be
careful going in large bodies of water
you will uh potentially drown if you
can't get up fast enough and you just
kind of have to jump after out after you
float down to the ground
okay understood no swimming
that's fine
alrighty let's see we'll need to make
four
[Music]
make a work bench
pretty sure you just need wood for
floors there we go that wooden walls so
you yeah you just need to make walls and
then just yeah wood for the floors is
fine
okay wooden platform is okay
um no so the wooden the wooden platform
is those little platforms that you can
phase through think of it like in Super
Smash it's it's like the same as like
the plot those kinds of platforms it's
the same ones I've been using to build
stairs so they're really really useful
but not for building your house
apparently people were saying you can
use them for doors but I don't know how
to do that so I got a door no problem
okay so uh all right I'll figure out
that uh oh I'll figure out how to make a
floor yeah it should be easy
um oh you just placed wood down that's
all you do nothing special regular
assets yeah but regular ass wood
Wow Let's go okay
swag thanks Terraria you need some beep
wood
some beep wood
excuse me
thanks to translate people what what is
beep wood well you said regular beef
wood so a rainbow I I see I'm sorry
please please forgive my language
please I'm begging you
I didn't mean to the channel
[Laughter]
[Music]
I know that gotta no problem
yeah I don't care
what thank you for the wood it's kind
okay now time to sit down to the walls
some cherry blossom trees beautiful
see can I kill slimes more easily
oh that's cool yeah they they have this
kind of like uh I think later it becomes
like a fairy tale biome I don't know
what it's called oh yeah yeah
I wanna see it it's so pretty you can
find unicorns and stuff in it um
oops
a pony uh my favorite pony in My Little
Pony is Rarity
there you go
um because bibu exposed me as being an
MLP fan boy here we go here we go
yeah you like rainbow yeah Rainbow Dash
yeah oh my God we are winning
it's not often it's not often I meet My
Little Pony fans I mean I've watched
I've watched some of it I wouldn't call
myself like a hardcore fan or anything
but I'm sure they're around some people
just don't want to admit it you know
yeah yeah true
that's a good point I
I understand that but at the same time I
love it so
I don't see why they're actually
exactly there's no there's no shame in
liking My Little Pony
yeah are you sure I'm stuck all right I
found a hole I went down it and now I
can't get out please
now it's a house
uh people will probably try to move into
your house but it's still your house as
long as you want it to be
um I think there's something like 20. no
it doesn't work
20 NPCs ish 20 something NPCs so there's
quite a few
cool
ask me I can I can help you what do you
need
to feel bad I feel like an idiot no no
walls okay so
um uh let me let me come over I wish I
had the I should I wish I had a mirror
a magic mirror yeah I should just give
you mine no no it's okay I love it let
me let me let me rush back
um
but you should you should be able to
just place it normally
um what I'd recommend doing is going
near
um
why am I constantly losing one heart
what did I do
um go go near the edge of the wall
and place it from there
well I see yeah I'm starting to do it
okay good good okay then we're all good
no problem you don't need to worry about
me it's fine okay
I'm I'm back on my exploration Journey
oh Wormhole potion perfect you
do you have to craft something
yeah they do yeah
people doing her best
hey people hey there never played this
before
first time
don't worry I'm really I'm not very good
either so we can we can all make
mistakes together
okay sounds good yeah I'm gonna I'm good
at that me too one thing I'm really good
at yeah
real good at making mistakes right oh
this place is booby trapped
and I I keep getting a lot of potions
too
where have I stumbled upon
oh
found something I have
I found I found a hole that went down
and I thought it wouldn't go very far
but it did and now I'm like
uh
about two-thirds of the way that we all
dug down
oh wow yeah you got pretty deep I know
kind of kind of crazy right
wow big respect
keep it moving I'm trying I'm trying to
see where this goes if I open this door
and let the squirrel in will the
squirrel stay in the house uh yes okay
that's fine okay keep the door open let
the animals in
the animals into our home look at you go
all right it's fine
no problem biggie
it's all fun
um some NPCs actually don't like to live
the way that I'm forcing them to and
will be happier if you make them houses
in other places but frankly I don't care
what they want
I care about mine you're using them yes
so um we again there's like 20 some NPCs
and we have to build houses for all of
them to move in don't feel like you have
to do that that'll probably be a my
project
um okay to help flesh out the the world
a bit and some of them you have to find
so keep in mind if you find random
things like um I think the hair stylist
you can find them they're in they're in
a spider cave so when you find a spider
cave there's a chance that you'll find
the hair stylist
cool yeah someone sell clothes
um probably I don't remember I've never
you you can get new armor which armor
kind of functions as your clothes you
can look up there's lots of armor in
this game and there's uh lots of ways to
get it and it all depends on what kind
of class you want to be too so I'm going
Summoner route
um but Summoner is really hard off the
start so I'm probably going to be using
mostly a lot of magic weapons until we
get to a point where I can get really
good Summoner gear
um but depending on what uh you pick you
can kind of look up and there will be
like guides for like what kind of armor
is going to be best for you at what
points of the game
I know kind of kind of a lot
nice
you know what you're doing here a little
bit
um
oh run and get get in the house get back
hey bunny you're mine now
[Music]
this rabbit is now my pet
[Laughter]
you are my pet
I can't believe you guys are just
adopting adopting things yeah
yeah oh yeah here's a cute thing when it
rains
um there will be goldfish that like walk
around outside they're really cute
um I love them they're arguably one of
my favorite spawns in the game
cool that sounds sick I actually play
this piano
I'm not sure
you guys found a piano
I found one last time I played uh
yeah I just found a gargoyle statue
nice I'm scared I don't know where I am
oh no yeah
well you're so far away yeah I mean yeah
I'm a little far
but it's a natural cave system so I
didn't have to dig this far
give me more
um
uh what
more word here what what
Woody wood wood
or wood please please put down the wood
there we go
lead and water not a great combo at all
oh
I love digging through water
you're thinking well in a puddle it's my
favorite
oh oh man I think I think I recall yeah
that's scary yeah he's not drown oh I
won't don't worry
I'm a pro
I believe it
don't put don't put any faith in me it
was a lie I'm sorry please forgive me I
already said it too late
you already said it uh I'm never gonna
outlive this
I will learn to carry everyone in
Terraria
okay do your best I will get out of
water again you guys you just gotta jump
you just gotta keep moving to the other
side and just keep jumping whenever you
hit the floor but you can't you can't
jump unless you've hit the floor so
you're just kind of stuck floating
I am uh what you can do is you can
actually just build a path across it
which to be honest is what I usually do
but I figured I would not do that yet
um leave it to everybody
else so they don't just walk in and be
like why is all the water covered up
okay fair enough
oh a star fell I got a fallen star yes
yes I collect those so those if you get
five fallen stars you can combine them
and then basically once you combine them
you can eat them and they increase your
Mana
cool so yeah they're really good you you
want those as many as you can
watch this incompetence was put on
display by a zombie eh oh that's when I
died it'll it'll give you funny messages
like that when you when you die yeah
it said something funny about bibutu
oh oh
it just you know the game likes to drag
you oops
no no no no no
my living streak was ended
the same so what do you lose your money
yeah you don't lose any items
um just just yeah
okay
it would appear that I can't put up a
wall if there's already a dirt wall yes
behind it okay so how do I get rid of
the dirt ball
okay so you need a hammer do you have a
hammer
see I do not have a hammer okay you can
build one the Anvil I think so yeah oh
cool okay until no problem yeah just
come uh get get some more
build an anvil thing
let's go
I need to have my own Anvil correct ah
you could you could you don't need one
yeah I have one so we can all share it
oh it's it's all for us you know for
everyone together I I don't mind sharing
sharing is caring
Care Bear that's true
it's past memories that did not need to
be sorry
[Music]
no it turned into a long Pig
I don't even know what that means
[Music]
though how do I use it I'm sitting at it
oh you you you just open up the Escape
uh and it it'll automatically you don't
need to do anything special with it
cool it just works awesome this works
wow that's crazy thanks Terraria yeah
we can grab some ore first I have a
present for you do you mind if I put it
in your house
yeah sure come here I'm gonna put it by
your piano there's a chest ooh I also
have a present oh a chest a fire
I'm gonna put a chest for you over here
okay thank you yeah so that way you guys
both can uh have a place to maybe put
stuff if if you so choose
thank you yeah let's go
I also have my chest up here hold on a
sec
this golden chest right here is that
yours yes
yes I see so when I open it so all that
stuff is yours gotcha but you are more
than welcome to take something if you
need it
oh that's okay I just I need to figure
out how to make a I need some more or to
make a hammer and um so what kind of
word do you need just lead uh honestly
yeah go in this in this middle middle
one right here there's some lead ore you
can go ahead and take it yeah thanks
yeah thank you appreciate it okay I'll
take I'll take some it's okay
okay that should be good
time to make a hammer
Hammer Time
Can't Touch This sled hammer
thank you
okay I'm going back down time
all right oh
what's happening
oh yes pulling my hammers we will know
I'll get you a new one
all right
why isn't it breaking it's not even
breaking the wall it's not even dead
sorry
no please
I'll make you a new rabbit I will here
look look I have a brand new one for you
check this out all right here you go
right here here boo boo wait here you go
there you go
that's there that's a fake Robin guys
you will get used you'll get used to
killing the rabbits it'll happen on
accident and then you will become you
will become immune to the pain do it
yeah I it really hurt me she's like
giving your child like a stuffed animal
because you can't believe they will take
care of an actual animal
that's what I can do
oh what the was that oh I'm so
sorry I was just getting attacked by a
monster
that was so crazy
sounds about right monsters in Terraria
more likely than you think
yeah
uh feel free when the sun comes out to
explore to the left or right of the map
I'd be careful going to the left because
uh you will run into the corruption and
there will be these evil things that try
to kill you and granted those things
will be everywhere but you know maybe
you guys aren't so excited for something
like that yet
right so
um it'll probably be to the right as
well but I don't know where um you'll
run into the nice happy place first so I
think Bijou would appreciate that
you got it
are you destroying the wall to put more
you have to put wooden walls instead of
dirt
uh yep
maybe we shouldn't have an animal yet
until the house is done yeah finish the
house
oh look a cute squirrel wants to come
inside oh wait wait wait
squirrel says let me in please let me in
yeah you can come right inside my hammer
are you afraid don't be afraid
do not be afraid
no Nintendo switch I'm not gonna play
Ring fit risu oh
guys don't kill Reese too
don't accidentally hurt her though
yeah Cali sound bye hey sorry
[Music]
yeah maybe a construction site isn't the
best place for uh you know animals a pet
after that after we finish after after
correct when some sick walls have been
made what up
so it's safe in daytime
um there will still be slimes but yes it
is fairly safe they're fairly easy to
beat so you shouldn't worry too too much
about like
dying
um just be careful and you'll be fine
you need this waterline
um apparently Merchant has a net to
capture small animals
so if you talk to the merchant um I
think we have one that lives with us but
there's also occasionally like a
traveling Merchant
nice let's get a gazillion pets yes yeah
we take really good care of and don't
hurt yes
that sounds like a good plan
let's do it I'm down
I'll put some wood up there too you guys
could have like a weird animal for a pet
would what would it be like besides like
oh my God I had a friend who had a
ferret she freaking loved it ferrets are
great
yeah no
we love stinky kitties thank you kitty
cats they can't help it yeah that's it
yeah it depends though it depends on the
time
that's true
you're blocked your block yep
I have a loft also cool looking Loft
nice
like looking
Bieber is the pet rock
yes
why do you do you have a problem with a
rabbit Made of Stone come on now I feel
like you'd be into that you know
you don't know that yeah
okay Mr turtle come on inside
portal turtle
hey you seem like a nice guy come on in
dude I love tour I love Turtles
Turtles we got him I
I love when you are just going for a
walk and you like walk by and there are
just like turtles chilling on a rock
yeah
don't worry I won't hurt him okay I'm
blasting down walls
now we're just putting up wood walls
what do you think about this Mr Turtle
do you like the wooden walls that I'm
making
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh
sorry I found something interesting
Underground
I'm trying to get to it there's a bat
that's trying to get to me but I made a
path through water so that the enemy is
coming down can't cross
oh but now I have found an opening let's
go
I'm not gonna be able to nine my mind
that yet
I'm naming the turtle Carl you can't
kill Carl because Carl has a name now
all right you got it no problem Carl is
safe
harl is safe with us
if Carl gets killed it'll only be on
accident
[Laughter]
I've only had Carl for five minutes but
if anything happens to Carl murder
everyone in this room and then myself
and then myself I'd like to see you try
yeah
that is true that is true but that was
in a game that you made and set up okay
just got a point so
it still I practice for that
for that oh I I can get an idea I'm sure
you worked very hard booboo
oh Nintendo switch no ring fit now it's
not the time
are you sure you could you could ring
fit
no thank you I'd like to work on
building this house thank you very much
but watching the race to play it was
really fun yeah you thought so yeah yeah
that was a fun game maybe we could beat
it actually I'm planning on Marathon oh
hello hello are we playing Baldur's Gate
no we're playing Terraria God damn it I
thought this was the gang
it's in the game yeah yeah let's wait
for our perms foreign
[Music]
it is what it is
well you had fun though right
um yes but it was also terrifying you
hate those kinds of games I remember now
it's okay I hate them too
don't worry it was so scary
he jump scared me plastic classic girl
didn't expect anything oh no that's not
good just the the ghost
I see
I mean gouda just jump scared me by
walking past me also called normal form
wasn't her fault slam uh have fun with
Terraria
I'll see you in our collapse yes I'm
looking forward to collaborating with
you tomorrow yeah
I love her she goes yeah she's pretty
cool she's pretty well I'm excited for
balder's gang yes when are we gonna play
balls
no I know you're a real fan did you I
know that you're an actual fan of the
game oh no I'm just saying um it's
really fun
because I played a little bit of the
Early Access and I've played Divinity 2
which is similar yeah
that one's really good
they recommended it
so
maybe we'll check it out beforehand
yeah while I'm waiting for Balter skate
oh I'm waiting
how long could it be
I mean I asked I asked like a month ago
oh my God
yeah yeah I'd really like to play it but
we'll see yeah
for now we've got Terraria to hold us up
yeah yeah how are you guys liking it so
it's both of your first time yeah well
you've played for three hours but it's
your first time with is it your first
time with people or have you played with
people before yeah we played uh with Ian
I believe yeah I think I didn't know who
was in it but I think uh
and I suppose you and a few others yeah
yeah Richard Watson was in here too
yes yeah Watson likes Terraria
I found lava
is that good
um it's not bad
I you just have to be careful to not die
you know understandable
's room yeah I made myself a lot too
cool
you got your own Loft as well nice
uh I haven't run into any hearts are
they only in the the evil area chat
please give me your wisdom real quick
I'm looking for the hearts to extend
expand my uh
no hearts are random okay cool then I'll
just keep looking thank you sorry guys
all good
did you say you can move through the
wood things like Smash characters yeah
yeah so the wood things uh when you make
the oh what are they called the wood
platforms those are like the Platforms
in uh
in Smash and you can just kind of warp
through them with the down button
s
yeah they've got to be the wood platform
so
regular wood oh
sure
oh uh people are saying it doesn't need
to be wood it just needs to be the
platform type
yeah correction
okay we just don't have access to
anything but like wood platforms at the
moment yeah
that is true
Bonkers looking good though
I'm getting my ass kicked
oh it's the worm that's why oh it's
fine
all right you're going um I need you
guys to hit the escape button
and there should be a little thing
um that has like a little uh there'll be
on the bottom right
um there will be that little thing with
all your armor right you see those like
six colors there's white red green I'm
on the blue team if you click blue then
we'll all be on the same team
um yeah so then um yeah it just it helps
don't ask how I don't know
okay I got it here I'm gonna give you a
ceiling because you need a ceiling oh
thank you you're welcome
oh I got so much rope where did I get
all this rope from
a blue team for the win
Let's Go Blue
what blue
I'm more of a pink team fan but that's
okay understandable blue is good too
is not bad per se
blue is my favorite color
but I have pink eyes so I have quite the
fancy for pink too let's go pink pink
you do
yeah
[Music]
beautiful and we all got pink in our
design
yeah it's our in common color
yeah pink I do have pink you're right I
ran out um I'm building a Vine not a
Vine uh you can go up into the sky
there's not a sky island up there
um but feel free to climb up the Rope
for fun if you'd like to that sounds
cool
nice
I wanna drop more stuff off what do I
have
um I'm gonna live in the clouds
um
all right time to cover this bunker in
dirt
Oh I thought you wanted it without dirt
okay oh it's okay no it's fine it keeps
it nice and secret you know yeah yeah
yeah like a hobbit a hobbit hole Yeah
Yeah Yeah precisely
precisely how it is and maybe some grass
will grow on it and some some rabbits
where'd our turtle go
ES
I know they might they might despawn
dang it wait what happened
oh wait
what does this giant gem do what did I
just create
why did I create bee boo
what there she is my my princess
ah
a torches
and I can make furniture now too
[Music]
let's see what do I want to build
a bed would be nice but for now I'll
settle for table and chairs
I really don't think there's beds in
this game you don't you're not allowed
to sleep really no sleep I don't think
so or at least when I played I
definitely didn't
only 13 nearly damaged for a platinum
short sword that's awful
yeah that does kind of suck
Maury bunker here
I'm already all out I'm already all out
that took everything that took
everything I had
how could they
so cruel
only burn or make furniture here
well I think I'm I pretty much got the
bunker all set up so I'll come I'll come
hang out with you
yeah
yeah I'd like to go on an adventure
together okay yeah um let me finish
putting my stuff away
yeah you bet
um and then I would be happy to do that
with you
hello okay in this side can you write on
the sign and stuff I think so
okay
my law
yeah vivo's place
[Music]
to say it's hard and sand Vlog still
vlog
Builder potion increased placement speed
and range
increases defense
Ruby
topaz
um lead or I do want a gargoyle in your
house I just feel like that would suit
you somehow yeah that sounds sick I'd
gladly take that thank you okay yeah oh
it's just ah what's with your bunny
statue okay there I think it's a
gargoyle
yeah look oh they're in love it's very
sweet oh it's a little bit of a weird
relationship maybe a little strange
that's okay I've got a mining potion and
a recall proportion recall portion
teleports me home that sounds handy I've
got 12 recall potions whoa you're safe
Gill potion
swiftness
Hunter potion
danger sense uh lesser healing potion
and I can get rid of this
okay that should be good okay are we
ready to go back into the mines girls
already yeah yeah I'm so excited
all right
let's do it
all right uh the hole is down that way
yes
are you coming too
oh hold on I'm just putting fire in my
room okay okay okay
I'm ready are you ready
okay
okay let's do it Follow My Lead
here we go
oh I'm sorry I have boots so I'm way
faster I forgot
the Hermes boots yeah yeah yeah
I'm I'm a human
she's zooming that's fine then we'll
catch up yep yeah I think uh
uh you it'll it'll it'll hurt you be
wary
yeah it hurts oh it looks so cute though
how could they I know I'm sad
yeah I wish it were friendly it's so
cute domesticate them
duh
here this is a pretty
pretty well made way to go down I feel
yeah right
yes okay okay
be careful come here I'm going to show
okay so go through here
jump up and and come out this way okay I
gotcha easy enough it's like a real life
uh like spooky cave full of water yeah
what the heck oh there's something
purple oh wait I I want to see if now
that I got this if I can mine it I don't
think I can oh I can it's Demonite orbs
perfect for me yeah so that's that's you
yeah yeah it's one of the harder words
to get because you actually oh don't
pick up my coins please please oh sorry
no it's okay you can have them it's fine
no oh you can make a graveyard if you
die enough
um it'll change the biome of the area
[Laughter]
oh yeah yeah yeah so if you die enough
in one place you just it up
yeah I think you can also like literally
just like pick up and move
um all of your uh gravestones from
whenever you die and get the same
similar effect
see whoa it's okay yeah feel free to
oops I'm getting hit by a bat
um that's what that was bad
perfect I'll build a way back up so just
don't worry about getting up
um just worry about going down
okay
sure if you say so Captain there's a
jealousy down there there's jellyfish
can we kill him yes um just be careful
because obviously they they hurt be
careful careful there's somebody uh
there's like an Archer or something uh
yeah there's there's things down here
oh boy there are monsters in the mines
Barbie monsters well that's okay this
way works too yeah
um there's a tree this way are you sure
you guys don't want to explore that oh
really sounds cool see sure cool
I'm gonna get this water to flow through
here
yeah drain it out nice I love doing that
um be careful there's some zombies this
way
cool tree I'm going to drown please
don't oh no please I'm going to do I'm
about to dress jump jump
you gotta jump
gotta jump okay
um
oh there
oh there you go the steps yep here
our monsters are coming yep uh they
can't really reach you in the water so
for real but where did people go
where are you stuck
um I can't I can't jump out of this
water
um
here I'll come get you
I'll stay here yeah keep keep digging
feel free if you find a way to drain the
water
um all right you got it leave it to me
thank you keep it to me boss
try to make a an efficient way to get
the hell out of here
maybe you got it
okay
okay progress
I'm Coming For You Bieber don't die
there's this like tiny air pocket that
I'm just using to survive I'm gonna try
to kill off some of the mobs so when I
bring you this way you don't die
immediately okay
it's like it might be hard to drink
that's okay it's it's hard sometime if
there's not like a proper
proper thing yeah but that's okay yeah
you don't need to drain everything
forward okay
we'll keep moving forward and see what I
find
oh those are some that's underwater yes
you can
[Music]
okay
I keep getting stuck too
give me one sec I'm so sorry I just
promise I'm trying to come get you
the water level is getting lower though
yeah the more space that you make
basically the the lower the water level
will naturally get so yeah it's if
you're ever trapped in water it's a good
way to start getting out is just to
literally dig your way out
okay keep getting the air pocket
survive okay come this way
Okay jump up
wait I'm too short
you can build underwater
I think oh
I'm drown again no
oh what's happening what's
attacking me hey
a slime what did you die
I'll be fine don't worry okay
healing potions maybe yeah I got some
I found a way out nice brother a way to
continue nice can you place box
um here just come this way come this way
can you jump up the high on this side
no
here
we'll get you don't worry
oh
yeah you made it okay ready there's ore
here feel free to get it
it's just lead lead lead is useful get
what you can okay will do and I'll set
up some more torches around here yes
help me Digby boo we'll get out of here
dig our way out
ah what what is happening what's hurting
us oh so um that was this this stuff can
fall so there you know how like in
Minecraft the sand falls
um yeah and so does like Granite this is
kind of like Granite it it'll fall on
you so you got to be kind of careful
um but we just didn't see it this is our
fault
yeah thankfully we're still alive that's
what matters yay yup to true
okay
getting a little work done
uh what is that Pink Lizard thing
oh there's a column feel free to take it
it's yours now
I'm scared okay oh there's a bat there's
a bathroom uh we got it it's dead okay
okay there's some monsters down there
yeah we're going to have to kill them
are you ready to fight I'm ready
okay put them up put them up
yeah
I'm dying baby no
there was an attempt it's okay I died
too
what is just a skeleton uh
it's fine it's fine it's okay they were
strong they like yeah so much we we did
pretty good like getting them down
though this is a good time to uh
quick stack perfect
okay you placing things down too
oh I'm just putting stuff on my chest
real fast
oh yeah okay
I will lead you down again be honest
yeah no right I love digging
wow oh I see a beautiful blue Cavern
down there I'm gonna try and go go go go
go go go go go there's a blue bird
oh that looks dangerous I bet he's gonna
kill me actually don't die if you let me
all right I'm not gonna I'm not gonna
free him yet there's a bat and there's a
a glowing blue bird
there's no way why would he kill you you
Calliope
you'd be surprised death has a has a lot
of detractors yeah I imagine
I wonder if it's the mushroom biome I
think it might be if it's glowing in
blue
yeah
ready
all right well I won't connect the walls
yet until we're all here yeah we're
we're on our way okay cool no prob I'll
just set some torches around here sounds
good
light up light the way yeah light the
way oh there's a Sterlington I'll fight
him
careful
all right
oh that's a worm okay Tremors oh careful
all right let me see if I can find like
a healing potion or something I've got
some
um so if but you you know your health
also just regenerates over time and it's
pretty easy considered yeah
I'm pretty sure unless I'm crazy
cool but otherwise um I can I can lend
you a lesser healing potion
prob
out of here
oh we got him all right okay uh hold
still come come near me hold still yeah
okay
um how do I okay
there you go thank you yeah no problem
no is this the blue that you're talking
about yeah oh so that's just a water
it's glowing oh wait no I see it I see
it I'm crazy yeah this is a mushroom
biome oh hell yeah oh yeah
let's go
yay mushroom
of these up whoa whoa
I'm gonna make some more torches yep go
ahead
okay light the way Mori light the way
okay oh there's some sparkly stuff up
here yeah I'm gonna get it oh ready just
lead oh no oh we're dumb
we got greedy it's okay just come this
way
oh surely
it'll just drain we totally won't die
it's fine yeah it's all good
I mean it's got to stop eventually right
yeah
ready
yep
and then upward or downward doesn't
matter which way
there's a man yeah it's a little like
zombie mushroom guy
it will try to kill you okay
but there's a pulsating heart thing oh
perfect so if you get that it'll expand
your health so go go get it go get that
it's worth the fight
I've been looking for those I'm so
jealous of you people
lucky uh oh there's something in here oh
no if you got damaged it was the silt
that fell on US ah
I see
we're coming bee boo
I'm on the oh oh this might be
curtains for me
oh you good
that was crazy yeah for real fun
cool
okay wow strong scene
oh I like those little hanging things
right isn't it freaking pretty pretty
beautiful oh big mushrooms
um oh there's fish down there too yeah
are these fish mean too probably I'm
pretty sure everything is easy for what
wait there's treasure chest down here
yes if you find a treasure chest go open
it and take what's inside
the loot is yours
Okay so
maybe drain it first
there's got to be a way to bring
I think I can get back by myself I'll be
okay okay I believe in you
that's a big big oh yeah you could drain
it that way yeah we're gonna see but
maybe we should explore the lower
mushroom biome first before we try yeah
just so we don't accidentally do the
same thing and then lose a ton of stuff
that's a good point
um
because there might be just as good
stuff down here sometimes you can find I
think houses in the mushroom biome
really I see pots and stuff yeah
let me go this way there's a bunny
statue cool
someone definitely lives here
Becca the zoologist
oh
new NPC mm-hmm
bundabarm
blowing mushroom
is this worm thing chasingly
um because he wants to eat you
ow I'll just ignore him
okay
we dig down again yeah down is good
um that thing is gonna try to kill us so
I'm not gonna go near it I'm gonna go
this way yeah let's stay away from that
worm man is very persistent yeah yeah
they'll keep chasing you you gotta kill
it
because Tremors worms man oh
biggie
okay
this is such a cool area
right I freaking love the mushroom biome
so much
pretty oh biboo
fibu is not surviving there's so many
worms they're really after you huh yeah
hey there's a pulsating heart thing you
can have it yeah
yeah go down there
uh oh there's a guy
give me your helmet give me your helmet
please can I have it
I don't think I can get it I think I
have to find it organically oh
really
yeah why that's so lame I know right I'm
like let me let me steal loot from guys
with cool loot
oh you gotta be like this yeah that'd be
way cool
what a shame right
getting lots of tungsten though yeah
yeah
we are gaming
we're gaming right now we're Gathering
so much stuff for the for the new place
take your time we're just exploring
yeah orange juice
yeah yeah I mean you can you can totally
make stuff out of whatever you want
don't feel like you have to just do wood
because I just like to do wood
is cool but I feel like Stone fits me
better yeah it does fit your aesthetic
we'll find a cool Stone too as the game
goes on
yeah
um I need to take you somewhere but I
don't know where it is yet on this map
but I need to take you somewhere that I
think you'll really enjoy the aesthetic
it doesn't help let's go I mean you'll
like that too it's okay just I'll keep
healing it's fine yeah just uh hit him
yeah that's fine oh yeah welcome okay
like whack-a-mole
yeah guacamole with bats yeah
because there's so many of them
there are there is a lot of them see
there's a little snail statue
interesting take me to snatch
[Laughter]
my Lord
it's for snails yeah snail shirt yeah
I'll have to look this up later yeah
it's a meme it's a meme I'm sorry
never apologized for memes yeah I don't
apologize you know what your Mainstreet
dreams narissa you're so right how could
I how could I have forgotten the
cardinal rule
yesterday you said tomorrow
so just do it
I saw
oh
boy that looks like an evil dude
we can kill him
yeah
idiot oh my God what
a big dummy oh that's so funny
okay I guess we can flood this place it
seemed like there wasn't much loot but
there is a loot up here so if we just
dig up uh the water will just flow down
um nice okay that's a good idea
all right I'll dig up too
form another stream yes
yeah
um wait uh We're not gonna be there fast
enough
okay that's okay
I believe let's go what a legend
she's unkillable
exactly she's tough because she's a gem
looks known exactly
okay
uh
hopefully you don't drown Cali
yeah you know it's probably fun
probably
oh yeah I'm I'm in a different stream
anyway so yeah it should be fine
oh I might drown yeah
my hero oh I'm doing my best
oh no water got in this one yet but I'm
gonna try I don't think it will again
um
I'm on the way
I think I know how to make it flood the
other way yeah
all right oh there's two chests one for
each of us
I got a flare gun
nice
what's in it
I found a magic mirror
that's good loot give me the magic
mirror review
what
away
nice
oh this is my Tombstone yeah
yeah from where you died last time
oh
that's a really powerful enemy good luck
okay
you might want to use that
how do I use it
uh great question I'm actually not sure
instead erase this let's run away
slimes are less scary than that all the
monsters are here great
Mori will live no matter what I believe
um feel free to shoot yourself home I'm
gonna start walking to see if uh to the
right is the thing that I want to show
you
oh we have a we have a fox girl in our
house yeah hey the more that's where
they moved into you're just gonna have
to deal with it I'm sorry
gamers
it's still your house but she's just you
know you you can you can change where
they live later
um if you really want to
um you can like set their housing I
believe
I see she really likes animals she won't
stop talking about edibles
I think you can buy things to help it so
you don't kill Critters I think chat was
saying
ah nice so definitely she'll help you
yeah not accidentally kill your bunnies
huge
and we got really low yeah I mean I
haven't looked at how how far down we
were I think we're we're still are we
are we halfway or how close are we to
hell
uh great question I feel like because
I'm looking at the map and I'm trying to
zoom out when I zoom out though that's
just it was at the bottom like literally
the bottom and okay let me look right no
no that's not how we're probably not
even or we're probably about halfway if
if even like that's probably yeah I'll
look in one second and you clicked M to
look at the map right oh let me see
ah no we are halfway ah yep I was
looking at the small map yep only about
halfway
yeah not not to be discovered
much more to be discovered there's so
many biomes we haven't even come across
yet right you didn't see that
baby did you blow up our house
[Music]
it's all right oh I'll forgive you okay
there it's fine it's okay
it's okay just don't worry about it
yeah
this is just a small explosion man
oh I really probably should get back to
work though but this is really fun
getting together and stuff yeah we're
together thank you for playing a bit I I
do plan on making this a series so it'll
probably be on Sundays unless uh people
actually want to play have a day that
works better
um but yeah I'll probably definitely
play a bit on my own too
um yay just to like really help but yeah
feel free thank you so much for joining
it was so much fun talking to you
always fun hanging out with you guys so
I'll do my best to be helpful yes I hope
you had fun I did I had a blast you guys
keep having a good time okay okay bye
good luck who will do try not to die
Mori out bye-bye
oh my God we just collabed with Calliope
Maury
[Laughter]
so cool
I'm trying to expand my map
okay it's not do I just use the light
crystals
um yes yes yes you consume them they're
consumables and they will increase your
hearts
um your goal is to get to 200 for now
so
uh Health oh okay
and just uh I think if you click on it
you can probably oh I died oh no so I
have 140 health for example oh okay um
if you hover over your hearts you can
see how many
so yeah I also have 140. yeah yeah
comparably close
okay oh I have glow sticks so it'll work
when it's in water
you get those from the jellyfish
I think
don't quote me on that
um also if you pick up the fallen stars
it's kind of a similar thing so those
will increase your Mana but the thing is
you need to actually craft them together
um I think you need five
but don't don't quote me I don't know
anything
so if you get five fallen stars craft
them together and then eat it
do they just fall from the sky Yeah so
basically when you run around at night
they'll disappear in the morning not
from your inventory if you've picked
them up but they'll disappear from the
ground in the morning
um
so it's it's crucial sometimes to go out
during the night time even though it's
scary
but where are all these zombies coming
from Leave Me Alone I'm trying to get
places
so yeah if you just run around at night
you're bound to run into one it's
literally just like a star
are you just going left I'm going right
you can go whatever way you want if
you'd like to if you'd like to come
right uh there's a lot of monsters but
you can okay I have a gun
amazing that is perfect actually thank
you bring the gun
Oops why can't I seem to time my jump
correctly
um
nice okay
so how are you today Bieber I got to
watch a bit of your karaoke but I had to
leave because my screen was starting I'm
sorry but I had so much fun I was so
glad I got to be there for when you
saying yeah
for you I know you did such a good job
too noises I'm getting attacked do your
best
I'm sorry I would help you if I was
closer
but you'll either be dead or out of the
situation by the time I get there
there's so many bad things yeah
oh oh I spy them
once morning comes most of them will
stop spawning and it'll be pretty safe
oh you poor thing
[Music]
loodle give me the chest my gun doesn't
do that much damage just sets things on
fire yeah sometimes you kind of gotta um
adjust it'll take time
um and you can get better weapons as the
game continues
so uh just have faith in that
as it goes on you will get you'll get
better better ones
yeah I I'm glad that you came by for
icing yeah no I was so scared I was
gonna miss it I was like no please I
hope she sings it before I have to go
so I was very uh pleased as a peach
but now I thought it's kind of itchy
after singing so much I bet yeah it kind
of ends up causing a bit of a throat
pain yeah
please leave me be I don't even have my
weapon out oh my God
frozen zombie I see oh no it's okay well
I could I'm going right still yeah
that's keep going keep it up
um only not even halfway
[Laughter]
yeah they're all saying you're saying so
well they all agree yeah I'm glad I'm
glad
my amazing Bieber not as good as narissa
oh shut up song stress
we don't we don't need to do any of that
here it's just the two of us
but if it was just a tool because I
would say the same thing
I'm sure you would
but still
he
people really does have that Riz
she's so busy I'm trying everyone's so
good at it you're really good at it too
don't underestimate yourself what are
all these fiery things everywhere oh
those are the flares that I shot oh I
see him
I tried to make a path over the water so
it was harder to drown I hope you found
that helpful
yeah
cherry blossom yeah yeah well I mean I
don't know if they're actually cherry
blossoms but I'm going to continue to
act as though they are because they look
like them
so therefore they are right that's how
it works
[Music]
oh good I think it is morning time so
it's just slimes now yay
oh
oh no I don't want to go down I
don't want to go down the hole not again
and I'm so glad I hate fighting zombies
yeah
they're cumbersome
and annoying
[Music]
I can't believe I can't believe you made
the thing that you made
oh you showed Kelly yeah talk about it
tell me about it I wasn't able to watch
your stream
I turned Sans undertale into Mori
Calliope and then killed her in front of
her
she liked that yeah yeah I hope so now
that I think about it I wonder I hope
she's not mad that I killed her in front
of her oh I know I'm sure she's not yeah
that seems like something she wouldn't
mind too much
so I'm sure you're all good
yeah I had made that mod for uh when I
auditioned
and I got in so yeah good thing I guess
a good mod killing Calliope Mori as Sans
undertale yeah that's so cool that you
did that
I'm jealous I wish I could make uh mods
and stuff like that
well I can teach you oh yeah one day and
then you can teach me singing stuff
right um I want to sing better I don't
know if I'm qualified to teach but I can
try let me hear you qualified okay so I
mean being a teacher and being good at
something are completely different
things right oh that's true so uh you
know the just because I'm good at
singing doesn't necessarily mean I'm
going to be able to say it I have the
same issue with my sister actually she's
she's a better singer than I am because
her Horn's not broken you know and um so
she's fantastic and every time I ask her
for advice she gives me the shittiest
advice she's like um just do it and I'm
like um I can't idiot
oh of course it runs in the family that
is indeed how it works uh we're we're
running all the way to the ocean
so shall we dig through the mountain I
guess so
for fun
yeah
might as well make a path to the other
side the snow won't fall on us right um
I don't think so because it's like icy
snow
you know yeah
so I think we'll be fine
now we just got a full mocha and shiori
I know oh there's a big thing um we can
go down there later uh let me go kill
these things will you keep digging
oh don't touch my people
attack me
oh sorry I got confused everything's
fine everything's fine don't worry
so how was your day oh it's pretty good
um I Was preparing for my collaboration
tomorrow with kiwawa Senpai I did you
guys decide what you're gonna do or is
that yeah yeah no it's it's been decided
we're doing uh it's already announced so
we're doing a compatibility test you see
a lot of people have been thinking that
uh we get along maybe a little bit too
well so um obviously I mean that's one
of the reasons I like Kiara is because
when I watched her streams uh pre-debut
I was like oh my gosh she's just like me
she's just like me for real you know
so I I guess it makes sense that we are
similar minded people but I'm sure there
are some things we don't agree on but so
we're going to be uh going through and
uh talking about things that we like and
seeing how we both mutually feel about
them if we have any separate interests
if we have things that maybe the other
likes that the other doesn't
um so I'm pretty I'm pretty pumped
that sounds so cute oh oh do your best
oh
yeah I make I make it a path
I guess you could just dig through it
too
just adding off flares
you're not gonna be able to get up that
um it'll be helpful for later okay
here's what I wanted to show Mori
um
you can get these blocks here
um don't talk to the guy okay don't do
anything over here got it oh there's a
guy there's this will start a boss fight
and we are not prepared for it but that
guy there is
ignore him okay we're just gonna walk
past and keep going and we're gonna go
under the guy no no no we can't
um there's a Temple here and we can't
Farm it I don't know if we can Farm up
but once we get inside of it we can oh
yeah he only activates at night so I
guess we're fine
okay oh thank goodness I forgot about
that
um but we will have to fight this boss
eventually
but um you can also then after you fight
the boss or maybe we can just right now
uh you can go in here and um don't go
down
don't maybe not now
I don't think we're um ready give me one
sec to build
um so I can make some wood platforms I
don't know what happened all mine I
could have sworn I had more
but now they're all gone
and I don't know how that happened so
let me just um I'll make us a nice
little path up
from Little stairs
or that sound
wow
same here I'll make some stairs upward
thank you
okay
oh and now uh be careful because there
is fall damage
oops
just don't die okay
yeah we're good we're good
see we're doing it
yeah Adventure
adventure for sure
and we're coming up to another pretty
biome oh I like the flowers can I take
them with me oh we're coming to a bad
biome get ready what's that mean
um you'll see get ready uh get your
sword ready
my sword is not great though that's okay
anything is fine just you need something
for these guys and for these these will
hurt you as you run through them
so this is the corruption biboo this is
the main thing that we just keep running
oh no go on without me
it's fine I'll get up I'll get out no
okay just get out
okay
ah
just ignore him okay just uh attack them
if you can
please
I can't oh okay just keep running right
okay
okay it's okay just keep running me boo
ignore them as much as you can
okay I am in a hole
oh no and I am safe inside the hole so
are you sure about it I'll just wait
here for you yeah
wait I guess some before I run I should
drop my stuff off
[Music]
um you just uh I don't know you press
you press the button
and the places it automatically
that's all I know that's all I can help
you with I'm sorry
oh yeah I could I couldn't do I have a
wonderful potion I could have sworn I
did but I might have put it down this
this stuff is very tough I'm trying to
like mine through it
um yeah don't do that it it won't work
um for now
eh where's my Wormhole potion
did I oh
good work biboo
they're saying there are beds I don't
believe you I've never seen a bed
I've never ever seen a bed ever in my
life
I'm gonna go through mori's chat she
doesn't have anything else
you're pretty empty too
that's because I'm pouring it I see
okay uh did you want Wormhole potion
because I have oh I have one too I I
just pulled one out it's just um since
we're on the same team if one of us dies
we can actually just teleport to each
other
um so that way if someone needs urgent
help you can be there quick
so yeah
I love Terraria man
this game is so much fun yeah 2D
Minecraft ish yeah it's it's similar to
Minecraft but it's more story oriented
so yeah lots lots more Adventure type
stuff
versus
um Minecraft which I feel like is more
loosey-goosey you know yeah
why not stairs where did that whatever
doesn't matter
I really want to make a graveyard I just
feel like that would be so funny
well all of them have to be in the same
place so it's like if you die a lot in
the same place it becomes a graveyard
you know but then you can inorganically
make one you can make one by force
because that's fun too
sword yeah when when am I gonna find
Abigail I've I've been don't get me
wrong guys I've been looking out for
because she's my first summon that I can
get but I haven't
um have you ever played Don't Starve
Together or just don't starve
[Music]
um okay so yeah yeah yeah there's
there's this character who has a flower
and it's got her dead sister in it and
the sister's name is Abigail
um oh
I think I played as her yeah yeah and um
in this game they must have done some
sort of collaboration or they must I
don't remember how they're connected but
um you can get Abigail's flower
and summon Abigail
oh yeah so it's kind of fun how do you
like choose a class do you just
um it's just stuff it's just stuff as
you go
um but you you can look it up if you're
interested because admittedly I'm not
100 the best at it
um
sadly
there was a collab people are saying I
see
hold on
I can't believe you we haven't beaten
anything yet
be nice to us ah okay I trapped a bunny
inside my house okay I'm coming to you
now okay
I'm just running as fast as I can oh my
coins yummy yummy in my tummy
um Good Luck when you uh get over to
this biome oh it's it's getting dark
yeah uh I must quickly quickly
it might be just warm to you if you have
a wormhole potion yes you can just click
where I am on the map and you can warp
to me
not only where are you
far there you go okay
um
must protect biboo okay
[Music]
okay keep running
so there's a chance when we kill Eater
of souls for them to uh oh ah
it's okay I'll Wormhole to you I'll
Wormhole to you okay keep running keep
running yes stay alive
yep you got this I believe in you okay
where's my Wormhole potion
um I think uh you might want to do it
quick I'm getting chased okay
come here I'll take you you'll never
take me alive
okay onward
here to save you another one
keep running just keep running ignore
them
okay okay I'm running
let's run yeah just go I'm running as
fast as I can okay
we're right at the we're at the beach
okay do you have another Wormhole potion
yeah yeah okay
perfect do you want some seashells yeah
yeah oh
now you can pick up some stuff here
and I'm just gonna
um
so here's one thing about this area Okay
uh this cursed area here if you pick up
any blocks from it even though I know
they're pretty do not put them anywhere
else because the issue with this is it
spreads okay
so if it's connected to anything else it
will spread
which is ugly and sucks and that's one
of the issues with the corruption there
will be a way that we can kind of Mega
clear it kind of fast but um it's best
to kind of try and get it under control
and easy mode in my opinion
um or not in Easy Mode but before you go
to Hard Mode rather
so can technically the whole world get
corrupted yeah
pretty sure
oh it doesn't expand until hard mode so
I think as long as it's not touching
anything people
come to me
come down the hole I'm making
okay keep digging
down yep
it doesn't have to be straight down but
yeah I'm just down
come on don't be shy
don't be shy
there's got to be a better solution to
this than what I'm doing right now
I'll watch out watch out I know I see it
don't worry
just keep digging
okay
onward
we ride
okay
um where is my where's my dirt
I've gotta have dirt I've been mining
dirt all day
there
my cheat code
so sometimes when you go in the Sandy
area why am I not digging
um hello uh you can actually find little
caves but they're kind of hard to get
through digging
um but for now we can just explore like
this
oh
um
nice nice
when we made it to the beach I think
there will be a guy floating on the
water during the day I don't know if
he's on a specific side or what
but yeah
you how much longer do you want to play
for people
um
I might want to eat dinner sometime
eventually
um we let me know because we can stop
whenever you'd like because I'm good to
end stream whenever I've been I've been
going for a long time so if you want to
eat don't let me keep you either
but I really enjoyed playing with you
I'm having so much fun I know right it's
such a funny food I don't need food yes
you do
I'm worried about your health we gotta
look out for each other
because if you're not eating then I
won't eat either
um when you were talking with sure and
phasma like how like it was hard for you
to eat and stuff yeah it's it's
stressful right like it's good stress
but it's still stress nonetheless yeah
but it uh makes it a little
difficult
look at us there's two guys yeah
um if we go to the other side I think
there's uh I mean left there's a jungle
biome I believe
how do you tell I already went there a
little bit I just didn't uh expand super
far
into the you know Abyss because uh
I'm a scaredy cat this is what it is
chat are you guys having a good time
with me and bibu our unexpected
collaboration wow
hi jailbirds
it's nice to see you guys I hope you
haven't been feeling neglected because
I'm hanging out with bibu but surely
you're enjoying getting a peek in on our
cute interactions
you can give them attention no I want to
give you attention you're mine bee boo
I've been I've been waiting to hang out
with you again because we I've been
meaning to get together to plan another
collaboration with you yeah anyways but
I just want to do zatsu
you know because I just want to get to
talk uh with you uh more casually
um but I just I'm sure people would like
to know yeah we've we've been talking
about a lot of a lot of I feel bad
because I've been like I've been
exposing nerissa too much I gotta hmm
calm down on exposing it's okay I asked
for like oh juicy confession I was like
this is perfect you know it was perfect
I can't I can't even say you're wrong
because you're just eventually made a
correct statement
oh
I had to I had to explain myself on my
stream people it was so bad
why no I'm Josh I mean I I was just
talking about it because of people were
like what why
what's wrong with you narissa
leave like sometimes things are just
girl things that like yeah you know I
don't I didn't really care that much
yeah I was like oh okay whatever because
it's like
I don't I would say normal but it's like
a girl thing like yeah girls ask their
friends sometimes and see people gets me
I was explaining uh because they they
were they asked what about flomoku and
chiori then
so I was explaining to them I was like
um
me and Booboo have a special bond
because we we got along right from the
get-go at first I think we we became
close very fast is what I mean well I
think it's because like I have I don't
know
[Music]
but you know for some for some people
um it's a little bit more embarrassing
and that's totally fine yeah
depends on the person
and and us sharing a bed too you brought
that oh yeah and then we we refuse to
elaborate more
but we we had fun
yeah we did
it was a very good time I like hanging
out I want to hang out with you yeah I
miss
Ed right oh no are we trapped
okay when I said she was you're such a
mom to me you are such a mom because
like
there were times where I'm like I was
feeling sick at some point
um of the of the trip and I was like
oh God I really hope no one notices that
I'm feeling bad but narissa noticed I
was like dang it she noticed I can't
drink this water are you okay
I gotta make sure my my baby girl is
healthy
don't drain the water please don't drain
the water
are we going somewhere specifically
going down okay oh careful there's water
right over there
we're just we're just having fun until
we die eventually until we die
all right how about this if we die I'll
go get food okay sounds good
next time we both die we're ending the
game
for now
people I want to go out and eat more
with you I was sad we didn't get to eat
my favorite food while we were together
I know I was too I was like I didn't get
to cook for biboo
and I was gonna let you cook even though
I like doing the kbbq stuff I was gonna
yeah she like she seems to like it so
much I will let her I do
well next time
because there will for sure be a next
time
you ever done a Yakiniku
oh
it's kind of the same thing right yeah
yeah it's very very similar
wait it's just like the Japanese version
or something uh yeah so but usually
Korean barbecue is marinated in a lot of
stuff not to say that Yakiniku never is
but um
the cuts of meat I feel like are pretty
pretty different yeah then the meat is
prepared different and usually the
grills I feel like at least in my
experience with K barbecue is pretty
different
um here we're gonna go this way if
you're okay with that
I I like yucky like like the Japanese
style Japanese barbecue I've had it
before but I really loved the Korean
beef brisket like this
is so good so I'm like
when I go to barbecue I have to have
that and and pork belly too girl you're
making me hungry I'm not I'm not
supposed to eat anymore today and you're
making me really hungry
what's over here
no
more yeah you like to eat at the end of
the day yeah another day oh sorry sorry
sorry it's sand it's sand I'm sorry
oh I had I had
but
the candy today did I count I suppose
um are you okay are you no I'm I'm
poisoned but don't worry about it um
here okay good here come on downward we
go down there's a slime that's okay it's
only a yellow slime look there's a house
oh my God this is all Platinum oh holy
I need it I need it all I need it all
for my armor
uh that looks like a trap I'm gonna
ignore that for now it looks like it'll
explode things and kill me
what's in the chest before you loot it
all
right
yes yes yes leave it leave it there for
me I'll be right in there thank you
uh you can take the chandelier too and
you can take the chest if you'd like oh
so that way you have a little gold chest
how do I take the I hit it with your uh
pitch work it's not a Pitch Perfect you
know what I mean
um okay don't move further than where I
am
in interest of not dying
okay
follow behind me
I can't see anything can you hold a
torch well you walk behind me
thank you
so make sure we don't fall into this
water and die
and then and then ask me again okay what
what's what shiny thing oh there's like
a sparkly thing right next to the
is that a box
um up here I'm pretty sure there's like
a bomb thing oh it's a ruby okay I'll
get it get it
Ruby's I mean any gem is good good gems
you're a good gem
you're a good bird
thank you
mom I was telling them you're nerfed
because you
don't have you have don't have part of
your horn
it's true
which means I'm technically stronger
than you
yeah I suppose
if you want to be we could we could say
that oh careful bats
Into The Fray okay
oh careful
uh kill him
don't be scared a lot of these bosses
are pretty weak
as long as you just slash them there's
more glowy down yeah yeah but there's a
house up here
oh
house first and then we can go to the
glowy bin
oh there's a worm too so get your guns
ready
oh
please
just want to loot this chest ah I don't
know
please I need this I don't need anything
else in here
I don't know what any of these wait I do
need this
what'd you get
loud in a bottle
feel free to take anything else from
there that you'd like obviously
you can um oh
paint yeah you can take the painting you
can place it on the wall you can take
more chandeliers
hold on
my inventory I know mine's full
well this is also marked on our map so
we can always come back here another
time
it's not like it'll go away or you can
just look for something because you
probably have something like a flower in
your inventory that you really don't
need
got him nice
oh
yeah pretty
wait is this where is this where is this
where the thing is that pool that pool
guys chat chat chat is that pool here
it's cool
is is am I close to the Shimmer oh not
not the Shimmer okay thank you
oh I see another one I'm going towards
it okay you'll go get it yeah thank you
you're you're defending me so you you
need more help
foreign
oh no I don't have room for it do I
give me
okay
nice oh gee
this is going this is going very well
okay we found a whole new biome oh yeah
oh
I'm gonna go this way
feel free to keep exploring wherever
you'd like um don't feel like you have
to follow me but I feel like I see
another area with rooms and stuff okay I
wanna stay with you okay but I need help
getting help um you can just build up
just like in Minecraft uh with any
random so if you have like dirt or like
Stone
okay
[Music]
I have lots of platinum more thank God
and then and then in the future for
people who fall down there you're making
paths for them too
oh there's a thing over there yep that's
where we're going
oh
[Music]
increase in night vision what'd you get
uh there's a night owl potion here you
can look
um recall potion flaming arrow Dynamite
so get that wild cloud in a bottle or um
uh get the cloud in a bottle
um and then you put that in your uh in
your like wait there's a guy coming I
got him
um put it it'll it'll help you jump
further
oh so you gotta equip it
um
yeah how do you equip something um okay
so when when you're in that mode you see
how on the right there's that little
area if you hover over stuff it'll say
equipment and not in that little like
green one in one you can set stuff in
it's gonna go in accessory
okay so did you put it there you see
that little cloud
yep and now you now you can jump higher
cool
wow getting decked out yeah exactly this
is this is why you have to explore
what do I not need of this or or of the
stuff that I have
and probably get rid of a mud block I
want the painting oh you took the
painting that's fine too
I can't see anything I don't know where
I am I'll be your light there you go
thank you
okay
I need the demon the demon Stone
oh that's pretty yeah right
it is uh because I have the Platinum
thing I can I can do it
otherwise I wouldn't be able to okay we
can go back on the other if you want to
explore the other biome a bit more that
we were just founding found over here
okay
[Music]
I'm so glad we have the cloud in a
bottle oh it's gonna make getting around
so much easier
not perfect oh you found it you found
two I found one earlier
they'll move forward
oh wait final more
need that
oh careful
come on just gonna cut through the
mountain so we can just get through it
instead of you know so just uh be
careful
there's one more line of it
and then yeah just cut through
and the bgm of this game how do you like
it it's really good right I like it yeah
I recognize someone like oh so that's
where that song is from oh
oh we're gonna die we're gonna
die I'm gonna die
no ah okay
I'm gonna get revenge for you one second
good luck
[Laughter]
where are my bombs
uh I'm counting on you
I saw them oh yeah die
oh yeah did you get them
oh there's another one oh hold on
you're best
is
do do
[Music]
yeah
so cute
I've managed to escape yes okay keep
doing what you do best Bieber okay
it's gonna continue to build my rope up
into the sky
because I have a problem
oh are you just
and then just you know so um there are
sky islands and you want to find them
and I haven't found any yet and I
probably won't for a while which is fine
um
but the thing is once you find them
obviously they're really helpful because
you can get certain things from them but
there's also like enemies and stuff
okay
so that's there
I don't think I can
why don't I have any dirt
am I crazy
but yeah you can find a lot of things up
in the skies that are kind of like loot
that you can only get from there
um it's really really helpful but then
it also helps finish off your map too
which is a big plus
um
so it's a it's kind of a win-win
situation you know what I mean
I don't have any dirt
I totally should have so much dirt I I
have some if you want mine I just I want
dirt in general because I wanna
um I'm gonna build a I'm gonna attempt
to build a sky Bridge
here ticket
I threw it outside your door thank you
um
oh I found mine as well
thank you Vivo uh do you want to climb
up and start into the sky you you won't
find anything there's nothing up here
but if you come up here
hold on let me oh my God
yeah go ahead
whatever makes you happy people
Sky Bridge time
vegan people won't eat today they said
laughs people please they want you to go
eat I'll eat after oh I said I get it
they just want to get rid of me yeah no
they want me to go too because I said
I'd end stream I can't believe they want
us both to leave how rude could they be
okay I found a sky island numro okay I I
always want to go it up
hi
please if there's loot don't take it I
want it it's my treasure
go go
so uh use your road to the the yeah yeah
oh I see
um
things can spawn up here
okay let me finish my bridge
attemptively
but it's so funny to watch the zombies
fall off the edge
yeah
um you can mine the cloud and you can
build with it
um
any houses on here any houses on
this island I don't see anything so far
I don't either
Flame
oh that's cool oh Harpy Harpy Harpy
Harpy oh is that bad yep they don't like
you they're like stay away from the Sky
Island Zoo human things ruin everything
they hit hard too
ah
[Music]
so if you jump here's a fun thing you
will die but you'll open up the map
[Music]
I didn't die huh where the hell did you
fall
I double jumped before I landed I'm so
over you I can't believe you I'm so mad
you're too good people
the game is like we won't let her die
she's too cute
okay now I guess I ought to go the other
way until I come across an island
[Music]
oh
I'll be your light yeah you might want
to kill the things in back of us too oh
okay
foreign
asses right off this bridge if we give
them the opportunity
no dying people we made it this far
okay okay got them all nice
um
okay
onward
what are you doing
flares like hurt them
they set them on fire
that sounds like it hurts them that's
nice
come on Never Take Me Alive
oh
okay nice
wow they just keep coming
yeah they'll just keep coming forever
why don't you just why don't we just
break a block so they just can't
um because they'll just keep spawning
as long as it's out of and that issue
then becomes when we are traveling back
yeah then when we're traveling back
along the way
um it'll be harder and we might
accidentally fall
so if we're gonna make a sky Bridge it's
best to just make
oh you jumped too early I didn't mean to
jump
people I suck
you're so good at this game and then I'm
like I'm bad like what is this this
isn't fair
apparently people are saying it might be
a Blood Moon but I don't think it is the
moon is just pink
it is very pink oh I got it I see a star
I want it get it get it get it get it I
got it I got it
proud of you oh
why can't I come up
oh
did you fall again nope
I'm just uh are you're about to die
ma'am I know uh
little lady
oh you're going down oh
it fell on me it happened I was on the
rope and then it fell on my head
oh no I'm sorry but you did so good so
if you want again what you can do with
the Stars if you go to the place where
you can build if you have five you can
combine them and then you can eat it to
get uh Mana
um more more Mana so if you want you can
do that
um it's really helpful especially when
you start getting like or like finding
magic weapons
oh that's just you I thought that
was a weird zombie just like
jumping towards me I was terrified
people
scared me
it's just me
uh
oh
sorry building a sky bridge is not easy
it's actually very hard
after you kill them you continue my work
Bijou okay I I gave you all my dirt
though yeah do you have anything else
you can use Stone it doesn't have to be
dirt
y
I know it's awful
we could just call it there too we both
died so technically we're going against
what we said we do when we die I'll
remember
hey yo
I see I see him well if you don't
remember I don't either
[Music]
you have so many flares here it is
comical
it's good damage it just like slowly
Burns
it's true it's very good damage I like
it it's smart I I never thought of it
yeah maybe maybe save them
okay here um
there
now you have some
uh let me go kill these zombies
don't don't come after my girl my bee
boo I will protect her with my life
I will die oh no don't die
it's okay my health is like full I would
die for you
is what I meant to say
so how do you know this is gonna take us
somewhere is it like the correct
elevation
um loud island or something yeah they
can be slightly different but the chance
uh we have a pretty high chance of us
seeing it from here and eat either way
like
um it gives us a better level to like
build from
so that way in the future
it's like instead of having to build all
the way up we can just kind of run
across and then like either jump down
um later uh or otherwise where's my
sword why am I having such a hard time
with this
ah did you fall oh no
hey opened up the map did you see any uh
Sky Islands no but there's a harpy
so I feel like we've got to be nearby
one sometimes that's not the case but
theoretically they can be higher up but
um it's easier to build like with vines
and stuff from here than it is to like
all the way from the ground
so it's fine
please no sir Harpy please I'm sorry
I'm a bird too I get it
chicken
yeah usually not all the time but when
you see uh those Harpy guys you know you
might be close to one
yeah see what's that what's that so I
presume there's a sky island potentially
upwards that we can't see from where we
are which is fine
how they hurt they do hurt oh
no oh
this is
[Music]
well then that's probably a good
stopping point since people died
thank you for playing with me bee boo I
didn't know okay I will I'll disappear
so you can say bye-bye okay I love you
I hope you'll play with me again next
yeah
I'll hit you up
bye-bye
oh that was so much fun did you guys
enjoy watching me play Terraria
I just I just want to go this way I just
want to go this way there's probably
nothing there's probably nothing I'm
gonna be able to see but I just wanna I
just wanna I just wanna you know
you can't tell me not to
legally you cannot stop me
plus I get gold
I figured it out figured it out so we
will definitely be doing more Terraria
as I've already said quite a few times I
definitely want to try to coerce
um
uh a lot of people to play with me
if I can make it happen I'd be very
happy
I I like I like Terraria a lot I think
it's fun I think it's a really nice
group game too
so I'm hoping
in the future that I can make it happen
what are what's going on here
what's that what's all this is it
cheating and telling me where the sky
islands are hello
well in our first Terraria stream
we were joined by Calliope Mori and
Bijou and we found one sky island
started building a sky Bridge built a
base where Bijou and uh Calliope also
built their own house and we started our
descent to hell where we found a
mushroom biome and made it about halfway
down still a long ways to go still a lot
more that we can do and find and lots to
explore but yeah for a little bit too
but she didn't play with us but yeah we
got to hear Kiana's voice which was very
very nice
so we're all
we're not quite caught up or anything
like that
um we've still got a lot to go but we
made we made a lot of really good
progress I think
what do you guys think do you agree
disagree
as a I mentioned it's kind of kind of
like my first time in in some ways
playing uh
and like kind of taking control I guess
while playing Terraria
I'm having a good time
so
uh for for a first time alone and with
uh two not none pretty pretty close to
First Time Players pretty much uh this
is pretty good oh but oh my God it's
been four hours
let me quick
um
save and close the game
uh settings save and exit exit wow
we did that we did that yeah this stream
was so much fun I'm glad you guys had
fun too because I had a lot of fun
uh effort for starting
that was a really good time
so yeah we we made a house we're
collecting heart crystals but I still
got a ways to go to 200 a HP
monocrystals I found a few but I need to
get that as high as it'll let me and I
want to find all the sky islands and
loot everything
uh
so
we'll keep doing our best we'll keep
playing more I don't know if anyone is
streaming but before we end uh let me
see if there's anyone who's up who we
can raid
is playing Hollow cure
shall we go see mumei give me give me a
minute to send it up
we we can be Moomin
you can moom too moomers
okay bay is also they're both doing
Early Access oh that's hard okay we'll
do movement because we said it first
sorry Bay senpai
sorry Bay time to move everyone so uh
tomorrow will be my first collab with
Kiara Senpai
um and then there's uh still a fun week
ahead I'll also have my first club with
Bay Senpai on Wednesday and then all of
Advent mine is shiori since she's gone
we'll be playing Apex together probably
fuaba will be the one playing this time
instead of the usual Mok local gamer
so please please look forward to it
um also lots of hollow cure this week
another spooky Saturday and our first
unarchived karaoke so I hope you'll all
look forward to it and in the meantime
thank you so much for joining me
Darlings and I'll look forward to seeing
you all next time goodbye for now
foreign
[Music]