[Music]
Eh
nice
def
n
el n
[Music]
masu
b 4
[Music]
iiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiii
th
tue
n
[Music] n [
Music]
masu
[Music]
panacea
ere
room 3 episode is 6 minutes
dancer popo previous 2 wifi espn coin ty
chime icu jic yo ahawaa
guuu demeure aqua nuka carmin today
please US space spain ran big booing patty
finger virus  These birds on Joy, martial arts spa monk-like
plate armor only
[music]
robbem sports pie t advice
Ai Mei a little work fish, the one you chose Packer
soraad
aaaaaaaaaaaa
er Charles arukitai toilet liquid Beijing michouekipo
There's a stone standing on the rice.
We love a san.
Modulo Sweets Day is Mrs. False Illness Book
Office Type Knitted Inalley
ender ender ender Huawei besar ah
Tomizawa Iu Tsukusan Beauty Department is Western
a Ibira 4 pieces Ie
Minamioi Dokuryu First Look Wonderful Yes Yes
Current Produce 1000 yen  How many coins are there at the counter? It's good to reach the event participants.
A 4 stepmother is available. Pins Warda Dion seems to have entered the rap voice.
Gyaaaaa scary Ernie this star is
this Chal's
nitr fb half's main caster
Tiller power selection quiz Ichishi Hospital 4 pin phone  meets day loop
position in the boy nope
meme
heoi ah badge ya iruzuregende te bridal bus this in future
hooked
andere stream ah
support our hospital ah ah culling deren 1 d render spring breeze tour
way sound just now  Hello f 4
I'm in front of you in the afternoon
End stopper and by  After the defeat, s Haneeeeeeeeee
#Tapun Koe Ellie 1 Papa
Seated technique light and dark even in the sun Ikar
1 away and Marine Cup first time stamping on the back interview
to me soccer poyo
[music]
noar barbora nebu sro osterman irex moose
Samuta
Ibosu Speedy espana
What is the convenience of the line
nu do the roastery?
Surfer nearer n with baby pain 5 en do do
Disiveween bag owner byway
[music]
Don't cry because it's hard to winston pin,
come on  Worth Wise Mini Bar Champ Blythe 3 base nonde
nof Pressure Beijing is ahhh
Umm 4 oxygen almost tan
Space Lapis and I met up Seyoedaaaa
Okay Kyustic fan book
Ah 1 bottle koso
This program is  This video is brought to you by the sponsors listed below.
[Music]
2 san  Aaaa
# ran darman door
ko parfait booty interview
avatar look amazing web go for it keio
[music]
aname
me
[music]
kakeroma is non-bar 2 hood tarp a can only see
ad spain winvale special episode 4 part  Tea is also
good
Zaifura-ku Shinhara washer do s admission
Open Zaal car voodoo in f chan feeding
main dou wife South Raiders tips book s Well, that's uns
over sea view Espas party by Ah Nassic
A
minute  This is a special interview talk show for English-speaking people.
The purpose
is to let people overseas know more about Japanese celebrities, while also
providing a brief introduction to them.
But
today, as you can see, it's different. A building 1 day i herb ace place
aev in to surf + meer please user occurrence nas a
Turf owner infant and yappayo winter wing
about this program booby prize winner ws esrb
sweets book spire woo sas oms day
diffuser yarn and store
4 rice option bath with pone king species good jen
gaff example ai guy right
tr 2 what is that lit  Misawa-san
ana redtop insider in sin 4
arm ajon and system ads big and small street posthumous work shoulder
9 good child put fire sea water sleep skin room old corner
Boonkam election day to dye 9 shoulder de poche some very very happy line
pipe voodoo bister  Rosso no chance blinker with day jaw
di ke earth ka Gesner
tone brass 2 sensor Tomizawa-san,
I'd like you to introduce yourself
please I'm looking forward to it I'm looking forward to it
Well then, I'll introduce myself Web version Money Miss Yusuke  Tomizawa
Hon Bandai Namco Al-Serve
Terrorism The Lies Brand New Title of Truth Opus
Franchise
Resin Stand English  Please use wear for
stream
go Japanese no I'm not saying that thank you very much I'm
glad to meet you I'm going to join you I'm going to have a tour of the island other than English I was surprised I didn't
know at all that time  So when I went to America, I
spoke at events like E3 and Anime Expo, and I studied English really hard,
but I haven't been there at all, so it's been a while since I've spoken English, but
to what extent?  Wow, I think it's amazing, but I think I can go, but it's a sunny day in Japan today,
so I hope you're okay. By the way, I
think it would be better if you explained the visa to everyone, Sanma.
Based on the work, which producer is the color?
Yes, that's right. Well, the
three were about 5 or 6 years ago.
Anon. After the release of the previous work, Beth, Berseria, I joined the
team. Here are the titles that I produced myself.
This is my first Tales game, so I think this Tale Aleph is a completely
new game.  I
think it's okay to say that this is Duece's first Teruzo application. It
's completely unrelated, but it's the Terufuwa series that Misawa and I like the most.
Well,
as for works that I have a special attachment to, I
like Vesperia so much that I even released a remaster of it. And
then there's Tales of Hearts, whose ending is so expensive.
I'm playing it now.  I
like pants. Yes, it's
quite old. That's right. I used to work at Bandai Namco,
so my senior is producing
this new work. And I'm making hair.
[Music]
Booby is funny, I'll tell you the truth. When
the moon comes out, the killer in that city talks about the town. Well,
maybe his head is too big, but that Piara is  My favorite works are
Thes Onbu Xillia City and Uni-iro.
Also,
huh, can is
amazing. It was the first Teruzu to do it.
That's because it's a work that I have a lot of feelings for. I think I have to mention the name.
Also, Belle Semiako, I
loved it.
Thank you. Yes, that's right.
Shinhwa, Nyahane, after all, there are a lot of users, especially in World.  I
think it was the first title I played, so I think a lot of people have
put it on the list of their top picks. That's
right, it's not just Tales of the Future, it was also the first Jr.
Pity!  It's
over. I see. At the time I didn't know what kind of voice it was or what kind of game it
was,
but I fell in love with it so much that I
became a big fan of Teru Atama. So thank you very much.
I was really encouraged when I heard that we could ask such a character to be the star of Son'n Anpa in the West.
[Music]
I've been watching all of those secret streams.  Well,
it's not like the tease of feel 2, Chiara is done, and they're selling it, so it's pressure.  I
think we'll be able to hear some really interesting stories around summer, so I'd
like to move on to the 6th question. I
'm a user avalarize, but I think the people watching this program right now are  I don't know.
I think there are still some people who don't know much about refrigerated soybeans, so could you give me a basic explanation and a little release? I
understand, Arthur, it's Araizu. That's right, that's
right.
Well, that's right, it
's the latest installment in the action RPG series called the Felzorb Booth series, which will be released simultaneously worldwide from now until the end of the year. The
Tales of series actually started in 1995 and is
already celebrating its 25th anniversary in Japan.  Series 2 has a very long history,
but in recent years, we have seen an increase in the number of opportunities for people outside of Japan
to play the game.
We are also aware that there are many enthusiastic fans overseas, including those in Japan, and
so Tales Barise is the first title in the series to be
released simultaneously around the world.  Ta  The
third one is that the translation is in 12 languages, so I'm going to
follow up on it with subtitles, and I'm going to aim for a March Patty that will get more people all over the world
excited and want to join in.  The
basic part of the world view has already been released in the PV,
but it is a fantasy world with two planets, the shop and Rena.  It
's a fantasy RPG set in a magnificent world where the drama unfolds.
Thank you for the Narou. I'm really looking forward to it and I've
been waiting for it for ages.  The new work is the 5th anniversary of the release of the new work,
but actually it was the one before that.
It was a Zen-style pen called Luceria, so it's been 5 years since the last time, so it's a perfect girl.
Brunei-kun ligand  I did Diving Celia a while back, and it was so much fun, so I'm really looking forward to seeing how Nakama will turn out
in his next work.
I would like to talk about that kind of thing. I
would like to move on to the next question. Let's start with the
first question. How did you
make the style of the watercolor painting of the SERVER ARISE?  What was the reason?
Well, this time, with Arise, the art style has evolved a little bit.
As you said, for the 2D game, we
are developing a Guji shader called Atmos Shader.  Not
only is the warmth in the picture small, but the characters in the foreground are
a little more realistic.
Ah, yes, that's true. In addition, the
effect of the light scales in the village is a little more realistic.  It
also incorporates a realistic style, so it's a very hybrid expression.
This time, I'm
challenging myself with that, and I'm calling it Sociedad,
but I think
it's good for Tales of, and the loop that puts the superior on is also up.
There are many people who have hobbies like that, and we have received a lot of responses, so
this Arais is, of course, an extension of that.
After all, it
's a title to commemorate the 25th anniversary of a well-known brand, and as they aim to
be a high-end flagship game for home video games, they've
decided to
push the boundaries.  But I
also had a strong desire to update the Rails of style a bit, to make it different from other works.  Well,
I had some regrets as I was discussing with the development art team and the art director about whether we could express it in a new way. It's not a pushy cel look, it's a little watercolor-like. It's an
extension of that, and it expresses something new, a
warm lifestyle.  I immediately replied, "I
think that it's possible to express something that is new and different from what I've been doing, and I've been trying out various things to realize that, and as a result, I
've named it "Kyogen Mart" after the one I've been working on this time.
So, it took about four years of development to complete the project, or rather to triple its size, and I got to
know the booths well
and did my best to get the photos taken.
Of course, it didn't take that long, but even during that long development period, we
kept evolving and we
got to a point where the station could see it as a product, which is what we're expressing today.  I
wonder what kind of impression everyone had. I see that everyone has responded positively to the new expression,
but it seems that there are also people who like the shades that are just there, and they are very interested
in our new challenge.  We are also very interested in what you think about it. I see,
thank you. I
think it's very fresh and good. I was surprised,
but in the end, it didn't feel strange at all and I thought it was very beautiful.  I
think it's the shape. Yes.
Then, how is the sound of Rise different from other games?
Also, were there any new additions?
Well, there are a lot of differences.
There is a theme that we have set for the Arise Development Department this time, and
those are the two keywords "succession and evolution of the
series." [Music] So,  I'm not trying to get rid of everything from  We have
taken another look at what makes the game so Tales of unique,
and we've carefully considered what we want to change and evolve based on that.
That's the
approach we're taking in development.  There are some small differences,
but I think you'll understand, but the feeling you get and what you
feel are definitely the same as what the Tales of series
has offered to you up until now.
In order to get people to like it and get them interested in it, the
changes to the appearance and the
tuning of the game design of the 8th specification were
done after a few radical modifications.
But this time, it's difficult to go that far, but
I wanted to evolve the battle system in a very positive way.
We are trying things like strengthening the village system for more people, and also the skit system, which was just announced.
This is also based on the appearance of that day, and is 3D-
based.  I've evolved it, so here is that
Well, in a sense it's a challenge,
but I think I can provide everyone with new expressions and feelings that weren't possible in the previous series, so I hope you'll
enjoy it.  I'm just introducing it,
but as far as I can see, it still
has that very "Teruzu" feel, which I'm relieved about. The
theme is "Fantas", but I'm told that it's really not like that.
And we want to be very careful about that, because it would be a betrayal of our fans, who we care about the most.
This
is true not only in the game production itself, but also in communicating with you all, so we really
want to avoid making mistakes.  I
think it might be a bit cold and not conveyed well, and I want to explain it carefully, because it hasn't been released yet.
Thank you for the Adol Narou.  Thank you for the next question. I'd
like to talk a little about the characters. Bride is the
same as the other members
of the Teizou Club. She's a big talker.  I
think how do you think this dynamic works among different characters?  Could you please
explain how it will be used? I
understand. Yes, when it comes to Zorbing, it is the character of the party. I
think this is what everyone thinks, so if you
receive it, the dynamics will be something that
I can't think of.  I think there are two things to it. One is how to express the
relationships between the characters in a compelling way within the story or world setting of Sabisa.  The
first is the characteristics of the 36-person party as a parry game.
For example, in battles and other aspects, if you have a
party of six people now, it
will provide a lot of variety in the gameplay.
These two are important aspects.  I think it's going to
be a big struggle. The story and the worldview of
this party, the
standing of this party is very high. I'm going to get to know a little bit about the worldview this time, and
the two big stars
are the trainer.  What is that? It's a bit
like being subjugated or dominated. It
's from that station.
Now Patty and the dam trainer are both races, so it's a high-
mixed voice
party.  The fact that they were not necessarily a friendly group from the beginning  The
second one is the main point this time, and it seems like they'll be
doing something about the money cart. Well, I do
n't know if they'll even get into a fight, but in
this world, it's impossible for a store owner and Rena to get along after just meeting each other.
When I have to make things convenient, I
can't get along with them right away. I guess
it's because I've experienced the plywood in the early stages that I can't get along with them
right away.
In that sense, this is a place where you can form deep bonds, and players can play in a way that expresses the world, the
situation in the world, and the party.  I
think I can keep up with that, so I think you
can look forward to the growth of the dynamism of the party,
and I think that there is
another side to that, the battle.  Party
This is really,
really, really strong as an action game this time, so this
Blue character, if possible, not just for promotion, but all
six of them actually play and get a feel for it.  I want you to enjoy  I
hope you will
meet Iron. I want to teach you one word here. I
think you can call this group relationship a "
family."
This is Japanese.  But this is a turn that is
often used in my live performances, but I wonder
if it's actually not understood.
Umm, I don't know. Court is
closed. Well,
what do you call the body? The
thoughts that I've been doing are  I
feel like I'm watching people like that. I
saved them from the egg. They're such
good friends.
Builder. And
later on, I think it would be nice to finish from the top. I see, I see. It's
far away, but...  I
thought it had to be thin. I thought it had to be thin. I
took a cat and
used it for the closed court. I'm going to make a character called Blue Sea.
That's the relationship.  I might be sleeping sometimes.
Avalize seems like an open world game. I'm
interested in the story structure. There
are a lot of military flags.
Oh, and I'm really curious about how the road will be tied
to the management's groove and how it will proceed.
If you know the name, please let me know. It
already looks like a world, so I'm going to start packing this time.
That's
right. We've made some pretty big improvements to the visual look of the world, so we've gotten a lot of feedback that it does look that way
. But, as a
side note, Arise is not an open-world type of game, it's a game that progresses in a certain direction.  It
's a driven type of game,
but it's not a one-way
game with no detours at all. There are
also side quests in Duck Village scattered all over the world.  There are
many discoveries that can be made by taking a detour,
so although it's not as surprising as previous Tales of games, there is a
greater range of characters and adventures.  I
think that's what's been created, and also, simply because the characters can jump or swim in the field, it
really does have a lot of action that makes it feel like an open world.
This time,
So, the
feeling of being immersed in this world by controlling the character is really pleasant,
and it's a completely different sensation from previous games.
So it's not important that it's a co-op mode, but rather that the player
can freely control the character, and the
character feels as if it's really alive.  It feels like
it's been strengthened,
so I think it's been sold as a school. I
see, so it's not an open world, but it's a launch, Okihara is especially that dog star,
and when there was a player  I felt that the
world was incredibly wide.
Well, that's right. In fact, the world is not so wide, but there are many things in the test play.
So, the sense of freedom that you felt there
can of course be felt in the main story, and
many such fields are actually connected to each other and create a world that can be accessed
once you enter the field.  Well, I'll only go once a year.
Actually, that's not the case. There's a hole story, a joker, some kind of subquest, here
till the
woman, and once you've landed in a field, it's worth visiting again. There's
also that kind of charm in it, so you'll never see that wide world again.  I
think the sense of traveling has been strengthened again. Hmm, I'll
wait.
Thank you. By the way,
Chiara and the viewers have also heard about the tsunami and their
pets.  I was really interested in the character, and the name is
similar, but that doesn't matter. I
really fell in love with him because he's so cool. I'm really interested in his
personality and battle side.  Please let me know in detail. I was
also very proud. I saw Kisara once and I was interested in her. Well, she is a cool woman, there
is no doubt about it, but
what in particular caught my attention? I don't
like that outfit. I really like her.  He has some strong equipment and a really
big shield. It's not very expensive. I
don't think you'll see a character using that as a weapon in other games.  I think that the
shield is a good weapon for the prefecture distance, and I
wanted to be protected in the position I wanted to protect.
[Laughs] I
think it's a long and small mistake.  It seems to fit, but as for "I'll show you my belly button
", it's
about the strength of that woman, but not just strength,
but also tolerance, and something about a strong woman.  I
want to praise that girl's character, and I
'm in charge of the design and engineering,
but as you can see from the first impression,
she's a woman, but she's very highly equipped.
Not only is she standing there, but she's also wearing armor.
As I said, there are two of them, the Rainer in this world and the
other seven.  Lena's
pedal regular army, or rather, this AK-like
squad, is a member of that type of squad from the very beginning,
and in that somewhat unique position she meets the main characters,
right?  The
equipment was given to them by the Southern God, and
they learned magic techniques.
That's the setting,
so that big thing is actually,
what's that? It's not a spell, but it can disappear or reappear with just one stone.
She
doesn't change her body, but
by using that equipment indirectly, she can
improve not only her physical skills, but also her technique.  So you
can use special techniques and skills, right? I
think it's a really cool character with a big floral pattern and hair. I
like that character.  Do you have any favorite things or things you dislike? I heard
that it's her, but I think that
's the case. I just announced this somewhere, but Kisara's
favorite book is slipcover. I
saw a video about fishing.  But
that air fishing thing, you
can call it a snack on SNS,
and I
liked fishing so much that if the
player doesn't touch the controller, it goes into a loop called a waiting motion
.  Of
course, each character has their own unique traits. The
next one is going to be a special one.
The salaryman is going to make bread for golf, so that really reminded me of that and I
wondered if the mixer was okay.  I do
n't think there are many people who would cast an entire school in a fantasy world.
But
then I think about the next one. I think
it was a necessity for her life as an immigrant child.
She talks about how she went on a lot of fishing trips.
There is a scene in the movie where she talks about it, but she loves fishing.
Well,
for four shots, Boob is Apa, but Polarize's fuel is Serve Quest.
Or rather, as one of the activities, I played it scattered around, and it was really
fun. I think it's not just about the sound delay, but also about the real distance. I'll post a
video of it later, so I'll
watch that first.  Would you like to have a good deal?
After watching the stories of the people above, it might be more interesting if you just watch a little more.
How she sleeps
at the high party.  I
guess you can tell from the video whether it's a high mom position or a good position, so let's take a look at the latest video together. It's nice.
This is the outside of C.
Let's see it with iron I want you to see it together
I last month chime idol like that
[music]
Extraction and a lot of things before
face 4 ad It's good It's bad taste I'm going
to do herbal tea with burna peewee groove use
existing is  asked Yes, get away from it Lady An Peg's advice
Felgra beige name said
Poo-style media perorating cure play new
ok web 2 do
?
Sei
Process Caster 0
[Music]
rename
go inside is cleaning - Yes  Ah, let's
go to Araicho and sleep. I'm not going to try my eyes anymore.
[Music]
Now I want to go back to the scene.
Eh, it's amazing. I felt something special about this group. It's really interesting.
This video is a little bit...  A little story about how Arise got to where it is now
The line is more like Tunaya, so there were a lot of dark aspects like that card, but the
promotional venue
is already a video department, so there are some aspects of this friendly party, and
well, this time it's the
outdoor camping.  This is a specially edited video to convey that there are field activities like cooking based on the marsh concept, and Kisara's fishing, as I mentioned earlier.
Thank you very much. Let's play it.  I saw that and my sister so I think that story is strange too. Well, it
's a skit story, but the shape and appearance were a little different in this one, but I wonder
if it will be controlled early on in places other than 8a.  So what type of cherry blossom lover can you enjoy in the final version of this game
? I
understand. It has happened many times already, not just at that 8-hour
trip, but
also at various times while playing.
It happens, just
like in the Teruzo series. It
sometimes happens at special moments, and sometimes it just pops up.  There
are some posts that you can read if you are interested in them, so as always, you
can think of them as a moment to take a break from your travels, but I
think Arise is a big  There has been an evolution
in the 3D model,
so I'm sure it's something that has changed. I see. It's a bit
like that, but it's not just that, it's also in 3D. I think you can
play all the skits that I just watched.  I
think there was a frame with a slightly big style, but it
has a cherry blossom edge that has fallen in the day,
so what's good about it is that it gives
you the feeling that you felt when you played.  It
feels like the characters are really there, like the six of them are traveling together. You can enjoy this skit on the Gin-Town Line, and
it feels like a natural reality.
That's what I wanted to aim for this time. I want it to feel natural, so natural that you don't even notice it. I
want people to enjoy doing this skit.
That's the concept this time.
Skid is evolving somehow.  There are
still some scenes left, and I'm really looking forward to the one with Phil.
Yes, that girl's skit is
like, as I said before, in the main scenario, Reina
is in a very dominant relationship.  However, I also tried to make it seem like the characters might not be able to get along,
but when I
looked closer, I was able to see a warm and
gentle side of the characters.  It's like the characters have softened a little bit, and the way they're layered in so many small details
is what makes it so Tales of.  I
think that app and Hii are interesting. I think that the pressure 3D helper is another one.
Isn't it like a lime or something? I
want to see it here till. I was wearing something like a cafe book,
but that's also in the game.  So, you can get it under the condition that it ends, but
if you want to enjoy something like a chicken dish skit, you'll naturally get a skit.
As mentioned above, the clothes are also good, but
all of them are reflected, so it will be a disease that has not existed in the previous skip, so I
would like you to enjoy this Neyoru play.
Then the skit will be  I'm not waiting for the suicide note, but if I
dress up the character in that costume, will they appear in the skit together? That's
what I mean. So, that Oarai chair is serious.  The
sound of the movie scene of the character's emergence is of course all 3D, so
the so-called "a suicide note" is also reflected, so the same goes for Tsukitto. The
only scenes that are not reflected are the 2D animation scenes.  I'm
really looking forward to it, I'm really excited. I saw this video, but I
was thinking about the competition, especially when I was playing at home, about roast chicken and my mother.  It looked really delicious
and the
pose he made after eating the spirit species was really cool. I
want to know what kind of effect the food in this game has.  Are
there any character events related to cooking
? Yes, cooking this time is something that happens a lot at this timing.
Of course, you can do it at the inn,
but the way to do it is to do it outdoors.
I want people to enjoy cooking in that way, but if
each character has a specialty dish, I
'm imagining roast chicken, but I
think that the specialty dish is that unique character.  If you ask for help, you
can get good things in the game, and you can
get better additional effects, and
there's that Western-style outfit, and sometimes you can
get a penguin-tied one.  There
may be exclusive skits, so please steal those various dishes,
find the recipes, collect the ingredients, and then find the special dish you want to use to get a
better effect and a more character-like feel.  Pick I
think that Loli-nee is one of the characteristics of Tales of, so I
have a plan recipe, so please try to complete it a little bit.
First of all, I'll start by collecting recipes. I
see.  I'm
really looking forward to cooking. In the second picture, there was
talk about cooking, but actually, Mr. A was the one who
got to play the trial ROM a little earlier.  It
's scary, really, thank you for letting me do it.
Re Berry,
yes, it's amazing. The
parent's curtain was 9,
but that's my impression after doing it.
First of all, the one that's
really big is the big tree.
For example,
when playing baccarat, the switching between your brain and the field is
quick and smooth, so you don't
have to wait. Because it's so fast, it's really easy to go from one battle to the next.  I
wonder if there is no fun in it. I see
. Thank you. This time, the battle is the
so-called encounter method, which is the parent and legacy method, but it's
like a good woman.
Well, there are a few different opinions on this, but
until now, after the battle,
In the results, there was a sequence where the characters stood up and talked,
but now they were
going to return to the field and have 8 voices expressing themselves
like that.  The comments from the other participants were interesting,
but I felt that there was no
awkwardness when I went from paddling to fielding, and it
went smoothly, which is why I thought it was great, but I
think that this time we want to aim for a little more balance.  You enter the headquarters, you go out again, and then you have the next battle. We've
adjusted the pace of the battle system a little bit, so that
everyone can enjoy it at the store.  I
guess you could call it the field member system, but I really want everyone to try it out as soon as possible and I hope that you'll have a positive experience with it.  I also feel
relieved now, and I think it's natural that many people say that things have changed since then.
Of course, I think there will be a lot of comments like that,
but
this is our own opinion.
Although it is a brand called Telezorb, we have one big goal, which is to have many people play this game without feeling uncomfortable. So we had to think
about how to strike a balance.  That was also something I was worried about, so I think that's the
right thing to do. If people who have watched the series so far can respond in a positive way, then
that's the best answer.  I don't know if it's true, but I
feel like Laserrise is not necessarily wrong in what it wants to achieve, so I'm
still
struggling with this, but I'm trying all sorts of things.  Of
course, that's
not all there is to it, so I think there will be a lot of different opinions,
but I'd like to
take that into account and make the series better in the future.  I
think the balance was very well done, and when I found out about it, I realized that Kochi was very personal.
But I really liked this one. Yes, it's a good question to ask.
Oh, I have another impression.
Well, I
think that in the test, we probably exceeded the limit by a large margin, but
even so, we weren't aiming for something
high, and as we walked towards the 22nd, we were able to swim and
there were waterfalls and such.  I went there to visit Atsuto and there
was a treasure there, but I wasn't aiming for it, the scenery was so
beautiful and I
enjoyed going for a walk, and I
got so absorbed in it.  It was really
fun to go for a walk. Thank you.
For example, even if there was no public, I was told that I had fun shampooing. Kuroko: I
think that people really enjoy making field art.
Usually, there is a treasure chest at the top of the roof.  Yes, there is something beneficial about the game,
so the basic idea is to go ahead and try it, but I
think it's not just about that, I want to make people want to go beyond that.  It's really powerful, but if you
don't put in the effort, you'll have a tomorrow in the game. We're making it, and I
feel like it's a beautiful thing. After I prepared the bill, I thought that way, but that wasn't all.
This time, I went to the swimming pool and it reminded me of the day I went swimming. I was
able to jump from a high place and do a big jump. I wanted to
try it because I could do that.  It was
only when I had that kind of feeling that I wanted to go on an adventure as a game, that I was able to fully experience it. I really
wanted to be a doctor, and of course, that was one of the things I wanted to do in the previous Tales games.  The
nest with the characters is the
most important brand, and that doesn't change in Arai's case, but even
so, I still want to take a little detour and think
about how I can approach the beautiful end of the year and how I can get there.  The ability to
cast spells on the world in front of you
is something we want to emphasize as an RPG, so we
really want to
add a variety of new features that match what you can do with that game.  That is,
in the end, the things you need to know to feel the characters don't change.
So I don't want to open up the world,
but I think a world that opens up the way to portray the characters is a better way to portray them.  It
will also be a tool for
If the characters have a conversation with each other and say, "Wow, we've come so far,"
and if that's how the appeal of Api is expressed, then a
home is more important than that.  I think
that
in a sense, it's about the level of detail, or the perspective, of how much of this
world we want to create, both
horizontally and in this world. I remember having
quite a few discussions about that, and
in order to achieve that,  You
may have noticed that, apart from the skips and movie scenes, we
have what we call short chats, which are voice-only conversations. In other words, the automatic chats that play
whenever you're adventuring in the field are  That
's right, this is
better. I think we've increased it a lot.
It's great. It
feels so
natural. I think that's important, and in order to make it feel natural, it's really important.  There
were some parts where we needed some variation, so in the end, we
spent about a year recording the whole thing. Here
you go. It's better to have a longer swing.
Just the last part is about that machine, but that
Chiara is a transfer of that past work
Basically, the main character in the head was
already fighting at the center of gravity.
For example, in the slow Symphonia, it's Lloyd-kun, but that Gya-ta is also a
wine character. Generally, the wine character is a
character who uses one or two aging sticks.  That
's what I felt most comfortable fighting with, and that's why I'd always chosen the main character, but in this game,
during the test play,
Because I was doing a test play, I tried switching to other characters and fighting,
but I was
surprised that
everyone was easy to fight and it was fun, so this time I
used various characters instead of the opposite.  I thought it would be like this. There was a
pipe attached to it. Is
that a
good thing? That's a very happy story. That's
exactly what I was thinking when I was in charge of the video.  The
series will also have 6 or 8 characters, and no matter how much the
characters in the party are composed, the
battles will be exciting, but I've
been hiding the game designer, but it's pretty
hard to say most of them, which is an
exaggeration.  Even if you take it, there are still a lot of people
So we're not the only ones that don't change the character, right? I
think that's the majority.
But we really put in eight times as much effort
into designing the character bottle.
Well, it would be a shame if people couldn't enjoy it, and it
would mean that they weren't able to experience the real charm of the work, so I wanted
to somehow clear that up as a sort of operation.  It's
easy to do. First of all, there are two things I did: the
Booster Pack and the Boost Strike. The
serving character can perform the support action at these two airy instants. I
think this was also a kind of lethal force. You
know,
you
're fighting together.
First of all, the feeling is to
make the audience feel like they're at a concert, and what we're
trying to do is to make it
so that you can quickly switch characters even during battles with your boots, which may have been a feature of the game.
So, I thought, "Maybe I should just manipulate it a little bit," and
when I thought about it, I
could change my mood and strategy.  I
tried to make it possible to change characters very smoothly, so I really
want everyone to try it out. I
especially liked being able to switch to Lee Si-yeon Jan when there was a target.
Yankan
Hon-chan has that thing, right? It's suitable for tunnels, right? Her
first attack really shoots down flying enemies and takes them down, so
of course, when you plan to use it,  By doing so yourself, you can
expand such opportunities.
It's really about how you manage the characters other than yourself or the characters you're investigating, in line with the play style of the person at that point.  There
is an option to do that, so I
think you will be able to create something that allows you to master the sound with the cone, so I hope you will enjoy it.  I
think that the individuality of the six characters has been greatly strengthened, and
in that sense, I wanted to try them all out.
I received a very sweet impression.  I
'm happy.
By the way, I think that for those who are playing for the first time, I would recommend the main character Arufen.
Good night, is there a character that is easy to play and easy to operate? A parrot. Well, there is one in the morning.  As you said, the most obvious thing about the former is that it
can be used in a wide range of situations, such as school plays, and the
former has an all-powerful,
attack-centered charm.
For example, while maintaining that aspect, the former
can also use spirit arts at the same time.  There is a character called Mu who is an underclassman who is a town lover,
but he is
already a person who
can be loved by others. He is a right-hand man who is a java. He is a person who can be loved by others ...
But
this time,
the three characters in the series are,
well, that person is, well,
in that sense, well, it's
a bit, well, well, let's go
with that feeling, that Hori
Hanjage is Fire Wire, the app is cheap,
by the way, that's the first time I've been able to do it later.
So it's an all-mighty. It
has an offensive appeal.
For example, there is a
character called Tsuyagari Mu who is an all-rounder who can use spirit arts without any problems while keeping those parts together.
He is a
very fun character to get into. First of all, Aoraora is not just about attacking.
It's a long-distance character that can be enjoyed by playing like that,
so
in that sense, if you
have a little bit of a patrol month, you can try it out.
Also, it's a matter of luck and the margin of victory.  It's interesting. I
think so. There are a lot of characters that are like, "Yeah, that's right," but there are
also a lot of attacks that you can use just like that when you're standing there. Also, in this game, you don't just attack the target, but you can also use attacks like in the past.  That violent act,
that branch action that went to the center,
is the focus of this time around evasion.
So how to avoid the enemy's attacks
by taking the high road yourself,
and
then
just by passing the evasion,  This feature allows you to close the distance between
you and the enemy and
counterattack more easily, so
please check it out.  The
performance is different, so I'd like you to try it out and see it.
In this work that focuses on avoidance, only Kisara is standing, so she can receive and return attacks outside the workshop.
That's what makes her different from the other works.
There are parts like that that stand out, so
Kisara is, I do
n't know, I want to focus on attack, but I'd like to focus on defense a little more. Ah, the opponent school
has a gay booby in the foreground, but, um, Nu.
So even though they're really offensive characters,
they each have their own charms.  If you really can't do this with fragments, there's also the character
Law. To be
honest, I didn't try it much, but I think it
was easy to do with the characters I tried out, except for Fen.  I
think it's Ninja-chan and Gizara-san who are using it. Knee-san's movements are
a bit slow, but he's carrying all that equipment and a shield, so he's a bit heavy to move around.  There
are various strategies for going inwards and facing the target.
That's right. With those 10 characters, you can keep your distance and heal at the same time,
so it has the
feel of a school RPG with public characters,
but you can also attack when you're active, which is
nice.
Hmm,
Toa's boost attack and Atako's boost attack were really
easy to do. I can do it over and over again with Bun Ibis, but if you
combine them, the battle becomes a lot more open.  That Tan
is boo-boo so the whole paralyzed demon party is checking the four schools,
so I think you can enjoy the feeling of being checked by the determined Arise, so even if you get injured, you can
still
feel like you're doing it in a flashy way.  I think that's a big part of why it felt so natural.
By the way, excuse me for saying this in English, but
a future in chess d 2
re re re re anders booth nice anfin aa ...
At the foot of the
moon bikini is the universe ie & pets a little bit still watch
Hermes turbo naa Ichatakado pickers we are ion  A little 60%
Martin D T 4 Lard Department Dio Fresh That kind of coastal vision Sonoo Town
More
Finger Watch Image Love is handsome darts
Yes Well, I want to ask the next question
Ah No I'll change the topic a little bit again
A score  Regarding the voice actors who don't pay, I think there are many fans of the dedicated voice actors, so do you
have any stories about the casting of the voice actors? I think it's the Japanese voice actors. Yes, mainly, I think it's the Japanese voice actors.  I was able to
work with that team on the original casting of the Japanese characters, but as always, we
hold auditions every time, and the selection process is very open,
so it's important to choose the right character.  It takes a lot of
time and energy to perform the role, and it's really hard. You
have to perform with a lot of
passion. [Music] The production itself is quite tough, so when you hear it, you have to prepare yourself for the audition.
So in this Arise, the six
main
party characters in particular have each spent more than a year  So I
asked him to record it, and well, it's been 7 years, and the game wasn't even finished at that time. Yes, it was quite difficult, but as I started shooting around that time, the game gradually came together, and I started to think, well, I want to reassess it.  I made a scene like this, so I want to shoot some more.
[Music]
It's a big worry for me as a creator. If it were real, I'd finish shooting all at once. In a
normal game, that would be the right thing to do.  But
in the case of Teruzo-bu, it's
really the skits and short chats that I mentioned earlier, and
once the scene is complete, the voices and
emotions of the characters are really needed.  Every time, something is
born one after another.
Yes, that's true, but we need to make the game as quickly as possible, and we
need to get the voice actors to start making it interesting.
So I always think that we need to start early.  But it's
not over yet, and the
recording itself was already completed about two years ago, so it's a
big deal.  The
promotion has started and I've been appearing on TV shows a
lot, so I'll start by apologizing for the wait.  When you
play this game, you can enjoy the feeling that our acting has come together as one true character, and that two
characters are really there.
Recently, I've been playing her in the 5 Promotion and things like that, and I've been
feeling a deep emotion while I'm doing it, but that's all I can say about the
passionate acting that's
present in her voice, especially in Japanese.  So, I would like to
convey the correct fashion to the voice actors of Manabu Sakano, and if
there is something close to it, I would like to surpass it.
As I said at the beginning, this is the first time that a new work from the Teruzo family will be released simultaneously worldwide, and that is
why it is a
big hit.
Consultation short-term written rent space sa  4 Selbelle Seya was also different, no, it's different, it's been
almost a year since I
got wet, but Vesperia Remaster was released at the same time, but now it's a star,
so I was
just making a work that already existed, so I was working on it.  We were building it at the same time,
but because
of safety policy, we had to take that much time and thought into it, and we had to
translate the audio recording into English and record it,
and then we had to do some more detailed projects, like Los Angeles's length, and we had to match that up too.  The
Japanese and English versions are completely different.
In order to make the Pound Boober version more consistent, the
translation is changed in a matter of seconds. The time doesn't match, so it feels like it's already being shown, and that's why the
voice is 4  I'd like to see the Derby degree in the voice recording of the a 5 version.
There are a lot of really delicate steps. It was
really hard to do this for the release of the Prince.
But from what I've heard so far, the voice actors for the English and Japanese versions really
suit the characters. I
think there are a lot of people who are always like that.  When you do something safe
I don't really want to play it as a good kid, and I
think there are many people who want to see the original second version, but is it true that the English version is
really similar to the character this time?  The
English localization team is really working on Arise,
so
for example, the Japanese
voice actors for certain characters are also active in other anime and other productions.
But in the American version, this voice actor is already part of the set, and he
does a lot of stuff, but he gets killed and then ...  I
believe that I can create a woman who can satisfy the fans of JRPG and animation, so I am doing it because ...
So, if you can get that kind of feedback from people who listen and understand your therapy, I
think I can now say it with confidence.  I
think so. I'm having trouble deciding whether to play it in Aero or in Japanese. I wonder
if those of you who are in Handa who understand
this are having trouble deciding. The first time around, the Japanese version
is 5th edition,
so...  That's right. You can also buy it at the game's express service. Of course, you
can also change it at the pitch.
And, you can change it around and check it. That's good.
That's an appointment. If you don't mind, we can move on to the next question. It's
okay.  Is it
okay to ask a question that I haven't decided yet?
Ah, I
saw this on the 9th of the west, but
that's the one I'm thinking of.  The horses are blooming and there's a lot of stuff happening
at the end. Kido Arm Iida-san is wearing a beautiful outfit and Sarah is
really big. What do you call that?
Uuuuuu.  It seems to be heavy and rated, but I'll tell you
what. Strandy said that and said something.
I wonder how many times I've already had to do this, but I'm
glad that I was able to experience the charm of lesbianism in a way that I've never experienced before.  We have had many visitors, but there are
emotional aspects to consider, and there was a lot of discussion within the company about whether we could continue to hold the event on a high level,
but we managed to hold it last year, and we
have plans to hold it again this year.
Actually, I
'd like to meet you overseas, so I'm
sorry that I haven't made any concrete plans yet, but I'm hoping to win.  I
want them to do it like that.
English:
That's it. Besides that, we're throwing events like Tales of Festivals that are centered around voice actors,
but it's difficult to take everyone overseas.
Do it.
Boo Boo.  If it's an orchestra, you can actually do it while listening to the local orchestra. I
wonder
if there's
something I can try, even if I don't understand it. I wonder if there's something I can try, like in America or Europe.
That idea has come out, so now that the distribution has started, we want to create an
environment where people can watch with confidence using Zoids,
and this
is an event that we would like to expand.  Is it going to be distributed? It's
delicious. It's been on since last year. I wonder how it was overseas. I
can't go to Uwaka, so I really want to see Chiara.
I'd love to see some plays that I can say, and other things like that.  I
think that I want to feel it at a live performance, and last year, I arranged the theme songs of the past titles, the
theme songs of "Let's Build It," and they are all important to everyone, so I arranged them for a full orchestra and made a
medley of them all.  Or rather, we did it in order last year and it was very well received,
so this year it's actually an encore, so we'll be performing the hard-hitting Arise
theme song and of course the set list will be centered around that theme song.
Well, everyone in Japan should definitely go and tell Miyara what they think afterwards,
but I
also want to improve the environment so that you can watch it on streaming services,
so I hope you'll keep watching.
Kira said, "I went to the Teiso Festival when I was in Japan." I was
really surprised. I was so surprised that it happened and I didn't know what was going to happen.  I
went there,
and the antiques were amazing. It
was a cheerful place, and the things they were doing were like a big cultural festival. It
was only five minutes, but it was really great.  It's
been a truly irreplaceable experience for all of you who love us, and we felt a tremendous amount of love.
I understand that it's important to create a space where fans and fans can come together.  I
want to develop more and more events that are not just games, but events that have a high level of appeal as a real thing.
[Music] That
's right.
Well, this is the bottom part. ok  Well, I think everyone is looking forward to it, but
I'm going to talk a little bit about the Teru Zone. But going back to Rise, I
have one question. The Tenzobe series is a story of two inner worlds, thematically.  The udon  I think
there are a lot of people who think that Teisou Barrise is a story about two worlds that are different from previous works. I wonder if that's the point.
As you say, it's a series that depicts two opposing worlds.
Asap, that's
right, and even for those who think that everything is just on one side,
Kaneda's way of thinking is safe, and
ur
is a fairly common way of thinking in that girl's series, but this time it's Rise  But
one of the reasons why I decided to make the structure of these two conflicts so easy to understand is that I
wanted to appeal to people who are fans of the series for a long time, but also people who have
become interested in the Tales of series because of this ice cream.
For example, I tried Shinji for the first time in a long time, but I haven't been back since then. So
this is a work that will be an easy entry for this series.  Actually, I think that I've
chosen to make this a
primitive and simple story. I've chosen to
make it a story about two opposing planets in a relationship of domination.  There
is one aspect to this that I chose on purpose.
And the other is that, yes, the binary opposition is very powerful, and I think it's
easy to understand, so through that
I want to draw attention to the more complex human mind and things like that.  I also
had one more thing to say.
This time, the characters will be 3D, and I
think that the investment trust will increase and the characters will become more realistic.  The
worries and comments of the characters, and the
relationships between the characters, have a certain
realism and a higher level of perceptual effect.
In that sense, in order to express the real worries of the characters in a world that changes in an easy-to-understand way, I
tried to use a simple structure.
So, in terms of the differences with other works, it's a little difficult to explain,
but with
that feeling in mind, I decided to face the conflict structure that is the path of this series.
That's how it feels.
Thank you for your hard work.  I
have a question I want to ask, and I think it might be the last one. The
video is about to be released, but now that it's
so close,
how do you feel about it? Do you have any thoughts about whether you've achieved it or not?
Yes, it
has been a long time since we started planning it at the end of 2016, and we've just started to sink in,
so
thanks to that, the gamers are almost done, so I'm
half looking forward to seeing how everyone responds.
There are many challenges ahead, so I am
half nervous about the reactions, but
as I have said before, I am also grateful for this opportunity to be with people from all over the world.
That was one of the goals I aimed for this time, so I
think it would be good to know what kind of reactions there are,
but I just want to know about it.  It's something that everyone can enjoy at the same time around the world. It's
fine for people to post comments on social media like, "That part was good," or "That character was good," or there are all kinds of reactions, like, "
This game design was good," or "That didn't suit me."
But I think it's important that things like this happen all around the world at the same time, and I'm
really excited that we're able to make it happen.
I'm really looking forward to seeing everyone's reactions all over the world at the same time,
but on the other hand, I'm really nervous, so I'll just crawl into bed and
wrap myself in my futon.  I've been looking at it for a long time,
but I really
wanted to make it so that you could touch the pork pattern, and I'm grateful for
your cooperation, so
September is already the index.  Well, I
definitely
want to face it head on.
By the way, I'm really happy about that one
year anniversary of Chiara's debut. I'm
really happy about it.  I
heard that it was close to the hotpot anniversary,
so that's the case this time too.
Haruyuki: I was
thinking that and playing, and last time, the first stream was for you on your birthday,
right? Well, this time, aaa
When the game comes out, I'll be doing it on the channel,
so please look forward to it.
Finally, if you have any comments, Mr. Tomizawa, please do.
Yes, that's right.  I'm not sure what to say, but I
'm curious to know how people will react to this, because it's something I've never done before, being able to do a session with people from all over the world, not just Japan, through Norma Talk with Cara-san.  Well, it's a recording, so it's going to be distributed, and on the day it's released,
everyone will be commenting a lot, and I think everyone will be reading it later, but I'm
really grateful to everyone for
that.  I'm
really happy to be able to walk this path. And
as I said before, through this Arise, even if there
are people who are really new to the club, I think that the number of people who are just stones will just increase.
So I
think that there are a lot of people who are really fans of Chiara but didn't know about Teruzu and found out about it through this show, and I
really
hope that those people will give it a try.  We all got
excited together and played the game like it was on a TV show.  I
think it's a work that can be enjoyed by anyone, so please take this opportunity to check out Pyuudo
Bar Rise
and the Martel series. It's a
baby-faced one, so please do it, everyone.
Since her debut, she has been talking about her love for the series, but I
really want those who haven't played the Teruzou Aogu series games to do so, and
those who haven't gotten around to that first one yet can play the previous one.  But when it's released, I
'm sure everyone will be able to enjoy it. I think there will be some more work before the release of the
official ambassador,
Basara, so
please pay attention to that.  Thank you very much for coming today
Ronin
Thank you very much I hope you will continue to support me from
now on I will continue to do my best so thank you for coming to this studio today I'm
looking forward to it thank you very much thank you so much
[Music]
[  Music]
4th
mar
ah
2 me up ring match zumure
4 nanas 2nd part ame to spin
tool like ya-plan do spinner this feedback pu tax
Nyan,
good ...
y hope you
guys are a threat
Ah
me
anders Cup noodle pattern or match horse is good
Vienna Vegas Scanpe cato
Caldis Scan day or uzarata work properly picture
Yay Koi Turbo Camp v see
re re re re  re re re sr deren ode ando
wever ender n seg burn i
amie plan swing easy to do mn game wii
chons no way
bead stone
water apartment pesh wo hem da jis n
re so me an goods 4 f 4 n san 2  Flyer rme
loss eust fur wool up the baby special okino 4
ten big star non 4 f bully store
Boon blue tooth bing this Pindar 4 txt g o in this
for men and half with b 52
ran wing rtm fence
special omsb double dow play
interview afb orenge about choice ace tezu
maple awesome 6 cars dain d 9 wine
aaaa rare animal
[Music]
Awakening
Pawsui Fan Meeting some ampeg scene slice iiiiiiiiii
Yuzuru suke tsu
ramm Fanning family 6 people home people pull rice up shark-like
Apon no um
this kids buson rend tear the game the
voodoo regex webo new world bound  Temperature poooo
new in the pubic area and invar selection pin story with showroom
soon autumn opening children pock and
like system
speed pro 6 a f sports re down to do world
manebi kupo cheese normal dk pace ah
100 pottery Inguk-san Cub player
[music]
voodoo re zu barrel ex par 4 watchin
fun 2 n barwick no ano star motion
2 wesker goods prune ender ender ender spencer
bagel follow roof 4 s arm by pink
des des myspace  f bridal anti-curve goods next web
n h 2
fence tooth is sjo main body ngu charming ikepod
mending sukesan aah
high adi comparison pen one after another naming row eeee capri pine
is dead ah ha
render swingway  5
nid smooth party in truth queen no monroe n swing
record lick fence dance home be careful
nu do do do so ntr 4 f b 2 f 4 o
um affin nurse ah walker e a pen pic dame 22  news
Passion-san, I'm a fan of the air ...
Tars shaved and put on Yu-Jung's buddy Yasso-
ue see less
Nan
pabo tion a english voice and skids charger department general
affairs
for a ios hegationee
secretary 5 door with 5 star hair
re the voodoo down tion department  4 s a mother
Windu worth to spain Kab e part Aya Blue dua Early
Arm flavor 3 bottles more than Senryu ice cream I'm going to return it I've already chosen the phone look
Super 43 years
Kubo Tarp leave it together chasing the mystery there line
Po  Spanish model geo art
a wear branche ok oh
use to do good old restio meara son ben
Darzer star web contribution icas Kuzo dapuu me
Ami sanso Habrakku free size down so md star
Zuru miss size backup
universe ns 4n Fourth Queen
Barbie background
maybe four 4 swim good pants Penny Lane Carr ok
ees 2 minutes free
Ah Pyon master in campus AP 1000 Cab e n
Wing Installer Starfighter
i finally Crop Mag as Grandis Mesh b Su
Mabao
this space e mail archive ga
Wig Teens all ages Carnation Spice Cheong Artwork
and Learner
ion
spy not
[music] i
Pink House also sucked
Aina's long celebration
together - Smart Pretty SD Navi B-side Che
PC Prom Spice Sisters Blue Do
Good Mend Geishu do n 4 al 4 wii your
ummm
homua off the [ __ ] Igu
[Music]
tb r star black scale meister 6 head od spice wheeler
batting evo pu5
d spice ns Benz sofa me to do n
y Heidi asame 2 r er 4 n
to it 5 harmful reason can't be superficial
Dog meeting sake taste face Wow wit
tarp then mouse 4
display leaf pattern blueway see wife map go
recorder
work Saaaaaaa
re speciale as cheongdun rr oson 4 promod
arty fragrance
arm bar bdu
booby endse so n re john r dare you  do pan
boo boo seata rearea face odense ah djno
nook that guy patti ap copy paste
isidea short ripe airweave yevs path scape fighter
ummm
well
eg south rapine
wissardin interview do up down dropper figure  weather
me
shareopti nds pass called sukidzu
airbag rubber figure part you do this local there
ran minute spin [ __ ] [ __ ] na bar 1 shirley dx 4 se
kisaran
new zalar mousse ube also air bar pe god
paan sqp pra  Day's Barby Barby Ren
Ispe Scene
in this om
8 items Kyu Sweet Pim Ah got a big loss
and Pfister Indan Imp Main PC's Itai to tears
Up type Wood Waa Ankises to Jan 5 ay Changer Bound  Color Pipi
yeah
Ogo Wade Ime Hanpen mother and brother Wow wow
three soy sauce Ah improvement English Mediga
Good
move
Mema Brainberry
Type Crane's Jack Ah
Sell repair
Abby Add salt  Well then, good luck!
[Applause]  It
's the day of the sea, Shizu, Etsuyuki Pyu is good,
Years Day Euro 4, Myz Nagatomi Rose Queen,
Ha,
Tira-chan Fanker with k sosa snipeer,
Ru, as wings ode to, Ga Boo Boo Line Girl, Wow,
order, p, 4 beers, Artist, api, Messer
Amebaa through pure blue do the face powder futon speaking wedge
exe to wind low hospital is feene
[music]
Japan office aim is oh creation to player times is noir
Morio Denki is pure good
dua a lot of pieces tpe
inoa dealer wit  Marsh love,
after getting rid of the point, it's fast, yt, heavy branch habit is caught, so merry,
maybe, so, display heating, b, silent zoom, fack, plate,
produce king, times pure, eat for, ting surf 33,
[music],
euto-man bath, anb, savior,
esprit, fury, 2walker,
ur bath  wa tu
[music]
voodoo catch general affairs fish
mylist work please 2
[music]
combo changed
rt home s over minutes res kids aaaa
killer
rebn old s pilot sk tsuba
saud day sofrafi zuchankeen
princess sauce miss scooby the bone aaaaa
vs dance skater  geskar beforehand game for a wedding raspini curler
abuf urano face wear rpg
uin
uzgreater mens ar pt fishing
reiran jeans no
pospe segar good a day etty teen layer fall nc derby paper
peros os one
fax web fingers to spain  Inchan View Aid at the Face Temple
Void also for Apai Nome
Boon-4 Masen Dadabidi Meet
Darwin Ranger We Are
V Yayuku Rod Race Wipestalk
ns At such times Wave Circular 4 IP Song
n  Snack chicken papa
Yeah yeah yeah Shaan yearly mockery game
thin Yuge re 4 Minfa me up tour
naaaa c mature da pastor so
maybe many long scene certain outerwear to do for Suzuki
up your Dal surfing reception stand Potter lens system e
ah ah ah
du good  Wereworld Life Taa ...
lee perry tape composition
aaron ya de power softel wings to spring spa 4 ae minutes
klaus
papiswee it justice first words
moriaki
web service cache up ks bate andeen canty shon
so live and computing casting aizu sky loose good
van dam
win not  you do stone
iphone  Charlie News English case 1 sale loss Raje plane
dinghy asino 6 Mr. r Wentz pass says someday 1
cannabis raw rescue songebooks
with me casting power 4 a such theory ek news tung
voodoo blinker pass days 2
Dart tour main is tim  Aje Cruiser 6
Fashion Dependence dulcet e 9 de Microcomputer Well, it should be mir
We are free come across me to do a power
boomsound
No, you can enjoy the power Go lonely
Hmm Painter style p a v chip quo x3 book application cap course ke
committee Tewo  Sabu,
yay, cello, sophie, unreasonable world, Iroha,
arm, rain, ramen, oooo, mail, skip, as, out, volunteer, large,
Inove, new, gyaa, b 2,
voodoo,
ko, disk, petit spoon, peruns, baa baa, boom,
patterned pumps, many,
learn, soap, eb, the oc, wii  Bar
voodoo r polar who do loop owner's face
katie yukyuanzen a rausa-
ish liar male hole down champion 51 ownership a
eeee vector blue commercial
[music]
voodoo
off blowgun dio fear
anderen the veil ender ender  ender
asaras per month spacks ender sticker love door love ally
bam me now it's over a
yeah
five major sentences along the web swing even 1 power yanaosan
no more chonchon smooth 2 c god super wife coaster
[music]
come on arenas beach a papageno dere
come on  Star Web Pay is Warner good
song learn a
good video We Love Crosswalk
Othello Pyuto Road attached is good
a thing Sazarea Swimmer Clip once Ashtar 4 day
out Chame 4 reduction Sama Let's go Boo
Boo senso  Dele-ins boo boo good
as old as a doodle
Star brewer pets
a
Doso flight web surface adventure sen
come been black pen mina-flets say body pot also yorinto
uh let's roll up our sleeves and express it with point vibes etic bookend
star world wing
abe  Is tuna noose forceful fiber boo boo boo block
muta speridine staff
seconds breath two companies exactly where one day turn um
double party up 3 nof pin
p mother is almost 5 times what
today
entity confirm 4
o good de
Vinnie ridge saya  Ting Griffin Computing
Micro Gray Calm PV Wind Call AB 8
Boolean
Aaaaa
Arp Mix Atia nee Kisara
Well Now Color Kiss
Access Count Dog Begin No No Use Year
Handshake Ansion Andere
Cute Place Pre N There
Re An Sam
Teacher  Burl Pipe Race add to do Cast Play Rally Car g
Dickey's Egg str  Black mud
a Yes, you
can wine can cultivated incubus sting in Christine Oh,
web play bar
Leno
Diff Let's with
Kenkyu Nice well, this guy Come
Weddy web Weep-chan
shock spanky not nice
re Undo back  Pets Dai Please
[Music]
re down the rope Down Supreme & Prime Outlets
web No. 8 in Space Ones
Ta-dah Fein
Swing Aboi
play Farm is Ugi Samurai good
defense
Hmm
Off is also smelly Pen Squad Sannu with Caster bent
to an end r 4 me web base ore
4 s power theory rice medieval r 4 terano lick burner rank e
already has preschooler form opponent's cha bye bye es pose yasunaga show
to andis so izumi shu inage that  Parrot p
re b 2 c  It's a pose in game
ah
ah Shima City Sumo Curly Up Shop Sumo Paris Sumo 2
Choice Design Ah
Ah Ah Ah
Yes New Finance Husband
Hun Nagoya Well everyone
receive Chura San Ah Vision Starware aim Ah Masu So Penota  Two of them are eeeeee bis
piy sway bar General Amoy Day
Unser is also Tim
but 252 Dondon
Honchaiso number number what Queens 06 good danpa
4 schools
whistle
Arthur filing pow jj
span This kind of pie
Inpopi Server Wise  Weiss tu
#should go up od Sayonara cure na tiaisaaann
pa no wii be a turn swap file na hypo nuun
fc Togu meksui person da
big
on top
difficult
mail
ah ah ah
feinker big guard poodle do  the faith pencar lf
aaaaaa
[music]
haaaaa  It's
good, but it's a game of iron and
twice. Well, it's
good, but the body is recommended, and the release is played. Then the plug star fighter is boom
blue,
and the painting is great. Ah,
I'm so excited,
and I'll put the character pocket in it.
[Music]
Ah,
ren
Yabe got Callaway goods from Kusumi toilet seat poi from the prospect of 9 a
That's a good coordination partner Padi
Esper is 8th place in the Tenkyu Festival
after all yeah The popular co-op up 19
Blue ta--- The dignified Farsi game 18th boi  Ahh ...  That
's unfair, isn't it?
Mizunaga  It
seems to be a good Mac account. It's sweaty.
Ep Tsuda tie and red
. Before that, IKEA Mino powder ruins and foolish. Symbol motor car
Polly advice network spar in s
burn ummm
a
selected move group
yaaa
haa haa
gerber
buuting r
Hanu blue rcc sound fan book book fathers haa chan language thin or beje wrap another while
sweets dagger
ana eh
ah worms also rice pour bellman for  Congressman
Baia's mother makes it when you can't make it.
Ran Way Bosnia C Fine Jasper Inn
Nearby
[Music]
Navy Road Copper Pot Leash Ah
Ici Turbo Pro Vowels Au Au Au Atsu
ny wii s penny
[Music  ]
Bubarre
re Hekyua r Dowonstay Village Downwear Department Scone
Pataka-chan
asaras cooler pan splat sound t 4 a
blue minute game mas Turfy is a hero quark wood without pre-genie
bays lease a man to do
hmm
baby version her as for face pace structure
web ahhh big
big liquor corner altarude  Neslon boost stance is Gosho Kou Che
Check Round Boy Ikona woman check
Used f
[Music]
Ah Farfa inch number Pampa
Gold Chai Jita
arrogantly Chest Puapuepu was about the bill tongue bar ovenware  Drum bar
love seal
Swept caster right brain unexpected high up
voodoo
archi
reason
to go fuse feed how you do see
iim 4
iphone dogranfary aaaa vu carp us persion finally
passive a lot of
yeah
ah
ok oh
open
aaa  Senkiyama skiing three or move
amp 1 showing sharp is also good together
Pocket 0 is very hot,
what is it? Boo
putter, Queso Ebisu, pine needles, tomo
map affiliate, ah, melody, days bays, n, non, Spain, paw, low temperature,
strong, ah,
mother, capers, coup de bijou,
fines, d, former,  Prius?
With this, the air conditioner is now right, my mother is here! More papi paa
Tomorrow please Ando
Kwaito hike up
a Tan Akiwo
Fuu
Baros News Joint a
re resides Comfort chef pants nude bbs Kaneko p
[music]
voodoo Star Pass already  a o
fundis can i car nfufu
then buy guard and distribution 525i zu birthday tree wallet 9 Polly's mornin
ah
description column ah
[laughing] Ikes
benefits good Kisana
sq
somwaaaaaaaahn ahhh I'm
worried why
home
store  About
Ferry season turbo poisae
Navi sound open Poe
ni poster a 5 af
Farah shop or Yankee Fufufufufufufufufufu
Kyuu defeat on the Shion attached in cur 99 qg Tomorrow Fight Tsun Chan Koi
Naane  Steaming Na-
mi Aa ...  Special Good
Straw Game Deep Blind Peg Day Santo Moon
Boolf Naru Martin Panther SE
[Music]
Voodoo
Indian Boy Front and Enter Sign Living House is also amateur good a
Cassa Made 4 Now Mother Variation Armor Guard Bucks  Wow
wow
7 save Bauhaus fighter brown carry kx loan
amimaido
[music]
and farm [ __ ]  Get drag damper and maybe
papa
yeah
line chasing and nihiinyan minutes Keio
recommended games
car jinkun everyone tide age color ana martin monomachi pyon
tekom Frespo inc define c coser zaboon  Blonde
hairy figure
No,
big,
hmm, over the dice, whiskey, pet service, Chester, loser,
borrow, Oscar, sports
[music]
why waste, key,
[music],
accu, lion, other, chai2stellar, starting soon,
hi to self, surf, yeah
meg n t
swaying pan zo samira kyutto or shape it gather choice suwa
reac started pin total
strategy star pink purple save a o 4
rice and access surfing soft with fufufufufufufufufufufufufufu  Continually  Pyuuu
why Jackie Penner worth pattern office wear Bobby-chan
Beta day is employee Edy  Jump with
B Chanpei
Oon
seat swollen dog lay down
Faber weather barked and said
n Hara Define cloth poster 3 steps inner car audio sound is y-san
evanescence ya da da hesitation challenge ah
huh Audi  Ice cone
speeder
There is already a tuber
name ortho m so proud speeder
ana
ga ah d
aaaaaa city wall rap is also uuuuuuuuuuuu open
outside point pair star make living in a young country great quadrilateral
wide circle my car
Rabbi Neisukaa Issho and the
Dim American Disk Life
Voodoo Feet Care rd 1000 yen Bestreben Active
Bath Town Douuuuuuuuuuuuuuu
Today Catcher
Okama
Web Nabeso Winter Ni Urine Iso is a
rubber Ni Nappa Yeah Love Orisaka also spoon insco Hey
yeah yeah I'm going to go ahead
and burp the toilet seat and cheers Yoishoku
car
1 year ago
ngaa ...
Dondon none Aps
nice Finn to do fab pass many enthusiastic 2 s power double breeze men and
women in the middle
sweet system page oh
shean shean weblog an hair pony teros cube
elegant tain sure win puro book
hoc fantasy also voodoo 3 sy 5 on face  Smooth,
wow,
loose, kiss
Komori is it,
Tatsuta [ __ ] Gyaru Gyaru, let's
do it, Ndoba Heath is good,
ah, you are the place and spoon,
ani,
please,
festival or fuse milli goods 3 girth under wow,
Whisper Woody
piece,
this guy city ta Usuda option osx people  It's
n
Pontendar minus lean angels hard to come
Ah Beijing abu ipu dalshin is ice small
swam yeah great
star n work turn so much like mountain
hoi oiden
wiser 6 pu
road Wimbledon ase  Sevigny asamana
Burn proposal
bape matching Sanhijuri time space division push fuping 4th place keep
Hyeongdo is Kuni Kimspoincan for new i san
pink ano minutes
rs and do prune
chain efriend ea polare aspd ese noo 220
ana curl  e 0 a day  Sun is a 6 way pinks denbo
dawn is always so I think
aurora ai pon
[music]
rennos
nachu away sonar bag for a hair
button type konde up art ran finally
art inform suit ha
wood as masuntsuki sarah hey
me  Now the source
nastran oas
dared is no big zara co2 taxi house s 1 o type
noah web xno vile purpose food 4 f watch
[music]
web color me shop ah pin p game pinkish stripes
Staff po
I see, I drew a turn -
choose father, neesuneeponi emperor,
pot suun
1,
do it, ah
fire,
pocky salar, deres 4 c rubber strap peropero wii
opal palm
with some terrific
foma, gyaaaa face system dizon  re
man who do as  Miscellaneous expenses my pain feat a
Melfo fc 4 re Bird Black Wonder degree premium WonderSwan
asn ios wii World Green States 1
Hmm No,
after all, defeat the one and
choose the spar I drew and guarded if it was my mother
Hahaha
Baseball Day
Aoya Nove love course walk pay tribe in cause
Jaaan
Isara costume big dobon boin stage stake yaaikui
starry eyes Marcyun I want to meet you color and mix it up day cho this kind of place
s can become photon Ryumi cleaner darker
sky  Quartz today supreme dowser work proposal ping game speed
interview volley cheek mother sister 13 r 4 use yeah nuh san also bauter
peep fure play attachment 4 garden play peep attached clip teaser attached 4 air
fighter with a
word convenient down prevention insights
in  to do 4 points Yusuke Tomizawa
voodoo 4 soe s ah
Yay ridere bank delivery see a st ste remeber
pair safety
post with ayu scan 4 b waype shintan tankokiteppa meet
ana lenses for san
ah
still show first dane
branch whenpe r end minutes
[music  ]
voodoo Pyuta Pu star Aa ...
in game eason 9 minutes
10 farspenber dice charger
use the apportionment format show
ice cha-san pain scum form ice love slave and pain
to do good
voodoo
3 compatible yes
office web author play in the legislator eh one point to compensation
maybe even know  Wear me under my
clothes
baby  There is no day practice, it's amazing, it's impossible, the media level is
good, the scope channel, the Sky can do it, it's good, come on,
fear, wow, the Orphen cover comedian, Naomebi, big pointy, Ray,
Tenor, off, Yupp, it's a bad image, angry, even if there is a game, your stereo
Art Police store outside rice toiu uru one day and said
phone buy
voodoo as par enos girly
up view spa pointer for pc you do
not
usp speech check p 100 a seat to do
rearrange rearea 4 te & scarf denver to do
Well,
pop enjoy rate 4 always good chairs, see us to manner
areas 1 to 6 after game position ape apes wedge
spoon
rear edcb prefecture funny car minutes
dx pink only apon queen queen ppc
boops par afip 4  xp xxx pack set meeting
Oshay and pet are bloomers are bad
2 Take away dark promise Spa Sports Up Sen's characteristic
Sen's Express Pack line
Yeah
Got a plan Hahaha Ebetsu
Palm Good day
Ana
Say Mocha 5th place game
Fashion 5 s to do anman Dohoodua
[Music]
Pe k
or 2
[Music]
hmmm
eme
[Music]
hmmm boo-
boo hmmm
[Music]
hmmm
[Music] hmmm
hoop
hmmm
[Music]
hit it
[Music] hmmm
boo-hoo
hmmm