[Music] My
bones get wet as I wish, and I close my jumps
on the ground.
Someday, my
voice will turn into a sweet one in the rain. It won't be long
until I leave.
[Music]
This place is the closest to the sky.  The way I
stood up
[Music] De
[Music] I
'm here Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa Aki I'm passing by Aaaki I'm
fine Kimekchamoto
Luaa
wait a minute Minecraft
has crashed
But Kara-chan's voice
De-chan
De it's so
loud
Maimai Gully
Lililili
Li now  I'm going back Yo
Big Senkyu Big Voice Senkyu
Big Voice Thank you for saying yes
and the Ehaku team has gathered together.
Wow, white team white white
[Music]
Chee, there are people who are
talking to each other. It's amazing. It's really telling them. It's
fun, oh, it's so much fun.  It's okay
[Music] It
's too loud, isn't it?
Ee-
chan
[laughing]
Width,
handsome, good, ok
, ok, ok, ok, this is what I'm talking about.So, I
'm a little disappointed.But, ok, that
's it this time, oh
oh.  You're here. You're here. Okay then, uhm. I did
n't get divided into teams, so I
thought I'd make a little announcement. Yes, I think so, but are you okay?
Please, don't fight with me. Stop fighting for me. Are you
okay?  I'm really
fine, I'm a
junior, so I'm fine, so I'm fine. If the junior is energetic, it seems like he's very
lively, isn't he?
Well, I would like to announce each of the white team's Emae competitions,
but first of all, let's do a follow-up. It's a
competition where you climb higher and higher.
Your score is determined by how far you can go within the time limit.  It
's a game. Yes, it's a game. I
'm here today. Good luck to Kia. It's a bird, so I
can afford to go. I'm sure I can go to the top in one hit
. How about one hit? I can't wait.
Nao Gaei Race Gui Re Escort
Race  Yes, this game is a
game where a knight protects the princess,
and the princess also has a lot to do,
so it's quite a difficult game.
That's
me,
and the next one is Iroha-
chan, and the fourth one is Mumemu. It's
good. I'll ask Himekoshiyama to play with these four. Yes, nice. Yes, I'll do my best. But
when I hear Iroha-chan's English, I'll
support her.  I thought I didn't have to do that.It was good, isn't it?
English is
good.Special EnglishGeniusI even think that
English is more lively than Japanese.That's
certainly not the case.Isn't that the
case?
It's not like that.As expected.  Alright then, next obstacle
Relay hey hey 4shiyun yeah yes Azuki-chan is
out Eame-
ame-senpai Yo-chan and E Yuzuki Choko-sensei Sensei
next, Shirogane Noel Leader Marumaru
Maru Leader Maruho Nobi Honobita  Routaro and
then
[Music]
[Applause] Muaja
Hime Hime Team There are three people besides me, but
then Kaela
[Applause]
[Music]
Kaaka is now the last one
Neri Saonee and the last Holomen
Hunter Hahome  The first person to hunt
is E Shirokane Noel, leader Holomen, Taro who
hunts, Taro Taro Jiro, Saroah, big sister,
and the second one is Chiara,
Kia
Pi, and then Aa-chan, Ame-chan,
big sister, big
sister, and the next one is Kaela
[Music]
Kaela  Next up is Neri-san Neri-san Saneri,
and the last one is Raden. It's
better than rodeo. It's arranged so that it appears once or twice.
Yes, it's a little bit, everyone. I've never competed before.  It seems like some
people don't have it, so yeah,
yeah, let's go around the venue and try out the competition,
please. I want to do it, I'm fine. No, let's do what we want to
do with this team.
Let's use all the calories we ingested today.  I
keep telling myself, ``It's fun, it's
fun, it's fun in Minecraft, it's fun, it's scary, it's a scary spell''
Okay, now I'm happy, let's go, come here, let's go, let's start with the first floor-up,
okay?
Oh, let
's go from here, it's a little dark.  Up
Is it difficult? It seems difficult. It's quite expensive
. It seems like there's a staircase all the way to the top.
Climb the stairs to the roof. It's
scary. Is it okay to follow the fire service law?
Fire service law. Think about that and make a Minecraft.
Hey, I'll fix it if I get caught.
[Applause]
Takeko
will be participating in the event, but
I've never done that Only Up.I guess it's
rare, because everyone else is doing it.Everyone has
done it, right?Yeah, well, well, but it's okay, it's
okay.  So, first of all, here on the far left, it
says E-debug item, number 1,
left, back, right, right-click on this,
Rat click, Kuk,
and then you'll get Ero's Trident, and the
weak and strong ones will come out.  Weak and
strong That's true. Left is right.
Strong or left is light.
Click,
press and hold right, then press and hold right, then
press and hold right.Release it and it will jump.Jump.Hmm, there are
strong jumps and
weak jumps.There are weak jumps, right?
No, the backboard is weak, so there are weak jumps.  When should I
use it? I wonder if that distance is short.
Okay,
okay, I'll do it. Clio, nice and nice. Ah,
okay. With this, we'll keep
aiming higher and higher.
Yes, it's hard, it's hard, it's
hard.
[Applause] Oh, I hit
it when I got home.  Even
if I hit it, I'm still alive. It's a pain. I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm
dead. I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm dying. I'm dying. I'm dying. I'm dying. I'm dying. I'm dying. I'm dying. I'm dying. I'm dying. I'm dying. I'm dying. I'm dying. I'm dying. I'm dying. I'm dying. I'm going to die.
Can you erase the real clouds that are
there in the book?  No, I
wonder if the cloud is interfering with it. I want a clear sky. Is this a setting? It's a setting that says whether there are clouds or not. I'm
sure it's there somewhere. Well,
it's in the video settings.  Hey,
Seona, this is it, this is
it, it's gone, it's gone, it's
gone, it's gone, it's gone, it's
okay  If I
do, I
might die, I'll die, I'll die,
so I'll go back to the checkpoint.Go back to the checkpoint.There's a
bed in the middle where there's dirt,
so click on the bed.If you
click, you'll respawn from there.
This is difficult. It takes a lot of practice, right? That's how it
feels. I'll practice. That's nice. One
Piece. Let's
go watch the next competition.
NEXT. I
wonder if I'll die.
Right-click on the left side of the debug item.
Right-click on the debug item.
Yes, yes, no, I'm
not going to
die. I'm not going to die. No, I'm not going to die. I'm not going to die if I'm in Bamo.
[Music]
Oh, please be careful, it's dark
, it's
dark, it's dark, it's real, it's dark, it's true, it
's here, it's here, then it's the obstacle race.
Come on, Tacha,
think here, Yokocchi is the
start, yaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa  It
's half a lap by one person,
so I see. So there's a line running from here, and there
's a line over there on the other side,
but the people who run all the way up to this point
have to part ways. That's right, from here.
How many laps are there so many people run half the race
and then come back to the other side? Well, how many laps do you have to split up into two teams? Well, that's about 8 people running, I
guess 4
weeks.  people
May
[Music]
Wow, let's
just run through all of those things.Everyone's
like that.Run around and find the weak points.No, I
think I like this one.I wish we
could talk about it.It's
pretty rough.If you touch it, it's a devil.  You
know, when I touch this hurdle, it's crazy. It's true. Maybe it's a slow one. So let's try running a little bit. Let's just let it slide. Or start pumping. Tart, yay, yay. [Music] It hurts. It hurts. It doesn't hurt.
Yaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa, it's a powder snow in here and a not a powder snow here, a ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-re-reta-re-reta-re-re-ta-re-re-ta-re-ta-re-ta-re-ta-- type, type of type, kind of type, type of type, kind of type, type of shape,”  Good, good,
good
[Music]
No, it's better to go from above No, I
can't take the bread, I can't take the bread
Click white, click click That's
on the left, right, left, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, I see, I ca
n't take it, I can't take it, I ca
n't take it.  The left and the left are coming out
and the left is coming out, or something.If there's bread in the inventory, that means I've
got it.I want to pass here, I want to
pass here, I'm
doing something.
Oh, that hurts. Something's happening. What's the pain? Is it
weird? Are you okay? I'm going to the insurance room.
Chan, I didn't
know you were the woman who hit your juniors. I couldn't proceed without defeating Rade. I see, that's why I hit you. I'm
sorry. It's
okay. Let's do it all over here. We
can't get rid of it with this whole body.  Yeah, okay
, this is a difficult place, but there's a remedy here, so it's okay
to go in the water, it's my way, yay, yay,
yay,
yay.  It's
amazing, this place is amazing, isn't it?
Genius Genie Genius Genius Laden
Genius Laden Genius Laden Genius Laden I'm not going to give you the Genius
[Music] I
won't give you the Genius.  I can't climb, I can jump, I can jump, I can't climb, I can't climb, I can jump, I can't climb, I can't climb, I can jump, I can't climb, I can't climb, I can jump, I can't climb, I can't climb, I can't jump, I can't climb, I can't jump, I can't climb, I can't climb, I can't jump, I can't climb, I can't climb, I can't jump, I can't climb, I can't jump, I can't climb, I can't jump, I can't climb, I can't jump, I can't climb, I can't jump, I can't climb, I can't jump, I can't climb, I can't jump, I can't climb, I can't jump, I can't climb, I can't jump, I can't climb, I can't jump, I can't climb, I can't climb, I can run and
jump.  I
'm going to swim through the pool and swim out. It's so
nice.
Nice.
Nice. Nice
.
Nolan.
Oh, nice, genius.  Apparently it's
set to make you feel hungry.
[Music]
Something like that on the right. My
listening power has increased
. It's not right. It's not right. It's left. I feel like I got it with a normal click.  It's
not that light, light. I do
n't even know what it is. I have to eat this. It's
like eating while running. Is it
like eating while I'm running? Or should I eat while I'm eating
? The next stage will be tough.
That's right.  Well, it's
best to munch before you go.You
can run faster in areas where the snow isn't too deep.If it's getting harder, you'll see that it's not powdery snow when you're flying through it.That's how it
is.There's powdery
snow ahead, so you can run as fast as you can.  It
feels like running and jumping.
If you hit the jump repeatedly, you can run faster. That's the ice.
By the way, jump red, jump render. It's
true. Jump render. At the last jump.
[Music] I
see.  The
timing is perfect.
[Music] It's
okay if you don't step on it.
[Music] I
see. Oh yeah, yeah, yeah. That's right.
That's what the obstacles were like.
Thank you for your reply. Thank you.
Next up is the princess escort race.  I want to go, I'm going to
escort the princess. Is there a princess today
? I'm far from being the princess or the first princess.
But what's wrong with that team?
Yes or no, which one is difficult, which one is difficult? I don't have Princess Gade, no, no, no, no, no, I don't think that princess doesn't smoke. But it smells like cigarettes, no, it's gymnastics. Her clothes stink.  I have
n't smoked today.I
haven't smoked today.I haven't smoked yet.
Well, first of all, let's choose one princess,
then we'll have three knights, huh, huh,
huh, Kaela, I thought Kaela wasn't there, but
Kaela wasn't there, so I guess I'm not going to
go home.Where should I go home? Find the princess.
[Music] [Music]
Oh, there's just four people in each group, so let's
try it out together.
[Applause]
Okay, okay.
1234 I see. The whole team is
here, so I guess it's okay.  Let's
try it out with the team and the members who are not the actual team Let's try it out Yeah yeah yeah let's try it
[Music] Or
Aki Agozaru White Princess Team The team is here
This is Hitoshi Which one is the knight?  The
princess might be more difficult,
but the princess has to
explain a lot of things to the other members,
but I
think you'll understand once you try it, so I'll explain a little while we're doing it.
In that case, it might
be okay for the princess to be Iroha-chan
because she can speak English and Japanese, so it's true that she's a
samurai or someone who has done it before, or a
samurai, but I'll protect you here, princess.
You were the princess, right? Good luck.  Here, Hime Hime,
please do it.
Other than that, I'm a samurai and the lightest of the Enthusiasts.
Please right click on this.
[Music]
Kaimoja This side
[Music] Let
's try it in the middle of the room. Kakaea
Chiara. Let's make it a princess here.
Kia. That's right. Yes, yes.
Himemasu
Opusmapuse
[Music]
Punpun Magical Princess Gozaru
Gozaru  I asked for the Magical Puri command,
then I think we'll start. Let's start the
game.
Let's protect the princess. Where do we enter here?
This is the gate.
Open the gate. Let's do our best. Let's get open.
Let's go.  First of all, I want you to get used to this,
so yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, nice, nice,
where
are you now?  I'm going to get on the train right now.
That's what I'm saying.
Nice, nice, nice. I just got on my senior's ride.
Eki
yes, oh, maybe it's the next button. Get
off. Push the button.
Button. Is
this the best thing to do now?  Climb to the end
again, Kado-senpai, move Kado-senpai, Kado-senpai, move, yes, stop, yes, let's move, yes, yes, yes, move, okay, don't do it.  Step on the
top, please, Akichi stop
Now, senior's senior, please move, oney,
nice, nice, nice, it
might be easier to tell if you say where you are right now, I already know where Chiara is
Rio, please step on the top, uhm, who, who,
please step on, Muu senpai, stop.  On the top of the top
Stop stop everyone stop stop oh one nice nice nice na
oh one sla So
answer what you're making Restart
Restart Architecture I'm going to do architecture Architecture How are you
doing architecture? Well, E button.
When you open your inventory, you can get a lot of things
like a creative mode,
so let's start making
things here. We can see the theme of creating our class. Everyone is the
same. Same.
[Music]
Oh yeah.  This is
Eh, I'll make it for you, I'll make it, oh
yeah, I already know what to make.
Yes, yes, from that list, the princess
will have a list. I have a book, so I've got a list from that list.  You have a choice, right?
Push that button, press that button,
yeah, yeah, yeah,
one more, one more, one more
[Music]
Oh,
no, wait, I'll do my best.
Yo, this
is it, nice, nice, my
princess
now.  I'll tell you what I want to eat, so I'll tell you what I want to eat, so I'll tell you what I want to eat, so I'll tell you what I want to eat, so I'll have steak and
Ellie, Tokierie, and
Steak.  Elite
Elite Pan Elite Pancake Elite
What are pancakes? How do you make pancakes?
I see! Wheat, eggs, sweet, I
need berries, barley, eggs, barley, eggs, where are the eggs?
Is there one egg here? Eggs, eggs, eggs, eggs, eggs.  1 piece of wheat Cut the
wheat and sweet berries on a chopping board with 5 eggs.  There was a place to
press the mark that looked like an axe, and I put it on the left side, and
there was flour.On the left side, there was probably an
ax mark, so I pressed it, and I
made wheat flour.  This is so
chaotic, I don't know. Is it
better to separate them? I don't
know, I don't know. I'm
cooking wheat and eggs together on a hot iron plate, and then there's a
little bit of flour. Oh, I
understand, I understand. I can
hear the frying.  No, I
couldn't hear it at all. No one was coming, but ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, they came. Okay, I'm sorry, I can't hear anything, right? Neru Kanamu-senpai, Asokamu-
chan, wait a minute
, Rai Hungry, me.
Oh,
oh,
three Potatoes, okay, okay,
thank you.
Well, first of all, let's cut the wheat one more time.
Well, let's cut the wheat on the chopping board. Ah,
wheat and sweet berry. Sweet
berry sweet berry.  Sweet berry Ayani,
Ya has it, I have it, I'm
going to change it, Emera, so cup shop, yeah,
shop Azuki is cutting sweet berries right now,
cutting them up,
yeah, uh,
putting in light berries, oh, wow,
wow, wow, wow, I'm sure I
can do it.  Wow, now you can fry eggs and comunico on a griddle
, but since it's a griddle, I wonder if it's
okay to say that.Iron griddle, grill,
grill, ah,
where do you put the wheat, huh, egg, egg,
something stronger  I
feel like there's something like a griddle over there.Maybe it's
made of flour.I'm opening it with this.Mumemme-
chan
egg Uh, let's put the E-egg in here, umm-
senpai.
pleas click hot play
Hare Okay, put it
in and it's gone, it's gone, it's gone, it's gone, it's gone, it's
gone, it's there, it's there, I've got it, I threw it, right
now throw it to me, throw it, throw it, it's nice, it's nice, it's nice, it's nice, it's pitcher,
it's pitcher.  One Wow Wawa
Wawa Light Click Light Click Light Click Light Click Light Click
Light Click here
Nice Nice Nice Nice
Nice I
made it with this. I made it so far I made it
just a pancake made of
pancakes that made pancakes.
Eh, don't serve it, um, this is the plating table. This, this, this, this, the sweet berry, the cut sweet berry, the cut sweet berry, um, this. It's so good that you can arrange it on the plate. Beet pancakes, oh, how about this? You
can see, oh, it's done. It's
really nice and delicious.  Yeah, it looks delicious, it's
delicious, it's cute
, it's cute, please give me that.
Sometimes we need coal, we need coal Yeah, we'll
grill it, we'll grill it, we'll grill it, we'll grill it, we'll grill it, we'll grill
it, we'll grill it, we'll grill it, we'll grill
it.  It's the one that guesses the uh-ka, and there's
only one spot where the uh-ka isn't known, and that's
probably the one that you can see in this colored box in front of you.  There
are 4 colors,
4 blocks, 4 blocks, uh, right now,
Iroha-chan is looking at it, and she's looking for what's missing,
right?  Let's try this. It's
difficult to explain, but the left arm is in Japanese.
First, the left arm is the upper left is orange. The upper right
is red. The lower left is red. This
is here. That means this is this. That's different. The upper left is here.
Orange orange.  The
top of the range light is the top of the light,
light up, yeah, red light,
down, right, left, left, down, red, red, red, right, right, bottom right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right.
Okay, one two, four,
that's okay. Well, I guess we'll come up with a strategy a little later.
Otherwise, we
might not be able to tell Mu-chan, so that's certainly smart. I
just found a genius, a genius, and a senior.  Did you just
know the colors? Is this a
genius? I saw something completely different.
What color is it? Well, what color is the answer? The
upper left is orange. The upper right is red. The lower left is
red. The right is red.  If you don't know what the bottom is and you know the color,
pink pink okay
nice oh nice nice nice look for that kind of thing Look for
that kind of
thing Chew I'll explain it to you a little later Oh yeah
Thank you Genius Thank you
Amo I'll defeat the monster.
Yes, I'll defeat the monster, but from now on, I'll
just have to defeat it.Semi-Ah and that thing.Well, I've heard that it doesn't seem to be able to attack allies.Even
if this
and that thing hit, it's PPVP, PVP, yeah.
PvP
Yes, you can hear the sound, yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah, I'm here, I'm going again.  It's
better to protect the princess alone. Yeah, yeah, okay, I see. Ah, I
see. The bow is here. It's okay.
Okay,
fight the monster. Peace, do your best and protect the princess. Nice, nice.
Nasuo. Next level 2. Ah, then this is also the princess.  There's only
one person to protect her and she's strong.Then
I'll protect the princess.A
bow might be strong.A bow is better.Acha, what is this?It's
dangerous.It's dangerous.Ah,
who are you?  Please, run away,
please, nice, nice, nice,
oh, I'm an old man who's last trusting. I can't force him. He's strong. Ah, where's my strength? If I fall, please call me and I'll come help you. Ah, okay, I'm dead. Thank you, okay, okay, where's the rest?
There's a magic guy upstairs too. There's a magic guy
upstairs. Wow, Wow. It might be better to go to the top first.
Oh yeah, but it's not
strong at all. It's nice, nice, nice.
Nana yeah yeah
yeah yeah
yeah nice oh wow nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice let's go back shall we go back o thank
you for your hard work go back come back come
back here I'm going back here please come back
oh but I'm not going back at all  We've been around for about 5 weeks, 5
weeks, 5 weeks are over, and we're
like, oh, it's a lie, it's a lie, it's a lie, it
's true.
Click right click Please right click Yes
Yes Yes
Eo
[Music]
Oh start Ah
Nonono cutting
Wacha entry
entry Re entry list Rio
Ah, how should I press it? It's
okay. It's okay already.
However, I was displaying everyone's icons on the stream to the number 4 person earlier,
so
could you please go back?
Sorry, I'm sorry.
Thank you, thank you. I
wonder if I'm getting it. I'll let you know.
Sorry, Solly,
thank you.  No, I needed a little strategy. I
needed some practice. Maybe I
don't need to be a princess. If I play while explaining it, I'm sure if I
can figure out the rules, I'll be fine. Well, maybe I'll
have to ask a Japanese person to do it for me.  Are you
going to do your best to speak in English? Well, I guess I can do some research on the English words I need,
so I'll give it a try. I
guess I'll try hard.
Maybe she's the good type. She's good
at playing Minecraft, so she's pretty good at dealing with enemies.
Minecraft is scary, so if she has a good sense of humanity
, maybe she'll try playing all princesses.
Maybe next time, yeah. Yeah,
yeah.  With Otis, I
want to go to the Gozarujiga line.Oki
Mase, Kibase, Holomen.Hunting
Aromeha, maybe
Holomen.Hunting is still being adjusted.It looks like yes, yes, I
understand.Yes,
but Holo member hunting
requires a lot of practice.  I don't think there's any need to practice.It's
clear
how much you know the members of Hololive.I think
everyone knows me who is doing that.Even
newcomers won't lose.It seems like newcomers won't
lose either.  What do you know about me
? I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I
apologized, I lost. I apologized right away. Um, the
battle against Kiba is a game where you fight in pairs,
so yes, decide on a pair by the day of the game.
Ah,
I see. I see. I see. I
don't think the trauma
of the two of them will come back to life, but no, that duo with the even numbers is not Touma at all. The one with the
numbers is traumatized.  What is that?
Yes, you can ask people to form groups of two.
Is it
okay
? I'm not going to participate, so I'll leave it to everyone. Well,
everyone will participate. I guess everyone should
participate.  Everyone participates
[laughter]
Well, we're going to participate as well. That
's right. Well, today is the
day. Now, for now, we
need someone who has to press that button. So let's take an
example and tell them how it's going to look.
Try using that example, and if you want
it, let's have it done with Azu-san and Iroha.
Well then, Az-san,
try right-clicking on the White Kiba Line and
take the answer.  I did that, and then I
found that riding club sitting on my hand.
Yes, that's right, so I asked the person who rides it to
take a look at it.
Wow, how strong is this? Iroha-
chan is nice. Riding on her head. Eh.  So,
you're
running around,
and Zuzu-chan is attacking, yes, it's attacking. I
see.OPERSON
Yes,
Allhor
[laughing]
Hor, they're
also punching each other, punching each other, and competing for the number of kills.Oh.
Even if you hit the number of kills, you
won't die just by getting hit, and I'm pretty sure there are only 3 hearts
attached. 3
haha, this will happen once you start the game. I
guess so, but
there's only one group.  So I probably won't be able to do it, but yeah, yeah, I'll
try one more group, then Yellow,
and then one more group, oh yeah, yeah, that's right,
senpai, please use me as a horse.I have no
choice but to do it then.Okay, let's
go and ride.
Hey, where did you go? I
can't lose to that Lerelet, right click. Now let's get that Kaela on the orchestra.
Hey, Kiara, I'm sorry, but I
need you to wait a minute.  It's
a little
weird.Right-click on an empty book.When you right-click while holding the book, it looks
like it becomes an elephant.There's a thick section.I
clicked on the block.What
should I press when I open the book?What should I press when I open the book?
[Music]
Oh, nice, and there's no white right now, so just
open this.
Open it, right-click while holding the book, and then
click on the block in the middle of white. Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa  Let
's go, let's
go, let's go, we're
fighting and we're fighting and we've got something. It's dangerous. It's dangerous. It's dangerous. It's dangerous. It's amazing. We did it. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Tomorrow I'll do my best and I'll go. Nice, I'm strong, I'm strong, I'm
the strongest.
This is good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's
good, it's good, it's good
[music]  Yayaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaan a
Fight
[Music]
It's all at the same time at the same time Wow will
beall
TE so 21 teams 21
teams 21 teams Yes, it's true, but the more you
swing your sword around, the more you can kill.It
feels like it's a good strategy.I
see.I see.  Surprisingly, it
seems like defeating a general will give you a good score, so I
feel like the general will probably become the leader of each group, Mio, Miko, Subaru, and so on.  It would
be great if you could use it in a match against one another.
Also, when one side is fighting with the other,
White
will beat up both of them and go on a fishing trip.
It's a bit of a strategy.  That
's right, so we all focused on each other, and we
all went to punch an octopus, and it
became a competition where we punched an octopus and crawled, and
before the actual event, we
had to decide on a pair of people.  That's what I'm thinking. I see. It's
okay to relax. It's okay.
There's a gorilla here. It's okay. There's a gorilla tomorrow. You
won't get killed, so it's okay.
Gorilla. Do you do it with the gorilla? Do you do it
with the gorilla? It's already decided.  I wo
n't leave. I'll come. I
say
yes. Well, I guess I'll go to Hunting. I
feel like I can't do it yet. I wonder if I can do it yet.
Well, I'll just tell you where it is. Yes, I'll
go.
All I need is some knowledge.  Here, let's get along, let's get along, let's just get along.
Friendly, this is me. Hunter, those
nipples are sticking out, but is it
okay for YouTube? Is it true that you say the neck? Is it
strong? I think it was bad after all.
Gozaru Yomi-senpai. Besides, it's pink.  It's the color,
but it's okay, it's pink, and it
's almost safe. By the way, in English,
those nipples are Nepos, Neponels are round,
Nils Nils are round, and Bars Nils.
There are two, so it's a figure. I
see, that's right. If you get one, you'll
get 2?  Well, that's
not it. No, that's not it. Isn't that what it's like?
When the actual Susu event starts, how will it be, who will
stand where, and what will it be like? Good evening.
Well, for example, the representative of the red team will be here.
Three hunters from the catching side
appear, but the red one appears.When the
hunter comes out, the red team is all
off, so the white team and yellow team all
participate, leaving only one
grouper.Hunter.  There are 3 people, ah, 3
people, ah, 1 team, 1 person each, 6 people per red team,
but I'll divide it into 2 times.
Sometimes the yellow team and the white team are on the run, so there
are 3 red, red, uh, and all the other white and yellow,
uh,
TE explanation, thank you
, uh, uh, the question will come up. oh, for example,
but...  Among these people, there are
people who catch animal poops by doing something like "Eroaaa" or "Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa" and to me I see that's what I see.So
for example if you
say Ajakana-tan I guess you can use it by right-clicking and an
item will appear.
What's with the rope? It's
not Kula, it's the lead that catches it. It's the lead.
Yes, it's the lead. If you right-click on the lead, the
rope will be attached to it and it
will take you away.  I can't run away anymore,
uh, I can't run away,
uh, right-click on this hunting catch, uh, and it
'll determine whether this cage is uh, an animal or not.
[Music]
Oh
Do
Yes
If it's a hit, it's not.If it's a miss, it
's not.If you catch it, it's heaven.Is this okay?  No, it's okay, it's an animal. That's probably
okay. Who are you?
Everyone's not an animal, so
remember that. Angel Angel My
Angel No Animal No Animal
No
Animal
Regarding the question that came up,
it's like a game where a hunter has to catch something. Yeah, it's interesting.
Oh, I'm sorry, I just have one more question.
Do people other than you run around here? Oh, because you run.  Escape,
oh,
oh, oh, there's so many things to do, so you can use things like climbing buildings and things like that to escape.Escape, oh, I see.  The
lead
gets kicked and the lead kicks in. Oooh,
that's interesting. It's fun. It looks like it's going to be fun. I want to do it soon.
Instigator
[Music]
[Laughs] I'm
really looking forward to it. I'm looking forward
to it. So that's it for the explanation of the competition and the
decision to compete.  Thank you, thank you
, thank you, I
really respect you, you're a
good person who worked really hard.Thank
you very much.I
don't have any questions.Ah,
yeah,
any
be, it's okay, thank you.Senpai is
busy, but I'm going to sleep properly.
Please, Nemi-senpai Yes, yes, I'm
at work.Aren't you sleeping while working?Let's go to
sleep, no, sleep, sleep, sleep, it's
okay.Yo, it's good, thank you, thank you.  Now,
Kakan-san, or should I say, I'm fine, even if I'm gone, it seems like it'll be fine. We'll
practice here for now.
Then, the broadcast will be disbanded here. If
you're going to continue, you can continue, you
can continue, you can continue, it's fine.  It's ok to do it.
Oh, then once you're done, do you want to disband? Oh
yes, practice and
practice.
Thank you, keep up the good work,
Yunex
Star.
Hey, right now, I'm talking in a
place where only the listeners can hear, and I can't hear them.
Thank you very
much. It was a lot of fun. I
also had a chance to seeu Gorillade at the Namine Sports Day, and I was able to meet the
newcomers.  Well, I'm
looking forward to seeing you at the highest level.
Well, I'll check it one more time,
and Kore-chan made it for me. For the time being, it
seems like it's confirmed now.  It looks
like this.I don't
think there will be any changes, but I'm sure there was an entry,
so if something were to happen, it would probably be on the day of the event.I feel
like everyone has changed.  She's a
cute, beautiful girl, so
there's a chance that Katas will be taken away.It's
okay, but on the day
of the call, it looks
like the callers will be divided into two groups, so I'm
still not sure if I'll get a spot.  I do
n't know who will take it, the person who wants to
take it.It's still a bit of a mystery as to who will take it.Also, the cat is
also cute.It's
cute.It's cute.It's cute.My junior is so cute that I can't help but want to
eat it.  I'll
stop here for now.
Thank you everyone for streaming.
If Katas takes the frame, I
'll do my best to use everyone's cameras. I just couldn't
get that in. Opti. What is that
? That zooming thing is in the cat's
sports hall.  The version is not out
yet, so I'm sorry, but this time there's no zoom. Why don't you use a MOD? It
'll get as close as you can.
That's how Kia will do its
best this time. I'll update the MOD by the time it gets closer, or that day.  Once the
version is released, I'll have to
download it a little bit quickly,
but it might be a little transparent,
but I'm wondering if there's a way to communicate
as much as possible with everyone overseas.  I
'm thinking about that as we go along, so it's Saturday this week, so
it's tomorrow, and the day after tomorrow, so I
hope you all have fun.  But Sane Kaneda's voice is the only one I
can hear, so I wish she'd come out with a follow-up. I don't want to. She was really good. I thought she was talented,
but I thought it was a one-chan nabe follow-up. I'd
like to agree on Princess.  Oh, how cute
. It's so cute. It's so cute to be standing next to you. So,
see you soon, everyone. Thank you for your support.
Then, I'll play the ending. Thank you for today. Goodbye,
everyone.
Bye-bye-bye
[Music]
Bye,
come on
[Music]
Thank you everyone, bye-bye Hanakaze in the room There's
still a little bit of splash left,
but it's gotten a lot better, so please everyone please do the
recording.The recording was also completed successfully.  I
've been posting a little less frequently,
but thanks to that, I'm
getting better, so don't worry. I
don't have a fever. Thank you everyone. Take a good rest. Good night.
[Music]
Bye.