[Music]
KY
hello can you hear me I feel like I'm
kind of quiet
this
[Music]
hello is the freaking VOD up yet or not
so Random to start off with that
question but I don't think it's up yet
right I mean not that not that we're
going to watch it now but I'm wondering
if we can watch it tomorrow at
all starting I wrote starting tweet is
it not going through
again Mama
M there it is
yeah sometimes I write a tweet and if I
then close the app like not close but
like minimize the app then it just it's
forever in that like grade
out like still sending phase why am I
the only one who has this issue anyway
and sometimes it's not even that uh it's
just it's just not even I can't even see
that gray still sending uh face not even
that I can see sometimes and I just get
surprised by tweets being and then
sometimes they're
double I feel like man I'm I'm so
looking forward to going back home and
uh streaming with my normal streaming
stuff cuz they have a really dope mixer
and all that here but like it's
everything is confusing and every time I
come here even if I was here yest today
I have to set up everything from scratch
I have to set up all my OBS [\h__\h] that's
why it looks like this
today just using like some random
Graphics from a free website
I have to set up all that set up I have
to set up the microphone I have to set
up the the sound the deskt sound and
then I can't even balance the sound the
same way that I I want unless I go I
don't know change everything up but like
I don't know how it's so confusing every
time it takes me like like also to log
into everything H takes me like half an
hour 40 minutes to set up my stream and
the reason I was late is actually not
because I was late Gemma was late okay
but sometimes people are late some times
that happens and that's okay we're all
just human you know we're all just human
people can be late sometimes it is what
it is but my stream I have a
meeting uh I think at like 100
p.m. uh
so uh yeah Jemma is human Jemma is not a
chicken I
guess yeah so I I we can't stream for
too long that's the issue with being
late that uh the stream won't be too
long but that's probably fine because
I uh yesterday during the stream I
yapped yapped yapped right and that uh I
was I'm I'm healing I'm in my healing
process uh and the yippity Yap was okay
would have been okay but then I met in
the evening
with
Pandora I think
[Laughter]
yes right yeah we're
Pandora I met with
Pandora
um as she told me that I met she told me
I met
Pandora uh and and then we yapped so
hard
because I we went to like a family
restaurant that's uh that was way more C
than I thought it was going to
[Music]
be the a taka thank you 36 months
everything around me was so everybody
was yapping and so I had to Yap even
harder and had to Yap so loud and um it
was that that's not good for my throat
obviously oh [\h__\h] ah [\h__\h]
whatever H whatever I met both of them
anyway yeah yeah yeah yesterday yeah
whatever I met both of them she's
confusing me uh so yeah it was so loud
and then I noticed like man I want to
talk to her obviously but like it's so
loud around us and my throat hurts so
much from
screaming and um
yeah uh now I feel like I'm not helping
myself for yapping so much so it's good
if the stream will be
[Laughter]
short
wait
[Laughter]
[\h__\h]
sorry time confusion I met that girl I
met the like like last week but yeah
whatever let's not make it worse
um so we're going to
play we're going to play uh Hol
[Music]
and because I thought I was never going
to play the S game again
[Music]
uh
H they added which means they added the
Wawa so I'm obligated to play it I'm I'm
being held at gunpoint there's a G to my
head I'm being forced I'm being held
hostage by the
SAS
um so yeah also I am Dau don't worry
because of the uh the earthquake um if I
wasn't d I probably wouldn't be tweeting
anyway um thank you for your concern but
it's fine like there's earthquakes all
the time but this one was a bit more uh
Stronger Than I don't know maybe it's
even maybe it is the strongest that I've
ever experienced which is interesting
cuz I lived in Japan for three years
before and uh there was an earthquake
that so when people say say like there
was an earthquake it's like I want to
tell you guys there's earthquakes every
day in Japan several ones but they're
usually like pretty small and like not a
big deal
um so the
Y yeah yeah for the Tokyo area it it it
was I think pretty
big it's pretty big but like nothing
fell down or so in in my room I was like
sleeping I was like maybe maybe I was
half asleep at that point I was going to
wake up soon anyway and then I I felt it
shaking pretty strong I'm like huh
that's pretty strong yeah but I lived in
Japan for 3 years and like I don't think
I've cuz I I never got alerts on my
phone and I've been told seemingly if
the I think if the source of the
earthquake is pretty far from
you like so that it's like really far
like maybe even different prefecture
then I guess uh it seems like you may
not get the notification but this time
the source was closer I guess so I got a
notification for the first time on my
phone I no
so yeah yeah the
epicenter uh but it was table don't
don't don't worry guys uh it's yeah it's
just like oh it's oh it's shaking whoa
and then the the
hotel there was like an announcement
that was just like after already calmed
down a little bit the announcement in
the hotel was like in Japanese and in
English was saying like oh don't worry
no need to evacuate there was an
earthquake but there's no need to
evacuate uh it seems is fine so yeah
that's what they
say I'm just confused that this is the
first
time so it must have been I'm trying to
think back cuz like the three years that
I lived in Japan some of those years are
very long time ago I don't really
remember any strong earthquake while I
was living
here
Sorry God damn
it I'm feeling better with every day but
yeah as I said I Yap too much and it
makes it worse but yesterday that dinner
really was really not good for my throat
but I
I don't have time and on any other day
to meet this girl um AA so I was like I
gotta I gotta you
know I heard you had pizza yeah oh
bloody uh you could feel the mucus in my
Thro let's
[Music]
go yeah yeah Pizza in the
cheapest
um
Italian chain restaurant in Japan so
cheap we had two pizzas but okay they're
small size even I can finish the whole
pizza that's amazing and I still didn't
feel full so it's like a small fin Pizza
um and I had a salad and she had a small
like you know one person pizza but like
really not like what what you think in
America is a small Pizza it's just like
Japanese size small
pizza but still like for me that that's
a good amount for eating Al Pizza alone
this perfect size perfect size
pizza so a little salad a pizza two
pizzas and uh she got drink bar like all
you can drink and I just I just got
water all of that
for we ordered more afterwards cuz I was
like Hy this is not why we got to we got
to spend more money in US
Dollars eight eight US dollar eight for
two pizzas one salad and one all you can
drink holy [\h__\h] it's so
cheap yeah eight [\h__\h] dollars I mean
this is Al the conversion I guess being
crazy right now but like the the Yen
being cheap as always but
wow wow I mean it's not the kind of
pizza that you think you get get at like
you know an Neapolitan restaurant or the
kind of pizza you get at Domino's or
whatever no no no no no it's a pretty
thin pizza but you know for for a small
cute lady like me this one pizza is
enough to
feel like the main course relatively
feeling I still had a dessert normally
normally I wouldn't have a space for
dessert but this was like a good amount
that I would be able to eat a dessert
too perfect yeah yeah I'm just Tangen
thing man not even playing the
game where's that lady here
hello for that amount you could get a
second and take no we had to it was two
pizzas for two pizzas all you can drink
and uh one small salad for
$8
crazy so if you guys want cheap uh like
it's not or like you know it's not like
you know the the pizzas you get in Italy
okay but if you want cheap Italian food
that's is pretty tasty go to
CIA CIA
CIA but it was so crowded it was so
loud
yeah really C it y y y y y y y
y
Pyle they must make money by having a
high volume of people eat there yeah
yeah for sure yeah there's like so many
like students like young people who go
to SI area the whole place was filled
with young
people
younglings tiramisu is my recommendation
for the dessert ah the thing is I don't
like tiramisu because of the coffee
flavor it's a TI if it's a Tiramisu that
doesn't have the coffee flavor then I
like it hi Ora saw you
yesterday Ora check your check your
Discord saw you yesterday
Ora uh what was I saying oh yeah so I
don't like coffee
tiu uh so for the desserts the one that
I order at Celia usually is there's like
this like um puffy bread covered in
cinnamon cinnamon cinnamon cinn cinnamon
sugar and then you get like some vanilla
ice cream with it and you eat it
together and the bread is warm though
so bread as in actually no I think it's
pizza
dough I think actually
P glazed no not glazed sugar sprinkle
lots of sh shinnamon
[Laughter]
sugar
it was a lovely evening yes yes indeed
mhm and yeah y y y y y y y y y yapping
is dangerous yapping is very dangerous
guys are you here to see me play the
game are you here to listen to listen to
my
yapping maybe I should hold you all
hostage with me playing the
game yeah both B both okay so I uh this
this this is this is the first time I
play this
so can you hear
this the music how do I get into H
because there's like different T ah
event ah wait are we not
permanent I'm in the game it's
me hi w
hi how exciting oh my god oh the music
stopped oh cuz I tapped out okay BM is
[Music]
loud your your mama is
loud uh in my
bed um sorry okay I'll turn it
down is this bad
[Music]
[Laughter]
by the way I was I dreamt of going to
the males but I never got there we just
like got to the the sea plane takeoff
place I I forgot who I was going with I
was going with two more H life members I
think and something we we kind of got
into a fight and then I like right
before we would board the CPL and I was
like I'm not talking to you anymore I
don't care anymore about you we're we're
just going to go to the males and then
I'm going to ignore you for this like
whole trip no no no I think it was I
think one of them was Kobo
maybe the other one I don't
remember this you know dreams
immediately
disappear uh so it was about going to
the moldes but I was really not happy
about
it please don't say Amen no no no no no
couldn't be amen could never be no no
no they hate each
other I don't know I don't remember
there was some reason why I was pissed
off but I don't
remember
uh yeah I got a clip recommended
something about me ah the drink teasing
ah I right I did that is that what I cuz
I didn't watch it yet yeah I had a I had
a warm drink and she right cuz I now I
remember than cute yeah yeah cuz like
she was like generally just kind of
seemingly freezing because you know
Indonesia is warm at the moment and
uh she was freezing and I'm like it's
not not a big deal I was I just had a
warm drink because uh of my fro being
strained and uh then like I just I don't
know I wanted to like interact with her
so I gave her my drink just so that she
would be like oh you have a warm drink
uh and then she really like liked
holding on to it CU it was warming her
but then I took it away from her cuz I
was like I I I think I I took it I said
oh I'm I just need to drink a sip cuz my
throat hurts you'll get it back then she
gives it to me cuz otherwise she
wouldn't have given it to me she was
like no no no Mommy and I'm like give it
to me my throat hurts so I drank and I
didn't give it back to her anymore and
then she looked like she looked really
angry at me she was like give me Mommy
and I'm like no no now it's mine
again this is how you get back anything
from your child or
perhaps your
pet you got to give them the illusion
that they're going to get it back yes
give them the illusion maybe even
replace it with something else trick
them trick
them
yeah it's pretty fascinating though
these hot drinks in Japan I freaking
love them I have one with me now but it
already is cooling
down oh it is already cold
damn yeah but I have fro candy so I'm
okay uh so so so so so
so Yuka maybe we play the game now let's
see it's been a while since I played
this oh it's a dog oh my my God cute it
looks like a
marshmallow wait ah oh she doesn't like
move with me I have to like is this
normal she doesn't move with the
mouse I just like Drop it like this or
can I ah wait I have to
ah sorry I never played this oh so we
start with the
[Music]
mascot
cute
okay I don't know what combines with
what yet but usually it's small to big
and the duck looks like yeah duck looks
like yeah yeah yeah yeah hold on we're
just going to chill guys we're not going
to try too hard ah
C oh my God cute right I I I'm so happy
I didn't get spoiled about all of this I
didn't know I didn't know there would be
mascots
K wait when does it turn into us
[Music]
maybe whatever whatever we're not doing
try hard
gaming
so no oh wait wrong I I looked at
oh
way oh my
God exciting yes the penguin K she's not
officially part of horory and she's not
going to be amused by this but okay
but I guess her mascot is a a penguin
nonetheless or what why I'm ashamed that
I don't know
but if her mascot is a penguin
then that's it I thought this is Louis's
mascot this
one she has
two wait there's two Lou mascots in this
game well but then it shouldn't just be
Ki then it should be the Duma chicken to
too okay Gano is just like the general
mascot of her like
Ki is like the general mascot for
me but I think in in the in the horory
song where there I think there's mascots
in that mv2
right I don't think wasn't that just GMO
in the in the MB also guys do you
remember when Lou when Lou
um debuted it and I saw the two little
BPS on top of Gano those two and I was I
made an edit of those like really
exhausted red crying eyes on top of
them uh that was a cusa
moment I still think it fits
perfectly oh the owl is so
cute so so wait that's M's that's just
M's
owl what what do what do M's fans look
like again God I don't remember [\h__\h]
when I when you tell me I'll
remember oh it did okay in that case
that that is her
fans is it no wait so yeah for M her
mascot is the paper bag or is it
or so
confusing when I think of my mascot I
got to be honest I don't even really
think much about Ki I I think
immediately about you guys being my
mascot I don't
know Yahoo double waited double
waited a so B There we go we got our
first human bird bird bird bird bird
bird
bird bird
dis duck duck
[Music]
penguin that is so exciting for me right
now I'm so happy this makes me more
happy than I thought it would I was
pretty indifferent about uh the game
like until until h came into the game
now I care about it a
lot cute doing great so thank you I'm
just like I don't know I'm just chilling
I'm just chilling this is now not so
nice oh okay wait we can do this uh so
this oh double duck a [\h__\h] a [\h__\h] and
there we go and there we go I'm the win
and it's a win it's a win they bounce so
much do they are the physics like pretty
close to the actual SOA
game I haven't played it in a long time
but it seems pretty pretty similar
physics seems like it to
me yeah but like when you drop them I
feel like they they bounce a bit more
than the fruit
[Music]
does
got to get used to that cuz you try to
drop things accurately and it just goes
wherever okay here we have a
chance ah come
on come on come on oh come on come on
come on come on
baby you you I I learned new
vocabulary come on now you wee little
shite you wee little shite come on now
ow you we little
shite why did I learn that is because I
watched uh I watched a movie historical
let's go medieval history movie I found
a new one it was a new not necessarily
new movie but I found it on Netflix I
think it was called Outlaw King it's
about uh you know again Scottish
English kings getting at each other's
fruits and uh yeah then some someone
there said to a little child you we
little shite I was like that sounds like
you little [\h__\h] just in
Scottish it's about Bruce the Bruce
Bruce
the what Bruce the the the the
what
Bruce the no no Bruce was the ending of
the Robert the Bruce Bruce no Robert
Robert the Bruce yeah uh was really
interesting kind of short though um yeah
he was king of Scots from 1306 to his
death in 1329 and this was like the
story about how he became King King of
Scotland uh while some we little shite
on the English side is trying to [\h__\h]
everything up and all that yeah his his
wife is really interesting to me
Elizabeth came back as is history lesson
I love talking about like British
history
yeah I love talking about that kind of
stuff even though like I watch this
stuff and then when I try to tell you
guys about it I I I lack the skills to
properly explain it and get it across
I'm so sad I wish I could retell these
stories
properly I love historical women I
do cuz like she was so loyal I was like
I I would have probably not handled it
the same way as her like she was being
held hostage
um by the English king and his son his
son is a [\h__\h] [\h__\h] and
um uh she she and the child of uh Robert
the Bruce who was his child from his
first marriage uh the wife died the
first one and this is the new wife right
and they haven't even been together for
that long and all that and and yet she
already has found love for him and all
that and she's great and then she's
being held hostage right and uh like
it's not looking so good for her husband
the Scottish King because um they keep
on getting uh what's the word like
surprised uh ambushed all the time and
there's just losing losing people all
the time so it's not looking good right
but then it's looking better then then
they learned their lesson from being
ambushed so many times and it's getting
better but she doesn't know that and um
so the English uh Prince I guess
whatever his name was forget him he's
not he's he's a we little shite um he's
like okay okay okay I'm going to get the
queen to renounce her title uh even like
because they're doing so good right now
on the Scottish side site we need to
side we need to do something about this
so he goes to her and um he gives her
like this thing to sign where she would
renounce her uh title and uh also like
say the marriage was not valid and
whatever and she's like she notices
that uh him making her do that implies
that that he must be feeling pressured
and stressed about how Robert probably
uh is like catching up and like you know
pushing
forward and that puts him in a desperate
situation so that's why he's trying to
get her to sign that and renounce her
title and so I was thinking cuz like
he's like really threatening her and I
was thinking you could just like
renounce the there so they treat you
better and then just like I mean he'll
be killed eventually just just
afterwards like get married again or
whatever like but no she stays strong
with her loyalty she doesn't sign she
says I can't sign it and her parents
they're also there they're like girl why
don't you just sign it because like
you're going to be like uh thrown into
even a worse prison H and she doesn't
sign it and then she gets like hung in
like a little like prison is container
over a cliff for several days
and she's like [\h__\h] but then she gets
eventually freed and reunited with uh
Den King of Scotland officially Robert
the Bruce uh is this out yes outlooking
yeah I just watch it like two days
ago so she she stand she stood firm even
though I mean I feel like the easier way
would have just been yeah okay I'll sign
it whatever with in the back of your
mind thinking whatever like he's going
to die I don't I'm just going to either
marry him again or nobody will know
about this and we we were just married
all this time for all that you know and
blah blah blah blah blah yep yep yep yep
sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry I love I love British
is oh oh Pop like popcorn
cute cute nice
too but they're all over the place I
don't think this is necessarily good
placement explaining these things in
Emma paint I don't think that's going to
go so
well Hon's arm is about to break she
like k k k please let me drop this
freaking heavy ass
bird ah see how it just like goes
somewhere else oh oh oh
M wait
I'm the last one I think in this circle
I don't think I'll ever see
myself unless this is way easier than
the S game but
like took me this long to get
M but she's so cute look at
her so
cute [\h__\h] there's the penguin well I'm
going to put that one here put this one
here um put this
here put that one here
too put this one here and then the next
owl as
wellie cute nice nice oh it even like
lifted it up I think I like that
maybe oh cute nice it went right in
there we like that we like that now this
little duck I don't know if I want to
drop it in there cuz next is
[Music]
hooie and most of I was
yapping well yeah but this is just the
second human looking appearing bird that
we see so far there's still a couple
more
you know I was really happy yesterday
talking to
AA because Aura went she told me she
Aura went to the Hol
Fest um she told me that and uh she had
a lot of fun she
said and and she she told me had a great
time she told me that there were girls
screeching for me she heard it in person
and she knows the the girls that were
screeching for
[Music]
me and uh yeah she told me all about the
experience of you know seeing it uh like
in the audience POV and she also told me
and this kind of makes me really happy
cuz I was I was wondering if it just
seems like this to me because um well
I'm kiaha but she told me that had like
at this event in Japan besides maybe uh
B's fans she said that kfp are like the
most present uh like like how to say
like you guys are just like you're
present you seem like you're a lot you
seem very you stand out obviously but
like not because of the color
necessarily but just because of the
amount of people you are like I think a
lot of kfp we may not have the the
biggest fan base you know but some
somehow still you guys are so dedicated
that you show up even from overseas come
to all all over to Japan all the way
over here to you know support me and you
do this also with like you know going to
Germany and all that so Ora was saying
like how how did you say it how please
explain
it seems like from how I take it it
seems like you guys are just like very
very strong like in your presence uh and
it seems like like out of the
English-speaking uh uh
fans the kfp may have been one of the
biggest fans who came for their Oshi one
of the biggest amount of fans who came
for their Oshi
uh overseas and all that you know what I
mean I don't know how to say this you
know do you know what I'm trying to
say you guys are just there you know
you're just there now there okay very
dedicated supportive and full on ready
to support very passionate when I went
to the concert I saw so many kfp fans
yeah I thought it was like maybe just my
imagination but yeah and she was saying
even on the days where uh you know I
wasn't I mean actually I was on both
days kind of but I guess like like uh
cuz I how to say even I would say like
day one was my main day and even on the
other days uh there she said she saw a
lot of kfp H representing me let's go
let's
go we strive to just be there yeah and
obviously like absolutely no problem if
we can't go all the way to freaking
other continent to represent kfp like no
blame you know that's crazy that's in
the first place in the first place
that's already like crazy to go that far
and not an easy thing to do even if you
want to do it [\h__\h] why don't you touch
why don't you
touch yeah but still there's like so
many of you that go that far and yeah
this year was kind of crazy on that
regard
tada
wait to hear the the screams in the
vud yeah they're going to be really
clear the screaming girl tweeted about
it I think there were was there several
cuz I heard one really loud clear one in
the beginning but also one in the end
and AA was telling me she knows the one
that screamed in the
end I saw on Twitter they were giving
gifts yeah KY was like giving out things
again uh I feel like kfp does that a
lot they were going off
yeah am I popular to girls I wonder like
out of all of thean I'm sure I'm not the
number one popular with girls at all but
I wonder how the ratio is if I'm if I
have one of the higher ratios I wonder
there's certain people that uh just have
bigger girl ratios ah [\h__\h] what is
happening I'm not doing so well okay
let's use the old sua tactics St from
back in the day oh no
so why cuz I'm a girl oh where is a girl
confirmed guys
y girls on the internet are not real
cannot be be true proof or it didn't
happen all
[Music]
wrong
actually that pink that Hue of pink
makes her look a little bit like coyot
like a mix of Lou and
coyot that was
crazy you've seen me ey ear you can you
can confir I cannot confirm you have
lady Parts actually I cannot confirm
that I did not see your lady
Parts time to go to onen
guys someone um I saw a reply on my
Twitter yesterday please don't worry
like I I I went um in one way I I went
with narissa to the Onan even though I
feel uncomfortable with Onan because in
one way because I want to be a good sfai
and another way because I um also felt
like I kind of want to be able to enjoy
onen more so I need to get over my my
stupid issues um also I just I just
wanted her to have a good time in in
Japan and I also don't didn't want her
to hang out too much with other
people but I did tell her I did tell her
though um that like you know we already
like hang out so much before so if you
want to like hang out with people you
haven't hung out with
yet then feel free to you know say sorry
Wawa I don't want to go to the on with
you or sorry wa I don't want to have
breakfast uh in bed with you whatever
don't worry I would understand if you
would prefer to use the short amount of
time that you have to get to know people
you don't know so well but she said no
no you know she was like self-conscious
again and being like ah nobody nobody
wants to you know and I'm like that's
not true you just got to you know ask
them I'm sure they would love to hang
out with you whoever really
everybody everybody honestly but she's a
little bit self-conscious about it so
I'm just happy I can give her the the
sense of security that she gives me in
in terms of like I know I enjoy hanging
out with her she
knows no she knows I have a good time
with her I know she has a good time with
me so you know why not be with someone
you feel comfortable with you
know but yeah I did tell her like you
know feel freid to be like sorry wa I
don't want to go with you I want to go
with someone
else I would understand you
know cuz she wasn't there for very long
have't picked up any family of the STP
to it's funny that you say that because
I think I think uh JMA
snuck fan into my back wait let me check
this looks like
family what looks like it she just like
without saying anything she's not oh
wait
no it's the pens oh they're cute they're
tiny uh if you don't know my
sister my sister really wanted pens a
certain amount of certain certain type
of
pens from Japan that like it's some
they're so cute holy
moly wait do you want to
see they're so tiny I thought they would
be
[Music]
bigger is there on the plastic my credit
card Reflection by any
chance all my social security number
more no I thought this was fan mail and
she was sneaking into my bag
[Music]
they're so cute I kind of want some
too I don't know my my sister it's not
like she actively researches like
Japanese things and Japanese culture and
all that um but somehow she found these
pens that she really wanted I
guess let me show you I kind of consider
wanting them to they're like pretty
small they're not normal pen
[Music]
size can I show this I think
so this is fine yeah
look they're cute oh they're okay they
come in like these pastel
colors and uh apparently the free set
and the four set they have different uh
ball Point sizes I think yeah but
they're fake they're small and fake this
is like you don't even even have any
size comparison so it's hard to tell I
think but they're kind of thick and
small yeah you've seen them apparently
they won some award
what I want them
too yeah my sister was so excited to
um know that I can get them for her and
that they're not even
expensive
pen keep the orange one yeah I like the
orange it's like a like a not I uh
poking Orange it's a like a brownish
nice Orange not that I poke your eye at
all
but yeah uh I forgot wait what would
they
called oh the all the colors have nice
names too one is called banana one is
called yogurt they're called oi uni uni
ball
[Music]
one from Mitsubishi
pencils yeah maybe I'll order some more
I don't want to order from Amazon again
I wonder if I can buy them in the
store where should I put this cuz
there's a hootsie coming next let's just
see what happens here here oh yes yes
go oh that just reminded me the way I
me and Aura were like aggressively
loudly yapping just because everybody
else around us was so loud and then the
people who were seated next to
us AA do you remember that really threw
me off and like kind of annoyed me the
girl on the table next to us suddenly
goes like really
loudly to her friend and I'm like for a
moment I was like maybe we were loud but
I look over and she she notices that I
look over and she still really loudly
aggressively goes
like like the loudest sh I've ever heard
but I thought it was towards us but we
we stopped actively yapping and she
still continued that like and looked at
her friend while doing it so I was like
what the [\h__\h] is going
on stop
Shing like what is wrong with
you oh it's okay she was just loudly
deflecting you should have shushed her
back no I don't think I first thought
and was concerned about maybe it was
towards me but then yeah it didn't seem
like it after observing her shushing it
was so loud what the
hell
yeah uh yeah she was louder than us by
doing the
sh
yeah yeah yeah that that's it do be like
that sometimes okay you go
here
oh we need the Lou to touch
eventually
close
oh I feel so good man it's been a while
since I played S Type game oh then I
should have put that over there I just
feel so good when they come by
oh I just feel so and I'm feeling
[Music]
good
wait wait we saw we saw m
we
we me wait is way the
biggest false
advertisement false
[Music]
advertisement I mean it makes way more
sense I and advertisement I thought why
did they make me the biggest I'm not the
biggest uh but I think they're going
going by height
then right like actual like height and
but because I saw it in the
advertisement I thought they made it it
made me the biggest in the advertisement
and and therefore I thought in the game
too because uh maybe because I'm the
leader I thought I was the biggest in
the
game oh is it it's that baa size oh wait
wait Lou would be bigger if it was about
height
wait is it
again huh M wait they put M as the
smallest Subaru as the second
smallest did Subaru have bigger B wait
no no no Subaru was the
first right that pops up M was a second
okay that makes more sense I think
then it was ruie then me I
never really thought about whether I
have bigger BBA than
Louie I never looked at it like that we
must be really close because I never
thought about
that let me
see oh pretty normal size I think you
never think about it because her legs
are just so
mesmerizing Prett normal size I guess
apparently I have bigger
ones who would have
thought
honestly horon is not about that hor is
not about
Bubba hor is about fun and International
friendship and um cute and nice voices
we have great
vocalists we about silliness and
dorkiness that's what we
represent um
so don't think too much about a b size
okay okay thank you uh but I'm just so
happy I got a kiaha
h
that's
that's all that's
[Music]
wait
[\h__\h] God and
now
just that's not what I'm trying to
do that's not the goal but it looked
funny so guys so guys so go look I have
new head I replaced my head I I feel
more comfortable like this this head is
nice I I'll keep
it
oh how you guys doing this is takanasi
Ki waa with a new head I know I look
different but this is just how I was
born please accept me for who I am thank
[Laughter]
you
cute cute maybe I should stream like
this I love it it's me it's me recognize
me I'm just constantly winking
now big head no balanced
head I right recognize that but anyway
you mean the Hat rain hi
[Music]
wa wa I'm still trying to get you
apparently you're the biggest totally
it's about height right surely it's
about
height would be a little bit uh
disrespectful if it was about anything
else it is is it is it I mean maybe it
is it could be both maybe it applies in
both ways I mean I feel like it could be
both way did you try did you play the
holot toi uh Edition
yet just going to play like this no I
moved
no I can't I can't do anything but like
90 and all that hold 39 you have to
this is the first time I'm
playing
uh it's free by the way guys it's even a
browser game so easy easy easy wait
reset that was fun that was
fun yeah in OBS I can only do like 90 90
or
180 I wish I could do like a more free
free uh turn whatever I wish I could do
that ah okay actually I don't mind you
going in there if you manage it then you
can combine with the other
one oh damn it ah oh oh okay there you
go she did it maybe you can go
[Music]
here there's got to be a plugin for that
probably I didn't I don't
really the way it pops it's so
exciting we're like popcorn BBS popcorn
chicken I don't really understand why
there's a need in this world for popcorn
chicken
W but yeah it is what it is a lot of
people like popcorn chicken I don't
understand yo ah I pushed it back down
that's okay that's
[Music]
okay oh
oh oh
[Music]
yeah by the way I've seen
complaints about the lack of armor
tangents yesterday and I would like to
publicly apologize for the lack of
Desperately necessary am
tangents um fact is I did not get to
hang that much with her during both like
when we were exploring the
Expo there was not much
interaction uh although one time when I
was like being a loner while everybody
was running around signing
standies uh I just sat down on one of
those like uh like beach chairs that you
maybe guys also saw that there were like
beach chairs I just sat down there I was
like I'm feeling really not social today
and there was another one and then Amma
came by and she's like oh and she sat
down next to me on the beach chair for a
little bit for a little moment so that
was nice but now besides that we didn't
have that much interaction but um I want
to say am was really sweet she gifted
all all of
us uh or at least all of
Ian um I don't know if she gave it to ID
but she gifted all of us like little
pretty
starshaped uh relatively thick uh stones
and all of them were like like I think
they were some legit
gems mine was like
green mine was like greenish green like
uh wait a moment
like a light green though it's not an
amethyst right that would be so funny
amethist no that's purple what could
that be we were like I was asking her
which one could that be oh Kyla got one
too so that that was okay turquoise I
don't think it was turquoise Jade ah
Jade no not it's it was more not like
this kind of green oh maybe it could
actually no it could be another that
look at it there's some lighter ones
yeah maybe it was Jade wow yeah we got
all like star shaped ones and at first
she gave me one uh me and the myth memb
she gave us one and then she was like oh
never mind sorry those are the wrong
ones she had apparently she had special
ones for for you know the myth members
like they had to be specifically these
particular ones she had different colors
you know and there there was I don't
know why maybe they're more special but
she you had to switch it
out and give give me different
one cute gift from Amy Amy gave me a
gifty yeah so sweet I'm going to cherish
it it's really
pretty so that is a thing and also okay
I'm I'm trying hard here
guys
uh
you know I was like CH chatting with
Amma and I was kind of aware because she
like wrote about it I think also um I
think in the community post like she
several times I think she uh expressed
her concern about
um about earthquakes and she even like
researched like uh you know about you
know buildings and all that uh so I felt
kind of kind of bad that she was so
worried about it but then she she told
me when she left when I said goodbye to
her she she said she told me to be like
careful and all that uh and I was like
oh don't worry like I there's one thing
that I'm more worried about than
earthquakes by far and that is uh the
airplanes that I'm flying with all of
those airplanes cuz I've been on a lot
of plane rides these days to Canada uh
uh North America several times I went on
connecting flights and all that and then
back to Europe and then again several
connecting flight so I get like all
kinds of airplanes I think one of the
ones I was on was 787 but I think the
787 is
fine uh I think I was supposed to go on
to but then sadly it's change I was
supposed to go on like a big big new one
that has like two floors I never been on
a plane that has two floors I
think I forgot what it was could it be a
380 I think but that wait that one is
not a boing though yeah
A380 I was going to go on that one I was
excited because When selecting the the
the flights it said that this one is a
really new airplane and I because I've
been watching so many like uh like you
know business class reviews and all of
that and at the same time looking at all
of the news with airplanes and looking
uh watching documentaries about how
boing has changed over its lifetime I
I've been watching a lot of that stuff
recently so I've been kind of like
paying more attention also I'm not the
type of person who will be like I don't
want to go on this plane because it's
the plane you know BL blah blue not I'm
not going to be like that I'm not going
to completely reject booing as a whole
now but I've been flying so much that it
has every time there's like a little bit
of a shaky shaky shake in the airplane I
do uh think to myself like okay yeah it
was a nice life I guess I'm I'm goner
I'm a
[Music]
goner I just like accept it I'm like
okay that's fine goodbye
world I hope someone takes care of my
cats guess I'll die
but then it's always fine but there were
some some stronger shakes here and there
and then I was really like okay that's
it that's it now I've made my piece yeah
that's okay I've I've I've done what I
could have
done that was a good
run
yeah it's just that yeah been a big
topic that you can't escape right now I
guess
yeah so I I told I'm like you know the
real concern for me is airplanes and
then it seems like that's also something
that's been on her mind and then she was
like oh I I just
completely um unselect all of those
types of airplanes when I choose to
fight I'm like oh okay I don't go that
far
but a [\h__\h] wrong I looked at the next ah
yeah there you
go is this going anywhere guys what do
you
[Music]
think so so basically me and Amma were
just having how to say like
conversations
uh
about how to say like our mind is just
going in the direction of Apocalypse
right
now yeah
death existential
crisis
yeah
yeah the end is n Doom yeah Doom posting
we're just Doom
posting I don't know I wish I could take
that fear from M though like I feel I
feel
[Music]
bad no oh oh God I can't scream so
much I'm so excited though I really
can't stay Cal I'm like in stream of
mode it
hurts it
hurts I'm so excited and I just can't
hide it I need to stop streaming
otherwise I'm not going
[Laughter]
[Music]
to
I'm reaching my limits you know I feel
like I could have a a really good throat
by now if I just wasn't talking the past
few days at
all I thought I would be fine cuz I was
definitely making big big Improvement
okay I was already feeling so much
better I feel very good like I don't
feel like you know wobbly in my mind
anymore like
in the beginning when I had a big
headache and all that and just felt like
fatigued and no energy and all that I
way better I'm capable of streaming but
I'm not capable of
screaming nice Dodge on it that was
dangerous that duck oh chill everybody
chill chill
chill that duck is going to be the end
of
me
stop scream I can't this is just like
builtin feature of Taki
Kiara you should
know a
[\h__\h] interesting interesting I have a
bad
feeling there's going to be
[Music]
explosions
we're filling everything up I need some
combinations but at the same time when
something combines it will pop like
crazy oh okay
okay
H there you go
f
it have mercy oh have mercy my bro don't
worry I have I have a deadline anyway I
have to stop streaming at the latest at
1:00 p.m. cuz I have a meeting so I'm
I'm just going to just going to hold it
in no wait let me take I love a fro
candy it really
[Music]
helps okay right we can do this I want
to see
[Music]
way if I if I put it on whoie it's not
going to stay there probably no whatever
oh
no should I put it right or left maybe
left it could touch the C right up
up uh
I I I have this is my first run for my
first run this is amazing I think but
I'm doing it with like brain empty and
tangs in between I'm not really thinking
I'm I'm just like cuz it's my first run
I didn't like think much about
[Music]
it
ah
it's
over it's
[Music]
over no I didn't get to I didn't get to
win but I got to
W that's
[Music]
okay one more time un un
un
un un
it was T over it was Wayne over no way
for me why does way evade
me why way why why does God say I had
enough of
way not a big enough share of
waya why does God not want to give me
more God is like you know the world
everybody needs a way in their life you
can't have it all for
yourself yeah okay I guess I've been to
selfish I've been I've been enjoying her
all on my own and you should share your
waya because waya is precious and waya
is
[Music]
love oh nice sub nice that was a fast
Shu see now I'm kind of doing it with a
little bit more not brain empty but
still pretty brain empty but that's okay
share W with us I I want yes I want the
way a monopoly what about hot Monopoly
can we make hot to Monopoly
[Music]
game though we'll give it another try
see how far we
get so yeah okay see uh was I done let
me see
I'm can
I uh
there ah uh this is not really a such a
valuable tangent but you know just
because we're on a shortage of Amit
tangents
um uh on one of the early days before
the Fest um you know ah when I went to
onen with
Nissa I I I I kind of knew that she
would say no but I offered uh I'm to
join us you know and she said no but she
joined us on on our lunch and we had a
good long long long long walk to the
lunch where we had fun talking
chitchatting and and she was getting to
know
nista yeah
and heart attack
JMA okay for heart
attack
oh she brought me more hot tea and the
my favorite bread that I missed out on
today cuz they oh it's so hot It's So
Fresh D where did she get this hot
tea you canot
even the is very
tar my favorite bread so we were uh you
know we were hanging out we were walking
a a long time having a nice walk and
then going to
lunch and then we ordered some yummy
food and there Isa and and am shared
some food because the food that am
wanted was like forcefully in a set you
even though the set like some parts of
the set you could order on its own but
one part of the set that Amy really
wanted to have you oh you couldn't have
on your own on its own and and then and
she didn't like the other part
oh and so n was like that's okay I'll
I'll have that the rest of that we can
share and then you can have the one
thing that you really wanted to have cuz
am was really she was really eyeing that
food I don't even remember what it was
they were sharing some kind of like
seafish thing like not really I think
the thing that narissa ate the part of
it was like a
scallop scallop I don't think all of oh
was it no there was like crab in there
too m it was a very like Japanese style
food yeah scalop scalop scalop scalop
when they say that word I think of a
German word
Gallop the style of horse
riding um so yeah and they were sharing
that food isn't that TI
and and oh narissa was like uh taking
advice from me what she should eat and
she was uh interested in something I
wasn't sure if she would like and I said
I think you'll like it I think this will
taste uh uh fit your taste butt so she
took it and she really enjoyed it so I
was really happy that I gave a good
recommendation and then uh we also had
nice desserts me and Thea shared the
dessert I'm sorry but a had her own
dessert she wanted a little bit
different one so yeah uh but that's fine
you know she got her own
dessert Gallop is also in English oh
okay well then you maybe
[Music]
understand wait for a moment I thought
about
ah I don't know if am will ever talk
about this but you know the you know the
acrylic pore that we did uh that I
uploaded as a YouTube short am was there
too and the reason why I have to say
this is because everybody was making
like like pretty acrylic pores the way I
was making it in the classic way of just
layering colors and then making
something abstract and well you could
say AB was making something abstract too
but her I I have a photo I have to ask
her if she wants to ever show her thing
or if I can show it if she doesn't want
to show it at all but I have to say the
thing she made is absolutely the am a
way 100% her personality is so unique it
stood out compared to any of the others
that we made all of us we all made like
you know kind of the basic ones but she
put her own personality in it instead of
making like an abstract like whatever
you know Spacey looking
thing uh oh happy birthday
Iris
congratulations yay please eat cake um
you're just glass no no no for real like
she this she had okay if you watch my
YouTube short you will understand how
they usually look like it's just
something abstract nothing you know know
like you know but she
she she made a face out of it and it
looks like a kind of abstract dorky
silly face and I really love it uh I I
was so so amused by it it's just so
typical am and her color choice I liked
that too U that was also kind of Amit to
me H really I really liked it this like
she added Strokes after the PO yeah like
uh I think maybe she first poured
without making the without the intention
of making a face but then she saw maybe
she saw something in it I was like okay
I'll build on that I don't know you have
to ask her hope she won't be angry at me
for mentioning this that she made that
but it was so cute I just have to
mention it I want to show it to you guys
cuz it's so cute I'm a Picasso could
sell for so much
money uh I think she was even using her
fingers for parts of it it's so cute so
funny cuz it looks so different from all
of ours like ours ours are you know kind
of basic beautiful but basic you know
but acrylic por you really if you have
no art skill you're still going to make
something amazing it's so easy to make
something nice
looking um hopefully I'm going shows it
off sometime I really hope
so I really hope so it's it's a
masterpiece
she should sell
[Music]
it the world needs to see that that's
what I'm
saying for real would be a waste if the
world didn't get to see
it so this
n ah it's getting messy again
[Music]
uh that's okay that's pretty good then
we do
this
a ah
[Music]
doio oh that was
dangerous you could even give it away
the Char yeah yeah
exactly let's not talk about I'm his
CH don't put that into the clip Kazuki I
swear please
don't sorry there's a lot there's a
lot kuki please please please
[Music]
please that feels
better well like oh my oh my sinus is
oh oh my
sinuses h
M ah what did you hear
that oh my God I heard
that through the microphone through my
headphones my my my one of my nose sinus
is opening up
again I was like I was feeling like
after blowing so much that my sinuses
were like really like you know like in
an
airplane and suddenly it opened up I
think you heard
it
[Music]
why is this so hot oh
[\h__\h] my S is went into airplane
mode okay okay okay okay okay okay we
got to get
[Music]
waya oh you're going to stay there I'm
surprised I was hoping for
that sheesh that was like a
baseball that was like like freaking
baseball home
run the the OE one the only MC by the
way was the craziest thing I ever saw
man just ripping off her
[Music]
head so
funny so [\h__\h] funny I can't believe
they let her do
that live on
stage I
wonder I wonder if she asked if she can
do
it otherwise they would have been really
[\h__\h] surprised but girl what are you
doing don't rip off your head life on
stage she don't be privileged yeah like
at least like it fits her character and
all that right it's it's in
character it makes sense it's been done
before like in in her
whatever some occasion
so just it just makes
[Music]
sense said it wasn't intentional I CH I
have to I'm so curious about this I have
to talk to them about
it what do you mean it's not
intentional how can that not like I'm
thinking about like the technical side
of aspect of it I don't see how that
could not be
intentional thank you blank for the
memberships and thank you CL thank you I
appreciate
[Music]
it
okay it was a that was the perfect best
glitch
ever N I got to ask them what happened
behind the scenes I'm going to get the
details that I can't tell you cuz
they're too too
technical I won't be able to tell you
but I just need to know for myself I'm
so
curious didn't look intentional I
thought it was intentional it's just a
OE kind of thing to do zombie loses your
[Music]
head P up thank you for the memberships
as
well big thank
you feels good man is is it would you
guys say it's just way easier in this
game to keep good or or am I actually
good natur a natural disas no a
natural
Talent I'm also natural disaster look at
[Music]
[Laughter]
me ah Ducks must
touch it's the nature
law I'm a Hal mess it's it's pretty
easier than yeah n yeah it probably
is I I shouldn't feel good about myself
it's just
easier
[Music]
there emphasis on hot oh thank
you
wow the scoring is is generous your but
your gameplay moves are nice wow thank
you it's been a while since I played
this kind of game you know and I didn't
even play sua game as much as others did
anyway just didn't want to like overdo
it oversaturate my Channel with
that which I'm sure you guys were
thankful for cuz again sua game again
was something was the fotm that I was
late on again which is another reason
why I felt like I couldn't like get like
play it too much
cuz it was already like being like less
Popular by the time I got to play it cuz
again I was in Japan and then I got home
and then I play the game
pop
[Music]
pop is yeah of course it's the H Edition
hello good
morning didn't stop you from watching I
don't know I I don't even know
understand but if I enjoyed watching CI
play that then I guess it makes sense
that you guys so many people enjoyed
watching sua games in general SAA game
streams in
general such a simple game and it's
somehow partially more riveting than
freaking alen ring or
whatever to stay over at Call's place
with this game was fun yeah I mean she
was busy it couldn't couldn't baby me
very much cuz she was busy playing the
freaking s game but it's understandable
you know these kind of things they need
to be done and I I wasn't really I was
just you know I just needed a place to
stay I don't remember why just didn't
have a hotel for a night and I'm uh I
didn't want to disturb her piece anyway
I was happy I could you know hang a
little bit with her
cats
K
[Music]
Kato oh my God sudden the chat
goes what you didn't hear how I said it
to your
daughter enjoy your streams what
impossible to and ghost cat cute
babies i' speaking of
cats I love cats you guys know that I
have an obsession with cats but I've
been really into Birds Bird videos these
days parrots and uh what do you call
those small colorful ones hor
no no what do you call the small
colorful ones budgies yeah I been
watching a lot of Budgy and mostly uh
parrot
content I really want a Parrot uh like
YouTuber or like Member One Day for hot
currently we're closed you know H is
closed a close
Community um but in the future I think
it would be cool if we could have a
parrot like parrot man why don't we have
a [\h__\h] parrot and the whole thing
will be annoying the [\h__\h] out of us by
repeating what we say you know how
annoying it is when people try to annoy
you with repeating what you're saying
it's the most annoying [\h__\h] ever it's
the most annoying [\h__\h] ever yes it is so
[\h__\h] annoying can you imagine the the
freaking SE that a parot YouTuber will
create
and they can create it because it's
their gimmick oh my
God I don't know why I get excited about
that it would probably really annoy me
but they can do it in a way that's just
funny haha funny right
hopefully two two are you kidding
me why do the wa not
touch I don't know I'll put it
here
no why you go further away you little
[\h__\h] okay that's fine actually look look
yo is this a hint no it's not a hint but
it's just I think if you're going to
make another bird ever in whole life I
feel like a parrot is an obvious
interesting
choice and also Flamingo but um you know
Lou is not a flamingo but she kind of
already looks like one so maybe we
should never do a flamingo it would just
kind of like you know be another pink
bird so yeah maybe not necessary even
though it would be cute but no Need No
need no
[Music]
need em emo would only acceptable if it
was a member that's from Australia
right I would say so austrich nah we
don't need an
austrich N no no no no there's certain
Birds I feel like you should make and
others that
[Music]
no
Troublemaker ostr we already have
tanakak Cari yeah we do we
do the yellow ostrich
[Music]
streamer no no no no need for do no
hummingbird N N I want a
parrot a Pon with a
G
no no no
no guys think
think what what the world needs what
could be a cool
design there's no need for anymore we
just need the
parrot just need the parrot that's all
we need guys don't you
[Music]
realize I need these [\h__\h] to
pop why won't you pop and go together
why are yall so freaking
[Music]
ah why do you hate each other so much
horory we need to do a horory outing so
that
[Music]
they oh very
forgiving oh a pigeon I would actually
like
that like a monochrome bird we we're all
colorful but we don't have like a
monochrome one I think a pigeon would be
actually kind of
nice
yeah they could either be like you know
the pretty wedding pigeon or they could
be the Trashy Street
Pigeon that that could go both
ways I would love a trashy Street
Pigeon they're just you know trying
their best in life but anyway I'm really
amazed with how high they can fly
without you getting disqualified that's
that's definitely something they were
annoyed about in the actual SEC game and
they were like we're not going to do
this here this pisses people off pza
thank you why why you give me red Super
Chat because I talk about burps and your
cat is like hoping to get one of them
and eat them serve them to their
owner holy [\h__\h] holy [\h__\h] unforgivable
in the actual s game this one
unforgivable we got the
wa oh I don't have much more time left
though got to speedrun
this
I'm having
fun I'm having a lot of fun however
there's a chance that if the Vault isn't
up yet tomorrow or like I I guess by
tonight cuz I got to know
beforehand I might not stream tomorrow
cuz I'm straining my throat so much I'm
sorry I reserved the
studio Dan
[Music]
wait I
just I just
realized this means that two hours make
one
wi I love the idea of that push it from
the right or from I guess anything works
right
[Music]
I'm so happy I can't help it I need to
screen right
now I win I
win I was just talking about I have to
end soon so you know I I I don't know if
I can get the
way but all you have to do is
believe oh my God I got all the birds I
got them
all y I'm so happy I feel so
accomplished
now
y that's all I've
wanted now I'm happy she's so pretty
look at her oh
nice she's so
pretty so yeah uh back to what I was
saying um I think you guys
understand I'm still sick
oh I'm so
sick
[Music]
sco old edgy
song although although I
mean I really hope the VA goes up
because the VA like a watch along of the
VA is not really straining for my voice
so that would be great but if they don't
freaking I wouldn't even know what to
stream if they don't give me the V to
watch I I was like seriously thinking
like I don't even know what to do I mean
I could play the the S game again but I
don't even know what else there is to do
for me I did a chatting stream you know
I don't have my switch with me so I
can't play switch games I don't I can't
play Yakuza cuz I'm not at home I mean I
could if I installed the whole game on
this company
PC maybe maybe even if the VL doesn't
come up I guess we could watch something
else it was going to be members only so
if you guys don't mind we uh any other
watch along we can we can still do that
oh we can watch another um I don't want
to start with the back watch long yet we
can watch another Indiana Jones movie so
I'm gonna put up a watch along and it
could be either uh the Vault or indana
Jones how about that okay okay okay
sounds
good got to play the games you bought on
sale eventually yeah but like this this
is not the day oh [\h__\h] wait
that
good idea right sounds good is the
second one Temple of Doom is that a good
one people were saying one of those
movies is really [\h__\h] was it the second
one or the third
one I vote for the Last Crusade that one
was fun no we're going to watch the one
in order the next
one Temple of Doom
[Music]
oh m
eat well we're pretty much at the oh end
of this night we're just getting a score
up a little bit
higher I'm pretty happy with this
Mo I'm happy if you're happy and you
know it clap your hands if you're happy
and you know it clap your hands
if you're happy and you know it and you
really want to show it if you're happy
and you know it clap your hands I they
clapping they're
clapping one of each member what wait
what what are you
saying what was I saying ah [\h__\h] doesn't
go there ah oh there we
[Music]
go oh
CES could touch if they wanted to but
they
[Music]
refuse let's
go so guys uh guess we're ending now
though like I'll go I'll say my goodbye
while
playing thank you guys for watching I'm
going to be back home soon tomorrow I'm
still in Japan day after also still in
Japan I'm going to meet um H who am I
meeting I'm going to
meet I'm going to meet her
tonight and I'm excited for that I got
to get pretty for that got to do my
makeup and
stuff
[Music]
uh like
so I'm excited for that and yeah
tomorrow so we we will have a watch
long it might not be the concert we'll
see uh but I'll see you there guys sorry
for the short stream I did have a lot of
fun though and you got some more extra
tangents let's
go
yeah you know I saw
clips and it's so funny to
me this is anyway it's always been a
thing with Clips in the past 1.5 years
maybe people are always
like since when does Ki sound like that
dude dude I mean yeah maybe my voice is
a little bit more husky right
now cuz I'm sick but I don't think it's
even that
different um uh but yeah
like guys did you are you living under a
freaking
Rock I sound like this for a long
time long long time get used to
it okay it's over okay that's fine
that's fine thank you for giving me an
opportunity to end
[Music]
this
thank you for watching that was fun go
play uh hold toisa and go get yourself a
waa or WWA maybe get yourself several
wahas show me how many waas you can get
in on one screen without turning them
into a winner it's the WWA
challenge yeah it's got to be at least
two so you can play doy you with them
it's like your dolls and you move them
and you have like the do you dance make
him do get yourself some waha Barbies
and make him do the doy you dance yeah
yeah yeah
yeah thank you for Super Chat I'm sorry
again I don't have time for a Super Chat
reading damn it we're going to have
probably a whole stream dedicated to ah
never mind a [\h__\h] next week is um a
special week but I I I'll squeeze in the
Super Chat reading before I start the
special
week
okay sorry yesterday I I I ran off cuz I
really needed to really needed to go to
an idol meeting this is a different Idol
meeting but let me see if I can rate
someone it's not
opening idle meeting different kind of
idle
meeting I couldn't even when I was I was
trying to run to the idol meeting and I
couldn't even run
because it was really that close it was
so bad I had to walk
carefully it was an absolute limit hey I
don't see anybody streaming to I mean at
least it doesn't like recommend
[Music]
anyone you're welcome for that
information well there's a movie watch
along going on that doesn't really make
sense to ra
into that's it wait I I am the only one
kind of the stream looks like it's just
a waiting
room oh there's nothing going on right
now I think oh the watchong is even
ending now
oh well okay that's that then oh well
another
time rated
anyways
uh uh wait uh should what what channel
is
that
oh
uh there it
is okay say
[Music]
goodbye I I start M tomorrow Members
Only
[Music]
sh