[Music]
so
hello stop with the green shrek hearts i
swear to god i'm gonna
swear to god i swear to god i get a sip
oh man anyway welcome to puyo puyo
tetris 2 i'm going to be playing with
nina my innerness and
kiss the toy
god i'm so [\h__\h] mad now here they go
it's an infectious disease
they've brought the swamp into my chat
get out of my chat
oh i need to join the others hang on
hang on hold on we're going to join the
others
you can still do it you can go ahead and
do it i'm here
it's yup it's your boy
that's how i sound it's your boy
it's it's your boy i i tried i tried
it was the belly guys oh yeah yeah how's
the audio
everyone say things everyone say some
things
it's your boy
okay oh turn them up i kill them up okay
wait oh oh the audio hold on i have to
ask a question
that's how it's supposed to be
it's just my that's just me this is real
this is me
i'm exactly how i'm supposed to be now
gotta let the lines
shine on me
now i've found yeah
who i
can i go to the room now or guys look at
my question in the chat do you think
it's okay
should i go to the room yeah it's fine
okay
come in come in here
it says you're from usa alabama wow wow
yeah you got you got me how how is
alabama how is that playing it's fine
it's fine is it called is it how is it
decent enough is that
where is alabama is it in the north of
america i forget
i feel like i knew it's somewhere
between the east and the west
part oh yeah that sounds very smart you
know
since you're so smart would you like to
would you like to explain what we're
doing today since you're so smart
ah so we're gonna be playing uh rio
wheel tetris too do you guys know what
real view is
no i know what tetris is i've played it
before [\h__\h] for dinner
okay well fifio you have these like
uh colored jellies and you gotta line up
four or more of them and then it's kind
of like tetris yeah you get rid of the
blobs by matching colors
and uh you try to uh get as many combos
as you can
lining those up and then you can get
more points
and then you can kill your opponents
quicker
now no i feel hey i already up
everyone's audio is just still so quiet
what the hell are you they're like
they're telling me
that just inna's voice is low um so i'm
like i don't know
am i am i turned up on this chord like
he sounds
as loud as kelly sounds the same to me
good now okay you don't allow one
i'll just speak louder which you said
while
whispering i was closer to the mic right
anyways i would like to say that uh we
all have practiced a tiny bit before the
stream and while i was an absolute
horrible mess
in the first two rounds i have since
then recovered well
and uh got a basic grasp of the game
uh cali is basically around the same
level as me i would like to
say although she has uh pulled out some
great moves like
throwing all those stones at me good job
kelly
yeah you're i mean yeah thank you that's
kind of you to say
hold on how do i how do i turn up ina by
the way
only ina do you have it do you have a
disney car do you have me turned up on
discord
how do i turn you up on discord right
click right click by the name
right and i'll help you volume okay it's
fixed
i fixed it hello hello well that's real
wow oh my god hello all right
so we're going for the first round okay
yeah you guys
i told you guys the
all right
yeah well let me put a let me put a cali
pog
oh it's because it's because it shows my
name on that
it's not anybody what oh i had it step
two
i had it set to lock the password isn't
up left corner but i thought it was for
friends
okay let me let me hide the lobby for
once
well we're gonna have to do this the
hiding
all the way okay i hit my screen to join
your room
[Music]
i thought it was friends only damn it
because it says join friends
hmm join a friend's room
hmm
[Laughter]
[Music]
maybe do a more complicated password
like one two three that's like super
complicated one two three four sorry
yeah that's the new password is one two
three four
what one two three four
oh yeah yeah yeah make sure you guys
cover the password okay
oh that is so complicated with the image
with the small
image you'll be fine okay
where i don't know i don't know where it
is i'm just gonna join for now
i can't find you okay okay let me give
you a screenshot screenshot of my screen
oh
thank you never mind oh no i'm in the
room
oh there i see i see where it is i see
where it is
no what do i put there
there's a small bird oh i don't have it
right now but i'll use a chicken
because i have a new pc so
um okay
that should hide it i think yeah
now don't show it don't show it kiara
don't show it i'm gonna make the cali
pog is a little smaller now
don't show it we got oh hi
oh amelia's here hey amelia oh my god
amelia's muted someone unmuted amelia
amelia are they loud
why are we stealing her ability to speak
that's just rude it's very rude
i can't believe we've done that i'm
ready i i
are you guys ready for our first warm-up
game
hell yeah i am i sure am ready
go so in this game we can choose between
puyo puyo mode and the tetris mode
i'm going to go for puyo play i always
better put your pictures right there
for your mode i want to be the fish
is hard
[Music]
you don't have to match the colors but
we are the master colors mm-hmm
and but you also don't have to make a
line like in tattoos and please you just
have to connect four
or more yeah yeah and it doesn't have to
be in one line it just
can be in random connections it just has
to touch each other
sorry i forgot to play press okay
no worries oh yeah i can make kelly's
pog
basically has a character in this game
okay i'll show you what i got can i hide
my
my my password uh thingy now by the way
i want yeah i put it away
uh yeah you can put it earlier just
remember to bring it back out when we go
yeah when you're in the lobby
what is that darn it oh no
i never saw that great thing again and
made a mistake
oh god i'm saying it's sad i made a
pretty costume i don't remember jesus
oh who did that what's going on stop it
i'll get you too you don't want the
phoenix and the death coming for you
that's right it wasn't me i'm not gonna
take oh no
ryan why are you making mistake you're
the best out of us
no you guys run against me in the
practice not just
[Music]
and the history has been recorded on on
twitter no one can take that away from
me
[Music]
exactly
who is doing that not me i don't think
so i mean i don't know
it's kara kiara i don't think so
okay look at this combos and chains look
at that
you ina
secretly like uh god
i always had inspired the theme here
on that one okay
there we go first one out baby as
expected
can't play video games we love it we
love to see it
some of my some of my viewers have
placed some bets saying that i will lose
especially after the first tweet that i
sent but i think they're reading
that uh
it's all right in the end it doesn't
even matter because you know
yeah could you stop oh god
oh that's no problem no problem i will
do that right now
exactly
i like how the chicken that i place to
hide the the password is perfectly
positioned in a way that it implies that
the chicken is
me because it's now on top of my
kuya puyo screen like in mine you guys
probably don't know what i'm talking
about because you're probably just like
oh yeah
sure sure yeah
i can do it i have a headache though god
damn it
happens to the best of us yep oh god i'm
this is my bad round
this is a bad round oh god okay safe
safe safe
show me those sweet combos
oh i made a mistake oh
okay
what the
i love that you have that did you hear
it
i did that's so good i i can't stand for
myself but i
i usually forget the sensor myself and
it just comes too late
nice
what the beep indeed
so you two love me ladies what did you
have for dinner today huh
i mean it's weird to ask that inna
because i guess she's in a different
time zone but she also lives in a
different time zone
like then she actually like sleeps in
don't worry about this so did you eat
the dinner yet you know
uh i had a meal i don't know what meal i
would call it but
no wait no i had fried rice
[Music]
but like i put like a mountain of hot
sauce on it
did you make it to make it spicy nice
yes
you like spicy stuff oh yeah right you
did say that before you were so excited
when the indonesia second generation
girl said that they like spicy stuff
yeah and then they're like i'm not gonna
eat spicy food but
spicy food i'm just like oh oh oh i
understand i
understand guys
okay get your image ready okay get your
image ready it's always been there
it's okay my image is there permanently
i'm too lazy to remove it
kelly what did you eat for dinner um
i had pasta what kind of pasta
ah it was tomato and mozzarella tomato
pasta
i'm gonna be this uh this emo kid who
looks like he's a fan of my chemical
romance
yeah okay that's fine
oh uh i'm gonna go for puyo puyo again
oh man it's tetris versus field for you
yup oh
tetris time oh i'm the only one oh i see
how it goes
don't the bloopers look so yummy they
look a little jelly yeah little
little bongos i'm not a big fan of jelly
for sure
sure sure hold on hey you don't like
jelly i mean i can eat it but
um i used to like jelly stuff much more
when i was a kid
oh yes but now i'm a phoenix that is a
million years old so
i'm kind of over that stuff you know
you're a million years old
no i don't even know i mean i don't know
man i've been reborn so many times i
have no idea
i think it's truck after like a few
millennia or something yeah
yeah it's hard to say you know yeah um
i mean didn't wait how old how old are
you now
like uh i'm uh years old
you can do it too enough
right you have the go xlr as well yeah
yeah emilia recommended it to me kelly
i need to pick one it's really good
like it's so fun to use and ever since i
got it
everyone told me that i sound even
crispier i already sounded crispy
after getting my short sm7b hashtag not
sponsored
but but now
it's like a whole new world has opened
itself to me
yeah crispy chicken is really good you
know
yes i mean who wants sloppy wet
old chicken when you can have crispy
chicken
can someone stop sending me all that
[\h__\h] over here
don't feel like nope
stop
[Music]
i'll take the time to hydrate myself
everyone hydration time
drinking water it is important
are you guys interested in what i ate
after i asked
which is basically a bowl of rice with
a bunch of uh uh
what's karu it's like
kind of yeah but it's a
it's a unique is uh
meat from the cow yes beef beef that's
what i love
from the cow
oh no i know myself
and like a pretty raw egg on top of it
and some salad
could you girls eat a raw egg
the petals if it's like maybe what's
gonna call it pasteurized or whatever
it's called
what it depends you can't eat your raw
rice
like they do like special treatment on
this so there's like no salmonella and
stuff
oh okay well you can eat it you would
you would actually i mean i'm asking if
you would want to do that
yes one suit i don't know it depends
apparently it's like really good if you
lift and stuff if you do work out it's
protein
yeah who needs that kind of stuff huh
let's just keep on eating pizza and
chocolate and all that stuff
they're not saying don't ask me twice
i'll do that
nice we got similar taste i like it
i'm getting hungry oh black yo oh
bless you thank you sean oh
was that good oh yeah
i mean what did you just say thank you i
said
[Laughter]
i say that in my super chat reading
that's probably how you picked it up but
dude um i i tried to like mix it up
every now and then and say for example
it doesn't it also means thank you but i
said uh phil and dunk
and my viewers would think i'm saying
i'm feeling dank
oh i'm not feeling dank at all me
neither in fact i am really boned right
now i really
yeah i don't know you know
[Music]
if you guys want to stay the same okay
i'm just gonna do texture yes
okay now that might as well i might as
well change to tetris right now
oh yeah let's do attention i'll try to
put it in
okay i'm not as strong
i wonder if they sell your candy that
would be probably dude
i mean it's probably like at least
there's candy that
looks like that probably oh two facts
okay let's see what we can do
the thing is with tetris how do people
have the time
to look at what's coming next i don't
understand oh yeah just real pros to be
honest
i can't even imagine it'd be really good
i already messed up i already messed up
no
oops should have never changed
[Music]
there we go how do i get something in
there though
oh no um
how do i fix the bottom line
no oh god tetris is not my
thing i prefer you know i feel like
you actually have to think to maximize
your uh
what you call it your combos
chains um
yeah you can like stack them up
certainly so that it'll like hundred
percent combo no
yeah okay i can't do that in puyo puyo
either and i definitely can't do that
in touches
[Music]
okay okay okay
my brain not working
[Laughter]
i know i'm messing up
oh no i'm not i messed up so i'm not
getting any change
i panicked
no be quick
do something online
slowly i'll go slowly
i don't know i feel like i'm gonna get
destroyed if i actually try
step off like when you like when you
like don't try
you do better but then when you actually
try you like mess up
that's a good point yeah i'm gonna try
to do the things that the professionals
do
where they leave one line open and then
try to
keep on you know clearing it all up i'm
gonna try that
okay no i'm gonna fix that one right
right now okay nice though
okay i'm gonna try to be cool now
i can't do it i believe in myself leave
me who believes in you okay i don't know
what to do
no no no no
already
oh
when i think of tetris i think of
suicide senpai
yeah terrifying yeah i saw her play and
i was like oh
i don't ever want to be against her on
tetris
you could be good if you want to just
believe in yourself
unlike your dreams for dreams no
confidence oh there we go
that's the end of me no confidence
no confidence all right baby
oh will you make a comeback kiara no
probably not even
do you believe do you believe if you're
trying to challenge me here you know
what happened to youtube when they
terminated me
the service went down yesterday so you
know what happened there my revenge is
bittersweet
that sure was you it sure was you
definitely it's okay this channel your
inner gamer
i believe in you okay maybe
[Laughter]
you can keep one and then you can uh
hold it until you need it and then like
you can like switch it out for when you
want to use that
i don't think i have the skills yet to
do something like that
first need to get used more to the room
to the to the
the whole situation mm-hmm see
cali cali kelly yeah want to team up
against inna okay
i'm cool let's do it i wonder let's do
it oops
okay okay our pool
this is the only way we could win i
don't know
you guys i think we practice matches
you'll you'll define
i don't know you know you have the i'm
pretty convinced that like the uh the
old ones have given you
like the uh
[Music]
please ancient ones give me give me more
straight sticks
what a straight sound
bats now can those encourage them
what do you think guys are you going to
win this one
together at least i wouldn't even bet
others but listen
they're still betting on email what the
hell you guys have no idea
the enemy is just too too strong and too
big
i mean she's on top of us in my layout
so
believe believe in your selves
thanks for the encouragement i do i
don't know
um actually no it's actually looking bad
for me oh damn it
oh god she's going all out now
she's ready to destroy us she's not
playing anymore
oh god no yeah
i don't even know what's coming anymore
i love you
what is that a one down
oh my god
please oh no i didn't just need a purple
and boned no matter what i needed
to hold thing as well in pouya i don't
think so
just touches
even though it's hot oh it's a hopeless
war but i'll fight till the end
oh you might make it fight for takamori
i believe in you oh thanks eda you
believe in your enemies
that's very nice of you keep your
enemies your en enemies close and your
enemies call your friends
your enemies close your eyes your
enemies close and your enemies closer
very nice
uh i quote it's
yes i'm just impersonating you at this
point
actually kelly you're still like how are
you still alive
alive thank you for doing the hard work
for us
it's so nice to have someone i should
rely on you know
cooking
[Music]
oh my gosh really that powerful
goodness gracious
it's okay not to make mistakes it's okay
in fact i'd encourage you to continue
making them please if you feel like
[Laughter]
yes
[Music]
thank you
oh no would you like a massage or
something
oh my god
ice cold what's cooler than being cool
with some aroma oils to relax here
that reminds me i'm going to go do that
after the stream is i just want
after the spring some fried chicken
fried chicken
oh i can send you some i have a lunch
thanks
i have some people to sacrifice sorry
and that people totally not
i mean like
it's not like i fry my employees or
anything like that
my child is panicking my child is
panicking
clear your ears everyone it's not what i
said
no need no need to ride behind kfc
revealed
okay
my rival is totally fine i don't want i
don't want to lost you from my rival
it's making me nervous
kelly yeah please tell me
you i think you're on your own soon or
maybe not okay
i'm scared mom
[Laughter]
still there whoopsie doodle
again against uh takamori or against
and like i feel like it wasn't fair that
we combined our power and you know i was
alone so let's do what let's do all
against each other
okay yeah
then it's time for me to kick your ass
callie wow okay that
escalated quickly all right i mean it's
fine you're allowed to feel that way
i in turn will hurt you severely so
don't worry
oh my god that's for the usual breathing
callie
certainly it'd be my pleasure
[Music]
oh my head turns goddamn
it's okay
category is foods
you guys waiting for concentration 64.
what did you expect me
or hesitation i'll go first you go
second
it's an old it's an old chant from the
schoolyard
which is scholarship
my school yard went to school i guess um
lessons whatever
[Laughter]
oh yeah the person who the person who
win
uh who loses like who has the least wins
at the end
must in their follow-up stream whatever
it is
yes and puyo at almost as possible as
many
sentences as possible so like pickles
you would be like hello everyone puyo
how's it going puya i'm sure you want to
do that here
i really hate it
i guess it's uh maybe not maybe from now
on because me and kelly played the
favorite
times i'm not sure how to count that
no okay from this game on which i lost
already
congratulations you probably know the
one who says
yeah probably not huh okay
that you're counting from from this from
the game before
so this is the second game that we're
counting
let's see let's see now i should already
try to learn how
if i can do it puyo you should you
should practice right now
i'm going to practice and bleal how's it
going
oh
[Laughter]
you should just take it oh i tried to
win anyway but i would enjoy having this
uh
this brought upon
[Music]
[Laughter]
i can't believe you actually like saying
it for you i like it
i i wanted a you call that in japanese
you call it the
gobi puyo
that's the part at the end of the
sentence i don't know what you would
call it in english because no one does
it i guess
real is there a word for that in english
uh um
chad seems to think the same
oh my gosh
[Laughter]
i think
i should turn it off for you yeah i just
ignore all the friend requests for you
there is no meaning and sending me
friend requests guys please
give up i heard you guys rejected
carol's marriage proposal appeal where
did you hear that
from your stream for you goddammit which
one
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh no you planned for this
you plumb for this no i didn't do that
i'm not that smart i think we all got
you all know that i'm not that smart so
oh it's working brielle i don't see cat
oh no oh no oh no
nice boy
what
like
i accidentally pressed retry uh uh you
guys okay with
i want cali to use puyo and her and at
the end of her sentences out
in her in
okay i don't know how to do that you
think my brain is anything oh my god
mine isn't either it's a conspiracy stop
it
stop
it's not funny when i do it i've been
doing it the whole time now
it has to be counting cleo no exactly
confused
he's working towards it
i'm i'm working towards he's wrong
what the hell kelly when did you get so
good for y'all the game i just really
don't want to say that
i just really don't want to say the
thing
she's motivated i know he's
very motivated it's cute
wait are we only counting the last place
or like
i don't know really i think it will be
very obvious in the end who had the most
loses anyway
i don't even think we need to think
about it
are you already preparing for a camera
yeah
what you're saying i'm okay with it for
y'all
it's
[Laughter]
oh my gosh
you have to do it so that i don't lose
the only cali loses you understand
i don't i can't aim like i'm sorry
[Music]
don't forget what you think
i think chad knows chad yes third that
was my third one goddammit
that that was the last time i lose real
i believe in you
thank you you know you're so sweet yeah
you're really so sweet
i'm so blessed for you
that's sweet i also want to hear you why
don't we all say
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh my goodness would you prefer it
no i'm not i don't think he's more of a
young person nope
maybe he is maybe you're right
absolutely incorrect no wait start it i
messed up
absolutely incorrect
[Laughter]
you're not making it easy for me we
gotta try your best i believe
difficult very difficult now let me
difficult
come on give me give me more give me
more reds come on yes
oh no oh you did it
oh my god yes yeah yeah yeah yeah
i can stay alive for a little while
longer but cali is doing pretty good oh
god
oh okay i gotta focus gotta get kelly to
say yeah
[Music]
thank you
i had a great time for you
but it's still we still have a long time
to go there's so many chances for me to
win puyo and turn this whole thing
around for you
[Music]
why
because
kelly's like super focused she's like
really desperate now trying to not say
puyol
you won't get me too
i i'm playing on my gamer hat
you can't see it gamer hat gotta get i
gotta get kelly's
fuel never that's not gonna work because
i always die first
how did i win why how do you do that
good job good job good job
nice dog
uh i don't know let's just do the way
whatever way you want to play how about
that okay
okay okay you're you're gonna that's
your choice actually stresses me out
i i just wanna i wanna give tetris now
that i know the whole thing i'd like to
try it
[Music]
um
okay i will do
i just realized am i getting the same
things and what if i copy exactly what
she does
oh my god it's already too late for that
but i feel like we're getting the same
like plus maybe
well now it's already too late yeah it's
too late
it's delayed too late when you're late
to a polling place
i had the same thing in my head
but like do we come i think we count the
i guess i mean i guess kelly loses as
well when i look
that's a strange line of thinking
um
okay okay now
and
did you forget how to speak english
sometimes i get to leave to speak
english
when i get too lazy to speak english i
should speak
dutch
or japanese
i just making noises if i get too lazy
to talk
oh god oh god what am i doing
is it impressive how i'm still alive i
mean like that you gotta give me dad i'm
still alive
i'm proud of you thank you no darn it
just hold on a little longer until we
can get cali
we're almost there oh no oh my
well what were you sending me he's not
helping me
is that happening oh oh darn it i messed
up
you had one job
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh well let's go after the whole thing
i'll master it
like right now i'm going to put this
away for now i haven't yet no i should
have helped you not
die first i should have done that
now now i'm forwarded
yeah we're really getting the same
please
i think so i should just really maybe
next time you try a bit slower and
so i try to follow you and then we can
defeat cali
but no i don't think i can do that and
then that that that requires some skill
which i don't have let's be real
is uh
what is it temporary i also want to say
also to say luck is temporary skill is
forever but
yeah i mean that's the way to sing
and that's the way to view it
give me purple yes thank you
oh how about this
[Music]
do you believe in miracles
oh i didn't mean to do that ugh
[Music]
no
okay i've had it with tetris i'll go
ahead and do a
i can i can people you run yeah i'll do
it all right all right
all right all right
you do so good each time well thank you
chad i don't know your mom
you're getting better you guys are
getting better every run
[Music]
that's true i guess yes yeah
as long as you keep as long as you act
no no greetings
one time let's see how it goes oh
oh i have a feeling kelly's gonna yeah
kelly's gonna
yes the ancient ones are called whoa
haha
i want to win i yeah i think we all do
and we know when we fame
wait
same you've been waiting the whole time
hey that's a good point
don't worry about it wait hold on no no
no no
oh no i got greedy
no why do you do that it makes it
impossible for me
[Music]
okay whatever i'm just gonna do this
that's okay
[Music]
you can look here you can do it i don't
know what's inside
i got a long boy can
brush up on your wheels um are people
gonna actually force me to do that
i guess yeah it was your idea though
because i told you
it was your idea it was your idea
i mean i don't i don't i don't mind it's
cool let's go what's my next stream oh
my gosh
my next stream is uh wait tomorrow i
have the day off
oh my next stream is fire emblem which
is gonna be a long stream i usually
stream fire emblem for like six hours
maybe i'll just do a quick gorilla
tomorrow maybe for one hour all
it's not cheating shut up chad it's not
cheating
is that cheating oh this is really
strong
[Music]
the next dream i never said if it it
that it has to be a scheduled stream i
never said it can't be in
uh
you are not the one to decide the rules
okay
you are not the one to decide wills
it's on my terms is any times it's my
thing of course
i do want to see a six hour uh video
stream though don't you
six hours you mean six hours of me
saying puyo
yes six hours of this game i could
probably sleep six seven
six hours and feel prepared that's
something else all clear
god oh god no oh why do i go nicer
thank you ah this is fun
good job good job what do i do with this
boy what do i do
what do i do with you okay
oh another
i feel like this is just becoming like a
fully character
yes it's fluffy it's not the intense
because it really isn't
can i have one or not oops
one win one
[Laughter]
oh well it's okay
it's okay i i'm used to it
i'm used to it no i believe in you
you got you won against me in the
practice room yeah how did you enjoy it
how did i do that i can totally tell but
that was when kelly was still a noob
and now she picked up some basic
knowledge about the game i sure did
to come very quickly
you're always hungry when everyone
drinks the high
[Music]
yeah if people like something that i
don't like i just don't get it
[Laughter]
why are you enjoying eating it it's so
weird okay
i mean you know you but like
i mean people people be people these
people like different things
that's true okay
i actually have to focus i can't focus
when i'm hungry
i'm forcing myself to do a gorilla
tomorrow instead of uh taking a break oh
man
but that's better than doing a six hour
full stream gone down
six hours
what if i what if i do a stream where i
just literally say nothing
then i also don't have to add wheel but
if i just don't drop
it like a stream i just look at the
camera for
one hour and just stare into your soul
i'm sure someone would enjoy that very
much probably
i think yeah there was a youtube like a
youtuber like in blue more times
who did that like she looked uh into the
camera
for all of her videos and said nothing
and sometimes she would say hello
does someone know who i'm talking about
i will not say the name but do you guys
know what
i'm talking about uh
you know what i'm talking about nope
you don't know maybe not i guess you're
not a boomer
oops no why i didn't do that
i didn't send that down there
no no i'm not talking about the girl of
the peas
they were mine
much older than that
[Music]
um
you're welcome for all the chiara noises
today well you also made a lot of weird
noises there young lady
i don't know what you're talking about
it's just a normal day for
taco noises compilation
there is a aren't there like
compilations like clips of uh weird
youtube noises
weird uh beach trouble noises i think i
saw something
today is a great day for them to collect
content
[Music]
i guess there's clippers who are into
that
oh wait no i messed up ah darn it
i think we don't even have to count
anymore
it's pretty obvious
just a little bit you kind of walked
into that one you know when you came up
with the
with the bus this is your idea
i was like kind of hopeful that maybe
like you know
me maybe
[Music]
maybe things that have been different
maybe maybe callie was just lucky
you know oh god
[Laughter]
you're welcome clippers
there are a lot of good questions in the
stream huh
compilation of chiara noises i'm trying
to make up for it
um cali concentrating so much that she
doesn't talk
what do you mean i'm talking tell us
about something that happened
today did something happen today you're
trying to confuse me and make me not win
no i already lost it
unarchived okay oh my gosh
sorry i was sleeping for that but i
heard you sang my song i did
actually i listened to the i listened to
a clip of it oh yeah
i tried i'm actually practicing your
song as well
well then we should oh i am i'm pretty
good at it at this point
oh yeah uh the love first
why are you doing this a dabbing
okay good job yeah keep going keep going
no
i hate this it's not fair
it's not fair
[Laughter]
um also shrek swamp infected my chat
shrek slump yes yes
no just everyone's spamming green hearts
and i don't like
do you want to go back to the lobby i
want to play tetris again yeah
like the green doll right right because
i sang many shrek songs look at him
infecting my ch i sang many shrek songs
and i replaced some of the lyrics with
the with the word shrek
and people just started spamming the
green hearts
oh that's cute i love shrimp
dead beets love shrek
did you sing somebody once i did i did
there's a bunch of green characters
there
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh yeah can we open up we can't be in
the same team right
i don't think the game would let us yeah
all right well here we go
anyway i also hit eight eight uh
what is it eight hundred eight hundred
[Music]
yeah well i i did i reached it right
before the karaoke and then i mentioned
it and then i said please don't
unsubscribe and then many people about
100 people unsubscribed
but then they subscribed back when they
heard that i wasn't going to discuss
it
[Music]
it would have been the trick if they
defeated one of those um
i won't stop singing until
one of those before but then um i
reached it like after like five minutes
or so i'm gonna keep on singing so i
kept on singing for an hour or so
ah did i because that's only
yeah cause i'm still i mean at that
point i'm celebrating now
celebrating for reaching the marathon
and there's also a lot of stones on my
field can someone next
like i'm trying to knock up celebrate
our all stones
together yes oh my god
oh wait that was the wrong one no
i saw it fly from your direction
is
well i mean let's be real i'm i mean i
wouldn't say i'm really bad at it i'm
i'm not good at it but i wouldn't say
i'm really bad at it
yeah you're fine you're getting better
exactly everyone starts somewhere yeah
there you go anyway i've messed up so
come on
we all mess up sometimes yeah i
literally boned myself no
darn it you burned yourself i'm sorry
but
my understanding is someone who's first
language is not english that sounds very
weird to me you're boring yourself in
that kind of a wrong
way i don't it's it's a family friendly
stream
now listen here we don't do that here
those families we don't do
family nonsense no we don't do it we
don't the family friendly streams here
i guess we don't i mean i definitely
don't
i've been doing it wrong the entire time
no not wrong but you're doing it
your way you think your family you know
extremes is family
are family friendly can someone can
confirm down
have you ever said the f word on your
string
i said fudge
i not i recall wow
nice that's i've said impressive
the uh s word a couple of times though
my mistakes went
oh okay okay okay i see i see i mean not
as bad as
it would be hard to like completely you
know
not say anything at all of those words
hey i'm doing good how long is this
going to be like that
there we go wall of stones
i was doing just fine
we need to do uh where we can just sing
whatever together
good idea oh my god can you guys do it
off collab
yeah we're planning on it eventually is
there is there like
english songs in japanese karaoke i
forget
yeah yeah yeah there are there are
you mean like if they are in the mouse i
mean if they are in the machine
yeah yeah yeah they are like plenty of
them
ah the new songs come in kind of slow
but they do come
oh man
why would you do such a thing
cause my my hp is running low
interesting are you implying that dr
oopsie doesn't raise your hp
it lowers it in the long run
look at what i'm doing guys look at look
at
oh
[Music]
i'm not learning but i wouldn't say i'm
learning oh god
some say some say look it's a skill so
you know oh dear
okay
[Laughter]
well done
one more time against me do you i don't
think we want to see
you losing again it could hurt your
reputation
can't lose a reputation if i never had
one
that's what i call a comeback my friend
congratulations i mean come back and
come back sir
phoenix's uh specialty exactly but i
truly think
i think it's a bit too late i already
lost too many times to make up for it
by now uh you never know
at least you came back in style and
you've done your best hell yeah
tell you
come on come on
wow
[Music]
no i should probably saved them
that was an accident oh that was an
accident oh no
[Music]
um
okay now you gotta go for the phoenix
town hey uh uh phoenix down it only
happens
when youtube bring terminates my channel
hashtag feelings down thanks guys for
everyone participating
i know phoenixtown is a revival item
yeah
in which game final fantasy yeah
see people pointed that out to me but
not here
[Laughter]
keep singing
[Music]
send me heaven i don't know what i'm
singing this is a random song that no
that doesn't even exist so copyright
can't strike me cause copyright got
nothing on me
oh yeah yeah yeah youtube got nothing on
me try to turn me need me again if you
can
but you got nothing on me youtube you
got nothing on me
youtube you got nothing on me
[Music]
youtube phoenix down only happens
when you close your eyes and you'll
have your ass in luke
oh
my child was just uh telling me that
your your
chat was broken it was i was i was
noticing that while i was singing what
the hell
was it i thought it was only me maybe it
was my
wow maybe it was your beautiful singing
yeah it was delicious
it was like a magical spell or something
[Music]
okay carbuncle
i think we are getting closer to to the
final matches all right i think
we know who the uh who the bots again i
think
whatever it is and that
unquote winner
i don't know i don't know what you're
talking about
i don't think it's that obvious i think
we have to start some recounts
i don't know about that not that odd
first comes denial
i mean
i mean in some worlds maybe
ways differently and then i would have
won
make sense right maybe i'll just i just
terminate
uh youtube again
again
people people um have made up a theory
though that it wasn't me but it was cali
as a revenge for me
oh or it was ahmed like there's these
two fairies either it was ammo
it was county what do you guys think was
it kelly romney i think julia is a
little more likely than me and lily is
scared
ground pounding you know yeah you might
not be able to tell it from just
i mean there has been evidence
everywhere on the internet even on my
debut
rew stream i showed the evidence of uh
on the ground pounding
uh coming into the youtube offices ready
to ground pound looking really ripped
and stuff
oh my goodness that was i mean that was
a bad run for me so
i saw that coming i did it i was a
little quicker than i thought
a little bit too quick you're a speedy
one
you're a speedy one miss
[Music]
oh my god wait
i just ate eight days until christmas i
mean okay
wow maybe nine days for you and you know
oh nine nine but i i i
personally from where i'm from we
celebrate christmas only in the evening
the christmas morning on the next day is
like nobody cares about it anymore
people
don't care so we give gifts we open the
gifts in the evening christmas evening
not in the morning
yeah we usually open it in the morning i
can't wait that long
to be fair we usually just like you know
open it like
we know what's in there already oh
why why would you know
[Laughter]
her eyes are scaring me wait is her eyes
wide open
yeah staring at the screen i can see it
this is how it gets to be sometimes
also in where i'm from um it's not santa
bringing the presents it's uh
it's the christkind which is a angel
oh it's an angel bringing a little
present
how is it is it the same well you know
right no
um in the underworld we do things a bit
differently
it's a child angel though
yeah those are those australian um
traditions yes this is australian
oh it's a it's a little angel
riding on a kangaroo bringing us
presents kangaroo
i'm still having a speak
oh i got distracted by the kangaroo
right there it came in clutch please
how many rounds left in like this like
run until you go back to the lobby
uh if i win once more then we go back to
the lobby
okay so if you win say no more say no
more
because i'm looking at the time we said
like one and a half hours
yes and this might be the last match
what all right let's make it count
i will win oh god hold
you can be slow you know you can just
take it easy
go oh you can still hear the voice of my
character let's keep saying
that my god
no no booyah
[Music]
oh
oh my god
ah
i'm barely alive oh my god
yeah okay okay okay okay okay oh my god
no
i'm still alive i'm desperate
[Music]
no i don't believe in anything
you believe in yourself no i don't
believe in anything
no confidence no
okay it works it works yes this is
[Music]
might win this one
and i actually concentrate i have a
chance for winning
oh my god but i'm an entertainer at
heart you know i'm an entertainer
i have to talk to give the people some
nice
oh oh my god you guys disappeared on my
will not change anything on the official
outcome
but i will still fight until the bitter
end and show you
that the phoenix never gives up i told
you this guys
a phoenix never gives up
[Music]
this is the way of life never surrender
never gonna give you up
never gonna let you down quickly
i'm gonna stop it why
stop it stop it just stop just stop stop
stop
know you know if you could do me this
honor and
play maybe you don't have to give it to
me but like at least like
give me a chance of re-re
resuming my honor i i don't speak
english okay i'm focusing okay go
but ian is still chilling no stone
blocks on the
board oh but he's got something else
is she gonna do it she's just gotta find
a way to connect those purple guys
oh
oh and she connected the green the the
little green beans
here we go i'll give you ten more
seconds oh until once
that's it why
you made me really nervous there you
know made me really nerdy
all according to plan
if i just stay calm if i just stay calm
i have a chance
you the final countdown
we're just we're just really like trying
to get those copyright strikes today
aren't we
yeah i wouldn't be surprised if we got a
bit of trouble with some having some
okay i have challenged uh my luck with
that many times before and nothing
happened so
i don't want to check messages for emma
john's angry messages
wait a second yes
this this game is taking a while huh it
is
maybe i'm getting better
[Music]
no it's not not looking so good anymore
how do you attack by the way
do you press a button oh my god
[Music]
um it's not so obvious who who has to do
the bachelor game i don't think it's so
obvious so we will have to count it down
yeah it's
sure about that i think so
i don't know let's do it let's do a
count uh i'm going to check
it says uh kiara
number
well i will i will take the honor of
doing the better game of the in my
following stream which does which
doesn't have to be the final one it just
has to be the following stream
saying at the end of every sentence i
say
for the whole stream okey dokey
yay apparently it's ina
that must be wrong what the hell but i i
believe that you that eno won 11 times i
do believe that
yeah it's very confusing
wait actually huh
kelly won one time uh-huh enough won 13
times and i won two times
i have one more round in the county i
have one more often than cali but lost
more often than cali
what hmm what now how do we count this
we did this
we didn't specify does this mean that we
get a puya
from cali what i'll never do it oh how
do you like
johnny come on tables doesn't it
i won't do it come on cali
how about we do it kelly how about we
both do it yeah
i won't do it why would you collide
what's the next stream valley do it
don't you i never agreed to it
how about you do it uh because you said
you have a segment after
after the stream ends no i'm going how
about you do it
i'm too tired i might stream tomorrow
though i might stream tomorrow i might
do a random okay
okay so maybe
yes yes yes that was fun wasn't it
anyone who has some something to say
like announcement or whatever it put on
uh you guys go ahead i don't have much
i've got nothing
um just a regular all week i guess
okay same here i think all our schedules
are up so if you guys want to check
those out
check it out for when we're streaming
but we finally after a long time we have
a a full member collab
at the end of like friday for some
saturday for others
she's already started she's already
started
uh i was just coughing so i don't know
yeah okay guys well
i think that wraps it up hasn't it yes
i guess oh my god are you dying
[Music]
i'm good i need to go get a drink that's
a good choice
which is why you guys are getting dj joe
for the odd show again so i know we were
supposed to stop but
i need to go get a drink so yeah
[Music]
so much
do me a favor
[Music]
is
i'll get close to your mind
[Music]
oh
all right
[Music]
peace puyo and whatever go play pio pio
tetris go play it peace pujo
bye
[\h__\h] it [\h__\h] it [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] it [\h__\h] it
[\h__\h] it [\h__\h] it
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] get it [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] it