[Music]
so
do
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
so
hello
anyone out there
[Music]
you're here where
where
[Music]
are you
why why are you guys all
a frowning
[Music]
come closer no i'm not i'm not small i'm
just i'm just um
[Music]
don't don't cry here
um um
[Music]
um
if i come closer would you give me head
pats
[Music]
don't crush
um it's okay i still got my limiter on
ah at the moment
[Music]
okay okay okay stop stop stop crying
stop frowning i'm still here i'm still
here
[Music]
um i usually want to give you guys head
pats
[Music]
ah
i'll slowly
come your way
[Music]
okay give me the give me those head back
give me give me good good stuff
okay so
um
well
since we've got sticky pngs and i don't
really have much of an opportunity to
use them
um i'm gonna use everything
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you for the
headphones thank you thank you
i want to give you guys headbutts too
oh
[Music]
so um
thank you very much for coming
today
today is um
[Music]
an occasion
ah
i don't know
am i am i shaking because i'm nervous or
am i shaking because it's cold out here
oh
don't you guys like hit that faster so
like it conducts warmth or something i'm
cold
headphone faster you're too slow
[Music]
it's just cold
oh
thank you very much for everyone here um
[Music]
has come today
um there's quite a bit planned
um but i'll go into detail about it a
little later
[Music]
okay so look at this
counselor is they're on my they're on my
shoulders
[Music]
you know um it was a
it was a closet dream of mine to like uh
be big and like have them ride on my
shoulders
i like the really really big meme where
um the anime meme were like there's a
shonen guy with really huge shoulders i
wanted to be that
and then i wanted to um i wanted to
place counselors on my shoulders so yeah
i can i can finally do that big smalls
was a was actually a big ploy
it's actually a conflated ploy so i can
live out my closet dream
i'm kidding
so um
as you know
as quite a lot of you know this is my
last
video my last stream on this channel
um after this stream i am
not going to be updating any more of my
socials
i'll be handing them back to
um my boss
that
my god
the
the absolute overwhelming support
that i've received
um
absolutely blows my mind i just keep
scrolling and scrolling and scrolling
and there's more and more and more and i
try to like um like as many as i can
while i can
and see as many as i can while i can and
then like you know a lot a lot of it all
of a sudden it just sort of like
hits hits you and then you start crying
and then
um
yeah
i mean
[Music]
i love you son i love you guys too
thank you very much
for coming here to see me off and
give me head pads
it means a lot to me
thank you thank you so much
[Music]
oh
wait wait
[Music]
i am getting a signal
beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep
beep
[Music]
don't go
wait
[Music]
huh
wait let me move over
what's this
it's not easy
big laptop
wait just a moment i can make it i can
make it look bigger just give me a
second
[Music]
look i'm just like your
lap cat
when you're trying to work on your
important things like a goodbye good
luck letter to sauna
um
the cat's just all over the
keyboard
that's me right now
yeah
i have cat ears on
okay wait so um
[Music]
so this
huge
huge letter
huge huge letter
um it's been passed around all the whole
live
branches
and then um i thought we can have a look
through it together i haven't read i
haven't like gone through and read it
yet i thought i should save it for this
stream
but uh one thing one thing in this
stream yeah
will you guys help me out
[Music]
okay i'll stop being a cat
yeah
[Music]
probably like this
hello guys
[Music]
yeah look around
some people have drawn things as well
[Music]
okay where should we start on top left
oh gosh i don't know if i can read all
these out
oh
okay this one's from zetta oh look it's
a bread dog i love how um i love how
there's just so many messages people
have started to
people have started to
draw on the border as well
yo yo
[Music]
um sana senpai red dog thank you for the
lovely memories i wish you big happiness
i wish you big happiness too
[Music]
oh yeah
um
i brought this around i passed this
around the jp
members as well i told them um
japanese is fine but i think everybody
did their best to write me a
english message
anyway
so i really appreciate the effort
[Music]
i pray for your happiness big sauna
forever companion
or kami
mia big god
oh
um
me
i think
or kami
[Music]
i watched her
i watched a universe sandpox stream a
long time ago
a lot of fan art that came out of it
okay this one though
asana love you
[Music]
um
i was like
wondering whose signature this was
[Music]
because i thought it kind of looked like
a bird it's a la plus right once you
look at it it's laplace like la plus but
then like i thought like the l was a
beak
[Music]
like
purple bird
[Music]
cute
one day
one day come visit me in the universe
[Music]
i wish you well and happiness
thank you
[Music]
ah
i've been thinking um
[Music]
i wonder
if everybody was just thinking
oh maybe i was just thinking i could
always collab with everyone
at a later time like
we always had time fit then
um
well i guess like the collab the collab
rush happened
[Music]
i did my best thank you for being part
of ian keep shining as bright as you do
love always amen oh look at this
[Music]
bro
sana i love you we are twins forever
i hope you're happy
[Music]
yes we
we are twins because um
we celebrate the birthday around our
birthdays around the same time because
of time zones
[Music]
will i remember where i'm looking wait
when i go back sana
i regret now that i haven't been able to
talk and play with you at all since your
debut
i wish you a lot of happiness
um
yeah
reading these is gonna be tough
[Music]
i used to
feel the same way
but thank you very much for sending me a
message anyway
blimey
the handwriting is so good yeah you get
to see everyone's um
handwriting
their english handwriting is probably
neater than mine
i'll call you some phi
[Music]
i love you sana you made my universe fun
you made
[Music]
you're not alone
maury i love you sana you made my
universe fun
you made
um
[Music]
you made being in halloween very very
fun i mean
[Music]
your first senpai
wait first senpai not first and fire
first
like nine ten eleven hour collab how
long how long was that
we
break records together
and
yeah
thank you for always being so positive
[Music]
see you again sana even though it was
short i'm really happy to know you
oh
wait i have a hairstyle like cobble
kobochan
yeah nickarasi what happened to your
head
good
always remember
[Music]
how to say baton
i'm kidding and thank you
for the really fun collab
kopachan
um wait wait this corner um
thank you
i hope you'll be fine and
meet
me someday
in us
wonderful aussie friend from
[Music]
oh rather
watch them i'd rather meet you in japan
[Music]
but okay if you want to if you want to
go to australia as long as we don't eat
spiders
as long as
[Music]
you don't make me eat spiders
i'm happy we could collab
we could do the australian collab
together
thank you
[Music]
um
dear sana
no matter what you will always be one of
us
no one can replace you and no one
will forget you
will always be supporting you wherever
you go
[Music]
laptop screen
love you
baby
[Music]
how is this rat so wholesome
hmm
no one will ever
replace you or i will never forget you
too
hey
hmm
asana you will always be a part of ian
and i am going to miss you so much
i will take good care of blue man gleam
love you
thank you so much
iris your future will be as bright as
the stars
i looked at this i was like oh
iris has been practicing
it still is chunky it's still as chunky
as ever
adorable
[Music]
thank you
um did i miss any on this side
nope we'll go down
[Music]
you are forever everyone's big sunshine
i wish you all the happiness
anya
[Music]
i don't want to say it but i will
because this is my only chance
um
[Music]
you're also a lawnmower forever i'm
sorry
thank you anya i'm glad we could collab
i'm glad um we could play a lot of games
together
[Music]
i mean um
i don't actually remember i don't
actually like remember exactly how it
turned out that way i just remember that
she made a lot of lawnmower noises and i
told her like you suck at like a
lawnmower when you play mario kart
[Music]
you are the brightest star in my galaxy
shine wherever you go
thank you
[Music]
i don't know how outside your big heart
comes from such a small shark
[Music]
oh
we can see
wait
we'll zoom in
sana
um
[Music]
i'm really glad that i met you your
passion and hard-working energy rubs off
on others including myself
thank you for being an honest and
motivating person who i'm proud to call
as my friend
i'll visit space in the future
so show me around then
rooney
[Music]
hmm
i'm really glad i met you too you're
honestly one of the most warmest
people
i've ever met
and you wouldn't
well
maybe some people wouldn't expect it
from you but you're just so warm and
sincere and just makes me feel feel
really great about myself
[Music]
thank you
you know um she posted the minecraft
tower yesterday
pictures of the minecraft tower from our
collab
and um
we both got really emotional after that
maximum gap miller
yeah i think like she messaged me saying
um yeah she posted it and then like
oh
should i should i tell okay this is my
last dream of
[Music]
chill she said she was crying and
couldn't stop and then like i looked at
it as long as i started crying too
um i don't know we'll always
see each other we'll always talk to each
other a bit
um
just like
and just like how it is
like as all like in hollow life
it's a little different
i guess
we work so hard together
in holly and
[Music]
you know part of that
is going away today so
it's a little bit
a little bit of comfort that we'll keep
in touch right but
you know the fact that
that's
going to win today it just kind of hits
you just kind of hits you
[Music]
what did craney tweet
it's screaming i can't see
[Music]
i don't know i'm scared
look
mine's on fire
[Music]
oh so cute
adorable
oh thank you so much i know you're so
busy with our birthday preparations and
she still took time to
draw something for me and it looks
absolutely adorable
essential
[Music]
ahoy
yo well
[Music]
dear sana i already miss you but hollow
aussie will be forever
i hope you find happiness in space and
don't forget us because we won't forget
you kiwa
oh cute
[Music]
you know we do have similar handwriting
i was like
um probably the d and the bees gives it
away
but i was like did i write this
i'm cute thank you
sana
i am so sad to see you graduate you're
a really cute junior who responded right
away to my clumsy messages
i hope you will continue to be a good
friend to me
[Music]
kanata
i had to think
um
in the space i had uh
a bitter go
um i told her that i often mispronounce
kanata as katana
just because i think it's because
um foreign names are a little bit harder
to memorize
and katana is a little bit easier so
i have to think every time i i hear a
name
[Music]
look at her name
let's continue to be friends
[Music]
i'm happy we could talk and i hope that
you're moving go smoothly thank you
[Music]
um
where should we go next
explore
sana
i love you
uh let's zoom in thanks for all the joys
you introduced me to i will treasure the
moments daily
renew okay betty let's go
[Music]
mama
cute
rina's been um
super sweet i know she is um
i know she's traveling
i know she is
high up in the sky
maybe you can see her
as well
um
i don't know i'm just
i'm just so excited to continue talking
to her afterwards
i don't know
it's that kind of weird feeling where um
[Music]
i look at these and think of these as
this is
these are probably the last messages
that
i'll get from the members
but
at the same time it's not the end
at the same time it isn't the same i had
to say
[Music]
yeah
don't say that you can still talk to
them i can still talk to them
[Music]
yeah she also started um playing pokemon
black and white for me
she's been giving me updates and i know
she's busy as heck doing a lot of things
i treasure our friendship too thank you
[Music]
well this one's
green
[Music]
fauna from the moment i first met you it
was so apparent just how special you are
i feel so lucky to be friends with
someone so witty talented thoughtful
sweet and cute
i'm sad to see you go
but i know no matter what no we'll be
friends no matter what please keep
shining like the star you are and find
happiness wherever you go
love you forever
fall for oh
yeah
good
[Music]
you know
though
a four four
which witty talented thoughtful sweet
and cute
that applies to you too i mean i'm not
going to um
i'm not going to say that i am not
all these
you feel like
you're talking to you feels like just
like talking to a sister
a sister around my age at best like like
i don't know
you just have like
a warm and fuzzy aura around you and i
just feel like
we're always in the same wavelength
[Music]
thank you
oh
oh yuffie
[Music]
oh
the line the linework is so neat
[Music]
i love you in every universe
iffy
[Music]
thank you for the beautiful sauna
i mean once you once you go back into
space maybe we'll maybe we can um
collide or something
[Music]
until um i mean you're an alien you can
go up to space
anytime
why
why is everyone so talented
okay let's go
uh up here
i feel so lucky to know you
you have left us with so many fond
memories
and
memories we will never forget
i wish you the best wherever you go
wherever you may go
thank you for everything
i love
you so much hot
me me
oh my god it's surrounded
[Music]
thank you mimi
thank you for
[Music]
all the
all the work that you took on especially
while you're
well you're doing so much in the back as
well
you're so
you say you always say that you're so
nervous and um
[Music]
you have you like state your worries but
honestly
you're like one of the bravest coolest
people i know
whenever you put your mind to something
[Music]
so thank you
she's like so brave
[Music]
huh
what
are these
are these my anchor highs
[Music]
i didn't tweet about it but i saw that
the views i saw all the debuts i was
able to um chat with them a little as
well give them a little bit of senpai um
act like a senpai for just a few days
best wishes
this month
oh so pretty
i'm taking a bath in a milky way
i hope i didn't sit on anything we
should wish the best
excellent
thank you for all your hard work sauna
senpai wishing you good fortune
bestie
[Music]
sending you good vibes and fortune your
way you got this
i'll talk
[Music]
i don't know why when i look at altar i
think of tartar sauce
why does why does my brain always lie to
food
you guys
i'm happy that
even just for a short while i was able
to become a semplier
before halloween
and you guys are super talented and
funny and
you guys are going to do great
wherever you want to go
yeah
[Music]
good luck i mean like not good luck you
guys you guys don't need good luck i
mean
i believe in you and i'll always be
cheering you guys on
thank you very much
tata sauce
[Music]
regis tartare
thank you for everything
i'm so sorry
not to reach you sooner don't say
you're sorry
[Music]
you
you did so much for
me
you grinded so much for me but you're
you were just
so humble about it thank you
um i hope you have a wonderful feature
meena
thank you for everything too
usa always so be um
excited to see a lot of things whatever
whatever you want to do as well
[Music]
um
okay here
i hope your future is bright
thank you for giving us the big love
glasses
friend hey
hey john
oh are you at the same mouse i think
she sent me a message but i haven't
looked at it yet because i've been
frantically trying to put everything
together for this stream
and everything that
[Music]
i'll look at it now wait
foreign
[Music]
live reading message i'm not sure i can
do that i mean it's not anything
suspicious but
just like the thank you for coming
the holiday life
[Music]
thank you very much for writing in my
letter as well
[Music]
i wish you happiness and best of luck
wherever you go
oh my goodness did you
did you literally pull off your tail
just stick on this letter
i don't know i love your tailor issue
i love it but i don't know if i should i
should hold on to this is that really
okay
she does that
it's okay it will grow back oh it will
grow back okay then i can take this one
[Music]
new fluffy scarf
[Laughter]
thank you i'll treasure it
hmm
[Music]
no
can i fit this on the screen
[Music]
always love you to jupiter and back
best of luck with everything sana is
eternal
[Music]
i'll always love you
too mom
always
be cheering you on
[Music]
and thank you for everything
i'm glad that we can have this
[Music]
experience together
foreign
[Music]
thank you
oh i'm flushing
oh my gosh where was i i didn't miss any
did i
just let me have a quick look around
ah there's so many
um
there's some in the middle here
okay
[Music]
ah not a god
hi
[Music]
i wanted to talk with you more i hope
you will be happy in the future
big sauna big love
[Music]
i
i didn't know she can draw
wow
thank you it's so cute i'll treasure it
[Music]
thank you not a question
even though your space
you are and will always be our brightest
shining star
crazy oi
you always be
um
the
less stinkiest zombie
[Music]
i'm sorry that wasn't very good
but
thank you very much
for your poetry and i i butchered this
ollie
[Music]
thank you for being just um i don't know
you're just
so easy to get along with
no wonder
everybody always wants to um
everybody always wants to give you a lot
of affection you deserve it
thank you
that handwriting though it's so cute
it's so cute
um
i hope you happiness and
smile smile
all days of your life sana thank you so
much love you
awesome five
thank you
[Music]
we actually wanted to do something
together but sadly it didn't work out
[Music]
um but thank you for organizing
organizing oh the america tournament
that was a lot of fun
[Music]
and thank you for getting along with um
the rest of halloween as well
thank you senpai
[Music]
dmt
okay i think
that's all of them did we get through
all of them
[Music]
i think we did
no bottom
click bottom
right corner
[Music]
one at the top i think i've already um
yeah i'm pretty sure i've already read
all of them
um
i started from the top i went around in
a circle and then up and then i just
don't know what the heck happened i have
no sense of direction there's no
direction in space
got them all
let's have a big look um
around
i'm pretty sure i got them all
thank you very much for
the huge huge huge huge little
[Music]
i will um
i will show you
in comparison to big sauna how big this
is
you deserve it sauna thank you guys
and thank you for um
helping me out
[Music]
i guess
um
[Music]
it might be time to go
well
i have some things to show you but um
firstly i mean
i don't mean i'm going i mean like this
stuff
this stuff
[Music]
ugh
look now you can see my face the council
counselors can stay on my shoulders
i got scared i'm sorry for scaring you
yelling grassy
yeti grazie for some reason is holding a
microphone but
should i put should i put him back in
the cage
[Music]
oh
okay
on there guys
[Music]
okay i think i'm ready to move on to the
next part
[Music]
it floats
ah i'll lay a light i'm sure it will
float too wherever i'm going i need to
well firstly i have a gift for you guys
um
just let me move away from the earth a
little because i think it's a little
dangerous
[Music]
oh
i guess i don't need this anymore
hmm
[Music]
um
here you go
[Music]
i hope
it lands somewhere safe
[Music]
um look up you don't want to
you know what i don't want an accident
to happen i did not think this through
[Music]
good luck
okay so
thank you very much guys i think
i think there was a lot of ways that
um
[Music]
things could have turned out
that might have been worse
[Music]
i honestly
i don't know i can't
how i feel right now i'll be i'll be
real with you how i feel right now um
it's kinda
you remember my glass in
um my birthday merch
i think it was called um is the universe
half full or half empty
um i just sort of thought it was funny
but then when i think about it
the universe is definitely half full i
just kind of feel that way
i mean how can i not
how can i not be dissatisfied with um
meeting all of you guys hearing
and seeing all your support all the
things that um
you guys have sent to me and made for me
and how can i
not be dissatisfied about meeting so
many creative amazing
friends here
[Music]
i really don't regret meeting them i
don't regret meeting the satellites
i don't regret all the fun and laughter
we had
hmm
i was kind of
i don't know i was kind of
terrified or like break down on stream
or anything but honestly i just feel
incredibly grateful right now
i can't be
i can't be sad
about
well this happening i mean
[Music]
yeah i'm just in incredibly grateful for
giving me these smiles and being able to
give these smiles
view as well
[Music]
thank you very
much i mean
the fact that it happened will never
ever change
just like sano's internal eternal our
meeting is so so eternal
[Music]
that will never ever ever change
it's it's fact
say thank you very much
[Music]
okay
so hello ian
i have worked very very hard for
the next part
of this stream
we're working really hard on it and um
it's gonna be circuit it's gonna it's
gonna blow your minds
we've been
before before under on the twenty during
the smalls
during the small stream
um we hardly had anything done but for
some like
through her
horrific
herculean herculean effort
we are able to bring
this to you
um not only in the talents i also
there's also really really amazing
people that
worked on some things as well so
i would really be happy if
you watch it till the end
[Music]
thank you very much for everything
um
you guys are the only ones in the
universe each and every single one of
you are the only ones in the universe
[Music]
is why
you know the fact that the fact stands
that you're the only ones in the
universe like each and every one of you
so you guys are eternal too
i'm i don't know
i just
i'm really really happy
to have this chance in hollow life
[Music]
to meet all of you
and
[Music]
i'm just i'm just
so
grateful
[Music]
okay so i think
it's time
[Music]
ah okay please enjoy
i love you all you're all loved by the
universe
i'm not alone and you aren't either
thank you
[Music]
is
thank you
[Music]
no
my
[Music]
foreign
oh
[Music]
i know
you
[Music]
my friends
me
[Music]
foreign
my friends
[Music]
me
goodbye teacher my friends
[Music]
my friends
boom
[Music]
good to see you
oh
[Music]
foreign
is
wow
[Music]
oh
okay
please
[Music]
oh
into
[Music]
my
is
[Music]
are you ready
foreign
[Music]
is
oh my god
[Music]
is
i'm ready
[Music]
m
me
[Music]
my
[Applause]
[Music]
i'm not alone
when our hearts grow bigger than the sun
there's no challenge we can't go if i
come up
is
[Music]
darkness and light
i'm
[Applause]
[Music]
there's no challenge we can't overcome
we send them over and watch
[Music]
the milky
i'm not alone
[Music]
the feeling that the feelings and oh my
my upside gratefulness for you guys
being here on my little adventure honor
yes it's an absolute thing to treasure
before ever and ever and ever sunny is
eternal but all the love and support
that you guys have poured out for me is
also going to be eternal terrible term a
total it's not a
i'm going to trigger it forever
before all alive i think i already
mentioned it but my self-esteem isn't
that great
i was pretty much wasting my life away
on the same thing without being able to
do
a lot of things i wanted to do and i
wanted to meet people who like me for
who i am
i wanted to
meet people
from other
walks of life
on earth
that ends up being you guys but whenever
i think about it gives me like just a
warm feeling well i
i'm great i feel like just so much
better about myself when i first joined
hollow life because when you're alone
for so long
i felt really unsure about what i'm
capable of then like you guys stuck
through me even though like it wasn't
always like sunshine's and rainbows the
whole way through yeah that's so so
precious to me i'm just so happy for
this small chance a small opportunity
that i was able to meet people who like
me for who i am
yeah i'm not alone
because you guys are there i could be
myself i could like say like those
randomized things or like just let my
brain like go everywhere and then you
guys like just make it even funnier
it's just so much fun and i hope
everybody in the future i also get to
experience this wonderful feeling of a
community that surrounds and supports
you but you know that kind of thing only
happens because you guys support the
girls and the other talents and everyone
so that is why i really want to say it's
so important to it's why it's so
important to support them
you should everyone else i just really
deserve it and i
i first-handedly
experienced that so thank you so so
much
thank you so so so much
i'm not crying because i'm sad i'm just
crying because i'm just really grateful
and so touched
there's people like you
i was able to find people like you on
earth and i feel this way and i hope
that everybody who watches the girls and
supports all their endeavors you know
give this feeling to the other girls
because i want them to experience this
kind of thing
if that's all i needed then it would
have been really nice but things are
really complicated as well i'm just
really really grateful and i just wanted
to put into words what you've done for
me
yeah don't cry because it's over cry
because i'm crying because it's hap it
happened
what
from a legend
hello
you know what i want i want headphones
we work so hard on these thermal lights
i have the whole set yeah gave birth to
look at all the penguins but like um if
it was possible no no
terrible
you look cute no yeah the tail is thick
time with all of you guys
remain on our cranius
we love you
[Music]
foreign