[Music]
you
[Applause]
[Music]
so
you
[Music]
so
[Applause]
[Music]
hey
hello welcome everybody to the first
full holy tonic
[Music]
thank you
no
[Music]
yeah second up is me i i i am the
first real real bird actually in the
whole life
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
look at my guarding phone picture it
looks like a phoenix doesn't it
i
am peafowl not turkey
[Music]
[Laughter]
and after that mummy joined me please
[Music]
generation of holo life english
i am an owl not a towel
[Laughter]
at least recently we have another hollow
bird psyche
[Music]
jp6 generation
uh horadori new member nice to meet you
yay
[Music]
what what kind of burn this
happy
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
so guys today we are here with these
horritory members and by the way if if
you have not seen it yet
nice
yeah thank you
for putting it on the screen i got it
because i've just thought like ah we
were such a cute lovely group we need
something to connect one another
[Music]
this logo is so cute thank you the
footsteps
the steps on the bottom so cute yeah
it's so cute
really i also think so
lucky
international
[Music]
[Laughter]
i think we should start with normal
normal mode but we can try other modes
too later maybe okay
okay a reminder of the prompts please
write in english
[Music]
for sure
oh whatever let's just go with the
basics
okay okay
[Applause]
wait what about the prompts we never
said anything about the prompt oh my
gosh
um
hello
i don't know
just anything i'll improvise i think
this is good i think this is like a good
opening yeah
yeah we never said anything about the
prompt you know something related to
holotoria
hollow birds dancing
i i don't know how
to ah
okay okay uh okay okay
dancing i admit that
uh i've drawn i've drawn louis before
but i don't really um remember because
you know i see her and she's only like
half half the body right
so
so i'm just gonna i'm just gonna yolo it
out
yolo dancing
and uh shuba dancing
yes shaking the yeah
[Laughter]
and kiama
kiawa
wait i don't remember how to draw
anybody oh no oh no i should have
provided references or at least like
put them like slightly like up you know
yeah i think you know i think can you
guys tell that they're dancing
can you guys tell i think so i think you
guys can tell i'm sorry mummy for making
you bald but
you know
we're on a time time restrictions here
sorry mummy you're bald and
finally it's me i can be bald because
you know uh there's not much time
the notes help yeah i think yeah i think
this is um
and they're all yeah they're not holding
mics so i think it's um
yeah i think this is cool um
let's color this
let's color this and you know just just
try to like identify
so that it's clear who's who
is like this okay
[Laughter]
yeah i think this is pretty cool
it shows who's who
yep
yeah what about the i think that's the i
think that's a very good uh telling
picture how do you guys like it well the
writing is real no it's not real we're
just it's because we have time
constraints all right um
i think um we talk
huh
um
uh let's let's
yes
i think it's because you know we want to
write it in english but also make sure
the english is easy to understand so i'm
just going to write it uh in a simpler
way
spice a spicy spicy
um
okay i'm gonna i'm gonna oh i'm gonna
try to draw as fast as i can
i'm gonna try to draw as fast as i can
um
yes yes yes yes let's go
she she yes yes yes yes yes
[Music]
yes yes yes yes
she oh i think if i color like you can't
tell anyway like who's who and who's
like doing what
yes yes yes yes
yes yes yes let's go
yes
oh they're not close enough to each
other but that's okay maybe if i um do
this like it will be you know yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay yeah yeah okay if i do this like
they will know who it is
spicy
spicy oops wrong color
yeah i think this is good guys do you
think do you think this illustrates like
their kiss they're like they're not
kissing but like soon to be they're
gonna okay like oh okay at the
okay that looks like they're looking at
each other
[Music]
ah no time no time no time no time i
wanted to like put like a sensor
[Music]
let's go
we're on a roll today
type your description okay wait okay um
we can go back
down
uh a movie is fine i think uh mummy
now loading
yes
done
yes yes yes
now loading i think that's okay
[Music]
mommy forgot
hello
we need more more difficult prompts next
time
a lot of birds a lot of very birds
that's okay that's no problem um let's
look at it together okay okay
okay
let's go we're starting
oh
so cute
this is my chat's fault okay can you
hear it you can hear me
yeah yeah
hi um
[Music]
are you saving everything
i will never listen to chat again i'm
saving i saved it let's go okay
next one from dana
look at me ocean
um before before the stream started uh
me and elena told uh subverted simba and
the others that we're going to the
maldives to make them yeah yeah yeah
yeah
and they were really excited to join so
what are samples i want to come too
right
yes
dynamic title i surprised this horritory
in molding
[Laughter]
[Music]
one is missing so good job
you added me again
[Laughter]
easy
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank you
mine's similar
[Laughter]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
louis and mummy kissing so we have a
subaru kissing
[Laughter]
speed drawing oh no how fast is fast i
don't know
[Laughter]
boys
see it's not just me me not it's
yes
m
true
masterpiece i think
i think this is a masterpiece don't you
guys agree
yeah don't you guys agree that this is a
masterpiece
whatever
eating each other
spicy
let's make a let's make a banned
illustration then
[Music]
with guitar
the drums
and then um
and then mummy
with the
keyboard i think
maybe i should have been on the
keyboards for you know the keyboard
jokes
then wow
and then
i'm with
i'm with i don't know xylophone maybe i
don't even know
uh bass dewey on the bass are we missing
any instrument i don't think so
that's your
hi
that was so fast
[Music]
so difficult to write the piano
so many people use horotoni so i always
have to draw draw five people
really putting some milk on chiara
sorry
[Laughter]
[Music]
the beach i like this one nice one
has a nice booty in that picture oh yeah
first thing i drill oh yeah
nice
[Laughter]
[Music]
and the duck
oh
[Laughter]
nice
everybody will eat ducks
[Music]
[Laughter]
it is a bird eat bird well
oh
[Laughter]
i love that that looks so good
[Music]
is
that's a good misunderstanding nice yeah
play a different round a different mode
um
oh
[Music]
let's go
[Applause]
hey guys what do we draw we should draw
spicy stuff um
yeah we should draw we should draw more
kissing stuff
yeah we'll just yeah we'll just make
this as spicy as we can um we have a
chiara
[Music]
okay you know what i'm gonna relive i'm
gonna relive my own i'm gonna relive my
own um
you know i'm gonna relive my own uh
kiara and subaru because
because it became saiso before
um who do you think should be on the
right who do you think should be on the
right
um
like holding hands
[Music]
why why
omg
please
i don't know
i i i don't have reference i don't have
reference oh my god i don't know how to
draw kiara dang um
yolo
yolo yolo um
[Music]
wow
holding hands
how do i draw a sliver senpai
yes i think like this
i think like this
omg
um
spicy
[Music]
what should she say i don't know
i don't know i don't actually know
okay we still have time let's just color
this so like we we know who's who
let's just color this so we know who's
who at least like it doesn't need to be
like a perfect drawing or anything
but let's just uh make it obvious that
you know i think
um
i like this okay
and
yes
omg
um what's kiara's eye color hi c
yes yes
omg
um and then she needs this this color
but
ah wrong color wrong color
hmm
this is this this rainy truly say so of
course
of course i'm say so what are you what
are you
i'm the most say-so-hollow bird in the
hollow bird in the hollow bird
what's kiara's nails what's the color of
kiara's nails tell me i don't know i
don't actually know
um
[Laughter]
uh
very very truly a bye
say so
it say so it's fairy say so
yes
anything we need to add no nothing i
guess
i think we're good
yes
blue hat what do you mean blue hat what
blue hat
perfect
very very perfect
we're done
the second half i don't know she doesn't
have her second hat on this picture
so ah yeah
um
[Music]
oh memories okay so this is
i don't think the order matters
i want iago to wear glasses like
sunglasses
so
this is
two three four five
um
first one is mummy i think
and then maybe it's me i think yeah
it doesn't look like me or or kiara i
don't really remember
and then
senpai
and then i'm gonna draw the beach and
fish
a bit later
um let's add the color so people know
who's who
so people know who's who
[Music]
what is this
eating strawberry
i get it
maybe maybe here this this this i think
and
all right
me and mushroom
[Laughter]
okay let's draw
hmm
[Music]
very stressful stress yes
let's take a look at
what it turned out to be
me
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
interpretations
uh oh it just looks like i'm sexually
harassing someone
they're like profusely sweating
why not start sweating
why did you make them sweat
because the asmr was just too much to
handle
you need to put that up on the on my fan
art hashtag oh yes oh yes
it was from that prop my my previous
prom
because it failed yeah
i'll save that one that one is precious
oh yeah
spicy sample pie
oh
mushroom
[Music]
right
[Applause]
[Music]
i missed something important i'm sorry
mummy left early
i'm sorry sorry mummy chill sorry she
had something to do
um
sorry
i'm sorry
like memorized oh
no time either
[Laughter]
abstract right here
you look at it and you think what do you
what do you see
how does it make you feel yeah depending
on what you see you can learn someone's
personality
[Music]
[Laughter]
but no way she can do that with a mouse
oh
yeah
i have the time
oh
[Laughter]
is that a cherry tomato or a strawberry
moment i was going for it i was going
for strawberry oh okay yeah um
tomato
think about what you want to draw nani
or kakuko
[Music]
again or what yeah let's do knockoff
again oh my god
oh damn um
we can try animation and maybe
oh
[Music]
um
rainy kissing feet are you serious
i'm gonna draw this
i'm gonna draw um
this this this
ah i know i know i get it i get it i
know what to draw
i'm gonna draw a chiara and i i think
how do i draw her okay maybe
i don't remember how to draw her outfit
you know
usually like i joke around being like if
you don't remember how to draw the
outfit then just just don't draw her
just don't just draw her without clothes
on but this is a stream i can't do that
you know so
i guess i have to draw her with clothes
on
[Music]
okay
i'm just like blatantly looking for
looking at refs like here
yes yes yes yes yes
i'm drawing something uh very yummy oh
my god
[Music]
and
i'm i'm i'm and holding with a kiara
so spicy
what's the color of her yeah
yes yes yes yes
um i think this looks enough like her
you know for a guard tick phone picture
like there's really no time
there's really no time to like draw so
detailed
yeah
uh huh and what about her
this color i think
and
and what else are green
yeah i am too lazy to pick colors so i'm
just going to use this color i'm sorry
kiawa
sorry kiawa but it is how it is
it is what it is
um what's my eye color oh i'll just
choose this green it doesn't really
matter
just use this green or blue i don't know
whichever you think is appropriate
whichever you think is appropriate yeah
what do you guys think about this
this spicy drawing
oh my so so spicy
so so spicy
oh no hand holding um
this is like
i know does it look like hand holding oh
sorry i forgot the sensor
hand holding
um
oh
maybe like i just draw this i just draw
the head
oh no
censored
no that's weird okay hand holding omg
love
i don't even understand anymore okay oh
i think this is
i think this is okay hand-holding
yeah
uncensored edition
i think
very good i want to draw a subaru here
and small subaru before time is over
or just everybody else looking
just everybody look in here before time
runs out oh my gosh we have time oh my
god i can't believe we have time
nicer
me
what are these overachievers when it
comes to drawing kiara and silvado
teaching bird 101 and everybody else is
okay
i got you
kiwawa we have kiwawa
and then
that's
the rest of the students are
uh
i gotta
make sure
this is
there's enough time so let me just like
draw the outlines first
uh-huh
yeah so
i think everybody can tell
who are the students
uh-huh yeah this is like the tables and
everything
i think they can tell yeah i'm pretty
sure they can tell
[Music]
hi
okay that's that's a lot of time okay
move down chiara png oh okay okay wait
i'm sorry okay
with bread
with bread but she's bald in a sailor
uniform
okay
[Music]
how do i quickly make her not bald
then yes
nice
hulatory fusion
[Music]
i
okay
[Music]
and then what's in here
what am i teaching you guys something
spicy could it be omg
i don't know guys why
who's that horritory
here we go
wow
nice wow
[Applause]
so different
okay let's take a look
starting with mine
[Applause]
to teach how to be a bird
[Music]
[Laughter]
in order to be a bird you have to know
the abc yes
do we mean do we know abc
abcd
maybe someone can recreate this and make
it into a proper fan art i want to see
it yeah that would be so cool
[Laughter]
please
yes of course i'm always thinking about
you
oh
wait who's that
i think we turned into survivor senpai
because of black hair
your art is so cute
[Music]
um i can do an art stream where i just
uh ship all the hollow birds and make
them
draw them in spicy
[Music]
spicy yeah yeah
spicy oh stand up
uh
why you rice scale face scary face when
i panic
oh funny because late
yourself in a cute way but no you're the
one who portrays yourself in the
terrifying way the most
[Laughter]
[Music]
simple art um with even less time i drew
a bit more complicated and i added the
earring
i
[Laughter]
we love nina i love you
oh yeah
[Music]
what is
turducken with hawk and owl uh do you
mean flamingo
rubbing for bingo
flamingo flamingo and kiwi
duck and go
go at the end go go go
go go go
go go go flamingo and kiwi go go
oh it's exciting as
okay
[Music]
animation
um so guys what what do we draw what do
we draw what what what
who who
who who who
kissing no no no not kissing please
no no not kissing this is the beginning
of the frame
uh you know what yeah sure kissing
everybody's gonna be so sick of kissing
[Music]
who is it who's it gonna be
um
who's it gonna be
what's it gonna be draw
more kissing
adi and mummy uh popular huh
um
because
[Music]
i always forget what kiara looks like
she has like her eyes
and her eyes are like
[Music]
ah
nice
i'm sorry guys
sorry for always drawing kissing people
what's moomy eye color
yeah so we know it's so you know who's
who
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh okay i know how to i know
yes this yes
yes yes
um
and then somebody's gonna come out from
here
uh
maybe
and this is i forgot what green it is i
think it's this green
what
is up
yep
yep okay i think this is good
so like
no but maybe not yet it's not the time
oh shoot
it wasn't the time it's not the time yet
it's not the time yet
so let's just
make um
kiara be kind of like
not noticing
not noticing at all
yep
like so she was doing this
and then
showed up
okay
easy peasy
what is this
okay
[Music]
wait too much there's too many hollow
birds oh no
i oh well
this one is kiara
okay
consume this is how the whole rotory
fusion happened i know right
i'm done
wow i can't wait like to see what kind
of animation
everybody comes up with
oh and moon makes color yeah okay we
have to
oh wait now if we press done we see the
whole picture wait did they change this
or has it been that way from the start
um
okay okay okay okay okay okay
can't believe meme is too hungry
wow very very wholesome we have we still
got a lot of time man remember the the
rounds before they were so so so fast i
barely had time to talk
i was just basically
trying to draw but you know doing
animation after like all that fast
knockoff rounds felt like you know a
really nice cool down
yes yes yes yes no speed run now i hope
everybody can you know make something
interesting
okay
it's gonna end soon must consume
add blood no no no no this is animation
you you can't be greedy like if we just
take everything then the next person
won't have anything to add
[Music]
dewey is crying because kiara
mummy
mama
i think
this is proper
oh it was it was orange
what color was it
think
i think this is
fine
yep
let's make this
[Music]
yep i think that looks good
consume the chicken rib chiara
okay
nice okay
there's a lot of time there is a lot of
time
okay create a new step for the animation
well after this will be the last though
there's a lot of food chain prompts
today it's either food or vacation on
the beach
it's just those two because like i think
before the stream we were talking about
going on vacation
basically you know me and kiara we told
the rest like oh we're going to maldives
and like
you know and oh maybe um in the future
someday
what the heck
hi i'm tensai
okay
okay go go go
go go go
nice
[Laughter]
the ultimate jiggle physics
yes
you guys like the drawing i think it's
pretty genius
booba attack
the hunker is badonkers let's go
rainy what do you mean why am i like
this
you guys i think it's also because like
it's been a while since i last did like
garlic phone
so either you guys don't remember these
kind of things i draw in gothic phone or
you know i guess we have some maybe we
have some new people who's you know
seeing me drawing guarded phone for the
first time so welcome this is the rainy
garden phone experience i think we're
about to see some amazing animation what
do you guys think place your bets
place your bets yo yo
you are the one adding spice to i know
it's like a secret seasoning you know
secret secret seasoning anticipation
[Laughter]
why are you like this but in a positive
way oh come on you flatter me too much
you flatter me
classic garlic we need more sensor bars
yeah i know i realize i don't really put
that much like you know sensor bar i
miss gardek phone you know like with the
whole id mems like for example and like
you know just people in general
it's really really nice um this collab
was supposed to be like um
last month but we had some issues with
it so i mean
not even last month it was like two
months ago but i'm just really glad that
we can finally get together and do this
thing oh wait we're done
hi
[Music]
[Applause]
interesting things going on oh yeah
oh yeah what's going on why is everyone
drawing such sensitive scenes sentences
[Laughter]
like
[Music]
not enough not enough
i think i think it's enough it's a lot
it's not oh
hi
okay take a look oh this is you
you were so happy did you get my idea oh
cute stop oh you guys added oh
who's joining who's that
so scary yeah why so angry
originally was i wan i was um working at
kfp and then music was playing so
start dancing dancing
[Music]
oh
this looks great in animation
nice animation
like i got closer too
yeah and the in the end it turned into a
little snake yeah
i added the eye color
cute
okay
i need to hide my boobies
[Laughter]
[Applause]
explosions
it was very important nina thank you for
that oh yes you're welcome yeah
who is that in the back though
i think
okay
oh i made it
[Laughter]
like an epic gesso
louise skin
mummy eating louis chicken
so dakara
[Laughter]
thanks
[Music]
[Applause]
just
hmm
oh
[Music]
i want to try
uh
wait uh do we still have oh do we still
have time can we do one more animation
one more yeah last one
okay
after once you can have breakfast mommy
are you gonna go back to sleep i'll do
both or i'll just eat more of you guys
i'll give you some substitutes from kfp
okay
[Music]
what should i draw um what should i draw
guys
what should i draw
time for uh maybe um
[Music]
i don't want to draw kissing there's too
much kissing
the story guys too much kissing going on
in here we need to tone down
need to tone it down
i need to tone it down um
and who i wonder i draw mummy a lot i'm
gonna i'm gonna draw
hmm
i'm gonna draw
yes
what's she gonna do i wonder what is she
gonna do
what is she gonna do
yeah i think this looks good
um so this is uh i'm hoping the next
person is gonna pull her right arm back
and then the three four five is just
gonna like do the
ton
yes
but let's see what it develops too yeah
welcome to the royalty thank you so much
hope you enjoy the stream
but yeah
hopefully it'll go as planned hopefully
they can um you know get the message but
previously i think uh the previous
gardek phone like back then we would
sabotage each other's like animations
and like more nonsensical stuff would
like go on which is totally fine too so
i'm kind of curious about you know what
everybody's gonna bring to the table and
what they're gonna do with my animation
i'm also really really interested in
like
what are these people gonna draw are
they gonna draw something yabby because
i'm not drawing the yabe one today so
maybe somebody's gonna draw something
away replace me replace me as the you
know yabe tanto for this session
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes somehow
everyone thought of breast expansion
well yeah i mean it was pretty easy to
tell i think
wow garlic phone is now new you can pick
up the colors from above why did i not
notice that
why did i not notice that
[Music]
um
looks great i think
[Laughter]
sun getting closer and subato's just uh
you know um what do you call it
sorry
you know this
face is like
sound looks oddly sinister as intended
phrase the sun
very nice very very very nice i wonder
what i wonder what they're going to do
with this one
i'll make shiva sweating uh i could do
that
yeah hopefully uh as time goes on
they're gonna like add more sweat
[Music]
the sun is consuming suba
yes yeah this adds the uh you know oh no
i'm sweating so scared or something
yeah speaking of turducken because louie
is a flamingo and women is the kiwi how
would they fit in the turducken
well how would you modify the existing
turducken
what
ah
okay
[Music]
i know what to do with this
i know what to do with this i'll be
surprised
because
i'll be surprised because um
because uh suba
will be
is this shuba or kiara
i think it might be shuba
because i just realized
and let's make these like move a bit
because of the wind
swim suits
this is let's make this like rattle a
bit because you know
nice
i'll i'll put on some clothes on her so
you guys don't be like omg
okay
nice
yeah it looks fine right i think it
looks good
stealing the swimsuit
stealing the swimsuit top
see through t no it's not see-through
you guys why are you what is wrong with
you guys
just add sensor bar no no nobody's naked
like she like i'm in the store i'm on
i'm in the store we can't you know i'll
get arrested if i don't wear clothes in
the public place maybe if it's like not
a public place then it's fine if it's
like somebody's home like in this prom
then it would be fine but here because
i'm in the shop it's not okay
[Music]
yes yes yes yes yes yes keeping it
watchable for all audiences and so we
don't really get arrested yeah we want
uh this this stream is very family
friendly that's why when they were like
holding hands
okay
yeah i don't know
um
i think this is nice
yummy
yum i don't know what's going on sorry
guys
yeah this is what usually happens in the
garcic phone
uh with holo id
like i always do this like people will
be like what the heck rainey
yes
maybe i should add this
yum
looks perfect
what do you think
think it's good it's pretty good we
should add more details on the hair
so that you know
i think it looks
it looks okay
i need to add the telephone cable too
[Music]
okay we got some time we're ready for
this
they kind of don't know that it's the
kfp though so
okay
kfc yeah
yep
okay
color the hat
oh oh oh yeah my bad
okay there we're done
yay
okay
easy peasy
and the last drawing what is this
huh
i don't get it what is this guys
spoon dirt
that's not what i think it is right
it's not what i think it
is it's not what i think it is what is
that
what's this
hmm
i i really don't know what's going on so
i'm just gonna
just gonna try to replicate this
i'm gonna try to replicate this
and then
and then yeah just do what i can i guess
wrong color
[Music]
uh
red
gray
blue
yup
i really don't know what's going on so
i'm just gonna do that
[Laughter]
[Music]
instant teleportation
that's too much details i think
but you can do that
yeah
maybe i don't know
panic roll
peace out everybody i'm gone
time's almost up though i wonder what
they came up with i'm curious i really
didn't understand this thing so i kind
of want to see what's happening
hello
oh
all right last last round let's see what
masterpieces we have created
yes please yes
where will this go
okay
what what oh she turned into person
she turned into the boys and she falls
over
what is this
wow
i don't know after eating after eating
the bikini top she becomes a person
and what's falling on the ground what's
falling on the ground
[Applause]
uh-oh
dana try on some cute swimsuits but okay
this is fine
that's that's great animation for you
yeah
okay okay
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
what i wanted to do is for louie to
[Music]
i like it thank you
thank you she likes it
she likes this video she has an
animation too good job
[Music]
[Laughter]
my implications were that super duper
simple comes pushes away dana and wants
the food for herself ah
i thought like suvaru's trying to get me
to eat something suspicious
looks really nice though the way it goes
up
it was supposed to be a single hair oh
it's nice
ah
[Laughter]
[Music]
why i have terrible
ah
[Music]
the sun
[Laughter]
thank you
[Music]
it's a bird eat bird world after
all it is
yes it's tough out there that's why no
we have to we have to
be strong together
not good not easy drama spirit
wins well because bird is is me because
i am a phoenix and and i will revive no
matter what
uh-huh um what if you revive it and i
can hide in trees
if you get eaten where do you revive
kiara
oh my gosh where do you revive
that that is a that's a different story
i cannot say that okay
but you know because the bird eat bird
world you know what we should collab
someday mina de corazon
[Music]
foreign
did you play super smash brothers before
i have but i'm not good at it ah
damn bad that's good because we're not
[Music]
smash each other so it's okay yeah okay
you would like to see that in a
different meaning too no
and what you're talking about what
are we talking about
out of all of us
[Music]
nice
we're the biggest
group of something i think in holland
really yeah
maybe maybe we can do more stuff
together but getting all of us together
for this collab was already very
difficult
yes
looking forward to uh collaboration
again
yes yes yes yes thank you thank you
thank you everybody
[Music]
yay
you learned some good japanese there and
i said yes thank you i'm so close to
fluent now yes
you're getting closer you're getting
there fight those like you're getting
close to fighting like
this
[Laughter]
that's simple enough one thing we can
remember that our ending greeting will
be otsu
okay okay
okay
everybody thank you for watching today
and in holo today we say
three
two
one
[Music]
[Laughter]
you
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
um
me
[Applause]
[Music]
you