​​​ ​I leaned buh...​ ​​
​​​ ​I... I...​ ​​
​​​ ​I...​ ​​
​​​ ​I can't do it! Aaargh!​ ​​
​
​​​ ​Japanese Culture School!​ ​​
​​​ ​I am your instructor, Tsunomaki Watame.​ ​​
​​​ ​And I, Shishiro Botan, as well.​ ​​
​​​ ​Today we have two students​ ​​
​​ ​who have come from overseas​ ​​
​​​ ​to learn various things about Japan,​ ​​
​​ ​so we shall teach them!​ ​​
​​​ ​That is the gist of this program!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm Takanashi Kiara from hololive English!​ ​​
​​​ ​I am Airani Iofifteen from​ ​​
​​ ​hololive Indonesia's 1st Generation!​ ​​
​​​ ​Both of you are great at Japanese!​ ​​
​​​ ​Right?​ ​​
​​​ ​How did you study Japanese?​ ​​
​​​ ​In my case, books and teachers?​ ​​
​​​ ​I didn't use them at all.​ ​​
​​​ ​I learned Japanese just​ ​​
​​ ​by talking to Japanese people.​ ​​
​​​ ​I see! That's amazing!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, really!​ ​​
​​​ ​For me, my beloved otome games​ ​​
​​ ​are all in Japanese.​ ​​
​​​ ​At that time, there weren't many​ ​​
​​ ​English versions available.​ ​​
​​​ ​So I was like, "Guess I'll study Japanese!"​ ​​
​​​ ​And I did it through passion!​ ​​
​​​ ​Wow!​ ​​
​​​ ​But I still don't really know if the​ ​​
​​ ​Japanese I've learned is really correct or not.​ ​​
​​​ ​Then I suppose that we'll​ ​​
​​​ ​become your teachers!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes, please!​ ​​
​​​ ​Teacher!​ ​​
​​​ ​Please do!​ ​​
​​​ ​Then it's time to start class!​ ​​
​​​ ​The lesson we'll be doing today is this!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ba-dum!​ ​​
​​​ ​Tongue twisters!​ ​​
​​​ ​Do you two know tongue twisters?​ ​​
​​​ ​I do, yeah!​ ​​
​​​ ​I do!​ ​​
​​​ ​ToNgUe TwIsTeRs, is it?​ ​​
​​​ ​There are a lot of funny​ ​​
​​ ​tongue twisters in Japan.​ ​​
​​​ ​So Kiara-chan, Iofi-chan,​ ​​
​​ ​let's fun have learning about them!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ohh!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm ready!​ ​​
​​​ ​Tongue twister quiz!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yay! Let's start!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yay!​ ​​
​​​ ​Quiz?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Watame-senpai will say​ ​​
​​ ​the tongue twister three times first.​ ​​
​​​ ​Then, Kiara and Iofi,​ ​​
​​ ​you'll try to guess what Watame said.​ ​​
​​​ ​Shall we do the first one?​ ​​
​​​ ​Question 1​ ​​
​​​ ​Now then! What is Watame saying?​ ​​
​​​ ​What is Watame-sensei saying?​ ​​
​​ ​Let's all think it over together.​ ​​
​​​ ​Theguestnextdoorisaguest​ ​​
​​ ​whoeasalapersimmons!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hmm, what?​ ​​
​​​ ​Theguestnextdoorisaguest​ ​​
​​ ​wheasalotofpersimmons!​ ​​
​​​ ​What?​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh?​ ​​
​​​ ​Theguestnextdoorisaguest​ ​​
​​ ​whosaalasimons!​ ​​
​​​ ​What?​ ​​
​​​ ​Did you figure out what she said?​ ​​
​​​ ​Hold on, hold on, hold on!​ ​​
​​​ ​What was that?​ ​​
​​​ ​You understood, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​(pressure)​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara, you're first.​ ​​
​​​ ​I heard something about space.​ ​​
​​​ ​Space?!​ ​​
​​​ ​The next door what?​ ​​
​​​ ​The alien next door?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Looks like you got a little part of it.​ ​​
​​​ ​A little part, yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​Watame, once more, if you would.​ ​​
​​​ ​Pay attention! Here I go.​ ​​
​​​ ​Theguestnextdoorisaguest​ ​​
​​ ​whoeasalalapersimmons!​ ​​
​​​ ​What is Watame-sensei saying?​ ​​
​​ ​Let's all think it over together.​ ​​
​​​ ​The next door @&%$%#$?​ ​​
​​​ ​I mean, she's not wrong.​ ​​
​​​ ​She's basically just parroting​ ​​
​​ ​what Watame is saying.​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait? Watame did something wrong?​ ​​
​​​ ​I got it! I got it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ding ding ding ding ding ding ding!​ ​​
​​​ ​You got it?​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, Kiara-san, go ahead!​ ​​
​​​ ​You eat a lot of shaved ice from next door.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, close!​ ​​
​​​ ​You're close!​ ​​
​​​ ​Am I?!​ ​​
​​​ ​You say it, Botan-chan!​ ​​
​​​ ​Who, me?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​Fine. Okay, here I go!​ ​​
​​​ ​What is Botan-sensei saying?​ ​​
​​​ ​The guest next door is a guest​ ​​
​​ ​who eats a lot of persimmons!​ ​​
​​​ ​That was good!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ohh!​ ​​
​​​ ​So good!​ ​​
​​​ ​The guest next door is a guest​ ​​
​​ ​who eats a lot of persimmons!​ ​​
​​​ ​Correct!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ding ding ding!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ding!​ ​​
​​​ ​I couldn't understand what​ ​​
​​ ​you said at all, Watame-senpai!​ ​​
​​​ ​Meaning that my skills still need​ ​​
​​ ​some polishing, huh...​ ​​
​​​ ​Time for ​Kiara ​and ​Iofi to try!​ ​​
​​​ ​The guest next door is a guest​ ​​
​​ ​who eats alaffa...​ ​​
​​ ​who ates alhaf...​ ​​
​​​ ​The guest next door is ahgaft hufw...​ ​​
​​​ ​KFP reigns supreme!​ ​​
​​​ ​KFP (Kiara Fried Phoenix):​ ​​
​​ ​The fast-food chain that Kiara runs.​ ​​
​​​ ​Clang clang clang!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yay!​ ​​
​​​ ​The guest next door is a guest​ ​​
​​ ​who eastatlo... pershimins!​ ​​
​​ ​who easalalalasimmons!​ ​​
​​​ ​The next-door...​ ​​
​​​ ​The next-door alien​ ​​
​​ ​doesn't eat persimmons!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes.​ ​​
​​​ ​Question 2​ ​​
​​​ ​Here's the next tongue twister.​ ​​
​​​ ​What is Watame-sensei saying?​ ​​
​​ ​Let's all think it over together.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ileanedbambooagainstthis​ ​​
​​ ​bamboofencebecauseIwantedto​ ​​
​​​ ​leanbambooagainst​ ​​
​​ ​itsoIleanedbambooagainstit​ ​​
​​​ ​Ileanedbambooagainstthis​ ​​
​​ ​bamboofencebecauseIwantedto​ ​​
​​​ ​leanbambooagainst​ ​​
​​ ​itsoIleanedbambooagainstit​ ​​
​​​ ​Ileanedbambooagainstthis​ ​​
​​ ​bamboofencebecauseIwantedto​ ​​
​​​ ​leanbambooagainst​ ​​
​​ ​itsoIleanedbamboo​ ​​
​​​ ​against it, yeah!​ ​​
​​​ ​I've heard this one!​ ​​
​​​ ​You got it?​ ​​
​​​ ​bamboobamboobamboo​ ​​
​​ ​bamboobamboobamboobamboo​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh no! The only thing she got was bamboo!​ ​​
​​​ ​Maybe a little bit slower...​ ​​
​​​ ​Maybe the two of us​ ​​
​​ ​can read it off slowly?​ ​​
​​​ ​Slowly? Okay.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's all think it over together.​ ​​
​​​ ​I ​l​e​a​n​e​d ​b​a​m​b​o​o ​a​g​a​i​n​st​ ​​
​​​ ​t​h​i​s ​b​a​m​b​o​o ​f​e​n​c​e ​b​e​c​a​u​s​e ​I ​w​a​n​t​e​d ​to​ ​​
​​​ ​l​e​a​n ​b​a​m​b​o​o ​a​g​a​i​n​s​t ​i​t ​so​ ​​
​​​ ​I ​l​e​a​n​e​d ​b​a​m​b​o​o ​a​g​a​i​n​s​t ​i​t.​ ​​
​​​ ​I still have no idea, even like that!​ ​​
​​​ ​I felt absolutely no rhythm from that.​ ​​
​​​ ​Read it with some rhythm, then, Watame.​ ​​
​​​ ​What is Watame-sensei saying?​ ​​
​​ ​Let's all think it over together.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yo, yo!​ ​​
​​​ ​I leaned bamboo against this​ ​​
​​ ​bamboo fence because I wanted to​ ​​
​​​ ​lean bamboo against it so​ ​​
​​ ​I leaned bamboo against it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yo, yo, yo!​ ​​
​​​ ​That was good! Better!​ ​​
​​​ ​Did you get it?!​ ​​
​​​ ​How about you answer with some rhythm?​ ​​
​​​ ​I leaned bamboo against​ ​​
​​​ ​this bamboo fence because​ ​​
​​​ ​I...​ ​​
​​​ ​wanted to lean bamboo against it​ ​​
​​​ ​so I leaned bamboo against it.​ ​​
​​​ ​That kinda worked?​ ​​
​​​ ​That works! She got that, right?!​ ​​
​​​ ​This is what you said.​ ​​
​​​ ​Bam!​ ​​
​​​ ​I leaned bamboo against this​ ​​
​​ ​bamboo fence because​ ​​
​​​ ​I wanted to lean bamboo against it​ ​​
​​​ ​so I leaned bamboo against it.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'd heard this one before,​ ​​
​​​ ​so I kinda figured that was it.​ ​​
​​​ ​I see!​ ​​
​​​ ​Time for ​Kiara ​and ​Iofi to try!​ ​​
​​​ ​I leaned bamboo buhgainst...​ ​​
​​​ ​I leaned bamboo buh-buh...​ ​​
​​​ ​I leaned buh...​ ​​
​​​ ​I... I...​ ​​
​​​ ​I...​ ​​
​​​ ​I can't do it! Aaargh!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm gonna explode!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's all up to you, Iofi-senpai!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey, wait!​ ​​
​​​ ​Your expressions!​ ​​
​​​ ​They're lifeless!​ ​​
​​​ ​H-H-Here I go!​ ​​
​​​ ​I leaned bamboo buhgainst​ ​​
​​ ​this bamboo fence because​ ​​
​​​ ​I banted to lean bamboo​ ​​
​​ ​against it, so I leaned...​ ​​
​​​ ​Bamboo?​ ​​
​​​ ​bamboo against it!​ ​​
​​​ ​I feel like you handled​ ​​
​​ ​the last one better, Iofi-senpai.​ ​​
​​​ ​True...​ ​​
​​​ ​That's because that one was with rhythm.​ ​​
​​​ ​Perhaps your Japanese ability​ ​​
​​ ​has improved after this?​ ​​
​​​ ​That's enough of the tongue twisters.​ ​​
​​ ​Let's go to the next lesson!​ ​​
​​​ ​Here's the next lesson we're going to do!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ba-dum!​ ​​
​​​ ​Proverbs!​ ​​
​​​ ​Watame-sensei, can you explain​ ​​
​​ ​what proverbs are?​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait.​ ​​
​​​ ​I...​ ​​
​​​ ​I was just going​ ​​
​​ ​to ask you that, Botan-chan!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's being a ​pro ​with verbs.​ ​​
​​​ ​Quite.​ ​​
​​​ ​A ​pro ​with verbs.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh!​ ​​
​​​ ​A ​pro ​with ​verbs...​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah...​ ​​
​​​ ​Verbs...​ ​​
​​​ ​So what are they, Botan-chan?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Proverbs are, like,​ ​​
​​ ​short lessons in the form​ ​​
​​​ ​of single sentences​ ​​
​​ ​passed down from long ago.​ ​​
​​​ ​Now that's teachin'.​ ​​
​​​ ​That's what I'd say.​ ​​
​​​ ​By the way, the script we've got​ ​​
​​ ​for this part is pretty threadbare.​ ​​
​​​ ​Neither Watame nor I have any idea​ ​​
​​ ​which proverbs we'll be teaching you today.​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, we know they're related to Japan.​ ​​
​​​ ​Both of us teachers​ ​​
​​ ​are very knowledgeable.​ ​​
​​​ ​Indeed.​ ​​
​​​ ​You'll be in good hands with us,​ ​​
​​​ ​s-so please come along with us.​ ​​
​​​ ​Please join us.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm in!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay!​ ​​
​​​ ​Question 1​ ​​
​​​ ​Here's one of the proverbs​ ​​
​​ ​we'll be teaching you!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ba-dum!​ ​​
​​​ ​"Do thy laundry whilst the demon is away."​ ​​
​​​ ​Have you heard this one?​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't go to the laundromat at night​ ​​
​​ ​or a demon will show up, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​That may not be entirely correct.​ ​​
​​​ ​Then, Japanese people, what does it mean?​ ​​
​​ ​What does it mean?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Please explain in detail.​ ​​
​​​ ​The demon is...​ ​​
​​​ ​Your wife?​ ​​
​​​ ​While your wife is away...​ ​​
​​​ ​Maybe this...​ ​​
​​ ​Maybe it's something to do with husbands?​ ​​
​​​ ​Am I wrong?​ ​​
​​​ ​Is that wrong?​ ​​
​​​ ​Husbands?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Husbands?​ ​​
​​​ ​That can't be it!​ ​​
​​​ ​We're the students here,​ ​​
​​ ​so teachers, please teach us.​ ​​
​​​ ​Please teach us!​ ​​
​​​ ​Tell 'em, Watame.​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't know!​ ​​
​​​ ​Tell us, Botan-sensei!​ ​​
​​​ ​Botan-sensei!​ ​​
​​​ ​This, well...​ ​​
​​​ ​The demon here means​ ​​
​​ ​"the person who intimidates you."​ ​​
​​​ ​"When the person who scares you​ ​​
​​ ​isn't around, you're able to relax."​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm pretty sure that's​ ​​
​​ ​what this proverb means.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, that!​ ​​
​​​ ​That!​ ​​
​​​ ​We seem to have an answer written here.​ ​​
​​​ ​We do?​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's take a look.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ba-dum!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ding!​ ​​
​​​ ​When a scary person,​ ​​
​​ ​such as your boss, a senpai,​ ​​
​​​ ​or a person you are hesitant around is gone,​ ​​
​​​ ​you can relax and take a breather.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's not literally about doing laundry,​ ​​
​​​ ​but a metaphor about washing​ ​​
​​ ​your mind clean and refreshing yourself.​ ​​
​​​ ​Botan-sensei​ ​​
​​ ​Correct​ ​​
​​​ ​Gotcha!​ ​​
​​​ ​I see!​ ​​
​​​ ​Wow!​ ​​
​​​ ​Do you have a "demon" in your case, Iofi?​ ​​
​​​ ​A demon-like person?​ ​​
​​​ ​I wouldn't quite say she's a demon, but...​ ​​
​​​ ​I suppose I'd say my manager.​ ​​
​​​ ​What?!​ ​​
​​​ ​"Please be nice to her, manager."​ ​​
​​ ​—by Watame-sensei​ ​​
​​​ ​Question 2​ ​​
​​​ ​Here's the next proverb!​ ​​
​​​ ​What is this?​ ​​
​​​ ​Hm? What is this?​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey, wait a sec.​ ​​
​​​ ​What?​ ​​
​​​ ​To cleave a chicken... do what?​ ​​
​​​ ​What is this?​ ​​
​​​ ​To cleave a chicken doth not​ ​​
​​ ​demand a butcher's knife.​ ​​
​​​ ​Do you get it, Iofi?​ ​​
​​​ ​No clue.​ ​​
​​​ ​No clue here, either.​ ​​
​​​ ​Do...​ ​​
​​​ ​you have something you want​ ​​
​​ ​to say to me, management?​ ​​
​​​ ​Takanashi Kiara profile:​ ​​
​​ ​A phoenix, NOT a chicken or turkey (very important)​ ​​
​​​ ​I can sense that.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm not a chicken! I'm a phoenix!​ ​​
​​​ ​They're similar, but they're different!​ ​​
​​​ ​Should we cleave you and find out?​ ​​
​​​ ​What is this, a horror game?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Butcher's knife?​ ​​
​​​ ​One of those big ones​ ​​
​​ ​they use to slice up cows.​ ​​
​​​ ​Butcher's knife:​ ​​
​​ ​A large knife used to cut beef and such.​ ​​
​​​ ​So it means using that to cut a chicken...​ ​​
​​​ ​Not me! They don't mean me!​ ​​
​​​ ​To cleave Kiara doth not​ ​​
​​ ​demand a butcher's knife.​ ​​
​​​ ​Does it mean that using a butcher knife to cut​ ​​
​​ ​a chicken is doing more than you need to?​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh! I get it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, could be!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ya don't need to grab somethin' so big​ ​​
​​ ​to take care'a somethin' so tiny!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah! You bet!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's see the answer!​ ​​
​​​ ​Meaning: You don't need to use​ ​​
​​ ​extreme methods to deal with a small thing.​ ​​
​​​ ​Nice!​ ​​
​​​ ​Watame-sensei was correct!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yay!​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara-chan, you were right, too!​ ​​
​​​ ​All right!​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara-sensei!​ ​​
​​​ ​Looking at this,​ ​​
​​ ​it's pretty much a literal meaning.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, surprisingly.​ ​​
​​​ ​There are quite a few proverbs​ ​​
​​ ​you can take literally.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, true!​ ​​
​​​ ​There's much more I want to teach you,​ ​​
​​​ ​but we're done for today!​ ​​
​​​ ​Aww!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yep. Too bad.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, too bad.​ ​​
​​​ ​Aww!​ ​​
​​​ ​How did you like it?​ ​​
​​​ ​I learned a lot!​ ​​
​​​ ​It was fun!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yay!​ ​​
​​​ ​Clap clap!​ ​​
​​​ ​I think I'll teach these to​ ​​
​​ ​my viewers sometime!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, nice!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah!​ ​​
​​​ ​For the finale,​ ​​
​​​ ​I've got an original proverb​ ​​
​​ ​to present to you!​ ​​
​​​ ​Original?​ ​​
​​​ ​That's what it says in the script!​ ​​
​​​ ​Have you awakened?​ ​​
​​​ ​I wanna hear it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Please listen attentively.​ ​​
​​​ ​"If you join hololive,​ ​​
​​ ​a fine comedian​ ​​
​​ ​you shall surely be."​ ​​
​​ ​—Watame​ ​​
​​​ ​"Hey, ain't that a senryu?!" Someone!​ ​​
​​​ ​"Hey, ain't that a senryu?!" Please!​ ​​
​​​ ​Anything but silence, please!​ ​​
​​​ ​Wonderful.​ ​​
​​​ ​Anything but that!​ ​​
​​​ ​Silence...​ ​​
​​​ ​Next time I want to do a lesson​ ​​
​​ ​on haiku and senryu.​ ​​
​​​ ​Silence!​ ​​
​​​ ​You wanna do that?​ ​​
​​​ ​Thank you for today.​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara-chan, Iofi-chan,​ ​​
​​ ​please handle the ending!​ ​​
​​​ ​Please like this video​ ​​
​​​ ​and subscribe to the official​ ​​
​​ ​hololive channel and our channels!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, everybody!​ ​​
​​​ ​G​o​o​d​b​y​e!​ ​​