[Music]
foreign
s are um I think
um they will be doing promotion first on
their stream yeah and since we already
did our promotion yesterday so we're
just gonna chit chat right now I guess
yes
[Applause]
you guys want to hear it again
oh my God what happened
by the way oh yeah any of you guys are
wondering it's on our description it is
on my description yeah and everyone's
description oh oh I kind of want to
wanna know
yeah so apparently uh I did an oopsie I
said that oh my God yeah pre-order is
closing an inner sloth and a hollow life
website no it's actually only closing
for the whole website yeah that's only
for the whole life website yeah
merchandisers you should still be able
to get them yeah even after the day yes
yeah yeah for the whole life one you can
get it until 11 59 PM JSC today yeah
today today
today November 28th which is our dinner
spot it's just still going so you guys
can chill
um
[Laughter]
wait what
oh oh okay
okay
oh
yeah there's only inside for the Ians
right now yeah
yep oh in the game you got um
hahaha
oh yeah yeah yeah
oh my God
it's Monday
happy yeah
um
well but here's the question for you
guys
from all of the merchandise that hollow
life and Among Us is happening right now
which one do you guys are most
interested in
oh I like the keychain with all the IDS
and Ian's like thank you keychain I I
love this holiday
oh I like that one too the emergency
kitchen yeah
oh yeah the key holders yes
I love them what about you
who's nothing
there's a lot of you in here
there's a lot of you a same same
emergency kitchen um
I'm very much interested like you guys
said I like all of the key holders
Miyabi senpai's especially already put
an order in that one
yeah remember you guys you guys you guys
can get any OC from hollow life
Productions yeah yeah
and even Stars ain't that cool
I actually haven't seen the Stars One
the Stars merchandises oh it's cute a
lot more like a charm yeah yeah
I need to check them out
I think if if we're talking about merch
I like the plushy [\h__\h]
like ah
[Music]
oh my God the real picture it's so good
right
I wonder if we can get like the Airship
if you buy the whole thing
um
[Music]
that will be spicy
yeah yes get them all before
wait
uh-huh before what before tomorrow right
um
no it will be gone by today if you're
talking about like Indonesian time
foreign
I kind of want it but they don't ship to
Indonesia unfortunately you know what
you gotta do you need tips
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
papaya oh yeah
[Music]
just in time for the reason to die I'll
make another one
thank you thank you
uh okay should we just play the the
basic the most basic one for for the
first one oh yeah sure sure I'm okay
with anything
okay
basic it is
already had a moga stream like this
right like four hours ago or so yeah
yeah yesterday
[Laughter]
why are you guys so fast
so fast
remote
come on all right
streamer mode works
[Music]
really tired huh everyone's tired or
sick the tire tell us
I think foreign
do we want to do like uh you know a
classic introduction of everyone yeah it
can also be a sound check maybe yeah
soundtrack it starts by the top button
yeah hello everyone hello it's on your
mouth is second generation how how's my
voice
[Music]
it's awesome
I'm gonna Channel my sleepiness to being
the best rat that I can
um hello
everybody
oh no you silly yeah
sexy
oh yeah
there's Bale's in the room yet I don't
sit here in the room no I'm not I don't
know oh yeah
I think next we are hiding what are you
hiding coconut I'm shy do you want to
hide with me yeah
[Music]
right
trying the whole life Cosmic Cube hello
somebody's dog
[Music]
okay compared to everyone else exactly
Beauty
is is you're just beautiful
you know that's all natural
yeah the natural beauty you know you
were born naked the natural beauty
I'll join you've convinced me
you're turning to Nature
clothes okay
I'm going to kill everyone
the sound effect is sending me
they say crony's low but I have her on
Max I can't do anything else
it's just her voice maybe her voice
you said you're too low yeah
well I think that needed
but then nothing happens I'm sorry
okay oh my god oh say again crony is is
this loud enough now yeah um
[Applause]
so crazy
let's have a fun promoting theme
everybody whoa
hold her yeah ready amazing
thank you for bringing me the energy
that we need
school
I felt that in my eyeballs
who's pantings
uh
[Music]
we did not only
incredible amazing intro
girls
[Music]
thank you for waking up so early
hello oh hi I'm the national movie from
all live English I have a stuffy nose to
go men
why didn't register to me that you're
saying oh hi I thought you were saying
Ohio but then you just cut it halfway
because you couldn't be bothered today
I also heard
nashimum she's just saving letters she's
saving time here come on
[Applause]
excuse me
[Music]
music okay
mutagus
oh I'm a crew man now
all right it's a pretty easy dolls all
of them is electrical the so easy
I'm really gonna be really fast
there we go
I don't like the Richter Middleton
creature meltdown
oh
don't worry
I'm gonna crewmate
all right
[Music]
can I change my BM
somehow I think one thing I want to
change my VM
[Music]
um
but I don't know what's a museum
oh what this one
oh wait that is the same one
how about this one
no no no no no no no
ah this one
I love this
oh no
oh no where's the body
oh two buddies yeah there's yeah oh yeah
where was everyone at
well
I was around I
just I just arrived on the shield
oh sorry but only should be muted
and all it should be muted never mind
the body I need to look at the map okay
um
[Music]
the body
oh
wait oh but like I've been traveling
like everywhere else like I've been
traveling the right side of the section
so I didn't really notice anything like
I was checking samples
[Music]
yeah we were on the right side
um yeah
[Music]
so fast
[Applause]
I don't understand did you all see it I
didn't yeah it was like it was like yeah
I saw it it went like that in front of
my eyes oh
all right we're all there together so
cronies kind of sauce yeah yeah she has
an obvious
um reason to do it
um you do it in front of my salad
oh yeah
[Music]
they were together though
well goodbye crony wait can I undo mine
well you know okay fine I'm just gonna
like yes I am the Imposter but guess
what oh my God
I'm gonna give this the Innocence the
win so
um
sorry for the team kill all right bye
bye
really
[Music]
oh my God
that was a really sassy line
nice trial
I shocks again
the other one is in there the other one
is in there the other one is in there
okay no one
[Music]
I'm seeking
zero four eight three oh
well that was fast
again
totally calculated so embarrassing
guys I just want to say if someone is uh
someone is being choosing as imposer and
the Imposter said that the next imposter
is someone don't believe it
I want to like make the vote Anonymous
yeah
[Music]
the thing is I already said Anya and
Zetta were in the room which means that
they're going to be innocent the only
two people around me were Kiara I had to
choose between the two
we both did so much work for us to win
that round right I was not happy I
totally had no hesitation to kill
anybody anymore
yeah but thank you for not voting me out
appreciate but there's one person
missing in the room local ready
I thank you ollie like when I was about
to walk over and Anya was there and I
was like crony you just got me in so
much trouble
it worked out though I'm also sorry to
everyone in advance but hey that's the
game
let's wait in the discussion and
Courtney was like no it was like people
were there and then everyone else seemed
not convinced and I'm like she
[Laughter]
were the ones in the room yeah
and like I was like I was hoping I was
hoping that Zeta would say something so
that people wouldn't ask me yeah she was
doing tasks
the funny thing is that I was like I was
about to go out from that room so if
only you had waited for like a few more
seconds I probably wouldn't have thought
that you know
100 or crony learned her lesson for next
round right yeah yeah twice
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Music]
[\h__\h]
oh no granny
how can I be impossible twice
it's very dangerous
people
and I was trying my best trying to turn
it on but people kept turning it off
but if you wouldn't have just admitted
immediately that it was you that I
wouldn't have known because there was so
much going on
you don't you shouldn't run away
I was in there I was in there because
electrical was out and everyone else was
right yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah how
could we know it was her we don't know
if it was her
killing it
okay too much yeah I saw it I don't know
I saw it that's why that's why I moved
the way I saw a movie like I don't know
I don't know no it's not Mommy I saw
Grande in front of my eyes killing it
was very unfortunate
[Applause]
oh you know besides what Luna said crony
just incriminated herself right away
anyway
[Music]
who knows
Direction melt down wonders look so fast
like I know I'm not even finished it I
don't know even finish it like
all right
give us time
okay
foreign
good
good good good good good good good good
good good good
good
oh
why is it mummy
okay
chasing me and then she went off to the
right side of the map
running around yeah
I thought he was the Imposter because
she was chasing me but she sorry it
sounds so suspicious right now I know I
do but you look confused to me nobody
chasing me around the table but I almost
called a meeting because I was like
that's kind of susp and I was like oh
it's movie so it's just probably just
being normal yeah it's probably
why did Ollie call the meeting just to
check actually I want to do a little
promotions
[Music]
yeah sure today
um why did you go to the electrical for
like one second and then you went out
immediately
oh I was just checking to see who's
inside
why won't you check who's inside why
can't I check who's inside I can be like
oh
why would you do that I mean that was
kind of sad yeah yeah if you don't have
any tasks like inside the electrical
then why won't you go inside
and see if I could stick to anyone
I mean Ollie and me were like going out
of the room why why didn't you like go
with us instead wow it's like you
definitely will tell us intense Zeta are
you going to the electrical just to
maybe
do something only we're like going out
but like you you like you you were like
going inside for like one second and
then you came out immediately
if you if you thought if you were trying
to like find someone then why didn't you
go with us
well because I don't want to get killed
there
were all in electrical we got somebody
got killed
[Music]
um
for that
McCombs is getting Savage
very scums
oh a song
foreign
[Music]
okay thank you
thank you again
[Music]
again
okay
[Music]
foreign
thank you
we're going down first
what up what up hello
when we were all in the admin room and
then I saw someone teleporting from
storage to the main lobby
[Music]
of us who were in the bathroom oh yeah
it wasn't me phone and Kiana you know
what what's interesting is that Zeta
came after that
I came from yeah but I wasn't I was like
it came from the other side I was
walking I don't know I didn't see anyone
teleporting though but Zetta Zeta was
like yeah I said I came to admin I came
here
yeah and we were doing stuff
interesting interesting I'm I'm
suspicious interesting so who can you
describe
it took to arrive at your destination
um I'm just gonna say I finished my task
s
i I have one left left the wiring
with those who haven't who haven't
finished the task
sure sure
okay I'm gonna I'm gonna go with Moana
Senpai then okay let's go with you guys
too and I can
are we voting Anya we need Anya to vote
oh yeah I'm sorry can you go skipping I
I wrote it I voted
no I hope you like space accidents
oh foreign
game over
[Music]
here
I think okay sauce okay good job
yeah cause that was so sucks I didn't
teleport by the way talking
[Music]
I thought you were just ignoring me on
purpose I have no idea how that song
goes I didn't even know that was a song
until later on
[Laughter]
do you want to try a different map or
stay in the same map girls
[Music]
I don't get imposter because I don't
know
mommy I'll make a new room I don't
really know the other metal okay yeah
you have to make a game I think
I'm gonna leave any wishes all right so
um
[Music]
is that the winter one the snowy one
snowy is the hardest one I think okay
let's try let's try paulus I guess I
don't like it that much but sure it
might be fun okay
[Music]
let's go
thank you
oh okay
man
well that was the place
okay okay
oh I can't I couldn't go from there
foreign
[Music]
oh office office
um
didn't you report
yeah
bye by the way I go to office first and
then I saw a movie nearby I think
no I was from the office and then it was
on the left room right left room of the
office
I think so I was in the office and and
then I go after you and go after you
Anya
yeah so you go first and then you sew it
I saw it it was like it was dark so like
I didn't see it at first
like I saw that it was right behind you
you seemed a bit suss
me I was right behind her oh she was
like acting a bit suss in that hallway
right before she entered the right
office so but in front of me is Anya
yeah but I was behind you
know it was actually Bae was actually on
the left leftish side of the of the
office I saw her I was in the office I
was in the office and then I saw I Saw
Mommy going away
I saw you I went I didn't go in the
office yeah
really I saw you I think go towards the
office I passed by you and said I think
yeah I think mommy is in your
Communications or something yeah
I don't know like like
was like around there but I don't know
why she didn't report the body because I
didn't see it first
yeah they and Anya are kind of teaming
up against Muna
or anything
you can choose whatever you want that's
fine
[Laughter]
Anna said nothing in this meeting
thank you
yeah
[Music]
updated
oh yeah sorry
thanks God I didn't say anything
um here
[Music]
foreign
do I need to press to the button do I
need to press the button
never again just looked there
we're going in together
to get together together
this is cool
it's cool
I'm going going
[Music]
mm-hmm
he's so cold
oh I'm just gonna stay in here
[Laughter]
really cool
whoa that's a lot of dead body whoa
where where's the body
where I wait where am I I'm here uh
security electrical
security
yeah I didn't go there oh
fauna and Ollie yeah like almost the
whole time yeah we were from the
specimen oh wait it was there
yeah yep on the way to the
Bay was suspicious of Muna and I didn't
see her the whole round no I was with
Mommy before but I go with Mommy before
yeah I didn't see moon but no I was in a
boiler room still doing my task
there's like two thousand boys but
um
yeah I didn't see mermaid too but wait
what side are you guys on
um
I was in the in the with suana and Oli
before fauna only and Zeta we made right
and we just like standing there being
fine
in the emergency room yeah
and whanau went to the specimen room and
then we met up with Anya and then we
went yeah
yeah I was mostly on the right side of
the map the whole time yeah me too so I
can't be on the left side of the map
um where are you I thought I saw you oh
yeah wait you said right side right oh
[Music]
and and I mean if you die you can do
your task faster so it's a win-win
sure I'm already done with my test so
I'll just follow people around oh I have
like one more I have one more I have
left one more
foreign
[Music]
no me you scary
it was movie at the end
anyway
s
I'm not really good at being imposter
guys no I'm not even it's pretty cool
here but it's really cold I was like I
was thinking wait or can we not kill
again do I have to report before we can
kill the kids I didn't know
we can only do one
would you like fire excuse me
yeah it's a new mode haven't you it's
there to explain
why did you miss it you should have
prepared and you wouldn't have you
wouldn't have missed it uh-huh oh yeah
what happened right gaslighting is the
victim's fault okay
[Music]
I'm missing one person
who is it
get in here oh she's here
I'm sorry oh that's okay I am learning
the game I don't know the straps here
I think we can at least squeeze in one
more round yeah maybe we can do one more
okay okay okay
wait this one is hide and seek bye-bye
okay
again
[Music]
hmm
so cold
laughs
it's not crony guys
[Music]
I am what what
you got it wait it's not reported then
no I was on the security cameras I saw
what was it what what how could you what
was it
[Laughter]
okay I see your body
it's amazing
I saw it on the security cameras it was
mermaid standing over crony's dead body
and also wait who makes no no I was
knocking crony earlier
that was [\h__\h] fun when she died why
didn't you report her right then and
there right
what wait wait what was her natural
state
[Laughter]
um if you were not an imposter you will
have reported
I didn't see her body
didn't the light is out
for the first part of the game
[Music]
it did a little bit yeah I didn't see me
so I don't know I have no idea I have no
idea because she was running she was
like there and then she went the
opposite direction so I don't know if
she really didn't see it or she and why
is it always I don't know
another double M I think it's
impossible no I didn't see crony die so
I I think it's Bae honestly but okay
yeah then it'll be it'll be all okay
good luck
[Music]
oh no
no okay
maybe I should
use the storage
how to get in
there
dare to fix it
foreign
thank you
[Music]
oh no
oh no wonderful
I'm gonna get it
I'm gonna get in
the task is already done
okay finally
never really gonna
they're like everyone is
I'm just gonna stay here everyone just
like
they all in these together I'm going
solo not going for solo
I think I'm gonna I need a friend where
is the friend says I need a friends
another one just like
oh he's so cold
everyone else like doing their task
together I cannot kill it I'm gonna I'm
gonna no I don't I cannot kill it at all
I cannot kid at all
good job
good job good job everyone wait who was
it okay again
uh get out if it's like it's so hard to
kill everyone I just let it go yeah
and I was like bro this can't be real
pee that you can see people's names when
they're watching somebody that's no I
just saw your your character your colors
yeah oh yeah oh yeah then you should be
able to like see the colors
[Music]
I was like about to kill you guys when
you guys instead but but you guys
instead not in like one step but have
like a different style so I just like oh
this is hard even though I do it okay
okay I think everybody should be off on
their own and isolated at all times
honestly oh
oh man
[Music]
can we just maybe do one more round and
in case someone gets imposter who
already got impossible before we restart
I just can't drive but it feels like
bugs yourself
I'm going to kill all of you
again
yeah if someone gets it like okay
yeah okay okay okay oh wait but won't
that narrow down who it could be
loud
oh yeah oh yeah that was yeah you want
to play one more round no matter who
imposter is if I get it again
let's do that well like if we get a
little imposter again either Muno or me
we could just do the emergency meeting
and cast okay okay yeah if I'm imposter
I'll be throwing it
oh [\h__\h]
well well
finally
something that I can understand
[Music]
all right
oh
what I I saw someone but I don't know
who it was because I wasn't looking at
the screen but there was someone running
again
the Rockets right oh yeah yeah by the
Rockets me me me me me me I I was
stalking fauna and then it got dark and
I lost sight of her but then I saw crony
come from the opposite direction
did I started stalking her wait where's
the body again I don't think yeah it's
by the wrong place the rocket oh uh it's
nearby the laboratory
oh that's so far
I've just been in weapons all I'm saying
is that I'm like on the left side of the
map
did whoever was did they cross paths
with you or did you see them escape to
the left
interesting interesting yeah from the
right to the left interesting I did see
crony run however I don't know I I don't
know
up
[Music]
I I did get it again what but like
should you cast me out now
but I didn't kill anyone so I don't know
what happened
doesn't pause then we'll just continue
like that
imaginary kill people I will just act as
if I did it
so like if I'm in pause for a good
should I just out myself and just
everyone have too many people yes it
down too much so I'm not sure we can
really do that
we need to keep Pony around
oh I'll just not kill anyone I'll just
do sabotage
yeah
[Music]
oh that was close
but at least she's honest she's very
honest
what should I do with this
[Music]
this is really nice where they actually
can scan even if you're a ghost
foreign
[Music]
she's in like the middle left okay in a
hallway and who was with someone was
with me at stabilizer so they're also
safe
um I I was walking up with you but then
I went to the left and I met crony and
she was coming from that area but I
guess she didn't she didn't touch it
yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
I won't lie
it's okay okay yeah anything can happen
it must be the other imposter who's
who's chatting your friends not oh my
God I I have no idea are you girls
skipping oh my God
[Music]
honestly I choose fauna at this point
you just said that and then muted
herself immediately to not get any bad
luck for it
foreign
[Music]
I think I remember the first time when I
played Among Us
I thought that this game is hard because
I have no idea how to do the technical
team
[Music]
but then I found out your juice is a PD
I have the vr12 slab right it must be
fine
all right guys I'm done
[Music]
wait am I am I am I able to see the chat
if I died
I don't know
I have nothing to do now
now
he's dead
well I just did
what you doing
we're not using the problem with the
chat
I cannot I cannot do it on on day I
always will you surprised me to chat so
I can literally cast on me but damn
I'm gonna see what they gonna do
[Music]
dead
kill I know it
oh no what you doing oh
it's really going there
where are you going
I wonder
let's report it
uh oh wow I have I have a theory like
Romeo and Juliet
what romantic romantic I have I have a
very big Theory so I will discussing uh
um and fauna at the very start because
they were the nearest people after I saw
Muna Senpai and since crony came out I
felt like oh oh it has to be someone
that then came out after meeting Anya
um Annie is in the pipe that would be
um going on herself doing booties just
to get in anyone's dress if she's an
imposter so it couldn't be heard it
couldn't be me so it's either KRS invite
or bae
but that's just the zombie Theory
I mean um
I
could have killed you right
let's say that your cooldown was not
done yet
I ain't sure about that Bae solid
argument I feel like I I really because
we're kind of dwindling to the final
people so if you waste the if you waste
the thing we're gonna we're gonna lose
by the way the body where's that
um beside the weapons is that weapons
like you better choose someone yeah like
between weapons and admin
why is Courtney still here
[Laughter]
imposters left
that's cool
oh yeah I mean I don't know why I'm
still here to be honest
or yeah
[Music]
but like really big props to like the
other imposter doing those really nice
job
[Music]
us
now following Bay
do you know that you've been caused
by a lot of people
what are you gonna do kill Kiara
your dad's definitely want to do oh you
didn't do that oh yeah I just have we
have a lion on your left
of course you didn't do that then what
you're gonna do next
oh so dead
you're gonna be dumb
hmm
yet
who was it was it
it was me
I'm sorry
in the Back Bay you stabbed me where in
the back
they was on a killing spring
I felt it in my spine when you did it
respect to the ones who stayed alive and
finished the tasks yeah oh honestly I
was dead and had to finish the tasks I
think it was me I'm sorry but I did it
if that's possible since it was hard for
the other imposter
[Music]
you know my screen I was like what are
they someone's dead
oh yeah but is it possible to do one
more since like that that one round it
was just pretty much one imposter
um
work
[Music]
um
and the killing time is like 10 like the
lowest 10 seconds and pretty much they
have to try and kill everyone everyone
before they finish the talk ah you know
who the do you know who the secret is
yeah so you have to you have to say that
you're the Imposter when you get it okay
and you've set the the running speed to
the fastest whoever's making the room
and then okay you just count to ten if
you're the Imposter and then yeah okay I
have the player speed on Max oh my God
that is so fast whoa whoa
buddy right yeah
okay 10 seconds
10 seconds it doesn't get any lower do
we have okay we have to do tasks
can finish all the tasks
[Music]
was too little yeah
so wait how many should I do
another
yes okay I have to blow it we're gonna
how are we gonna finish it
possible so no recording though no
reporting um which which one do you want
to do
you want to do the normal one for now
okay lower imposter Vision as well oh
we're not gonna mute ourselves by the
way right yeah
[Music]
I'm it
by the way yeah
[Music]
oh wait oh wait I'm sorry I think I'm
not sorry
oh wait you're not supposed to do them
oh sorry I'm just giving you a head
start here I come okay okay
yeah I canceled I canceled my past
are you faster
I'm meant to die in this
I have no idea
oh God oh my God
if I'm dead should I do the class
oh
let's just say yes
[Laughter]
I wanted to die
um
oh my God oh my God oh my God
dying play the elevator music oh my God
oh my God oh my god
let's go
what do you mean I haven't killed anyone
in a while
um
[Music]
wait is it only is it only movie and Bay
now
running
back
holy and who
um
there was like two imposters
[Music]
I don't think so we can haunt her oh
is only
not anymore
I've been
[Music]
oh no it's actually harder than I
thought
um
I think it's good I think it's well
balanced but oh
you'll try it again
four three two
possible
[Applause]
I think that would work so that we would
win what okay
[Music]
kick her out
okay okay pick me up all right goodbye
goodbye
oh we have to wait
while we're waiting why don't we just
you know doing the marketing
[Music]
just do it
is incredible
we just we just followed me
[Laughter]
[Music]
all right will it be fun again
we learn easy
[Music]
Cube oh God
yes oh I got like oh wait was everyone
there
[Music]
can
you count
stop counting okay stop counting please
wait what
probably so okay
oh man I think it's Target
I have no idea what should I do but
[Music]
what is happening
the Keystone that is broken no more
so now
well this is piece
[Music]
okay I won't
I can't do this card
all right no oh
[Music]
wow
this is so sad oh I feel this is so
small there's no not in the cafe at all
I was doing a white thingy Mommy
one more time and boom
[Laughter]
all my fault
if we lose it's my fault
[Music]
oh it gets hard when
there's only a few people left
I already mentally gave them
[Music]
um
did anyone
Miss imposter I mean I never I never got
one only an onion me we have cursed
yeah I know right
it's not fair
I'm going to sue someone I don't know
who but I'm going to school probably
maybe
or hello
means milk in Indonesia
how
do I say please give me
please please give me
uh it depends that you can at least give
you can always just say
uh something dong
I will marry you or something like that
sorry
anyway guys
right now it's gonna end soon oh I'm
gonna show you yeah in like 12 hours I
think so okay guys yeah
acrylic stand oh yeah
really cool t-shirts
[Music]
yes
I'm so spontaneously especially to the
ID members who already did their
homework yeah
thank you
sometime
it was really fun thank you nice to see
my face
thank you thank you
[Music]
[Laughter]
all right guys
well it's it's actually I've already
done it uh yesterday for the marketing
I'm just here to help the Ian but
I'm gonna say again
I'm gonna say again for the last time so
we
for the last time don't forget to buy
the merch Among Us Excel life the link
in the description because today is the
last day of the hello live the cover the
cover one the whole life one merch so
if you want to get it you have to buy
today today is the last day thank you so
much then I am Moana
from online Indonesia generation one
Saloon bye bye don't forget tonight
uh membership okay
bye bye
[Music]
yes just gonna see again among us exhale
life we have collaboration Rich where
you can buy anything and merge any merch
is available we have our code stand plus
the emergency meeting kitchen sticker
and play tag and also from the inner
slot we have a sticker mangas posters
t-shirt well just for saying for you
guys the order is available until
November 28th yes today from the Holo
live one the acrylic the plushie the
amazing meeting kitchen and the sticker
and a playt so if you want to boy the
girls of the merch you can buy now
before 23
59 Jesse
yes
and then I'm just gonna say that
if you download the Cosmic Cube it will
be available until December 20th
outside of December 22 cannot denote The
Cosmic Cube from the among us again so
if you want to having the Among Us
ex-hole life merch you can
download it now
thank you so much everyone I am Muna
hoshinova
I'm gonna head out
[Music]
peace