[Music]
foreign
good morning
[Music]
down
so
me
[Music]
okay
good
wow so many people calling me potential
hello audiology
my audio
oh it's at the max for me my microphone
hello
how are you guys
how are you i just woke up before the
stream
um
[Music]
okay
aren't we aren't we all tired
today we will continue
our um
our adventure in super mario 64.
yesterday we started
yesterday we started we got a bunch of
stars and i wasn't even that bad i
thought that would be really bad
i think everyone thought that oh oh i
forgot to tweet i forgot to tweet
let me tweet that i started because
otherwise nobody comes
did you guys see the burger that i just
retweeted
somebody made my both of the burgers
somebody made the the yacob burger and
the phoenix burger did you see it on my
twitter
[Music]
that guy was not the only person though
i saw someone else like right after the
stream doing it as well so
funny so funny
bye dad please come
[Music]
happy mata
yeah it looks good and and and
and he says they loved it
he made it for his family they loved it
he says they loved it so
my phoenix burger with the pineapple was
not a bad idea
uh-huh
you guys can't tell me that that was a
bad idea
there's people who enjoy that there's
people who enjoy
pineapples just like me
[Music]
are you all feeling dank today
i all feeling dank
[Music]
yes we all feel bank
thanks for the um for the super chat
after playing some super mario at some
point
i will uh
get into the super chat reading
my throat is not ready yet so i'm gonna
go ahead and uh
eat eat a cup cough drop no doubt
before we get started let me remind you
tomorrow uh
tomorrow three hours
same time as today minus three hours
there will be a collab on my channel
with all members and um
i'm organizing it mostly so
i'm thinking of some things and uh
after today's dream i'll have to focus
on it because
i want it to be a good collab we want
people to think oh
yeah i'll do my best
i'll be moderating it so i hope i'll do
a good job
thank you thank you for the
super chat i read them all later i hope
you
will all stay we'll have another
feeling dank session
hmm
today i'm well prepared
i'm prepared but mario is sleeping
thank you for the super good bronx again
again
mario's sleeping should we wake him up
should we wake him up with a loud
kikiriki
by the way for the people who missed it
missed the meaning
thank you canadian people who miss it
it's um
the german
sounds that are
possibly a rooster but also a phoenix
mix
all right it's a german sound so
three two
[Music]
whoa one what what what where's the
sound oh i'm muting it
is it so loud
it's just is this good
perfect okie dokie tell me if you want
me to change it later
good morning mario i also just woke up
you see we got eight stars yesterday
eight stars in two hours isn't that
quite the speed run
[Music]
um yesterday we had some issues
here because i
i thought when i was opening the
the treasure chest i thought i
automatically
get back my health because i i did get
it with the first
treasure chest that i opened so i
thought it was just because i didn't
even try i just got it
but later on we realized
like i was a millimeter in front
of the last treasure chest and then i
died
because i just didn't realize i need to
try to get the bubbles
well let's get right into it yeah
where are the treasures again uh i think
i have to
go to the eel again right
[Music]
yo i am ready give me all the stars
that camera though
[Music]
maybe that's should we go up for a
second
[Music]
wow and back down again
where are you mr eo
[Music]
wait i have to like i still don't get
this like last time it just kind of came
out while i was like not even looking
hello mossy moss
speak to me speak to me don't look at me
with your veins
[Music]
that's dangerous that's a very dangerous
place come on i'm dying here
hello okay i got better get up
i don't understand how to get him out of
there
[Music]
oh yeah okay this was exactly like
yesterday
i go up once and then he's out there
nice nice okay okay okay just how i
wanted it
just how i wanted it let's get in there
hello i already know the order i think
i think i remember on actually no never
mind i don't remember
tonight
[Music]
i think the the one in the back was the
first
right hello yes and now what to how do i
get the bubble i got it i got it i got
the bubble
but the controls man they suck what was
next
i think this one please please please
yes
bubble bubble yeah oh i got them i
got them which one are you i don't want
you yet i think i don't want
no no actually i don't i do think it was
you yeah yeah yeah
oh
[Music]
no
please open yourself to me no i'm gonna
die no i'm gonna
yeah okay that was close that was really
close
intense this game is so intense
it must be you it must be okay okay
okay i was so stupid to get a bubble
whatever bye bubble
us and you and you you are
the chosen one hello please give me
bubble
what happens now what happens now what's
happening
earthquake earthquake
oh no the water is going down
it's so cute and he like falls down like
that what no where's my star where's my
star
where's my star that's not it
[Music]
stupid camera oh my god how do i can i
get like to zoom out
the frustration
i just not look at where i'm going
ah the challenge
i just woke up okay
come on this cannot be the hard part
[Music]
it's because i can't see [\h__\h]
okay
[Music]
this cannot be that difficult
i hate this
hi
this is so embarrassing what the hell is
going on
yep
[Music]
stop it mario you need some
anti-slipping shoes or something
[Music]
focus focus focus focus
i don't think i can play this game today
go to the right side how do i do a
backflip again
oh my god right side there's nothing
here to hold onto
[Music]
okay oh hello i see something
okay you stop
you stop
[Music]
i cannot
okay let's try with that
this is unbelievable
can someone get him some anti-slippy
shoes
come on we can do this mario this is not
the hardest part
the hardest part was not dying
underwater
okay now we don't want to slip down
again
[Music]
which which side do we go do you think i
can make it up there
you think i can make it up there the
right one okay this cannot be the hard
part okay jump
okay so it's not that hard okay it's not
that hard
well but now i have to go down again i
guess getting down is easier
but how do i oh my god please stop
camera please please yes
uh i guess i can jump on the bar back
flip
i shall try
[Music]
it did not work
no oh my god
[Music]
oh my god oh
my oh my
oh my god
oh i think can i quit this level for now
my money
i was so good yesterday i want to show
them how good i was
no i can't i can't i need to i need to i
need to stop
how do i get out of this level please
tell me baby walk
how do i baby walk
crouch and walk oh okay
please just no it doesn't work
it doesn't work
[Music]
how do i end this
i need to i need to go to a different
level right now
[Music]
it's
i don't have the patience for this do
you guys have the patience for this
dude do you guys i just woke up i don't
have the patience for this but
if you have it then
if you could just stop where i want you
to stop that would be awesome
thank you
precise jumps it has to be precise jumps
now it doesn't it didn't really make
sense to go the right way so
okay precise jumps nice
cool ah okay
now this part is no no no no no
no no
it's all good it's all good it's all
good
it's all good i hate this
what is the camera doing honestly
should i just try to reach that platform
directly
the camera though
no don't
are we honestly spending like 20 minutes
on this
[Music]
is so embarrassed of me probably
oh now you can walk on there huh now you
can walk on there
[Music]
mario get your [\h__\h] together shikoto
simonai hola
because of me my papa can't do work
because he's laughing so much at me
that he can't do his work he just wrote
that
[Music]
[Laughter]
this is unbelievable i was so good
yesterday i swear
i swear i swear okay proceed precise
jumps
see i have eight stars i got them in two
hours
i was so good
[Music]
am i the only one who struggled here
please tell me no please tell me i'm not
the only one
yes no
yes you are the only one um
[Music]
i want to keep my cool camera out don't
make me insult you
in german angry words
i swear okay
but it just gets so close i don't want
that
okay you want me to
what no don't look there
just give it to me
[Music]
here we go oh my
god unbelievable
[Music]
oh my god oh my god i cannot
go in the stage anymore for today no
more
no more where did we go
i don't remember what was in here alice
yes please just give me snow
just give me snow freeze that freeze
that
water forever
oh i have to rise with the penguin yes
yes
[Music]
well how did i do that
i'll win you have no chance
get out of the
i didn't way to do that
okay keep it going kiana this is the way
i know hey
beat some fake has to task all that
where is that
game over okay
[Music]
but where is that the shortcut again
that where you go for the wall i didn't
in order to get that shortcut i have to
not take the first shortcut right
which i took accidentally
right no no short it
oh i can't use them i can
yes okay i think i understand come on
guys stop
okay but i took that by accident anyway
so i didn't really want to take that one
it's so dangerous please don't take it
yes yes it's straight
whoa and now for that ah no
da da
[Music]
you're such a loser mario
i brought you your baby and that's how
you thank me
no am i disqualified okay
okay okay okay
wait but does that disqualify me if i
use that shortcut does it disqualify me
phoenix versus pancake
i don't think so hmm
[Music]
no oh but i i can win without using that
right
let's go
this is the funnest part in the game
honestly
a nice curve a nice curve oh eat that
bucket
[Music]
don't do that mario just go straight
oh my god are you gonna win this
where am i where am i where am i where
am i no ah where am i where am i
where am i ah
did i win please said i win did i win
anyway
[Music]
did i win hello
hello sorry i didn't read
[Music]
how do i restart how do i restart how do
i restart
nope i cheated i did not cheat
[Music]
i left the finish line early that's it
you can't take short it but how would i
win if i don't take that shortcut
[Music]
let me get out of here
don't exit the room okay okay okay huh
what are you giving me that star for huh
[Music]
how do i get up there again should i
just uh
take it
okay so what i did was fine until i left
that room for a second
i was dizzy
i was dizzy because mario was just like
he honestly i don't know what's wrong
with this guy
this time you have no
chance
let's go fight me
don't do the thing again while you bump
into me you
fat penguin why am i so slow oh oh i
didn't speed up
ah
come on come on okay now straight mario
don't do
[\h__\h] thank you kelly
could you just kill that penguin for me
i'm so sick of this penguin
now don't don't do anything weird mario
just go down
no go down and stay there
just wait wait for that bastard penguin
hello hello i was
what is your problem
[Music]
i hate you what
how am i supposed to win cross the
finish line
don't use the wall shortcut but the
other shortcut is fine but even when i
use that
that one first
[Music]
okay let's go
oh bye-bye
[Music]
i didn't want to do that i didn't want
to do that
yes
[Music]
this is this is fine
i don't want to see your stupid face
ever again
let's go don't have time for you
no no i keep doing this why do i keep
doing this
oh and my game over again game over
mario it's all your fault
[Laughter]
[Music]
i
oh i i can do this yes
yes yes champion race i'm the champion
give me that title i deserve it much
more than you you stupid
bad penguin
[Music]
you went first though are you aware of
that you tell me that i'm cheating but
you go first
okay no cheating eat that
i i didn't i just came i just came here
hey hey i was faster than you yeah i did
not take the shortcut hi
talk to me talk to me
[Music]
okay
here we go
i see today we're not getting anything
done
[Music]
i i see what's inside
i'm not getting anything done
just let me win please
uh amelia hi i did the normal slide
without the penguin i think that's the
star they're trying to give me because i
didn't win against the penguin yet
oh my god
go away go away
go away no
[Music]
yes
why why in every in
every
why am i always the bullied one
okay but i think i got the gist no
cheating just be fair
be square be fair be yourself
ah but you are cheating if you bump into
me
[Music]
oh my god can i throw that penguin off
of the race
please
i was feeling really calm there for a
second
to shy spangling
[Music]
okay last try
best try
just feel it just feel it
[Music]
yes just go straight
straight
i don't want to talk to you i don't want
to talk to you i don't want to talk to
you
no no no no
no i don't know
i i i
i
[Music]
here we go
i don't deserve
[Music]
but now i feel like i remember
everything
it's in my blood now i feel
it i just feel it now i
i don't i don't even have to try it
anymore
it just flows with me you know
[Music]
are we gonna spend thank you
we're going to spend the whole stream
with trying to get
up those little bumps in the ship
and trying to win this race even though
i basically already won it
is this the whole stream today
is this what we want to see
no we want to see my pro gaming moves
get out of the way oh my god
[Music]
i i just
oh
is this is this what you want to say
guys is this what you want to see
i'm losing my mind over here
[Music]
i only read part of that amelia
yes uh pain equals victory or whatever
go away i know
i can feel it i can still do it i can
still do it
[Music]
now we have to don't [\h__\h] up here
i did it i [\h__\h]
did it you can't say i did not do it
[Music]
[Laughter]
one
[Music]
yesterday i had so much fun with this
game
[Music]
and now it's only pain
it's only pain
[Music]
what's the next thing
yes we are going to add penguin to my
menu
oh red coin okay
now this is something relaxing
to calm down our aggressive
feelings just relax
and find the red coins
they are here to guide me with their
wisdom
i hope there wasn't anything up there
thanks for your super chats
i hope there wasn't anything up there i
really hope because i'm not going back
up there
okay
[Music]
where are the red coins number
two is there something down there
[Music]
how do
oh my god i thought i was gonna fall off
the cliff
[Music]
thank you for this super chat
my marriage ceremony with kelly
[Music]
will do she doesn't know about it yet
i hope she didn't see that super chat
i hope she didn't see that oh my god
thank you
no no no no no no no no
no no no no no
i don't know what that guy is talking
about
i don't know
[Music]
i don't know what he's talking about
yeah don't don't don't listen to him
[Music]
don't listen to him i think um
well um
i hope oh my god
see this whole thing is making me a bit
nervous now no no it came over no
ah is that did cali just
kill me there
did you just kill me there that must
have been callie
kelly don't kill me i just
i just want to show you my love
please understand understand
that was all me okay well i guess so
oh yes i need this for
a change of a change of uh
i don't know how do you say
[Music]
yeah i missed them perfectly of course i
did
do you need to get the right coin
this is how a phoenix flies wait oh wait
i noticed i remember this is
disappearing right
okay get down there get down i'm scared
this is gonna disappear right
i can't fly forever so let me let me
stop there please
please oh thank god i wanna fall down
yes i know i know it's gonna disappear
but what do i do when it disappears
[Music]
all right i can always reset the nice
okay new hat please
i have a new hat wow
[Music]
eh how do i look up again oh my god
that that didn't happen um
i hate the camera
[Music]
hello
the third the third jump the third jump
the third time the third jump
the third jump the third jump
i know i know i know i know i know
[Music]
hey go up oh my god
oh
[Music]
yes
come on come
[Music]
of course we're not gonna get the coin
i'm on these ones
come on
what i'm there i'm right there
please let me let me land on there oh my
god
[Music]
i don't see them
you're kind of doing a horrible job
there mario
why are you so slow
[Music]
i'm having some issues here excuse me
customer service of
whoever's selling the hat what
i'm never gonna do this huh
i'm never gonna get those coins huh
okay now we're high enough now let's
focus
stay on this altitude please
come on you're phoenix you know how to
fly yes
two of them now stay up there stay up
there stay up there
focus how am i where are you please
stay up there let's do that
use your slow okay down down down at
least one at least one
nice try where am i
okay i think we need to maybe make a
landing first
yep yep where am i no no
[Music]
oh
give me something else to do give me
something easy i need to impress those
people
i need to impress these people what am i
doing
what are we doing
i guess we can do the red coin mission
but i don't think that was written there
what am i doing does someone know
find the cannon okay
what candle
kiara xa has stopped flying
i need to impress the people who are
here to watch me
don't step on me it's not the thing i'm
into it's not my kink
[Music]
hello
sleep well little baby
there's a star there
there's a star
i can't get there from here right you
have something to say to me
did i find the cannon i found the cannon
i found the cannon
[Music]
that was not even on purpose pro
gamer what do i do with it where do i
shoot myself too
to the start should i pull
or i guess to the pole
[Music]
does it have to be really accurate
the sun no no no you're telling me
[Music]
huh
the sun the sun
and for the pole ah i see some people
are trying to
throw me with the sun
[Music]
[Applause]
you can't fool me guys
that was so close that was so close that
was so close that was literally so
close
too high
you mean you want me to aim lower so i
can get
like below that platform
to start i don't see the star
[Music]
stars below
[Applause]
at least we didn't die i think i think i
know
[Music]
we were close very close maybe a little
bit more to the right
aim higher what happens if i
aim to the sun eh
i actually want to know where's the sun
what happens when i do that
[Applause]
[Music]
huh
you told me to aim to the sun
well joke's on you first of all
i'm a phoenix i am the bird of the sun
second of all i don't die i revive again
and again
as you can see jokes on you my friend
okay how did i get there though i got i
got there by accident
i got there ah
oh my god oh my god
oh my god why is this happening
i don't see it that thing is in the way
oh yeah let me pass
don't step on me this time
[Music]
i fell down but like
how do i how did i fall down at the
right spot it was like i think it was
like really close to
ah
i was really close to dying there when i
fell down
go to the left shortcut left from here
hello it's me tiara i'm back
this time i will not aim for the sun
i am the sun now let's see
where do we go where do we go
that was really close that was really
close a little bit higher
i think a little bit higher
aim for the shoulder point
[Music]
yeah aim for the sun shut up i just did
that and i regretted it
second pillar
[Music]
oh wait the pole on the pillar pillar
[Applause]
[Music]
one more time no this should be it this
should be it come on come on come on
come on
aim and maybe
wait i was too i was too low
so here
no okay that was too far to the right
but at least i don't think i'm gonna
spend 30 minutes with this
that's a good thing
[Music]
here in here
higher here
[Applause]
hello star hello hello i've come to see
you
and catch you here we go
yay no i will never forgive the people
who said aim for the sun
never okay what's the next one
red coins
eight red coins here we go
where are you is something here nothing
is here right wait actually what happens
again when i look up here
it's a teleport right i don't need a
teleport though
oh there we go number one
pro gamer move yes
yes
aim for the sun again why do you keep
telling
me that i know you're just trolling me
because i am the sun yes that is very
true and uh
thank you for for admitting that
the sun has the red coin oh shut up i
don't believe a word you say
i don't believe a word you say
[Music]
you can't fool me i'm not as stupid as
you think
[Music]
me
sleep sleep
go to sleep go to sleep
sleep just leave okay
so i'm scared to fall off
hello hello
what just uh
same thing
slowly that's a bit too slow though
a little bit too slow
okay now the platform
uh wait how do i not [\h__\h] this up
what the hell was that marielle
[Music]
i want that
language you know you know i think um
the problem is
like for me english is not my first
language so it's really hard to
control myself like that um
i think it's easier for someone who
speaks it as a first language for
example like if i speak
german i can control myself like that
like if i if i want to like do something
like f word
i can do that in german but in english i
don't really have like the
[Music]
what the hell was that excuse me i'm
talking here
we're having some serious talks i'm
gonna get over here
hello leave me alone
[Music]
how do i get there
i'm almost dead
i kicked the board to kick the board
twice which board
which board which board
which board are we talking about jump
kick the board
oh the wooden plank
at this one ah
oh no oh my god
[Music]
unfair i say unfair this is f
foul full power
hello i'm back again
[Music]
thank you employee i read all the super
chats later on okay
i don't know which one is the right one
let's go hello i'm here again don't mind
me just passing
[Music]
i don't want to wake up i want to wake
you up
i don't want to wake you up i don't want
to wake you up
are there any red coins here at least
yes
that was all on purpose yes yes
wait is that not how i get it
i think it is how i get it it's so close
though
use the cannon don't jump just run
huh
[Music]
mario but you almost did it
almost did it
[Music]
almost could you please move a little
bit to that side
no no no no i don't want to fly is there
a red coin there though
is there a red coin what a legend well
thank you
was there a red coin to the sun
no no no we're not doing this anymore
you won't fool me i knew it from the
beginning you're just
here to film me
okay maybe not
bye eh
papa gotta
maybe i was too low because i aimed like
i think here maybe i need to go higher
i can't go higher than that
that's the highest i can go hey no
is my papa trying to fool me
because some people are saying no no no
no no
do i trust my papa i trust him i love
him so much he can't be lying to me
[Music]
i believe in you
i can fly
[Music]
papa
why won't you why would you do this to
your precious daughter
[Music]
huh
i can trust no one in this world i can
trust no one
i gotta do it on my own
top 10 anime betrayals
[Music]
eh
well i'll i'll definitely never never
go for the sun again
[Music]
wow wow
that was such a top 10 anime betrayal
that was number one though
unbelievable hello
[Music]
who can you even trust anymore if not
your own father well
papa i still love you no matter what
happens
no matter how much you tease me
i will never not love you oh i have to
go down here again right to get the that
red coin
already let me get you a second time
so was there something here or not
[Music]
i feel like no no not the sun
i feel like maybe there was something
here
why did i fall down please
let's go maybe there is a red coin here
hello
off the wall
wait that's where it came from that's
where it came from
oh okay we don't go there ah
[Music]
oh that was a good save mario
oh top of the pole
[Music]
there was nothing on the top of the pole
what was there
[Music]
ah well thank you for that oh i see a
coin though
[Music]
maybe we'll just go up higher and see
and get the ones that we wanted to get
that stupid wooden plank though
that stupid bomb okay how do i keep
these don't just
go yeah come on come on
that doesn't work that's not how it
works okay wait
do i need to do that jump or whatever
i'm scared i'm gonna fall down
definitely
jump kick i'll do a jump kick
okay nice i didn't even know you could
do that
[Music]
i'm so scared i'm not good with these
narrow paths
oh my god especially with oh my i should
maybe change the camera
okay this is better oh i'm gonna fall
down
right i'm definitely gonna fall down
camera is that all you can do
i need to do some kind of special jump
right normal jump is not enough right
yeah oh
okay it worked i see you
i worked so hard to get there
i saw it coming though i definitely saw
that coming
[Music]
yes hello yes hello don't mind me i'm
just passing through again and again and
again and again and again
[Music]
do a kick flip for what
how many more coins do i need
is that was not the last one was that
there's probably still
a few more was that the last one
when you're just just too stupid for
everything
oh my god go away please go away
okay
okay plank you're already there thank
you
this camera
[Music]
oh no no no
mamma mia
[Music]
okay my friends
i
i have no words left
i am speechless
[Music]
i am losing faith in this world and in
all
human beings
get wall star what's work
use the teleports but aren't there
coins on the way to get
[Music]
like this one
look off the trumps
above the steppy boy
no no no i did nothing to you
shoot corner of wall for free start okay
i mean
maybe not right now because i want to
get those stupid coins now
[Music]
give me that thing
come down why are you coming down this
do you have you ever heard of something
called gravity
[Music]
wait i'm doubting my english it was the
right word right
you guys are making me doubt my my my
english
[Music]
so go up again
go up
hello again me alone
now go here because i'm sick of the
other way
it wrong way there's a red coin in the
head of the second
[Music]
frog
i saw a coin i saw a coin i saw two
coins but
[Music]
how do i get that
oh on top of that oh it's a good thing
that i look at the comments huh
[Music]
okay now we can move on i think now
there's nothing left down there right
nice thanks guys
what would i be without you i mean i
just said that i don't trust anymore and
i lost faith in humanity but what would
i be without you
nothing
yeah kind of contradicting
but that's just how i am my life is
contradictory
[Music]
that's how it is
that was some strength there mario
this is the first time i thought you
were strong because the other times you
keep on messing up
and i just honestly thought of you as a
loser
no no no this can't be true no no no no
game over
[Music]
is this because i called him a loser
okay is this because i
i'm i once one thing i can say for sure
now i'm never gonna
clear this game
i highly doubt that i will
ever clear this game
[Music]
where was it again not here no no no no
more swimming
never um
[Music]
this is the one star door
120 stars impossible impossible let's be
realistic i mean you see my gameplay
here don't you
i'll try my best but i i really doubt i
mean clearing means 120 stars right
that sounds impossible i mean it would
probably take me like a year
[Music]
okay again here we go again
we go again here we go again
we do this one first
[Music]
that was close
i'm always so close to dev oh my god
please make it stop i'm so scared i look
good
don't mind me
oh my god oh my i don't wanna know
what's down there i don't even wanna
know
i don't wanna know
[Music]
i don't wanna i don't wanna know
i don't wanna know
i think we're gonna go up first not
gonna go down there right now because
that one is easy
[Music]
relatively
okay here i am again
this time i shall not die
yes
she said that and obviously it's gonna
be alive
everything's cool
just focus focus
be careful
okay this is not so hard just do a
normal jump
and then just stop moving
mamma mia
[Music]
is there any easy stage is there
anything easy and easy that i can do
is there anything easy
what's in here manika
[Music]
these doors be deceiving me
i did the first bowser yeah it was it
was actually
i mean the fight against bowser was not
that hard is this something to do here
hello
i wanna do something else i wanna
do something easy this game broke me
how do i
uh you guys keep on saying where is
luigi though
do i have to can i do something is there
nothing here
downstairs lava stage no how to
go in the door which door
which door
the corner of the wall is easy cannon at
all
you mean from the previous level
[Music]
run around the statue 2401 times
you know what let's just go down here
is the only thing down here without the
lava level though
don't listen to them yeah i kind of
figured
to not listen to them ever anymore
where is that thing
[Music]
no okay this picture
alone really scares me but maybe the
first level is not so hard
[Music]
the memories
let's see let's see how we do maybe we
can first try
i just have to kill the boss right
that's not that hard
where where is he though what is you
i'm just gonna run right through this i
don't even care
what is going on here hello oh hey i'm
going quite fast
huh speed run here we go
hey this really has speed run potential
and we're already here what do you say
about this guys huh
how do i kill him how do i do i just
bump against him
[Music]
oh
i i did so well
i did so well
[Music]
i did so
i did so well
oh my god i need to play my jrpgs this
is nothing for me
i mean like it's not made for me alone
okay we can we can just do it again
we'll just do the same thing again oh
the red coin mission here seems easy
[Music]
hello it's me again i already won
against you but let's do this again
fight me if you think you can
ha you are very wrong second time
the only enemy to me are those stairs
[Music]
how do i how do i climb those stairs
how do i climb those stairs a triple
jump
that sounds very dangerous how do i
climb these stairs
jump jump run fast okay okay i'm scared
i just i just here we go
um three noble gems okay
can i still do it
i don't wanna die again
[Music]
yeah but he just grabs onto it stop
grabbing oh man
[Music]
why do i start the first jump here
[Applause]
hey
[Music]
ugh
i'm getting better i'm getting better
and the boss clearly
is no match for me
clearly
this also no problem
i'm just run speed rounding through this
easy clap okay and we always kind of
have to uh jump into the lava here
and here obviously as well and i'm gonna
die okay
friends no that's okay that's okay
that's okay
next next is a game over but sure enough
[Music]
we stay positive we stay motivated
uh yes don't mind me
uh fire doesn't hurt me lava does a
little bit
a little bit only a little bit don't
look at me
what are you looking at
me i don't
i didn't give you the permission to look
at me so stop
don't have time for it all those eyes ah
every time
how was i so good yesterday and so
horrible today
i just
[Music]
i
i just opened the door
a game over count i don't i don't even
i can't even count anymore it's just i
die so
often
i i can't even keep counting anymore
goodbye thanks for the super chat
okay now this is it this this is not it
this is it it's time to win
i need a win i need a win
[Music]
i've come again you stupid bully
everyone's just bullying me always
always
yes of course this just this is just a
part of it
this just has to happen you know now
let's wait until the lava is gone let's
just wait
yes oh my god that was close
hello i'm here again yes i know i know
i'm too stupid to get
that stupid star i don't know what's
wrong with me
but you're not in the position to laugh
at me okay
you are you are not
in that position now
thank god thank
god oh my god
okay now let's get right back into it
don't get stuck what
what what do i do
what do i do we go there again
what do i do
thank you for super jazz
does someone know what the mission is
[Music]
red coin i mean i guess i can do the red
coins yeah is that the mission though
not again the red coins should be easy
they're all over there
[Music]
no you're stupid
shouldn't be that hard one two
[Music]
three
no problem no problem no problem we will
not die here
that would be ridiculous bye
[Music]
no lava you're not going to kill me
again here we go
[Music]
at least something right back into it
easy clap
ah don't get started what is this
what is the second stage i just go to
the boss state it says something fight
who do i fight this time
i'm just gonna go to the to that stage
again
[Music]
i'm used to bullying i'm used to
bullying oh my god
let me get some coins to the right coins
no problem no problem i have to fight
the small ones not those
oh go back okay
[Music]
camera
what's with that idol what is the matter
with that eye
mario nice move do i go on that side
wait i want to read the messages fight
the small enemies
three of them there weren't those the
ones that i was just trying to fight
go to the boss ah there's three of them
but on the boss platform okay okay
oh my god no
any coins any coins any coins i need
coins
oh my god don't mind me
don't even look at me
we can do this oh my god
what the hell was that i heard the life
no problem no problem i i i know what to
do now
what does he say that does he say let's
go it sounds like
hello i'm here again
yes probably many more times you will
meet me here
[Music]
cuts
every time
[Music]
it's just tradition you know at this
point it's just tradition hello
where's the i thought that was free of
you oh is it the other platform
ah is it not you ah
um i'm like how bad but we can do this
half that i'm fine
hello
[Music]
we do the trick that i did before with
the big one we we get them over here
okay this is not so easy
you
[Music]
everyone is just always ganging up on me
yes number one down down down down
[Music]
you win some and you lose some
okay
[Music]
confuse him confuse him make him dizzy
or something
yes come on
come on
[Laughter]
again i'm not ready for this oh my god
why do i need to fight you
yeah okay okay now no one can take
this goddamn star away from me anymore
panic
[Music]
intense let's go again
what's next what do we do
[Music]
does someone know
i'll be reading all of them in a little
bit i'll be playing maybe
um how much longer should i play like i
wonder how much time the secret chat
takes this time probably much
less
[Music]
run around the eye okey-dokey
what happens then run around the eye to
kill it and get a star
yeah that sounds difficult
[Music]
okay i knew i had to do something with
you our battle has finally come
it is time now what is that is it that
easy
oh it's just a coin
[Music]
are you for real
no i like hats but i hate flying right
now what do i do with that
what
[Music]
okay okay i can go back but where do i
fly and
someone said into the into the volcano
i don't see a volcano is that in the
middle of volcano
i shall try ah
bye hat what do i do here alone
i'll just teleport back
[Music]
no no no could you please stop
teleporting me thank you
i don't want to fly anymore
okay here we go
no wait wait i have to do three jumps
wow
[Music]
wow great that was great
thank you whatever
hold a on the third jump
just call me sotori did you just call me
so tony oh my god
wait wait what do i really have to do
nice bug hello
volcano wait what exactly do i have
to do go into the volcano but with that
with the cap
[Music]
i don't need i don't need those
i can just go into the volcano like that
again no grab them let me just take that
round
[Music]
is that supposed to hit me or something
maybe a backflip
would do that trick
okay wait but maybe not when it's uh
erupting
yes almost
was that how you were supposed to do it
i'm almost dead though stupid camera
what the hell
where do i even go is this camera
do i go on that side that that seems
like a long jump man
okay come on kiara show them what you
got
hello i'm resistant to fire
it's not like oh my god that was
a savage
you you go first you'll go first and
then i do a backflip i guess
all right
follow the path to the top okie dokie
will do oh no
this um reminds me of the beginning of
today's stream
precise gems please
exactly like that exactly
where am i i can't turn the camera out
where what is that
oh where do i go
where where does it go does it just lead
me up
to the start
where do we go
oh what's happening that texture the
second star okay awesome
any star i'll take it
yes is that what i needed to do go off
the pole
[Music]
mommy
i don't even know which way i want to go
anymore
but how about i just
don't fall down here oh my god
okay i guess we go for the different
route again yeah
that was on purpose that was on
your facebook how the hell do i do that
pole jump
stupid cameraman
it be like that exactly
here again oh my god that was close oh
my god
hello cole so we meet again
i'm surprised i can i actually managed
to to grab the pole the first time
so i need to get up there right
but when the camera is like that it
seems
difficult these are all the angles
i get really
really
jump back in
hold where's the other pull i see it but
how is that even possible
flip off the top
oh my god i'm scared whatever you just
said
sounds very difficult i've never done it
before
i'm so done i'm so
[Music]
done
try how about we get the real first star
i want to show these people how good i
am at games but
it's just the games are trolling me
the games are trolling me at this point
and here we go again
[Applause]
it's my destiny it's my destiny
i have to fulfill my destiny
let's go pole dancing mario
you're amazing though thank you that's
uh quite
quite the compliment seeing as i
absolutely suck at what i'm doing
my destiny i'm just gonna go for it i'm
just gonna
oh maybe not maybe
oh no no no
i'm alive
i'm i'm alive but probably not for much
[Music]
longer
i'm alive life has given me a second
chance
i shall use it wisely
how about we don't [\h__\h] up here for once
for once
oh there's a heart there
thank you wait what does that do it
should be
okay okay okay
we got our life back we got it
now let's jump over there
oh okay okay okay
jump here yes yes i even make this jump
or should i no i should be able to make
it
okay okay okay now now we're talking
now we're joking
i've never come this far
this guy i'm scared oh no poles
i don't i don't
um i'm not good with poles
how do i jump there
do i just
rotate just face your back right now am
i not actually facing my back but do i
have to be in this position or
in the this weird position
spin around turn around okay
oh wait
okay like that and now just press a
backwards long jump jump not like that
uh-oh like that
don't hand up don't handstand okay so
like that
do i have to move the the joystick
or does he just jump already i don't
want to mess up now
i don't want to mess up just press a
wait are you sure about this this camera
angle it looks uh
okay okay okay
uh this should be all right i hope
come on
game over
[Music]
why
wait one second my chat died i have to
reload it
[Music]
i think what are these noises
no ah
well i guess it works it works in the
stream so i'll just uh
my my popped out window is not working
anymore
press start to play oh well
why is it not loading
okay just close that window
one second please
what are you guys talking about
[Music]
okay now i got the chat
okay
here i go again
[Music]
all right let's go um i think i want to
clear that level
and then maybe i'll quit for today
and read the super chats
[Music]
oh the pyramid level where is the
pyramid level
boy you scared me there you
actually scared me
[Music]
punch the ghost the posts are here
what do i do
what do i what is that
[Music]
i punch you
what do i do with that that was the
right one
no i'm
scared i'm so scared no
no no no actually this was really
really scary in my childhood
i was really scared of this
i barely have any memory of it though
[Music]
i have to find theresa
oh i i'm really bad at horror games
wait probably that was not the right
door
what do i do yeah
what the hell was that where am i
yeah i hear some carnival music
actually i really don't remember this
[Music]
was it the camera
where did that come from which side did
that come from though where's the piano
i don't see a piano
just for a different start
but where was the piano that you guys
that you were talking about
easy star in piano room
but wait how do i get out of here
[Music]
how do i get out of here
hello this is scary i'm scared i'm
scared i'm a
big big chicken when it comes to horror
games only when it comes to horror games
usually i'm not a chicken otherwise
do i play with you again
ah no no let me go up i want to go up i
want
go up oh my god here i step on you again
now
you go up right
wait hello
i'm here again you
i don't know if this does anything but
i'm just gonna do it because i don't
like you
coins is that all you give me
is there anything else here no okay
let's go for that right there
oh we're down outside again we're
outside is there anything behind by the
way
[Music]
okay
okay back door
should i go to the back door
what is the left rim in the mansion
gosh i hate this camera so much
[Music]
left door they say alrighty
this door the first one oh
piano give me a star please
[Laughter]
what do i do what do i do
oh my god this is actually scaring me
what the hell
[Music]
just calm down please come down please
jail okay
slowly leave the room
[Music]
what if i slowly approach it
and then punch it
it's just a red coin that's it oh my god
this is minecraft
[Music]
let me out
let's go here again
[Music]
okay um i think
uh no there's nothing here right
[Music]
how
i think i'm losing my mind
slowly but surely
what
[Music]
hello i'm here again
i is dead already nice
see one thing i can say i did not die
yet in the stage
back door what's in yeah what's in the
back door
that actually i'm very interested in so
let's check it out
[Music]
panic move but it worked what what
what is this oh wait the ghosts
are
[Music]
okay so i killed two how many
two goes out of five
[Music]
don't look at them
three out of five well let's kill you
two
while we're at it oops i got some time
for you oh that already killed you
yes
[Music]
two more a teresa is the japanese name
for buu
okay um now how about i don't fall down
here anymore and the thing is just i
don't see where i'm going
okay can we just walk straight there
now don't fall
[Music]
wow
ah
try from the other side
the other side
why is that the only way that i can get
back up from there
or is there a faster way
[Music]
chiara's pain is cute what's cute about
my pain
wasn't there something here where am i
hello that is a bit dangerous because
like if i
slowly walk over there on the other side
this boob will bump against me and
probably
push me down
turn it around or maybe it moves does it
move when i'm
gonna turn around no i can just jump
over there
you know how how i am with jumping you
know how good i am with jumping
don't you i'll try yeah
[Music]
slowly slowly slowly slowly there's a
door
where does it lead me
you're the last one you're the last one
come on me fight you
oh my god no don't kill me here
i
[Music]
where is the star what do i do to get
this up go back
kaidan central room
okay i don't want to fall down again so
i'll go this way
[Music]
you know if i already get scared at a
super mario game
imagine me with horror games
[Music]
stairs again i
love
[Music]
so are they going to stay there
thank god thank you guys for helping me
i don't want to go in there again
anymore though
so
uh i have 15 stars does this mean
what i think it means not that one
that's not it right does this mean
[Music]
yeah bunny right
let's just get the bunny and then i
think we're done
[Music]
i came to rescue you a golden bunny
i didn't have her as a golden
[Music]
please wait for me
believe in me i'll do no harm to you
where are you
oh i coordinate you oh [\h__\h]
we have something to talk about
[Music]
how much i love you
look at those gorgeous flips i can do
come on
[Music]
is
senpai award
[Music]
you are so beautiful
alrighty
i'm so happy i got to meet her
so for today
i think that's it
so i'll read super chat now if that's
okay
[Music]
um
that was fun
yay well i did really bad today
i did really really bad today let's be
real i was much better yesterday
[Music]
we had such a horrible start with those
stupid stairs i guess it wasn't really
stairs but you know what i mean
yeah i could have done
much better i think i hope you guys
enjoyed it anyway i hope it was somehow
entertaining and not just too
frustrating
i don't know i i myself thought
the frustration was killing me so
let's see i'm gonna scroll down the
super chat now
and then we'll we can do some
german lessons basically
i'm sorry that i suck one day i'll show
you my skills
when it comes to um jipgs
i mean even then i lowkey sucks but
yeah but i think yeah these
i guess they call it jump and run games
is that what they are
i'm not really good with those
yeah it's not it's not my best
genre a platform up down platformer
yeah no i was never really good with
platformers
oh so many super chats thank you guys
but um i'll try to play some more times
honestly it isn't gonna be as horrible
as today
i don't see myself clearing the game
anytime in the future
but i have to say for a super mario
sunshine
i have a bit more uh
confidence honestly i know someone said
like if she can't
clear this then she's not gonna clear
super mario sunshine but i feel like
for me super mario sunshine was always
like easier
but i don't know it's harder i don't
know but at least the camera is not as
shitty
yeah sunshine is also less slippery i
would say
the the camera like the camera is a big
reason why i
[Music]
have issues i think i mean you would say
that is uh
making up excuses
i played sunshine a lot when i was uh
smaller
i never finished it i just played it
like every once in a while
we'll definitely play it at some point
but uh
who knows will i ever clear a super
mario game
i doubt it anyway let's start
with uh oh yeah for everyone who's
leaving
alfredo for everyone who's staying
uh we say dankeshun
we say thank after each name
okay you can you can uh do it together
with me
[Music]
months
feeling dank
now here you go it's it's not that much
uh this time i think so we should be
able to get through it
quickly
did you have a good party break good
because buckle up all of this
is only the beginning my fiance and i
were riding along with you all
we've seen your warm and kind
personality and we love you thank you
okay thank you i love refrigerators
function
before
said that right brandon wilson thank you
can't make the stream but since it's
payday i can finally send my support for
you fly high and fire you wonderful
phoenix i love all that you do
thank you so much cute huge majestic
symphony intro from phoenix anime what
pancakes
[Music]
yeah this is from yesterday by the way
this is from yesterday first and then we
do the one frame tomorrow
free free jtm adwolf17
ryan john thank you they were charging
my switch yesterday at this point
a little birdie told me that the show
away reaper's heart
that a sure way reaper's heart
is cheap wine here's a little something
you can prepare for your next day
but it was the only way we could get our
feelings across we love you and you're
irreplaceable
oh thank you you don't have to be sorry
for me reading so long it's my choice i
i chose to do so
yummy no blue eyes
vince thank
we know you love mario and zelda so i
wanted to ask if you're going to play
the new
hyrule warriors when it comes i've never
played a hyrule warriors game
i'm not sure if it's a it's like it's
not an rpg right that's just like a
fighting game
i have to think about it i'd prefer to
do one of the
rpgs actually so yes
wind waker would be awesome but wait
windbreaker is not
ported for any other console yet right
it's only gamecube
i don't have a gamecube at the moment so
actually it's probably not possible
[Music]
thank you
i also don't have a wii u i'm not
planning to buy a wii u i never had it
with you i heard it's uh
not the best nintendo console
definitely not gonna buy it just for
windbreaker
maybe one day it will come for switch
how possible how high is the possibility
for that but wait what was the other one
that
that we are all waiting for uh to come
out
to be ported to switch um what was it
called the
zelda game that we are waiting for to
come to switch i think it was originally
wii u a skyward sword yeah
i never played that one if that one
comes to switch i'm gonna play it for
sure there's also a lot of flying right
yeah wait was it ever announced already
or
eh you guys don't like skyward song
i think it has a lot of potential
flying on first yay perfect for me
flight simulator where was i
uh
thank you
you got it right this time indeed
[Music]
i really appreciate it
please have a small amount as thanks for
your dedication you read super jazz for
4.5 hours that's impressive
[Music]
um
i'm sorry i didn't notice your talent
sooner or
others in l you bring a lot of positive
energy every stream and your ability to
bring out the best in your fans and the
rest of your life is second to none
you guys want to make me cry again
stop
no no i don't want to cry thank you so
much thank you
your message warms my heart thank you
really thank you mr x tackle
tako thank you
ssj
why would i need a pro controller
do i need such a thing
[Music]
are the first thing i watch in the
mornings they make me happy and
energized for the rest of the day you're
amazing
i'm happy to hear that a more precise
movement
yeah i guess i could kind of need that
but
[Music]
does it make such a big difference
i i don't think so i don't know
how much is it anyway
[Music]
um
noisy neighborhood ghost rider i already
saw this on twitter i already saw
screenshots of this one
excuse me miss i seem to have got lost
again would you mind telling me the way
to the underworld i've seen you a few
times down there
thank you that was really funny i
already saw that i was wondering how
why didn't i read that one yet i i guess
it was uh in this
in that stream okay that's why i didn't
see it before
nice uh humor you got there my friend i
hope you find your way to cali in the
underworld but
keep in mind she belongs to me thank you
[Music]
on my transaction zero five perennial
banking rape halloween make red
my green dancer kiki is
function by the way am i ever saying
you're wrong correctly
you're wrong correctly your name
corrects
please let me know like you've been uh
superchatting for a while i really
wonder if i even say your name correctly
probably not
you're wrong correctly
rectangle magazine th
really if you're saying it's correct
64 thank you soon
can't watch the stream live to live due
to work but i wanted to support you with
a super chat
oh thank you keeping awesome you're so
underrated and i hope more people
realize your majesty soon
honestly um
i'm glad to have the people who are with
me now
because i think everyone who is here now
has a good heart and i just
i just feel like these are the good
people and if there's people
who don't even want to give me a chance
then i know they're not
not the ones that i need here
no if you're not even going to give me a
chance
then i don't want it
it's so hard to figure out what's a red
super chat but thank you
for the rex and duncan try disabling
your spoke effect
i'm not the one with the smoke effects
do you mean the smoke uh
super chats and about start sankishan
pointy start sound again
thank you i made you emotional
you make me emotional zero four five one
jim
thank you um merciless thank you
[Music]
thank
thank you
i skipped that name thank you abraham
sims thank you
very much
thank you thank you thank
about technical stuff via super chat two
times first
game audio is echoing one minute later
now it's fixed audio
good go burp go thank you
i am tofu
thank you george costanza
[Music]
translation is a true talent look
forward to seeing your
best of luck thank you
not even
five thank you nate the great thank you
lucky fives thank you i didn't want to
add to the suffrage chat live stream so
i saved this for after thank you
you're wonderful and your cheerful
demeanor has helped me feel motivated in
the mornings
thank you thank you blaster boy
one two three four five six thank you
looking for the top
thank you channel
this name
thank you thank you but i need my last
cough drop i'm really straining my fruit
here
with the happy thank you soon i don't
want to say that i'm like in a boring
tone but it's killing my fruits
[Music]
also i didn't eat anything today i'm
gonna get breakfast after this
i woke up and then straight went into
streaming
didn't even eat anything
here we go
no i'm
i'll eat after this don't worry yeah
a little bit late breakfast never too
late for breakfast
i like those restaurants who do like all
day breakfast
smart people intellectual people yes yes
yes
psycho
thank you
thank you girl you need to watch the
mouth youtube can
hits you in the ad revenue for it really
was it that bad i feel like the only
swear word i actually use
is the effort
i wonder if that's really such an issue
well my management told me i can i can
use it
if i need to also this game is just
making me so aggressive
it's asking for it
crank missile thank you i love you
phoenix and i love that you can talk
both you
both to your japanese and english fans
it helps bring us together
is
finally i can simp for the fast food
keep going love you
thank you
[Music]
for that
by the way i was in france uh
two times in my life but both times i
didn't really see any
anything of the city and i deeply
regret it yeah
one time i went to paris
and i went there for a convention
but we were so busy so i didn't even
check out the city
and went back and then another time
was uh i went to disneyland
and again i did not check out the city
france has like the only disneyland
in uh europe you know it wasn't even
wasn't wasn't that impressive
aurora's the first thank you smackpot
thank you soon
tonight five to
finding out my favorite whole life ian
member loves my favorite thing deserves
some super chat love
your favorite drink is dr peppa yay
your dedication and doing these live
streams were so cool get yourself some
more dr pepper and some magical dress
this weekend
no ah i cannot rest this weekend
like i my goal was this first week
to stream every day because the first
week
is the most important and tomorrow is
the collab but tomorrow
i'll only be doing the collab yeah um i
think i think for now well i'll think
about it because the collab is so early
so maybe i'll do something in the
evening i'll think about it but
on monday i'll be taking the day off
okay
but the whole week especially the
weekend is very important so
let's power through it together but
thank you shane thank you for worrying
about me
sunday uh japanese standard time 10
10 a.m i'll be uh reserving the slot
i think after the stream i'll be i'll be
reserving it so
yes
thank you
that has so many zeros how much is that
it's so confusing some currencies have
like
crazy zeros and then it's
uh i don't know is that i wish there was
an easier way to
to see this
it's like five million zeros but in the
currency that i know
is not it's not that so confusing
why can't we all have the same currency
all over the world would be so much
easier
be 4k for gamer thank you
journal
always make me smile i'm a poor ice
fairy so that's all i have the rest went
to cantaloupes but here's a blessing
from a b-day
kid instead uh your birthday keep up the
good work if it's your birthday
happy birthday thank you
for seven thank you
thank you so
[Music]
thank bronx819 again
here you go again i have to go to work
in three hours again but this is too
adorable to not watch also i can't send
super job for archive
thank you thank you thank you for
support also
i love the icon you have there
carlos banker thank you blaster boy one
two three four five six thank you
shout out to simpleflips what what does
that mean
anyone who knows thank you for the red
super chat thank you
really appreciate it
simple flips speed runner
ah ah simple flips is a speedrunner ah
backbeat highway thank you jake33w0706
thank you all of you
know know that guy wow you all know
about
mario 64 so much wow
pencil x thank you red from disco
thank
[Music]
short stories from me
you want to listen to my short stories i
see i was thinking of something similar
for the future
we'll see what i can do
michael
i could read you a german story
that's my kind of asmr chiara
reading a story in german a good night
story in german
really are you gonna listen to that but
i should probably put like
subtitles in english and japanese
i wonder if there's like a copyright
problem if i read like typical german
fairy tales
fairy tales do you call those fairy
tales like hansel and gretel
i wonder if that's if i could do that
hansel on critter do you know that
don't give us ideas you're giving me
ideas
cough chop hit smart are out of
copyright
free use damn we got a good idea here
hey can i really read the grim uh fairy
tales
that's probably what let's do that
oh that would be fun uh i'll wait until
i get
um a mic upgrade cali might be giving me
her current mic the one i'm using right
now is her previous mic
and she might even give me her current
mic
so once we got a good setup
with microphone i i want to do that
that's such a good idea
high fructose corn syrup thank you soon
keeps on dealing me those microphones
man
alexander anderson thank you carlos
danger thank you
here is my favorite audio book
er bumpers thank you
[Music]
function
so i can finally catch you live for once
never got to play this as a kid really
what
is there anyone in the chat who did not
play super mario 64 as a kid
i guess you i guess uh the people who
are like i don't know
16 17 18 probably didn't play it
wait the me me the me people are the
ones i did not play
who did not play it what so many
wow
wow i guess everyone
under like 20 or so did not play it
man that is a
well but now you can play it that's so
good that that nintendo brought out that
collection i honestly say
you all have to buy it if you didn't
play it you have to buy it's such
classic it's such a legendary game
you'll probably all be better than me i
did anyway
thank you steve royal thank you
[Music]
patrick
we reached the current stream already
yesterday's stream reading is done we
reached the current one
benchmade
today is my birthday can you sing me
happy birthday song in german
like not english birth japanese is fine
too
i will to say in german happy birthday
alex aka
in the clouds
your stream last night was fun so i
tried the mario games and it reminded me
why i enjoy playing games i'm excited to
see more of your streams also thank you
for sharing on my birthday
again so many birthday people
happy birthday thank you very good
cookie thank you soon
streaming at the time that works for me
this calls for salvation yay
[Music]
that is good i'm glad that this time is
better for some people
i think starting from next month my
streaming times will change a little bit
i'll be able to stream uh
the stream that was yesterday that time
slot i'll be able to stream
longer than that and
yeah so they will change it a little bit
not not completely but a little bit
where was i uh ah dante mercer
thank you can you get hundreds
george leon thank you great fail thank
you soon necromancy for kids thank you
shin
bony bard thank you
give you your uh pink orange flame on
your left eye
we will see if i ever got that
that makes thank you dear kara is going
to make a joke about kikiriki but your
employees could not be first
i apologize and promise promise to
kakariki from now on please tell them to
let me go
good job employees and yes
if you actually say [\h__\h] properly
you will be free but everyone
every i just want people i know it was
fun at first but i just want people to
get the greeting right please
is that too much to ask i know you want
to tease me guys but
i'd appreciate it if uh we could get
more correct greetings in the future
thank you
[Music]
but none of them make me smile as much
as you do thank you for all your
positivity and hard work we appreciate
you please stay true to yourself and
your whole dream
thank you that's so sweet thank you so
much
thank you i want to hug you
it's also your birthday what the hell
everyone's birthday
happy birthday thank you soon
jimmy mcrobbie thank you vice ravana
thank you
stomach hungry chicken cooking feeling
tank
feel and dunk jay
payton's 22 thank you soon hey girl i
love your streams here's my support for
kfb we love and support you thank you
for helping me during tough times
greetings from chile it's funny how
we only today
today one week before it was our debut
it's been
only one week exactly one week
and we already were able to make so many
people happy
that's wonderful that's what we came
here for
bronx again thank you so much
oh please don't force yourself to to
throw all these super chats okay
thank you thank you so much i really
appreciate it
thank you
there's so many canadian donations here
thank you soon
select thank you your german singing of
99 love for lunch was adorable more
german songs
we will see what i can do yeah thank you
funny funny
[Music]
and pineapple on pizza and burger is
good fight me i will not bite you let's
fight those people together who don't
agree with us
canadians where you at funny because
this person uh donated in
uh british pounds
uh i'll fight he's fighting with the
canadians
oh no the pineapple war is breaking out
logan thank you mad scientist thank you
secrets not a good username 360 tanka
did you know that pineapple pizza is
actually a canadian invention
true fact
are you sure
let's google that
pineapple pizza origin
by the way the man who invented hawaiian
hawaii pizza
died
sam pana polos who was born in greece
and moved to canada when he was 20
decided to try
pineapple on pizza in genius to attract
customers to one of his ontario-based
restaurants
rest in peace you hero
we just put it on just for the fun of it
see how it was going to taste
we were young in the business and we're
doing a lot of experience i love you
i love you
so it's a it's a guy from greece but he
moved to canada so i wouldn't say
it was a canadian thing
the guy who invented it was greek
what we could find about that he
definitely
did a good thing
night king thank you first thank you
your streams are the confidence and they
are the hand of my day thank you
thank you says thank
wow it's interesting how apparently
there's many
new people uh getting interested into
her life recently
i wonder where they came from
actually i would love to hear that
happy lump checkers
[Music]
the camera sucked yeah thank you so much
please come to the collab too thank you
stay with crystal thank you thank you
i am winning of course foreign
high fructose corn syrup again the
canadians are at it
can you oh i don't know i don't want to
say
things that you guys asked me to say
because i never know like what what it
is about
so i'm sorry thank you glory of combat
again
[Music]
getting over it mario edition yeah that
was definitely
close to it in the clouds time cushion a
random teammate
israel
thank you thank you sweet my friends
thank you sansam alright
here to invest in non-slip shoes
thank you i need those dab marios
isn't that
have really motivated me to be better
especially picking up other languages
again
oh that's nice
s k g
uh
when i was in school i tried to learn
german and japanese but gave up when i
graduated and now i'm inspired to get
back into practice ooh
thank you for the streams they're always
entertaining
[Music]
i'm so happy with the japanese please
continue to connect ian with japan
thank you soon i will try to do my best
i will do my best
in the clouds thank you soon
[Music]
i wonder if he's still watching probably
turned off
is
[Applause]
today i was deceived by my father i was
at the point where he
lied to me
i knew you were doing that but
i i just wanted to make you laugh
thank you park downing
bin in 94 reggie brown
fish page 47 dj
[Music]
he's the best papa definitely
sugary mess
i want to donate to the cannibalism for
uh the kfp empire thanks for the stream
thank you for your investment dear
friend
it's it was a good choice we will use
your money wisely
[Music]
do penguins taste like chicken
i wonder what they taste like but
i would never eat a penguin never
i mean i was quite angry at a penguin
today
but i still wouldn't eat it i would
maybe burn it
and kill it but not eat it
that goddamn penguin
i'll i'll burn you and i'll give you to
good
penguin name
[Music]
i love watching your streams and i'm so
happy to join them keep up the care
amazing work
much love from california thank you
thank you
[Music]
i wonder i think guys you need to ask
gura
if she eats a penguin
jk pankishin oh also industrial
wait actually let me
change music now
canadian trains canadian trains what of
canadian trains are they there
oh because all the canadians donated ah
bingo phone banking
sister since serious thank you thank you
so much
for the glory of the kfp canadians let
your voice be heard forever and press
camera
wow what an impressive uh text
to go with your super chat thank you
sorry bryce hollinsburg
how to not be bored mario has a lot of
complicated movement tech i suggest when
you get a chance to just experiment with
different commit
yeah i didn't i just went right into the
stages i never really practiced
so yeah you're right yeah thank you
bronx 819 lauren
blueberry tango shin definitely not
springtangashin soutakoma jangkashun
v thinking tankashin rasulu dankashin ak
hetsan kashan
bryce holland swift thank you another
good username thank you
cilantro here's the money to add penguin
to the way
lady jack angel yuki park town
gustavo ramirez
[Music]
i managed to get a crown and fall guys
before you could complete this race
magikaya
[Music]
good freaking job thank you so much
thank you jen
it was a long ride was it
thank you thank you
thank you spector from parents
[Music]
i think it's time to change to ppp bird
language here we go
tristan made pippi bean
devilish ppp kyra auric peepee ping
gartenda pippi bean sophisticate ppp
warlock wallart pippy bean vulture
pippy bean belly that
[Music]
pvp
actually my lips are hurting from saying
ppp i'm straining
ah my mouth too much
huh
good job tantrum please put this money
towards your marriage ceremony with cali
thank you so much for that huge donation
thank you
i will use it wisely possibly for the
upcoming marriage ceremony i don't know
if she'll
accept the marriage but i'll give it a
try
feeling dank crispy and dank flame on
boy
i won't win i want to win cali's remix
contest and get a custom voice
her confessing her love to you
good idea i hope you win
if someone else wins get that message
from me
feeling feel being dunk never knows best
free and dank mad scientist fiona dank
troy fitzwater film dunk
secret sympathy and thanks thank you
despite as whole penguin i hope you're
having fun with maria i'll never
forget what experienced it for the first
time back in the day
yeah indeed tank
and this bagel film tank out loud fiona
tank
tapioca senpai and tank alvaro diaz
fianc
jonathan parrish film tank confirmed
i gave to your wife here's yours
employee
number 137 thank you thank you
thank you so much i love how my
employees are paying me and i'm not
paying them
that's how it's supposed to be right
packaging replicated 24 danger soon
cyl thank you could you teach us the
effort in german cordova
effort to die this
it now that you asked me so directly
it's hard to say it
it's almost the same though it's just
one letter difference
thank you
very much
he made me say it he paid me to say it
not my fault he forced me to say it
[Music]
your papa does love you he just also
loves to mess with you
that was the first time though i always
thought he was the sweet kind of papa
who would never do something like that
to me
i was wrong i was so wrong
definitely not fair flames pp
that led to the most fun i've ever had
in my 10 months of watching whole life
what really i'm
so happy to hear that
ice husky i've started making a game
based on kfb what
i don't want to spoil too much so my
idea doesn't get stolen good good idea
but so far it's a mix of tycoon and a
mini game thing could i get
yes you have my approval of course you
have to call
that approval if you need something from
me
let me know
that's the second game already someone
made my loading screen into the game
which i was kind of hoping for anyway
[Music]
thank you for the sweet message thank
you shipping
jared hayes pakishan
i love refrigerators
i always enjoy seeing people play this
game it's a trip down memory lane for me
when i was hospitalized as a kid i spent
most of my time
time playing this game been a game ever
since
gamer
yeah it must be i feel it must be really
nice to see
some someone play such a nostalgic game
yeah
it's like going back to your childhood
then
[Music]
thank you for streaming and i believe
that you can beat this kiada i was
having a terrible night right now so
watching your stream is cheering me up
oh
i'm so glad to hear that thank you so
much
well if you believe in me i don't know i
guess i'm gonna believe in myself too
huh
thank you thank you ask perixx
thank you good job just want to let you
know you've been doing an amazing job of
being an entertaining streamer since
your debut
thank you looking forward to many more
from a live long kfb employee
you are giving me your whole life you
swear
thank you so much i'm looking forward to
working with you
thank you soon thank you so much thank
you thank you
perfect oh my god i am on fire
[Music]
intestinal clouds
please be careful you keep giving me
heart attacks no if i die you and kelly
can split the rest of my bank account
thank you
we will use it wisely streaky
i love you canada i am drunk but i won't
regret this this because you are so
cute cut amazing and keeping me from
this terrible world
you can say anything i will adhere to it
my captain my my captain
hashtag ksp
fur life i love oh whoo
i wonder if this person fell asleep by
now
it's kfp not ksb
thank you
[Music]
uh again the drunk person suddenly
writing in german
even though they're donating in u.s
dollars
sorry i
let you lol
when you're drunk and you suddenly start
speaking broken
german thank you
by the way he was writing i'm gonna
throw up sorry i'm gonna throw up
sorry i put you lol
drunk and [\h__\h] thank you
thank you thank you
[Music]
i don't know how to say her name ever
tmd
did you like my twitter post about the
marriage i don't think kelly has seen
him yet but even where to ship herself
yeah there's nothing she can do about it
christian camilo thank you
all right we have reached uh the end i
have to refresh now every donation that
follows after this
i will not read i repeat i will not read
any domain donation coming after
this giraffe click click
[Music]
and
where was it
i think that's a good stop no no no you
already
you no no no i won't be reading those no
no no
everything that is in my updated uh
window right now
no no i i appreciate it
and let me just read the rest no not you
won't read me well i accidentally read
you
no no no
all right let me scroll that's still a
lot oh there we go okay
[Music]
me calm down from a panic attack earlier
also forgive papa for his drawing
oh i'm so glad i could help i hope
you're okay
i hope you're okay
i wish i could do more but as
[Music]
what is that word play i don't
understand
that
i repeat every super chat coming now i
will not read anymore i repeat
[Music]
eric thank you thank you
i've had so much fun watching you this
stream your life is contagious and
your smile can brighten the darkest days
i hope you have a wonderful day
and know that everyone in the kiara fan
club will continue to support
you support and adore you always oh
so sweet thank you thank you so much
thank you thank you thank
[Music]
thank you
spectrum you are the first to remind oh
thank you suggestion next mario 64
stream you should spend a few minutes at
the start
just practicing all kinds of jumps and
flips i might just do that in my free
time i guess
yeah but thank you for the advice i need
to practice
indeed thank you so much
for
[Music]
oh
we're almost there guys just a book
thank you light pancaking sermon
joseph golden kitchen yeah
i repeat all the super chats coming in
now i will not be reading but i still
appreciate them thank you
donovan byron trail
thank you you didn't have super chat on
on tuesday and that was my birthday oh
happy birthday afterwards
foreign
if you don't archive the stream can you
still super chat and have no problems
with copyright
thank you so much
i saw you you're not invisible
oh wait first city i'm not sure about
the answer to this question
but thank you cheese 360. zero thank you
franklin fernandez thank you
oh you reminded me of something with
your super chat message
it's been a wonderful first week i'll
continue to support you and the other
members of holo ian by the way do you
plan to show fanatical stream i've made
some for of you
actually i want to do more in the future
on stream
[Music]
i wasn't really planning on it i was
gonna do like a meme
uh thing with that template that i
posted previously
uh maybe in the future maybe we'll do
something like a fan art
contest or something in the future and
then i might review them but generally
i do retweet a lot fan art a lot of fan
arts on twitter
so but yeah i want i look at all of them
i look at all of them
so definitely i appreciate the fan out
i'm probably already saw the one you did
or at this point
the same birthday and have not missed
the stream since oh thank you
thanks for giving me something to look
forward to every day i'm keeping you
thank you so much
your cheerful and fun personality makes
your heart glow the moments and most
vibrant halloween oh
thank you thank you tankaroony
in the clouds on verified time question
marawi
that's the end thank you all
so
i will now work on the collab for
tomorrow i'll also
open the slot on my channel for it
so that everyone can go in the waiting
room and
wait wait wait wait wait
they
i hope i'll see all of you tomorrow in
the collaboration
and until then
thank you so much for coming today
i had lots of fun actually
i was more frustrated but yeah
i'll finish in bye bye
bye bye see you tomorrow
[Music]
quickly enter this now
anyway