[Music]
here we go here goes the chat whoa
hello everyone can you hear cali can you
hear the game can you hear me
on the other side i guess i kind of want
the music to be bumping a little more
guys let's turn up this bang and music
it's been
in the background for me for a long time
and i want to
bang it even hot even higher here we go
the music is awesome
it's like such a beautiful jam vibing we
are vibing
hey guys hey hey guys well
well i think everything the sound seems
fine no okay okay
okay a little bit higher okay okay i'll
turn it on a tiny bit
okay okay let's see
well welcome everyone we are here today
because we are playing together as
takamuri
uh bleach brief dolls well they actually
got
a big big major update with a lot of new
content
including the arena and so
i thought that we should give it a shot
we together aren't we the best couples
to do this stuff together we are
i mean i guess it has been a long time
since we have done a collaboration
stream together so i pose i suppose now
is a
as good a time as any when you say a
long time
but it was just last week oh
i mean i guess it just feels it just
feels like a long time i suppose
if we don't talk for a week or like
don't collab for a week it feels like a
long time
yeah it does well anyway i'm talking
about
english and who are you hi oh hello
there
hi i'm uh lori callipe from whole live
english
um i'm i'm the resident shinigami reaper
hey
what's up what'd it do you can see why
i'm excited
this game must be perfect for you
so yeah guys
we i guess we start right off with
telling you guys that you
have to download the game i think you
can
use the link in our descriptions for it
and by the way
there is free services uh the japanese
server there is a cert
an asian server and there is the global
server and will be today
playing on the global server together
yup yup that's right and um it's super
easy to download
um and really easy to just get into
um you can just you can just go head
first into that bad boy um
plenty of tutorials to kind of show you
around um
the ui and whatnot and i get you real
comfortable playing it so i
highly recommend you just jump right in
you guys maybe you'll play against one
of us someday i don't know
possibly i'm gonna i'm gonna keep
you for myself gary ah
we're gonna work hard together today and
and forever until eternity
um yeah i don't know i can't make any
promises on that one listen
i can't make any promises on that one
listen
oh well so um
want to talk a little bit about bleach
yeah sure thing one moment guys i have a
qr code that i want to give you
just to make it super easy on the screen
as well yeah let me go ahead and
grab that qr code right above
me grab that bad boy
[Music]
here we go give me that trying to scan
it
guys try it try it i challenge you do it
just from your screen from your screen
you should be able to
all right from the stream screen the
stream's going streaming
screen all right scan the code
do it do it challenge accept it next
there we go just to make it easier for
you guys
just to make it easier for you guys so
you can just go ahead and make it super
easy
yeah it's luxury yeah
you guys hear me take that snap yeah
it's taking a while from there oh
[Music]
did you get the qrx on the screen i did
can you make it a bit bigger i had this
issue with it before
let's see there you go
no problem guys take it
it's big now big qr code it's a bit
blurry now
i think it should be fine kiara can you
just use your phone i got it i wrangled
that bad boy
all right y'all
is this big enough if i have it up there
guys
here you go yes oh i got it oh now it's
on my face ah get out of my face
there we go here you go guys check it
out
don't cover up your beautiful face huh
okay i'm shy listen can you guys get it
from here
it's okay i've noticed that before i
already know about it anyway
are you ready yeah sure thing here
where'd you put yours
by the way i'll put it in my top right
uh
above my logo my own logo cool
sounds good i don't want to cover up the
name grim shady because it's so iconic
i love that name i i'm so jealous now
because i got
i came out with a really basic boring
name kiara
hodo and yours is green sounds
so cool cairo it's okay everyone is
dream
shady it's me yeah it's me
let's see
[Music]
okie dokie and there we go so
okay let's talk about beach
yes a bleach um i know i have a bunch of
bleach fans that are here
i know that you guys are really excited
for me to play this game um
bleach is just a whole lot of um
nostalgia
uh for your boy because yeah it's true
back in the day
and this is actually this is this is
something that i just recently
remembered
um one of my first like christmas gifts
from my mother that i ever received
when she found out that i liked uh manga
and anime
was a volume one of the bleach manga
technically it's the first manga volume
that i ever owned
um was was bleach um
thank thanks to your mom i guess oh [\h__\h]
lady dead i think i was not active long
enough in the game i got kicked out
oh no that's okay no problem get back in
that bad boy um
but yeah so that's probably um why it's
kind of um very it's a very nostalgic
franchise for me and also because
um and this isn't so much bakken's a day
i did i did
watch the anime and read the manga back
in the day um
but then after that it was kind of um a
long while before
when i got into reaper college i guess
um my roommates were really really
really into bleach i had a friend
who was a huge fan of kampachi
and drew so much kampachi fan art so
like
that whole like arc um where like
kenpachi is kind of like the
the the main i guess in that arc they
focused on
i distinctly remember so watching so
much of
it because my friend really really
really liked kenpachi
i really hope that she's doing well
wherever she is she knows who she is so
i hope she's watching this and being
like hey
that's me i'm that friend
shout out to your friend who campacci
fan friend yeah
i think i also like uh kampachi's
bangkai the best
it's really really cool sick waiting a
long time
a lot of anticipation leading up to it
how about you kiara who's who's um
do you have good memories of bleacher
well to be honest i i'm not the best
informed person but bleach was like well
because i grew up in a german-speaking
country
um on tv there was like barely any anime
on it when i was younger but
one of the few like let's say there was
a handful like maybe five
five animes on german tv in in german
language german dubbing
and one of those five animes was bleach
so i kind of like when i was uh
i i think i sub um how do you say
subconsciously
yeah yeah just like i watched those
other
uh animes which i will not mention but
it was like
i think i didn't even realize yet like
that it was like what an anime is and
all that but
from from back in that time i do
remember
bleach a little bit um it's just been so
so long because i was a
really small baby phoenix and i barely
remember what happened back then
but it was one of those few legendary
german uh the freely legendary anime
that made it into the german tv
so yeah that's a long long long time ago
yeah on that one it's still here
because it is so legendary and we have a
super fun looking game
in front of you right
yeah oh about the fun guys what would
your bank i be
that's a good question bangkai being
like okay so like your ultimate freaking
freaking signature starting move myself
around signature freaking move unleash
the final the final form that you've
trained for ages
ages four i don't know i mean it's
already pretty obvious that like
my um my like my shinigami my sword my
uh
my zam pakuto i don't know how to
[\h__\h] say it
i'm so bad at the pronunciation would
obviously be ricky
right yes i would obviously use ricky
right so like let's see i haven't
actually thought super hard about what
kind of
sig bonk i would have just something
really stereotypical grim reaper
right probably i mean i feel like for me
but it'd also be super cool
i think you know what slicing it up
except actually little known fact
shinigami don't don't eat your souls at
least not where i'm from
not where i'm from you wouldn't eat a
dollar bill i've said this before
right we basically treat souls like
currency so it's a little different
a little different i say actually i was
gonna compare
your job to their job but i guess it's
there are quite a few different
differences
i will say though i kind of do want like
the cool shinigami robe
look what's going on because like my
outfit's pretty dang but like
i don't know you should wear the outfit
that ichigo wears
i mean i i kind of i kind of want my own
my own i guess kind of uh look
from the bleach universe i can't say
that uh
those pants i know they're kind of
styling
i don't want to sleep a little bit a
little bit
by the way my i think my move would be
something obviously phoenix
fire related so maybe like yeah it would
be called
maybe a turtle flame or something like
that
yeah uh yeah i can see that
yeah in the background i already do have
my my weapon you know i have my sword i
don't know why i didn't pick it up today
i think it's because it would be
covering up you
but that's i think i'm already equipped
perfectly
that's my zampakto
look at you
am i really isn't that kind of an insult
no no no no no it's not what the hell
you know what juniper means no can you
explain to me because i feel like i keep
getting the wrong
like impression is uh
a second second grade in uh
the thing before high school
it's officially oh you mean like middle
yeah yeah but in our system i guess it
would be eighth grader
syndrome it's like you know when you as
a child you you act like this you have
all kinds of magical powers and all that
but
i mean we we do it's not we don't act as
if we do you
you're a reaper i'm a phoenix i can i
can totally spit fire this is not just
my imagination
oh yeah is that a fact but it's like the
edgy teen face yeah
edgy no oh actually i guess edgy
pre-teen face
oh i see it
i kind of get it when you phrase it that
way it makes a little more sense to me
yeah well anyway to go back to the topic
uh blitz brave cells is as we talked
about
originally a popular tv anime and
uh it was also it's i think it's is it
still continued the manga
oh no it's ended i believe it's ended
okay
well and then and now you got this
smartphone game
uh but you can also play it on pc on
steam if you don't want to play it on
your phone for whatever reason
and then you can get all these fancy
characters you can build teams you can
fight together with them
and take on super super big strong
enemies
and yeah also there's some co-op uh
things and arena and all that up to six
people can play together
with new friends let's go have some fun
like we are having
today yeah very excited
you wanna uh explain how we do the co-op
thing
um yeah sure absolutely
all right so yeah let's see
uh before we do before we actually uh
jump into the co-op
we're going to need to um it's
it's that time everyone yeah it's that
time do you know what time it is
all right it's gotcha time you guys um
we all knew that this was coming
um let's see if if we can be lucky
because i'm not sure
a lot of free pulls a lot of free pulls
right so we're gonna do all of them
uh yeah i mean i'd like to but mainly
what we're trying to do here is
we're doing the uh the guaranteed
selectable six
is the main gotcha we're doing so go to
the shop summons characters
choose a six star summons so basically
you get one of five characters
chosen by you and um and now let's try
to
use that in the co-op exactly we'll use
the character that we get
uh in the co-op so yeah do you want to
go play
sure let's do select for free let's
enter the gotcha hell let's
go into the catcher here we go
all right so we go and we get only one
right
uh yes so basically you choose five
characters to use in the summons and
you can see details use character by
tapping and holding on their thumbnail
image
by megane prince hold on a second sorry
i love this
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh yeah you're going to probably be
choosing completely different characters
let's see what you end up with
i'm going in the show has a lot of
a lot of cool mega nays and a lot of
cool uh closed eye characters
we got we got to start with the homie
with my main homie though
i think i think so look only
this is those children oh that's all i
got let's see
yeah i think it's like santa claus
um so i think you guys everyone here
um in in my in my chat realizes that
i've put up a poll
i put up a poll saying um who is your
favorite bleach character
now uh there are only two selections but
that's because the right answer is in
there
um so uh it is a bit
a bit rigged though uh because again
ichimaru
lost the poll um i don't understand how
that could happen possibly
um but it's fine also because uh gin
also won the poll
again is the best my favorite kelly i
guess
the fox space i basically got
it it's christmas over here because i
got that's so in a christmas
santa claus outfit oh my gosh it's
christmas and june my dog
looks really cute are you pulling yet
no i'm looking at i want to look at the
homies
i want to look at the homies i'll i'll
summon some others meanwhile i guess
can i summon those this just has like an
array of just
incredible mega nay characters i just
that's another thing you can do so okay
i just want to point this out really
quick
um you guys can watch ads to get
character
i just thought that was really cool is
it bleach
ads because then i'm fine with it oh i'm
i'm not sure
actually i haven't tested it out yet i'm
going to test that later
nice oh that's her again
so cute i want to try
grim
it's just just so shiro wait i'll jump
in again can i do that oh yeah
yeah i want oh what is this beginning i
need to see my options
there's too much going on in my head
right now okay
um i chose i chose grim jio as my first
free character
but i don't think i get him in the co-op
unfortunately
i think these are the homies
i remember chad i got in the chat
i always used to be so taken aback and
i'm like oh someone said chad why'd they
say chad i'm like oh that's just what
they call them
you will receive one of the characters
you selected did you choose the the
sticks
yeah i already got that i'm doing
different gotcha oh well i'm waiting for
you
okay cool wow i got the christmas lady
that's
it nice
nice good results i think
yeah i mean i really i really wanted
again but
i mean i still hey i'm cool with rookie
as well rukio was the first like
what the hell i i know i can't i'll give
you i'll give you again
and i'll give you chad let's try it wait
did you get gin
yeah i think so how i remember getting
him in in the other
gotcha that i just did okay explain to
me where the where the gacha is
um
beginners beginners kickoff summons okay
yeah that one that one i gotta give him
i think i got him even
twice no what
freestyle start getting
oh wait can i add up my team here all
right kenpachi
kelly they come as level 200. wait what
oh heck yeah ones we don't have to worry
anymore about losing
nice
wow lucky what is with all these cute
cones
all right who else did i put in not
enough spirit orbs no
no
all right all right but we're not
fighting with this team because co-op is
only with one character that's right i
think we'll both be using our six star
character
holy damn level two yeah i'll use reiki
yeah that's sparkly
oh yeah all right all right all right
first thing for ya i will i will get gin
another time i'm certain
my poll still stands you guys know what
to do go vote
go vote so
for the for the co-op we're gonna hide
the screen for a moment but
uh yeah yeah okay hide that hide that
bad boy
all right all right you guys aren't
allowed to see the secret
wait where's my screen uh
this one there we go okay i hit the
screen
are you just i guess write the write the
code to me and
in discord we'll do we're gonna do the
droplet trial
okay we tried uh by the way off screen
which
we tried before doing the gaja and we
uh gloriously failed and died two times
two out of two times but we didn't have
our six stars yet so
now we have obviously higher chances
yeah exactly
and there's a there's a little
surprise i guess i'm gonna explain it
while you're setting up the lobby
yeah there is a surprise this time
during our playthrough if we can clear
the quest
three times which i am now hopeful we
will manage to do
we have got the permission to give all
players
20 spirit balls and 10 gotcha tickets as
a gift
yay yeah thank you
thank you very much i'm hiding because
of the matching guys did you listen
we have to hide you guys aren't allowed
in here it's our it's our secret
it's our secret room our secret room
now kiara are you able to are you able
to use the character that you pulled
oh wait yeah i have to set that up
that's right uh
let's see no i'm not
i'm also not but i do have hanatara for
some reason who is it level one
um yeah recommended level 120
um maybe let's not let's not do that um
i'm going to make a new room
and we're going to do um level 20.
i can be ichigo level 20.
i had this issue earlier as well okay
yeah
i'll send you a new one i'm making a new
room but
but then if we can't use the six stars
this is gonna be
uh it's fine it'll be a nice challenge
all right
rarity descending the right attribute
all all it's all them all hit cancel
choose the green
tab ah
kelly you figured it out i figured it
out okay
uh when you're like when you add you you
know that you did the the
the you opened that window right where
we want to change the character
yes and even further on the right side
there's two signs for kokoro
right in japanese
and in one of those windows it should
have uh
the character that you pulled for me it
was the green one
okay me too actually okay okay perfect
now
we're talking now we're cooking all
right cool
here we go making the room thank you
very much chad you guys are chad's
okay you're making a new room right yep
level 200 woo baby now we can just go
right into it so we're going to do
we're going to do the droplet trial
we're just going to do level
um 120. let's do technique droplet trial
that sounds fun uh create a room
we got that technique no we do we do i
chose the one that was uh green for both
of us so
all right and here you go here's the
code all right
and one free free four
i'm gonna switch back to the main screen
but i am going to go ahead and cover up
okay in fact i'll use the qr code
i am in it it doesn't
say the code anymore i think though once
we're in that room
oh it does for me so i'm gonna cover it
really yup oh okay
all right perfect now we're going to go
ahead and switch
okay cool here we go
ready ready let's go are you ready to
party kiara
i am so ready
exciting stuff here we go on to the
battle we go
kiara and the grim shady the real grim
shady
get it right i'm the real grim shade
it only says scream shady in your name
all right party time uh look at all
these six special attacks i got
oh down you go rich money all right
oh my god wow
that was so sick following freaking icy
moves
you need my help i love it rookie is so
strong
oh my god oh wait my health oh no i
gotta watch it
i can't just go in ruthlessly like that
there we go
yes we should not overdo it we gotta be
saving those big moves just kidding i'm
gonna go ahead and use my powerful move
right now
[Music]
yeah maybe i don't know probably should
have saved it i don't really care that
looked
sick no need for saving
your special abilities no need for that
you're right you're totally right i have
a bad habit of doing that
saving my specials i love those aoe
skills i have like they're all fire
themed is that a phoenix it's like what
the hell
that's really cool it's a perfect match
it's almost as good and i'm super
planned yeah
seriously all right i got it sorry
where are we going all right where to
next i'm in bad
shape right now i'm just gonna although
otto
is gonna lead the way okay here we go
oh no i don't need your help oh i'm dead
here use the spirit orbs to continue
it's fine i'll use my spirit orbs and
i'm back to life
it's cool leave it to me
we gotta win this kiara for the viewers
where are you at i guess i guess we
still need to oh
no i have 40.
you must continue yeah we can do it for
the viewers for the viewers
i want them to get the free stuff
for you guys don't worry yeah don't
worry is there going to be like the
final boss that i should get
your question
it's okay we'll play it again we'll play
it again after this
we'll play a different trial i panicked
it and i skipped it no shh
yes i took it away from you guys
no problem only i want the viewers to
get the free stuff
so i'm cool with it i had one hp for the
longest time
oh my gosh that's kind of impressive
though in and of itself
that is impressive mm-hmm the clutch
i will protect my prince
[Music]
okay easy
we're going that way ah the i think that
everyone
shows us where to go oh okay cool
nice okay party time lads
yeah again when he's frozen so grimly
like fried chicken yeah
hit him with that fire who are you
fighting
oh i think i really just figured out
what my
like ultimate final move technique would
be kill him with a baby
i like use my my scythe turns into um
the bass guitar from my roki cover
and with one stroke everyone just dies
that sounds dope
it actually reminds me back in the day
papa reaper used to like watch a lot of
anime with me
[Music]
and actually used to watch bleach with
me as well bakkens a day
and i specifically reca yeah papa reaper
i specifically recall him saying
you know kelly if i if i had an
ultimate technique for my sword it would
turn into a piano
and and if i hit one key everyone in the
world dies and i said
dad i don't think that's i don't think
that'd be a very good move
he's like why not haven't and i'm like
well if everyone in the world dies
that's just kind of
i mean it's not a great
yeah not really for me
my parents did not really have any
interest in anime
oh yeah i mean mama reaper didn't either
but
she she was happy to get me manga if i
wanted it it's very nice
for a little holiday present more into
gaming like we played world of warcraft
and stuff yeah yeah you mentioned
that yeah they're big gamers but not
oh you died again i'm dying so much
yeah but the good thing is we got some
heroes to revive ourselves so we're not
gonna fail
yeah i think we'll be fine yeah for the
viewers for you guys
yeah let's go
[Applause]
go
[Music]
yay it's a perfect foil for each other
i'm surprised that
those are level 120 and we're 200 and
they're still
killing us so often yeah but we're also
killing a lot of them
is the thing yeah i don't think we're
really we realize like how many
people we're taking down there's a lot
thank god yes i know right
and i love being able to attack from far
away that's super on brand for me
actually
my scythe can do stuff like this so oh
yeah flash and then like a sick like
blast what looks like air but it's
really it's the sci-fi extending
yeah oh whoa a boss battle time party
give me this but i have to break it okay
now give it to me
all right while you're frozen i'm gonna
beat you up
and here we go and here we go
we have to do it hey kiara do you have
any accessories by chance i don't think
we've really gotten into that
yet nothing added
at least no that's fine it's okay we're
we're going in we're going in
just uh just raw like this my dog no
problems
okay let me out don't
[Music]
hang on let me get out of here i need to
run i need to run no no please
okay i'll come back back to life back to
reality
oh my god no problem
we can do this we can do this we just
have to be careful be on the defensive
oh my god i wish i still had my special
skill both of us we both wasted it
yeah it's honestly it's my fault because
i chose like a really hard level
next we'll we'll go to the the medium
one
no okay
there we go we're just not uh that
leveled up yet
he's fine oh my god the boss is there
she's dead almost i think oh really
oh sick wow that is a really heavy
uh medieval flail oh my god
okay i need to use more of my specials
square
my where's sheet dam and a jewel nice
finish yeah we did it uh-oh we're
returning and i'm dead
rocky's like a phoenix
all right i was getting back to the
lobby quest clear
the screen oh no there we go okay
oh should i send you a friend request
i'll send you one i don't know did you
question
yeah send a friend request i'll send you
one
yes let's be friends
also send you a friend request so you
are now friends beat me to the punch
yeah so i just uh i've just figured
something out
i did that yeah i just figured something
out kiara
um it's that the stage that we were on
was meant for four people so actually in
reality
we are really good at the game
where we good or where are our
characters good it's a good question
that's a very good question that makes
uh
one out of three victories we want to
get
two more victories in order to get those
free stuff
for the audience exactly exactly so
this time a new one we're gonna go on a
stage for two people
oh okay that's good then it might also
not take that long
exactly this is this is actually a lot
of fun i know there's also
the arena and which is the new feature
and we wanted to try it out but
unfortunately the arena is a bit
buggy at the moment so we can't play
that today guys
i hope that's okay but you guys make
sure to check the arena out
once it's available once it's fixed
and then you're gonna have a lot of fun
in there i promise you
yes indeed i went ahead and created a
brand new room kiara so i'll give you
the code
this time uh we're going to be tackling
a bit of an easier
level um stage let's see this one also
looks like this
people though so let me see
hold on all right so we're going to be
doing
um like a lower level stage
if that's all good with you yeah no
problem
i did test the arena in the tutorial
though
so i i did see that and it's it's
very interesting we do want to check it
out someday
i only did the tutorial yeah that sounds
really fun we should play it together
let's go level 20. create the room i
think the arena was for
three people maximum three people so
we can invite some more friends next
time yeah exactly
all right new journey okay
there you go okay there we go
so recommended uh we got recommended the
accessory fusion trial
and it's beginner mode so i think we
might not die this time how about we
make it a challenge to not die at all
this time
unless you have to use the spirit like i
don't want to have to use them
yeah all right let's do it start the
quest
all right let's make it
okay here we go in the city oh it's oh
like
oh are we flying this way oh
okay cool oh yeah these are much easier
they die immediately
leave it to your boys to pick a
professional shinigami mission right off
the bat
it's just my inside instinct
wow wait are you level 10
yeah i think that's why it's recommended
level 20. we do well on this one we'll
go up to level six
okay and try that trial
i missed some some sparkly things okay
we'll get them next time
i would waste why'd i use that then fine
[Music]
you know what that fits me it's my boy
this is another this is another homie
right here who i also i remember
really really liking back in the day
there you are
mostly because
that dude is so short so freaking small
little chat nose chat look at chat nose
you like short people chat knows they're
calling me out kiara
i'm calling you out too right here hey
you stopped that hey
hey listen well not bad not bad let's go
back to the co-op quest menu and i'll go
ahead and start up a brand new room and
this time
we're going to do level 60 kiara so we
might get just the right balance here
that's that we needed a little bit
off balance because one was super hard
one was super easy but the next one
will win as well no problem all right
let's see
uh let's do um accessory fusion trial
level 16. i'll create a room sounds good
to me
all right and here's the code coming
your way
jag it's the first number that's it i'm
ready
i am so ready all right
i got it i have received the secret code
there we go all right
okay let's party
okay let's start ready up here we go for
the
immediate we got to do this for everyone
for the kfp employees for the deadbeats
this is for everybody what
yes this is for everyone what did you do
huh nothing this is for everyone this
battle
that's why we must win i mean the
presents yes
yeah i mean it's fitting that you're
dressed like um like a santa because
it's like you're going to be gifting the
kfp
employees and the deadbeats uh by
winning these battles we'll get them
those spirit balls
also works really well because my powers
are super icy
iced ice baby
and put in some little moves okay that's
a big one
oh wow oh yeah get them knock them down
we make a good team mm-hmm
perfectly balanced okay
yeah i think
i think caleb knew that takamori was
unbeatable and perfect they're mostly
harmonized
yep exactly of course now this
this level feels um like pretty good for
us
like yeah yeah difficulty wise
i did like the the first one though
because it was quite the challenge
it was i like a challenge give me a run
what's it called adrenaline like yeah
adrenaline
adrenaline all right we're gonna go up i
thought so too
it's fun okay here we go
boss battle battle give me some of this
we don't need the health until maybe
later so
oh
you want to use your special skills uh
oh yeah i might as well huh
i mean it's time anyway here we go
show us what you got yeah here we go
[Music]
[Applause]
yay we we have finished three out of
three battles
all clear what does that mean
that means what it means yes we're
giving
everyone 20 spirit balls and 20 brave
souls
actually yeah it was uh supposed to be
10 but we're actually giving 20 brave
souls gotcha tickets
yay y'all thought we did it kusatori we
did it
for you guys free orbs stuff everyone's
very excited
they'll probably just receive it so in
the game automatically at some point
look forward to that
yay so let's get out of that co-op um
all right go back home
wow you got nice hair yeah
wait who grim gel yeah
yeah i love green juice
and he got that kitty tail yeah
wow wow it is quite long
another one of my favorites some a real
cool
real honorable homie right here do some
spins for us grimshaw do some spins for
us
are you looking at my stream no no no i
have i have my own little my own little
grim jam
oh you got him too he's spinning him
around he's doing a little dance for me
dance my little my little ring-tailed
lemur boy
well
uh i think that was that was a lot of
fun
uh i think we had a blast with that but
unfortunately
it has come to an end
would you like to make the announcement
actually first kiara i want to i want to
get something
i actually do want to i want to play one
more round if it's okay
oh is that okay okay okay
okay did you put did did we miss
something
no i i wanna i wanna play an upper
mid-tier quest
if at all possible is that okay of
course
of course why not
okay cool let's do it awesome i
i have the itch i want to play just a
bit longer if it's fine with you
you could even if you want a bit of a
challenge you could change the character
from your level 200 character
to the
wait where um wait wait wait are there
yeah we could change but they're level
one
the other ones that we got like
let me see let me check out the trials
here because i want to see like the
recommended level
maybe like upper two maybe level 100
might be good might be a good one to
check out
the droplet quest yeah i feel like that
might be pretty good that's pretty much
uh like upper
upper level upper mid choice okay
awesome yeah level 100 might be good um
let's see how about accessory fusion
trial
um let's do the green one what's this
kanji
because
okay cool that's like the only one that
i don't like understand
oh okay cool it's a like
like special vasa special technique oh i
see i see
cool let's do that one together and i'm
gonna go ahead and
hide the password real quick and make
the room and this will be
our final go at it i have a good feeling
about this one okay
all right all right let's do it create
that room
going in for an uh extra round
whichever one you guys want just just
type it in the chat let's go party time
okay i got here i got your key okay cool
cool
all right we got this one i'm excited to
see how we fare this time because this
is like
i think this is the perfect for us more
difficult than the last one we did
huh yeah it's more difficult
this one's more difficult than the level
61 but it's not as difficult as the
first one that we did
that one was like 120 or something like
that so i think this should be fine
all right start the quest here we go
let's see how we fare
all right you asked for uncle do you get
an encoder
here we go
[Music]
all right here we go okay
all right hey guys little walk in the
park yeah just a little
a little sampo together osampo oh my
gosh
okay nice nice day outside
yeah you lovely for someone here a
lovely mori if you will
yeah we're in amory so
rainbow in the morty could not be more
fitting i'm gonna burn this
a bit
you guys
[Laughter]
right winky donk yeah but now we're out
of the morning oh now
now we're not in the forest
okay yeah this level is pretty good it's
about like challenging um
oh pretty tense but not unbeatable
we're not failing at the first second
that's good
where am i where are you right here
you're under attack no don't hit that
one no ah i'm gonna have to use it early
it's fine
just use yours for the final boss please
okay wait them away that's
that's the way to go nice
hit that hit it shaky yeah grim shady
you can count on me
stand up
okay the health orb i think we'll make
it out of this okay i spoke too soon i
spoke too soon
oh no okay from here i'll get them from
here
attack from far away yes keep a safe
distance
that seems like a pretty good technique
actually could have reached them
probably yeah nice strategy
okay oh we're in the morning again by
the way
my favorite place i might
die soon all right no worries i got your
back okay
i'll just keep going far away i just
rise again
is that yeah that attack is that a fire
manta
or a phoenix i'm not sure oh good
question
i gotta revive once here i'll let myself
revive one one time
me too me too yeah okay
i feel like we're actually pretty close
to this one i feel pretty good about it
oh there's another okay
nice oh you're still here hang dude
sorry i was gonna i had to
all good in the neighborhood had a
little talking them oh my
it is boss battle time boss battle time
let's go
[Music]
that's my dude no what are you doing my
dog
friend you know
my dog it's so cool all right i think we
won
yay we're done we're done we're done yay
[Music]
yeah quest clear leave it to us
yeah that felt really good
i don't know why but i got kicked out
again sorry but we're at the end anyway
so
it's all good no worries got all kinds
of item bonuses yata
let's go back home okay let's go
let's go uh spin around grim joe again
oh hold on
i love kenpachi sorry i'm really excited
again
yes it's too fun to spin them around
oh man i can't wait to go draw more
characters
four out of four out of three uh
for all the free co-op challenges i
think we have uh
done very well with that and that was a
lot of fun like i love i love all of the
the like fighting effects the attacks
that we had and for some reason
there must have been some fate here
because
me getting a character with all those
fire skills
it is it is meant to be yes
i think so that it worked out almost too
perfectly i would say but there there
were no forces at work you guys that was
just
that was just the god the gotcha gods
giving us all their luck
thank you thank you caleb for sponsoring
this and there's also
a currently running campaign as you see
saw see sauce
as you've seen the uh six star
received six six star characters uh
campaign
you get a chance to roll it that's the
same one that the same that we did right
yep maybe you guys will i don't know be
pretty lucky and get uh your favorite
character gin ichimaru
uh from the series bleach i don't know
maybe you'll be a little luckier than me
any possibilities can happen anything
can happen you guys i'm gonna probably
go back and try to get
to try to try to get my fave let's be
real not satisfied huh you must get more
and more from the gotcha
it's okay i understand i understand i've
been very addicted to gotcha games
before and it's just what happens but
we're trying to control yourself a
little bit okay we don't want to lose
you
it's easy to lose yourself there yeah
it's okay yeah it's okay
a little bit more it's okay you you're
not that deep in there yet
i didn't realize like i always used to
be like ha i don't understand
the the gotcha thing and now all of a
sudden with these feelings of wanting to
pull
in i'm like i'm slowly starting to kind
of get it i kind of understand now
there have been some in the past that
have similar like things like that but
not
it is my first like like really like
gotcha yeah maybe
possibly maybe my second and that's like
the best you could start out with or
like
get into because it has like all these
connections to you
yeah you know that's actually good
everything that was those hollow
libraries
you're right yeah hollows but i i
recently have started saying holos
a little bit i can't stop myself
i won't know where that came from hey
listen definitely not my job come on
come on man listen but i have a list of
characters that i want to pull
actually i'm going to read them out to
you guys you guys know
obviously i think you guys know who
number one is again of course
um i got rukia yeah go ahead and cross
her off my list
little check mark um
we gotta get una mr hat and club
so the the the one big memory i have
of um of urahara is that at every single
um gathering of fans of of um
of anime and manga always had like maybe
500 people wearing his head
oh yeah oh mr keys okay
and i'm picking up my phone to go ahead
and make a lot of free stuff in this
game
go ahead i'm going to go ahead and do
that rip the band-aid off you guys i
also owned one of those hats
i couldn't help myself hats are very uh
cultured and useful
you should try this one as well and then
i did get gampachi
and i don't have toshiro yet and i
wanted to get
an ng and i have grim jio use grimshaw
for the next co-op or arena
oh god the friend requests
are you getting
that's a lot of friend requests i can't
accept them sorry guys
you cannot accept cannot accept
let's see if we got so far you can punch
can't forget are you going free so many
come on i'm looking through all the
characters that i got
what's with all these coins there are
literally so many dude that's what i was
gonna say i was like really
should we make an army with them
you know what yeah who of the same
character cannot be on the same team i
see okay
well then i just have to pull different
cons that's the way that you fix that
problem
ah smart you put in chat you need chad
callie
i do how come you didn't get the chad
i remember this character so sick look
at him with the shades
i don't know dude you seem to get you
got a lot of the characters that i
wanted so i'm like
i'm not salty or anything i'm just you
know you know
i'm just yeah whatever man
whatever i'm sorry i took i took your
luck i don't know it kind of uh
went over to my side no no no it's not
on purpose
it's cool man
i you know what after this i i'm
definitely going to go get
but that was really fun because i do
want to at least
see how playing the game is with the
homie because i just remember i used to
be such a big fan back in the day and
still kind of am in essence oh the whole
squad is here
we got grimshaw we got rukia we got
kenpachi
yeah on the stone that swivels as well
so cool kelly are you are you i'm ready
to uh
say goodbye to you all your beloved
characters no
is it time already i want to play
i want to play with them more all right
well i hope
everyone will enjoy the three rewards
that you got through us
and i hope that you guys will enjoy the
co-op mode and the arena
you can already play the arena we just
didn't we weren't able to introduce it
today
so sorry about that but you definitely
should check out and as you see above us
there is a qr code or maybe cali
somewhere else but try out the qr code
and otherwise the links in the
descriptions are there as well for you
guys
to check out and download the game get
it today
or get it never oh no or i mean whenever
but but today would be the best day to
get it so
yeah they got a huge update everyone hmm
have a good time and maybe maybe you'll
run into one of us i don't know
um who could say because i mean i i can
speak for myself when i say i i'm going
to be doing a couple more
polls reliving my uh nostalgia trip hey
listen i didn't think it was going to
hit me this hard until now
and i'm like eh i'll well i'll invite
you to
my circle of anonymous gotcha players
help you out later on yeah sounds good
thank you
yeah appreciate it please be kind to me
really
yeah you know it's part of that circle
no way no way
heck yeah my dude please please i don't
know if that's a good thing or a bad
thing
anyway i just wanted to also say um a
big thank you to k-lab again for
sponsoring this stream
thank you so much uh for letting us play
your super fun game and and for giving
our fans some awesome rewards
for our very valiant efforts it's very
fun we had lots of fun yeah i want to
try it again
maybe maybe next time we can do the
arena
yeah i want to try to read it soon so
with that said
uh i'll say goodbye to my peeps in
german and in german we say
and you remember ken i did i did and
and for the dead beats we say do you
remember quesadilla
um what
bye everyone see you later thank you so
much caleb for sponsoring and hope you
guys enjoyed playing
bleach brave souls catch you on the flip
side bye bye
bye thank you goodbye
[Music]
so
you