[Music]
Wow, Doremifa Sorashi's Hello Live
Device's Riggs's Manabu Egg Doseji
So, Wow, wait a second, let me just start tweeting I
'm really sorry,
again I'm really sorry for
messing up today, huh? I completely forgot about the task that was due today.  I
went to that dance lesson today after the dance lesson, and it was a little longer than usual,
so I'm
really tired, so I might not be able to stream it.  I
didn't really set a frame for it, and I
was thinking of doing it as a guerilla game, but I have
n't been able to do much hardcore Minecraft lately,
so I wanted to do what I wanted to do today, but I had to
go home when I got home.  I didn't know what time it would be,
so I posted about 19:00 to 20:00,
but I forgot to do the task,
and it ended up being 11:30 p.m. Sorry, sorry,
it started.  I
posted this
today.DanceDanceIt was hard today.It
was hard, but I got compliments.I
drank a little water from the manager.I
still have some work to do, but for now, I'm
busy, so I just erased the day that was a little urgent.Work
today.
Only the final one came. It
's good, it's good. Well then, let
's go right away. But while I haven't received any money, a lot of things have changed.  I
heard that today during the dance lesson, I heard that the company president
apparently died. I do
n't know why,
but I only attended the first day, so I'm
a little lonely, so I guess I'll play the background music. It's so
loud.
How about making it loud?
[Music]
The BGM is a little lonely, so let's keep it like this. It's the
first day. It's like a bridge.
No, everyone, there's that person who's nowhere to be seen.  Takokoko
to senpai and now
Hello there Hello polka senpai Ah, this house is
evolving so much The house is evolving so much That's
right, that's amazing What's
going on What's going on?  I
want a lot of food. I haven't picked it up. Is it
full? I was able to pick it up. Good thing I picked it up. I
want more
food. How much food is there? I want more food. I don't know.
What happened today?
I just connected to Minecraft for the first time today, and have
n't done anything yet. Do
n't just sit around and eat. I
'll eat a lot of food, but that's okay.
Lyrica's body was stiff because of the stretching during the dance.
Chashi-chan was acting up and
something was happening.The
scissors were already running around.I
heard her talking to herself a little while ago.It looks
like she was doing some stretching.  It wasn't
even a dance, but before the dance, he was
doing some kind of stretching motion to stretch his body.I
thought, ``The president wasn't stretching at all,'' and when I looked at him, he was so hot that he could
n't move.What
if the truth were true?  That's right, Popolka-senpai. I was
actually making something. Ta-chan got so stiff
during the dance that she
couldn't move.
Hello, Ah-chan. What are you doing today?
Eh, why are you wearing clothes with such a high exposure image
? Yes, these are baby's clothes. Red is not good. I
thought I should give the baby iron armor. Well, I wonder
if Yuu has Popo or Po.
Ehaa-chan also has iron equipment.  Isn't it nice to have a light car?
Kaha-chan is
also doing something. Polka is equipped with Diamond, is
n't she? Polka
was in a lot of trouble today, so she's already equipped with Diamond. What
happened to her? It's scary.  Yo
This guy had a big hand, and the
iron guy died. He died because the iron guy's head was cut too big. I
always had the impression that he was doing some kind of farming,
but why did he die? He's a
dangerous guy who is also in the village.  There are times when the
attack comes from Peace Village Popon.That's
why it looks even more like Popon.It's
amazing that Popon looks so big.It makes me look like someone who only wears shoes, so I do
n't want to wear any clothes.  It's
a bit difficult because I only have my own clothes. Well, I
had one on one and smoked this and that. I'm
sorry, I was smoking,
thank you. Thank you. I finally ran out of clothes. It's my
first time today. It's my first time today.
Let's get along as friends.
What are you doing? It's scary. I just
came here, so to be honest, I don't know anything about it.
Hacha told me that.  I'll give it to you.
Maybe Hacha is a senior.
Please tell me. Please tell me. Please tell me. I want this. I
got this equipment from Pol Pol. I was
using it on that first day, so I think I have it. That's
amazing.  Achan-senpai, this is a baby,
senior-baby, what should we
do with this? What should we do? Take it, take it, take it, but it's about money. So you
won't give it to me for nothing, so you won't give it to me anyway.
No, I was
just bragging. Of course I can't say it.
But what do you think? I was just asking for your opinion. I don't
really care. You don't have any fancy equipment. Well, you do
n't have any equipment at all. That's what I
said. I made it, I made it, I made it. I can't make it.
Maybe I won't be able to make
one, so how many should I make? I can
make one, but I don't know if it's an ax or something. I don't know if it's an axe or something, but I
wonder if I have the right equipment, like rice, and something like a sword.  I do
n't know if that's a good thing or not, but no,
if that's the case, wouldn't it be better to give it to the bees as well
? Tsuruha is so
exciting that it's such a waste. What should I do? Let's go to Tsuruha. There are
n't that many people who think Tsuruha is so cool.  Even if there's a big sword, you'll
die anyway if you have hardcore armor,
so why not make sure you're smart?
[Music]
Lots of nauseous peeps.  It's too loud
to say, just go to sleep.
Is Po-senpai producing raw fish? There's some raw fish. There
's about 30 of them. I want a tree. The
bed of the tree is floating. It
's floating. It's true. I made a fleet.
Free.  I haven't made anything. I haven't made anything. It's
like a mission.
Yes, now that I think about it, it's a mission. I wonder what's going on.  It
was on the responsor, right now.
Spongebob lives there. That mission was over
there. Yeah, I
don't know, I don't know. I
'll take a look at the server. It's
probably more written on the respons point than on the server.  I feel like I was doing this. I ca
n't make any money.
What's the point? I'm always doing videos like this. So when I
go, I'm going to do it all the time.
Was this Miko-senpai's dick?
I'm sorry for saying that I didn't have Chikicha of Miko-senpai because I thought I did it Nenachita ah-ho
Senpai and Senpai are going to get some ice.It's kind of
shiny, isn't it?That
Tsuruha is so shiny and silky.
Okay, so there you have it, Pipi, but you have a diamond in your hand,
so it's true that you can make what you have now.
But I only have the nose that I didn't have, but I
'm going to go there. It's amazing. I'm here. I'm
coming.
Wait a minute, let's work too.
Hey, what should I do? It looks
like something.  A
certain Rami is here. Who is this? What is this
horror? My Utara house is here. I'm going to go there. It
's very suspicious.
But it's a house of love, isn't it
?  No matter
what happens, if the inn is bad, the magma bucket will burn. Don't put it in here. I made a kitchen. You're a puppet. You said you earned your money by doing it. I love this interaction. I don't know what to do. I can't sleep.
What's this? This is this. This is this.  Yay,
trap,
no, this is this place. It's
amazing, so I can only go here.
Ah, I can't even enter here. In this case.  I
love you. If you do this, Ha-chan
will come too. I won't
wait, but are you fooling me? I'll
show you off. I'll eat, sleep, and live happily ever after. It's
good. I'm not going to destroy this.  Do
n't break it! Don't break it! But I've got it.
This cat, this cat, this thing looks like a door.
Hey, where is that? I
can't die here, and I can't come back.  I
won't waste it, but what should I do if I don't give it to
you? Why don't I give it to you? I don't have any
diamonds, no, no, I don't have any, but I'll
open 10 diamonds from here. It
's not worth it. It's not worth it.
5 diamonds.  5, 5, 5, 5 Ah, no, no, it
's not worth it. Is it something that has no value? Is it
okay to call it something? After all, it's not just the shape. Well,
what can you give me in return? Senpai.
Haa-chan must be feeling kind of sick. She's like Chi-chi. Do
n't get irritated if you don't feel like that. Damn, that's
20 diamonds. It
can't be helped, 20. The baby's
gone, so it's 20.  I'll give it back, then
I'll give it back. It's raining, so I'll give it
back. It's
raining. Ruchi died here
.
Taa Biné died. There must be something like lava.  Is
this town evolving? Is this
town here?
There's a response point at the response point in the back.
Follow me, Hacha ni Kinaa-
chan,
Babauaaaaaaaaaaaaaa  Are you bubbling with Makoto?
Or Bubbabu Acha is bubbling just because she's a baby. She
got licked. It's
jippurupurupu. This is the mission.
Mia, there's also something like a gate.
Hello Grosso, what do you think?
But there are some things I don't understand. It's
okay. I just redeemed it, so I don't
know if I didn't take it myself. It seems like I have to take it once. I
want it, right?
Wait, I'm going to write this, I'm going to
take a book, I'm
going to write this one, I'm going to take a book. No, I'm going to take a book, but I
don't know what it is, so I have to get this one.  If I don't
take the diary, I
forgot where I left it.It's
not there.The diary rulebook.What happened to
Subaru-senpai's
death?Blast blastWhat was the lava resurrection?None of the blastWhat was it?Subaru-senpai Did something disappear?What happened?
Unfortunately, he didn't come back. Since he's a hard core, it's normal for him not to come back.
But he came back alive, Botan-senpai.
What happened to Subaru-senpai?
Well, a lot of things happened yesterday,
I died, and I died today. I died twice today. There's no way I
can revive this.
There's nothing I can do about it. I can't
revive it. I see, I'm still alive, so
yeah.  Well,
Kirito-san and Anna-san got along really well.
That's right, he should still be alive, but he's dead.
He's there, so I'm going to start working now.
That's wonderful. At first, I was
given so many blessings. Where is that thing?  Niniki
Niki, is it
okay for Niki to give me a diamond
?
By the way, you should
stop being Noel-senpai. You
should stop being Noel-senpai.  Is it possible that
the mission
got lost this time? Yes, it's
true that 20 bigaris were written. Oh, nice. I didn't
get that. It's terrible.  I think it's
about time for Ran to be in the loca-smokin' lower house.I
think I'll be doing it since 5 o'clock.Thank
you very much, thank you for your hard work.I'm so surprised
by the mission.I'm going to
go pick it up at Leather.  I was so
shocked and surprised
that I thought it was a bug, but I
went to
work with someone who didn't know anything about it.Jano-
chan, yes, this is what I did at Mission Co.
This name is on the same level, please stop here.
Achanka is more knowledgeable, so it's more detailed. Is it
true? I wonder if it's okay whichever one dies first.
This is a bad bed. I
have a bed that's sleeping. I'm sleeping.  I do
n't have it in the west, I don't have it in the west.
It's over here. There's
so much water, so much traffic.
The traffic is so heavy. It's like a typhoon.  It
was so outrageous. Just now someone or two people
slept together, but this is a bet, this is a bet. They're
good friends. People will think that I'm good friends with Kinne.
Wait a minute, that's not true. Wait a minute,
that's a big deal.  I wonder if it's okay. It's raining. So
bet. A bet. There's a huff over there. I
was nervous, but it's wrong. It
seems like something went wrong with the distribution settings, but I wonder
where this cat is.  It's
not chan, it's not chan, it's
okay to lower chan in the comments.I see, I'm going
to do something like Gudosu next.Tara and I need it.  I'm
sorry that I got it and went in. I
have a production machine, but I'm
sorry to kill you, but I don't need it or something.
Well, it looks like it's going to happen right now. I'm going to
get a twisted mushroom.  They
don't want to throw something delicious at each other, so the two of them go out to get the frog eggs with someone they've never been with before. That love
event is like a frog egg.
It's hard for people who have never been involved in an action game.
What about people who have never been involved?AaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaAaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaA,
Where are the frog eggs?  I'm
trying to cheat. It's
mostly from the Nether. I
forgot about the Sole Sand Glow collaboration.
Well, let's go
get a lot of those stones. How about
this? This is a book.  Let's take a page and then write it down. Let's do this. We'll
take one here and there, so we'll look at what we've done a little bit on the
page. We'll all take it as we go. We'll
turn the page on the bottom right, and then we'll open it.
The name Gusto looks like I'm
going to make a big potion with the same words as me. I'll
defeat 3 skeletons. I'll use the keyboard to say "Wow" and when I'm
done, I'll write something on the bottom right. That
's difficult. I don't know the name, but this is the only thing I can do. I'll
defeat 3 skeletons.  I feel like I can do something,
but I don't know what to do.In times like this,
press the button.I figured out that you should just ask your senior.That's
right, where is it? Button, my
senior, yes, I want that diamond equipment.
Well, I only have a little bit left.
Should I call it? Daya, I only
have about 20. I'm
going to stop. Where can I make money?  Chiro It
seems like Chiro doesn't do it. Also,
something happened. I don't know the rules,
but I don't know. It's
like gambling.
Even now, I don't know if Chinchiro would do it if Peko-chan was there.
Well, that's enough.Speaking
of cheap, it's cheaper to go diving.I
don't know if it's better to go to someone who hasn't had any trouble,
but I know how much it's better to do.I
guess I'll write the reward here.  It's a nether  It
seems that if you go to the Nether, there will definitely be a reward.There is a need for the Nether.However, in the middle of nothing, here and
there, I wrote another one.I want to dig together.  Spreading false information,
there are people out there, there are
people out there, it's like there's no one lying, it's normal, there's no one
there.I don't know why, I don't know why.  I can
write the characters I want.
Wait a minute. I'm sorry. I'm currently
processing. I'm sorry. I did this. I don't remember that voice very well. I have
n't heard that
voice
in a while. I've been doing it since today, or just on the first day. I
see. That's what happened.  I
thought I'd get some diamond equipment if I played it every day, but
somehow I
ended up taking that board.I do
n't remember what it was.
In Soul Sand, I
want to
try and figure out who that de is, and try to help him by clinging to someone who seems to be strong. I wonder if there's a diamond somewhere. I wonder where he is. I'll try to find Punch. For now.
Meguri Tsutsue This cute
house This house This
cute pink house I'll
open someone's chest as soon as I get home
Cute cherry blossoms I
'll open someone's chest soon  It's
not good, I'm trying not to open it, but the manager is
looking for it, so I'm in a place where I can see the first mission.
Okay, now I'm here, Pekola.
This is a travelogue full of senior diamonds. I wonder if this is
what it is. Hello, I'm chatting with you. I'm speechless. I
can't say anything. It's here, Coro-senpai page.  The
number keeps increasing and I can't say anything.
Mission number 1. Hey there,
that's what I mean. Thank you for your hard work. Today,
however, it looks like you've
got a lot of diamonds. Senpai, it looks like you've got a lot of diamonds. Oh,
yeah, I think you've got a lot of diamonds.  Oh,
give me
something. Oh, give me something. I
want more. I want more. It's weird. Ah, I
want more food. I want more.
Isn't there something good about it?
Thank you, Pecola, kind and gentle senior. Ah, the
door has been changed.
Isn't there something else that looks a little better? Look, the
Great War. Where are we going to use this
? Rua, there's another one stuck
in the cobblestone.  Thank you very much for the stairs. Do
n't you think the stairs are a little better? Isn't
this
wooden thing being
used as a garbage can? Is
that a silent nod? Is it because my
friends are leading me there?  I told you to follow
this and that, but I was silent, and I was
gradually giving up the bait.
Please stop, I'm going to kill you. I
picked this up. There's
nothing I can do about it
. Oh, I'm
so surprised. I don't even know if it falls.  I was
so surprised, so surprised. I
don't even know where this place is. He asked me to
follow him gently. He said to me, "You're about to die," and said
silently, "I'm
drowning in death." He came.  That
Pecola who definitely gave me something like that.
When I'm feeding something to my dick, I
'm feeding you that this world is not sweet. Oh, I'm telling
you to self-destruct. Oh,
that's what the manager sucked. [ __ ] that [ __ ].  Chief Bachi
was given gunpowder. He was given dangerous powder.
After all, he was being baited into it by various people,
causing crimes against various people.
If you have something that looks good,
this is probably the one, right? It's so
bad, it's so different, I wonder what the eyes of the cloud are. I
have a string of threads, but I feel like I'm clinging to it. I
want a diamond.  Equipment I
'll let you want it, but I'll get diamond equipment,
so I'll get a lot of hands, and I can
exchange it for power emeralds and exchange this equipment with villagers
properly.It's like an iron factory.  It's like he's
low on iron because he's taking everyone with him.
He's already made some for me. That's
right, what the heck is Loki?
Oh, what the heck, how many
beds do you have? Don't you have a bed?  Hey,
Loki, what do you mean Pecola-senpai was attacked by that [ __ ]?
But I should have just gone to bed. Loki, it's too bad. I should have
been working already. Oh,
today was my last day, so
everything ended up being work-related.
What should I do, I have to cross over there and go to the village.
Wait, wait. What's
that? It looks like Bancho Be. What's that? Pecola. At the beginning
of the first Be, I drew the girl,
Yokecha-chan.
What do you have, Ammolite?  I'm
like, Loki, are you okay? This is Loki, Pecola.
All I can hear is, ``Is the delivery date okay for my senior?'' Good morning, good morning. I'm
in bed. I'm
sleeping peacefully, and La isn't even there.
I like it, I'm in bed, I
'm in bed, Ika-chan, I want her body as well
as I'm so tired of her. Yo, Fuwa-chan, I feel like she's going to give me something.
[Music] I have
a feeling that the flower was great.
Wait for the boss. Isn't this flower's name cute?
Magic at all.  It's not cute, thank you. I'll move around and
pick it up. Why, why, why ca
n't I pick it up? I can't pick it up. I can't pick it up. The
enchantment was discovered, it's not there, it's not there. I did
penetration 1, so I did it.  The
stone block is already Nemopan, so I
can't pick it up.What's that?I'm picking it up all the time.No, the glue is steamed, round, and the penetration 1
is garbage.Nanoe trash, I got trash.Now we're being
used as a trash can, senpai. Karae
trash can.  This
[Music]
No matter how many times I go through it, there's nothing. It's important, I don't have anything to say. I wanted to
do a mission or something,
but I don't have any equipment, so
wait a minute, I'm going to go do some min.
If that's the case, what's the point? If you're going to go on a mission now, I'll
give you my equipment. I'm
thinking I'm about to give up, so
just give me the long one. Of course,
leave it on.  Alone, I'll
do my best. I'll do my best. I'm sorry if I die. I don't know if I'm going to die, but I'm sorry if I die. But if I didn't have this, I'd be a little confused. I can't go to the Nether.
That's how I win. Hey, I
picked up something.  The one I
got from Pecola-senpai,
by the way, it's
gone on the first day.
All I have is those boots that came here.
And the boots are the only thing I got from the poke box.
Something was wrong with me at the beginning. I need to get
these.  I smoked things I didn't need,
and I got some things I didn't need.Thank
you for the things Pecola-senpai gave me.Bancho, I'll
definitely come back.Of course,
leave it to me.I have a diary.It's the first time I have one.  All I
have is a diary and a rulebook. I
can't write without the help diary. What's the point? Is
there a locker somewhere in the diary that isn't in my locker?
Punch Pancho
Punch Punch Punch Punch It's here. It's there, it's there, it's there, it
's there.  Chacha,
chachatane Apiko-senpai chimachigomeakakechimachi
If we're going to dig for diamonds, let's go out without saying a word.  I
thought so, but even if I dig, if I'm
going to do a mission, I
want to do a mission, and I want to dig diamonds. I
can't go to the Nether alone, even if I'm alone. I wonder if anyone is going to go to the Nether?
Wait, you're going to Neji,
but the only one from Mission Neza is
actually Neji. Wait, Neji.
Hey, it's really
scary, scary, scary,
stop. It's inside, so please be quiet. That's right.  I'll
definitely put it on and come home. Of
course it's been a while. Of course
. It's inside, so I'm going to lie down. Well, I'm going to
go home and sleep in my diary. I'm
addicted to it, so thank you very much. I'll definitely
return it.
Absolutely, of course, of course, of course, of course, of course, of course, of course, of course, of course, of course, of course, of course, of course, of course, of course,
thank you, Bancho Nasu, Bancho, I'm cool today, I'm really cool, I'm smiling for a long time, I'm smiling, I'm happy, I'll praise you.  I
thought to myself, ``I don't think it's good,'' so I
went home.Of course, of course, of course, of course, of course, of course, of course, a kind leader is really kind.This is the kind of place where you want to respect the leader.Where should I go to the Nether?  I
received a diamond equipment from the Banchou.Thank
you,
Banchou.Thank you for the danger.I'll
definitely give it back to you.Good, good.It's
not a good start, but I fell in a place like this.
Wait a minute, I want to leave the body diamonds and everything
before I go.No
one will steal them.Let's
put the diamonds and a little bit here as well.I do
n't need the nether auto block.I got this just in case, so I'll
leave it there.Or I'll
get it from Pecola-senpai.  Ta-Yako:
Just in
case, I
caught a glimpse of Pecola-senpai and
was sweating,
but I'll leave the rulebook behind for now.  Let's
leave the iron door behind
for a moment and see if anyone else is there. I think I'll go on a little trip with Namakon. I
heard a voice saying that I want to go to the Nether and do a mission. Apparently, I'm writing a diary in this stay.
So, I guess that's the end. I
want to go. I wonder if
this is someone's power.
Defeat the Gust and
complete the mission. Once you complete the mission, you can use the diamonds to get your own equipment.
I made this and returned that equipment to the Chief. Is
n't that the
perfect plan? I thought that my body wouldn't be returned. The
mission was a success, and I'll
definitely return it and show it to
you. I got it from Aluka-senpai.  I
want to go to the Nether, do you have someone to do missions with me?
Kamiko is going with her friends
[Music]
Senpai, I want to go, I want to go, I
want to go. Where should I go?
[Music]
Kabuto-chan is here.
Otan-chan is here. This is a different exchange.
Kana-tan is here.
Hey, Miku-senpai.  It's better
if you don't get anxious. You
can trust me. You're a great senior.
Where should I go? I'm heading to Ka's house right now. You might
have to wait a little longer. I
understand.  What is
Kaela-senpai
's house?
Where is Kaera-senpai's house? Where is Mikomiko-senpai's elite? That's right,
she's an elite. I
guess she can do it. Oh, I'm
in the middle of the day, so I'm
probably going to sleep.  When I was sleeping, my senpai came looking for me.
Maybe Kara-senpai is good at Minecraft. I
don't know who is talking to whom. I don't know. I don't know anymore.
God, God, God, isn't Pecola-senpai? He's the
best out of all of them, and Pecola-senpai
, and Kara-senpai are the
best. It
seems like they're better together, right? There are good and bad
skills in Minecraft.
[Music] Huh,
huh, that's right. The
god of this world is Pecola-senpai.
But what does that mean that he's already as good as a god in Minecraft
? I don't sleep at all, everyone. Should I
stop sleeping now?
Now go back to my senpai's house.
There's someone who knows somewhere. My stomach is like magma. I
can't sleep. I
don't know much about it right now. I'm sorry, but I don't have much knowledge, so I fell asleep. I'll
go and pick him up.
Hey, thank you very much.  Where
should we go?
Thank you, Amiko. Senpai.
So,
would you like to meet up with Rocka first
? I don't know anything else.  I wonder
if the baby reeds will come too? Meow,
the sea has been caught. It's okay to
sleep. It's okay to sleep in the mud. Somebody's sleeping. Their bodies have already moved, so
leave it to them.
[Music]
Oh, there's more of them.
What, they're still here.They're both still there.Sadness, sadness,
sadness.Ah, I'm
really looking forward to it.Diary
[laughing]
How many pages have the 10 people written?
Ah, there are zombies, there are zombies, oh, stop it!
Stop it, stop it, stop
it, stop it, Minecraft, I'm not good at it. I was surprised. I was surprised. I was surprised. I see. Oh, you
came to help me. Oh yeah, I
can't abandon you.
Thank you for being so kind. Wow. I
can't make any progress with my brush.  I was
surprised. I'm making a work.
Yes, that's right. Please make a countermeasure appear.
How many pages will it take for it to appear? There are
still a few pages left. It's still early days.
Nanadebeto, maybe I have one. I do
n't care. I have money.
Oh, I don't want it, baby. Oh, it's not
good at all. I
want to appear in Aki-senpai's novel, so I'm just going to rip it off
and run away.
[Laughs] I'll see
if you can write about it later. I'll make up some content. I'm
sorry, but I'm going to return it tomorrow.
Please, your nickname is Bed Toro. It's
not bad. Let me steal your bed. It
smells nice, but I'll chop it up.  I'll
do it. Thank you for your name. It's funny.
Miko-senpai is a good girl. I wonder if the Bancho has yet to write it down. The
residents are nyan-nyan-nya-nya. I'm
writing down the 10 people who were alive.
[Music]
I guess it's in the main house  It won't come true, residents.
Please wait here and let the baby bubble. Please give me some
rice. I can't help but eat some food. Well then, I
'll give you the food that Pakora-senpai gave me.
This is amazing. As expected, this is definitely not food. I was
given it. I can make it with this. It's a bit
small, but yeah, I
think it's better to just tell Pecola-senpai that way. No, no,
Pecolo-chan
said, ``Give me this rice.''  I didn't give you this. I'm
sorry to keep you waiting. Thank you very much. I do
n't have it at all. See you again.  I
can't help it, Ninochama-chan. I'll
give you the rotten meat too. I
didn't have a body, rotten meat. I
left my luggage in Karoka. I got some money and meat,
but it's
rotten. Meat is rotten.  That's 64 pieces of rotten meat. That's a lot.
[Laughs]
Well, then you should become me. I
guess you didn't even have a single piece of bread in your body. I don't understand why.  Leave it
as it is. That's the
emo-looking diary I was writing earlier.
Let's go here. Let's go
here. I've completed Rap 2. It looks
like a kindergarten.
There are a lot of
villagers here. It's good to equip the villagers Mikoyo.  I
waited a while and borrowed it from the manager.
That's right, I borrowed it from the manager. He
told me to never die.  I
heard you're going to die with the Bancho's equipment on. I'm
sorry, I'm sorry if you're a baby.
What's that?
Yeah, I'm almost running out of durability.
But don't
worry, it's money.
Zomiko-senpai, please make sure you don't find out.
Wish,
Masumi isn't going to die, so I guess that
means I'm protecting her. I see that she's protecting her, isn't it?
Good job, good job, good job. It
's been quite a while since my senpai came in.
Well, according to the theory, Mikan and Mika are three
hours old and three
hours old, but it looks like it's less than my body.
But I have diamond equipment. I'm in
debt from someone who didn't want me, but yeah, I'm
already in debt.
But that person is already dead, so
Drasbar.
But I heard through rumors that I made it from Sumaru's diamond.
[Laughs] That's
crazy. I'm back in Mario's world. I wonder if he's
doing well.
Hello, I'm back. There's a lot of people
here. Hello, halohahahaha
[Music] I'm
not the god of Naimacra.
Please take care of me. Thank you very much.
Ma,
mama-
chan, that's
good. Maaa,
mabeaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa.  I love you like a grandchild, Nemikomoyo,
Mikononononomiko, Mikokokohaha, I
've exchanged hello, I'm
full of diamond equipment
[Music]
Now that I think about it, I don't have this shield. I
can make it without running a shield. I don't have iron. It
seems like iron can be obtained with something like a steel movable machine. I see, I have to
fly from here to here.
Free Free Iron Miko Free  I can defeat the iron myself
Hey, Tete Freete, let's make it before the money comes out
No, no, no, where, where, where, where, where, where, where,
this is not the free iron,
that's not it, just punish him.
No, let's go. I'm
dead
because I don't have a shield because I don't have a shield. No shield. I don't have a shield.
There's a place where I can get it, so I'll stop by and go home.
Okay, I'm sure someone is going to die.
Stop this Frank for a minute.  I'm sure I'm going
to die, I'm definitely going to die. I have to give it back to the chief. I
can't die while saying things like that in these clothes.
But I'm going to get beaten up.
Wait a minute. It's good that you have darkness.
[Applause]
[Music] I
don't have much money or equipment,
but I can't run, so I eat, wait,
wait,
and I can't leave it behind. I wonder if I'll
live. If I
don't die, I'll live with my nose.
Try my best.  Let's live, it's
cute, it's delicious
, it's delicious, it's here, it's here, it's here, can I go
home? I
don't remember the way at all
,
mama,
mama, if I fall here, I'll definitely
die If I fall, I'll die  All you
have to do is follow
Miko-senpai. I can only see Nemiko-senpai.
Oh, that's where I
met Miko-senpai.
Tako-senpai-senpai.
Miko-
senpai has come. Go back, Miko-senpai. Go Beck.
Wrong direction. In the
other direction. Miko. I
believed in my senior village and followed her.  Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work on the iron trap.
Unit 2 has been completed. Well, this is it for now.  I have a
favor to ask of you.Will you please
lend me this shield?It's a shield.I
want you to
give it to me.Rather than go and get the one that was at Free's place, I
guess I should ask for it.  But this thing is so worn out, I'm
sorry, but I might have brought it with me. The president was going to bring it, so I changed my clothes. President, I changed my clothes. I didn't change my clothes. Thank you for bringing me back to life. I didn't do anything.
President.
What are the 80 diamonds? Yeah, he hasn't come back.
That's what he promised. Is that what he
promised? I can take his diamonds.
It's 6 of them, but I haven't taken them yet. Whether I
take them or not, I'll do it for now.  80 of them.
Why?
If you don't mind, where should I go? Baby, don't do this. Don't do this.
Okay? Stand up.
This is terrible. Thank you.
Kindness. Go to sleep.  That's right,
Licca-chan.
What, what, what, what? What's wrong
with that? That's it. It's the one that appears when you don't sleep. I wasn't sleeping at all. I just wanted to say thank you to my little senpai. Is that
okay, baby?  I was doing that, but I feel
like I can't see you. I was digging a little downstairs.
Thank you so much
for everything. It's incredible. I'm glad it came back
to life. I borrowed that ingo.
Thank you very much. I was able to get the shield. I
lost it by myself when I started, but I
should have gotten this for the baby too.
Isn't it good for the baby? Who is the baby
? Ah, I'm sure I got the shield as well.  I didn't have it, so I
took out the button. Give me another one. Please
take the shield from over there and wait a minute.
Thank goodness I need a shield.
Ya vertical thief vertical
thief. There's one in here. Anyway, this is it.  I'm sorry,
but please
forgive me. I'm sorry. Thank you very much.
Yu-senpai, I'll
definitely return this to you. I'll
be waiting for you. Thank you very much. Do
your best. I need your help.
Thank you for being so kind. You're so
kind. This world is so kind. I'm Annie.
Senpai, Kira-senpai, and I'm angry.
Somehow, we got separated. Yeah, I'm back. A-chan is
n't here, baby. Why?  I got a
shield for the baby's shield. I
brought the baby's worth, but it
seems that the two hands that can be used as both hands were brought for her.
So, survive with two hands. It
's not all about defense.  So, I
can't do the mission with this. Well, that's right. If someone ca
n't stand it anymore, I'll give it to
them. I'm sure it won't stand up, but I wonder if it'll ever run out. I'm sure it could run out and run
out. Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's
fine.
Sister, I'm
looking forward to it, sister, sister, of course I'm going to eat my life, I'm looking forward to it, okay, let's go, this is
it, she, she, you just got
back, oh, I got that phone to go home.  I'm going to
go to a fortress like that. This is the only fortress that
hasn't been found yet, so I don't think it'll be easy. Maybe I
should have a lot of premonition earth blocks. I
don't have any, but it's hard to play.  I
want an earth block that doesn't have a stone to go up with the stone,
but I think I already understand the earth block By the way, I understand that you're going to bring a bed with you.You
can just leave it here.The
bed.  The
bed is so hot. The bed is so hot. I
left the color
here. It's not like this, Sumiko.  It
looks good when you say it, that's amazing, that's the
last thing I want to do I
want to write about today's story I'm sorry for the money,
but I died Do
n't do it, it's really no good Today is not today or anything, I don't want you to die Hard
Core  Wow,
is this the first time I'm feeling sick? Wow, no, but they don't attack me.
Yeah, you should never attack those pigs. If you
do that, they'll attack you all at once.  It
's so weird. Be careful. Yeah, it's gold. It's not gold. It's gold, but it's like quartz. It's like a white block. I gathered it up. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's expensive. It's gold.
[Music]
Why is everyone selling gold? It's not gold. It's gold. It's so
fast. It's so
fast. Thomas Magma. It's too early. It's too early. No, no, no, no, no, no.
Nice, going next door is amazing. Next door next door neighbor
Sui-hai died.
What do you mean?
Chanesai-chan senior Miko-onee-
san, what do you think?
[Music]
Wahashi Tera Stellar Stella  Now,
Stella
[Music]
Stella, will I become a star when I die? Yeah, I'll come back, right
? Maybe, I'll
be back. Thank you for your hard work.
There's a huge person in front of me.
[Music] He
ran away
quickly,
ran away, and left a stone behind. I'm
glad you came. I'm in
danger, senior, please bring me some alcohol.
Okay, come on, I've got zero energy left. I
'm dead.  More than ever, I'm going to die one more time.I'm
leaving behind.Go ahead.Go ahead.I'm
scared and don't know what's going on.My heart is
strong, my baby.Go first.It's
okay.I'll light the way.
Even in the middle of the day, we are dealing with magma and
doing it properly, but you can't dig this thing, it's
like gold, it's okay to leave it alone,
but when there are pigs, they will be seen as the enemy of digging, so
when there are pigs,  No, it looks like it's okay now.
It's a learning experience. Gold.
Gold. Wait for the gold to turn into a flag, so stop.
Flags, flags, etc. I'm
trying something like that. It's so crowded that
one person starts a fire.
If I do, everyone will
catch fire, or something like that, so I'll try to survive on my own, but on the
other hand, I'll feel bad about it.If
I die, I'll die, and I'll have a broken head.It's
okay.When the game comes out,
I hear a sound.
I have a gust, and it's almost
time to kill one.  You
can defeat him by hitting him back,
but it's quite
difficult.If it's difficult, then maybe it's better to stop.Ghast It's
better to play Gust with a bow.I
see.What are you
talking about now?What are you
teaching about Gust?
You're so jealous that you're going to fight.
What happened?
What happened? You said it was mine, but you're the
fastest running away. You guys are slow, so it
can't be helped, right? How far are you running away?
Senpai, I was so scared. I've been
waiting for Senpai,
but he's already gone. Hey, everyone's dead. I'm
not dead. There's no need to be so scared.
Makuto
was the most scared, but there
's magma laying around. The magma is
gone, and it's useful.  chan is whispering to me. I feel
like I'm going to die from being pushed. I'm
scared. It's true that I'm going to be pushed.
Strider was referring to Fuji. I'm
Nero and I don't have any blocks, so I guess I can
calm down now.
[Music]
If it falls, I'm in danger. Do I take the blocks around here? Is
n't that guy going to attack me? It's dangerous
. He might come if I attack him. Basically, I either
wait or he doesn't attack me. The water
evaporates and I can't use it.  That's not true.
Yeah, that's right. You can't erase lava either.
Because you have to squat on your legs. You have to bend. Is
n't that right? You have to fall down or open up.
But I don't think I'll be able to find anything,
but there's a path over there.
Stop it, I'll do it in one shot. Wait, that
's terrible. It's amazing. It's so easy to kill me in one hit.
Oh, nice,
nice, nice, nice, what's this?
There's a lot of people who are putting out fires.
[Music]
It's okay.
[Music] There's a guy over there attacking me. [Music] It
suddenly attacks me.  I don't think so,
but since I'm looking at it, it's that kind of person.  It's
better to go in
another direction, right? Is this what you were aiming for? It's true that I went somewhere else.
This white thing that I've seen before seems to be buzzing.
Someone's doing it.
[Music]
Someone's doing it already.  It's like this. It's
okay to take the white one, but maybe. No, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, I've
taken it yet, so I'm sorry. No, my
body has taken it, so run away. I don't know.
No, let's kill it. Looks like it's okay. Where's the gust? It
's firing. Wow, the gust has
already done it. I haven't done it
yet. I don't think I'll take this. I can't take that. I
can't do anything but look good, Ka-chan.  That's right, I
just need to build a pretty house. I'm
done with hardcore, but it's fine. The one who was
around here was doing it just a while ago. I
wonder if it's scary.
There's Yonai. What is this thing doing
? It
's around here. It's doing scary things.
It's a pig pig. It's a little nearby, so it
's in there. It's over there. It's because I took it. It's
not good at all, it's not worth the money.  Oh, you
took it, that's scary, nice  The crows
are so scary. What do you mean? Why
did they want to kiss me
? That
can't be true. That person from earlier, that
person, is digging. I can
hear a lot of cries.
[Music]
Isn't that the
way I'm going? Oh, I'm going white.
[Music]
Hmm, are you going here? I'll go ahead
of you. I wonder how straight this way is. I
wonder if this is how I came.  For
example, I feel like I can go home,
but there's something shining there, but there's also a road in the opposite direction.What
should I do?Here, let's
go straight.Let's go straight.Someone
made it, and it's safe.  If I
go that way, I'll probably go back.Thank
goodness I have medicine.I don't know how to go back.If I could
go back alone, I'd probably go back.  I
wonder if I can go back alone. Is it okay if I take this? I heard that if I take this glow stone, I'll get 2 diamonds. I heard it's the one I want to take. I can't get it. If I don't use the touch of the one I took, it will break. That's right.  Dad, I do
n't know anything about that. I wish I could have taken something that I didn't know about.
It took a while, but that's not possible. I do
n't have it, so it's impossible. Well,
even if I get something that someone else took, it's not possible.
Is that no good? Yeah, that's no good. It
said, "I'll get it." I think it said, "I'll get it." Wow, I
can see everyone's names. Is this one from here?
Come on. Gather 4 of them.  It seems like it's okay,
isn't it? I think it's going
back. It's going back. I see. So let's move on to the next one.
Dangerous, oh my, yes, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous,
dangerous,
dangerous.
What, what, what happened just now? I
thought for sure I was going to
die. Is it because I thought for sure that Gumakacha would die like that
? I don't know. Well, I didn't know either,
so I was provoking it, but I thought so.  I was
laughing at the fact that I didn't know about it. I
think I'm going to go back here in the Nether, but I think we
should start over from the middle of that road we just took and go straight
to that long bridge.  I think it's good I think it's totally good  My
beginner friend disappeared, and
my paba-chan
fell into the magma at the entrance and died.If he
didn't, I guess he wouldn't know about it.Isn't that true?
There are times when you fall into the magma and die.
No,
there's something, there's something, there's something,
there's a magma cube
. Someone should do it for me, please.
Thank you. I just need to get four of these.
Oh, I see. The glow stones haven't left yet.
That's right. If I collect 12 Dursts, I
think I'll have enough. I think I only need one
Glowstone. Is that the case with Glowstone? I
think I only need one Glowstone.
Thank you, that's enough.
Yes, I took a lot of potatoes. If I was alone, I would
have done it. It
seemed dangerous,
but the fact that the bridge was half-open was a
great way to ease my fear.
Yeah, why is it all so jisco jisco manin? No, I'm
going back a little bit and that road is a little vague. I see, it's
okay, it's dangerous. I'm
sorry, I'm sorry, but the money dies next time. It
's boring. Let's
expose everyone here.
[  [Music] I do
n't have much time left,
so I'll let my juniors go in front of me.
Wait, but the backs will come too. It's
pretty dangerous, so I guess it's better to stay in the middle.
Thank you, oh thank you, as
expected of you, Koyori, I was a senior.
Yoka-chan, this
is hell. Even in
hell, there's only one flower blooming. Is
n't it okay to stand there? That
's not it.
[Music]
Solo mackerel, 1 to 7 diamonds, Dragon
Ball, this world, Dragon Ball.  It's
like, Dragon Ball is serious, and it
's a solo. Dora without solo friends.
[Music]
Wow, it looks like he's never seen Dragon Ball or
Severe
Ball. Is
that okay?
If you put it there, it seems like it'll be good to go in. So, do it in a spacious place, do it in a spacious place,
dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, shift shift Okay,
open the
oven. Let's make one flower bloom. It's okay. Do it
in a spacious place.
[Laughs]
What about this place? It's not showing up. Hey, there's a lot of
popo blooming. Be careful. You
can do it facing backwards. It's shifted, so I guess it's
okay.
This is cute. This shiny thing
is stylish.  This is the first time I've
seen an Indiana Jones movie.I've never seen an Indiana Jones movie
before.  I
wonder if I'll
take a look at it, starting today.I was doing it on the first day, but I was there on the first day, and I
was on the first day, and people were asking me all kinds of things,
but I didn't collect many things on the first day, so I did
n't understand anything on the first day, even if I watched it.  It looks
completely different,
so let's take a look at the diamonds. It's
amazing. I haven't seen it, but I'm not saying it's too big. There are
about 6 diamonds, so it's amazing.  It's
okay if you don't run
away. It's okay. It's okay. I'm the most scared. I don't want to die. I don't want to die. I don't want to die. It's okay. I'm going to die and Ah-senpai is coming so I
feel even more scared.
So what's the point?  What do you
mean? It's okay. It's
okay.
[Music] It's
so cool. I'm used to it. I
'm used to it. I'm
bored. I'm scared. What's up? I'm bored.  I'm
in the back row, but if I do it myself, I'm sure I
'll die from the magma. I'm
sure I'm good at the front line. That's
right, Kara-chan is taking care of it.
Ah, that's what it means.  It's
okay to be a senior who is said to be gamed, so it
's okay. The comment section is more jealous of my seniors.  I've
been told that I'm a surprisingly good listener, but don't
get involved with someone more senior than me. I don't
want to be scolded, I'm a kid, right? I
don't want to be called a red monologue.
Ah, I learned professional wrestling. I should act
like Neme Master.  I'm sure you're thinking something like
that. It's
easy for people to say things like that. It's easy to say things
like "Bawa"
is ignored. There's a person who can no longer be treated as a partner. It hurts, it's a
lie.
This is my big senior
[Music] It's
scary because it's open. He's leading the way so I
don't fall. He's
running away from the fortress, running away. Hey, it's a bit
like this. It seems like magma tends to come out here as well,
right? I remember.  Let's go, I
remember, the best I remember It's been a long time since I played Minecraft
Uncle Maeternal Hub Eternal uncle
What do you mean Infinite or Infinite uncle
Naru uncle Amazing uncle Uncle
San uncle  It's
funny to want something. That's what it is, uncle. I was wondering what you meant. Yeah, I thought, "Why are you talking to me, uncle?" Place, uncle, uncle, that, Miko-senpai, you're cute today too. Hey,
that's not the case.
Hey everyone,
if you can find something called the Nether, you can get it by dividing the diamond pile,
so you're a cash kid. Seriously, how much is 30 pieces?  I'll
get 30, so I'll divide them up. Even if it's just for one person, there
might be only 5, but it's a ghost, a
chance, a chance, a chance, a chance,
a chance. I'm lining up like this. There are still
people who can get it. It's
okay. My
seniors are
still here, and I'm still here.  Mission
[Music]
I'm scared of the voice
[Laughter]
[Music]
Leave it to me,
Ray will do the damage, do
n't kick, don't fall, what, what, what, let's
sing!  I can't
defeat him, so I'm still here. It's true, it
's true. There
's a trace of what happened.
Nice,
nice,
clear.
As a senior, I feel like I do
n't need anything anymore. Magma falls from above.  There's
probably magma on top of it,
so it's definitely creeping out. It's
scary. It's the first time I've ever seen this. I
dug it with something like sand delta.
If so, can you give me a mission? Don't dig here.
There's a possibility that magma will fall from the side. Wow, I
understand that the best place to take it is on a flat
surface. Yeah, this is cool. Sad. This is scary when you look at it from above.
What is it? I
haven't done Kare-chan Gust yet. I haven't done Kare-chan Gust,
but I don't have a bow and I've
been here before. I've never
been to soul sand and bones like this.  But
Yeah, but I
thought it was the same area, not
here, so it's better. Here it is. What is it?
Which one is it in the bottom right? 4
[Music] I can't
see the bottom right there.
[Music]
No, it's true.  There's a
bridge. 4 That's it, that's it, that's
amazing. Thank you so much. It's amazing. But it's
such a low place. What should I do? How
should I go? My dream is to build it. How do I
do it? This is amazing.
Those are bones. Can't you wash away the bones?
Nasuho I brought water, but it
falls down and makes stairs.
If I aim wrong, I get
magma. Is it
dangerous? What I said earlier became reality.
110 pieces.  I said something like, Okay, I
want more. Is there a maximum of 30?
Yes, we'll all have 30.
What's going on
? There's something here. Kill me.
Give it to me and kill the gust, but I haven't killed it.Kill
it with a weak nose.I don't have it now, so I can't give it to you.It
would be scary if it explodes while I'm doing it.I guess I
should just lend it to you.Is it even possible to lend it to me
?  I think it's totally possible to lend it to me. It's
all right. Gust, I
don't know
where it is. It's
gross. It's impossible.
[Music]
Oh one nice, one wow,
delicious
Umakara-chan,
oh
my gosh, Umai Umai went to such a dangerous place.
Are you okay?
Goi oh my, I was so
surprised. It looks like you're dead. I can hear Ama's voice. Look here to see if you're in danger. Thank you very much.
Thank you, thank you very much
. Don't die, everyone.
[Laughs] There's nothing
left to do.
Death.
Alright, Cal-chan did it!
Thank you very much. Nice, nice. Thank you, Sky.
Ooh
Another
Brave Brave
Those eyes are the purpose. Ya
Pawn, please make a potion for Miko-chan.
Everyone should make it too.
There's a mission for Skeleton Skeleton Skeleton, so I killed it. I did it in TT.  I was
holding it down and fell.
Should I go to the skeleton? Are senior skeletons the
only ones in the Nether?33
There's something wrong with my body and chest, so I guess it's better
if I don't stay here anymore. Visa.
There's a skeleton.
Zaskir. He's here
because he looks strong. Let's catch him because he doesn't want to go home. I
want a potato. Is this going to go down? Yes, I want a potato.  There's
still a ghast down here.
[Music] There
's nothing here, so I
'm back here again.
Thank you for the stairs. Don't press the button. Do
n't fall. Stop,
stop.  Stop
it, I don't have an arrow. I don't have an arrow. I don't have an arrow. I don't have an arrow. I don't have an arrow. I don't have any arrows. I don't have any arrows. I don't have any arrows. I don't have any arrows. I don't have any arrows.
Thank you, thank you, nice.
Thank you for doing that.
Nice. Now the mission
has come. I was grateful.
[Music]
Wow, it's dangerous here
. If I get off here, thank
you very much. Masukori-senpai, Koyori-senpai.
Where are you, senpai? Wait
a minute, senpai, senpai, senpai, senpai, senpai, who can't make the stairs properly.
It's true, you're digging so much, senpai. You're getting in the way, senpai. Is this place dangerous? It's
okay now. It's okay again.
Gusto, I was able to defeat Gusto.  I'm glad I was able to defeat it.
Maybe it fell too much here and there.
Even though I was in trouble, I did a good job of digging, so I
won't come.
Good, I
want to explore a little bit, I
guess I'll die.
Wow, it's
scary and Blaze is scary, but I want it No,
I want a potato, so I have to get a potato.It's
like a potion.Is it there?I ca
n't get it.A sandwich came out.I wonder
if I'm digging too much.Let's take a look.I see, go ahead,
go ahead.
Also, it's amazing, I
'm scared of the
food, it's
annoying, I don't have it,
no, I
've got my hands on it,
okay, let's make a dangerous staircase, oh,
here it comes.  There's a
guy shooting at me, there's Zasu.
Hey, there's something here. I wonder
if there's
more. I
don't have any milk. Even if I fall, I've
only got one cup. I'm a
senior hero.
Ha,
Yuu, even though I came here like this, maybe many times, no matter how I did it, I got it, thank you very much.
Since it has 3 spikes, Nemisu seems to be able to give it to her friends, which is
true.It's
really reliable.It's a
head saw that she likes, but it's okay to
display it as a
mushroom.  The
mushroom that I need is green.
Hey, thank you very much. I do
n't mind if I take it, so I guess I'll go ahead and pick it up. I'm
following behind my senior at the
mushrooms. The mushroom I caught was the red mushroom. The mushroom was brown.  Inki
Masu Rays might be over there. There's no one here.
I understand.
Oh wow, wow, that's amazing. This is what Minecraft has to offer
. After all, it's a horror game. This game is
the Blaze.
Wow, this is money.  Is it okay to take it? I
don't know.
[Music]
Lala, it's okay to take it. Take everything and
run away. Do
n't do that.
So don't be like that, senpai,
you're freaking out. Don't be so scared, senpai.
Seriously, it can't be helped. It's okay. I'm going to get worried after this.
Senpai has
taken a lot of stuff.
[Music] Ta
hee, hee
.
[Music]
Hee.
Howl, what? I'll get Kiara-senpai to protect me.For
now, Kiara.Maybe I
don't need this.Is this also a mission?Never Woot's
Nether War Nether Woo
Mission  I wonder
if it's okay to take this?But I'll take
one.If I'm going to
make a Chao potion, I'll only need
one.I'll
take all of them.I
took a lot of legs, so I guess I'll
take them too.Hehehe, if you have any left, take it.It's
okay, Momo.  If I had it already,
I'd like a lot of it, oh, oh,
oh, I'll
leave it there.  I'm
not leaving it here, I'm leaving it behind and playing it.
What's this?
Uh, before I say yes, I'm scared, so stop it. There are people who are freaking out. Stop it, they're freaking out. Oh, I'm scared, so I told them to stop. They're freaking out, aren't they
?
What's wrong with being a normal person
? It's
okay, it's okay, it's
ok, I need it.
Wait, Senpai's here or on the road. It probably ended here.
Ah, get down, let's
jump, okay. Probably not
. Yes, I don't want to do that. It's true.
Thank you. That's nice. Where are the other seniors
? I wonder where they are. I saw
this building. There was a place like this.
That's so nice!
Oh
[Music]
Nanao
takes it for now. What's Tao's sound? Oh, Asami-senpai took Blaze.
Nice, nice.
Spire, but that's not really today's mission
. It's so true.
Ooooh
Charizard Yeah, I'm
ahead of the curve
and destroying things
[Music]
Oh my god,
something
[Music]
Cancer is dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous
Yaho, you defeated me, yay, I'm sorry.
Oh, scary, scary sister is also around there.  Oh
okay, I went looking for it. I see. I
have nether wart. I
have nether wart. I have
it.
Go go, I'm so scared I can't see anything Let's
follow our seniors Let's follow our seniors who look strong I wonder...
[Music]
Asteaste
Oh, I was surprised. What's wrong with the octopus? I can't get enough of it. What's going on
? I'm going to get separated right now, everyone. Maybe this way.  I
think it's over
there. I can hear a lot of voices. It
's
because they're digging that block. It's
okay.
It's
dangerous. I
understand.
[Music]
Miko, senpai, Miko, senpai, Miko, senpai, Miko, senpai, senpai,
senpai, Wow, a voice that sounds like Kaska, Miko, senpai, ah, I can hear you, Miko, senpai, senpai, Miko, senpai, that's cool.
Yaha, I almost
died in 3. Yo, it
was dangerous. I'm in
danger. Let's Go Raise is really
there. It's
scary.  There's nothing, it's a shame, it's a shame, it's
a shame, it's a mission, it's a mission, it's a potato, it's an endless
potato, it's an
endless potato.
Endless
Potatoes Where are the potatoes? I'm scared
[Music]
Should I just
keep up with them? It's there, it's there,
it's there, it's true
Oh, mug, waa, there's so many, so many, so many, so
many, so many, so
many, so many It's burning, it
's burning, it's okay  I see,
the spa is
dangerous.The magma cube is also dangerous.This cube
won't attack you.If you
knock the monster down, you can
dodge it.You almost
hit Akoru-chan's head.Eat it.
Yes, it's scary when you do zero distance.
There
are two. There are two. It's amazing. There are two
.
It's true. There are two potato spawners. Gusto. Oh, that's
amazing. What's a potato?  Well, that's the
enemy. It's the enemy called Blaze,
and the one that drops the burning thing. It's
called a potato because it looks like fries. I
wonder if that's what it's about. That dowel thing was over there.
Cheeks Thank you very much, thank you. I
wonder if you can't tell from the spawner here. Oh wow, what's that? Stop it, stop it, don't stop it, it
hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts. Don't die. You're in danger. Don't
die. I'm really pulling back. This is
so backwards.  I'm shooting from
Ok
, what should I do with this? It would
have been easier to rent it.
Shouldn't I block this place too?
It hurts, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, it hurts, it hurts.  I was so surprised, I didn't know
what was going on. I started
eating food, but I felt like I was going to fight. No, I'm seriously going
to die. I wonder
if I can't do it. Aya, it's
okay. Husband, I ca
n't do it.
[Music] I can't do
it. I'm scared, so I'm scared to stop. I'm scared, I'm
scared.  I can't get close to it, I can't get close to it. It's
like a octopus. Let's go from the last episode. Is this going to boil forever? I'm not going to get hungry. I don't want it. Wow, what
should I do?
[Music]  You're
brave too. Are you
okay? It's
okay. Is it
okay? It's better not to destroy it. It's okay. I don't think you should destroy the spawner.  I'll get angry
if I put a tie around me, but I go and it
hurts.Ah, I've
already got the items.I'll
do my
best.Ah, it's okay.It's okay.It's okay.It's okay.It's
okay.It's okay.
There's a lot of things going on. I can't go if my senpai dies.
Yes, it's dangerous. I'm
scared. It's stopped.
Magma
[Music]
Mushroom, it's over,
it's over, it's over, it's over. Cue,
thank you, thank you.
[Music]
Oh, even if you do that thing over there, pick it up.  I don't know
. The way I did it last time. I
picked up the hote.
The name of GO is the name of that enemy. I
really want darkness.
Nare
Yami
[Music]
Oh, what's wrong with this? It
hurts, it hurts, it hurts!
Someone needs to kill me.
Even here, it hits me.
Even if I hit it, I hit it.
[Music]
I'm bored  Oh, you're so nice.
Wow, that's right there.
Hey, nice. I
can't do anything.
[Music]
know,
BUknow
howi
help?
[Music] Oh, you're not
strong enough.
[Music]  I
just got it, thank you very much.
Nice, nice.
[Music]
Seriously, what are you doing? I didn't really understand this,
so I was watching it. I was like, ``Oh no, I ca
n't hit you, I can't hit you anymore, I can't hit you anymore.''
Yeah, yeah, it's sad to have to go back without killing,
but on the way home, I
'm going to clean up the road a bit, so everyone can come. Wait, I do
n't even know how to get here. Hey, but that's not it.
Where is it?If you go back to the burned road, you can
take him to that splendid bridge.Nice, it
won't be good.If you go there, you won't be able to find it.The
first coordinates are there.
[Music]
Make a note of that too.  That's right
. Show me your current coordinates. Does anyone know?
[Music]
Pick that up. That's what
everyone wanted. That's right. That's right. That's
right. It's
dangerous. [Music] [Laughter] It's dangerous.
Here
[Music] I
guess that's it. The senior diamond is Ah, what about the mission? It's not like the diamond is here.
Well, it's not, it's not, it's not. I see.
The boat is owned by Netherboat Haka-chan.
I have about 23 of them, that's amazing.
Please give me at least one. Yes, I'll grow one.
Yes, I'm sorry. I understand.
Thank you, and
I'll just get one. It's not safe to go home. It's too bad. I
can grow it somewhere else.
How many potions are
there? I wonder
if it's one for every potion. I
see, so I have to grow
them.  Ah, I
fell behind, but I thought I'd make it a little easier
. Ah, oh, I've already done it.
[Music] I
fell down, knocked down the oven, and
something was running. I'm going to
grow a lot.
Yes, even if I get a lot,
if I say I want one, will it be enough?
Yeah, cow, please give me some milk. Yes, yes, yes, yes. I
dropped it. It
was fine. The milk is like this. It's
dangerous. It's yoga. Let's go to yoga. Oh, please.  I
didn't need to be in danger, I don't know how to do this, I don't know what to do, so I
thought I should just create a new path.Oh, I see.Ah, if you
understand the first genius.  It
might be dangerous to go home. I
need to know how to get back there. I
wonder if there are more steps. I'll leave it to you. I'll
leave it to you. It's dangerous. It's dangerous. There
are so many shifts. It's
such a scary world.  It's spreading
, I'm safe. I'm safe. Let
's go home. Let's do this.
Let's go back to the place we promised.
Ah, I can see it there
. There's wax here.
No, wait a minute, don't open that part.
[Applause] I'm sure you're just here. I'm
sure there
are no more blocks left. Thank you.  I
think I can go home.
[Music] [Music] Ae [
Music] [Music] Ae [Music] [Music] Ae,
it's alright, it's alright, oh my god, I'm
scared of magma, so let's go behind it. There's a pot portal.  Apparently,
there is a portal. It's wonderful. It's perfect.
God bless you. Do
n't use it randomly.
Is it okay
? Nora Portal. Is there such a thing? Nora. It's a long way to go to the portal.
Probably so. There's Yoishi and stuff.  I don't know, I
don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't
know, but if I put it up there, I'd be surprised if I could get out of it.  It looks
like it's going to cost 4,000.
[Laughs] No
one will ever use it. It's
okay. No one's going to die. No one's going to die.
We're going to give this clothes back when it's our turn. We also missed the
diamond clothes.
That's right, I
'll pay it back by making equipment with the diamonds I received.It's
not a debt, it's just a loan.It's a
debt, but I borrowed it from a friend.  It's
been enchanted here and there.What's the
enchantment?It's shiny and
doesn't have any strong effects.It's true.His
defense power is so high, so I guess he
exchanged it with Uncle Neo.Oh, it
's Uncle Iron.  Yeah, yeah, yeah,
that's easier.
But let's do it.
[Music] If I
get it from a steel factory and exchange it, then I
can exchange it with Mr. Tetsu.  I
got the emerald, yes, yes, I
exchanged it. It's cheap, but it's not difficult. I
know where it is. It
's across the bridge behind the first house. I see. It's
out of focus. Let's go see it later. It's okay.
Koyori-chan knows that she can make it, but she
doesn't know anymore. She's suspicious of my chat.
However, Koyori-chan played solo mackerel in 30 minutes and
got 7 diamonds in 27 minutes.  I
found 13. Wow, what's that? I was
digging for something, and before I ended up at minus 54, I
just came across it. Yeah, that's why I met the
senior who was singing, and I had a different chat with Kia-senpai. That
chat was in A-senpai's
chat, yeah, yeah, yeah.  Everyone at kfp is
doubting me, but I'm not scared. I
got 6 in 3 hours.
No, I got 4, but I'm happy for 3 hours. I wonder
if I found happiness. Happy, happy, happy. Happy,
happy.
Tarahahapi
[Music]
Hahahaha, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's
dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's
dangerous, it's
dangerous, it's dangerous, it's
dangerous, I'm not scared, Senpai, I'm not scared.  It's
because money is stupid. I'm
going to Japan again this summer, so let's have fun. Let's
play. Let's
play. I want to do something fun. What do I want to do
? I'm a genius with money. It's fun.  It's
not Kagenius, no,
it's not Genius, then I'm
going to go there. I'm a good idiot. I'll
take a look at my educational background. I'm going to
ask my senior to go with me. I'll probably call
someone from en.  Who's out
there? Oh, I'm so happy, I'm so happy. Let's
all go. Wait, wait, wait,
wait, what's okay?
Mushrooms are difficult. Mushrooms. These mushrooms. We
don't need them. We don't need them.
Okay, green, okay,
green. Hey, it's everywhere. Where can you find green kino? I guess it's
only in the Blue Forest.
Listen
[Music] I
asked the woman who was listening to it. That's right, that's
right, that's right, it's called Blue Forest.  It's
only in the real land that Mr. Ao seems to like.Maybe you should look behind him.Thank you,
that's how bridges are created.It's
almost
gone.I
want it in the red part.
[Applause]
Why don't you just give me the block, even though I still have the block? Yes,
what's wrong? What's wrong with my
senior? I don't know what's wrong with the factory, so I
'll take you there later. Thank
you. I don't care for the new guy.  For
those of you who don't know and are new to me, I'll let you know.
Thank you. I
want to eat. I'm going to
press on. When I get home, I think I'll eat.
[Music]
Open the road. It's
nothing.  I
'm saying today's outcome is amazing, it's amazing,
it's like I thought it was impossible in the net, it's amazing
[Music]
and the colors are so beautiful Yeah,
yeah, what time is it in Australia? It's
7 o'clock in the evening in Australia.
But at 7 o'clock, yeah, yeah, yeah, it's
golden.  It's time, it's a little bit. Usually, when you
start broadcasting at a time like this, it seems like it's a good time. Yes, Alan is Kira. It's the
time of the day. It certainly has the image of midnight.
Yeah, it's Europe's prime time,
isn't it?
Mayadana-san, you're the same as Ka. Te-
san seems to have opened up a path for you,
but you can stop it now. No, you commented on it, and you should stop it. I
love you too much, so I made a face.  Do
n't step on anything. Oh, I see. Well, it's
dangerous here.
There was something that looked like slime. There
was something like slime coming from above the magma.
If it's coming from above, be careful! It's dangerous! It's
dangerous. It's dangerous. I'm doing my best. It should be okay.
Okay,
oh, this
is a hot tourist spot.
Whoa, what's this? Something happened on the green.  I'm here
OFF Oh, I wanted to go to all the biomes in the Nether.
It was a real story. The octopus is really
blue here. It's blue as it was yesterday. It's
just the forest that I haven't seen.
There are mushrooms here.
There's a mushroom I want.Can't you
just climb it? Aomori Aomori Aomori Aomori sounds familiar. Aomori, that's Aomori Ken, probably. Ah, I know. Aomori Ken. Or Aomori, short for Aomori. It seems like it's just a mushroom, but it's still a mushroom.  Is it still a person
's name?
Koto, I want, I want, I still
want, I want, I want
, I want to be careful, be careful.
Mushrooms, wow, they're scary.
Jump
Wow, I wonder if this is okay. No, no, no, it's fine here.
Thank you, this or this.
No, that's it. That's it. That's it. It's true. There
's one more. Wait.  Wait, I
got 2 of them, I
got 1 of them, I got 2 of them, I
got 2 of them.
JustJust Yeah,
yeah,
just is nice too
[Music] You
did it
[Music]  It's very
wide.
If someone gave it to you, it's
not
worth stealing. So when you come here, you can say that you took it. I
think it's fine. I'm sorry.
Thank you,
thank you,
thank you. Oh, I can
make a shining blue door.
What is the blue door? Shall I take this home?
Well then, this is a blue
door. I wonder if this is what you were commenting on. It's
definitely blue.
Let's go home! It's
dangerous. It's okay. It's
scary. I
killed Subaruba-senpai. I
fell down, but the lava is
standing like this. It's so
blue. It's
so scary when I look at it from here.
[Music]
[Laughs]
Hey, this, that, that's scary. This isn't doing well, is
n't it?  It's tough,
right?
[Music]
It's scary, you guys are scared. I'm
not going to fall down on my minecraft.
Okay, let's make a door. Let's give it to the other guy. Do
n't tell me. There are only four pine trees. I
have a pine tree. I'm going to
grow a pine tree behind the pine tree. My friend
did it for me
.
[Music]  It's
quite far away, is
n't it? It seems like there's no place to put Ramatsu.
Magma Matsu. Will I get the diamond called Ikoma Magma tomorrow
? Ikoma.
There's a mission report book. Ah, that's it.
If I write that I've done a whole thing, I'll
get a diamond. I'm so grateful that I'll report it myself. If I
don't report it, I won't get it
. I didn't even know that, but I'm afraid I'll
miss it on the first day.  I'm
scared, but I'm not scared.
Well, I haven't died even once. I'm not afraid
. I won't put it down. I'll
have to collect the diamonds all by myself. I'm not
asking for anyone's help.  I
made my own materials at about the same time,
and yes, it seems like I'll be revived, but I have to collect 7 diamonds, so I
guess I ended up collecting diamonds, right? I
collected those 13, making 13 blocks.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no one's body,
axes and axes, axes, axes, ice axes,
and even iron I have to make myself.
Yeah, if I don't grow a pine tree like that myself, it
will be dark, so my Pi. What will happen if I die one more time? I have to go back or
else I won't be able to do it. But if I don't go for another four days, I
won't die. Let's kill the pine tree together. If I don't
cook it, it will be calm.
Come on.  Why
did Kakeru Ikari Ruri-senpai die?
In this Nether, there was someone who was trying to
defeat the gust from earlier, but there was someone protecting him, so he was
panicking.  I
plunged into the dripping magma and
burned, but someone seemed to be protecting me. It
was attacked and the three of us were there. I see, I
thought I had to do something, and then I plunged into the magma.
That's kind of you, haha. It's
an honor.  He's the honorary lord, isn't he? He's
being praised for something. It
's cool that he lost his life. It's
so cool that he lost his life to protect his wife and baby.
Ya,
thank you very much. I'll
do
anything if I can. I wonder if there's anything wrong with it.
Support, support. I'm
looking at you here. Wow, I think it's a good idea to put up a sign. I need a sign. I
need a sign.
Oh, if we keep going like this, we'll be able to
go to a place like the castle from earlier.
That's wonderful. Happy, happy, happy.
Nice.
Here, where is this going to go? I'm going to go to the
morning and go to the concert.
[Music]
There are so many roads,
right? I'm curious, but I'm
alone
[Music]
Hey,
what's a wonderful fortress? I'm
writing this about the castle. It's
wonderful. Oh, Opi-chan, Pi-chan, Pi-chan, Pi-chan,
Pi-chan,
In such a narrow place, in such a narrow place.  By the way, I
should have taken the photo at the fortress. It was so
good that I didn't take it. I ran away and came back. Oh,
Piku-
chan. Yeah, yeah, I got it. The six of us did it.
Thank you very much.
Yeah, okay, let's go home, let's
go home. Let's finally go back to the ground. I was
scared. Let's go home. Hey, I'm alive. Wait, everyone, the blue holo.
Wait, everyone, the arena has been built. The arena is
amazing. It's been done. It's been done before I knew it. It's been done before I knew it.  The
bed is here. Take the bed. I
didn't want to do this.
[Music]
That's nice. I see. What will happen tomorrow
? I'm scared. I wonder if I can confess.
Hey, don't look at me. I'm still in the middle of the process. I'm
sorry I haven't been able to take a photo.
Okay, so Miko and the others
successfully completed the mission.
Great, thank you everyone. Thank you for the end.
Thank you, Kyube
Mabe. Thank you for sending Kyukyu.
Thank you, you two, for the mission.
Don't forget to write the mission
Mission Don't forget to
write the mission Everyone come here Are you going to
write it? It's like I'm going to block it. Yo, I'll write it all. I'll write it all at once. Ah, I'll
write it down. Thank you,
Masuha-chan,
come on.  Okori-senpai
said, ``When I went there with Akaku-kun,
our names were probably already written on it.So let's talk
about Piglin Fortress.''  I
'd like to ask for more, too.I'd
like you to write Gusto yourself.Oh, I don't get
it.Is it okay to do this?I'll tell you.There
's no reward for diamonds, so I'll draw them.I'll
draw them for Kara and Kiara.
[Music]  ] It's
okay to draw, Sho-chan, here it is, iron,
iron, iron, iron, iron, iron, iron, iron, iron, iron, iron, iron, iron, iron, iron, iron, iron, iron, iron, iron, iron, iron, iron, iron, iron, iron, iron, iron, iron.
Thank you for all the items. I do
n't need them, so I'll just leave them here.
Put in the things I don't have. I'll
get stuck with the iron. Yes, I ca
n't put in the
iron. Thank you very much.
Uncle, please. Uncle, this is uncle. Wow, you've
developed quite a bit.
Monnaka-chan, who came to town for the first time in about 4 days. I'm
sure you're standing there like that. You've
changed so much in just one day. Everyone is amazing.
As expected, everyone,
loki loki loki, it looks like
it would be better to sleep. Do you want to sleep? I'd rather sleep
next to my senpai than this sloppy
ajako.  I left it somewhere for a while. I'm
heading back to the Nether, so everyone goes to bed. I do
n't have it. I don't have it. I'm sorry. I
can hear my senior's voice from my left ear.
Well,
what's that?I'm going to clean my ears.I
want to scrub my ears.It
's free.I'll
pay for it.Okay, just pay for it.Then I'll give you
10 diamonds.That's a little diamond.  I
told you, I don't have 10 of them,
so I don't have to borrow money
. Somehow, the memories of that day came back to me. I
got caught in the mackerel trap.  Did
something like that happen to me when I was in debt?
By the way, here it is.When I
right-click and talk to the old man, it
comes out.Emerald.Ah
, there are some things that are sold out.Ah,
there are some people who can do it.  Wow, I
made an emerald. It's nice. I wonder if
this person will increase the number of emeralds. This person
sells diamond boots downstairs. I
see.
Thank you very much. I'll exchange these now.
I wonder if I'll get the same one as the one I'm getting right now. Maybe, thank you. There's an
old man over there too, so you can choose the one you want.
Thank you. There are many kinds.
Thank you.
Okay, let's go report on the mission.
Let's go.
Yes, I'm more senior than you. I'm more senior than you. I
'm better than you. I'm the most
kind. Remember
that you're kinder than me. I
'm reporting a lot here.
[Music]
Everyone is fine making potions. I see. I
haven't made any
potions. I'm going to go make a potion, but there's an
automatic potion making machine. There
's a statue stand in that house. I think it's in the corner of Ka's house.
1616  The
date has changed to 16, but it's
okay because I'm so lazy.
Senpai, I'm going to make a potion right now, but I have
n't played Saul Sand Popo Soul Sand Gust Gust Skeleton
[Music]
Nether, I
wonder if someone will write about this. Is it Nakanade-chan? You can wear a Netherwoot and
get some more. That's fine
. I'll just make a field there.
Glowston. Are you wearing your shoes?
Glowston.  I'm going to finish writing this, and
then I'll go back to Glouston. I'm
going to draw this here, and I'm going to draw this here,
and I'm going
to divide it in half.
By the way, I don't have a house. I want
to build a house somewhere. I want to have one. I'm going to make a caressing potion. Hey, wait, wait, wait, wait, it's dangerous. There's a lot of movement, but this is my home. Hey, let's build a house somewhere.  I don't know
what's good about "Ochi Ochiochi."
Well, it's annoying, but the splashing here is
a bit noisy. It's
small and cute, isn't it? A house like this is small.  It
's better to have a house that's close to some facility, right? Yes, I think it's the strongest, no matter what. The house may not be newly built, but tomorrow, it doesn't have to be a new house. It doesn't have to be a new house, so it's better if it's rich. A house that's
close to a book is better.  That's good, that's close to the liquid.
Hey, don't open the chest of the dangerous person.
Um, Richi,
that's right. Maybe building a new house is quite important.
But Richi-chan, it's okay.
Naochi, I don't know where I should put it. It
seems convenient, but if there's a train station over there, I wonder
if it would be okay to put it there. I think it would
be closer to my senior's house.
On the first day, there was a village here.  There were a
lot of people gathered around,
but I guess that's the one in the middle. Fall
here. Stand up here.
Then, let's stand here. This is the only one that's
hungry.  It's
easy to take a diary, right? Just a little bit.
But this block isn't that cute.
Well, at first it's a
simple, simple house. It's
too small.
Wait a minute. There's a lot of things in the Kade's Kade's.
Leave it
there. I need the
key. I should have thrown away the key for the iron door. I
had it with me, right? I
got it from Pecola-senpai.
I'm kicking through the iron door. I
can't go in there. It's too big. I can't go in,
but this
house is fine. I can just go in here. It's
fine. I
can just sleep here. It's okay.  I
want something like a house.The number is increasing.I
made a lot of money today.So, wait, I
'll rent it for a while.I'll
go home for a while.I don't think that's what it's for,
but I think it's a
cadet house.
Okay, okay, I'm sure there are some. I
want a chest.
After the chest, I want another bed.
Yes, it's for carrying purposes. I
want a temporary one. What is a
Jann House? If I have a house soil, I'll have a house.
Yaroi.  Don't look at other people's houses
and say they don't have personality.It's
personality.It's easy to forget that you want the tree you want
and the bed you want.Fleet
Chifley.
Bed free rice, a lot of
rice, thank you, I've got a lot of food, thank you
very much.
Even if I do it,
it's okay. Is it
okay to make this tree?
Or should I make it grow after I do it? I
don't have a skeleton somewhere. Later on, if there was that
thing that could be flushed,
that would be it.  It
came out, it came out, you
can do it like this, it's okay, it's
okay, it's hungry, there's a dangerous one, there's a dangerous one.
He's an assailant. Hey, you
can kill him. Oh,
hey, there's one.
When I went everywhere,
everything
seemed to be calm, and it
started to feel like it was crawling.I wonder if it will fall a little more.Yesterday, I
planted a tree.  The
one who plants the trees, why
don't we destroy 1233 of them? There are
a lot of people who grow them, but they
haven't come out yet.
[Applause] The
leaves have
not come out yet.
Come on out, white guy. There's still a lot of white stuff
over there. It
's fine. It's fine if you cover it white and white. If you
bury it here, it'll
be perfect.  I
dug about 3 or 3.
Hey, y'all,
y'all. I want the cherry blossom one too. It's a
temporary house.
Well, I have to make a potion. I was
really surprised when I made the potion. I was also fired up.
Well, you
guys said we don't have a roof, so let's
build one.
But even if we build a roof, we won't be able
to get in, so let's
build it like this. Hey, if it's like this, we can climb it. Well, we can climb it with this. It's
fine. It's great. I don't
feel like this.
The ceiling is a bit low.  It's already low.
The ceiling is low, so my body should have a high ceiling.
Ah, the ceiling is so low that I
have to live with the awareness that my head is always hitting the ceiling.
Well, that's no good. What should I do? I've come up with a better
idea. It
seems that the appearance of the octopus enhances imagination. I
can't enter this door. I
'm going to enter from here. So I'm going to open it. Perfection is back.
Hocha is also back.  Now that I've changed my clothes, I'm like, oh, I
don't know how to make scaffolding, but I don't know what to do. I
want to climb up here.
[Music]
Hmm.
Wow, hello, hello, hello, hello, I
'm building a house. Hey, nice Kanade house. You
can come and visit me. How
long will it take to finish? I'll
be able to finish it soon. Oh yeah, please come and
visit us.
Please come and play with me. Yes, I took one.
Yes, it's
okay. I don't care. Just take it if you think it's enough. I'll go. Yes, it's okay. I'm looking forward to it. I'm not
that good at architecture, but it's
kind.
Just pat it like this,
okay, okay,
okay, let's just make the roof. Now the house is complete. Alright, okay, it's cool. It's starting to look like a house.
[Music]
Okay, let's build the roof.  It's
not what I thought it was.
[Music]
Hmm, it's
not what I thought it was, but I
get it. I get it. I understand why.
Wait, I'll fix it from here, so I
wo
n't put that in. No, no, that's not
it.  It's
pretty cool, isn't it?
And you can enter from any direction. That's
great.
Even if it's empty, if it's not empty, you can't enter the house,
because you can't enter the door.  Do
n't make it all empty, you don't have to
sleep.Kade will
defeat the skeletons, so go in here and get a chest.I
want a workbench.Um,
make this one.With the
working agent, that's a chest.What
's a chest?Chist,
Chist 1
2Ma  Is it okay if I put two of them here? It's
okay if I put a chest here. It's okay. Karadez
House is completed. It's okay to complete it already. I
want something like this.
Hey, I want a garden too.
Hey, I've got a great idea. If we
do this here and there, the
zombies won't come, and no
one will come. Hey, they're coming. That's
a lie. Well then, there's one more
trap,
two more
traps, and the
magma will flow out. That's dangerous.  No,
that's dangerous. You
can't do that because your body will die and your body won't be able to enter the house.
That's
hardcore. Let's go safely.
Come on, come on.
Is this coal?  A
lot of planes have come out, they've
come, a lot of them have come here, you're
lucky, you're good, you're good, you're good, you're good to dig, you're good to dig,
and now you can't climb.I can't climb anymore, but let's dig anyway.Let's just dig.It's
okay.  It's starting to look like a secret base. I'm so busy
digging this place that I haven't decided what to do with it from now on
.
Hmm, I'm going to dig it up and make some ground,
and I'm surprised to find that it's a
long hole.I
wonder what I should do.So let's
dig here and
there.Let's dig all the way here, and
then we'll make it so we can climb out from under the house.  It's
floating, it's fine, it's fine, it's floating, go
ahead and put it on.
That's it, that's it, that's it, everything here is so
good.The
exterior of the house is pretty
cool, but I
wonder if it's a little more musical.  I
think it's nice that it's big,
but it feels like there's one more voice.
Hmm, that's nice, but the ceiling is also digging here.
There's also a lever note block. There's also a note block.  What is a
musical note block? I
asked a senior colleague and he
told me. Wait,
climb up on the workbench once. Climb
once, then go. Make a stone
pickaxe.
Make a stone pickaxe.
Then come back.
[Music] Here you go.  Are
you a genius who's not good at iron
?I'm sure you're a genius, but iron
is limitless.Thanks to Ia-senpai, I
risked my life for the entrance.It's true that if I make a slight mistake, I'll
die.
[Music]
There's a big difference. The
blue one came out. I ca
n't get the lapis to come out. I
wonder if there's anyone who'll die from being angry. It's a bit pitiful to die from being angry.
Well, there's a ceiling, but I'm digging one more layer.
Tasaru
[Music]
Neoihichita
This is one more step
Holeto Ochiochi What's this
about building a house? There are
n't any events or anything. If you build a house, it
'll be like a diamond.
Oh, it's already over. That's
stupid. I didn't [ __ ] yesterday.
That's what happened.
Where did you hear the voice of someone else
? The baby was alive. Oh, I lost my voice. Oh, I
don't know about this.  I don't know if it's not there I don't
know if I'll open up the theory or not I don't know if I'll open up the theory
Well, the water is flowing,
but it's a little scary Hey, it's
this dark Timer
Matsu
Ei Ei
Ii
Well, I guess this is fine. It's getting a lot brighter. With
this water, there will be fewer people dying from peeing. It's
kind. It's
very gentle since I let it down. I
made a mistake and got blown away. It's only round here,
so I made a mistake.  I
feel like I've clearly made a mistake,
but
okay, okay, okay, okay,
okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, but I can't climb any higher than this.In
that case, I'll just
put this here.
[Music] I
wonder if there's enough. It's not enough. Damn, it's not enough. It's not enough. Well then, I get it. Let's use our heads as long as we don't have enough. If it's like this, they won't find out. I just felt like I had some left over. It's not just fashion, but
Mie.  It would be
cool
if they didn't do just one step here.Also, it looks like they left one step in instead of in the middle.That's what I
was looking for.I don't know.
Well, it's not easy if it's in the nether, but
wait a minute, I want to climb to the top, but I
ca
n't climb up once. It's so big that I can
climb, but if I
can't, I'll climb from here
or do my best to climb.
It's dangerous, it's
dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's
dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's not going to be in
the net, it's
falling again, stop it, it's true.
That's
okay, but I
can't climb it. I can't climb it.
Who was that? Who built this house?
Wait until you're exhausted. If you can, look for it.
Where is it? If it's in the Nether,
then it's here.  Let's go and plant some cod.
[Music] I'm going to
find something good,
so let's put it up. It's
dangerous, it's dangerous.
Eh, ladder, ladder, ladder, I want a ladder.
Eh, I don't have enough trees. I
want to go and dig some trees.
Koho Kihashi is
here.
Oh, I'll plant this
later. Or I'll plant it later.
But it's time.  I guess I'll build a house and then go to bed.
Well, ladder, ladder, ladder,
popo, let's do
this like this.
I'm going to make a ladder,
and I'm going to make a ladder, and I'm going to come into the house, and I'm going to
go down from here,
and I'm going to go down here.  I'm
going to
put it in from the inside.It's
stylish.I'm glad there's someone who understands the sensibilities of the body.
Hey, I'm
going to climb up now, and I'm going to go to the nether, and I'm
going to plant some cod.
Isn't it okay? Ooh,
here, what's this? Let's make
sure the water runs through here.
In case someone falls in, we
can't set up an end
here.
It would be kind of you if I let you do this. It's kind of you. It's
not for me, and it's really
scary. It
might be a bit too much for me.
No, I don't want to drown and die. This is a
scary, dangerous control. But now, let's
go to the special tower like this.  Sorry, there are
n't enough ladders, so if you don't have enough
ladders, dig a little more, or even if you fall, you
can just keep climbing.
Oh, there are so many trees falling,
so I'm going to plant this one too.But
let's just do this.
This isn't it
, this is it.
Ei Ladder. I've done quite a bit of ladder work.
33 I guess I
can block it like this.
Wow, this place is scary.
[Music]
This place is a little scary.
I'm trying not to fall in love with you.
Well, I'm scared. Hey, it's not like this. It's not like
that.
[Music]
Oh wow,
wow, I can do it. Oh wow, wow, here,
like this, like
this, here, like this, everything.  I
think I've installed it. Well then, I
guess Karadez House is complete. That's the
house over there.
Hey, I don't like it, it's hard to live in, so I'm
going to go outside.  I
think I'll erase it only once,
but it's okay, it's
cool, it
's cool. Kanades House It's cool, isn't it
good
?  Okay,
that's great. I was foolish to wish for that. Good morning,
good morning, Senpai.
That's right, that's right, I have to give it back. This
is something I borrowed from someone. That's
right, it's not mine. I'm taking it off. Right
now, I think Hajime-chan is still here.
Well then, it's still okay.  It's
still okay.
I'll hold you when the time comes. Tomorrow, I'll
tell you that it was mine first. No, I lent it to you. It's nothing like that to me.
Senpai does things like that.  That's what it is
So don't be fooled anymore. But what is that? There
were a lot of missions with my body, right? I didn't do skeletons. Potions, you
guys. How do you make potions?
Koyori-
senpai,
Koyori-senpai.
Oh, that's right.
Oishio automatic.  Is it okay if I press the production
machine button only once? I'm
making it right now.  You
just have to wait. There's
water here after all. Is it
going to come out here?
Why is it so long? I'm
sure I said it.
[Music]
Sa's water haha. I
see. A
potion that contains redstone.  I
don't have any nether wart to put the ingredients in. I
guess it's impossible to make a potion. I guess I'll
give up on the impossible potion. The
pin is already
made. What's the
matter with the bottle?  I've
already done
this. Oh, I
took this. I did all three. Is it
okay to take this
and that? Thank you. Yay, I was able to
make a potion too.
Thank you, Senpai. If I don't write here, I'll
take this too.  Well done, I made a potion.It's
a little obvious,
but I don't have enough pages, so let's do this.I think it's
good to make a potion.I
want to make a table production skeleton.
Hey, I want to play skeletons, so where
should I go? I guess I'll just have to wait for night to come.
Skeletons: 3 diamonds,
5 TTT, which gives me a lot of money.
Where is TTT?
Trap
tower. Are you
sure you're gay enough to go to that place from the Nether?  So,
what is it
? It's
streaming right now. It's streaming right now. Ah, okay. I'm
still streaming too. I'm middle-aged, so yeah, yeah, yeah,
what are we going to do here? What are we going to do now? Trap Tower  I
want to go to TTT and defeat the skeletons. I
mean, I can complete the mission of defeating 3 skeletons even from TTT. Is that no
good? I don't know about TTT. I don't
know either, so I didn't write about it,
but the skeletons are over there.  If it's a skeleton, then it's
written in the comments that it can be
done, so it's probably okay. It's okay. It's
round. Okay.
Good luck. Yes, thank you. Good
luck. Yes, thank you.  The place you can
go to from the Teti Nether is a bit
surprised. Why would you
put a hole in a place like this? You'd
be
surprised. Is this a trap or a part of the Nether? Why is it the other way around? Come on over.  That's cool,
but it would have been better if it wasn't a tree. I think it would
have been better if it was black. Let's
just kill the skeletons and then go to bed.  I've
also built a small house. I
wonder if something will come out around here. It's
already night.
Skeleton-kun,
skeleton-kun,
here and there. I'll
come out and wait here.
Well, I
want to draw a diary. Hey, I'll
draw a diary, too.  I want to
go to a dark place.Skeleton.Skeleton.Skeleton.I
have a bed.I'll leave it
there for now.I wonder if it's okay
somewhere.Skeleton.  It's
scary even in Meza.
Everyone is sleeping.
Uwamori
Moria. It's already morning.
[Music] I can't believe it.
[Music] No matter how
many roads are made, I
won't die. I
won't.
[Music]
Ayamero Yaba Bed
[Music] I
made it half way because it's so funny.
Here. Yeah,
what's this
?
Ah, I'm dying, I'm dying, I'm dying, I'm dying, I'm surprised. What's
that? Is this wrong? It's a clumsy way to
climb up here. Ladders, ladders, ladders, ladders, ladders, ladders,
etc.
[Music]
Awawa
Something goes back and forth to the world,
right?
The world is actually round. The world of Minecraft is round, but it's not true.
Omira and Evil are sleeping here. What happened here? Oh, you
guys can smell it. Come on whoever has it. Ah,
ita,
ita, 2 of them died right away. 3 of them.
3 of them. This one won't explode.  Wow, that's amazing. So let's
go home
now. What's up with all that water? Let's go, let's go home, let's fall safely.  It's
safe, it's safe  Dachi
and the others, it's
okay, we'll definitely be able to go home from here. Hey, what
was that mission
? It was like the two of us going to get eggs.
Hey, where are we?
This is where I came from.
Is your mom okay? I
borrowed
this. I went home a little well. I went home well. It's amazing to be
under such pressure. I'm
going to borrow a little bit and go.
Yes,
please do your best. Yes, fight hard. Yes, bye-bye. Bye-good. Hey, baby, it's going to be tough. Whatever it is, go home and click on the bed.  I want to get out somehow,
so here we go
[MUSIC] It
seems like it's dead. There's one left
[MUSIC]
There's
Skeleton. Why don't we play this?
Okay, let's use mushrooms.
Mushroom Opi is amazing. I'm sure this will help.
124 I
started hardcore Nether Soul because I'm Bo. I
did Sound, I
did Gusto, I did Skeleton. I did Potion, I did Cloth. I
did Cloth Stone. I did Cloth Stone. We
did Frog Eggs together.  I couldn't do it. I
did mushrooms, I did the Nether, I did eggs, but I
didn't. Le-senpai is
great. I think he's good. I think he's good. I'll
leave this behind. So next, I'll write a diary.  I
think I'll end it by changing it to Calero.Let's
draw it at home.The
diary was drawn in a private place.Well, let's
draw it today.Let's make today's
diary May
166.I still have 16 hands, and
tomorrow will hurt too.  I think it's going to be complicated if we have to do it, so it
's not Friday.
Thursday.
[Music]
Hmm. I
logged in today. Well, what happened when I entered Minecraft?
Ke Pecora-senpai Pecola-senpai
fed me a house with an iron door that I received.  I have
no choice but to order the
food from the side of the door.
Now that I think about it, I was
given the
iron door that Pecola-senpai gave me at that time.  I installed it in my house and it won't
open.The
only way to get in and out of my house is through the side of the door.I'm
so happy that I was able to make my house look cool.Isn't it okay?  I
went to the Nether wearing diamond equipment. I
completed a lot of missions.
Emiko-senpai,
Kaela,
Senpai-Chiara,
Senpai-koyori, Senpai Anya
. It's over, thank you very much.
Baby,
and the baby that was erased from my memory,
and the RP
baby.
Good
[Music]
Hey, we're together.
I'm glad we found the fortress.  It's just so
good, my
seniors were so much kinder than cats.Raph
was the kindest person in the world.
[Laughs] I wonder if I
can convey this much to my baby.I
can't convey my feelings to my baby.In this case, a friend is better than a friend.And
then he passed away.  I'm
going to give it to Heart-chan. If this is the case, I'll be able to get through to this heart.
[Applause]
Well, I
'm glad that I was able to return the equipment I borrowed from Bancho Bancho without him knowing.
Bancho was the
kindest person in the world. The kindest love in the world. Is
n't it okay to not give back even if you don't give back? Even if you don't give back, you can give back even if you don't.  It
's okay, it's okay, it's okay.Anyway, the way the
date is written is strange.Let's
match.I'm the type to match things like this.So, it was
May 16th,
so I guess this one makes more sense.Hmm, do
n't open it.
Hmm, I'm so happy.Yes, I went to the Nether.I went to
Mikuria.It's
not that bad.Wait a minute.I'll
think about how to draw it.I'll
copy
and paste it properly.Don't do that.Live, live,
and return Daya's equipment.  I
thought they were going to raise a flag,
but they made it home alive.
Yahoo! It's
okay. Just do this and do it this way. It's
okay. 5  I
built a house on January 16, and I'm glad it hasn't opened. I was
told not to die. I was told to live and return the diamond equipment. I
thought it would really raise a flag,
but I guess it's okay if I go home alive. I'm going to do a lot of
missions next time.  I
cleared it.I went to the Nether and found
my friend Miko-senpai Cal-senpai character Senpai Col
Senpai-A-senpai Thank you very much I
was happy to be able to find the master.
Love and Bancho I
'm glad that I was able to return the equipment I borrowed from the Bancho without dying.The Bancho was very kind.I
guess I should
leave it as is.I guess it's already 3 o'clock when I put out my diary.  It's
already been 340 minutes. I've
done a lot of work, so I'm going to
return that equipment to the boss.
Well, the grass was getting in the way a little, so
thank you to the manager for all the equipment. I'll return it to you.
Well, let me know next time.
Well,
thank you everyone for coming today. It's a bit rainy,
but that's what happened.
New House Kade's New
House.
Thank you very much for joining us today.  Good night! It
was fun to clear so many missions. See you soon
. Bye-bye-chan.
Just subscribe to my channel. See you soon.
[Applause]
[Music]
Ah HV
[Applause]
[Music]