[Music]
ad
me was
in
uh hmm
[Music]
Hmm hmm
hmm
[Music]
Hmm
ben 1 minute
ana
dme
[Music]
Hmm
hmm
[Music] Nm
men
d
[Music]
Hmm hmm
Hmm, it's
in,
hey
[Music]
Hmm,
hmm,
good, good, good
[Music]
Take
me, hmm,
hmm.
[Music]
Hey
That kind of triumphant return Hella Te Chinu
Mokkai
This program is brought to you by the sponsors you are watching
[Music]
On Wow web worth
Dobon Arthur  Saying the department
see you by 4 books
[Music]
bo Yu4 cats Ie no
Homae Nekogata
[Music]
Every kono Raipon zobu
Watch Kiss  c 9 a 5 af
aaaaaaa
[music]
kendra
busking to
do
s 4 fe bag mom by bo
bu at the voodoo
voodoo canadas
scene with this show
so
4 me isoda  I will always
explain my talk at the beginning, so please listen to it.
Hope is Wipeout
Papis Up Interview ni
FEEDING MAIN ME JAPANESE
HORROR tend to
do us part EARTH BOOK BROTHERS
U BY THIN SAD SAD YALLA
SO FAR AWAY A It's a 5
interview talk show.The
purpose is that
I will be the main character while mainly talking about Japanese talent.  I
want people overseas to know more about it,
but Japanese people are also very welcome, so
please feel free to comment. Hosso
Takanashi I'll send it to you as a character.  I
always use Nehashi Tagamo, so if you
like, you can say Eero Gachi or Japanese,
but
please tweet with the hash tag ``Follow Talk''.Impressions and mother
screenshots, peace please users
photo Pester Mood
japanese songs to
the  Fire Pure Beans
Entry Pression Top Days
Oh yeah sound and putter and arm b wave
pick in Europe s go back to
windows As always, the end is after the distribution  I'm going to
search for the alarm, so please. I'm
happy to meet you, wipe my herb,
undo, something like that. I
'm under a lot of pressure. Well
then, get the laser,
get a nude weapon, say sour taste, or Usuda-ma-nya. I
wonder if that cat won't cry.
Hmm, meow,
Magumaguiyaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa a  The
thunder cat, the
line that changes the train Branagh
[Music] I
mumble, I
don't know.The cat is also a
good mother and sister with a few porridges.I'm healed from the beginning.rene
Road Pied 3 Sweets Heaven and Earth.Waiting for the
Speak Space check song moves.
Yay, that's right. Rice
porridge party apeace 510 laps of
surfing. At first, I would like you to introduce yourself.  I
think so, please feel free to use either Japanese or
English.
Well, first of all, let's talk in Japanese. This is Unhoro Live
Gamers' Nekomata Okayu. I was really looking forward to
chatting with Kiara-chan today. Hmm, it
's English.  The cat that says my name is,
uhm, I
want to meet you.
Please,
yeah
noas fm 4 a 5 a 6 e
aseru a
perso.  SASAMI 2
Day Purity Garse Garas Osugi Bawa Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh  Really? It's
not just a joke, it's
true. I want to know deeply about Ohana and my seniors,
so please tell me as much as possible.
Ne-yo
pandas auditor or say
Senpai Webber Renu with much
information overview s
past
right-hand man introduces yesterday's color close-up eyes
I think it's Jung Il
[Music]
a
4 sc department
Wedge type is press pass tune Now
paste from the first question
What kind of activities have you been doing lately? I have
n't changed much since I debuted with 6. I guess I've been playing games for a long time.
face the voodoo
Spanish Games All Finance What
games have you been playing
lately? Recently, I played Pokemon with Subaru Champ. I
want to see it, I saw it, I ate it, I
saw it. The backgrounds also look great on everyone.
Hey,
Pokemon is on sale.  I'm so excited because I just did
it v I want to move on Specific
Refined Pokemon Senpa Epoch Gate Line The
9 Pokemon are Subaru Senpai, meow,
meow i  They call him a sleepy company,
and he looks like a mother pie prepuri.
Oh, how do you feel now? When you
deal with Subaru-senpai A8, Hokkai-senpai is the 2nd factor. That
's right, Pokemon-senpai is a subordinate.
Apply for certification.  Even though I'm a high-class person, the song loops Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa When the
orchestra is Subaru with my seniors, I'm the
one who stands up Ahaaha I'm the type who plays with hair that way
[Music]
oren down fur leather
style
Decoup 6 yay
4 as Evolution Panp
Pazu hurries up Puzzle with a bird's eye look that makes me die. I
have that Subaru-senpai and Ribbon,
and I have a bond with Holo Bird, so I
hope they'll be kind to each other.
Oni
Sweet ek 1  Please don't crush Mari
Archi Subaru is Very Easy Aizawa
Higashi Checker Pocket Mons Ince CAD
is the sister district patron of A
How did you first find out about this live show, and
what made you want to join it again?
8 Hey,
when I was working at an onigiri shop,
No. 8 came to my onigiri shop and the
onigiri were delicious. If you'd like, I'll do a
follow-up live.  I
gave it to you from the time when the rice balls tasted good unless you opened the package and touched them.Is this
just a game?
Thank you very much.I
don't know anyone who can make such delicious rice balls.  It
seems like you should come to the Horo live after all
Darhodo na
carerra
apsalar
Do those Gamers' knee highs fit? Ah, originally
Fubuki-chan and Mio-chan were
included in Gamers,
and originally Fubuki-chan and Mio-chan were in the game center.  I've
met Mio-chan, and I was
like, oh well, if that's the case, then I'll come to Gamers if I want to hear the sounds of the
rice
porridge.  This live game
good
big star 4 ap chubby
wish army re mirror up
blizzard center mu senpai this child senpai round
pipe ac center ohno questionnaire
6 s  Kimisetsu Ah, Fubuki-senpai Mio-senpai,
yeah,
mom fire iii new dumb
fanbu forever a 3
to Guam game center
alea archaic good idea
still us it's so bad
yay finger in the
nose over you doing
a s web Corone-senpai if you get lucky
it's an idea  Ah,
I see.
So, after all, only
people who are good at games are allowed in? I
like games more than being good at them.
Ah, I see.
5 notes  Match birds
noco Buu Horror Game Spin
Boom
Goo Duravingins is Lintu Poota
folks Gotei type pose Um, I
think everyone likes games, but it's
especially good for good games
People who are planning to stream mainly games  It's the kind of place
where you can get in. I
wonder if that's the case. Something ok ok So take off your clothes. Let's go, cat. s Chains are ok. I
haven't had a language barrier before, but I'm curious about overseas.  Is
there something you've always wanted to tell me?
Well, quite a few people come overseas and visit my broadcasts,
but
I don't understand English at all, so
[Music]
Canal Parry I wonder
if they like me overseas.  I'm going to listen to
Kao that I wanted to listen to
hta socs Anshi Seinda
Esperia Peter TC I have a lot of dinner Tsume ni
M Tokoro Buyuu insertion scene see band
Shidasu Spear brother
Ing Situation and the 9th floor of Earth
Spots to you The action is as follows
Powder Warp Labyrinth Hall 2 Stream
Washer Louisa's crawling feeling
c I don't know the event and spin Wish
Sharp-edged and of course personality a Approaching
voice is here
A
gentle park double  voice,
calm voice,
mop tail,
oh, there are a
lot of round faces, there is also s.I
wonder if everyone in the Heisei world is surprisingly enthusiastic.Also, it has a variegated atmosphere.
Pete Kaori I
like the movie button It's
saying that
Babu Shake c Yum It's not that different from the Japanese color It's
good
Hey, that's right. It's a
big improvement.
There are people who said they're going to abolish Okayu Senpai.
I'm glad a.  Gaeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeyyyyyyyuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu paulownia
paulownia tree.  I
told you to just say ``Ara ara''
Teso TR Oto Sears user
by Nogoichi 4 and PR Hopek House Dazzling
Goods Impressions n Den branch I
heard various Spanish poker fighters
Kaappa
Bria Which cat
Ahaha yeah  Febu-chan Base A Part 4
Graduation fertilization, okay, then I want you to
hear the best message from porridge-senpai. It's so powerful. It's so good.
じゃあおかゆ先輩の
一番いいあるあらまで
32いっ
[音楽]
ああああああfaker んああああああ
ああ
はい
ドキドキすですかああああ台湾とバターが
なんかこれ読んだらあのくろにぃちゃんに
ちょっと似てるねって言われて Taaa
16-4 Center Wenzhou jis 4 a
Pippo etc. Brush Sanzobe is Ikkuroly
use for
I wish I could hear it a little more I do
n't know.
Please do it in a row ok day p and
suddenly 6 e
a 51 It doesn't show
up
Well, it's a little bit, you might understand a little bit
Yeah, I know, I'm using the cannula on the web Ka
Tiyaya Oh, it's
definitely not because it's a little bit
And uh, then the second season is also sunny.
In terms of the nature of doing things,
what kind of nuances does this mean?
It's the nuance of a baby's sexy older sister.
Well, the sexy older sister Alara
has a different feel, so I thought she would be happy to
go overseas since she doesn't have a character.Oh, I've
seen her in anime before, I guess
because of her lines and barking.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa the yuukosu 3 rows of floor chairs are even more cursed with
spice salt Bambi empty room
cute car
boo boo
eater re
Aichi Pure Chii-
um  ran, pervert, and moon, not moving,
all right, let's go to the question
a 5th time senior What's your favorite type of streaming so far
? For example, games,
karaoke, other chats, collaborations,
etc. Oh,
a number, I like them all no matter what.
Of course, if I
had to choose one in particular, it would have to
be games.
OC Settings
SR Former Barter 1 System 4
ABB Games
rpg
Hmm, that's the kind
of action game you like
Oooh
Mysterious Fish Tube Pegway Fair color The
cherry blossoms of the game with the game are
definitely going Hmm,
us are you doing
[Music]
No, I guess this blood is mixed No.
Okay, that's right, that's right. Raise the sutra a.
Okayu-senpai always has the image of being calm,
but
is there a secret to being so calm?
Actually, this is not true. Hmm, maybe he speaks slowly.
There are quite a few things that people just talk about that aren't very calm, right?
re
asp stance easter
witches ate
resend gent rp for a
spin Stars Marmy Saun 2 style
Even at meetings, I get really annoyed, and
even when I play games, for example, it's just...
Can you stay calm even in games like Jump Money and RT?
Ah, but it's true that Jump King is
not a game against other people, so it's all about you.  I
wonder if it's bad so I don't get irritated Eh,
usta re 4
compilation tale cars jumping
alea alea
cheese security council fa 4 a
[music]
reporting
Yes, there are
a lot of other people who
say it's cloudy, but I'm talking about people who get up and cry when jumping.
Oh,
and the rest.  I guess Jump King
has amazing environmental sounds, like the chirping of birds
and the
sounds of these species shaking, so
beautiful that I might have eaten Greening.  I
think
Oh God Sensei
[Music]
voodoo
sapere asobe
Undo then it's already rubber pure
posy Gameaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
game still is this card with pocket
That's amazing That's how it
feels I see.
That's the way the jump money is.  I've never seen it before,
but it's an email with a mental breakdown.It
's a strong
porridge cat.I love Bach and I love the top king.I really want to
buy jump money.
But I wanted to see Money Senpai's Sayakaa Senpai's Bar When It Disappeared, too,
so I looked it up. Tese
Backup
Rxw Doon
Ende Ser Fine Teaser
Follow Inja
Peer I finally found Moma Senpai's bar Well, the
angry one
Waha re Chapter 1 per Camp  after ka
you do sentence afe nr 2
points 5 u vinegar audi s
teensless cheesy
let's take a look  We've
come all this way to a fast goroaha Oh my god Ah,
rest next haha
4 a car
[Music]
ok
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa Carcassonne, the Nero guys are the favorites for stage 2 that will appear this time, and
Monoclay was the wrench.  Hey,
I'm the one you were looking for.Usually I
call myself Monogray, but this is my
bad name.Matahitori-
san.That's when I was playing against Paper Mario.
Clay's state is also really cute,
but the moment he turns from clay to these guys is
terrible. He's
like a passer, and then he writes the truth. He's
like ran, he's like this, he's 4, etc. I
feel like Lorenzi is probably the best
so far.  I've met a lot of people, but it's
rare that they're as nice as you
[Music]
If I recall correctly, Mario said something like, ``I want to go to the castle ruins.'' We've
come this far, so these guys are  I
'll tell you a secret, I'm a cat, and I
think these people are [ __ ]. I like the character. I know that I'm a pen. I'm
amazing. It's amazing. I
'm a gan. I love this Loren.
Bin Sekiya This is an
important place that my family has continued to protect for generations. We
can't let bad people enter the ruins. You
must not tell anyone the secret of the transfer.  And I
like that Ogi is a little kind. I
'm Lauren, a 3rd year junior high school student. I'll treasure this. I
'll make it into a necklace. When I'm done using it, I'll hook it up.
In the evening, the 0-wrench soldiers are in heart failure. There
's Grams Obayashi.  Or something like grapes
decorated with wind, etc. That's
cool. I wonder what the punch line is when I participate.
Ah, thank you for the moon porridge. I
like you too. You're Lorenz. You must
be really cool. Oh, you must
have been cool. Clear
. Are you at the Nitten bar? Are
you one of them? You're the aftermath of this one-sided line.
Gaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa.  You've
been doing this for a while now.
4 It's
been a while since I've been able to check it out on Clio, but I guess we're
connected.
Well,
Clio-san, you
still don't understand, right? You're 32 years old.  It's
this charm that I may not understand.
Clio, who is 32 years old, probably doesn't understand it. It
doesn't have the first-class true charm.
I think that I'm really cool because it's completely obvious. It's true. I think so too.
After all, it's me.  You
're the only one who understands how I feel.
This is the moment when I'm the most angry.
The character is surprised by Bippa. Is
this okay? Are you
doing this?  Should I
add that or am I already putting it in?
Dating videos may be cut off recently
orestes
molding other 4 se e
re
booing
w cab e
sapere
mayte  No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Boob Clear 4
Sorry for coming in,
server driver Well then, the 8th
century type is very cool Hoof
Divorce is cool Cute isn't it cool
What's so cool about it?
After all, it's a dead factory.Form
is Gree.  The
hem of the main lake is in the hands of the main lake, and the
quiz's Peppets Corner Live is
more cool.
Takihara-chan loves Shrek,
so Kido is
losing to him. Ah, Minami is like that. Shukihara-chan
is just like Shrek. Let's go back before we get into a fight. Tank 18  Better than military law,
Mr. Alpha is coming!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaare big c 3 big
tools tomorrow ah
second grease filling Harpy Dosu Is
Charles pattern really convincing?  The
reason why I don't have one is
because I'm green, but even when I
'm overseas, I'm showing off my green heart.That's because
everyone who sleeps likes the main character, so it was only for
a while.Well, every time I get drunk, my heart
becomes greener.That's right, this time.
Hey, this time I'll call it low range instead of
shoyaku Ueiro Wrench Green
Shake Reruno kokoa Hmm
Moomama That's what it's like to be in front of Saa and not to leave.
Kayu-senpai is really strange and I like
him. No, but lately, that character-chan is the Slytherin ion-treated Earth that you know. [Music] When he gets really angry at Tsurizari, he gets angry a lot, but the listeners are like me.  I was doing it while saying that it was nourishing.I
see, sensor arase with
me on.It's the failure part.Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa That's
to this Scanner 2nd ward yane Plan ya
Chiffon 2
Anus
Albus other
As ng Fashion s Feast Embankment
Dome Power Weed Corp Leader
March I'm
sure that's also the senior who was placed there and went to 3rd grade,
but I watched it a little more Boo
Boo iPhone RAIO
Slytherin Proton Beam Shooting 1
Fiennes Abri Ondas
Gameway
Aheahe  Takeseian has 9 more episodes. I
see. Next time, let's show it to everyone.
Swivel rio Tesaanamonda  Let's
go to the big question aoa
meow ga eh hmm,
what caused you to be on display? Did you
do something bad?
Yes,
that's how Onigiri Ah became a prisoner.  When I was judged in the Horo Live Trial,
I naturally felt like I was the prisoner character in the first place.  There
was originally a Polo Live trial, and I was tried and found guilty,
right? That's
so
true. Oh yeah, that's right, and I'm a prisoner character to begin with.
Well, my sins are everyone's sins, too.  You could even say that this
Onigiri-
ah is
wearing a prison uniform.Now,
who is the real trial about?It was a
long time ago, so it is a trial that only those who know about it are familiar with
.
Eh, he's different from that police officer who sat down at the live trial right now,
right? That's right, that's right,
that's right, he's different. And
who was in charge?
Mio-chan was the one who judged me. Hey, I see
. It's the
office sensor. Op First.
Grab the board and tomorrow two and a ferocious off turn A
fandom scope possible asos
good box
re catcher strengthened burger crossing
being with phone
adele
semanas axolotl wings 4
People 2019 is amazing
use me senpai
rear are you doing
aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa a
There are various theories, but the
most famous ones are that I
bought Subaru-chan's sandwich, that I
tried it, and that
I'm aiming for it, and that it's
Aker and Shion.  He
said he was tricked by the porridge, and
that's what it felt like to be
judged.
sender
eto
firecast recent battery
convidious study masu kun
biglobe finder c 2 r
1000 part 1
some n box appdarcy
appy
force loose o  2 Aqua
Senpai Harukawa Bye New Order Half It looks like you're
drinking to Thumping Every
sure as entertain
James Foley Senpai Fruit
Inc. to do
Moon r rr Starborn Star
Bone
Well,
well, I see, I've changed my understanding, Senpai, that
version
looks like a literary child.  So I don't
know why, but I can see the Netherlands, and the players are cleaning cats. I'm glad West 4 is empty.
Campion Hey, soil cleaning cats. Yeah, I see.  It's
been a long time since my sister, that one, has that been forgiven. Now, I'm wondering if the statute of limitations has expired for me. I see.
Oh, I
think she's been forgiven, but now she's at the house
depot.  give 4
103 spy naon spoon 1
khan It was quite a while ago
hmm, just in case
Super Hearth hearsay
My Mebi guideline is just amazing I
might have to do that cyber again.
If I don't ask Nemiu-senpai, I'm actually in trouble.Ah, I'll bring it again.Ah, aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa!  It
's safe. It's
safe inside this serge.
Thank you, Akira. Let's move on.
Why, why didn't I do anything? Instead, I reacted.
Teacher rav.  Vince goes on and
on about the oily penless and good government story. The
end of the lip story is ok
a. Let's go to the Tokina people too.
Yeah, I'm not myself. A
porridge-senpai used to be called the bottom of the night.
Tayone 1 Physical Induction Uke
That's how it came about,
but I joined the Emperor of the Night.Originally, shortly after I joined the follow live, I was
already at a nigiri restaurant.
Yeah, I'm working and I'm doing a follow-up live while I'm working, but I've
given up streaming, so I'm
preparing for tomorrow's cherry blossom rice balls, etc.,
but I can't start streaming until midnight,
hmm,
and Dragon Quest also has a character called the Emperor of the Night.
Well, I
like the Emperor of the Night, and his name is cool,
so he
was drinking, and when something happened, he
suddenly called himself Sakura.
Asoshi Sensor None 1  c
join 4 sc first poncho burgess
outer right rep asaras een
peat layer 4 blocking first pair worlds
flags is lie arm c black with
type wind nighter board web
even turn enter but
so test
andare a 4 s 4 a
sanja
seaside  se 4 Wow
vale Stan to do in Now
I'm holding the bar and making more and more scones
Now my grandma is running the business and I'm walking
Hanena has appeared in Tokyo,
so I'm already leaving it to the grandma to stop her from getting bigger.Centre's
Onigiri-e face, IP,
buy pin hand over gram, senior's first time,
bib, yeah, Enka, painless,
Momo-kyun,
Dress too, f Park, come on, pipe.  Todao
Neefice with desuummmm,
can that rice porridge senior even make delicious rice balls on his own?
There are humans who eat them like heroman.
What's your favorite onigiri? My
favorite is Mentaika-oo
irelia
prodes flap ear to
do so re not to do
in thai Kohn Ahrends Eye
pro sway bar s aaaa certain
aipo Ruffing Spot Warp
roll laugh
won e 8 a je  Sleepy
Fix 4, Salt Spice, and Upper Pakyuun.
No, stay calm. About 10% Seiko rack on the ground.
In Air Hockey I
see, Kiana doesn't like mentaiko town.
s 4 I do
n't really like it. I don't really like it.
Also, I don't like Sakura Nanyo
's tabunne fish type of things.
That's right, I'll
stick to it
OK. I see, then I'll move on to the next question.
Mars wine 8 It's
me, the pipe, it's me. No, I'm
sorry, but I got mixed up after all.
Passy the car make-up staff who speaks for the cat
Poo Migon fur voice helper right arm to you
Meow
meandering system
ah
oo
A total of 7 delicious photos tomorrow will be amazing
Yingshue mom par uc 2
sharp star with speed v  It was
a bit difficult for even Japanese people to understand the flowers and seniors outside of Wikipedia.  I
heard that you can manipulate the original source.
What kind of thing
is that?
Yes, I'm going to try it now. Hokke Shiboshibo
archi Bumura
Artist photo writer Please go ahead. No, please
take Kiana-chan away. And
that girl too.  Even though he's short, he's extremely
good
at it.Even though he only talks within the frame, he's also very
talkative and talks quickly.  And
Kerke, thank you for your help.
Well
then, it seems like I finally understood, but it was too early. The
woman who was translating couldn't make it in time.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
for to
say, this is what the plateau is.  Are you okay
?
adagio club This is not even for everyone It's
already been found out
I've been with Neko Aomori 4 Day Plain Wartime
with Neko Aomori Entis is Aomori
Puchchan early  I've
heard it before, I'm sure.An
apple with only fruit on the inside.Erotic
SS.Alright, it's
Aqua Perry.The
bread poster is also famous.Alright,
then there are some other famous things from Aomori.Food,
food, etc.  I wonder
what it is.The Nebuta Festival is a
popular festival.Is the Nebuta Festival held in the summer
?  Mr.
Webrier's Special Burger Molly
Shimade nas Pesstick
Alt Happy Summer Race Car
Nebuta Matsuri Lee Perry to do Hey, I
've already said a lot of things
Omooma Blow Room Black Other School's Sketch
What is Doll Nokketon?
Nokkedon  r I eat a lot of sashimi or something like that
on top of rice
rws oar Define form
for
regends 4th day Nod
Witches
sameera
Poodle Ice 4 AB User x
Army Angel Needs Star Wars
Blue Boy
Stamp Seafood Heeha
way I see, I see. After all, I
think the most popular way to talk about love is Nekomata Onna-style.
Dad. It's
true that there are brave people who embrace less.
Everyone is returning
Nekomata Toray is still suppressing lies Aomori Uichun is doing
ippei Eye Seho and Kim 3 J 1 I
hope we can meet someday I want to get older.
At that time, the action is good.
4 e 4 e 4 minutes
Sorting ah wohasisappe
After all, it's famous. Everyone
says they know it.
Hame na waa
boo boo
s pou dou
[music]
It's a dialect like dou.  Hmm,
but it's cute. Is it really okay? Really
okay. Thank you.
3 Sufu
Yeah ISO Apps for Emi Veel
Windy Scene
OK, next
is it suddenly, but the
case  Is it vulgar
?Manufacturers who have been
stalking and crushing stones a number of times
Saizeriyaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaathbeashup with vulgarity? Manufacturer who's been stalking me for a long time.  The
moon appurya has risen - before
that Silver
Khan was mounted a From the computer
Game period
Yeah yeah
Supervised concert concert aaaa
Surprisingly
rare Can you relate to Satoshi's voice? Ais There are a lot of
OES and scanners Is it
painful?  Sweets Khan,
Hmm Percy, I'm
having tea with you.
[Music] I
wonder
if Ubi's business is going to be good. My
mother is playing
Ryoko in a famous metropolis. Ah, Corn, Hmm.
Big city city ca Titty
Khan wears naked clothes when he sleeps I'm
bored
Cherry blossom loving event Halloween class is
full Come on, it's just Dawn
Hmm Halloween Halloween
amema Family Mart Lawson
Dotchin
naa 7
Effect female time Oden etc. Khan I see the
phone call Aoke Pom Pom  No,
giving a present or receiving a present,
which one do you prefer? A The
person giving the presentation is
the distance to the station, the distance to the car, the train itself, or the
tray. I see.
And what color are the pants?  It
looked like they were confirming something like Burn Burn Big Flow Watch Koin Dark Color Cute Teaching Study Thank You Party Banao Raras Releases Charking Form Kick or something,
but
National Straw Tuna Japan cad Howard is so stupid I was
told something like this all of a sudden.  I do
n't know, I don't know, right? Oh, I'm sorry.
ok ok Thank you for answering the speed quiz that I'm studying and studying and learning.
To calm down, Neil rb 2 up
this as pse
errorlevel I
want you to calm down a little by cutting corners,
but
next time a I want you to know
how much the flowers and seniors that the characters choose are really popular by taking pictures on the hood.  This
is a clipping that I think is
en with my mother and my
healer and my g round loan
ok ok cherry blossoms a
please enjoy
this is
welcome.
8,
Rokuto-kun
Welcome, one night of happiness Hot
Club Guilty A Welcome, young lady,
young lady, my
voice is broken, the sky is clogged, and my phonie, are you my
brother? Is this your brother? It's not Oniimura,
right? It's a voice like Orochimaru.  It
was raining today, so I thought I'd fill it up,
but I still had to wait for the customers.  I
thought it would be a good idea to introduce a lot of people,
so I brought
some crazy
members with me, so can I introduce some of the more toxic members? Edo Ten-
chan, this is what I'm like. I'm going to have a
friend from the Aso tribe come to the Edo store.
Yes, please, Sascha.  Don't laugh, I didn't. The
flower and the madness are crazy.
The flower and the green anchor
were a little different. I
don't mind if you tell me the name of the flower and the madness.
A Is it salt?
Thank you, you can call me Shion.
Hmm, after doing that, I found out that it's been 8 days.
Thank you very much, aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa The girl from Yagua is a tree.
Today is the first time I've
opened Domperi, so I don't know how to remove the freshness.  The
woman who was there to teach me how to get the best out of it was so
surprised.10 days later, I
thought I had created a new sound.
No, Shion, thank you, I had a new woman. You
probably already know a. Did you
buy the Boys' Federation? Yes, how to
use it.
And I love you, Shibaike. It's
enough, right? 2 Ah, yes, yes. Yes, yes.
Yes, it's
true. I'm
going to become Chompoo.  It's okay to wear bar shoes
[Music]
Buber Elina
Don't pass, let's fight now, Ten-chan.
There's a good girl, Tencha.
Do the same thing, whether it's reading six places or urinating, big sister.  I'm so
sorry, I'm so sorry, I'll bring you more guests with better manners. I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'll
bring you more guests with better manners. I'm sorry, I'll bring you better guests. My
mother turned. I'm
studying Kato's high-quality conversation, which is typical of that window song 6.
Did you hear that she was finally doing well?
Wait a minute, one of the older
sisters is 8 years old. I
know it's on this day, but the other one is just a little bit
older.  I was
wondering if there was ever someone this sexy. But can I ask your name? Well, I guess it's not Choco-sensei. It's Hirai, but it's me. Machi Yume. Also, I
forgot about this duo. No, I
didn't see anything before.
Ayame-chan, I
really don't want to be so sophisticated. I heard that you were
invited because of [music].
Maybe it was
something like that. That's how it all came about. It's great that you've become so sophisticated.
What have you been doing? I'm
so surprised that you haven't calmed down.
Well, that's a nice voice, but you have
n't forgotten about me
. You're
as beautiful as ever, so I'm sorry
.  I thought I didn't have to say it.As
usual, if you make a sound about it, you'll
hate me.
Ran
Boober Shiana
n Amena
Ask the slightly used hoodie that's 8 times warmer.
There's
something I'd like to ask you, so I'm going to stop by for a moment.
Prefectural Prefectural Prevention-kun
raised it. I
kept quiet from everyone, but
the girl who gave me the mountain bread was very sexual,
wasn't
she?  Oh yeah, I
have a push girl who I have from outside without any indirect personnel, how much will it cost?
If it sounds like it, I'll need money, so I
'll go.Eh,
including the husband's part pin-chan.
5 Parker is good
Me Rar Me
Rar is
a bit too much. Farry
Saha
Rar
Ah, Gardipusbem
JAPANESE Saved Pedition
Heart was the best funny paulownia that I showed in the colt mouth
Ander IT year art.  That's
right, I'm going to
take it. Ah, that's
amazing.
Hey, thank you very much for coming,
but I don't have any money. If
I
were Chiara, I wouldn't have to have money. I'm
sure,
stop it, aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa after all
After all, money is the most important thing, so it's hard to know whether to offer it or
not.Raira
R Fuchu Blazer
Red Army Birth
Releases Mail Pupu LC
caralal ounce small she
wants a many week wife needs
nerf and old man's
staff bag riku and emptied out
I don't like it, but that's what I found out Oka,
senpai and Rikuto-kun are so messed up  You
know what I mean, right?
That's what I mean, substitute Omenzuki Paris Koi error
porridge Senpai slash Kurt-kun
eme Shake Puppy and gross prize
ane Ra-Mike 4 s  Question
a I'm going to ask you a question,
but I'm going to ask you something about the mist in Osaki.Does your
sister get popular on the road?I'd
like to know if there are any of these, please.
Oh
no, I don't know if you'll fall in love with me like that. I
'm matching Kamatama. Ah, I'm
sorry. What's going on?
Ani Endo is a
drill. On days when I'm running, I'll paint it on a folder or a box.  I
think it's because they're small or there's a lot of them around, but I
know how to answer on Durapen Road.  I
think the
reason why Sony is going up is because
of Karl's personality, his
calm and slow personality and that rear guard too. He
has a soothing voice.
Even if you don't feel happy, you have a
very strong image of being kind.Hmm, I see.I guess
Shichinohe likes kind people.I
wonder if if he gets angry, he won't be able to be happy.On the other hand, if it were in the countryside, there would
be a gap.  Maybe I'll fall in love with that too
I wonder if that's what it is
Hello
alen geere
not for now 3 to
do 4 s words are you
do
voodoo arm performance
Please give me some advice if Beige and Romney were to be chosen.
a But good luck with the skillful La-chan c 4
Now, I think it's fine to
leave it as it is, but really, I don't want to be delinquent in any form, like
skiing, or something like that.  I
want to be with you
Hey, yeah,
but now I'm who I am, so that's
it, I-chan, I'm not good with Apari, I'm not good with Mars, I'm
good with Nike,
rar
parades the voodoo
warner b also pop one posture y
one urb also pop nane b be
escurve exenc line score poko
fiennes voice di sao
kohase pull out well with me phephe
phephe phephe  Fefefefefefefefefefefefefefefe
Hehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
knowaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaIiiI
think it's a dollar value less than puuu I think the version is fertilized
dan  4 Ending S
Wow, I'm swimming like WHY
, and I meet you, Minorena Aya Aya Aya,
and I'm sorry why this is a great party.
It's difficult, there's a lot of things, but
ah, ah, ah, color bar, Giselle Mibu,
year,
haha, let's take it away,
please.
How our feed is blocked by those who like it. I
think you have a good brain.
[Music]
Baby Baby
Let's move on to the next question
a.
Why did you get so close with your female senior?
And please tell me a funny story. I wonder
what it was.
How did I become friends with Mr. Ro? I don't know what it was, but we were already working on a version. So, I was
interested in him from the beginning, and even
though he passed away, I wish we never spoke to him.
Well, that's
what we say at school.  We're in the same class,
but we haven't talked at all, but he seems to be a little curious about me.
Hmm, it was a [ __ ], right?
So,
hey, I'm already doing the version, so let's go together.  I was like, let's do it, and I was like, ``Let's
do it,'' and I was like, ``Let's do it'' and I was like, ``Let's do it'' and I was
like, ``Let's
do it'' and I was like, ``Let's do it.  I wonder if there are any
jokes that I don't know if it's okay or not.It
's like, ``Two people, Kita Tokoro-san, 3 people, haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa child around the pen-like thing that happens to me.I see.
a
Yoshi prevention setting I
entered and sensei-senpai around senpai with me
Anh Okaa-
senpai re-entered as reason bag
ces
deren
cheer
rear
entered bkos porridge senpai
asme stable garden scene by day
puso n-senpai to
do angels dm wow figure
brand people are  you
do too Eppisodoa
Nakkaeeeeika episode
[Music]
Sato
Mokoro is currently
taking a break from streaming.
Hmm, let's spend the night together in a little while and
help us plan things.Hmm, that's
great, and I want to do a lot of things that Kokoro-san wants to do.Yosa,
Sea Hill qualifying bye.I
also care about the coronavirus.  Because I'm here
Ran Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa that
me to do
all Pingu
[Music]
Do by Taaaaaaaaa Corone Senpai sb
When I was Chaffee Senpai Open Fog
Okayu Senpai sw Plush and
listen to Nyaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaato
tt apis
order kamaru
year  The
fishermen's association has disappeared.Enter
Next
question.a I
heard that Okayu-senpai once lacked confidence in his own voice and singing activities.
But now there are a lot of cover songs, and there
are also original songs. Was there a reason for you to do that kind of thing?
oo
Yeah,
well, this must have been true in the first place. I don't know what it is, but it's
not like I have a really amazing voice.  I thought, ``I
like stabbing songs, but I didn't think they were normal.''
But
then I joined a professional live show, and I started
doing onigiri with that person, and now I'm like this.
There are people like this who go overseas and come to see me a lot, and
people like me who have a really good voice like porridge, and thanks to you, I can
sleep a lot better.It's amazing that
listening to this voice makes me do my best in all kinds of things.  The
person taking my place praised me so much
that I thought there was something I could do for everyone, and I wish I
could give something back to everyone who is supporting me even a little like that.  I
guess
that's why I began to sing songs for preparation, etc.
So I guess I've become more confident in my own voice
?
Well, it's more than that, because
there are people who are looking for my voice.  I
guess I've started to think that my voice should be better. I
see. com The cat got on the desk, and
Mac convulsed for 5 seconds.
Hey,
down that hill. My senior is here.  I'd
like to say hello to Takemura-cho Kui.
Senpai.
Okay, let's do an error life.
Panamera
neu yfc how to do in
the ace
lea lea
web to do away Harley
fake fur
rexd scarfless eeveevo 2 pou
dou dou
Manufacturer
Special Dasmeer 4S
One to One High Voice
XU-like Hass is perfect
Hurry up, it's Affi, it's cafe,
porridge.That pronunciation from last time is possible.Flow
chart flo s There are
people who say they really like Zuno Wakaba.Happy
1009 election.The
wall called Poison.Hmm, Uchiha,
Okaya Senpai's public management.  I
thought it was really soothing. Really
a
happy
jane carr min aye ai
glee season stroller miboisu muto
seriously so sweet  It's
sweet and sweet to take away.
Wow, I like that one from the Japanese public morals.
That's what Lidi said.
Well,
Buddha, what did you finish it with? That guy's money
,
electronic carp set point, pen line,
toilet bowl, etc.  Hey, I'm
listening to Daikonja's song,
so I think the next route will be blue too.
Who is the Vocaloid p that you like and would like to recommend,
and how do you
decide which
songs you would like to have a wider range of songs?If you like Vocaloid p, yes, the
Vocaloid p that you would like to recommend.P
wrote my first original song.
This is a song that Mr. P covered by Vinocchio, who was so interested in P that it made him hungry. That
's right.
I've been listening to a lot of vocaloid songs, and I guess I'm pretty good at singing,
but the range of songs I can sing is actually quite narrow.I'm not
really good at songs with overly high-pitched melodies, so I'm not really good at it.  I
wonder if you'd like to cover a song that you can sing with your own voice and that you really like.
Okay Mr.
Hiroshi. Hmm, I'd love to go to the place, hehe, Pale Blue.
I had a Prius voip lamp ebp
p coenzyme
meter my left arm Kusumi O's son yen a
offset 4 companies 3 fatal cushion guarantee out of which is
weak Outer is I'm
cute selection Proust 4 N support shoes
size  was able to ro
ri
soares series herb ore
to do c sensor c pinch pub
swing form error
reiter hi rose red
one for sentence time 4 ce car
chair 2 points seonghwa c face
with blue stone line ct
voice na loud amp
micro There
are a lot of people who make vocaloid songs in really high keys It's
hard to lie
anand When I saw the second live menu, I was like,
Chlorine Nsaa
A Pocamp's first mix-friendly exhaust
Black rock shoes or something
Hey, if you have a lot of fun, go to the government
No, no,
no, house winning genes are station uc  2 glasses of
Keith traffic Good Sherm 30,000 What do you
say about Wands I see
a
abuilding
pet pet
next
jaan a
mom fano as round well it seems
like it's really very popular Okai Senpai 1 a What do you
like about wandering and what kind of things do you like about it?
For those who haven't heard of Ace Maru being shown off, please explain.
What I like about Iisei Maru is that it
makes me sleepy too, so after that.
Wow, I wonder if it makes the taste or cooking even harder for me. I'm
doing Welcab nails while leaning on my sister Mike. Oh yeah, I
see.
Yeah, I
'm calm, but 8 How do I do it? Hmm,
I'm not very good at making raw marls.  I
don't have anything like that, so I'm
talking about something like that, and I'm
just scratching my ears endlessly.
4 o
Ponun
[Music]
Noon, I
think it's only for members.  I
wonder
if Sakuraan is a little sister or a yandere or something like that. I want to hear about her beautiful surf.
There are people who say that big sister Amengen is dangerous.
Allen Geller's smile is kind of in the zone h,
right?  Is it okay for a couple of seconds se
Caption form pip hit ia
home
uscpa
renren
us army
das
preserver for star
leisure paper style p
to
do go to menu
pointing graffino ras op
pod uce starkson ah 2 min
4 s center sweet wing wii
party u do me patio
winter umm
ren for the pain 4 mmc
psy 50 p step windchill cedars a
paro dependent a kind fence defstarn
yac ceiling
dela
standerd
0 a place pointer nas
char you
do ecchy
[music]
fence 4 s compatible asomin
webshop souther
web  Font Park 1
Take off Shumai Blue Du Philippines The number of problems
is high The government is right Let's
join the membership I mean, that was
disbanded and this
Yuna was rubbed but there are
many Aso Tsuki Sailors  The clothing worn in Star 4 City is
Ishida style drinking One Point
Two Five Maine State 5
Did you notice that registrant
ranked 22nd with 1.25 million people?
Ah, thank you very much, but my 9009 sister
tried to commit suicide. R Jeanne and her sister tried to commit suicide. It wasn't
broken. It wasn't broken.
Oh my god, I just streamed my stomach. I wonder if it was you. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's for sale. It's a
loose inator. Aru
Ezaki's.  Thanks to you, I was able to sleep.
Maybe there's no merger group. If not, then Nomura. Don't you think it's
Rapika already done?
[Music]
2 pieces
anoano
Why don't you give your free time to the doctor?
Tomorrow, the members of Kanai Hanshin might not do it. Tomorrow, the Atsumori bastards will be tenor and unhappy. The
organizer has thousands of possible ovations. Steamer is
amazing 2 ccn
over Suchi Spoon &  Parsen's wife has a good brain.
Yay, will of hair. Suti. You can
put on and take off your clothes. It
doesn't matter what you want, you can take your time.
That's right, Chiara. Thank you for congratulating me.  That's
fine,
oh oh
oh oh oh oh, I don't notice
it. It's a little kids floods I notice or face cat.
Okay, let's take a look at
February's questions.Test
In the morning, the seniors have been active as original members,
and have been active as much as all of you
.
Hey, please tell me about your next goals and dreams. That's
right.
Well, I guess I'd call it a goal or a dream.
But,
hmm,
what I realized the other day is that I really
want to make my daily broadcasts really interesting.
After all, I hope to be able to stream something every day so that everyone who comes to see me
goes home thinking, ``Today was fun,'' and thinking, ``I laughed a lot.'' So, hmmm.
In a nutshell, my future goal is to further improve my gag sense.
desperate Arthur Oop
Lens Sub itc worth
parano
rearrange
ios Buy Jeonghyebin and issuer It's
true that this is the answer typical of that senior mom,
but if she can't release an album, Mom...
Maybe I want to do a concert or not. Well, I
would be very grateful if I could do something like that. I don't think so, but it's fine. I can only focus on what's right in front of me. When that happens, of course it's amazing. I'm grateful and happy, but the only
thing I can do now is take the first step.  As we move forward step by step, what we
need to do is to improve our daily conversation, right?
I see.
Shui Nousai
ffc 1 to
do
oranger
carender arm can o 2
o 4 s  an ping surfer
hurdle face with wife
[ __ ] the boo
boo
sabae green 4 s army
[music]
do degen good
total 1000
meow ok I think it's good that's
it entrance radish slowly slowly I
enjoyed it
Diva zone
enjoy av  day
as much as pass pawn
then
this is the last question
remodel
rear wing 4 s 4 a ra
ap up ape
That's right saj
A Well, this is the last question, but after that,
there are times when the performance of the song is interrupted,
so I hope it's still there.A
For the seniors,
Horo Live
is the only thing that seems to be my other color.It's everything about me.  Well, it's
already the worst so so long bay
birdie 8 f 4 ab Spain
ise pressure Wow
Bach is always there I don't want to lose it I guess it
's Navi, isn't it?
Well, I think that I
would like everyone to listen to the dark people after the
song of such a porridge senior fire.
Shobuhiuuuuuuuuui
League Losing Performing Ah, Ah, Ah,
Mejiro, 3 Cuttings, and Maona
If you
put some mayonnaise on some idiot Pabach's struggles, it
'll taste good. Even if you cry, I'll still be
hungry. I'm sorry I couldn't digest it. I'm sorry,
but I'll buy you something sweet and eat it.
Sorry for the inconvenience.  At the end of the day, I'll
listen to the doctors and make it into a heart bomb and
swallow it.Ah, now I'll spill tea on the information overloaded dress and
Lame and Patty's menu, and I
'll set up Modi with you.
Magma Boo,
gunfight, lose and lose in the middle of nowhere, I
hope for a future where you too become a group of hungry masks. Mag is also a game,
naked mug, before the world ends, yay, it's so
good, God, Milan is just like it is,
it's murmuring darkness.  3
This world has to be tasted, right?
[Music]
Opposition club student Mille-feuille Sando
Roughly seasoning the total number of aurora who wish to remain anonymous
Take it with a grain of
salt. If it tastes good, it's ok.  OK, I've
eaten a lot of good and bad
food, and now I'm wiping my mouth.The pizza chef, Noriko Colorful Cos, is
still suspicious.Ah, after the attack on Soryu, the
bar utensils are sorting out poisonous and poisonous ones.With
you.  Mag bending It's a bending mug.The number of teachers in the game
is bending.
You too. I hope you can survive the wet construction work.
Simulated bending.
Tsuneko is also in this place.  Key
Majitami
Tonight's dinner is a
mumbled darkness Majikami
Next it's your turn
Mogumoguyo 3 Majikami
Yam,
do it as it is Momoguguya
p Serjikami
Enjoy this world Delivery mah
Magemagemage lose lose lose lose lose lose
until the end  But darkness,
positive winding, winding, losing, losing, losing, losing, losing,
winding, bending, magma, winding, winding, winding,
winding, winding, winding, losing, losing, setting mop.
Lose, lose, lose, lose, lose, lose, lose, lose, lose,
lose, first of all, Miyagi
yeah
me,
thank you very much,
aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa  I
understand d too. It made me
understand. The device is great.
So Sue-san at Worlds
Karasuyama, bring your wig.  s It's
like they're singing Good Words
[Music]
[Laughter]
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
well, they're going to perform. Dads,
Iida and the wall a. Porto, I'm here to interview Uruto Ward.
How was it?
Really, Nandroki Ara-
chan is an easy person to talk to, even though she came from a foreign country. She
gets excited a lot, so it
felt really good to talk to her.
Oh
caren  Joy Tsudesu Apis
Resentment Overseas B
Oaza
Saaakaan type noas Daily
Pfister NBA I'm piggybacking consecutive holidays NBA It's a
dangerous parrot meow, but it's
not over yet It's still a long way from now Since it's the 1st
anniversary, I've prepared a special sound clipping
So, everyone, please watch it together.I
want Eisai to greet me in German.I wonder if that's okay.
Oh, the payment line is good for the blue villas. A
good arc with the blue fader.
Jump out. The
blue wizarding, Cao Cao, the entertainment floor. sa.
Blue Star, bye bye. Epice. Garden.
Dosu doppel grandma going.
Please use the bridge turn and
tweet your impressions.
It's a charm
day. Aoueda Day
[Music]
If only there was, it would be a
lie Wan Meow 4 layer paint Pulse-like Next Next, the
scenery of the lure and the right arm is blocked
Wes Seekers word
processor p Farmy xh Sca
bar end sports brother, let's take a look
Change the masu Thank you senpai Oh, the
street is so
[Applause]
ok
adas de bar in x car
wedge
Do you like Amelia's pose?
A 1 dive melon love
Let me show you Japan, I'm a pick-me-up guy,
haaaa. It's too embarrassing, so I'm a fun girl too. If I
see it, Ichikawa will definitely stand in the same government. Is
n't that a dream? It wo
n't be possible this time, but someday.  I
want to stand together with Dai. I'm
definitely
watching this. Ueokapi Illustrators. Wow.
Please write down the swimsuits of Chara-chan and that operator.
But I'm curious about what kind of swimsuits Permanent will wear.
Well, I'm not surprised until the return.  teeth  I
compared the Guardiner, March 7,
a little bit of a pin, PIMP version of PIMP
4 wins and right arm Ah, oh,
but I
got a hot water, but Yoro -chan's swimsuit
That v cut is low,
that key no swimsuit was on, oh
good
[Music]
Please remember a certain peer Oze Payon's
well dopia
Onomatopoeia table 4 e
now onomatopoeia
Eh,
0 drinking bar
a Dream is an
onomatopoeic word Waiting for an onomatopoeic word I
don't know what that means First of all, it
's ramen, but in the old days Mikasa Kiao Ah Okay,
okay, bye-bye, people say I'm sick Ah,
they're attractive, they've got
big boobs.  -Dad The
reason why I chose him as my partner for that first collaboration was because
at the time, he was such a great senior, and he was such a
fun and cheerful person, and we got along well.
I was wondering if I could do it,
but that's exactly what happened just now. Well,
one more thing would be nice, too.
As a member of the bird race, I
think we're having a lot of fun getting used to each other.
But when I first started, I didn't live 2 d
like I said before,
so I guess I
have a complex in Japan about my luck and being in the spotlight.  It was a
good time to be creative, and I didn't really have
much self-confidence.Thanks
to going overseas, I was able to get a lot of people to
see me.Was
this 3D woman of mine very
popular?  Things like sakura and noon
moon
in have been
recognized as their identities.Hmm, there's
no way I thought of myself as a cat either.  I'm
looking at the rock gorilla-chan in wait.
Winter we are n Mel. I
think you've recently started studying English, Anko English.
Karan, tell me your favorite English words.
3rd place. Even so, I can still understand things like "i
love you."  Monjihona
noon It
seems simple, it
's a nice word, and I like it because both
Japanese and overseas people can understand it.Next
time, please introduce Chiara's aroma, if not the movable true one.I think
orange or tax would be better.
Ah, the orange looks perfect, hmm. I wonder
if it's the aroma of the management coming from the sink. But then, I
meet a little chicken. It's
like a spice, so meow. My
Navy is good. Get rid of the comet. Wow. Looks like it would fit.
Convenient happy secure.
That's why s. Former senior.  I wonder
if you would say that the psychopath water is called Kvass.
But it really makes me think that Chara Boun Kyun often says
that Okame Sua's water senior is a psychopath at all.  I do
n't think so.Sledding
field: It's
not like the whole thing is going to happen if you wake it up.Well, it's
fine.FM hi.Space
Rover,
fast.Pop on.Can you
understand it in English?
Airhead
Haruhei0That's over.Bach, Hey,
air.  air
after
air no hane ga
north I
don't know, I don't know what it is, but
that girl's...  I
boiled moko balls without flour, but wow
! Hey, I've never met anyone in Ameshida's house. That's an
unusual name. I've never
met someone who turned around when I heard the three letters of the 725th class tree car.
But
ano hi, it
's good that everyone thinks car intermediaries are cleaning and pharyngeal smarts, isn't it? He's the best guy among all of you.
2nd place I don't think
this is the
success or failure story of this one leg How many times have I been running I wonder if I do
n't know that I want a
process There's a
space in between Im up It Committee
Chesty I think I'm going to be defeated
[Music]
ana
rar
It's a fake array fiber, isn't it? I'm sorry, I'm sorry.  It
's the building No. 1. I don't understand. I
don't understand the owner. I won't take it away,
but I think it's cute that he doesn't shave his head.  How to be, it's fine, it's
a moon-like
alphaville, pains
add up, it's a cute Hawaiian Honjo,
right? I see,
ah
abcd a good
h i j k l m n o b class ah
at
uv
dwf
wine tax
This day and the speed of sound gigantic bear fake fur
wars clip 2 I
have a question that reminds me of the
same board jacket store. That's why I'm
angry
because it's a cutting board. I'm putting on
that bandage and wearing a bag. I
have a difficult problem because nothing moves when I run.  I don't have it, but that doesn't mean I
don't have it now. [Music] Hmm, I guess it would have been better to run.
[Music]
People who couldn't handle the Ron system were bookmakers, right?
This character has been doing that Ankei survey many times,
but
on Twitter, even after bathing, the 50 Park is
made fun of, Chopper is made fun of Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa, 50 park  The
hood 1 haha
5 means 8 It's the best place that has changed the scenery I see. I've
put on a cherry blossom wall, and I'm
playing with double the amount of wavy leakage.
[Music]
Oh.  I'm
in Yomiuri,
but I couldn't say it because of the language barrier.Have you ever been
reluctant to tell someone overseas? Especially so,
of course. Hey,
there's something I need to tell you.
Also close up and press it. Many of the
early towns are
new. I have a
loose heart. It's
better to go overseas.
Pen type.  I'm
so nervous, uhm, Miku, I
feel like it's time for me to play around with my senior run,
but I'm already talking a lot about this dog.I was
just watching that video of mine, too.  I was
going to see the
spring song that was over, and I was so nervous because it was so out of the blue, and it was
so impressive, like I was just sitting there,
and it felt like it was completely different from what it is now.
E-chan Encyclopedia 2 Before we met, you
sent me a birthday illustration,
which made a great impression.Before we met, I
received a smile.A
very
funny episode.It was so funny.
I don't think there's an episode where I was happy even though I won.Um, I'm a 2nd gen, I'm a
2nd gen, right?I'm a 3rd gen.I feel like I sacrificed myself to Nandesu.  It
's written in ``
Oyomo mode chocolate daikon radish'
' is a newbie, so ``Shinjuku Bach'' is Shinjuku Bach.If
there were 1000 people there, we would be
Baby
Babuba 6. What are you talking about?
Where do you get 3 hatchets?
Ah, you
have gills and you're not a feminist who touched me.
Please stop jamjigwang. It's the last time. I'm going to start
reciting sutras. Please stop doing it.
On that day, I kept a steady hand on my nerves. My
first impressions
were: What were you all like?
[Music]
Oh, what
? I was so excited to be working with such cute girls.
Hey,
cat!
[Music]  ]
Calf function
Henna donai ya Jai ​​2
Please play Bach, my husband burns Ogura.
i Turn answer goo meet
green green
Why did I think you were wearing pants
? I recognized the rice in Ennoshita.
I'll leave it to your imagination.
none
big h The part is plastered [
music]
]
N
study me
Double 52
Open the sentence Blue Water Mibu Moe
Confusion is still rice
Study 2
Thank you for your life. From now on, I will do my
best to evolve further.
dere
n
minutes
[Music]
Yeah Nn
Yeah
[Music]
Nn
Boof
n me [Music] Boof no me
Yeah
me
[Music]
Buuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu
Nn
me nn nn
me