everybody
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
oh
it's allowed
okay do you hear the switch
um I hear the switch yeah we're on
stream now
we're live we're live live
[Music]
here okay okay okay now you should hear
better
why are you so loud
I'll turn it really quiet because it's
annoying me
yeah hello everybody
can you hear us can you hear us
hey that's my intro
that's my intro my name is yay
[Music]
my name is
yeah and then there's me
guys is this is the audio okay like for
me it sounds like everything's not well
balanced but I hope it's more balanced
on
the on the viewer side I think I can't
hear myself but yeah it's hard it's it's
hard to hear ourselves um if we're
screaming then we're it's because we
can't hear ourselves
[Applause]
looking to the right because my
microphone how about the bgm the game
bgm
when they say it's really low but for us
it's really loud
[Music]
because we are reusing like studio
equipment that I don't really know okay
uh well well actually I can't help wait
wait do you know this thing
how do I bring down but the thing is
like you know it okay they made it so
that the switch is only a monitor hold
on hold on your monitor
all right the system oh actually
Thailand's trying to fix it
make it better I mean there's no no it's
already working there's just it needs
Improvement that is Monitor and um
but then it's so loud
okay maybe in our ears
we need to like you know get in the
switch voice to the uh-huh that thing
oh but we can't wait wait I mean I mean
you know Japanese everything's Japanese
I mean uh you know what if anything we
can we can I have personal down yeah
yeah
on the mic on the mic yeah yeah we put
it we put it like this yeah no no the
Minecraft
but it's good
yeah also the headphone is too big for
me I'm having one ear out yeah
or hold on if uh well we can we can put
down the microwave like this okay this
one no sound if like this yeah but then
we have no games oh okay
what if we like put all our headphones
down we will not hear our voices but we
can put the Switch music really loud for
the chat so that it's like actually that
they hear yeah well if it's not just
hear it faintly yeah yeah okay yeah if
it echoes then okay if it goes then who
cares let's go and I will want to be so
bad okay time to collect your headphones
come here oh you can keep someone one
over there so you hear it you want oh no
no
guys don't don't be mad at me she put it
all the way to the loudest attacking
that was Kyla okay let them here let
them here
[Music]
see there's still sound proof like you
can barely hear
but a little bit you should put one over
there
do you need to lose
this oh we can barely hear from this one
one hour technical one hour
we can't we oh this one this one just we
can just blast it on we just put it
here
on our neck you want to be choked by
this headphone it's like a muffler you
know what actually right yeah actually
just put one here no
[Music]
I mean even for this game the sound I
mean I don't think it matters
guys it's really funny and he will like
you know say funny things oh actually
the horse has a name
um
when I was searching for the PNG for the
horse the horse has a name but it's
already good now they're saying that
it's already good yeah it's good for
them but not good not ideal for really
let me know one of them let me just add
a little bit she can hear it just a
little bit
I mean this one is fine this one is fine
this one this one is not too long
vertically to play yeah this one is not
too loud really
yeah okay okay I'm gonna I'll put it
I'll put it on my neck like a necklace
yeah okay sorry guys it's choking me is
it is it is it fine now
okay
then in case you didn't know guys
there's uh this game I played it before
it was like football and so on and it's
like really fun and they brought out a
game a version that's for more than two
people and people were making fun of it
in the Nintendo Direct why and because
it's like who needs this and I'm like I
need it
[Applause]
I need it
I I think I might have played this once
with quality Senpai but I don't know but
I don't know if it was
um the same version or not so I know
we'll see
horse cute though
Kyla is on the very edge wait wait
because
um that guy's in the middle ah okay okay
I needed to be realistic
oh we oh I am actually in the middle
yeah but you know the controller I am
the second
oh I don't it's okay it's okay two three
two three two three two three two three
or we can switch control nah the names
never mind it's fine it's fine okay then
are you girls ready to have some
International
Indonesian Austrian
[Music]
oh this one is random okay
nice
yes
[Music]
I wanted the green guy let's go let's go
I'm funny
[Music]
it
is
oh yeah use the joy-con yeah so we can
do like a team contest
um but then like how are we even gonna
split the teams right because we're
three people one person would be alone
I'm not sure if that works like that but
we also have the option of like a quiz
party where it's more like questions
because I don't want to do that then
there's a bingo party bingo party
device is the Bingo but we don't want to
use the smart device no no so we could
just do other and then just choose the
games for ourselves all the settings
ourselves
they say well Kyla can be two player
okay
[Music]
uh that's fine okay then but I lose my
egg
[Music]
yeah I will I will be careful this time
okay are we seriously going with four
people
because like when we choose Free People
yeah it will just be like you know yeah
exhausting against you okay fine okay I
hope I can get my egg again
Orange
that really reminds me one time uh wait
it was
if I asked me what was it let's go
what's let's go in English and I said
let's go let's go let's go let's go
let's go straight
[Music]
yeah yeah we know you so Kyla is up for
a challenge yeah okay so she's gonna be
up against us but you know we could give
Kyla extra points
for being a smaller team
do you want more points or or little
points nah little points is fine
yeah really
I remember just playing this for fun
it's just okay I think this is not okay
okay
let's go
let's go but I think it's gonna be red
oh okay it's a control stick on your
channel okay
ah uh the larger team will have an
advantage in some games not everything
yeah not always seems okay well she's
two people yeah that's two people
used to controllers so that I can be
like two people no but then it's a it's
a two feet
I'm Kyle and Ella it says one person
here yeah that's why we need to do like
four pieces
always separated on the on the OBS too
yes yeah more or less okay
let's go there's new games in here
[Music]
lots of fun okay
let's go oh oh oh okay okay I've never
played this
this is different version what is this
what time
team contest
eleven
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
you gotta win you gotta win for a couple
oh
once
[Music]
uh nobody's scared of clouds are you
scared
not really except
how biggest balloon wins okay how to
pump like like this
okay this way yeah but like this do we
have to press anything
where's Horus
the balloon
I think if you if you pump it too much
it
how blow up your balloon
is this is this a bigger balloon pass or
what no
um we'll see I'm gonna pop it until it
Pops Pops
I get him Pump It Up
and Down okay okay
press wood
wait wait I'm scared are you
oh I'm done press wait what press what
press this this is
[Music]
constantly press yeah
just constantly press it okay oh oh this
is scary I don't know when I don't know
just let me help it
[Music]
oh it goes away
maybe one more
foreign
done okay
I think
bigger no no no no no no no no I think I
think it's the same maybe I don't know
she can't be bigger we can't let her be
bigger
[Applause]
[Music]
I'm just a little bit bigger
okay okay here we go okay
hey
[Music]
sorry it's okay
well we have just begun so yeah yeah we
just begun there is so much more to come
maybe we can try balloon
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
it's you left team oh press a button
that's nice
okay
the next game will be squads
okay well it doesn't really matter any
game is fine we're in the kitchen now
are you ready to play yes
[Music]
kitchen timer
what what
oh yeah are we gonna kick
welcome to the cooking account okay make
sure your aprons are securely tied
this time you'll be trying your hand at
making the perfect sizzling sirloin
steak sirloin steak
my spiders
[Music]
the steak is done flip it over okay are
you all ready
wait what
and what about the teams
how do we know when it's done we have
two
looks like you're all finished wait what
yes that's it oh it doesn't show
um like it's like kind of like a secret
yeah we need to guess the timer right
yeah yeah and then later on they'll show
us yeah how it was the earliest it was
the latest looks like
okay
every Chef understands the importance of
veggies just flip it and they will
register this has been heated to Boiling
Points
no no just flip it at 10 seconds okay
what do you thinking get set
go
oh it's raining oh
I don't know I don't know I lost count I
don't know I lost count I don't know I
did drain it but I don't know
I've never looked at timer
[Music]
I don't know if it's the right time yeah
Ready Get Set 11 seconds
the last stage is the Clincher you'll
get double points for this one
did you not lift it oh I I I flip it
again
maybe maybe it's fine okay I think it's
fine they registered the movement no
it's not vibrating
oh yeah
kind of failed I didn't read
[Music]
instructions
oh but this is the first game in history
[Music]
we're having kfps for dinner yay
on
it
yeah
[Music]
so the loser of the last game will
decide oh
yeah you get to decide
which one do you want okay
that one looks fun I want the squats oh
my God
[Music]
up
how okay no more headphones
[Music]
keep my headphones
yes okay
I hope you're ready
squat squat okay don't follow any other
cue oh get it oh but we can't hear
it again okay just use it again on your
feet the workout's about to Huggle it do
we hold it like you can also play
sitting down oh just try to sit up no no
we stand no no no no no no no no no no
no it's gonna be harder make sure you
hold your arms out straight ahead
hold your joy-con in both hands
if you're playing sitting down steadily
raise and lower your arms
okay okay okay okay I'm so confused like
do I move oh okay okay so we have it up
you have to press no no no no no no
okay so it's up okay start Squad squash
squash
squash squash Squad oh it's the guy
squash Squad
I don't know
the training right it's so difficult
because it sounds so similar wait I'm so
confused who's the guy and who's the
girl
does not practice I think it was already
[\h__\h]
there were 20 squads get ready to raise
the bar in the second half oh it's
squash and squat oh
[Music]
no oh
my gosh
Squad
squat Squad squat
yeah
squash
I don't know I don't know listening
issue
[Applause]
[Music]
don't show my individual count no no
that's not so bad but like I was so out
of it like the timing was so difficult
yay oh my God
so hard to hear wow
the results
[Music]
I think they have this game
oh I won next game will be
ninja please
all of them we haven't done before
[Music]
okay no
I think
[Music]
I can't stop staring at Horrors don't
move when he's looking okay
don't move out here when he's looking we
have to stand up too I don't know I
think just move this off okay
no problem no problem
s
oh walk
why do I not get the there we go no no
no
that's what team needs
okay to the goal okay okay we need two
people let's go
don't move while he's looking okay
stop looking at me
okay be careful
[Music]
oh yeah
my heart
okay okay we get it now
okay I go faster even the tiniest
movement he picks up yeah I think so
like even when I turn around
when I
went out to freeze
when I turn
around free they're running so much
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] no I can't breathe
come here just keep your console steady
last one zeta last one I'm on my way
creepy
[Music]
and she's already there
[Applause]
[Music]
she needs to win some and she needs to
lose something yeah she wants some
that was so funny
we're like what the [\h__\h] is so fast
how can you be so fast oh
oh
I don't I don't want to see this kid
anymore
I hate this kid I'm sweating I think
they turned up the AC again oh did we
I'll turn it on because I don't think it
will get rich yeah we can't really turn
it on
that's why you need your water stealth
games
will be
um what do you want
you first I guess are you first
are you ready to play hey everybody
[Applause]
[Music]
to greet the aliens
keep the [\h__\h] they say
keep the binge
trying to focus
goodbye
oh okay contact protocols after this
maybe
the guy just came back
my arms hurt
oh
yeah
[Music]
look at their posts
foreign
[Music]
if you can't do it like at the same time
listening issue yeah
okay the workout's about to begin
to begin also play sitting down just try
to sit up as straight as you can no no
no we're standing okay we are standing
no squash make sure to Hold Your Arms
out straight ahead and pay attention to
your surroundings so you don't hit
anything okay hold your joy-con in both
hands then squat
if you're playing sitting down steadily
raise and lower your arms
okay actually squatting okay okay the
real deal face the other no watch out
your arms and
gotta face each other more or less yeah
okay Squad Squad
squat squat squat squat
Square
this is so fun what just happened
okay we have two rounds all right more
or less okay okay
let's go
even higher okay okay higher higher
let's go okay
[Music]
okay Squad stretch out your arms and
start squat
Square no squat squat squat squat squat
highest
come on squat squat
s
Square no spot squat pain nice
[Music]
good
wow
all right one oh I guess I guess it's
like two okay square square
[Music]
it's fine it's okay and then you cannot
literally can't win but you wanna you
wanna two people yeah
the most important thing is we have fun
yeah
draw a card whoa
or something
the chance cards you can draw from wait
what
these oh
yeah wow
[Music]
this one oh my God
let's go wait Kyla did you not want the
points
[Music]
let's go
yeah because like squats will make you
lose
five oh no oh god oh this okay you have
to stand up again okay what
what
okay okay okay okay
let's go I like this okay okay let's go
[Music]
okay okay
he's got the strongest hips
okay let's go
really funny okay
first contenders are
[Music]
oh
hold the joy-con behind your back and
hip level okay keep still wait what
still Kyla wait well keep still hold on
stop moving I'm sorry I cannot oh yeah
oh okay okay with a big butt with your
hips Chad they told me to stay in the
middle so I'm getting his bumps from
left and right they told me to stay in
the middle did you like it I like it
though round one okay there's no Tempo
about this right
come on
[Music]
yeah
let's go okay let's go let's go
yeah okay no press oh yeah now you press
a button anybody okay
hey don't look at me
get the monitor I can't look at it
if I'm facing that way still
it doesn't matter if she sees you oh
okay right oh okay right now give a
small push yeah push with your hip okay
so what's the difference why why do we
need a small push maybe right here
maybe there's some kind of strategy give
a small push just a small yeah one
pushing Big push no yeah but I'd only do
big pushes okay okay opposite side I
think it's fine what do you mean
they look funny
this is cheating she's Silas not even up
facing the opposite side
okay
let's keep it a fair let's keep it fair
let's keep it fair why did they not
choose me I'm the biggest hip in the
world but not close enough that you
actually well I'll call you that though
okay okay
and timing timing still keep the keep a
good like rhythm
put your hips
I can't do this
in the end you won't need it
shouldn't even it should be fine round
[Music]
s
sit down sit down
to be fair my muscles still hurts
it's okay we'll win in other games
that's fine I want the ninja one ninja
okay
stop her let's move on to the next game
[Music]
ninja ninja
do you want to try again oh but it's a
really bad press a button when you want
it to stop no but we can stop it oh yeah
you're present are you gonna sell like
when by the time you yeah
okay I don't know what this is though I
think you'll throw shuriken oh man
or yeah one team Frozen again
the opposing teams throwing stars what
do we get swords or is it again
what is it timing yeah you have to
imagine how long it takes for you it to
reach you you know I think we can look
at it no I don't know you won't see it
you have to guess it are you ready to
play everybody
let's go
do it well when you play oh okay
no no we don't have straps oh
yes
deflect all the throwing stars okay okay
what who is the sword who's the star oh
[Music]
just like this oh okay okay okay okay I
got it I'm gonna eat away my joy-con for
real foreign
to strike but what is the distance like
you hear the throwing stuff when I hear
it shake your joy-con
oh
don't kill me
kill me don't kill me no in my heart
yeah
face your robot
okay I'm looking at you no don't mind me
man I'll put the nice seam when you
throw it then what just oh
is it
oh my God
really yeah
wait what button okay um next go go okay
okay protect my honor no I think you
just have to press me too yeah yeah
oh you're throwing stars oh oh we're
we're throwing that okay look at each
other then oh okay
okay okay
I should use the sound of the throwing
star as a guide for when to strike
okay okay ninjas on the left take aim at
your opponent making sure to give
yourself enough space so you don't bump
into anything oh you just throw it
together yeah no anytime
attacker how is she gonna do that
oh we only have a certain amount of uh
display of swordsmanship yeah I think I
think yeah okay because it said at the
top left like one all one maybe we
should like not Spanish but like just go
yeah like one by one right so I kind of
like pretty good oh
both sides remember to give yourselves
enough space
get ready
six nice
change roll okay
Ninja on the right ready your sword when
you're ready
again but let's not let's shake yourself
but she's pulling down the sword all the
time so I'm gonna
oh okay oh
both sides remember to give yourselves
enough space
begin
s
right I think
no because it's not it's not uh it's not
detecting I think her yeah
my what is it controller is not
detecting yes
button oh did it mean that like Santa
missed Kayla with the Stars
but can I try
um
[Music]
get ready
Kyla just has a really serious face
[Music]
we're gonna continue this forever is it
yeah yeah forever the change roll okay
Ninja on the right ready your sword
[Music]
let's go
I want to see if it detects then yeah
okay
you have to I it won't let us test both
sides remember to give yourselves enough
space oh let's go but get
me okay I'll see you're good
okay
it's hot it's so easy
we all have a long way to go keep
striving
so
we both get like according for the guy
the results are in it's a draw when this
happens the points you could have won
will roll over to the next game oh
really means a win two points
oh no no no no
no no
oh no okay then
[Music]
yeah let's go I think it works even
without chairs though you can just go
like oh okay I think that was how it was
really yeah they don't have chairs how'd
this work I don't know making a circle
and trying to snatch a seat oh wait what
oh
wait maybe we can't do a circle but
maybe we can run on the spot maybe
and then yeah
oh no I mean we can we can just sit on
our chair right right really the last
game ended in a draw
we'll test it test test test test are
you ready to play
what if I fall down for a long time you
have to you have to sit
call me what if I fall down don't I
catch you
try not to be the last one I catch you
we'll be playing a fun game
sit down as soon as the Music Stops okay
rewind oh stand up hold them like this
will do some practice
on your feet push a button
okay when you stand push a button so it
can calibrate when you're uh standing up
push a button
wait what hold your joy-con with both
hands so it's upside down now they now
they know that yeah
sit down
okay why is it so late yeah why is it
taking so late well
checking for everybody see how many
people will be out
okay
[Music]
we yeah
it's so loud
almost fell against the table oh yeah
okay it's not me please help me oh
okay okay
results
[Music]
what do you think of that oh
wow
a big win because I think I saw in the
corner of my eye Kyla was like falling
over on your back to the chair no no I'm
I'm squatting uh um
[Music]
[Applause]
all right team is
that sounds good yeah
oh
yeah
after all that squatting
I don't accept
[Applause]
okay I think the viewers
yeah I use I use once already yeah
it's okay give it back give it back
I saw it in the video
[Music]
let's go
shut up Horus let's go hey why are you
so mean to him though I don't like him
[Music]
for a jump rope contest all right let's
go
you can bring it on Kyla you're the
first to jump
uh oh what what oh wait I should turn
off my shoes
how do you take your shoes off maybe it
gets really fast make sure you're
putting okay pay attention to your
thanks
okay okay so we need to wait for the
ropes right yeah
what do what do you do us too oh wait
what I don't feel too bad I got what
what just happened no I think this is
still practice right
it's still practice right is it already
starting or not I don't know
it is
[Music]
happening it says now at least yeah
once you've got it we'll move on to the
real deal
for real I think that's one okay
three I just already jumped
okay one times two people
yeah can we do more calories
[Music]
more
please
[Applause]
understand
it's okay we can play some like extra
games like just choose ourselves
[Music]
I think
oh what is this oh oh there's so many we
don't know there's a the question marks
are all games we don't know are we oh I
think we need to like unlock it first oh
I wonder we can try we can play the jump
rope one right there we go oh we need to
grinder okay
grinding kind of loves grinding games
yeah grinding I gotta grind this by
myself
let's go let's go let's go let's go I
think you need friends you can't do it
alone
[Music]
make sure
okay three two
it's really loud
don't give up keep on jumping like a
faster
don't stop what do you mean don't stop
what's up
that's that's it go down
29. oh oh
no get some help get some help but for
us we have to switch over jump together
okay okay but I think the price is
okay
[Music]
congratulations
oh
okay okay is there a game that we
haven't tried before ever let's try it
we cannot we cannot oh
we haven't unlocked you know what let's
just add like another like 20 minutes
yeah let's go actually
[Music]
change places should we turn that on
because then there are some games
changing places
okay
this one is disabled it's fine disabled
yeah all right okay is this my world
okay
how about we mix up the teams or mix up
[Music]
what can do
we can do no we can do ID versus Ian
okay
[Music]
wait wait
okay okay
nice without extra points okay sure nice
[Music]
if you're happy type one
say go Papa
we're still Barefoot yeah it's better
this way it's okay free the feet yeah
yeah our feet are more quiet inside oh
okay
[Music]
okay hopefully we get new games okay
let's go you'll get a point oh it's
three three win online
okay this is fun though it's like shorts
anyone can win each other and we can
unlock the new here yeah yeah yeah now
let the games begin
[Music]
because no one lost we couldn't choose
anything
yeah it's okay next time we can cook we
can cook let's go let's go let's go
let's cook
[Music]
sorry don't flip both of the dishes
right flip and lips
[Music]
again it's flip I think do you have
nothing else on the menu nice bit of
steak over a high heat okay when one
side of the steak is done flip it over
okay are you all ready yeah get set go
go
[Music]
they were way later than me let's see
who's right a little cook
let her cook let it cook oh please let's
take a look at how you did
[Music]
it
you know what is because I was counting
in
Germany okay
okay ready yes get set
go
[Music]
oh they were again much later than me
oh especially
it's not detecting I don't know I
imagine I close my eyes yeah feel it
feel it there's a slow down on your
performance
but if I close by
oh
now you know right guys I really got no
clue of time for the best result I can
see from the length of your screen yeah
um it's hard to count okay
the last stage is the Clincher you'll
get double points for this one
at the same time now you were waiting
for me
I'm I'm just waiting foreign
[Music]
eight
okay
can we get the quiz show loser girls
from now on oh not the questions okay
oh
[Music]
show
get your thinking caps on let's go okay
let's think let's think how to pick
let's think you better keep a clear head
on top of my head
start with what is this pressing the
buttons for true and false answers
we have to press it now
press it down press both buttons now oh
the Press Box
[Laughter]
no thanks
what's a sport where players kick the
ball with their feet nice oh no
yes what oh like that
[Music]
I thought it's gonna be like one two
answer
okay okay
nice nice I can do this question too no
they said suck
which pulls on a magnet attract each
other
negative and negative
damn that I I don't think that's what
they were gonna say I thought it was
North Pole yeah
[\h__\h]
two times
it could still be anyone's game is it
gonna be hard double that's cheating
okay a greeting you'd use before noon I
don't know it's in English
good morning
okay no problem I think I was the first
baby good time
there we go
so we've got time for today see you next
time
Morgan
okay I'm on the same level okay okay no
problem
because the points are a little bit
unfair but no problem
ain't nothing new
show number two I don't know they're
talking like literally so many games and
they don't give us the new one yeah I
don't know why I'm ready to stop the
room
but I kind of want
even though it's unfair to me I want
more questions
we just have to stand up and if I get
the last question and I get double
points okay
[Music]
okay
it's time to find out we picked the
picture okay oh picture start with try
pressing the answer okay it's a bit
different this time
I'm sorry I'm blind
come on
which is
male
okay I think I picked the wrong one
I think I'm late
let's go okay look at that
oh
my birthday that's oh that's a that's
not a woman yeah like a female
I know I know I just click anything fish
I want just the wrong way
[Music]
we have one main cell it's fine tell me
the point don't get those guys
they're so confused right now but they
got the spirit
right facing
oh oh I'm bad with her
no
no we'll see I guess
well I don't know what just happened but
okay
oh no why did I work so hard in the
first two rounds
it's oh my God no we need more quiz
more quiz
[Music]
I think we'll get this until they're out
of this shows okay should we do another
question yeah
three all right all right okay I hope
now they actually won the quiz I hope
you get it wrong again
[Music]
okay let's go okay what notices we get
it right now yeah
no stupidity okay
okay that's no stupidity what is this is
it still with pictures or something else
okay what's this now what's this now
please no math please
oh
Wow
[Music]
first question
what law is mentioned three times
okay okay okay I like that kind of map I
like it I like it that's the mask yeah
okay all right
but you're still like leading yeah yeah
purchase with five dollars what I don't
speak dollars it's 455.
someone was really fast too no no I
think
I think I got it yeah
skills
yeah it's not 460.
okay okay
that's four 902 a.m is
8 58 A.M
returns
oh [\h__\h]
well at least we got it right
at least we got it right it wasn't
formed me being alone I would have won
this game
nice oh time for today today
[Music]
the final game is over here are the
results yeah
[Music]
I'm a lucky charm
nice
can we do one more short one yeah but
[Applause]
[Music]
let's go
okay
[Music]
oh use the control stick on you okay
okay
nice round baby let's go let's go it's
in the wins again even though she's
alone yeah no no no no no no no no no no
no I can't win alone of course you can
no solo no if you pick the right uh okay
[Music]
okay good exercises I want to play the
balloons okay I haven't done that in a
while oh no okay we can do that unless I
have something new
[Music]
yeah
more statues I want the the looking one
when the games begin
[Applause]
okay we can't choose here oh we can't
there's no jump rope apparently I'm
really bad
Chihuahua please okay
no clock switch this is difficult
things are securely tied
okay
[Music]
it's the same
this is ring it's the same order every
single time over a high heat
when one side of the steak is done
amazing
get set
go
uh
I might be late
I might be late I kind of I lost track
of time I don't know me too
I'm just getting hungry
wow
[Music]
I will never be able to do this okay
this has been here just like a boiling
point yeah be sure to drain it at the
right time okay are you all ready no
well yeah get set
[Music]
like a little little spring
all right here's the lowdown oh no
performance oh no
but we can still win if we combine our
powers
[Music]
get set
up here
the last stage is the Clincher you'll
get double points for this one
said that was fast yeah that was fun I
don't know I don't know I think that's
11. yeah
I don't know I didn't count
I think I was a little bit too fast yeah
I think so dude look one second oh there
we go
[Music]
everything
okay
let's go
[Music]
okay maybe they have new balloons
and the question is why we keep standing
up actually but it's fine it's okay it's
fine it's okay we're just getting some
videos let's go we stand I can't like
slouch on the chair yeah
let's go let's go do you also always sit
like this oh like blow up your balloon
until just before it pops
right oh oh we press it yeah
okay remember
don't pop it I want to pop it okay no no
popping fill the balloon with it that
was really good at this I think no it
was you Sr buddy
oh yeah yeah
got that then let's play Hey brown one
press the button
first balloon is
this one okay
[Music]
let's go
stop yes stop stop stop stop stop stop
stop stop right there that's already
perfect wait let's look bigger than that
no no no we're perfect it's good though
yeah we are perfect it's kind of like 99
I think
should be 98.99
[Music]
so close
so close good very good one
yeah okay okay
who adds the Finishing Touch no stop uh
hold a little bit
more
um I I can leave the finishing touch to
you Kayla okay okay ready here we go
okay okay
[Music]
[Applause]
the team is losing
[Music]
as long
because
she will get the blank one
um
and one negative heart
it's fine it's okay it's okay just one
this one
[Music]
foreign Paul
nah come on okay but they have different
it's kitchen
we make pasta now I don't know or or do
uh we can do the jumper yes yeah because
I'm really bad at it
will win
this one this is not the final thing no
no no
Ella will carry the jumper okay but true
but if one messed up everybody oh [\h__\h]
oh no
if one messed up okay I will look at you
and I'll jump at the same time as you
okay okay oh yeah they're looking at
each other
oh
yeah
okay let's go
[Applause]
see how far
three two
okay so either I mess up Kyla's score
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
I like
I think I think the problem is your head
is shaking you need to keep it like
steady steady
but it's fine it's fine yeah better Zeta
can win actually you know no no you can
win three times
[Music]
[Applause]
okay okay let's go let's go game should
we do the hips or something like that
there's nothing new right
[Music]
we can do this one no um well
okay
[Music]
no no no no don't do the hip bomb no no
no but I didn't
nice why not
I'm good at the heat pump I think I want
this one are you ready to play
one two
yeah okay let's go
let's go okay
okay let's go let's go
above the battle of the butts the bottle
[Music]
use your hip movements to knock your
opponent out of the ring
[Music]
I can't even bend over
pressed
[Music]
you have to win bro get the best oh yeah
unless you're on your feet
stand back to back but not close enough
that you actually burp into one another
last time who won when you were again
you lost oh yeah true okay okay
give a little push with your hips
smaller smaller push small push okay
okay
I'll just do it like this because let's
go a little bit sprained round one
ready let's go
oh it works
okay
[Music]
okay now it's me again okay let's go
oh press the button okay
everybody calm down everybody calm down
oh come down okay [\h__\h]
so okay okay what does that mean that
means we can choose one more game like
separately
it's just one more game if you get
things great next up I'm gonna need you
to give me your names oh no just just
just press anything I think but I I had
this for a moment
[Music]
a different game nice
what did you press this one yeah because
I was because I was holding it because I
was holding it like this yeah okay you
want to like left right right yeah left
right
it's fine okay
again
[Music]
so we can do differently we don't have
to do the uh hip game we can't do the
game because
we can do
it was fun I'm a cactus Ah that's the
one
sushi sushi
yeah choose yours
I love oranges oranges I'm orange do you
like fruit yeah I love fruits I eat them
for breakfast all the time nice one two
three
twins what if what if ten people
participate did I say one two three yes
do quiz they say do quiz
[Music]
just a quiz show
okay first things first you
well that's like a whole like quiz like
season we're playing oh really yeah a
medley of mindfulness oh wait there's
the whole season welcome to the course
like you know like several times let's
see not only one time but like many
times
delete the quiz you'd like to play
challenge a mix of questions
combo quiz come here
they can't see it the quiz party
his categories put together okay and
together oh it's not against each other
to start with is it try pressing the
buttons
against each other so this one is not a
theme anymore it's a it's a team press
I've already pressed
okay yeah yeah okay
let's go
[Applause]
it's okay it's okay oh general knowledge
General no everyone needs to know this
right
let's go
two seconds
two seconds okay
rock beats
scissors
I think I'm kind of late I think I'm
kind of late I got it right though and
then I got it wrong
favorite rock paper quiz show I should
be playing alone
your stomach or your spine
oh well spine
which one
but spiny's in the middle
okay okay okay oh same time you press it
together
in the middle oh it's not in three wait
well yeah in the middle and in the back
a greeting you'd use when it gets dark
is
good morning good morning
oh you little [\h__\h]
I mean it could be good afternoon
depending if it's dark or not yeah
possibly it depends on the time zone in
the time yeah
[Music]
brain teasers five days after Friday
[\h__\h] know
Thursday
I think it's Wednesday right it might be
Wednesday
do you guys keep track of things no
that's right we got it right
now okay
[Music]
hi what's this nine months from
September
June
maybe maybe
are you I don't know I didn't count I
didn't come
it might be it might be
done
I didn't even count I'm just guessing
let's see where okay stand okay please
help results oh wow really I was like
nice one
turn things around oh I got one wrong
[Music]
then choose the one that's the correct
answer as quick
answer within three oh it's the One
Direction
um
which
don't lay eggs
okay okay okay okay that scared me fish
eggs so yeah okay
you would think it was something about
witches five which is free or so because
it was five bites and three fish or
something
it has nothing to do with that question
seven hmm
I think the adult is what me not in the
room
wow amazing oh I'm late
I'm late
for a moment in my head I even thought
it was a separate like animal oh but
it's like yeah baby adult
witch has
four legs
what Nanny what's her face has like a
really embarrassed face did you get it
wrong oh really whoa
what
is you know there's a lot of chickens in
the chat
you should know oh no
I'm sorry for her I'm apologizing
explain I'm sorry guys I'm sure some of
them have questions
they're just hiding it
a minute is 60 seconds but
60 days long wait what I'm impressed
ice
a man of this
song guys let's go
yeah let's go guys oh
guys starting from today starting
day she doesn't understand it's a 60
days long Here Comes let's go here comes
that explains a lot
[Music]
fabulous no
no
do you think so
do you think I deserve the massage
have you ever gotten a massage in Japan
oh never they're they are so joy-con to
pick the quiz and they ask so detailed
like where does it works
they give you an iPad and you have to
choose
so don't focus on that it's really good
but yeah nice one
that was so much fun
this is a good game
right here nice nice I want to play this
more I I want to like unlock all of the
games you should you should get it and
then do lots of off collapse of it
because it's all really yeah I'm
planning to like you know play it by
myself
no oh that would be a bit difficult but
you can try it I mean you could try I
mean
all right it's more fun when you have
played with someone else no you can't do
it because then the the news yeah and
stuff you yeah I can oh I guess that's
it that's it I can do it
they jump jump together what can you do
no but you know that a lot of games are
with phone but the quiz and then you
have to have like so many things
we should do a 10 people off collab
sometimes and then New Mexico
um eight with joy class and anything
above eight you can have just any phones
you could have like hundred people
really really
so for jump rope it could be like 50
people yeah
I saw it on the video it was like a room
full of people like in the hotels yeah
okay
maybe maybe another time we I don't know
if we ever can get so many people from
off collab
maybe someday we could arrange it
possible I want to be there too yeah
that was really good thank you
thank you for inviting
especially with uh I think
Ella first pull up
but in Japan we already met um
well I think it's the third time or so
before
all four yeah yeah
it's nice to meet you nice to meet you
too nice to meet you too
almost fully completed the whole idea oh
yeah
[Music]
I'm Gonna Leave Japan soon so I don't
know when we can meet again but I I hope
you continue to have fun in Japan and go
get that massage I really recommend
because in Japan yeah yeah right they're
cheap relatively like at least compared
to Europe they're cheap in Japan and
they are so so good at what they're
doing I can give you something
treat yourself treat yourself
so in the end what should we say my
greeting or together a good thing oh
okay
three two one
[Music]
it looks like
that's it wow well I'm I'm hoping to see
your free DW soon
because you're like uh doing so much for
it like dance practice right yeah I'm
dying tomorrow dance practice tomorrow
oh fight up
always remember to stretch before yes
ideally you also should stretch
afterwards but I don't do that either oh
really ideally apparently well yeah okay
do you want to
say something about your performance
today
about not knowing time
we're like oh this explains a lot yeah
it was so fun and I'm sorry guys like my
my sense of time is just real bad I'd
rather look at it and well yeah from
starting from now one minute is 60 days
long oh no GG so when you want to stream
like when you say you want to stream
like today eight hours oh no no no I've
never said that
it happens because you know like this
right every single time I touch grass
right yeah I went out and then I went
back home it it was really exhausting
like I say to them like oh guys you know
I've been like um doing work since from
morning till now and then I'm very
exhausted right now and then probably I
just gonna stream like two hours and
then suddenly I don't know it just the
streaming is just kind of charged me oh
charge the energy up so especially when
the game is really fun you get into the
moon
would you say that when you're with
cloud
he forgets about time or like oh no is
she late is she ever late
[Music]
actually I think we're the Holo hero I
think Hollow hero is not the late type
no no no yeah
so so so not like super early but not
yeah
but four important stuff yeah foreign
[Music]
time concept over minutes
I will be streaming again after this oh
thank you yeah today after this yeah
what are you streaming so you go
no I think I'll be streaming something
else you don't know not yet because my
schedule is girl every single day it's
fine it's fine it's like 9 p.m now yeah
I'm starting my stream at 12 at 2 and 1.
it's fine oh my God anyway I wanna play
soccer but I'm borrowing Ella set up
because I don't have anything to play
It's like a game too maybe when I'm home
in Austria okay okay then thank you
everybody so let's do it one more time
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you