[Music]
do
oh
ah there we go
[Music]
german
i always remember that as i'll feed us
in
that's that's three phrases but yeah
that's um
more than three words because some of
those are are multiple words yes
so you know a lot of german now
no yes
isn't this nice beautiful ah
where's the moon romantic too oh you
have a nice cape where is that is that
cape from your
your shader wait i have a cape yeah you
didn't know
i have a cape too i think it comes with
the shoulders i have a cape
but you're just cuter than mine because
yours is just a smiley
oh i didn't even see it's cute
kierra
[Music]
uh collab with everyone else we were
we're making uh
you know when when i was like doing a
flirt with you
um i didn't realize but i saw it in
clips afterwards that apparently
callie was getting jealous and she was
like throwing snowballs at me
like she thinks i love snowballs and i
didn't even notice
she was so jealous
[Music]
like kind of is like a twist joke on
words
yes and then with nothing it's like no
no no no no no no i don't know
or what was the other one
[Music]
what no bird here tori wait
that's one theory that's just my name
ah don't worry about it
oh my god my goddamn neighbors i'm so
angry
oh yeah you guys don't understand my
neighbors um
didn't let me sleep all night okay maybe
not oh i was
up all night until 6 a.m and then i
tried to sleep and then later i woke up
and they
for four hours they've been hammering
and banging at
something i don't know what what they're
doing some construction or something
it's
so annoying i've been doing it for hours
i barely slept so i'm super tired but
it's okay i am here i will take another
nap later which will then
uh end in me again staying up all night
again as per yojo but yeah
you know if you if you give up on your
sleep schedule it's it's a lot easier
yeah you definitely didn't you slept
like earlier than me
i sleep dreams my time my sleeping
schedule is basically
tuned to japan
that's actually really true yeah i do
have to get new curtains too
just to block out the sofa
i have all those uh light blocking
curtains too and you can
uh anyway uh what was i gonna say
uh we're we're having uh are you gonna
talk about nia incident last night
oh yeah yesterday but let me take a so
beautiful oh my god in my
shaders that looks so beautiful holy
oh my god well yeah uh i
yesterday i logged into minecraft while
i was watching pagoda's minecraft stream
and i just felt like it i didn't really
have any goal and i was alone i wasn't
streaming i normally don't play games
when i'm not streaming
but i i went online and i was like
i'll do something so i went into the
nether and
i was like i'm not gonna go too far i'm
just gonna explore a little bit
so i went around a little bit in the
never and then of course i got lost
after after a while of finding a lot of
gold
ghasts and uh figuring out how to fight
them
properly but i did get lost in the end i
didn't really find back anymore
so i went to our i went to our discord
and i wrote
does someone have the coordinates uh of
of of
the what did i what exactly was like our
whole homework
nether you want the coordinates for it
yeah it was uh we had some communication
issues there
because i wrote does someone have the
coordinates of our main
nava portal i got lost and i took the
coordinates
standing right here you sent them to me
and then i was following those
coordinates for like an hour
and i was like yep i'm pretty much there
but
like i can't i can't find
the gate what the hell and on my way to
finding
to following those coordinates i found
good as
never fortress and i was like wow
here that that must be super close to
the to the
to the nether portal then wow wow that
it was so close always
so i was looking and looking and looking
but i couldn't find
the entrance and then i wrote that you
know
you know was just uh i don't know how
they
were just checking up on me so i was
like actually
i still i'm still lost in the
netherlands i just can't find it i'm
super close but i can't find it and then
were you realized i was like here are
you are you in the nether
i was like another coordinator
so then she gave me the real coordinates
and then i was following the real
coordinates but they were so far away
and then i i really couldn't find it
anymore
[Laughter]
and then then however i i um
i got to the point where i found my path
again at least and the path was
this this single block path that gura
made
uh on the way to her fortress and i have
a screenshot so you can
imagine it better let me show you
uh it's on my stream only but oh yeah
this one one block fab the fate in the
brown is on the end of that path
uh you don't see it anymore in this
screenshot because i got
closer and it's over already but at the
end of that path there was a pig
and it's one block and you guys know how
clumsy i am there's no way i could fight
that on this one block path
it was a pumbaa without falling down so
i was like anna
you know i found the puff again but
there's this pig
and i don't know what to do i i can't
find it and then she was
she was there if you look if you look if
you look close enough
let me make it bigger she's on the other
side
what at the moment i wrote to her that i
can't make it she was already there on
the other side of this he said
you said your your uh girl's a path i
was like but i
am a girl's past and i didn't see you
and i saw this pumbaa on like a path i
was like oh there's a pumbaa and then
as soon as i saw the pumbaa kiara was
like
you know i have a problem
i can make it across but there's a pig
and then she she fought the peak and uh
happy end
my life was saved by inna because
otherwise i would have never made it
back
home i used the heated it off the uh
of the past got the egg roll i got the
air grill
i ran back to summer sale and then you
you're such a pro
minecraft player you easily killed that
monster that
pig you just gotta be one with the
system
and one more thing i i personally
didn't understand when i tweeted about
it i personally didn't understand why
you wrote
matata but it was because of the people
oh my god that's so scrap that is
reaching that is reaching enough
it is not reaching it's literally pumbaa
i did not realize that until um
someone else like people were trying to
figure out
why uh you wrote hakuna matata and what
actually happened
and then um i saw one person actually
um suggesting that it might be because
of another pig
and i was like how do they know
how did we get to that conclusion and
then that is when i realized that makes
sense
that makes sense how did you think of
that genius don't worry about it
[Laughter]
oh well okay so after all that's uh
introductional
introductional talk let's go into the
never and first of all
find the right spot for
the second kfb branch yes actually uh
wait for a moment i need to bring one
more
step busy talking that we
all forgot about uh well thank you for
uh thank you for saving me yesterday oh
no worries
you know i actually wanted to go to
sleep once but she realized i was
still a lost child and that's when she
decided to save my life
what an angel need to cook some chicken
again
i'll have some food if you want no it's
okay
i i i i i really have
more than enough food i just need to
cook it oh
oh what am i doing i can't
yesterday i finally learned how to
properly um
how to properly uh fight a guest with
the crossbow but i also learned how to
reflect
um the whatever they shoot the fire the
fireball yeah
yeah i can finally reflect it properly
nice
i can't do it properly because of the
layers
i was getting too late oh because this
server
has like oh um because the server is i
guess in japan
is it i think so oh
well silly you're a pro gamer so that's
that one for you okay i just have a
i have a lot of steak to fix my mistakes
okay
oh by the way um we are first going to
find a spot and then come back with
materials and we have to figure out what
materials to use because we can't just
use
the wool that i used for the original
kfb
unfortunately
[Music]
but yesterday when i came back here i
was i was waiting down in that safe
house okay
i was waiting in the safe house and then
suddenly this dude comes in
and shoots me and like what the [\h__\h] it
was running running
and he was pulling me and shooting me so
quickly wait is that for me yesterday mr
taylor's
is that still from yesterday
it was shooting me oh that one was me
i think it's funny still still why did
he attack me i didn't do anything though
i don't think he's a i don't think he's
awkward anymore no
you're fine just wait around here
i think i know but but is it possible
because i wasn't here enough
okay and then he comes in intruding
this safe house oh my god he's coming
again no
no no but then okay let's let's reenact
the scene
i opened his chest and then he attacked
me does he not want me to open the chest
i wonder
is that his chest oh she opened the oh
chest opening chest aggressive
apparently
oh [\h__\h] that's why oh
no good that he didn't see it now
[\h__\h] it's not right
[Laughter]
sorry i'm grumpy okay i'm grumpy from
waking up against my will
i grumpy waking up against you what if
we wha
oh i mean is there anyone around
okay i'm gonna die i'm gonna die
[Music]
he's gone
well we got my revenge from you got some
accessories on your head
yeah don't worry about it okay let's go
oh oh an arrow
[Laughter]
should we expand though um
i mean i was thinking about like near
near girls atlantis was a good spot
um the question is do we actually want
to um be helpful with this branch and
put it somewhere where someone might
need an emergency food ration
or do we just plant it wherever it looks
good
[Music]
[Laughter]
yes i don't know
i mean where where would you travel
here in the nether that would i think we
gotta go this direction
okay and then uh
where this minecart stops at the gold
gotcha uh-huh
there's i mean it's somewhat flat area
that is true so i was thinking maybe
there
because that's also where you changed
trees oh that's also where
um there's also
um where you can go to the slime farm
place at that place too so
have you ever seen it
a
[Music]
need to stop leaving minecarts out
but that was because of that stupid pig
cause he keeps no maybe not
there's a lot of mine cards oh my oh my
god oh my god oh my god
no no no no no no no no no
no
open spot here
remember remember the first first full
club
was it or no it was the second one where
you just jumped here and died
[Music]
doesn't only mean what you implied
it also means it's fireproof true
there are touches on fire but don't
worry about it
but it's okay oh my goodness it's really
dark with the speeders that i have
um i i had to lighten mine up a lot
hmm did you did you visit my where where
my rail goes
no not here actually you didn't shall
you go i want to see
uh it's um on first look it's really
nothing special
we would have to travel further to see
what's special about it
i think this is a this is a good
candidate to put kfp because there's a
lot of customers around too you know
yeah except we'll have to uh
and some entertainment with gotcha
[Music]
the problem here is that there's a lot
of gas always attacking so there's
always a lot of fire
that is true it might destroy the
building
so we'll have to like guest proof it
somehow yeah
definitely but not not only the building
but maybe also the surroundings of it
partially
i'm still drinking my tea because i just
woke up and my voice still needs to warm
up but oh yeah
i was blowing into the mic for like 10
minutes
cool down her teeth it's what you call
nekojita but i was jealous
you were jealous do you want to be blown
on or no
chow chow i would have been jealous oh
like a special chiara
i do i did blow on them sometimes uh for
as a punishment for sending empty empty
red super chats
[Laughter]
what is that silence are you judging me
no
okay well okay so let's build the
let's build it like uh wait uh uh
uh somewhere out here what have all
these holes and oh my god probably a
guest
let's make it let's make it um pretty if
uh
eventually
i actually need to bring some i didn't i
didn't we should really
uh let's just bring
[Music]
like the chest with like tools and stuff
because they're gonna need heart a lot
wait one second inna i need to do some
blowing um
close your close your ears or something
stupid red super chats write something
in it god damn it
they always do that it has to be
meaningful
i'm sorry now you can you can open your
ears again
i don't think i can choose that honestly
i don't keep them doing that
okay let me let me let me show my new
skills let me show them my new skills
find me [\h__\h]
oh sorry sorry wait wait wait why why do
i keep on doing this today oh
because my keyboard is resting on my
graphic tablet oh that's right
like me uh so dark
i will protect enough but don't destroy
my rails please
i definitely can do it uh follow your
rails
no no no
it's not it's not even like it totally
burnt goddammit
people are asking for bgm i didn't turn
it on on purpose but i guess if you guys
really want bgm let me turn it on
oh oh god damn it oh wait i have to
change the settings
um oh it's so dark here
okay there's bgm now is that um
in our stream disconnected oh it's it'll
be back
oh kelly is in the chat
[Music]
oh did you just fix uh did you bring
rails with you
no it's the ones that broke okay
wait i need to bring some later okay oh
we need we're missing two here though i
don't know where they went
yeah there's more down there and there
is more missing
down there too but it's okay i'll bring
some i'll bring some
when when we come back we should we
should go and uh bring some materials
now
should we put it in here what's his face
what's his name
phil you gave him a name
i don't know i think girl and uh i'll
make them names
thank you kelly we'll have fun we're
already having lots of fun
we're having lots of fun cali we're
having so much fun
[Music]
okay and cali do you see this how much
we love each other we chase each other
i don't i don't this is one-sided
oh wait is that though this is the slime
form
oh i never noticed this one before
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh you better bring my stuff over here
i'm gonna wait i'm
[Laughter]
okay so enough yes
what do we use to build it i don't
want it to be only like one one boring
color i wanted to have
but oh yeah does them
does this wait let me ask my viewers
does this thing does the trim light burn
uh
yeah it has a light it's the glowing
thing
on the uh on the trees
so we can use um a combination of uh
like concrete or something like that and
then make it a bit orange with the
shroom light because we need some orange
elements otherwise people are not gonna
recognize it as
its original glory over there so
uh we gotta we gotta i barely have any
though do you have more
uh i have hot i have concrete
oh okay okay i mean we can collect the
green light
okay white concrete okay oh wait have a
few more
here okay but that's not much
oh we are we gonna cook some chicken
yeah caffeine boys what up are you guys
working
are you guys working mostly moss
[Music]
are you working properly i'm so proud of
you guys
i am so proud of you you're doing a
great job here
uh so who is um who is open
for uh changing branches uh we're right
now
um planning on opening up a new branch
in a really nice
uh spot a really nice paradise
um i am putting the applications right
here
and you please fill them out and send
them to me i
will need at least 10 workers of you um
where you ask oh don't worry about it
it's uh it's pretty close
okay okay okay okay
i didn't tell them i didn't tell them
where it's gonna be
wait a minute don't these batters
attract
pillagers no i haven't seen them in a
while
oh that's fine oh maybe because
[Music]
maybe because uh i killed them all
yeah it's fun isn't it it's okay i
didn't really
feel it i feel like they came much more
often before i pulled out up these
banners
ah they don't they don't okay
do you have my stuff i do
here's your bowl i'm gonna
oh that's not yours this is yours i'll
take it anyway
i'll take everything give me your
diamond sword give it to me
i think this is my is my golden helmet
broken
yes oh well it was pretty close
to breaking that's okay and an axe and
your pant
you want your pets back yes i had pants
oh uh i was i was lacking shoes i think
thank you thank you
what else was your shield
what about one about my breast armor
uh there was none
i had like i had a golden helmet i had
breast armor and then i had either shoes
or
i must have missed it hold on hey
are you gonna give me new armor it's the
uh
community chest i put some in there oh
yeah they're a little bit used
but it's okay your
your your iron farm is so useful
it's useful because i just afk in my
house all the time i'll take some errors
too
take your pick take your picture and now
i'm gonna uh i'm gonna make an
eye and a golden helmet quickly um
ah and then the pickaxe i need a pickaxe
all right
oh yeah we should bring materials this
time huh yeah
forgot about it so we're using we are
using uh
oh wait i have your pork chops huh
oh concrete okay i have you can keep it
you can keep the pork chops
we're using concrete okay how much do we
have
what color should be can we make orange
concrete you can
but i need some concrete powder to do
that
concrete powder and some orange stuff
orange
there's a concrete powder what's the
recipe
well we have a lot of flowers outside we
need sand and gravel actually i have
quite a bit of sun and gravel
i can make you orange
orange but actually no white is fine
because you need some orange too if you
base it off on the uh first branch
what was that right sorry no no if we
paste the uh
the desire on the first branch i need
some white and some orange but the
orange can be
um it can't just be this room light
that's fine
she must not glow though yeah it's fancy
it's darker than ever anyway though
that's true i think it's fun it's like a
nice uh
never virgin another version of the of
the
but i also kind of need i mean
um yeah if we really want to copy it
then we need red as well
okay but the orange can be uh
substituted is that what you would say
um i do have something but i can make
more okay
i guess it's going to be a somewhat
small branch
it can be a take-out branch you know
like to go
only take out good idea
good idea okay but inside
maybe i'll make some what did i make my
chairs
out of hey let me see
how did i make my chairs and my tables
oh with a carpet
right oh let's see
i think yeah with a carpet and a fence
and then a stair okay
okay but that can be out of any material
because that's gonna be inside
okay fences and carpet
i'm gonna make i'll make some white
carpets
and
[Music]
carpet uh how many how many concrete do
you think we'll need
how many do you have we can build it as
big as we can with
how much concrete you have okay hold on
i'll see what i can do
that's enough
[Music]
sorry sorry
applying for the transfer tension for
real
got some wow already yeah wow
you're getting a medal for being a brave
volunteer
who is one sooner working than ever
who wants to do it me too what
wow what okay they're actually asking
for it okay
complaining and now they're all asking
for it interesting
i thought you guys didn't want to go
but they they said that working at kfp
is already hell
so that's the difference that's not true
though
that's right it's a beautiful experience
to work it give me okay
you sad when you guys say that oh i
should probably bring back my gold
okay i i'm not concentrating we have to
we already spent like
um half a half an hour i forgot how i
used this before no i have this like
automatic
like easy to make concrete kind of thing
i forgot how oh
oh i saw i i used your what's that
what's the other thing that the the
the the cobblestone thingy oh though
it's the thing right beside it it's the
uh
uh concrete nina you're like so
innovative
amazing why did do you why are you
making everything automatic
you are you are building a nice future
for future whole live english members
oh wow there's so many i'll take some of
these peace why is there so many
pickaxes
playing around here
[Music]
oh wait put that back
put a [\h__\h] chest over here on the
outside right here
oh okay but can i can i have like
one you can make iron one wait there's
plenty of water and these other stuff
oh
don't worry about it i'll pick it up
later how's it work
i'll pick up later interesting is that
how it's supposed to work
uh sort of it's supposed to drop down on
its own but it's kind of weird so
i just have to do it manually
[Music]
yeah later so interesting yeah
it's very concrete because you have to
put it in the water
um
no i'm just understanding of you guys
but the cobblestone thingy is genius
because i'm like
cobblestone is like you would think it's
like super
excessive
accessible and everywhere but
but when you need it you don't have any
cobblestone
[Music]
okay um and then we check this here
and then
okay um i think i have enough
building blocks to go into another now
probably
nice so i
also got
okay i'm gonna
[Music]
um make some
pickaxes uh-huh
and then i'll jump into the never and
wait the
the shroom lights they're supposed to be
collected with
pick axes right no idea
i feel like i collected them yesterday
with pickaxes
anything oh okay anything
[Music]
ah windows windows
yeah should we bring like a furnace and
um
put stuff in yeah we need chests yeah
because we're gonna put in food in there
i don't think we have to put an
automatic cooking device there because
i just that's not that's not how i do it
i don't want it to be automatically
that seems just like too too horrible
for me
um are you sure that's the real reason
yeah i just feel too bad like i don't
want to make it
a farm where it kills the chicken and
then cooks them
i don't know i can't do that no that but
it's fresh too humane for me
it's fresh like you might do that with
your with your
automatic farms absolutely absolutely
not humane unbelievable i i
i don't know how you can be so so
so reckless i don't know i can't even
find the words for it in english
i roll the tapes roll the tips of
kiara's
deeds come on you mean the one where it
goes like
[Music]
you see that one where they added your
singing oh
yes
your singing makes you so much more
dramatic
the moment where i had to slay my
chickens and it was
i was just so so she admitted it she
admitted it
she's slain the chickens
everyone who heard that you're going to
the angel room
i've uh i have i have footage from the
usual room
uh oh where did you get that from
uh they they want to remain anonymous
but
there has been reports
i um are you did you maybe go to the
usual room because
you're kinky like that and
wanted to check out the
the ghost but i heard
ungodly things happening in the usual
room
yeah one of the one of my recent
um uh uh ideas
that i put in there is a legos so that
like a lot of legos so that when you
walk around in the usual room
you will always step on legos and it
will hurt so
much isn't that a great idea
and you say i'm the inhumane one
legos how could you
out of everything in the legos
and then there's one more thing um i put
uh i put a
uh what how many pieces was it like a
million pieces
uh uh a puzzle and they have to
complete but then at some point they
would realize oh god there's
one piece missing after all these
hours of completing the one million
piece puzzle
they realize one piece is missing
did they ever say lego my eggo
okay maybe maybe it's not uh you know
there's a there's a waffle um brand
called eggo
and they're and their their slogan is
like oh my egg
i know enough enough
did you get the joke i mean she probably
at least knows the brand
they're the uh they're probably the
frozen what are
waffles that i'm naked
most
[Music]
like cold chat i've eaten i've eaten
yeah frozen waffles cold
i've eaten frozen waffles before i think
oh at least like
like like cream waffles and ice waffles
from uh what's that what's that the the
brand with the actual good waffles
echo
what's it called does someone know
the one from i think from europe
like belgium yeah yeah
those are frozen waffles they're fresh
delicious
yeah but there's just one brand of
belgian waffles that's like really good
frozen waffles yum yum yum yum yum yum
now that's droop waffles no no no no no
no
no no no no no um
there's no one know what i'm talking
about
oh sure
i buy them over here often oh wow anyway
keep on forgetting how to get off of us
he's still sitting in there
if we would uh attack his minecart would
would that count as attacking him and
as long as you don't hit him i don't
think oh
you're kind of there jamma
but okay if you hit it with the sword
you can get it down in one one go
the minecart ah oh yeah i know actually
but i always forget all right
actually i need those i need some shroom
lights i'm going to get some
swim lights okay should we build it like
right at
the um or should we build a like
a little lady i think it would be nice
if it would be like
against some kind of
uh wall um oh
cali is riding angle toaster strips were
the best you toast them and dip them in
the syrup and it's like french toast
paradise explosion in your mouth and
stuff wow she's getting really
passionate
that's why you never let go your egg you
know there's always gas here
where are you no it's okay it doesn't it
didn't see me
but it will see me soon maybe oh i
stupid cast
where is it oh i see it's
why should we build it i should rebuild
it well tinto you figure out
the location oh i'm going
to do something oh
[Music]
i'll see you another time okay
we can start building let's build it up
our torches actually
okay let's build it next to that because
there's no nice
wall to build against so let's build it
next to the to the building like
over the gate over the gate so when you
when you
when you come out of the gate you're
basically like
at the kfp location
it's like it's like one of those like
you know when you go on the subways but
like when you come out it's like
literally just like
food chains like everywhere ah
but i think this i think this space
would be nice enough oh yeah right this
year okay
yeah okay then can you can you start
filling the concrete foundation or
something like that
or whatever foundation and i'll go
quickly get some shroom lights
[Music]
well as wide as we can with what we have
well the rails like bend here so it
can't be that big
oh and it's okay
[Music]
you guys are all very welcome so jealous
i haven't been able to sneeze for like
the longest time
well that must suck yeah
you poor poor poor poor
totally human being i totally believe
that why don't
why did i bring a white one what the
hell
uh i need some black
[Music]
thank you for the sneeze chats
one two three four how big should the
doors be
i hear the guests oh you can hear it
kill it it's like kill it it's like way
above the fire
we can't get it yet it's like way above
us
stupid gas just waiting for the right
moment
don't hurt don't hurt inna oh
yay i wanna hunt it down
do it do it ina so far oh i see it
follow your instincts and kill it
[Music]
where is it where did it go where did
the light go that i wanted to get
[Music]
what
it screamed did you heard it yeah nice
one
i wonder like if we is it is it
uh too big of a project to
put uh like a cobbles stone ceiling
over the whole area over there so that's
the stage
at least we have your cobblestone
machine that could help with that
this is a crazy i idea
it's okay we can put glass too actually
so you can see the
exterior so glass doesn't burn uh and
then ever
nope but uh i think they said
they can't see through glass them all oh
really
oh that's that's weird that's so
why can't they see through the glass
they're stupid you can't see if their
eyes are real
[Music]
oh my chat is going crazy because i
missed some something that kelly said
let me see what did you say on it
mom that one's your attention dad wants
your attention
i scrolled up all the way but i i
couldn't find
what you said it's gone oh i'm sorry
callie
oh kelly kelly wants my attention oh
oh oh
oh wow how how nice
[Music]
oh my god
oh my god are you following me yes they
are following me
yes they are
help me guys help me what are you here
for aren't you supposed to fight them
oh they don't want to come out of the
forest interesting oh no they do
they do that they do
[Music]
first tiara where are you
i brought a pig i think we
should um where are you by the way
looking for you you know oh you went
there to look for me
i think i just saw you yeah
can you kill that oh no it's not
attacking me what's wrong
oh it's going for you now
[Music]
uh
that's probably not a great place to
stand
um was that was he attacking the
the pig and then accidentally attacked
me uh
uh that's two desks could you pick up my
myself or you think it will could
you oh i have a whole bunch of stuff i
don't have a chest
though oh no
i'm guarding it i'm guarding you okay it
should stay there it's not that far away
it wasn't friendly fire it was the
hotline
really but yeah it did say it did say i
was uh killed by the hogland it did yeah
it's not me
oh my god all the cool cards
five minutes
fine oh oh he's stealing your stuff
wait no one's looking right there's a
there's a hopeless stealing yourself or
they better not take my golden helmet
right now i don't have a golden
headlight how am i gonna oh [\h__\h]
it's okay you're gonna attack me like by
the way you bet oh my god oh you know
this is oh my god you know wait
i just realized i just realized this is
gonna be problematic
are you gonna stop attacking me once i
pull down my helmet am i gonna even
survive though until that point oh
oh [\h__\h] there's so many around there oh
god oh god
he doesn't attack me okay okay
okay i'm running i'm running
they don't see me as is someone
following me no that's fine
okay i have a golden handle that could
have
turned into very difficult there's more
stuff here actually
you see it okay okay okay okay
there we go okay i got it all got it
all good oh you must have crossed them
right here oh
i am oh thank you thank you
yes okay um i'll go collect some
mushroom lights again
okay be safe yeah i'll try i'll try oh
wait wait before you go you should look
at how big the location is gonna be
oh my style i think that's uh it's like
right
no it's okay oh there's a zombie not
nice
but um i think i'm i'm gonna
let you get more carpet and then carpet
out the area uh-huh
inside because i don't want it to be
like that that's uh disgusting
[Laughter]
all the children are running around over
there
[Music]
recently i've been experiencing some
morning sickness why do you think that
is
huh recently i've been experiencing
morning sickness why do you think that
is
[Music]
did you eat before going to sleep no
before going to sleep
mm-hmm well a few hours before
like like like five hours before
i sound like i mean i'm i would probably
be fine if i would eat uh
now because i didn't eat i just woke up
and went straight to the
went straight to the pc ah you should
digest your food before going to bed or
sitting down for a long time i mean i
shouldn't be the one saying it but
i think it's just because i don't eat
before streaming in the morning
um probably you should probably eat
something like
like even if uh even if you have a
troubled digestion stuff maybe get like
a cheek
or something
whatever them too is my company is
somewhat far away from me you just suck
up
on it just go there once and buy like
10.
yeah but every time i go to the
convenience store i buy
so much as if i'm going to the
supermarket and i think that
the person who works there hates me
because i buy so much
and they spend so much time with me i'm
sure
i'm sure they're
they're you think judgmental glare is
not as bad as when i went to buy itunes
cards
oh why do you think they wouldn't like
that uh
so when you buy specific
itunes cards it's annoying there's a
there's a limit to how much you can
put in uh yeah and so
if you buy multiple of those then you
gotta stand there and scan the cards
many times so
[Music]
anyways
how about that yeah where are you are
you up
or down here right right right right
side right there
i see you save me save me
save me these are small ones
nice okay
you're not that bad come on there's no
one over there
there's like these oh my god there's a
baby
or if you hit them once they run away
the people with the small ones maybe
but they're doing a really bad job at
protecting the forest i thought that was
those villagers
or whatever they are are supposed to
protect and kill them
uh protect the forest and kill them
you're not doing a good job on that
you suck you guys suck all three of you
suck
i died because of you guys because you
are not doing your job
and you know what happens to people who
don't do do their job you might not be
working for me but i'll put you in the
usual room anyway i don't care
but it's the usual job or use your room
the uh
yeah a reward
[Music]
not really but some people maybe take it
as a reward but but they're
they're being very dramatic about it so
i don't i don't think they're happy
about it oh they're happy don't worry
they're happy
but they're always like no no don't put
my name
oh they're enjoying a hundred thousand
temples
you think they're all masochistic and
they enjoy oh yes i'm stepping on legos
tonight all day long but they are
i see you
he did it oh they did it
and they i think they almost didn't
goddamn it they
[Music]
oh my god and i realized they party
after they kill a pig wow
that's a
i think i hit one of them by mistake oh
are they following you yes
oh does it reset when you leave than
ever
uh i don't know and there's the portal
there
you think you're gonna be fine i'm okay
for now i need some
[Music]
goddamn pigs
okay is that a baby that's a baby
damn stupid baby
you challenge me you challenge kfp i
have a whole army
we all we watched a lot of the rings
together so we we know how to fight
i still only have 11. how do i only have
oh how'd i only have 11
do you have some of my room lights when
i died uh
i don't think so
what's going on do you have my room
lights is that why uh no i'm being
hunted by
zombie pigs don't worry about it
go for the portal go for the portal no
where are you are you guys
i'm okay i'll be fine i'll be back in a
moment
yeah don't be about to know me i'm just
uh recovering one day she still
before when i looked at it well
if someone wasn't crying out my name for
help maybe i would have done something
more
i was collecting straight lines and i
got mushroom
nothing changed with the concrete
foundation
i think we're uh oops you know when i
hired ahmed
uh she was doing so much work so quickly
she was so efficient and you are
inefficient
[Music]
well that's just how it is oh
look next time next time you cry out my
name i'll just watch you die
you could never do that you would always
protect me
sure about that you're an angel hear
about that
no i believe in the goodness in your
heart
i have a cross but i'm not afraid to use
it
i think you would always protect me
because you're you're such a
please
[Music]
a raise would probably go into the
negative because you uh all my kfb
employees are paying me so when they get
a raise they pay me more
you you're welcome to i'm gonna i'm
gonna i'm gonna
put in my uh letter of resignation and
go search for
a better series you think you can't
resign oh that's funny that's just cute
oh there's still time guys she thinks
she can resign isn't that funny
i'll resign when i die which isn't what
it's might be soon
[Laughter]
she's new guys she's new
are you talking about me who is asking
you to save you
you can't be employees kfb employees
chickens
are you in the nether again yes
don't worry about it i'm sure you can uh
build the uh
basic
i i i don't i i i mean
i from what i've seen from inna's
[Music]
projects and buildings up until now i
i will i thought it would be a good idea
to
to cooperate with taco bell to get some
of that nice
architecture going but i don't i didn't
see much going on yet
don't worry soon these arrows will find
a new target
no no no no no you can't do that no no
no no no you love me i love you you love
me we are best friends you know what
happens to when you
when you fall in love cupid's an arrow
right at your heart i know that i'm
probably soon gonna fall into lava or
something like that
out of running away from the pigs as
quickly as i can
protect me guys protect me yes yes
i'll be there soon hey good job guys
you're not dancing this time though why
not
okay oh
i have 23 streamlights
only 23. you spent all this time
oh we have 23. i send it off like three
waves of zombies i think i lost them
when i died because you didn't pay
you did you you took someone maybe if
you didn't die
you accidentally shot me with an arrow
and did i the last hit wasn't it was
done by a hawker maybe but maybe other
maybe you shouldn't be
standing there in the first place
[Music]
peace peace
shake hands peace
[Music]
i think i'll have to do the deed
oh my god i just tried to help no
oh kiara where are you um i'll i'll try
to quickly
uh go for the never portal and hope no
one
yes just run just run
we're just killing off our customers no
no biggie
oh another guest i don't know if this
location is good enough potential
i think i just like shot an arrow at the
fireball and returns it to the cast
wait that's the first time you did that
i don't know
okay okay so
this still looks the same interesting no
problem with that it's a totally
fine
and looks looks nice
it looks nice looks good job yeah
[Music]
anything else oh it looks looks really
nice good job thank you
you're lucky today
so i i think i think i'll put um
the the shrooms oh like here on the on
the edges
and that would be the approximately the
height
of it and then maybe on top we put one
more
layer of white do you have glass and in
between
do you have glass oh yeah glass oh yeah
oh yeah right
uh hold on hold on can you give me some
mess oh yes
there you go i only have the block style
yeah flux is fine
we're finally getting started
well we'll need some need some uh big
thinkers need some time to
start their creation so to get fully
inspired and prepared
and all that we're we're not just
messing around here we want to do it
properly
wait this is wool oh this is yours
i was like what is this thought it was
concrete i was like this sounds
different
hold on let me give this stuff
[Music]
i don't i don't i don't know if i want
the whole
wall from from one side to the other to
be
uh glass i'm not sure um
i think i oh you ah oh
oh good i like that idea
okay this is where the the creative
architecture
of the inside of inna
the inner side wait this is still wool
it's not thick
you can give it back to me
yes i'll take it and i'll cover up that
hole because it's
scaring me also i should probably eat
probably the chat also keeps on telling
me to eat i mean like in
in in the game yeah because i'm close to
dying
but i won't listen
okay where's my pickaxe
oh that looks beautiful it looks really
fancy
oh wait
[Music]
here it goes ah this is like super close
the gas is here
it's fine wow i will i will challenge it
yep
oh are you playing tennis oh
try to sit down
okay i'll be there soon
oh no come here come here you little
coward
i haven't died in a while come here come
here look at me
look at me face your destiny
[Music]
i got too cocky
it's now it's too high about that
i forgot when the last time i died in
minecraft
oh there's oh is it so long ago pumbaa
now
is it not see me stupid stupid
wait i don't have a golden helmet oh
dear
what did you pick my stomach by a chance
what did it break
ah what did she pick some stuff up
oh my helmet might have to go back
wow you still don't have your helmet no
and my cross
oh should i pick it up for you the
helmet is that over there i'm surprised
i didn't i
was surprised i didn't see you
let me see if there's a golden helmet
um
i don't what's that broke there's
something here
but no golden helmet i don't even attack
you that quickly interesting
[Music]
i thought that was my shield
wait even my sword is gone hmm oh no
i could give you my sword i have two
yeah rip diamonds how are they not
attacking you here have a sword
oh thank you you should you should
probably uh burn oh
okay that makes sense hi
enderman is there another guy oh my god
okay fine okay you did it oh good job
thank you are you leaving us alone do we
have
peace now i think i have to go back to
get
some golden armor
uh building here i'll continue i'll be
back
that is a it's a kind of a pain in the
ass to build in the never huh
that was rough
they keep on they keep on attacking
that's not us
[Music]
oops no wait do you have
all the kong oh my god concrete burn too
rip i have 28 left
but we definitely need more i have the
red concrete so
oh okay um i mean we can just make more
more glass walls then um
i have the glass the shovel
[Music]
one one two three four four
four
oh what's this guest here
oh oh yeah because you killed the guest
is that the first time you get a gas
tear
[Music]
oh are they so clear i don't know
what what what can you do with a gas
stove there's navigation
apparently what can you do with a gas
tear oh my god there's another ghast
here
[Music]
look at me
wait oh disappeared no too bad
wow i feel like if those stupid gas
wouldn't keep
like coming uh-huh no i'm so stupid
then we would probably already be done
by now
um
[Music]
oh
okay um i might have more class
okay or not i can just burn some more
now i have too many i have too many
glowstones now hmm
this is really really small
[Music]
oh i see you there so
uh maybe we should really put a
a cobblestone ceiling over this whole
area because it pisses me off they keep
on attacking and they keep on destroying
them
i mean we could just cover up the rail
but
i mean um yeah the reels
definitely need some protection
and yeah okay that those are my rails so
i'll take care of those
[Music]
we'll bring a chest over oh yeah
can you bring one yes yay
a little extra
[Music]
ah
and sorry guys i didn't i didn't check
your answer so what can you do with the
ghast here did you even answer oh
i think oh
potions what kind of potion
regeneration potion
oh there's another one oh my god
ender crystals
wait my steaks are gone your sticks
my steaks i have a lot of sticks i'll
have a lot of steaks too
i'll bring chicken
you bring chicken okay which makes me
think
i also have to um go back one time
and get some yeah
mama mama will take care of it
this is this is a business that only
mama chiara can take
care of oh that thing oh i see
oh do you know what i'm talking about
i have a i have a i can guess
[Music]
okay
oh it's so slow oh i feel
oh you're back hello i'm back feel bad
you can take my card
because i think we took uh all of the
cards out of them yeah i'll leave one
here
stupid neighbors are still banging after
all these hours they're still banging on
something
oh wait i'll be cut contact
i mean i'm either really
for hours i don't know man i couldn't
contact someone
the contact says that they're banging on
something they're doing some
construction or something i think
i i i didn't i didn't mean to
yummy now is it better if i say they're
hammering
does that sound better
apparently not
well then how am i supposed to say it
it's not my fault that english is such a
suggestive language that's not my fault
it's not even my first language
so um
there was an effort
yo friends did you fill out your
applications
did you i'll take some of that chicken
and i'll put it into the nipper
cause we we're not gonna we're not gonna
cook the chickens in there that's just
why chickens no no sorry guys sorry guys
i meant phoenix's sorry sorry
obviously sorry about the confusion guys
uh oh yeah i was gonna
make some carpet yeah the application is
filled up okay okay okay
imported chicken yes it will be freshly
imported from the
real world isn't that nice
well we have the wolf oh yeah are you
back at base
uh yep uh if you go into my house i was
baking some glass but i forgot about it
could you bring someone over short
attention span
i see yes
i uh in which house you have a couple of
houses it's kind of cool
i only have one house
the uh oh and all the cats and dogs
okay okay okay is that enough carpet hmm
wait oh it's not how you're gonna do it
oh
you kind of you kind of have two houses
though
wait what no
[Music]
oh there's the guys get rid of the other
did you get rid of the other house
yes ah i don't think this location is
safe potential
yeah i know wait wait
where are you doing that inside or
outside the glass
oh the uh oh here i have it i found it
there's two guests
two are you gonna be fine
i'm coming back
[Music]
stop banking oh my god what the hell are
they doing like for real
oh
they better be done after i'm done with
streaming because i got to take a nap
mommy's got to take a nap mommy has to
take a nap
hey i have to stop banging i want to
but the thing is like i i probably don't
even have the
privilege to get mad at them because
they probably think the same of me
because i'm so loud when i stream they
probably hear every word i say
[Music]
huh why
if there is no if
there is no reason to film like um
embarrassed or flustered or anything
because i'm not
saying anything wrong i'm just talking
about my stupid neighbors
wait no i wasn't holding it i was just
trying to
okay somebody else
like [\h__\h] yeah i'll kill it
i'll take him out with that i'll be
getting uh
the walls ready okay
okay i got your slime ball
nice are your body is gonna come up for
i gotta fix those
yes uh what happened there uh
a guest happened two guests actually hey
i thought they can't burn it uh
yes i have the glass i'll just place it
myself
so we have a pattern here interesting i
hope you like the pattern that i put in
the back
yes oh wait a minute i'll copy what you
did on that side
yeah oh wait no i messed no i
uh yeah another
what oh okay okay i thought you got rid
of my uh
no no no no no that just disappears
because okay wait is that correct
yeah and then the glass goes there yes
okay
[Music]
yes
this is this is gonna be such a
beautiful building in the middle of the
never people are gonna be like
they're gonna come sightseeing here
they're gonna check it down then they'll
be like
who built this fancy building in another
it's so beautiful
and then we're gonna be like that was us
that was us okay are we gonna
um keep it open here or should we build
a door
a door might be nice um
what kind uh maybe the the kind of white
door you have at your at your
um huh oh the iron it's and then a
double a double door
oh do you have a crafting table yeah
yeah
you put it down i did bring one
i can make it probably wait i can put
the chest down okay actually
okay good then i can put my chicken
there
uh iron door
how did i deserve that that empty red
super chat
messages
[Music]
thank you though thank you uh you
maybe have a stone by chance
ah stone a single stone no i don't
i don't have any stones right now i have
more glass
and i have wool and i have a smooth
sandstone stairs and i got shrooms from
lights
[Music]
you can have that cobblestone
there you go
i'm gonna make the tables now oh wait i
have coal
oh wait i only need one nevermind i'm
just talking to myself
okay
nice
and then in between i do want to
damn it oh
[Music]
let me put some more glass there
that looks nice doesn't it chat does it
look nice it does ride so fast that
looks beautiful
oh beautiful well that might be a
prettier branch than the outside brush
[Music]
nice but maybe
can we do we have more white concrete
yeah we do hold on
do you think we could instead of the
carpet and replace
all of the all the ground with the white
concrete because like even if i put
carpet there it's gonna
oh i have 44. i think that should be
enough
maybe all right
i just wanted to put conch or
cobblestone because it was stronger but
stronger against gusts and
fireballs etc
wait you say that there's still a chance
that my
kfb brands can be destroyed by guests
yes
okay but we can we can build the ceiling
with cobblestone
yeah yeah yeah it's just that we gotta
make sure they don't see us uh
to the walls somehow
it'll be fine are you they they can't
see through the
through the class right and for uh i
don't know how they can be that stupid
but
apparently that's the thing oh no will i
have enough i mean i have more at home
under something smooth
so smooth so
beautiful almost as smooth
the how would you call them those those
sideburns that you have
huh
that wasn't very smooth of you sorry i
don't know what to call them
uh i ran out but i do have more
questions
oh okay okay yeah okay i'll continue
building the the tables okay
and if you have time you can get started
on the uh the ceiling
you have cause i don't have any
cobblestone
all right leave it in the chest actually
so okay
i'm actually gonna move the chest though
feel free okay
[Music]
oh um it didn't pick it up
god damn it goddammit
i have no space there's a oh remember
you can leave it on the floor while you
move the chest
all right you said you had no space
you can leave items on the floor while
you move the chest itself and then stuff
everything in the chest
afterwards yeah okay i got it okay
oh i mean i don't think we need them
because we have the glowing stones oh
if you feel like it's inside it's always
good to have a bright
space and no why not
food restaurant it will probably make it
more comfortable so yes why not
need a welcoming environment especially
in the nether
are you sure you feel safe yes
[Music]
i'm sorry that's phoenix meat excuse me
no confusion there
right i almost forgot what i came here
for
sailing ceiling sailing i
will build the ceiling
[Music]
uh i just hope no one looks at it from
the top the top the cobblestone doesn't
look so pretty oh my god
am i safe
okay he doesn't see me anymore it works
it works and he doesn't see me
but i think i have to kill him so that i
can continue working
[Music]
most restaurants use darkness to hide
what you're eating apparently
chad said some restaurants they use the
darkness so you don't really see what
you're eating
is that what happens i can't be yeah
eating phoenix meat honest honest work
there is no doubt about what is inside
my burgers i make it very clear
there is no doubt about that oh
it looks really nice on the outside oh
you're back oh
yeah i'm back welcome back and the guest
decided to i think uh zombie pickles are
riding on the kfp employee
let me see right here
[Laughter]
that is so cute i saw that before that
is so cute
is this the uh kitty zone the kids
see my employees are so great they they
wait where's the button out there
they care for the children they hang out
with the children
it's just a great relationship that we
have
with our guests with our customers
that's why we got such high ratings
everywhere uh uh-huh
i see yes
all right no i'm not hurting you i'm not
telling you not at all
but if you're doubting that what i just
said then you're doubting that my
employees are the best employees
ever and then i don't think they're
happy with that
oh sorry there's i put some cobblestone
where
where it doesn't belong oh hold on
there oh thank you
oh my god nice dodge nice dodge kiana
yo i'm here i'm here i'm here
[Music]
until
okay i'm trying i'm gonna go up there
again and
probably uh until i make it up there
again there's gonna be another grass
and another gas and another gas and
another cast and another one
and another one and another enough
no more gas please
why did they fall off nah
[Music]
ah all right
you keep working tensho yeah i'm trying
i'm trying
i wanna i wanna get in there
[Music]
i was just gonna try a wall
i'm gonna get rid of that eventually
maybe i'll do it now okay
so what else do we need to do though the
cooking station serving and there's
nothing
we don't cook it here we import it uh
from the from yeah but you still need
we still need like a cashier and stuff
you know oh yeah
okay do you by any chance have a
leftover
bell bill maybe i have
maybe i still have one i think i still
have a leftover bell
hmm is that my counter at the original
branch we have a bell
um where you go like full karen and be
like
what is with my order i i i i i
don't i've been waiting for so long why
are you telling me to get out of the
store i don't give a [\h__\h] i have
rights to be here this is unbelievable i
will call the police i will sue your
[\h__\h] are you this is how my
my my oh wait i ran out of i ran out of
cobblestone
oh yeah
in our story we don't have a problem
with parents we can deal with them
yeah another oh i guess there isn't
oh i should have brought her away hold
on
[Music]
so i um you don't have cobblestone then
i should i'm gonna go get some
okay okay we almost found off the
ceiling though the ceiling looks like
[\h__\h] though
i mean maybe from the inside you have
more stairs by chance
stairs yeah i have uh downstairs just
one one
uh
there you go oh my god there we go again
i'll fight i'll fight you
look at me
skill nice
[Music]
oh very nice very nice
professional tennis player
yeah we didn't use the red crown cream
on the inside like the
serving but actually uh outside would be
nice too to have some
more color on the outside like maybe
how about
how about using it
i know where to use it i know where to
use it i think
um
do you want to give me the red concrete
yeah i can give you off
wait thank you thank you
thank you thank god these toys
i would say uh it should be
either the ground level because i i
think i made the kfb original branch
also with a red grounds
like like no it was it was black and
then i think it was
red maybe or i mean we don't have to
completely copy it we could make for
example
this part red ah
and i think that would look quite nice
[Music]
i can't pick it up i can't pick it up
i see i see i'm full my inventory is
full
okay i can grab it i think i got it
that's full there god damn it
okay oh no
nice yeah i like it i think i like it
should we make uh this column here red
too maybe
like this one the one next to the door
yeah
okay yeah or the one um
or uh or yeah okay okay
idea idea no uh-huh
no no no no no no no
no no no we could
wait do you have a silk attached to not
destroy the the nope glad
okay well then it's five
so i was thinking we put glass
here again so that it's a two two
oh got it oh can we put
buttons on that uh
red in the middle and then instead of
yes we can yes
and then here the glass oh very nice
oh
i have a little bit of glass i have
eight
and it might just be that's just enough
yeah okay now
don't mess up
nice okay the back can stay the ladies
oh this looks cute without those
changing colors
nice oh that's supposed to be the cash
register that's cute
that's a cute idea oh
button on glass doesn't work didn't you
okay can you put it
should you put it down below then okay
down below
oh the button you need you need like a
button or a contraption to open the
thing
ah that's fine uh i also prepared
stop banging oh my god hmm where did you
put it
here
oh this one is
oh we don't have a ceiling here
oh yeah i was going to get the
cobblestone but then we did something
else
[Music]
but i don't like the ceiling is there
nothing prettier that we can use
i mean we can do it oh so strong like
iron
me that's gonna take a lot of iron but
we have a lot of iron
you could try it or stone actually just
not cobblestone to stone it's like
polished i think i have a bunch at home
okay
i think we should make one trip home
uh but i am going to
leave some of the materials in the in
the chest
i want to use pressure plates outside
because the piglet and
stuff oh chad was saying we should use
pressure plates on the outside too but i
said i don't want to use them
i mean we can always do like uh
um
okay i think should we try polish dart
polished what polish die right oh
i think i have some at home it's still
it's the same material as our base in
another
so you can see on the way back
i'll bring some minecarts back
good idea yep
oh you could make a red and white jacket
roof yeah but the roof kind of has to be
something else than concrete because
apparently uh concrete doesn't burn but
it explodes still
so we want to make it out of stone
like some some kind of stone
so not not everything can be fancy but
we'll make it as fancy as possible
don't worry clark this is the um
how much go away
[Music]
do we look like we have time for you
yeah
this is what it looks like what do you
[Music]
think
yep okay okay i started
okie dokie
so as i was saying we are we are we are
successful business women we don't
have time to deal with these stupid
magma thingies
okay you bring those was i supposed to
bring something else to you
i want to just look for a bell and this
site
oh i do have quite a lot i have a lot
oh i can bring some
uh l actually do you have a lot of of
those streamlights left
[Music]
i think there's like i think i have like
in the in the never chest oh okay and
yeah i think i think
i don't do i not have any bells left
bells no i thought i had like one more
bell do you not see a bell i don't see a
bell
i want a bell i mean maybe it's like
from um village villages right
yeah yeah but i think the the close by
ones
do you have one nope i did not
um
i think oh you can craft it with gold
apparently
what oh i thought
oh that makes sense belle
wrong what's it called what's it called
no you can't okay
no you can't you can't so i guess it's
just it's an item that you have to get
from a village well unfortunate
i'll eventually add one when i find
another one
we're almost done now almost there
i'm gonna start putting the uh ceiling
back oh you're back in the nether
yes
[Music]
i wonder what quartz blocks look like
though
we wanted to farm a lot of courts don't
we
[Music]
but it's everywhere it wouldn't and we
wouldn't like it i think but
um no it's okay with that guy right
[Music]
let me change it later so
by the way why haven't you opened the
taco bell yet
uh oops when is gonna be the opening of
a
taco bell i don't know i haven't thought
about what to uh
what to do for the friendship for sure
well tacos wait i'm like visualize
are there tacos uh it'll be back
well good that we have two streams going
exactly
hello guys how are you doing guys
you want to fight you do the you do the
gas style just keep doing your
thing
if i look up i cut out probably oh
i'm not trying to outgrow it i thought
you were fighting it
hey can we leave it burning like that
actually that looks nice
oh yeah
we're not going to be going up there
anyways so
we can just light it on fire with like
foot and steel
that's that's nice i like that because
uh their boss is a phoenix so
oh nice you killed it
what's up good job and you'll see it
from so far away even when you get lost
you'll be like
oh yeah that's kfb
i mean i don't think anyone will get
lost
here are you sure about that i'm i'm not
oh no the fire is gone opening some
applications welcome
congratulations you are you are part of
kfb now congratulations
congratulations oh they're children
though i need to bring some seats
congratulations you are hired
what's going on over here and you get a
and you get a job and you get a job
and you get a job and they're probably
gonna escape because um
because of the automatic could be maybe
make the inside a button too so that
they don't escape i wonder
i don't think they can trigger the
pressure plates are you sure about that
they're very smart my employees are very
smart
are you sure they're gonna die
what do you guys mean they're gonna die
yeah they're too light to trigger the
pressure plates i think really
they're triggering it they are
triggering it but then
you didn't make it outside me but
they're they're gonna figure it out
like how my cat uh figure it out to to
open doors
i heard that you're trying to escape huh
uh mama won't let you escape you applied
for this job and you're gonna work it
now
okay i'll bring some food for you guys
you guys get a pop-tart view on
everything that's happening
what look up
[Music]
i was surprised myself it's first thing
we're like
i don't wanna she's making a
brand new never i'm not gonna work that
as hell
but now they're like super excited about
it i wanted this there and there you go
there you go are you guys okay blink
twice if not
i don't think they can blink there you
go
so they're okay should we actually light
it on fire
on the top of the room i mean
there's probably gonna be more guests
that are gonna help you with that
[Music]
definitely
um problem
like stop thinking
i will put you in the user room and i
will i will keep your eyes open i have
my methods
[Music]
i didn't wanna i didn't i didn't want to
be
i wanted to be a good leader i wanted to
i wanted to be followers is not the
answer can't you
i know i know i know but
sometimes they kind of they kind of they
kind of made me who i
am now i didn't want it
to be like this i didn't want to be this
violent i didn't want them
to like he's scared they're running
no there's more outside on this
[Music]
don't let them go they're still children
they're not gonna be okay and they're
never alone
they'll be fine
a lion raises their club puff
you're not gonna be okay i have to
protect them
no no no
no you guys are afraid
we make signals
did you really let them all escape
enough no
they did it on their own they're smart
as you said
well there's still a bunch of them in
there okay good luck surviving okay
good luck i'll give you some food
because i love you
good luck surviving good luck good luck
oh my god there's so many escapers
you are supposed to take this
what is it you're not gonna eat my
children are you oh wait they're coming
oh my god
they're coming after me i'll wait oh
wait i can't bring them the jar is not
my
my position that's not my job potential
okay my children come over here
come over here let me feed you mama
mama brought some food come here you
love your mama don't you
you don't do you do you do that you love
your mama right right right
right let me feel you mama got some food
come here babies come here babies yo
no baby i love you i love you
[Music]
yes it's mama you can never resist your
mama
come here come here get some food come
here follow me
follow mama
oh such a good baby a good baby
yes good baby good baby good baby
ah so proud of my babies
um huh yes you're going back to the real
ground
yes yeah could you bring um
uh like maybe like uh four fences and
two gates or something i'm not sure how
much i need to make this properly but
yeah we need to i mean i'm just i'm just
doing this for them like if they're
gonna
escape they're gonna be out there and
jump into lava and [\h__\h] i don't want
and that's dangerous come here
[Music]
that's the right choice babies that's
the right choice
interesting how they see me through the
windows but the guests
doesn't gas to don't
anyways we always come back of course
you do
what did i come here for again what a
flinders deal right
[Music]
oh babies
what happened guys weren't we supposed
to escape no it's dangerous outside you
got to stay with mama
trust me mama is pesto just sit under my
feathers i'll warm you
i mean it's already pretty warm out here
but still
um actually it might be too wrong for
you guys so maybe i should put some air
conditioning in here but
yeah okay
you know how did you guys ever see like
um
uh an image of of
uh a chicken and even after after
she um uh hatched her babies
even after that she still uh
the mama chickens will still sit on
their babies
and then she then they would stand up
and then wow you see
under their fluff coming out so many so
many little babies
it's so cute it's so cute
it's so adorable
ah they're all talking to me they love
their mama
it's too late guys
it's the right choice
sit on us they want they want they like
that they want to be sit on
there's two types of employees in the
world
[Laughter]
there's only one type no yes
are you gonna be back soon come here
oh wait i did have some pants but i
didn't have a gate so
um could you outside of the door because
i'm gonna i'm gonna
um how about you just put all the
chickens
here we put the fence right here and
then put the gate right here
but they have to to clean the tables and
stuff oh you can lift them up once a
while
don't worry about it
i only brought one gate and six senses
we're we're running
short on uh
if you put it like right in front of the
door but there's a gap right there
oh we can move it we can move it
uh we have some customers reading out
there yeah we're not open yet
dudes we're not open go away hold on
i'll
give you i'll give you the fences you
can i only brought six and
one momma has two mama has two i can i
can take care of them
my babies i don't wanna give this to you
a ski thing
and my babies i just i just hatched them
i can't give them away yet
wait i think you took the it's just
i'm defensive you can work while doing
the uh doing the uh
babysitting job
okay but now they're gonna run out
all right
i'm gonna get them back i'm gonna get
them back no problem
i kind of uh can't be here
guess it can like like you only made one
like
one gate yeah i had i brought what i had
oh that's fun why does it
oh how does it do that because of the
button
[Music]
okay this is a really annoying people
are gonna
be really frustrated when they try to
get into kfb
you can put fences and then put pressure
plates if you want to
yeah how do you make pressure plates uh
you go to the crafting cable
and type in pressure
do i have any i don't have any of the
material
[Music]
all right can i not use cobblestone
can you not use cobblestone for that i'm
not sure
no apparently not
i have iron okay let's go for iron then
we might want to fill in this little
uh
clip of that right beside qfp
[Music]
wait a second so if i just put it in
front there it will work
oh it works nice
one second let me hydration time guys
hydrate yourself
um
okay they're still backing banging out
unbelievable
context you know the context do i have
to repeat myself
there's new viewers in the chat
well that's their fault
i'm not gonna keep on explaining myself
also maybe i should just uh
i'm gonna recreate this whole thing i
gotta fix those rails ah
but no problem um
what is it uh one of your employees try
to go into the
store but oh he wants to go inside
oh i see now they're regretting that
they left me
you never leave mama it's not gonna end
well
no one wants to leave mama mama's
cooking is the best
you know i don't really like cooking yep
[Music]
i don't really i mean i
wait
i can't cook some french toast and some
wow that fire up there it really does
look
badass wow right oh so good
what is it what is it stupid thing
i ran out of rails again goddammit oh
i thought i brought some oh
wait where did you put them uh
not sure where this is
i don't want my chickens to fall in here
so i think uh kfb is done
yeah something sounds like it's opening
but
let's not worry about it don't worry
about it
i mean whenever there are too many
employees
i'm just gonna hire some more until they
understand
that escaping is not an option
one day they will understand run away
of course they will understand before
it's too late they will understand that
it's better for them to
to just stay hey
it looks pretty good yeah okay so
maybe we should have made the ceiling
like too hot oh well
chilly okay
stop wait hold on okay there's like a
puzzle to get in
yep oh wait uh wait i'll put the rails
in
the chest i didn't bring any redstone uh
let me take the stuff though ah
i have one unless it's okay i'll fix it
eventually
but everything everything sounds like
it's burning because of the seal
that's a nice uh frying sound that's
true that's true
freshly crunched
you do do you want to put it into the
furnace
so we can cook that and then yeah
there's a lot there's gonna be some
fresh food too
actually i guess
a fridge a fridge would be nice
looking good
or maybe a red fridge
totally looks like a fridge nice
yeah with that i think we're done you
can't
see it has been completed looking nice
[Music]
okay oh yeah nice employees look here
apply now for the new position at
another branch
wait let me let me let me get let me so
we can take a prop right here guys
so we can take a proper um picture
let me let me let me grab my employees
okay now they're looking at me nice
[Music]
i'll hatch it you guys just keep on
laying the eggs
let's take one from the outside but
first we would probably have to kill
them
wait a second this is so confusing
oh it's running away coming back um i
don't trust it
i'm missing all my shots
[Music]
where are you i fell down though
the pits the pit of death yeah oh i'm
burning yeah
is it destroying everything again uh no
we can't be safe
for now okay kfb is the the
safest place in the neighborhood uh
something blew up right outside but it
can be fixed
maybe we should reinforce the outside
too a little bit yeah
yeah because beyond and i
when i have some time i'll i'll put some
concrete here and there
the rail's kind of broke but maybe don't
worry about it
did you kill it run
what the gas oh
think we killed i think we killed it one
thing it's not running away is it over
there
is it that one anyway we gotta take a
picture quickly
uh right here from this side but maybe
maybe like from an angle oopsie
uh i think just down here is okay
the
[Music]
right here okay
and
[Music]
oh jump okay hold on hold on hold on
okay
one two three
and the front was made oh my god
one two three okay
wait wait one more one more i post
okay okay one two three
i'll jump later okay but you just jump
in here free okay
one two three four
i kind of support for myself okay maybe
it wasn't the whole second one one more
time one more time
one two three yeah
it's just like i did it no
why when why would i hurt it i only
hatch eggs i don't lay eggs
there's a big difference there
okay
[Music]
thanks for watching thank you guys for
watching and
uh have fun working at kfp we are still
taking applications if you're looking
for a job
this is the time i think at the moment
it's just very uh a lot of people might
be looking for a job so
um i think there this is a really great
place to work uh our employees
only have good things to say about kfp
and um
maybe in the future taco bell will have
an opening too in cooperation
with uh with with me i would love to
help you although you'd probably be
better without me
thank you for helping me build the
second branch of kfb today
thank you thank you for having me
it's okay the the process is part of the
fun
yep yeah nothing i'll end it with eating
some nice cooked pork chops and not
chicken
we would never we would never cook
chicken no
no no no no no see i have pork chops in
my hand everything's all right don't
worry guys
oh
quick hide bye guys
you