[Music]
so
[Applause]
yeah maybe you should maybe you should
use it more often
i'm a sheriff i'm sorry i just can't i
can't help myself
i can't help myself sometimes it's
totally fine i like to howdy
get so excited to be a cowboy i mean
you were only a cowboy for that one
stream
are you saying you're still a cowboy now
i'm i'm always a little bit of a cowboy
just a little bit inside yeah
well welcome back everyone on to the
second takamuni stream did everyone also
watch the first one i hope you did
did you yes you i hope you did and if
you did not uh go maybe watch that after
this uh if you would so like
if you would so please do yeah
never miss check out your life hashtag
hashtag yolk what that's a
that's a little other hashtag that we
use
at kfp that's uh that's very sweet
yeah i think nice job and we got some
snowfall in here
and the theme uh topic down below
says it as well but we did go to
[Music]
yeah in japan they sometimes jokingly
call hokkaido
deck idol because it's just so huge and
takai means
big in japanese yeah yay
yes yes yes yes as you uh can see
already it was very very snowy for the
people who don't know
wait my snow is like kind of like
bugging out damn it okay well you guys
get used to it
um it's uh hokkaido is um
in the north very most northern
prefecture of
japan so it is insanely colder there's a
huge difference from when you're
in i don't know tokyo osaka whatever and
then compare it to
hokkaido right now the snow there is
absolutely insane
yep and in the city it's pretty it's
it's pretty snowy but when you get into
the inaka it's like it's like go f word
yourself snowy
like like literally the the amount of
snow is about as tall as a small child
um it's it's that snowy and no but even
even in the city
it was like they had these mountains of
snows like on the side of the road
right it's like yeah like mountains
literal mountains
it's snow everywhere and it's constantly
like this kind of snow that you see on
the screen right now oh it disappeared
again
and that's that's the kind of like
powdery
cute small snow that's like constantly
snowing it's amazing
yup right how much how much
how much snow do you think falls in a
day uh
i i don't know but as i as i was
actually watching
i was watching some of the snow fall
just like the powder snowflakes yeah
and i had like this i had started
getting really really deep thoughts and
i thought to myself
what if every single snowflake that that
was falling through the air was like an
alternate universe or something like
that would there even be enough snow
i wonder what are you talking about i'm
just talking about my deep thoughts that
i had while looking at the snow kusatori
just saying i'm just trying to eat the
snow right now see that's something we
didn't do did you try to eat the snow
yes hey really a little bit and then it
tasted bad so i stopped
i forgot to try it now i'm doing it
hokkaido snow best snow i mean it
it kind of tastes i mean you got to
think about it this way though
you don't know where that snow came from
it wasn't like the water that made the
snow
yeah but listen do you know how weather
works
do you know that the water that that
makes up the snow
that falls down it has to come from
somewhere ah
you don't know where it came from i i
will tell you one thing about that
are you sure
i think that you're saying that to
protect yourself from the truth
it's okay i'm invincible anyway so i'm
not not exactly invincible but
i mean i guess you really don't have
anything to worry about because you are
immortal but still
you do so that's why we can eat snow as
much as we want but honestly i guess but
you you humans please don't do it
oh a little bit hurt a little bit
just don't you say that now but then
if it's if it's pure white then it's
okay to eat guys
if anything happens if any of you go to
the hospital uh
kiara's not responsible for that
afterwards she's just told you
thank you for the disclaimer yeah you
know just covering all the bases
on that regard so by the way
um this trip like originally i wanted to
go to hokkaido
anyway but how did this happen anyway
like
like you you kind of loki like
invited me to this trip right you were
like might be cool to go
i mean i've been before um so i wanted
to
go back yeah i just felt like going back
that's one important point is that uh
kelly has been here before and so we
we went to places uh she showed me some
places that she
has been to uh back then and
and she was super proud of showing me
those places it was very cute
well yes some of the really tasty food i
wanted to
i wanted to show you i don't know i mean
i
i don't know i'm so tired of solo travel
at this point
i'm tired of traveling by my dang self
so i thought why not bring someone along
this time so here we are
i get that i i do travel a lot on my own
as well and but it's nice to be with
someone
and it's also it was very nice to have
someone who had like
a little bit of experience in the place
where we went to
so we will introduce to you i took a
[\h__\h] ton of uh
photos uh to show them to you guys
and and um got them checked with manager
son
thank you genma thank you very much
and everything should be safe um we went
for
four days right four days yeah yeah oh
four nights four nights five days
four all of a sudden five days four
nights
yes i have to say though the first day
we pretty much didn't do anything yeah
except you know set up for this
yeah so that one kind of uh yeah
yeah it was a little bit of a wait yeah
yeah
but yeah let's get started so let me let
me get rid of the
phone which one is that um
we start off with a very random photo
maybe but
the thing is here guys we
we were at the airport and uh we met up
at the airport and we both wanted to
like have some kind of breakfast
right for us it was kind of like
breakfast right
and then kelly wanted to go to starbucks
so we went to starbucks and we ordered
one after another but
we we made the exactly stable
yeah i mean you can't resist the
strawberry cake man i tell you what
every time i see a strawberry cake i
want to eat it you you wanted it too and
it's tasty new
frappuccino as well yeah
that that's a new uh frappuccino in
japanese starbucks it's like what was it
like it was like chocolate
with something and vanilla it tasted
like a cake
it's a very yummy frappuccino that was
really good and then we got some
strawberry cake
see this is this is just that was the
first moment where i realized wait we
have such a similar
taste in food and and stuff like that
it's yeah we'll eat sweets for real
meals
even though you technically really
shouldn't do it but we'll do it
so yeah we waited for our flight because
we were a little bit early
and we talked about stuff a lot of stuff
right
hot gossip callie got some things off of
her chest which i think was really
necessary
right i mean we all got stuff like that
yeah
yeah yeah so and then it was time to
board the flight i don't really have any
picture from that but
uh kelly got us some nice seats
yeah i did i mean well here's the way
that i figured
i mean you guys always come over to my
streams and you know send me those
those super chats to say this is for the
homie moon here's for your
your vacation etcetera go go marry
kusatori and whatever and clearly
uh the marriage thing i won't do it um
but i thought to myself why not use that
super chat money to get um
to get some decent um seats for us
so we were comfortable yeah because of
you guys thanks for paying for my
upgrade kelly
you're welcome i got you it was pretty
cool it was very comfortable because up
until now i
always only uh like i i've been on a
million flights especially long distance
flights
and but all of them economy class
because you know
bro broke burp but right same name
no money reaper yeah but it's after like
a million flights
in economy just freaking hurts because i
got some chronic pain too
freaking hurts man
finally could relax yeah this one was
very nice very very comfortable the
ladies were really nice to us to the the
flight attendants
sounds fun not a bad point what did you
actually the only problem was that you
couldn't sit next to me
yeah i mean that was bound to happen you
know we were a little bit
we were a little bit late because
initially we wanted to go by train
right yeah but they but the the place
that i wanted to sit in in the train was
closed
not
ticket yeah that available that was
pretty last minute
yup all right so
we boarded i don't as i said i have
nothing from the flight and in the first
day nothing really happened so
yeah except suffering lots of suffering
the next picture is just pizza
oh yeah that's right that's the pizza
yeah you got pizza we got pizza because
we didn't have any time
uh to go out to eat because you wanted
to play minecraft and and i wanted to do
um a release stream
even though i was cardboard yeah you
were also cardboard yeah
that's that's uh we tried for hours to
set up my switch with your capture card
uh with the with the hotel mod uh
tv monitor it just didn't work out even
even though we tried really hard so
we didn't have time to go anywhere fancy
to eat we just got room service
and then he also ate some pieces of my
pizza
yes it was pretty delicious i gotta say
not bad not bad
i took off the olive stone and you liked
your lips now that sounds something no i
don't like olives
i don't like garlic you said you took
them off for me oh yeah
yeah that's right oh yeah i fed you but
i took them off
you didn't now you didn't feed me with
your hand or anything you just let me
have it
don't give them the wrong idea
they would have been very happy with
that idea though
[Music]
i mean i mean it's my it's my the food
that um
was supposed to be mine so i did feed
you my food somehow
yeah and i looked like a good mommy bird
i picked up the
the food carefully that you didn't like
on the pizza
yes thank you thank you for doing that
you're welcome
yeah so that's the first day nothing
really happened
and uh we woke up and we got some nice
breakfast
eh yeah you can write in this picture
you can kind of see
that we were very high up can you guys
see that
what floor was that like oh my god i
think it was the
the 30 35th yeah it was so freaking high
we were in the middle of uh
sapporo
they got they made us some omelettes
yeah they were good omelets too it was
the kind that you go and you
you say hey may i please have an omelet
and then a chef makes you the omelet in
front of your eyes
yeah that was yummy although i'm i
when i go to hotel breakfast the one
thing that i
always grab for is the fresh fruit
i like to eat eat lots and lots of fresh
food you didn't you don't really see it
in the picture but i got a lot of
pineapples in the back
what did you eat pretty much the same
thing except
what else did i get that was kind of
different oh you got something
you got even got some cakes i think yeah
yeah there was some
cake and then uh you could make like
a tasty fruit yogurt and i made a tasty
fruit yogurt
it was pretty good and then what else i
got soup curry
you could make soup curry for breakfast
that blew me away
i was like whoa okay cool give me the
vegetables give me the soup curry and
you just put it together and
there you go soup curry for breakfast
one thing though that
i have to say is that we i think both of
us
chose very western options
and because the hotel breakfast
definitely had a lot of
japanese breakfast options
we went for a lot of the western options
yeah um
i mean i the the japanese breakfast
options are
nice too which is not what i'm used to
yeah i actually don't mind washoku
we did have a lot of japanese
traditional food
on this trip we did we did yeah since
the view is so amazing i got some more
pictures from the view look at that oh
look at that that was our breakfast
view yeah it was pretty cool you can see
the whole city
that's so amazing yeah it was and it was
it you don't really see it on the
picture but it was snowing like
constantly
it's it was like it was insane let me
try to make it a bit bigger
look at that yeah me tail wow
wow yeah best view in sapporo honestly
yeah it was really cool you could see
the mountains and the city and the snow
was falling too so it was like a snow
globe
meaning outside being like inside a snow
globe actually
oh yeah it was very nice we were both
very uh
tired though i think at least me i was
very very tired because uh getting up
for breakfast
so early is a real pain for me
oh yeah that's right meanwhile i would
just roll out of bed and be like all
right let's go
this time actually i think oh wasn't it
like well yeah i was like i was
like i was still in bed and you were
getting ready and i was like i'm not
gonna go i'm gonna continue sleeping but
the last second i was like okay whatever
i'm gonna go with you
yep yep i didn't want you to go alone
and
i i felt like i would have regretted not
to go
oh it's okay i didn't go on the second
day though did i um no no you didn't
yeah that's okay though i enjoyed a nice
time alone by myself looking over the
city which was nice
the thing is though like i i generally
only eat like two meals per day
and i figured that on the second day
after the breakfast we would have gone
for a ramen for lunch uh-huh so i was
just you know trying to keep some space
in my belly
true facts which was really necessary
because ramen fills up so
much oh my god true especially if you
eat all of it
so while we were at breakfast we were
thinking of what to do honestly
um for we had like uh two days in
sapporo and we didn't really
plan much for like what exactly we would
be doing
i mean i thought we were mostly just
going to walk around the city and that
kind of thing
too so we tried to look up where we
should go but
we ended up on the first day
to go skiing i really wanted to go
skiing i think both of us both of us
right i only went skiing
once in live up until then didn't did
you
actually i i skied quite a bit i used to
you know reaper parents would take me to
the snowy mountains of the third layer
of hell
and we would i went to ski school
but that for both of us that was a long
long long long time ago
yeah it was a long time ago i was a
little reaper so i had to try and
remember all the skills that i had
acquired
we both really didn't do that much of a
good job
um there's in in sapporo there's a very
close by
uh place where you can go i forgot the
name where we went but
um
it was pretty close it was actually just
a half an hour
right we were on the train that's new
oh we were for 15 minutes on the train
and then 15 minutes on the taxi
and then we arrived here i mean i really
wasn't i actually wasn't really sure
about
about going skiing because it was so so
sudden and i was a little on the fence i
was like ah we really gonna
we really gonna go skiing today but
eventually i
kind of warmed up to the idea how i get
it warmed up to the idea
over time i kind of thought okay yeah
sure this could be fun
and it was close by so it was okay you
know originally i think we were if we
were gonna go skiing we were gonna do it
on the second day but we ended up doing
it on
the first day for some reason yeah but
i it was i i wanted to go skiing again
for such a long time
and you know i thought it would be like
when you when you like haven't uh been
on a bicycle for like
a million of years that you would just
you know remember it again
how it works easily yeah that was not
the case
not so much the only thing that i
remembered was pizza and french fries
so hear me out when you want to kind of
like slow down a bit you put your skis
in a p
in a pizza shape and when you want to go
really fast you put them uh
like french fries uh side by side yeah
and and then you that you do it like
that and then you go side to side side
to side side to side
well you
[Music]
went very very very slowly but yeah
it's fun i i we by the way we by the way
had nothing
no equipment or anything we just rented
everything like uh the the whole ski
clothing everything
we were able to rent like the goggles
and even a hat
and stuff kelly actually
in the beginning she was like i want to
be safe she got herself a helmet
yeah it's a big old helmet i eventually
took it off because i didn't like it it
looked really clunky
but safety comes first um now i already
i mean you know the snow the snow pants
were kind of sexy though i gotta say
they had like i mean you had the snow
pants and then they had like these
overall strap thingies on them
you know and i was already wearing
something kind of you know tight under
under it you know my athletic wear and
whatnot underneath the big jacket still
felt kind of sexy to be honest
i kind of liked it yeah um it made me
feel like a cool a cool
uh a cool ski skiing
gal i guess you know we definitely now
i'm getting weird feelings inside of me
i'm gonna stop talking about that
what do you what you guys see now is
from that angle like i guess i guess it
doesn't look very steep
this was like the beginner's um skiing
spot
there were a bunch of spots yeah slopes
there were a bunch of slopes that were
much much more difficult but we went for
the beginner's one
um it does look kind of flat here but it
really wasn't that flat it was
quite steep at some points right
um but steep especially in the beginning
yeah but my my camera i guess just made
it made it look kind of uh
flat anyway so we spent uh
all our time here and
guys
remember guys when i wrote on my twitter
that um when did i write i wrote that i
that some yeah i had a near-death
experience well let me tell you it
happened here
yeah and yes it did i mean
listen i thought it was pretty funny
just overall because you are so excited
about skiing you're like let's go let's
go and then we get to the top of this
mountain you look at me you say callie
i'm scared and i say i say all right
kiara
follow me follow my lead remember pizza
french fries and
and i say i'll go first and i i went i
decided
wait a second i got a graphic for that
and uh i wanna
i wanna show a little bit so let me let
me take this
little ski woman as a as a example okay
this is cali okay
now please explain how you were skiing
all right so i was going side to side
to the side much slower it's much slower
well yeah slow in the beginning because
it was steep but then once i got further
down i
started going a little bit faster you
know you go side to side you turn
you turn left you turn right and if you
go fast it can
it can be kind of exhilarating but also
scary when you feel like you're losing
control so i was skiing side to side
right
she's saying that she went faster out at
some point but that's the lie she
actually still was insanely slow
no it was the [\h__\h] okay listen now hear
me out
hear me out here's the deal here's the
deal
so yeah sure i may have been going side
to side and
it was fun i was enjoying myself it felt
fast to me but
but that's the way you're so i mean no
no wait kelly kelly
and the side to side is correct yeah but
you were constantly with your skiers you
were constantly stopping yourself you
were constantly like breaking
didn't feel like that way to me at all i
felt like i was going super fast
when you're watching from far away it
doesn't feel like that now you on the
other hand
okay okay so imagine cali like being
here on the side
from side to side slowly and then now
comes me okay i was i was trying to do
the same thing in the beginning but
yeah sure you were i it was i was i just
wasn't able to do it now imagine this
little pink
guy here this little pink girl is cali
she's slowly
slowly doing her thing and then i go i
try i try i try and then like
okay and then i just i just was gone i
did that repeated for many times i just
swooshed
down to the bottom look okay just hear
you screaming as you go
straight french fry ski down past me
straight down the mountain
no side to side just straight down i
couldn't stop
it no turning i couldn't stop it was so
scary it was so freaking scary that the
snow was low-key pretty
pretty hard pretty stiff pretty hard
it was like i was so assuming but don't
worry this is not where it happened
this is not where it happened we've
repeated that whole process for for a
few times
went up again i lost my stick once
we went up up up up up and then we did
the same thing
cali goes slowly
and then i go i try it i try it again i
try to do the same thing as carrying i
go
and then like and i'm glad again
straight straight down the mountain once
again straight down
we repeated that for a few times and
and wait let me let's take a look at the
picture that i'm showing you in the
background again
uh see now
it at the end at the very end where the
slope kind of stops there's still like a
lot of
room to play around with and like stop
yourself that's why i was fine with that
zoom speed um it was like like maybe
like
20 meters of of space that you could you
know
slow yourself so i was fine but
it's at some point ah we were actually
saying this is the last one
right yeah we were i said this is the
last one and i held myself back from
saying
you know you haven't wiped out so far i
held myself back
i didn't let myself say it i said you
know what kiara you
never mind i was legit though every time
i was going down there
i was somehow having fun but i was also
at the same time
every time screaming like
[Music]
i was legit so so freaking panicked and
scared
so yeah then here comes the last
the last slope and basically
um well once again i hear you screaming
as you go straight past me
yep and then i lose control
and i watch the whole thing too yeah you
were behind me because i
i i was i i over uh how to say i
i passed you yeah and you passed me but
where where you passed me i was
basically at the bottom of the
the hill as well and so i saw i saw it
happening all to my right everything in
vivid detail
4k i i i don't know how much speed that
was but but in full speed
i i like crashed
into a fence and like
with my full body like my full body was
like getting caught
in the fence but then uh my my skiers my
hat my goggles my gloves
everything would like heat it away
everything fell
in like a 10 meter 20 meter
radial distance the net just absorbed
you
the net came with me i ripped out the
the
nets everything was like yeah it was
scattered everywhere
and i was like i was dying
i i i was on the ground and like
oh my god it hurt so much everything was
gone
then and people ran up to me cali was
there instantly i don't know how you
wear so fast suddenly
understand my skin pretty quick suddenly
there was also like five or ten staff
members around me and they were all like
it died
it was it was
i thought i was going to break something
like the moment the moment like when i
was
like speeding into that defense i was
like
am i going to die what the [\h__\h] i can't
turn around i can't turn around this is
too fast
it was insane it was well you didn't die
so there you go
but it still hurts i have like um uh
like i still have uh like a green blue
oh my god it's it's yellow now yeah
huge bruise on my arm and uh i had i'm
i'm fine though like it and just in the
few uh
in the few first one hours uh
what hours i can't talk english anymore
it did hurt a lot
but yeah that was that was my near-death
experience
and death was near me at that moment she
was like she sure was
she was like i started
i started loki crying because of the
pain but
but kelly was like we're so sweet
[Music]
he was so worried about me i just wanted
to make sure you were okay
you know it was so
[\h__\h] crazy it looked painful it
looked painful
why did that have to happen
yeah well i mean you were doing very
good up until then so i think you could
consider the rest of it to be
a victory as long as you have fun that's
the most important
i used to be able to ski well though
yeah well i mean maybe you're just out
of practice you got to do it a lot more
you know yeah
crazy crazy very crazy experience so
that was that was the first basically
the first day
of our trip
and it was so so cold oh yes
like even just just for one second
taking your hands
out of the gloves yeah like listen i'm
not exactly a hot-blooded being
but what the [\h__\h]
like that was freaking cold yeah with
that let the ski cloth so we are fine
totally fine
but everything that was not covered by
those ski clothes and the gloves
instantly was freezing to death
yep and and it was formatted in a way
that if you wanted to like
return your things that you rented and
that kind of thing
you had to walk up this mountain yeah
and so
with the ski shoes if you tried to walk
up it you'd probably try
you'd probably break your legs because
you know you really can't move your legs
around in those it's a very steep hill
so you had to walk on your tippy-toes
and if you tried to come back down i
mean kiara you saw it as i
i grabbed a water bottle and i tried to
walk back down the hill to where you
were waiting with the skis
and i was waddling like this and
eventually
gave up and i just i i just sat on the
ground and started sliding towards you
it was impossible it was very cute the
way you were
i was very scared that you would fall
and then break yourself something as
well so
yeah i thought i would too yeah i said i
told you too
i told you from the distance to sit down
and just you know slide down with your
ass
yeah yeah eventually i did eventually
that's that's a safer option
the only way yeah that was but
even though i hurt myself pretty badly i
still
um have to say it was a very precious
memory because i wanted to go skiing
again for such a long time
and it was so nice to finally you know
get get out of the
city center where we are right now
out of the busy streets with so many
people finally get out
breathe some fresh air in the nature and
and
see all that snow and do something fun
that you usually don't do
right it was a activity that's
that we don't normally do cali
yeah yeah something different
we went back quite early and
since i was uh very exhausted
i i took a tiny nap and you went uh
quickly to buy some omiyage
yeah it's for a manager
and then and then we went for dinner
going tell me where did you bring us
oh yeah so i remember last time that i
went
to hokkaido um
i went to a very delicious soup curry
place
i recall the reason that i recall it so
vividly is because some reaper bates and
i were visiting hokkaido
and we could not find a single place to
eat at all because it was a saturday
night we wanted soup curry and every
single place was full
you needed to have a reservation and we
were we were crying we were starving
and eventually we walked into an
alleyway and found this random soup
curry place
went inside it was just the most
delicious soup curry i've ever had in my
entire existence so i remembered it
and i thought i want to go there again
so we went there um and then i was so
excited we got up to the door and then
it said
closed mm-hmm yeah but
but they let us do takeout so we got
takeout so we got it and then we quickly
went back to the hotel room
i honestly uh forgot to take a photo of
the soup curry but it was very yummy
it was good it seems to be some kind of
specialty
in sapporo or in hokkaido
got no pictures but the view that you
see right now that's the view that we
have from our hotel room
oh so we were looking at that while we
were eating the sukkoi
it was very yummy it was pretty it has
it has like a
has like a lot of vegetables in it right
and uh yes we're good for you a whole
chicken leg was in it
yeah a whole chicken leg which you
enjoyed but i just i just got vegetables
because i
i'm not into i'm not into that yes i'm
not about that chicken but
you got to choose how spicy it was of
course kiara and i both chose zero
yeah that was funny i can handle spice
but yeah it was fine it's fine i can
handle spice it's just
i don't know i want it to be safe
it was very yummy perfect
dish for like the winter nights
yep in the cold winter uh-huh
yummy yummy and then we went to bed
and we woke up to this beautiful view
this is i like it
i like the difference from i mean in
that photo because it's night you don't
see all the snow much but
it was still filled with snow but then
in the morning it's like
you can you can barely see the back yeah
and i love the idea that um i love this
the idea that it snowed so much in the
night
as well there's something really cozy
about that knowing that you're going to
sleep and there's tons of snow falling
was beautiful just looking outside the
window was so
healing so nice healing yep
that's the word for it what did we do
then did we just is that the day where
we just went to
the next hotel yeah oh okay
oh ah before we went we got went and got
some ramen now here
i even took uh the name of the shop so
japanese people oh promotion woo
like literally right outside of the
station it was underground
it was very yummy and i have i even took
a photo of our orders
there you go yeah so right side is cali
left side is me miso ramen is like the
jab at the hokkaido
specific not specific but kind of serves
miso ramen as a specialty i guess
yep so i actually do the tasty boy photo
oh yes damn it i forgot that one but um
because it says here uh on the right
side the second tag says tasty bold egg
and i
i thought i showed callie when i was
overlapping the
tickets it said tasty boy i mean i order
my ramen i order my ramen for tasty boys
lots of extra yum yum yum yum basically
we got
miso ramen i got it with corn and butter
that was yummy
you can add stuff on top of it and you
got it with
the tasty boy the cornbreader you got
also got a
sapporo classic beer yes
of course and you got the the genki no
miso ramen
yes and indeed i the genki
it did come out it did very much so uh
deru
it means
the ramen that gives you energy oh yeah
yeah yeah
yeah the gang the genki sure did
[Music]
the um what do you call the meat again
uh oh like a like pork yeah but but it
doesn't have like a special
name that's it again i don't know
what i said i'm sure they will tell us
i'm sure they know
oh god i forgot all the names of the
ingredients not nuts
what's the white thing in the middle
again oh um
the bean sprouts yeah bean sprouts yeah
i love them
i love them that's mine and then
callie's looked similar
but she had the egg the tasty boy
the tasty boy oh and i think in the back
you got some scrambled eggs right
[Music]
so good oh my god
so we were sitting there and eating for
like i don't know a whole hour normally
in japanese salary monday
like 10 5 or 10 minutes and it's gone
but yeah it took us quite a while
especially i take a lot of
time because i eat ramen like this
because i can't slurp with the i can't
use
i i can't totally use um
cali help me out there chopsticks
chopsticks yes
you can totally use chopsticks but i
can't slurp so i just use the chopsticks
to place
the noodles on the big spoon and then i
put all the other ingredients on it
which is actually quite a nice way to
use i think because you get
all the experience uh at once in your
mouth
sure yeah properly though
yes i did i what even is the proper way
to eat it i wonder we just slurp it all
in
yeah i guess so huh either way it was
tasty
it was really yummy very filling i went
with an empty stomach
but it was very difficult to finish
we made ourselves uh on the way to our
trip we had a few difficulties there
kelly do what do you want to talk about
so basically i had reserved a shuttle to
take us to
the ryokan which is a word for
the traditional japanese rest house in
place so i reserved the shuttle far in
advance
um and they told us
all right you need to meet we'll meet
you outside of this building
okay they gave me the name of the
building and so
uh we asked uh mr taxi driver son to
take us to that building
well wouldn't you know it uh deadbeats
and kfp members guess what
uh in sapporo there are two of that
building
yep there are two and we got the wrong
one wouldn't you know
whoa yeah so we um
of course well kiara talks on the phone
because your boy has a hard time talking
on the phone
racing to death because when we were on
the phone we i had to take off my gloves
and was so [\h__\h] cold and then yeah
the wind was the wind
yeah i thought a snowstorm was happening
the snow was swirling all around us
and cars were rushing by it was so it
was freezing i almost started crying
luggage just falling over because the
wind was pushing it and kamisama was
really having a laugh at us
yeah um on that day and yeah it was not
a nice experience also because like
i i did i honestly um because i i didn't
really plan the trip so i didn't know
where exactly we were and where exactly
we had to go but the lady on the phone
they were kind of like um like
pushing us to quickly like come to the
to the shuttle because we they were
waiting for us
and they they want to leave they got to
live on time and we just
had no idea where we were where they
were and this was so
frustrating and in the end i was like i
told them we're gonna go to the taxi
quickly and give them the ashes where
you're actually at and we're gonna
quickly be there but in the end they
were like
no just take a train from sapporo
station and just get there on your own
a bus from zappos station and i was like
cool thanks thanks for nothing that was
i think that was our low moment of our
trip we were both
except like super pissed off and and and
sad and
frozen it was horrible yeah
i didn't understand because you know the
staff at the d.o.com were very very nice
but that was just
uh they could not help us yeah in that
moment it was just like
it's it's you girls just it's your fault
you were at the wrong place
and i guess yeah we were i think i feel
like we need to make a disclaimer
though for the people in the future
when beings of the underworld and other
immortal beings like you come to the
surface and we don't know what the heck
is going on
i think you know we probably wouldn't
have been that exhausted and stressed
out and pissed off if it wasn't that
cold
yeah exactly it was just the weather
that was making it really today
yeah we were legit in pain because of
the the cold this is it
so we went on that bus we waited for
like an hour outside
to get on that freaking bus yep
but then thankfully it took us uh like
it let us out right in front of the
hotel uh it was not a shuttle but it was
a normal bus but
uh it took us after i think it was like
one and a half hour trip or something
like that
right something like that yeah and it's
pretty quick
throughout that whole trip like we
looked outside of the bus window and was
everything was snow everything was white
it was beautiful
it was basically just as you're seeing
the photo the whole time
yep so we went pretty far into the inaka
and now now you all know why
um we were able to stream fairly easily
um in the beginning and then why we
stopped being able to do
that yes cause we went here we were in
the snow mountains
uh after the after that so um
hotel's wi-fi was good enough for
streaming but
uh gosh where we both relieved when we
finally
landed in front of the hotel and it
looked so beautiful from
outside but it was even more beautiful
inside look at that guys
very tall like a fairies thing we were
so relieved when we saw that
that's where we went in yep
i've been waiting for that and we went
into our room the room
was the biggest room that they had in
the hotel kelly got a really nice room
really beautiful yeah it was real big
this is like the living
area mm-hmm very spacey and it felt very
homey they had like a lot of like
like i don't know very homey items i
don't know
yeah it felt like a home it actually had
uh two floors like when you go up and we
had uh we want to explain that
yeah so you know i mean the the two beds
uh there were two uh the two beds of
which there were two of them
separated from each other um there was a
room
uh next to the main uh where those where
those were
um for sleeping but the the second the
second floor
um actually had a a private
uh a private onsen a private bath and i
was really looking forward to chilling
in the hammock
the supposed hammock that was up there
yep wait i think
i have a picture of that somewhere you
keep on talking i try to find it
well you'll see you guys will see what
we uh
how the hammock situation turned out but
it was very comfortable uh the bath
yeah and there's something really
amazing about uh sitting in the hot
water
and then looking out and and seeing the
snow fall um and you're naked
yeah so like you go and you sit on the
side of the tub
and the snow is falling on you and it's
really cold and then you get back into
the tub and you're nice and warm again
and you keep switching over and over
again that's how you do it
oh yeah so uh in the first
uh night here once again we just tried
to get
our stream working uh but before that
yeah kelly
kelly went in several of the onsens
already on the first night
like that yeah and oh yeah we got
massages
uh-huh stone massages yeah but before
the massages wait like
this is all uh in in the right order
before the massages
we had this is by the way some specific
launch that was only on our floor for
the special people special oh yeah
it was a special lounge and they had
free alcohol free red wine
look at that it was there's a little
boat up there it was so pretty
there was a bunch of really comfortable
chairs there
with some nice music a lot of plants and
snow and
wasn't there a foot bath outside there
was
you could go outside with your with your
free drinks and put your
feet into the hot water and then relax
with your alcohol and your friends
actually i i didn't really end up
spending any time there but it was
really really pretty
and so yeah then here comes dinner
we got into the into the restaurant
of the hotel how about this nice little
room
set up for us yeah it was really
comfortable like it felt like a real
like
cat cabin lounge you know cabin in the
snowy mountains kind of feeling it was
nice
and the music they played the music
yeah that's right didn't they have uh
like
it was like piano versions of like um
jubilee music it's beautiful they were
playing really really
sweet jubilee music was very nice but
yeah
let me show you i took a photo of uh
pretty much every item that we were
eating but yeah they served us
uh the specialty alcohol mm-hmm yeah
yeah
yeah you couldn't drink it then you gave
it to me i mean i
drink both of them i tried i took a sip
and it was
um probably for for people who drink
alcohol
it was totally like easy like kelly said
she couldn't even taste it
tasted like juice but i tasted the
alcohol anyway so
yeah of course you did well well well um
let me say one thing most of the things
that are coming uh now i
wasn't able to eat unfortunately
sorry about that you didn't realize that
no problem but
yeah they definitely tried their best to
make a more edible menu on the next day
but let me show you
so okay this is easy this is one of the
starters this was this was several
courses i think like seven
courses or something or six but right
something about that
like that six or seven what was that
callie
yeah well i think on top of it uh that's
uni right sea urchin
yeah uh even your boy has a bit of a
hard time with that one
uh spanish is tasty tomato was tasty it
was something kind of like
kind of like tofu i guess i kind of
forget what it was really
i thought that was good a little bit of
a different
texture than normal tofu
to the japanese people i'm so sorry i i
apologize
so many times to staff because i could
barely touch any of the food there was
some stuff that was insanely delicious i
will show it and we will get to that but
yeah
chad is saying that they really like uni
i don't hate it it's just i can't i
really can't
get too into it i know a lot of japanese
really love uni as well
so you know you can gladly have mine any
day now this
was uh this looks like a feast
uh wait is that photo turned the wrong
way
possibly i'm not sure it's potentially
it confuses me but
there was a lot of sashimi and
some some uh ebby uh what's baby again
in english uh shrimp shrimp oh yeah but
some baby
guys look a little different they're
really big i mean
they were really quite quite large a big
shrimp
yeah the sashimi doll was really high
quality right
yeah i ate all the sashimi mmm that was
easy for me to eat
i love sashimi so actually i don't know
if this was on was it on the first
the second day where i finally tried
some
i don't even remember it it was oh you
tried it on both days
actually oh maybe yeah you had a little
piece of the maguro yeah um
on the first day and then you said you
said i thought it was okay but you
wouldn't choose it
yeah it was i i i just there's this one
thing that i don't understand about
um sashimi and sushi like people say
that when you don't taste any of the
fishiness when it has no taste
that's when you know it's good sushi or
sashimi but like
okay but if you don't taste anything why
what what's what's all the
the hybrid texture extra i don't know
it's hard to it's hard to explain why i
like the taste of sashimi it's like the
less fishy the more i enjoy it
personally but yeah
a lot of people are saying prawns
they're a thick shrimp
they're the big boys
i really can't get into them i have um
i've heard from some japanese friends
that they like to just crack open the
heads and uh eat all the
contents of the heads and that makes me
feel very strange inside
i cannot do that so i we left those we
left those thick boys
um alone and were like if anyone wants
to eat them
please uh enjoy um we just ate all the
sashimi
yeah yeah you ate most of it i was
totally fine with that i tried
i have to say um yummy i gotta be honest
up until now
um i just i didn't really you know
gave it a try up until now but i gave it
a try
and it's it's okay uh
i i see why it's popular i like i
i it's not disgusting or anything
it's just i prefer it if it's like like
i don't know grill or something
yeah hold it on the grill please
but it was nice too it was nice to uh
experience uh some really high quality
uh sashimi
yeah it was it was high quality stuff i
could tell
it was really tasty
now this was impossible for me like
when it was even i didn't know actually
well no wait this was actually
that was still one of the ones that were
somewhat manageable because inside there
was like some kind of uh
you know the the brown vegetable mix or
something like that
it was it was i think it was something
like a fish paste
mixed with vegetables and i i enjoyed
that quite and there's egg also in there
as well
um and i think burdock roots maybe
yeah eat them and they're tasty yeah
it wasn't quite it wasn't quite my taste
uh
but not crab not crab it was good though
i tried
and then oh now this is where the good
stuff happens
and so we got this uh super high quality
beautifully marbled ragio beef
mm-hmm and we created that marvel we
grilled it
on the top of the song i don't know how
that works but
it was it was magic magical magic that's
not your typical type of yakiniku that's
a special type of yakiniku
mm-hmm
[Music]
but this one this meat was
the best yakiniku meat i've ever
freaking
had ever you remember the time when we
went on our spot eight and we had uh
um teppanyaki but with that really good
meat
uh-huh that was like a really really
good stuff but this was even better
yeah i have to agree i'd agree on that
that was insane when i
you you know what i was eating i was
constantly having an
orgasm what can't you do
you can't you can confirm that actually
huh hey i was kind of i mean
i can confirm you were excited you were
exci you were excited
you made me excited very excited
yeah every bite i took every little
single meat
piece of meat it was like a whole new
universe
opened itself up in front of my eyes
yeah that sounds um enlightening it was
it was so soft and so juicy
and mm-hmm so i don't know ah
i mean yeah it was very tasty i quite
enjoyed it
that was that kind of the main course
but it kind of topped it with another
main course
which was uh uh wait was that it was
a nabit right nothing yeah yeah
we had a as you can see here cali with
the wine in the background
yeah and it was eating honey you didn't
take a picture of my time
i was eating panini i love crab i can't
eat the brains but i can eat everything
else
we got uh i told them that i can't eat
uh crap
so they only brought it for her but we
were eating nabe and crab at the same
time it's a hot pot when you when you
put like
that uh dead stuff in there
the meat and the vegetables that was
very yummy but we were both
already super super uh full
indeed it was a lot of food and after
that was
uh oh actually yeah dessert was supposed
to come after that
but we were running low on time because
i was going to have my massage and then
you were going to have your massage and
then
we were going to stream and so they said
we they bring the
dessert later to the uh room and that
was fine
yeah mm-hmm
after
here comes massage when i took a photo
of the massage room while i was naked
course you did
we booked uh would you like to explain
the the
massage that we got yeah stone massage
so you lay down
and you know they give you the typical
massage with the oil and all that stuff
and you know
get d deep into the tissue and whatnot
and then they take out hot stones
and then they rub the hot stones on you
while they massage you
[Music]
and they did a little facial too it's
nice yeah
yeah they put some i don't know lotion
and stuff on their faces and
wiped it off and then they put some new
lotion on the face and then they wiped
it up and then they
then they put another lotion on our
faces and then they wiped it up again
i don't know what happened there but yet
the hot stomach was really nice with the
oil
yeah i love hot hot stone massages
they're my favorite
they remind me of the underworld because
we've got lots of hot stones that we
force uh the you know the prisoners to
welcome
all you guys after you after you after
you join us
you got to walk on some hot stones get
ready really reminded me of home
uh so it was enjoyable for me
i got very sleepy after that but also um
i kept telling
the masseuse to please go a bit stronger
on my shoulders because i can't feel
[\h__\h] and she was going stronger and
stronger
and then i still wanted her to go
stronger but she said
i should probably do like like an
another normal massage
in the next day uh if i really want that
so i did go on another massage in the
morning
uh alone not a not an oil massage just a
normal massage
yeah yeah yeah it was
to be honest that wasn't
the hot stone oil massage was actually
better yeah
you can't beat the hot stone i got i got
really frustrated
uh because of the second massage because
actually it didn't help and i mean
that's just always the fact so it just
really frustrates me
oh well oh wow
the hotel has a freaking bunny it's
adorable
it's a a white bunny and we kept on
checking it out we went to the lobby
several times per day
to check out the bunny yeah
both of us were really inspired by that
bunny weren't we
yeah actually but funny story you know
your boy is your boy is uh all by
herself uh
here um and so after playing with this
uh sweet bunny rabbit i decided that i
want to
adopt um a sweet little bunny rabbit to
take care of it
have as a friend here um because i can't
i can't get a cat it's not allowed
but bunny is okay so i'm gonna get a
bunny yeah
yeah i hope it's as well behaved as this
one yeah this was
this one was so quiet and they kept uh
this little cage
on like uh on a on a table and
and the the gate was always open but the
bunny just stayed in there the whole
time and got pepped by all the visitors
and it was super quiet
and super super sweet we caught a little
cheese
i want to get a bunny too eventually so
we both just really want bunnies now
we're like
in a bunny hype or something yeah
exactly i haven't decided on a name yet
by the way debbie's but i'll tell you
once that once i named the bunny once i
choose the bunnies i'll show you guys a
picture you'll surely get to see the one
yes yes yes yes
it was so sweet i was i was wrapping my
arms and my
one arm around the whole butt and with
the other arm i was like carousing its
fluffy cheeks
really sweet bunny and i and i got um i
got a little video of it
cleaning with ears i don't know if we
still don't know if this sweet little
bunny
um was a boy or a coat we couldn't tell
we couldn't figure it out
we don't know yeah but so cute click
click clean in the little bunny ears
i have to say that this was one of my
highlights on the in this hotel
and the bunny had a 24-hour shift oh
yeah i asked the staff when i when i
went down there before i went to sleep i
i met a staff
in front of the bunny and and i asked
her like if that bunny is just there
24 hours per day and she was like yeah
yeah and i said wow that was a really
tough
job to do 24 hour shift every day man
yeah we're working overtime
i'm glad that we met that bunny me too
uh i don't know but like there's
something about petting
cute animals that just gives you so much
relaxation
hmm it's true fact yeah
scientifically prove it
[Music]
um
yup so i'm gonna do my best i think it's
a really good idea
because i got cats at home which i'm
gonna be seeing soon again
and i have to say once i got my cats my
like i feel so much more
like content and happy like they they
got rid of my loneliness completely i
don't need anyone else
besides my cats anymore so really
recommendable
all right this is uh the little um
hot tub i don't know what you call that
that we have
on on our second floor this was hours
only
and outside on the snow snowed
uh balcony so on the left side
you see that but if you look to the
right side oh no that's the
where's where's the other photo damn it
you will see it eventually i have
another
photo somewhere in the hammock yeah of
the the snow
the the the mountain of snow oh yeah
yeah yeah that was very nice and uh you
know
i i kind of i like onsen but the problem
that i have with onsen is that i feel
very shy around
other naked people and
like i don't want them to look at me and
stuff so make sure it makes me very
that's why
it's good that we got the private yeah
exactly otherwise i would get really
nervous and actually anxious but
i did go into this one and and it was
super nice because like
it's super hot but then you put one leg
outside in the snow quickly
and then you you cool down again it's so
dope
yeah you're supposed to switch and ah
it's nice i spent quite some time in
there it was very very nice
oh i see i see um
and then yeah we went to sleep after a
failed stream that never happened
and after that good night video we went
to sleep pretty late but we got up early
again to get some breakfast
yeah let me tell you you went hunting
for all the wash the non-washout
yeah there's much more variety in that
breakfast buffet
but both of us went for the simple
options
you picked the yeah this is yeah i got
some vegetable tempura some sweet potato
a lot of pineapples some salad some uh
what's it again budo is um
grapes yeah and some curry can't believe
they had curry for breakfast but that's
actually i don't know yeah that's
actually quite common
in really yeah cause a lot of families
they cook a lot of curry on in for
dinner but then they serve it again in
the morning because they still have so
much leftover
wow
i think yeah that's that's cali's place
you got again some yogurt with some
stuff
what explain your breakfast please yeah
well i got
yogurt and then it had blueberries and
then
um oh you got the napoleon
yes not though but it wasn't it wasn't
as as good as um
most not so that the taste was
was darker and deeper uh than i usually
like for not though i think that the
that uh the the soybeans that they used
were a little different this time
but i love natto i'll eat natto forever
especially with rice
and then i got yeah curry and then sweet
potatoes and then they had uh
tomato tamago um
and salmon what world reached one
million
yay
thank you thank you thank you glad you
guys enjoyed it
i'm glad yeah thank you guys
yeah thanks for checking it out and for
getting it to one million during this
stream i think that's
my my second video that reaches 1
million
the first one being sorry
[Music]
it's like the it's like
all right would you could you please
explain to our viewers who don't
understand what the controversy behind
natto is it's like pineapple pizza
so so in japan um there are people who
love natto and there are people who hate
natto
it's it's a very japanese thing i don't
think you'll really find it in many
places um
outside japan but basically it's
fermented soybeans
and you kind of you know mix mix them up
together i mean at least for me
i i take my ohashi my chopsticks stick
it into the cup and then swish it around
a lot so i can mix the soy beans
together and the juice
i mean i don't know if it's really juice
but like the uh the fermented part that
the slimy part
starts to kind of come out and it makes
this like um really tasty mixture
it tastes to me like fancy cheese um and
then you eat it together
uh with rice and it's really good for
you it's super healthy but
a lot of japanese actually also really
don't like it
and most foreigners that eat the natto
also don't like
yeah so it's very rare uh to be liked um
by an underworldian yeah
i was very surprised that you like that
because it's also super stinky and like
it's like a fancy cheese um i guess so i
guess you could compare it to dad
hmm yeah see chad is split too there's
half saying oh f word yes natto and many
saying oh f word no i hate natto
big
i respect you for eating natto oh my god
yes and yeah you had some of that
the the fish which is very typical for
japanese traditional breakfast
yeah it reminds me of what um what death
sensei would give me and all the other
swinging trainees for lunch
i see yup we eat a lot of fish after
that we just spent
the whole day in the hotel because they
got like several types of onsen several
baths
several uh things to do and
so oh yeah here's finally the photo the
other side of our private bath
looks like that check out the hammock
it's
really easy to chill in the hem the car
you can't see the hammock because it's
covered in snow
on the left side on the very left it's
kind of cut off at that photo actually
yeah um it was that i mean honestly it's
just it's funny
i like it i like that it's so covered up
in snow that you don't see [\h__\h]
yeah yeah
i guess so huh actually it was
interesting the last night
um i kind of tried to dig through the
snow a bit to find
uh what was underneath the hill because
there was a little shovel-like thing
and i kept doing but like i couldn't
find anything and there was just too
much snow so i gave it up
it was just too much snow but i love it
it looks so fluffy too
it looks so soft oh look at that that
soft texture of the snow i mean it was
really beautiful to watch it all falling
down while um
while taking a bath that was cool
actually when i was chilling
in the bath uh for a while like for half
an hour or 40 minutes or so that's the
longest i've ever been in the bathtub
but
i was just chilling there and just the
snow was falling on my head making all
my hair wet and like really cold
it almost like my hair strands almost
re-freezing into like ice
into actual eyes your hair turns into
ice which is funny because you're a
phoenix and
i'm fine nice
nice so refreshing
yukiya
[Music]
as you can see here we went to the cafe
that was next to the hotel which served
like super special apple pie that it was
really popular for
um yeah but we both we went there and
wanted to get apple pie but then the
apple pie per face
looks even better so we got the same
thing
we always get the same thing kelly yeah
well i mean
we just have similar taste in sweet
taste
that was like a apple pie on top with
some ice cream and some apples in there
yeah because i was getting hungry after
the breakfast because i didn't need so
much so we ate that
and then we went to
yeah that's when i finally for the first
time in this trip entered in onsen
you've been on a bunch of them already
but then
um yeah you told me about that uh onsen
the old one
right super super old from way back in
the day
from long ago a preserved onset
and we went there yeah i only went there
with you because
i i you said that there is not many
people there
and it wasn't indeed actually uh after
like a few minutes it was only us
because
um the other uh woman left
yeah i think that she probably got
afraid when she saw you know grim reaper
and phoenix
and then we had it all to
it was a very very nice i uh it was
super hot
oh my god it was so hot and actually
like left side here was for
um men and right side was for women but
they apparently switch it up
per day mm-hmm yeah because you said you
were there the day before and then it
was swept
yep they switched it so indeed
i actually since we were alone i took
the opportunity to
take an a photo of the inside of the
onsen
which is something you normally can't do
but i did it
can you criminal imagine this guys me
and callie
chilling in in the onset in the hot
water and then i was suddenly like wait
kelly wait kelly i actually i
i gotta take a picture for this for
office for a stream so i got up
just purely naked ran back into the
changing room
took my phone ran naked back outside
and took a bunch of photos
i hope i i i hope you weren't looking at
me running around like
nope as i told you i didn't look at you
and uh
you requested
now don't try don't even try to find my
naked body in any reflections
yeah your naked flower is going
manager went over it and nothing was
found
i think we're fine don't even try i know
don't even look for it so basically this
is like a really really old onsen
it looks very old but very very classy
yeah
super old onset and you had this view
this open view too
no i went closer and took a closer video
a photo
this is how it is yup you can see the
snow falling it was really beautiful
and at night it's even more beautiful
against the black sky
it was very quiet too very serene i
guess
we were in here for a while talked again
about many things
about some crazy things yeah
yeah had some deep conversations now he
was chilling in the onsen
you know i think it was fun just telling
you all these
talking to you about so many different
things in a whisper the entire time
because
very strict you must speak in a whisper
kind of rule that was going on
it was uh definitely um an opportunity
to get
to know you much better mm-hmm
actually i'm really glad that uh we were
alone because if we weren't alone we
would have probably both tried to stay
as quiet as possible
to not bother anyone yeah but like this
we were able to talk a lot
for me that was the only real onsen that
i
entered in that trip because the others
were more filled with
with women apparently right yeah it
wasn't very small
yeah i went to the big bath and there
was really a bunch of incredible
different stuff they had several
different huge baths
that you could chill in my favorite one
was the outdoors one
um and you can actually um it wasn't
very popular because it was so cold
but actually what i did i spent most of
my time there um i kind of went to the
ledge
and i i uh pushed all the snow off and i
sat on it
um on the ledge and just let all the
snow fall on me on the wintery night and
i looked up into the sky it was all
black and tons of snow was falling
and then i'd get back into the into the
hot water and then stare at it again
and the landscape was just the most
beautiful thing i've ever seen in my
entire existence and i actually want to
go back now thinking about it
i can imagine it must have been very
nice
but even this was just nice the one
where we went together was also really
beautiful yeah and it was
fun also being able to just wear um
yukata the whole time oh yeah
yeah um i brought a bunch of clothes but
i didn't end up using them because we
were
constantly in like japanese like these
ryokans
always japanese traditional hotels they
always prepare some
traditional clothes for you that you're
supposed to wear so no one walks there
in their own clothes everyone
like kind of wears the same clothes
but it was very comfortable um
[Music]
actually since it was my first time at
the ryokan it wasn't the first time for
cali but it was the first time for me
and i didn't know that you're like
apparently supposed to be
naked underneath so at some point hot
waters
yeah on the second day i asked kelly
because i wanted to do it right
uh i wanted to make sure i'm dressed
appropriately if we go to the onsen
together
so i asked her kelly kelly kelly weird
question are you
are you wearing panties underneath
you said no so i also took my panties
off
this is really supposed to be like that
though i'm not sure it depends on what
you're going to do
oh so for example i was going to go
straight down to the
oh the onsen oh so you don't have to
wait let me i mean some people will of
course
it's not i want to ask japanese viewers
japanese viewers now what do they say
someone wrote we have
another
they say they say normally you wear
panties under that
on the doors oh my friend stop
hold on all my friends told me
oh man we broke some rules or something
hey wait a minute wait a minute wait a
minute there's a few comments in there
that say
oh it's it's all right i guess but most
japanese people wrote that uh
you should be wearing something
underneath
hold on
on the first day i was wearing panties
but second day i asked you and you said
no so i also didn't wear
them
[Laughter]
oh wow i'm feeling a certain way right
now
some people are going to be contacted in
just a couple minutes
we got quite possibly bamboozled both of
us
[Music]
well i will i will erase the knowledge
that you have given me cali
and i will uh wear panties next time
yes please do as well
what the [\h__\h] that's funny i legit
believed you
well i legit believe the people that
told me that that's what i was supposed
to do
i don't have that first time that i went
to an onset with japanese friends
now what are you doing wearing pants
what the [\h__\h] you're so loud that the
discord is like
clipping you
angry angry kelly very angry
what the [\h__\h]
is
never again
but i mean i mean i do
i would understand the logic that like
for example if you go
with those close to the restaurant you
might want to wear panties underneath
and but if you go to the uh straight to
the onsen then yeah you're gonna take
your clothes off
anyway and like what's the meaning
behind wearing panties there i guess but
i don't know it
and then i mean otherwise i wear them
we went for a little while after that
actually
kelly went to another onsen after that i
went back to the room
and just chilled a little bit and and
then we had dinner we met up
again in the same restaurant for some
dinner uh
now this time they tried their very best
to make a menu that especially i can eat
all day they were content contacting us
and asking if uh i i can eat this can
you eat this can you eat this can you
eat this
while also constantly calling me uh
calliope
because i'm yeah in their mind that's
who i was
kelly is still alive yeah yeah i'm still
here okay
so yeah um they managed to make a quite
edible menu
for me i'm but i'm very sorry i we told
them that because they were going for so
much trouble we told them that
we we we can totally go somewhere else
like we don't want to put too much
trouble on you guys
so it's totally okay we can go somewhere
else please please don't change your
menu too much
but they really change like everything
everything
yeah you know they were going to give us
they were going to give us shirako
witches you want to tell them what it is
you tell them what it is it's um
it's let's just say it's um it's fish
milk
male fish milk now that sounds okay but
but it's not yeah i know i've heard it's
quite delicious but i'm not
inclined to try
like the first night i wasn't able to
eat
barely anything so i told them i can't
eat like most of these things
and then i love how they go from raw
fish to okay but you must be able
to eat fish semen right i'm like
what what
what no you're going in the wrong
direction
you're going into the wrong direction
so yeah they did end up making the
edible menu so here we go this is uh
oh yeah this was the only thing that i i
didn't really like the starter
i don't know oh yeah yeah more uni
yeah and this was not exactly tofu they
said it was uh something before tofu
forget honestly i wasn't super intrigued
by it either
impressed but yeah and wasabi in there
too
yeah everything after that was all uh
good i think
yeah okay so they
they um really tried hard and i ended up
making
uh this um soup for us that's like uh
with uh uh duck meat that's okay
okay yes
yeah it was fun for you that was nice
yes that was very yummy but
that was just the starter and it was
already like filling up so much
damn i mean didn't you well i was eating
that didn't you also
eat uh oh yeah you were eating the sushi
as well and
uh look at that sushi date they brought
even more sashimi
sashimi they even brought even more
sashimi on the first day
the one on the bottom left is koi
um i ate all of it uh i ate one piece
actually yeah one piece i ate and the
one
the one on the top right and top left is
again a tuna maguro
and i forgot what this was and i forgot
what that was
i don't remember oh yeah i forget too i
i have no idea but i ate it
the white fish at least
i ate it and it was not good it was
probably macro
ah mac really you think so yeah it looks
like it
oh people know their sashimi huh
they can recognize it by the looks
that's amazing mm-hmm
but even for sashimi noob like me i
could uh
taste that it's top quality top-notch
best
sashimi ever it was good
but this is a combination that's right
it was good they brought out this huge
uh hot plate
with lots of onions and meat on it and
they closed the lid for a little while
and then they came back
and opened it up and then they said now
please
and we did
um it was really hairy mm-hmm it sure
was i
um i can't let me let me think about my
wording here
um i kept kind of like you know feeling
um the the
hair part because i couldn't believe it
and it was very hard to eat and and the
main attraction of this
particular crab um are the the brains
and the inside of the body so i had a
really hard time there
but the legs were quite delicious if you
managed to get the meat out they're very
good
taste like tarantula it looks very fancy
very very hairy i totally
i said that the this uh
this crap maybe should go to the salon
that i visited
to get my hair removal oh yeah
that's a good idea yeah i'm gonna i'm
gonna recommend that
hair uh haircrab where i went
or i know that was that was what you
were eating on the side
while i was eating the yakisha with the
yaki shop it was kind of for both of us
and uh unfortunately i didn't take a
picture of the inside of this one
but it was just a
pig
so use your imagination and
uh wait they they are potato mashed
potatoes
that's when we found them like wow okay
they really couldn't they
i said no to so many things so that's
you can you could see that they were
really really desperately trying to
get some combination of food that
westerners can eat
yeah it's true but it was very yummy
it was like really thick pieces of pork
and uh and mashed potatoes yeah in some
kind of japanese sauce mustard
yeah but also i feel like spicy the pork
was must have been
in some typical i don't know japanese
dashi or something like that before
something like that yeah yeah where's
yummy
i didn't take the inside but the bowl is
really cute right yeah i want the bones
pretty
mm-hmm
and then we got to the dessert look
it's bitter chocolate pudding yes with
some strawberries on it that was yummy
no no it was high quality
it was very yummy that was good
i we're getting close to that guys but
after that dinner
we went to remember cali where we went
after that yeah the hot place yeah
basically we had uh 50 minutes of
solo time look like we really it was
like rented out for us
and this room and
which is like [\h__\h] it's like a stone
sauna
it i would say it's not as hot as like
typical saunas
definitely not as hot we were definitely
sweating when we got out though
only a little bit though yeah i was i
was barely sweating only a little bit i
mean a little bit
but still i mean it was that was hot man
it did not stay in there for too long it
was very comfortable
and the the stone underneath the towels
you can't see it right now but there's a
stone that's like the central heating
stone oh yeah then it was really hot
yeah yeah i wonder like is that
might be a stupid question but does the
heat come like naturally from like some
magical stones below or
hopefully not i mean that's a that's a
lovely romantic thing to think about but
i think it's definitely a machine that
is heating up the stone
[Laughter]
magical stones it was very comfortable
so basically they they had like a guide
of how you should do it um wait let me
show you the next one there we go
it's like um
[Music]
like they said okay lay 10 minutes on
your back
then turn around 10 minutes on your
stomach then get out drink some water
for 5 minutes then get back in
10 minutes on your back 10 minutes on
your stomach and then get out again and
that's basically like 50 minutes of
uh yeah this japanese style of sauna
that was nice yeah that must be like
good for your blood
blood pressure and stuff right i got the
feeling because
the entire time and and your boy doesn't
really know about
blood and having a heart and whatever
but i sure could feel it
when i was laying down on that stone so
i guess i confirmed that i do have a
heart
i felt my blood just pumping and i was
like whoa i have blood
no way it was very human body
yeah that was nice and after that we
went to our final mission that we wanted
to
fulfill we went to the night lunch
the night lounge that was so nice
would you i wait i'll show the pictures
and you can please explain
what that was yup
well first of all we went through that
little path which look at that
look at that bag of snow and again i say
the height of a small child
[Laughter]
that was so nice we we um we changed
into some
some slippers and walked over there it's
like like pretty much
the building next to it but i don't know
it was like maybe
a two minute walk for the snow
it was pretty lovely though i got to say
it was falling very softly
this is this picture i think shows
how nice this was yeah please explain
kelly yeah it was amazing so what you
could do it they had they had free
hot wine your boy was there for that
your boy was there for that hot wine i
tell you what
free hot wine and yaki ringo yeah
[Music]
grilled apple and yeah grilled up and
yaki imo grilled a sweet potato
yup and you could grab some and then
what were you drinking kiara
i was just drinking hot apple juice
new hot wine i got the hot apple juice
and then
it was so freezing at that but we put
like our our feet into this hot
uh foot bath and we have blankets too
yeah more food we were covered in in
blankets
and we were looking at the snow falling
down and actually you don't you don't
see it on this picture but
if you would look a little bit to the
left there was a tacky
and um what's it calling it a little
waterfall right yeah a little waterfall
uh-huh and the snow was really really
falling but there was
there was so much it was falling very
lightly there wasn't a lot of wind but
there was so much snow falling down
and most of the people spend uh their
time inside because it was too cold
outside so it was most of the time it
was only us two sitting here
in our little circle and next to each
other it was only us
it was so nice although the foot the the
foot bath
it felt so hot to me almost harder than
the onsen for some reason
so i had to keep on like uh pulling out
my leg and then putting it back in again
it was so
comfy this was so nice it was such a
like
lovely like ending to our trip i loved
it
it was i want to go back already yeah it
was so
nice we talked a lot of stuff here too
we went there we were there for like one
hour
before it closed it was just
great so
so nice i want one of those in my home
corner underworld
everything was covered in snow like that
i don't know if you guys can
recognize it but like um like here
and here this is like a pond and but it
was like part here this part was frozen
and this was not but like and and here
over here was that the little
uh not a waterfall yeah the tiny
wonderful
so you heard you were here you were able
to hear that wonderful
that silent waterfall sprinkle and ah
like largess um i'm gonna inhale that
fresh
snowy air oh my i can't
i can't explain enough how beautiful
this was
it was so romantic i mean
it was like a juice like a dream yeah i
want to go back that was like definitely
one of the highlights
i'll never forget it so i wanna just
bathe in these memories me too
nice nice well but all good things come
to an
end and we uh after that one hour of
chilling there they closed and we
went back to our hotel room but wait
wait wait actually i took a photo of the
food it looks really yummy look
doesn't that look yummy wow i'm such a
photographer
for you
[Music]
and i could have stayed there for hours
to be honest yeah
for real and uh then
we i i one thing that i definitely
wanted to do was build like some kind of
snowman
so at the very end to finish it off
nicely we built a snow bunny
inspired by the bunny in the hotel
we just yeah we didn't have a lot of
time yeah it was so cold
oh my god we kept on like touching the
snow and then dipping our hands back
into the hot water but it was just
insanely cold so we couldn't build
something properly because we didn't
have our gloves with us
look at it isn't it cute
cali builds the head and i built the
body and the eyes and the ears we made
together
it was hard getting like um an actual
like real
uh like a circle like snowball because
it was like powder snow so i tried some
of the water and like really clump it
together and eventually
you did a good job with the head
honestly it was so hard for me to make
the the body into something that would
stay
but you did a really good job with the
move the head
thank you you made some nice ears and
eyes too thank you
i'm so proud of a bunny that when when
we left uh
and we said goodbye to the staff there
was like one one guy operating it
i told him
i was like please we made a bunny
outside please take a look at it
we were so proud uh-huh yeah and we told
him that it was really really beautiful
i like to remind the staff of uh like
how we how much we enjoyed it i like to
tell them because i just
i want to make people aware of yeah of
what they're doing is great i want them
to know that
yeah i agree completely
you you want to you want to let them
know and and the staff too was so cute
just a
cute cute little og song seemed so happy
we made a cute bunny
cute cutie pie i hope i hope that bunny
will live on
[Music]
bye bye forever dear bunny
so that was the last picture i had
prepared um
after that we slept another night and
then we got up early and checked out and
went back to sacramento city and then we
went we ate some lunch and then we uh
went to the airport and then we flew
back and then we separated but it was
up beautiful amazing trip amazing
memories would you like to
say some words about the trip it was
great and i want to do it again but
you know back to reality oh there goes
gravity
you got to go back to real life um but
it was a nice little escape a nice
little time to relax
and have fun together yeah yeah um
i overcome a lot of um
what have you said there were a lot of
first timers for me i tried sashimi for
the first time
i even tried crack meat for the first
time because i did i did try yours you
did give me a little
yeah i let you have some yeah and i
tried uh
well awesome like not for the first time
this was actually my
uh second time but i enjoyed it i was
able to enjoy it much much more than
previously because the first time i went
to an onsen it was a really popular one
that was packed with people like no
matter where you look there was a naked
body i was just feeling so uncomfortable
i didn't know where to look
but this one thanks to being um
only with you i was i was able to feel
comfortable
and i'm really glad we did it and i know
there's a there were a bunch of more
onsen maps that must have been very
pretty but i'm just glad
i i was able to join one of them
same here it was nice to go on a trip
together yeah i wasn't sure how fun it
was going to be
we had a great time yeah a lot of first
time and finally going skiing
again even though i hurt myself
it had a little accident and even then
it was for me very precious memories
and i have to say um hokkaido is
absolutely beautiful
we didn't see that much love like
there's still so much more to see
so much more but what i saw was
beautiful
the the little parts that we did get to
see were great yeah
i i i definitely think that you gotta
visit hokkaido in winter
but it's very hard to get around in
winter because it's cold tell and you
will freeze to death
so i do want to visit again in summer
just to properly check out
and the city and all that and just to
enjoy it
without freezing to death even though
the snow is so wonderful i wonder if i'd
enjoy it as much without the snow
yeah the snow definitely makes this into
what it what it is like the snow has to
be there
but i just want to go again when there's
no snow so that i can
look around in peace
what kind of very beautiful one thing i
was surprised about is that for example
when i went to the south of japan
uh or just even in kansai uh only
japanese people spoke in a very heavy
accent in dialect but in the real title
that wasn't really the case honestly
um
is because we had a lot of conversations
with like hotel staff and that kind of
thing
they don't want to speak in the in the
accident that they have
maybe that's that but even the for
example the staff
at the ski resort resort is this ski
place
they were also speaking normal japanese
and did the taxi driver was speaking
normal japanese
like taxi drivers usually don't change
up their japanese for foreigners
wow i don't know i wonder why
oh because it's a tourist area that's
why they speak normal japanese
beautiful i want to go again mata is
thank you kelly for giving me the
opportunity to like
uh get that off of my bucket list
sure no problem it was fun i had a good
time with you hmm
me too it was nice best memory ever i'm
so happy we did this because also
i got to know you like like much much
better and there's like things that
i i already spoiled them but like you
talking in your sleep or you being a
puriku symbol
things like that what the [\h__\h] but you
were asking always
for my chocolates in between yeah but
that's because i like sweets i'll eat
sweets forever
i have an infinite stomach for sweets
but i guess full just like you
i didn't finish my ramen come on man
that's something to be proud of that you
didn't finish your ramen
well you didn't finish yours either i
finished more than you
no you didn't i did you're the proof oh
there's no proof
where am i there's no proof is my brain
i ain't more raped
yeah i can i can
swear on my mama
oh okay but yeah
anyway you genuinely saved me a lot in
those uh vashoku dinners
because you ate so much of my food i was
honestly yeah i was trying to be helpful
i didn't want it to be multi-night yeah
i was so impressed because you could
just
eat so much it was impressive
you were eating like all not not all of
it but you were
at least half of me so that my food
wouldn't look like untouched
i was doing my best but i was still
really following
yeah it was a little today yeah but i
did my best
i can imagine oh well
[Music]
anything else you want to add to that
i mean i think i pretty much said all i
have to say hmm
it was fun i hope you felt more i hope
you felt
like like relaxed and uh
like you were able to take some time off
from you know all the stuff that's
happening
i mean i did get a chance to relax and
that was nice
i needed vacation i'm gonna read super
chats after this and so you guys
are uh welcome to stay for the super
chat reading
and and for kelly once again
thank you for going on this trip with me
i had a lot of fun
beautiful memories lots of nice photos
and some special bonding time with you
so yeah it was very very nice
do you want to say auf wiedersehen to my
my viewers our viewers here
okay avatar zane and in german we say
auf wiedersehen bye bye thank you for
watching
bye bye thank you
thank you bye bye hokkaido
you're welcome to leave any time kelly
you cannot i mean okie dokie
if you want please okay talk to you
bye later you
see you in the collab tomorrow
oh wait she already left though yep she
gone
oh she gone ah i'm all alone
[Laughter]
i'm all alone oh no
well guys i'm gonna keep on streaming
and read the super chat and stuff and we
might go
into some more detail about everything
and one second one second one second i
need to figure out something here
where the hell am i there we go
there we go hey where am i
oh it's so so snowy here
ah yeah i feel like there's a um
probably a lot of things left unsaid
so maybe you guys can get that out of me
uh through the
new super chats we will see should we
read them here
should we switch i don't have to chat on
here i guess let's move over
didn't fix the chat here but hey my
stamps didn't go up automatically as
they usually do
that's some improvement i shall
to realize i felt very anxious about not
streaming for those couple of days but
i'm very glad that you guys all
um were supportive of that anyway double
bgm oh dear lord
now it's fine okay
yeah thank you guys for for waiting for
me and
you know being supportive even though
i haven't been streaming for those days
and even that one stream i did was super
scuffed
and i'm really glad i was able to go to
hokkaido
what kind of was the dream that i've had
for such a long time you know actually
um the first time i've been to japan was
ages ago and honduran
could have like checked out more of the
city because i basically saw enough
nothing much of sapporo because we went
skiing
which i mean that that was also an
amazing experience but i basically saw
nothing of zappodo
it sound nothing but it was just too
cold to actually go sightseeing
i mean i guess you're not really
supposed to go much uh sightseeing
anyway but
but did you see odori park see that's
the thing normally around
this time in hokkaido in sapporo in the
odomy park in the middle of the city
center
they have this snow festival of the ice
sculptures maybe you guys have heard of
it before
normally that's happening right when we
were there
right now and but yeah
they're not doing it this year so we
didn't see it unfortunately
maybe next year
i always wanted to go to hokkaido in
february
because every time in february there
they have that
like snow festival
[Music]
they didn't they weren't it wasn't
happening
that's kind of sad
but understandable
there's always next here yeah but then
again like if i was on
if i was going to do some proper
sightseeing i don't want to do it in
winter
because it's so freaking cold oh my god
honestly freezing to death
is possible it's insane
i feel like they maybe maybe they built
a wider road in hokkaido or sapporo
because they always gotta push the snow
to the side
and make these snow mountains on the
side of the road because otherwise
if if the roads weren't wide enough you
just have only mountains and you
couldn't drive through them
that's what i thought
a reason to make the attach they say yes
they say yeah that's why so smart
there's also this other thing that i've
heard that in sapporo
maybe only in sapporo which is like the
kind of the capital of hokkaido
um that they kind of heat up
the roads so that at least in some parts
of the city
and there's no snow on the roads
so i wonder that's true too
[Music]
i know
yeah they did they really do that sounds
really expensive yeah i told that kelly
i
i gave her some knowledge that she
didn't have felt very proud of it i was
like hey callie did you know that in
sapporo
they heat up the the roads from the
ground from below
and she was like no what that sounds
super expensive she said the same thing
can't they have salt and they use salt
and stones and all that as well
but it's just too much honestly it's way
too freaking much snow
oh
[Music]
how is there so much snow like even in
the city
it's amazing like where i'm from there's
also a lot of snow but it doesn't stay
in the city center in the capital it
doesn't stay
in the bigger cities it just doesn't
stay underground
only like when you go to the mountains
we have a lot of snow
and we're like a country that's famous
for
um for lots of snow and going skiing and
having nice mountains and all that
i live in australia and we don't have
snow while you're living in the wrong
australia
i'm from australia you know
ah
[Music]
all right let's go get the super chat uh
which ones do i have to read
oh my god we might have a lot huh wait a
second
i also have to prepare for tomorrow i
gotta go shopping someday today
to get the ingredients for the chocolate
tomorrow
valentine
i gotta buy the ingredients and like the
basic stuff
like i'm probably gonna buy a scale and
stuff like that so really basic
baking stuff i don't have any of that i
gotta get all of that
done super chat reading
are you guys excited for the
announcement tomorrow
i am very excited
[Music]
it will be amazing
i am very nervous
but i'm more nervous about the the
baking
the making the chocolate part rather
than the announcement
i'm very happy about the announcement so
that's that
i might not be able to read all of the
super chats but i'll try to catch up as
much as possible
and so animal crossing
and i guess minecraft probably
minecraft before minecraft i i think i'm
caught up right
oh god there's a bunch of super chats on
the field and
couple q a that didn't happen i will
read those too of course
okay here's the scuff minecraft
nine hours super japanese no no no no no
no i
so okay minecraft the scuff minecraft i
have to read but the minecraft stream
before that i did read right
the the one that i still streamed from
home
did i i did probably right
what do you guys say yes yes yes okay
okay
okay let me drink some water and then
we'll get started with the superchat
meeting
let's have some small talk while we're
reading the super chat
by the way i was speaking more japanese
than usual today just because
we i wanted our japanese viewers to know
how much i
appreciate the beauty of japan
i just wanted them to know that we
really enjoyed the trip
[Music]
stop thank you you made my day in the
stream oh
really why what was the announcement eh
there's no announcement the announcement
is tomorrow
in my solo stream thank you for sharing
this with all of us you didn't have to
and the fact that you did is more than
we can thank you for
you're welcome you're very welcome you
know me
me getting up all the out of the hot
onsen naked
running to get my phone and taking nice
pictures it's just for you
just for you guys
i wouldn't run around naked in the cold
winter for anyone else
you are welcome
[Music]
i have a i have a earburn from king
because i know you guys want me to sing
king
and uh i really like elena's cover
so much damn it so good
[Music]
but
so good now i wasn't really planning on
covering it but you guys i will at least
maybe sing it in a karaoke stream
let me eat i got some some noodle some
noodle
some fruit stuff some special ones with
herbs
maybe that helps
her singing is so good yes
i wanted to cover pretty much every
hello live member didn't cover you don't
have to tell me
you just never did a cover because
pretty much everyone did a color
that's nothing new to me it's so funny
how
that song got covered so many times it's
like a like a trend or something
ah oh never mind
only seven of them cover it i guess that
has like a like an actual cover yeah but
in karaoke like it plays pretty much a
version of king from every whole life
member
some of them at least sang it in karaoke
streams
yeah i like how and they make like
uh the the cover art fits the original
one
for every every every cover
[Music]
i'm gonna try to practice it i've
listened to it a bunch of times but i
don't
actually know how to sing it anyway
let's get started
oh you sent a letter oh i hope it
i hope i can get it before
uh before i leave japan
hopefully it arrives soon thank you
skye
[Music]
they were trying to spell out something
with these single super jets
a million times i will stop here my dear
uh my dear mate
my dear mate
if you have such a ridiculous name i'm
not going to read it 20 times
because it makes me feel uncomfortable
[Music]
gotta skip those it's just tiny smalls i
hope you guys don't mind sorry
i'm gonna die if i read it it's like
summoning some evil spirit if i read
if i read hentai is pog for more than
five times in a row
i'm summoning some kind of hentai evil
spirit i don't want that
no no no no no please no
[Music]
nice guys everyone there's so many of
you guys uh
here right now for the super chat
reading which i'm very thankful
for you guys but
you guys better come tomorrow as well
right um
i think i think i'm gonna do the uh
announcement
after i'm done making the chocolate so
you gotta stay until the end as well
it's very important that every single
one of you is there tomorrow
it's about the same time as now i think
wait let me see uh collab is at 11 a.m
japanese center time oh yeah
the announcement would probably be
around right now
but the actual chocolate making starts
um around the same time as this
stream started
always here boss thank you i will
definitely be there thank you
i have an exam tomorrow on a saturday
sunday what
you better watch the archive okay
be there for sure thank you one missed a
second thank you thank you guys
there's no sleep for me tomorrow
thank you i i would appreciate everyone
being there because
it's a very special stream that you
don't get much often because i'll be
actually making uh something with my own
hands i'll be
i'll be making some chocolate and then
there's an announcement that's like
super special
that's not something you get that often
amarini
yeah i want to i mean who else would i
give it to maybe maybe a
genma maybe my manager
thank you for the rest super chatzugi
thank you did you guys realize
everyone who watched both of those
takamuni streams today did you guys
realize how
cali warmed up to me throughout
those two streams because in the
beginning she was very soon and very
tired and very angry
i think it's because she was very tired
but i legit was
i was legit getting very sad in the
beginning i was legit like what the [\h__\h]
man
kelly she was so grumpy
uh it was very painful in the beginning
but she warmed up to me at the end of
that stream
of the first one she was already very
kind again
she was brutal in the beginning right
right
i was there because i gotta be honest i
had some tears in my eyes
[Applause]
because honestly we were bonding so much
during that trip
for four to five days we were getting so
close everyone
everything was so hard harmony and happy
and then we get back and the first
stream we do
she's just so angry and so grumpy
and i was like what the hell happened
what happened in those four or five days
it's it's just all over now what
what was that for what what's going on
why didn't we
go back to the beginning yeah i think
she was just very sleepy so mad
oh my god i she but during the trip when
she was uh
well just woken up she wasn't that
grumpy to me
that was just today
it was quite sad
oh well thank god she warmed up
yeah when it came to the question kiss
on the forehead which
was just a general question she was
getting so
angry which part would you get his
forehead
cheek or mouth why you need to get so
angry about that
yeah she was so defensive
[Laughter]
so great
we noticed i guess that's how you guys
feel when you get like
i don't know a friend zoned or something
i guess a lot of you can relate to me
how i felt today in the beginning of the
stream
could you guys relate to me oh my god
[Music]
yes we can hashtag relatable
kiana being rejected is so relatable
[Laughter]
oh man
kelly is like the grumpy old man in
pokemon she needs her coffee or
otherwise she won't let you pass
oh but cali doesn't drink coffee though
ah oh man
my chef got switched this week so i
can't watch any of the streams live this
week well
i guess you're lucky because most of
them didn't even happen
but hope you both have an amazing trip
together enjoy your stay thank you so
much
thank you well you didn't really miss
anything
if you got to watch the streams from
today then you didn't miss anything
she's just shy maybe oh
she definitely is a shy type yeah
in some ways she seems uh
kind of shy in some ways yeah
[Music]
it's pretty cute but i'm shy too
but i'm shy in a nice way
but i don't when i don't you know when i
feel shy i'm like
[Music]
but she's like no now listen
you listen
yeah aggressive kind of shy why are you
doubting me
why are you downing what the hell
you guys don't know me you guys don't
know me that way
cause you you and me we've never been in
that kind of situation
where i would be shy
because well maybe one would have been
when i offered you guys to marry me
you guys said no but if you would have
said yes
then you would have probably experienced
kiara being shy you missed out on that
you will never you will never meet
shahida
i accept and shake my head
you're one of the smart ones but most of
the people reject it so
i said yes are you smart too
not all of us rejected you well thank
you
i'm happy to hear that
let me make myself bigger okay
thank you for the red super chat
happy taka money week hope you two love
birds are having fun we don't mind the
scuff and can't you please give us an
emote for shrug later on
ah i could do that yeah
that's a good idea can i meet shaykh
genie thank you i will try maybe if i
get to your super chat but
it's it's hard to work with that you got
to give me like some kind of you know
something i can react to it's a
situation you know like i don't know how
about you
how about you propose to me
then i can probably act that out anyway
come this night continuing
hyped for the good news whatever it is
yeah baby other good news
ah wait which one
are we talking about here canvas knight
not sure which one oh yeah
well actually not sure but
the game one
is that a pre-chat super chat or is that
during the stream i don't know the game
ah yeah ah me being able to stream tails
off
that must be it ah thanks guys you guys
have a better memory than me
wow yeah
i'm really excited for that too i don't
think we're gonna start anything anytime
soon because there's nothing
releasing anytime soon that i would be
uh wanting to play from the beginning
um and i have some other games that i
want to play right now but once we're
getting uh
once we're running out of games to play
then we can play uh one of those tales
games that i already played
because the ones i have permission for i
already played except tales of a rise
which
didn't come out yet so our first
hands-off game
might just be tails of a rise when it uh
comes out because yeah i played the
other one and
yeah although we don't have permission
for tales of dysteria
if we have permission for that then i
might play that
thank you for the super chats guys thank
you
uh there we go there's a marriage
proposal
eh
i i like
you but i don't know if i'm
ready for it i
i feel like maybe i'm i don't know i
like it but
can it really be me but actually i
i like counting
like maybe i can have
more
if you really like me then
i i i will think about it
[Music]
but but i i will i will write you a
letter with the answer
i i can't i can't answer you now
well thank you
thank you
i'm very happy to be proposed too
will never marry anyone besides kelly
stupid
did i just turn into your rebound crab
what what
what
ah oh wait i was actually speaking not
to you
krabby crab i was speaking to yama to
cuda but
you also kind of proposed to me huh
actually i don't like eating crabs but i
am
a crab uh i i i
am crab because i'm cancer
and because because i'm born in
july
so i do feel some connection there with
you kanye sama
oh man crap confirmed
my heart stopped why because i'm crab
[Music]
thank you for the proposals guys let's
keep it up let's keep going with
the super chat reading
necromancers
[Music]
are you also proposing to me yeah
where do you marry me i know we haven't
known each other for a long time but you
make me feel things i didn't know where
possible i promise to work hard to make
your eternal life happy
chat what does that mean in the end
what does that mean is that not you
saying but it's a chat saying it or are
you trying to marry the chat
it's from the chat it's not him saying
it
oh well okay i can marry the chat but i
i proposed the chat before and they
didn't want to marry me what am i
supposed
to do
don't die don't die wait are you dying
from
the cuteness like from the broken heart
i didn't exactly break your heart though
i kept it open
somehow i think
yeah thank you guys thank you
we accept you now tangel well now it's
too late
now it's too late
you think you can play around with me
like that chat
you think you can first deny me and then
later and be like ah i want you after
all
nah that's not how it works
i'm not gonna wait for you guys forever
unbelievable
i want someone who instantly knows they
want to marry me
who loves me true and full
someone who's sure about their feelings
for me
which doesn't really describe cali
either does it
yeah that scent yeah
you have a problem there oh well
monochromic tank is
hope you have a great vacation also tell
dad i said hi oh sorry
i didn't sorry i'll tell her afterwards
that you said hi
thank you bronx for the red super chat
wow i appreciate it
very generous of you thank you for the
support
it was a amazing vacation indeed
looking for the top that sounds like
something you did not write yourself
since the first time i saw you you've
been like a ray of sun in my life it's
thanks to the energy that you give me
that i can support you every day i love
your kindness how thoughtful and how
playful you are what that means that one
step by side forever
that's where is that from
let me see let me google
where is that actually
wait no google doesn't show me anything
is that south mate
is that an actual i wrote it oh wait
really
wait are you serious all right you just
say no that's that's pretty cute are you
just joking around
will you please marry me i know we deny
the ones before but i just realized how
much european citizenship will help my
career but
[Applause]
for you well that's
that's a hell no for me what
you just want to use me for a visa
oh my god rude
what is it
oh my god no
ask someone else some some other
european for that
thank you guys thank you thank you
looking for the top that's
a really sweet message if you
considering you actually wrote that
yourself and
assuming that some of these words are
straight from your heart and your your
true feelings it's
quite quite sweet
if you're
a ray of sun well
the only pieces i need are the ones in
my wallet
i know you yaga do i know you don't want
to marry me i know you're one of those
people
i know you're one of the deniers of
happiness
you guys just don't know what you're
missing out on
you just don't know
give up chad kelly has monopoly yes
i mean should probably not use it but
i'm also born in july so what
so what crap
you think that's going to make me marry
you
shut up looking for the time
oh my god is that another marriage
proposal oh my god
i'm so popular i fell in love the moment
i met you you've been with me from my
happiest and saddest of times i love you
ch
chat
oh my god
i don't understand you guys i mean
i mean i guess i do because the chat is
pretty wholesome you guys are pretty
awesome i love you guys i understand why
a chat wants to marry itself
i i don't know if you can marry yourself
because chad
marrying chad is
kind of weird but good luck with that
good luck of that i hope you find
happiness
chat you are now married to each other
you are all
spouses of each other i pronounce you
now
to be spouse and spouse
congratulations my chat is married to
each other
yay
yay beautiful
beautiful oh i wish you all the best of
happiness uh honeymoon
you're not getting any days off from
work for your honeymoon you gotta work
and work hard can i marry why
potential you gotta ask why potential
yourself
she's not here right now thank you for
the super chat
okay guys i'm gonna focus on the on the
past super chats not on the current ones
please
stop thank you thank you thank you guys
i love you thank you thank you
okay back to the current and to the past
ones
oh my god wait the ring the ring for me
marrying who wait what the hell do you
love what
oh my god
oh my what the hell
uh holy
macaroni
holy macaroni i hope you don't regret
that afterwards
that's too big that's too generous
thank you what the hell
let me let me give you an echo kiss
wow oh i'm what the hell oh my picture
oh my god
[Laughter]
oh my god oh my god those that that big
super chat kind of
brought out some kind of cursed chiada
again i don't know where that came from
thank you so much oh my god is that i
don't know if you want me to buy the
ring for me and kelly or for me and
the chat or for the chat with the chat
who is that ring for
if you like it then you better put a
ring on it
oh
might be enough to buy rings for every
single one in the chat
maybe
it will be a cheap ring but if
we give everyone a a ring it has to be a
cheap one
candy rings ah yeah that could work
everyone gets a cali ring
everyone
six thousand people five hundred dollars
for six thousand people
yeah we need to get some discount or
something
or we could we could even make the rings
out of like leaves out of grass
now that doesn't cost any money so i
will use the money for myself afterwards
[Music]
songs
don't worry about the cardboard i think
it would be hilarious if you guys just
picked a different face for each video
ah yeah too bad we actually ended up
being able to fix the cardboard but we
didn't get to use it much only for one
stream and then afterwards you know
everything failed we were so proud of
finding a solution
and then we couldn't use it man
i got nothing to say wow okay
thank you fox i wonder if that was when
i was uh
no that wasn't the other minecraft
stream when i was like what does the fox
say
that was in the minecraft stream before
that
thank you though thank you i appreciate
it
jacob thank you ghost two hundred thank
you
thank you soon canvas night sunglasses
i used to travel a lot with family and
hearing you too is making me so
nostalgic hotel internet sure has come a
long way though they used to make you
pay for it
oh yeah that's true isn't it can't wait
for a fun tug of money we love you too
thank you
did you show her your don't say what it
is
no i didn't i want to show it to her in
person
i want to show it in person
because i want her reaction on stream
[Music]
so we gotta wait a bit more for it
christian sarabian
oh my god what
hey kiana i've been in love the first
time i saw you this may sound as iconic
and overused as it is but i was
it was love at first sight hey i think i
want to marry you but i don't think
simba and kobu would allow me to do that
oops
frankie and i'm sorry tanjo is that like
some kind of fto reference
is that a fgo reference because there's
a kiana in there as well you want to
marry that kiana
oh wait lion king what what there's a
kiara and lion king
what what
what
yes nanking too oh i've only seen lion
king one
i think
what there is a kiara
in lion king two what
what simba's done it really
[Music]
actually the first time i've saw seen
lion king was in 2020
i never seen it until then are you guys
surprised about that
you're probably very surprised about
that aren't you
yeah it is true
um i like it though it was really nice
you're so late i know right that's one
of the few movies that everyone has seen
that i just haven't seen
up until last year i watched the
the cartoon one yeah
[Music]
i don't know if it was 2d or 3d wait was
there a remake
maybe i've seen the remake maybe that's
what i've seen i'm not sure anymore what
did i see
was there a remake recently
yeah a bad pretty remake ah that's
probably the one i saw
i don't think i've ever seen the
original one
wait let me look it up uh
lion king 3d
got it
no wait yeah that's the one no i watched
the one that looks like realistic
i think why not wait i'm so confused
yeah i think that the one with um
the one with um oh uh where one of the
voices the voice of the bird was at that
talk show uh
not exactly a talk show but uh what's
his name again the british one the br
the brit that lives in america who has
his own show
yeah john oliver yeah that's the one
that i watched
is that the the real the like
realistically animated one
that's the one that i watched i did not
watch the art uh the original and i
never watched the musical
because i think there's a musical
uncultured potential
oh the remake was so bad it i liked it
because this was the only one i saw
but you got the wrong one oh dear
watch the original one
the new one was beautiful
yeah original way battery lion king
watch along when
classic disney watch long please
animations are classic
and well yeah
i think i've watched some other uh
disney classics but this one i just
i don't know why but i never watched it
keep tissues for the og i think i also
cried during the
the new one pretty sure
proposal rescinded
that's okay i wouldn't have accepted
anyway because you just want me for the
visa
you just want my european visa
anyway continuing and where were we
celia is one flyer
thank you for the pinky very proud of
our kiara even though a cardboard one
viva lucky i love the voice thank you
thank you
not sure why you were proud of me maybe
because i i streamed even though
everything was going wrong thank you
i was really like normally honestly i
would probably
and not stream if everything was going
wrong and i had to change the game and i
had to be in cardboard and all that
but i i streamed anyway and i'm proud of
myself too
thank you genie for the pinky
ernest louise
some people every now and then there's
some people who ask excuse me what does
that mean thank you
and then people thankfully help them and
tell them and say
german for thank you
so
[Music]
so there's a place in australia called
calliope
what it's in queensland so there
theoretically you could
live inside cali what
you sure that you don't you're not
talking about california
it's cali is california you know
wait what there's actually a place
called that
in queensland is that
for real
california is in the u.s oh
yeah i know but so what
there's also kiara in australia well
that's just [\h__\h]
australia has both italian camp no
that's supposed nah uh
uh okay let me look it up that's
[\h__\h] there's no way that that is
true
australia kiana
what what
what
kiana is a suburb of perv western
australia
situated approximately elf 11 kilometers
northeast of perth central business
district and 8 kilometers from midlands
[Music]
what australia
oh my god wait what is it what is it
what what is it with australia naming
their
cities after people is that just a thing
they do
calliope is a rural town and locality in
the gladstone region
yes we don't know ourselves apparently
yes
let me take a look at the map here
okay that's not a human name miriam
mount maria that's that's a human name
what is this doughboy
elliot
i don't see so many human looking names
there's another church there's a tree
island again
there's a place called nerdy but with
double e
oh there's a there's a place called
sexton
i'm just checking out the australian map
right now
lake macdonald oh my god
did i have lots of mcdonald's food
there's a place called ocean view but it
doesn't really seem to have an ocean
view because it's quite far away
i don't know i don't see well okay now
we're in brisbane let's see what
brisbane has to offer
i don't see many or any human names here
maybe that's really what the hell is
that like
how high are the chances of the country
has both kiara and karaoke as
like city's names what
it's absolutely insane
[Music]
name
[Laughter]
what on earth
there's a there's a city called casino
interesting
there's some funny names here but not
necessarily like human names
[Music]
i can't stop can someone close my google
maps i can't stop moving around
i wanna i wanna visit the fake australia
you know
they wanna visit this australia one one
day
nothing beats uh the real australia
obviously but
i'm gonna visit this this fake one that
has like newcastle and brisbane and
sydney and all those places
the fake australian must be nice there
read super chat what is there anything
uh what what what what what
what did i miss
me
okay back to zip attack meeting
[Music]
all right i'm back i'm back
i've been crying from laughter this
entire time your streams are always
amazing even if there's a bit of skull
really was that stream so funny thank
you
i'm happy to hear that because it felt
very scuffed to me but i'm glad people
enjoyed it first like i didn't even know
what to do first i was like okay i'm i'm
going to
uh get some diamonds but then i didn't
get any diamonds
i got lost but then then i got back up
and i started building a chicken
scoffed just a bit but great thank you
we actually enjoyed it like seriously
thank you
better than the debbie mic
[Music]
wait i never i never listened i only
listened like because
people i wanted to know how that sounded
like on stream
so i tried to listen with my laptop and
with my earphones and stuff but the
audio isn't so good with that so i
wanted to know
what it actually sounded like i gotta
check it out
after the stream because i i don't
really know
how that microphone sounded like i if it
sounded decent then i'm glad i got it
because i got it just for traveling
purposes
[Music]
um
some japanese uh viewer just wrote that
it feels sad that i'm leaving soon and
it's really crazy because the
day when i will leave is coming closer
and closer and i'm getting actually
quite stressed out because i gotta do so
many things before i leave
ah scott's dreams have a fun part to
them you can't get anywhere else
that's true i guess i see how that can
be sometimes enjoyable
[Music]
sorry that came very sudden
sammy
uh as long as where was i yeah as long
as um
there's not like five million scuff
streams after another and it's just like
uh
like the main thing if it's just
once every every uh every few streams
and i guess it's funny
thank you guys thank you
[Music]
hi
thank you thank you guys thank you bless
thank you you could have at least
written out bless you
god damn it low effort super chat
thank you thank you bless you thank you
thank you uh
i'm still stuck in the office because my
human boss didn't recognize takamori
week as a holiday in my religion
it's funny how you put an emphasis you
emphasize the fact that your boss is
human
what are you what are your mutual
account name
but yeah that's kind of weird should i
what's wrong with that dude
so obviously takamori week is a holiday
but the holiday got kind of cancelled
because we didn't stream that much
anyway
i hope your boss is happy now it's his
fault
oh wait i guess mulder account name is a
chicken huh
oh i guess it oh yeah you guys are
chickens oh yeah i forgot
wait i forgot i forgot
you guys are chickens
there was that huh
lego
it bothers me that you changed your name
from yamato
stop to yamada i understand that you
probably
like i don't know did that because
because i don't know to stop it in
between the name because
yeah my dick with a sap but it bothers
me because
it's so hard to stop myself from reading
that part
could you change your name back to
yamatokura stop
please
change it back
please also it says i love your body
thank you i i can relate
i can relate yes
thank you for the red super chat telling
me that you love my buddy
i love it too
[Music]
we care about mental health on kfp 10
minutes later threatens with usual room
what you got a problem with that
is there anything weird about that
do you have a probable band i'm asking
you
i care very much about the mental health
of my employees
there's no denying that
it's very important to me yes it's my
number one priority
no i really i really i really wouldn't
want anything bad to happen to you guys
hashtag volcanic yolk
thank you for the support thank you for
the generous donation flem derp
kofi thank you looking for the top down
question
[Music]
thank you
we're done with the scuffed minecraft
stream super chats okay okay
let me try to get a little bit further
next up is the the super jets from the
canceled
a couple q a
my mouth hurts again i can't talk
anymore
damn it i'm trying to honestly i'm
trying to read last messages right now
because i
there's so many that i have to catch up
with
take a rest acquire tea
don't have a cup right now up here
stop after this one yeah maybe
by the way is it so or is it some now
that you're here now that i see you in
here is it summer some
because i read your super chat
incorrectly possibly
where are you give me an answer answer
me
answer me it was correct
yeah but i don't know which one was it
is it song or some
sum number one or some number two
ah
only the personal actual name can give
me an answer to this
[Music]
thank you by the way for your support
saying that
i shouldn't stress it if if we have
technical issues
looking for the top down kitchen oh yeah
that's probably where i announced that
it's gonna be difficult to stream
look at umbrella thank you and blue
beauty dominique
67 michael murphy thank you
[Music]
thank you don't let it spool the rest of
your trip thank you i
i it didn't it didn't i mean
the trip wasn't about streaming to begin
with anyway so yeah
it was a great
great vacation
and i was also very happy that you guys
enjoyed that small club so much
it was teddy overload
so much
and and no i did not make it on my own
cali was doing making the video with me
okay so it's not like i was like you
know
controlling her or anything no no she
was there and she moved
like you know it actually happened okay
true story
because some people were doubting that
but now
she would have said if if that wasn't
her she would have said it you know she
likes to
be honest and then she doesn't like she
wouldn't like it if i used her body you
know for stuff like that
without her consent
she wouldn't allow that
[Music]
why didn't you use your hats you are so
bold
if i don't sleep with my hats obviously
i sleep uh
mostly most mostly naked
most of the time not another winter in
winter i like to wear some more clothes
[Music]
oh that fluffy tweet by the way was
because i i was uh cuddling the
the bunny and um
[Music]
sweet that was because of the bunny
some people didn't know what to make of
that tweet
it was because of the bunny
[Laughter]
[Music]
hang on
yeah but after the bunny i jumped into
the into the hot
tub outside that was also
so relaxing
[Music]
there were so many things to do in that
one building
a hot tub and the snow is 10 out of 10.
exactly
absolutely best outside map is next
level
actually i told cali about something
that um we have at home i think
it's not only in australia where we have
that but
like i used to me and my family
we used to when i was younger we used to
go to this uh um
public pool like thingy where there's
like a bunch of pools
and um they had one pool outside
which is like a hot pot pool with like
salt water
and it's really nice to go there in the
in the winter
and because like we would like uh
like run into the snow and then jump
back into the hot salt water
i don't know what to call that in in
english but in german it's called
sole bacon because it's with salt
but it's a it's uh not like an onsen so
you you're supposed to wear
your swimsuit obviously an open air saw
not no
it's like an open-air
hot pool salt bathtub i guess so
you guys don't seem really familiar with
that
you guys don't have that in like america
and so on
it it's super um like uh
healthy apparently the salt water is
pretty healthy
nope is that a european thing
i mean it's like a normal you know those
places uh water parks i guess which have
like pools all kinds of pools but then
there was this one special pool that
they have which is with salt and it's
outside
and it's hot not as hot as an onsen
but pretty close to it it's
know
it's a hot spot but with many pools five
to ten sometimes with different meals
yeah there's like minerals and salt and
[\h__\h] in there
um yeah i didn't know i thought that was
like a western thing that i thought you
guys have that too
in in america and so on
i hope there's no size in it do you say
that because there's salt and [\h__\h] in it
stupid thank you so much for sharing
those memories with us i'm glad you
enjoyed this trip and i hope
you can enjoy more of those in the
future thank you too thank you for
listening
wait a second wait a second guys
ah it's like a formal bath i guess
wait i used to go to this one when i was
younger which
what was it called again it's so
nice
it's so so so nice
i can't find it
i mean even if i show you a photo i
guess it just does it just looks like a
normal pool
it looks like a normal pool
maybe you guys if you ever visit uh the
real australia
then you guys can check it out
i really recommend it um
yosho are you guys still awake wake up
everyone
we got a few more super chats and that i
will will read
we'll probably not get until the end but
we will get as far as possible i'm awake
i'm awake yes ma'am
yes angel very good very well
very well
okay
okay w h-e-i-n-i-c
and no this is queen nick thank you
slowest cycle pump thank you
thank you for the pinky sometimes it
can't be helped enjoy each other's
company without us and we'll hear you
next time
thank you thank you for being so
supportive
um
[Music]
um the good night video i'll read those
super chats too
uh super jets for the good night video
premiere
i'm back how much did i miss where when
did you leave
have you ever tried an electric bath in
an onsen what
no what what is that
dog
[Music]
reading so far i'm hungry and my friend
hurts thank you for blessing the people
even more with more takamori you're the
best boss that guy could ask for thank
you you're welcome
that's the most i could do or at the
least i could do
and also in some way it's the most i
could do because i couldn't stream
electricity and water don't mix well
that's what i would think
at this point we should count when you
are not hungry during super chat
readings the other thing is i didn't
really eat much breakfast i only
ate one one piece of uh small bread
in between the two streams
i gotta eat more
one second you know what uh let me check
my
my contacts one moment
uh okay i'm so hungry guys
wanna stop for now i don't know should i
i wonder like how much would it take if
i would continue
oh dear there's a lot of uh
animal crossing super chats yeah there's
a lot of super chats in general yeah
i should probably
i should probably take like a separate
super chat reading stream to catch up
either like tomorrow or the day after
tomorrow or so
because tomorrow there's two streams as
well
yeah i should probably do like a
catch-up stream to be honest
at some point today no time maybe
tomorrow evening
maybe not i don't know
what what am i planning for next week
oh i'm planning to play sims on monday
by the way
seems fine we're gonna recrease the
holiday we're gonna recreate the
vacation guys
on monday i know
[Music]
because there's a you guys remember when
i said that i want to recreate the
holiday
in sims 4 because there's one specific
um expansion pack that is
very suitable for that i think there's a
there's this
winter getaway pack or something like
that sims
sims 4 winter winter escape that that
must be it
yeah snowy escape
you can actually like go skiing and
snowboarding and [\h__\h] so
oh yeah and actually it is it is that
that sims 4 um uh expansion pack
is inspired or like it's supposed to be
a japanese
um snowy escape it's in the japanese
mountains they even have like a snowy
onsen
and stuff like that in that expansion
pack it's absolutely perfect
even the name of the mountain that is
used in that sims 4 expansion pack
is uh has a japanese name and they even
have
like these uh japanese furniture and all
that
and the japanese you know uh ryokan the
traditional type of hotel
it's so perfect guys it's perfect for me
[Music]
it looks wonderful i have to buy it and
install it and then we're going to play
it on monday
sims 4 already has so many expansion
packs it's amazing
expansion pack me
apparently you can even or maybe not ah
you can
it looks like you can no that's probably
not it
you can even do sightseeing though it
looks like they're sightseeing
i wonder if that's like supposed to be
sapporo
like the area it's definitely supposed
to be hokkaido
definitely speaking of the winter
japanese winter area must be hokkaido
[Music]
pumpkin perfect okay
well well then i will leave the super
chat's here so remember guys when i ask
you again next time
we gotta uh continue reading super chats
uh from the point of of the animal
crossing that the animal crossing stream
has to be read
okay thank you guys oh wait i'm still
why am i still in the discord by the way
hello okay okay okay
okay
look
happy snacking oh yeah thank you i need
to go buy some chocolate things i don't
know
i don't know what to make yet i think i
want to
make some chocolate cookies or something
like that
i wonder if i can make that with my
small tiny oven
and with the tools i have i'm definitely
going to buy some new tools though
now
will you be making them with kelly no
i'll be making them alone but i'll be
making them for cali
it's gonna be in your house yeah
actually i
i
wait why why did my manager bonk me on
discord
manager how did i deserve that bug what
did i do
what did i do half an hour ago
i've been bonked by my manager half an
hour ago what did i do
whoa
up until now was never angry with me oh
the google maps engine and she bumped me
for my tangent
denma has never scolded me even once
we have a really good really cool
friendship
that's because i never do anything that
i should be scolded for
google maps is banned
i'm a good i'm a good talent
that managers are very happy with i have
to say though okay here we go you guys
don't believe me you guys are pressing x
to doubt me
well gemma told me before
i'm easy to work with because i always
uh reply
like very fast i always get to work very
fast
i'm praising myself here
oh that's true
janma though working with me
i know it and i love working with gemma
oh ah i wanted to clear something up by
the way
uh genma the jay in genma doesn't stand
for japanese
doesn't and uh genma is
not cali's manager people people make up
these things and then
spread those things and then everyone
believes it and it seems to end up as
being
a fact it is i never said that
genma is mine and kelly's manager she's
not
i keep hearing so many conflicting
things yeah because people make stuff up
what's the j4 then i will not tell you
but
it's not for japanese and uh janma is my
manager
and manager for two other members i
i don't know if they want to say that
doesn't it doesn't matter but
it's just it just it kind of uh bothers
me that
people make up these uh things
so get get your if you don't have any
facts and make don't make up any facts
yeah oh
jacksonville yes yes it stands for
jacksonville yes
uh-huh uh-huh
i mean i guess how you could assume that
it stands for japanese i guess because
of because
like maybe that person manages the
talents who are in japan but no that's
not that's not exactly
what it is this is jojo
josu and mah
ma just admire
just enma
[Music]
that's a good one helena and
just anima bestest
ah that might be because i told you guys
about denmark and my members only stream
maybe maybe i didn't tell you guys any
details either though in the members
only stream
well anyway but she was she was very
happy about
the fan art the genma fan art
she was very excited about that
it made me also really excited even
though it's not fan art for me
for some reason i was also getting super
excited i kept on posting all the fan
art
on our discord and feel and i was like
oh look look there's even more gem my
fangs look at this one look at this one
look at this one look at this one look
at this one
are you going to finish the design
intention um i feel like
many people already portrayed her quite
nicely you know with a suit and stuff
like a sexy sexy suit clothes
i'll leave it to you guys maybe one day
i'll draw her
again properly gmt yeah
genma magic
people are looking for the official art
though um
take i feel like the the mamaloni fan
art was
uh pretty perfect take that as
the official version i agree with it
but i also like the other ones many
people just uh drew her in like a
t-shirt with like a name tag and stuff
oh i like the business style i like it
yes yes yes yes yes
okay so now i will say goodbye to you
guys
and i'll see you tomorrow uh first of
all there's a collab stream at ina's
channel
we will all be there all whole live
english members will be there
and danny after that i have
my once again
once again i say it once again my
valentine's day chocolate making with
announcement stream
be there oh b square we don't want to be
square we don't want to be square
no no no no no no no no no no no
[Music]
not
hope you guys enjoyed today i hope you
enjoyed the takamori streams
the q a and the and uh and the trip
review
hope you guys liked the content from
today
and we'll cherish it in your heart just
as i will
thank you guys for watching thank you
guys for staying up so long with me and
watching those streams
thank you see you tomorrow and in
germany
[Music]
thank you so glad to be back with you
see you tomorrow bye bye
bye bye bye bye bye bye bye my stomach
is growing
it's like oh give me food
give me food
got some stuff to prepare for that oh my
god i really do i really have to prepare
a lot of [\h__\h] for tomorrow oh my god
so much preparation
what happened
[Laughter]
to
well excuse me okay i like how i like
how you
say that so aggressively
maybe that never mind i'm not gonna say
what i'm gonna say
i gotta i gotta learn how to control
myself
[Music]
bye bye guys see you love you
if anyone has a simple recipe for some
chocolate cookies or something throw
them over here
although i might just choose something
japanese because i got to get the
japanese ingredients and stuff i don't
know
but if you got something simple some
ideas throw them up to me at twitter
[Music]
you