[Music]
hell bye
[Applause]
[Music]
Mary
scas Mary
[Music]
Mary Mar
among why not what's not to love about
those
guys welcome everybody to the uh
Christmas Holan holiday Among Us stream
we have gathered here today with so many
lovely cute girls and we're going to
have fun choking and stabbing each other
right sounds like kind of
fun let's go awesome well we're going to
um do it without proximity chat by the
way guys uh because you know we have
some first timers here I think it's
Advent girls's first time among
using first timers
that's we're
not yeah we'll find out how they act
when when they're impostor we can't tell
yet like for others maybe we already
know a tell but for these newbies we
don't know what is their tell maybe
that's maybe you could tell us would you
be so kind when your introduction to
tell me what your tell
is please
nah you got to find that out that
information is classified G need a
little cash money up front first I'll
try well okay then let's start with
introductions let's start with the only
one who's a real astronaut here
Amy hello Amilia Watson number one
astronaut
detective yeah I like Among Us so I'm
excited to play Let's Go's
go because maybe there's some new viewer
at this point who don't understand why
is am able to wear her own clothes in
the game and why am I wearing P's
clothes and is wearing man's clothes Amy
do you want to explain H yes we have H
we had a collab with Among Us where you
could get a few uh Hollow live outfits
and items in the Among Us shop but I
don't think it's available anymore it's
kind of AIT time
thing too bad if you missed out me and
are P right now oh Oh I thought this was
a keyboard slam you guys are actually
you guys are in a room okay oh yeah wow
okay I thought you just slam the
keyboard
ke keyboard slam I know that's what it
looks like code looking like a slam Oh
no you're giving them hints you
G and slam welcome to the slam jam
please join there we
go fertilizer who is CM spam is all
right well I guess that's more
[Applause]
[Laughter]
oh you have color
too yumy you had a Spam color that was
am nice box oh while we're Callie's uh
you know bullying her for her name Cy
please introduce yourself so we know
that's really new oh yeah if you insist
me it's me Mory Kai H life English is
hardworking
Shinigami uh I'm in a place with very
terrible internet so I can't stream my
POV but I'm very excited to be here with
all of these lovely ladies as a sheriff
completing my tasks and making sure that
we win the day let's go yes you wouldn't
kill anybody she is now known as C spam
Cal I guess
it's but yeah I'm so happy you're
joining even though you can't like
stream properly thank you so much the
dead beats they trained me well I wanted
to show off my new skills that the dead
beats
have with members fairly recently oh we
got to watch out she's good at the
game the dead Beast you just ask us how
you kill
people okay I guess I didn't help at all
that you played it recently it was
unhelpful well okay moving on to fauna
where is she where is she I can't find
her here you can't vote me as the
impostor if I'm hiding
right there is f from H live English
promise hello I'm here does it feel does
it feel like normal now like it still
feels weird to me to hear that
introduction
promise yeah I think so fresh still it
is it is still pretty fresh but I like
it FR I think it's boat fres off the
boat not boats I feel like everyone been
traed by boats
recently this current Tren in the whole
lot of English of watching school days
what's going on no I I wanted to this
last we finally got told me about the
tree and there there's a family
St why do you like
it there's a staircase did you know
there's a staircase I know now
thanks I have no idea what these girl
are talking about good I'm so confused
it's too cursed it's nice that everybody
is having fun school days and all that
fun a jolly season it is great PC of
Cinema yeah yeah all right Iris our
number one Christmas lover hello yes
you're number one Christmas lover here
hiis it's Iris from H live English
promise
you're uh I love this game but I I I
really SU at being imposter but yeah so
so yosu yeah but I'll do my best are you
really bad at it I don't remember I I
was horrible at imposter last time I
played this I screwed up so bad she gets
imposter maybe you just need a better
mate to work with cuz you're dumb d m oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] this on my face bit of a poopy
head what you're talking about the lobby
will fall apart it's no problem let's
take our
time okay yeah by the way have you guys
speaking of Iris have you guys all seen
the yesterday and today's episodes of
the Holo Ian Advent calendar cuz Iris
was very involved in them I was very
involved in them yes just and they were
both in
3D space yep so Iris why did you do it
um oh it's CU you know we needed some
light to bring up the Christmas spirit
you know what better light than actual
fire right yeah oh that makes sense and
you know it was my whole plan so that I
I could become the Christmas tree in
order to become the Christmas tree you
needed to burn the actual Christmas tree
first true you burning Christmas trees
that's kind
of it is the master plan it's pretty lit
yes very lit
it was
fire indeed fire fire light the fire
fire fire light the fire light the
fire okay uh everybody's uh joining in
again in the lobby I think I'm coming I
got my name I freed C spam he doesn't
exist
anymore SP she real more com spam I'm
sad is it going to hide the code if I
have streamer mode on yes yes it's
hidden for it does yeah it's hidden
people self introduction please hi uh
bomu I'm clu sparkling Gem of Hall life
English Advent and today I'm a space
Rock but that doesn't mean you're
allowed to Stellar Stellar me out of the
ship so I am not S I am
nice
wow okay that was pretty good you give
me nice sauce how
are no no that doesn't work here doesn't
work
here
man so you have to prove yourself prove
the truth you can't fool us people
you're sus dang already you already Su
already why you doing
anything I think I think it's her yeah
think pretty good
guess it's
definitely
okay let's move on
too
police
I'm I'm not
I'm together
we your voice okay
Mo sometimes I become a dragon sometimes
you know but as long as you know I'm not
Chihuahua I'm not Hua
I'm there we go and together we we make
the best crew mate you know G dogs great
crew mate not kind of unfair it's kind
of yeah if you're imposter it's two it's
two two of you guys
imp I think I should bu them out right
away every
timeo well let's look who that but
indeed as a crew mate they might be very
helpful cuz it's two brains for one I
guess I guess who's on the keyboard
who's
controlling controll I'm the legs you're
the brains I'm also the the pointer
finger oh yeah nice looking forward
to that'll be nice to see one one day
they will play separately but today is
not
today isn't this game a mobile it maybe
somebody could play on mobile I
was I sure con right really work on this
side well okay and then
please imposter hi
darling devil Diva
Raven cute I'm an impostor today because
I'm pretending to be M and yes let
go oh my gosh fake it till you make it
fake it till you make
it we're we're a nice couple n aren't we
how ironic I should be running away from
you I don't want your child
narissa even if honeyworks made a song
about our child I don't want
it okay and then
please this is
oron from live English Pro what H life
English
promise um please don't arrest me I'm
going to be a very good egg for today uh
cuz even if I want to be an impostor I
never get it I almost ever get it so you
trust me I believe her I trust her 100
TR yes I trust her 100% I trust everyone
100 what chances everyone only says the
truth I look so
kind none of none of us will get
imposter probably yeah probably none of
us yeah that's how it works how many how
many imposters are we doing I set it to
two two it's cuz we're
n should do free
I is good
okay and I I have in case you're
interested uh two long tasks and five
short tasks uh as well as two common
tasks I don't remember what common tasks
were that's
suspicious what you you don't
remember oh yeah cuz imposters don't do
tasks well it's been too long they added
or something right like you can do stuff
now or
something like rolls or something r oh
yeah wasn't there something besides
crewmate now like um uh like besides
imposter like the Spy or something like
that
not that's I don't know how does that
work though I don't rul for that one at
the beginning so yeah there's four rols
there I don't know you girls can
probably see them in the settings uh on
the on the computer here there's a
scientist who can access a portable
vitals panel so they can check at any
point of time if there's somebody dead
so they always see the status of the
crew and then there's an engineer who
can use the vents even though they're
not an impostor but then you might be
sused and you have to be like I'm not
the Imposter I just vent because I can
oh that's pretty cool really and then
the guardian angel uh is the ghost of
the very first one of us that
dies oh is that how it works the first
person that dies is something like that
the garden it say the g Angel is the
ghost of the first Dead crewmate they
can temporarily shield and protect other
living crew mates so I guess if you're
the first one that dies you become the
guardian angel and then you can protect
somebody else so that they don't die
yeah if you do it properly and well
timed you'll be able to prevent
imposters from killing their victims
sounds amazing me throwing so that I can
become the
guardian
a already are yes no the
wow and then there's a shape shifter who
can who can change the appearance and
disguise themselves as other crew mates
Shape Shifter why would you do that
though that just confuses everyone it's
just Mak imposter or they're not even
harder to find too because then you know
the Imposter can say I'm the engineer oh
no I'm the shape you know like please I
promise I'm not a murderer it doesn't
say that it's only impostor but why
would why would why would a crew mate do
this I don't know why would turn one off
but I like the other ones yeah should I
should I keep them or should
I oh it is okay yeah just doesn't say so
so wait does only one impostor is only
one impostor The Shape Shifter is that
how it works uh I can set how many there
will be I can say
two I can say we want two or I can say
we I want uh one or zero I can set it in
the
settings but if I do one then only one
of the uh imposters will be Shape
Shifter but only 50% chance the one will
be oh yeah I can I can make it higher
too that we have one for
sure default is good right it's probably
default okay okay default then let's
keep the rolls then let's go we're going
straight to
the ince your before
we before before we go um can we have
the visual tasks off because if we have
it on it might be too easy visual tasks
off oh yeah
true yes very good okay and before start
I'm taka I organized this thing the
logos and the thumbnails are
commissioned by me
[Music]
so don't kill me because I I paid for
this
[Music]
[Applause]
okaybye byebye byebye
bye-bye I I
muted I'm muted
right I'm
muted
he okay I'm ready
[Laughter]
okay
oh
what
huh hold on it's not safe there's two of
them now how do I get out of
here it's not safe to kill both of them
at the same time okay oh what the
okay oh Call's bad oh okay how's
bad
I don't know any of the task I don't
know any of the T
though no
no I'll miss
you you guys tell the only real
astronaut you know what that means we
don't have a chance of getting back to
our own Planet no
unbelievable so who saw Watson I didn't
see her at all I didn't see her I didn't
see her at all no I didn't see her while
who who reported just now me I did tell
us it did tell us about it where was the
body so I was going around
Communications um trying to figure out
the mushrooms and went on and I went
down uh the the little zipline and then
in the storage room am was dead stor
storage room
oh we saw around the
Busom you
me wait so fok was also in the storage
area no no we were at the mushrooms and
we were having problems with that and
crony Senpai was around and then crony
Senpai went down but Senpai was there
too yeah mococo was chasing me
around confused I don't know what's
going on I have mushroom
problem I had like a meat problem I
don't know like it I suddenly turned
into like a a lighter pink and there was
like a chunk of me chasing
me did anyone get the PO and then they
changed into people or something like
that yeah what is that just an effect to
freak you out or does it do something I
don't know I think it I think the the
the mushroom like if you touch it or
something um it hides the the people so
you can just like kill them and run away
swap my skin or something like
that why you know that
H yeah my skin got swapped as well yeah
me too SW the skin a wizard and then I
had a little worm next to me for a
moment and then poof it was gone and the
light was back
on weird I I don't know what what goes
on in this map I don't know I feel like
I trusted crony Senpai and now I feel
like I don't trust
a
lot I will say I passed by and I was
actually running away from crony cuz it
felt like she was chasing me I didn't
see
you where were you you you followed
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
me whoo
there she burn
everybody goodbye okay
goodbye I don't know the fact that she
had like her own like um name everything
oh oh oops oops
[Music]
oops oh who do I kill who do I murder
today is there anybody oh oh mushrooms
oh oh mushrooms oh this map is really
[Music]
big where is everyone there's
nobody oh what is that I don't know what
that
[Music]
is
oh
wait wa I just saw narissa like 5
seconds ago though Nissa is in the the
South part of the map with the lab in
the ho I don't know this
map um wait how do I look at oh I saw
narissa around like next to the
greenhouse when I was Ming to the
labatory above the green house
I saw her walking around I didn't see
anyone near her see anyone else yeah I
only saw Nissa when we went up to
Communications and that was the last
time I saw
her we didn't see anyone except
forite and I think she's good scared us
I ran away instantly cuz I will be
honest I don't trust anyone who voted
for crony in the last round what like
imposters were trying to get her out
because
they Ved her because
[Laughter]
tell us before huh huh told us something
important when we're going to start yeah
I'm about to kill her who did
it there's only I don't think'll
ad really that's true imposters still
but crony could have been an imposter
though honestly like I don't know you
turn know it doesn't say who it doesn't
say
oh I wouldn't put it behind her if she
self-recorded because look at her look
at her um her icon like she it's all why
why are you so suspicious of her for no
reason I don't know I feel like you
wouldn't be this suspicious unless you
were the impostor in your shirt I'm not
I swear to God I'm not I I I I said
outright that I saw like narissa passed
by just 5 Seconds AG if it was actually
me I wouldn't say that I didn't see you
though uh no I was pass I passed by her
when she was going greenhouse and I I'm
currently at the meeting room I went the
opposite direction that's why I think
she was like stuck on a that beo and
Irish Senai are suspicious I think wait
why I swear I'm not were you I'm not I
was walking around I was in the LA the
lab wait where's my map the lab and then
the rest was on like the top 10 seconds
I'm vo
bio I don't have enough
[Music]
IR it's not me I swear it's not me is
not me uhoh
I God two V was
enough we get
him I thought we won yeah tomb told you
was excuse me you didn't even notice I
was dead
guys literally I pass me and bio killed
me
immediately report good team you two
that was pretty
funny I was surprised well you know what
we learned from that because call was
pretty quiet sus out was the quiet quiet
one
the fooled me cie he fooled me
too
strategy I was just confused cuz like my
voting was super rushed I was like wait
wa wait why am I suspicious all of a
sudden literally just Spiderman
everybody pointing at each other no one
in there it was peer pressure peer we
don't have to vote you don't we don't
have to vote just felt like I needed to
vot Iris out that was
weird I thought it needed to be like
majority vote to even get anyone off I
thought to I didn't think enough to kill
me only a little bit of us left so two
was enough yeah people had already
died we're strong at this H we're good
we're pretty good doing our time wen't
you the ones who I thought you guys
were I guess we S no matter what you
can't be helped
well that was a good first round let's
let's try to be you know wait for an
extended voting time oh sure of
course yeah uh it's currently 90 seconds
should we do 12 or at least a yeah at
least 120 120 is the
max good Chad says apparently we can
vote or skip the vote if you're not
confident like who it is you don't have
to vote pretty confident
prent pretty confident voting yeah I was
pretty confident
too well now you should now you know
then you maybe cannot trust your
confidence yeah true
enough all right then let's start
another
[Music]
round even though this is really fun
here thank you crony for finding
this yeah see you on the other side bye
bye see you guys
bye how do I do my
stuff um okay so I go
here
[Laughter]
uh bu bubble bubble bubble you guys like
that I won the first
one I was so
good yeah yeah yeah look at me best
imposter oh go with Rea
okay
oh oh do I play video game please don't
hurt me please don't hurt me please
don't hurt me f don't hurt me please
please
I I love you milk or oops I said the
word man I love F oh I oops I said it oh
that was bad
oh okay what do I have to
do um um okay
cafeteria there is no one
around it's strangely quiet what do I
have to do
oh
y get get
oh clean up where is no one has oh oh
sorry no one has reported anything I'm
like
Strangely I like strangely it's
strangely
quiet
yay
marshmallow where is
everyone
oh no not again come on yeah come
[Music]
on what all right I'll break it down for
you oh please I did all my tasks you
guys could see me I think some of you
saw me watering things in the the
mushroom place I moved some storage
around roasted some marshmallows went up
to do my tasks in the communication room
and what do I find Watson dead middle of
the floor I didn't see anyone leave
though was anyone near Communications
recently communication top you take a
little like a what is it a z wire the
zipline
zipline I'm far from for a little bit
but we didn't see much I justad Zine
yeah I was just in the jungle
area yeah I know there was there was
like oh oh okay these white white things
are okay yeah the line you can go up and
down but yeah I wasn't there yet um in
the bottom right um there was a lot of
shape shifting I don't know who is
who what happened with that the mushroom
is that the mushroom stuff working on
everybody everybody got a skin shift
right
cuz we don't know who is who and then we
can't prove like oh that person was
there or whatever but we all look
different like not like each other right
so it's not sheep shifting yeah no it's
just the mushroom power is that somebody
doing it or
yes oh by the way yeah I just want to
say idea I haven't used it yet but when
pass by a mushroom it does
it I can vent but I'm not the The
Imposter just saying I didn't use it yet
though I wonder recently was anyone
around upper engine Lookout or mining
pit because the impostor may have tried
to escape by going down the
ladders I will check it out I was
walking that way but I didn't see
anyone okay I've been down over in the
left area for the whole whole time doing
my tasks so I Haven even gone over there
I haven't been up there yet I have tasks
and
communication I was going to go up I'm
currently passing I was passing by the
greenhouse I was going to go up but and
then you didn't see anybody run past
well no I didn't hard to tell still at
least hard to tell
didn't but people was kind of
quiet actually bi boo passed by me and
didn't kill me
so didn't me this is the first time I'm
doing T I can tell you I've been doing
water with narissa and then I did the
marshmallow thing and and I did the
video game I shot
asteroids and I haven't been up there
yet so I I do have task there okay okay
we'll see we'll see evidence
inconclusive but keep your eyes open
yeah I'm maybe don't don't go alone
don't go around alone guys go with a
buddy we don't need a
buddy
fine
together
mut muted muted I am muted okay um okay
I'm going to communication to do my out
what's up
oh I see
oh don't hurt me oh oh look it's me
what's
this oh it's
polishing
[Music]
oh oh we polish o and then we
go
any dead bodies up here any dead bodies
no
okay call might be good
then
huh
it was for
go I knew she was
innocent was a little bit suspicious
though she was I passed her going down
the ladders from communication to the
lower part she I see her maybe went up
the communication where'd you find her
so I was going up the L to the
communication and I didn't really see
her body but um I saw the the vent which
is the plant kind of opening up and then
closing so they vented
to yeah they vented to wherever it is
from Communications
oh oh does anyone know where where the
vents from Communications connect to
they can go anywhere right I think all
the vents can only usually I don't know
in Old Maps events only connect to
certain other events I have checked and
then I could have told you but it is a
B I can kind of say I think crony is not
self-reporting at least because like I
feel like I was I was running around
with her a little bit alone she could I
saw you yeah yeah and she didn't and
then I saw cie running around I think we
were alone for a little bit but she may
have been on cool down as well but she
yeah she was coming down down from that
she was she was coming down from that
area yeah I told you I crossed paths
with her oh yeah okay but yeah and Cory
said someone
[Music]
vented where were you yeah where were
you the beach we're just kind of going
no you Wen I don't know what's going on
the map
yet it'll show you where you are oh tab
yeah hit tab the map will pop up there's
also the map icon on the top the map
icon right yeah the top
right there's a set I see a map but I
don't understand it it has a lot of
marks on it
yeah a lot of marks that is that is it
exclamation
marks a lot of marks on it does it have
some x's on
it l the marks I mean I don't see so
many marks on my map
yeah what does an imposter see maybe
does a previous imposter want to tell us
what they saw like Kelly yeah I saw some
x's with circles on last time and I
click them
sabotage a lot of marks on the
screen marks I'm get him get yeah get
him you have anything to say to defend
yourself from we're just
doing
would be
[Music]
many oh I hope we don't regret
that
oh I have to do my
task I got my revenge
I I wonder who the other one is
[Music]
that oh what what is this
I can haunt
people
oo what is this
do oh hey hey yeah you where' it
Go who do you guys think it
is how do I do my task do I look at
this
I supposed to find something oh Comm
sabotage can I unab the comms I
can't I don't have anything on the map
to
do
I can't do the calm
thing oh now I can do stuff okay now on
to task live everybody
live oh
nice
uh oh and then
oh who who's dead
wait I just saw her like yeah I saw her
too I just saw her too I feel saw her
body right underneath the the
ladder the the left ladder like check
the map you can check the map and see
exactly where the greenhous like close
to the green house yeah wasn't she just
with me at around like yeah I saw
everyone at communications someu there
also Lookout and then I went down and I
saw her she moved
fast and then
died is there anyone around there I'm in
the lookout right now I'm in the mining
pit I wasn't it
[Music]
was we all went to Communications home
yeah everyone like uh everyone
except uh who was it like r
and
FAA uh I think they were around like
Communications and like Lookout and then
everyone else went to the other coms
um I am sorry FAA but it seemed you were
being just um you know a little very
cautious I don't know if you were
careful about being stack killed but you
moved away from the the radio like where
everyone was trying to fix it oh that's
well you needed to go do the other thing
right to fix it I was the first one
there in the radio and I tried to put in
the code but I think you have to put in
a second
code yeah also I had two tasks that I
did in
Communications oh okay I did them cuz I
was I was in Lookout I was putting the
code in I think it was the first who
arrived and then nothing was happening
so I I thought I would go to the other
one and I saw cat was like doing the
code at that point as well so she was
like she already arrived and then I left
her alone there and I was about to go up
to the other communication thingy but
then already F so then I went back and I
saw I think I saw crony again or so yeah
but I didn't see FAA and I didn't see
Iris at all I saw you Kiara I saw all of
you guys I don't know I know I saw all
of you guys' Communications I I was I
was with fa alone for a while and she
didn't kill me yeah I saw Nissa go down
go down I didn't I was going to the
green down where are you right now um I
ended up in the lookout because I got
lost and I was very
confused so you
all yeah little suspicious of crony cuz
she didn't vote for Fu Moko she we have
time we're running out of suspicious
enough to vote [\h__\h] yeah
I don't know I I I don't know either I'm
gonna
skip you're gonna
skip
skipping
we good luck crew
mates what did Amy
say
oh oh they so oh I have to do task okay
have to do
[Music]
task La I got to do my work got to go do
the homework in the
[Music]
laboratory oh like this Boop and then
and then Boop wait and then Boop and
then and then this and then this and
then this wow pretty pretty Rock okay
and then oh and I got one more to do
down here and then we can
go like samples and then we got to go
narissa is stay alive
narissa oh
gemstone
mushroom mushroom
okay I'm done oh Amy
Amy
[Music]
oh oh who's that I can't tell who anyone
is oh that's cloney where is Iris
I want to see the action oh there she is
there she
is there she is FAA no FAA run FAA fa
don't get so close to her
FAA fa
run fa why are you following her that's
not safe fa fa
[Music]
no uh hello hello help me I think no say
trying to kill me ah you are so I can't
believe you I was not cheed everyone's
vitals and I decided to go back to the
meeting area canell and I saw her and I
got a little scared so I ran back but
then she chilled so I thought it was
cool but then she hit the emergency
meeting button much to my surprise no
the thing is there's a little bit of a
backstory I was running around and the
there back story yeah I my task what do
you mean backstory
I was running around I was I was you
know I I I was running around crony
alone she didn't kill me I was running
around fauna alone she didn't kill me
and both of those I kind of thought were
sus and then I found you and you kind of
followed me and now I think if it's not
cron if it's not fa I didn't follow you
what do you mean I ran into you and then
I ran back to the meeting area you are
so fake
K I was also around crony and she did
not kill me either yeah even though she
could have and as I was doing tasks I
could have killed crony too and I didn't
which I would have if I had the
opportunity to if I
were everybody tell me Iris uh and tell
me FAA what are the remaining tasks that
you have I'm done with tasks
and yeah I saw yeah B sorry you felt
like I was chasing you I I was I was
kind of scared I was kind of scared you
were like stick to me like whole time
yeah I have I have a task to do at the
dock okay and then I have one at the
cafeteria then do it and then we win yes
task wi let's go guys we have also I
think people who are done with the tasks
can um wait in the meeting area or
follow yeah I mean we have to do the
tasks we can't just wait in the meeting
area no no no like people who are done
with the test can follow can I add on I
do think I do think Nissa is a little
bit suspicious Nissa you and me Let's
Stay Together
I'm stay with you
no you or not we're staying together
now tag along with you guys if that's
okay just to see if one of you okay
still safon is there wait then maybe you
twoo are the imposters no I'm done with
my tasks as a thing so I they want to
kill me it is kind of scary oh my God I
didn't kill you when you were around
yeah what the he oh you two didn't kill
each other because you're
both oh my God come with me and why you
pending it on the blue women yeah let's
just all stay together and we'll see
what the blue women do oh my God we
follow Iris does anyone else have no I'm
all done oh yeah we just follow Iris we
should pressure her follow yeah let's
follow yeah yeah you can totally follow
me
okay nice hey who voted for me bow bow
down wait am I getting okay okay good
you better you little [\h__\h] love you k
please don't kill me okay okay let's
follow Iris see what she
does she's just standing
there bow
bow I
falling B it's not safe I don't know why
you're trusting Iris one it's not
[Music]
safe
it's so
quiet
oh win who
was excuse me I was it was desk what who
was the impost impost though Iris I
wonder who was it was ir and
IR
[Music]
you know outed themselves so good you
put us on
the doing I'm sorry I was supicious of
you FAA I'm sorry I was suspicious of
you Iris didn't kill fa
fa I wanted I wanted to keep someone on
my side so and because crony was susing
fun in the beginning I was like maybe I
should keep her on my side and kill
crony
in and like I I saw that Iris was uh
going into the same room as uh narissa
was so I was kind of waiting outside the
room to see I saw I saw I was like oh no
I think she's sus I was trying to kill I
was trying to kill you actually um I
when you were inside the lab I was I was
following you and I was goingon to kill
you but then I noticed you were moving
weirdly and you were like running away
and then Marissa came comes in right
away like oh never mind I can't kill you
here gave up went back I think I was
playing a little bit too cautiously but
um so difficult there's only there's
only me that's Li I was I was worried
like it was still pretty good
yeah still impressive yeah I can't I
can't believe you suspected
me I was
pinging
all's well it ends well hopefully when
we're together alone in the males
nothing I won't kill
you don't drown me in the ocean please
we're missing m Molly yeah
M oh sorry I was stuck let me just I'm
here sorry join us um I don't want to
like you know make any hard rules
because you know you just kill whoever
is
there but please do not kill am right
away next
[Music]
round no no no we need our we need our
space on out to do her job yeah kill me
first I love being the
ghost no pressure yeah no
pressure okay we complete I changed one
thing I changed that the votes uh you
can't see who voted that makes it really
hard for me to try to vote someone
oh boy let's
go see you
later
bye do your task okay
muted
um uh okay
door playing video I'm alone again I
don't like
this
anybody I want a friend
[Music]
friend any friend oh army army
army arm me I don't want to arm
me okay okay
um oh okay I go Army I want to go with
army I want to go with
army I will protect
ony
Amy no one's going to go for Amy so I
want to be with army I protect
Amy I'll protect you
Aly I'll protect
you
don't kill her FAA don't kill
her
[Music]
H hello oh for a moment I thought you
were dead
again oh no
no
well is dead Det I just saw her alive
like less than 30 seconds ago must have
just happened I just found it in the
meeting room but I was up in the drop
ship if you look at the map and then I
went down and I found her body there and
biu was up there and fauna was up there
and bi looked like she came from down
below so I'm a little sus I austral you
because I knew no one would kill you so
I thought it' be safer with you down
under like story but but was following
the both of us though so I'm kind of ss
of fa I was just making sure no funny
business was going on who was around I
was alive like less than 30 seconds
before she was found dead like I it felt
like like 10 seconds before so I'm I'm
like What's Happening that was a really
fast yeah I only passed by in that area
it was like bioo and fauna and that's it
I think in that area specifically you
see anyone like coming from that
direction
I
saw storage room and then I was using
the
zipline and like wasn't taking the zip
line up with me
yet oh Well people would you like to
defend yourself why boy I was following
Amy because I no one was going to kill
Amy so I thought Amy was the safest bet
but saw you didn't she not following her
but coming from a different direction I
was following Al this entire time
you did not
see I was running away from you so I
didn't always see you I was following
you the entire do you want to kill her
why are you following
[Music]
her inclusive evidence I've done one Tas
so far it was asteroids I haven't done
the rest because I was following yeah
the asteroids the video game didn't you
do asteroids in the last one too yeah I
have what is the asids one
like she has I went straight I will do
my test
now
I skip foro out I feel like
she's last time too I don't want to
die I don't know if you have by the way
Iris I don't know if you know but you
mut oh it's because she's dead oh never
[Laughter]
mind but she is dead I just wanted to
make sure she joins conversation you
know
I or if I die it's or Su one of them
out byebye people this is the last
time are we
voting I didn't even vote for her I
voted I just
ski I didn't vote for you people it
wasn't me oh thank
you I just like Say by
byebye people oh no we we ski it
bye that's the last time I trust you
guys to to to how do I do this oh okay
that's the last time I trust you guys to
say go with someone cuz I go with
someone and then and then I get I
get framed that's the last time dang
it go
away it's father I watched her kill for
oh [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] I knew
it she said she said
the switch
the maybe that's a shape shifter no that
makes it so much worse I went I know
it's not bi boo because I went down
because I saw bi boo pass us we were
both waiting to get into the kitchen
because last round Fu Moko and I were
frying fish together right so as I was
waiting I went to get beo because I was
like Advent together strong and then
when I came back it was right in front
of the kitchen it was right in front of
the kitchen is where is where the death
just happened and I saw someone running
up to the Splash Zone so where was
everybody and don't
lie wait you found which which of the
two bodies did I don't I don't know
where I don't know
where then I have something to add I was
just up at the very top of the
communications and there was crony and
there was fauna first there was fauna
and me and everything was cool then
crony joined I left and now FAA is dead
okay can you confirm this crony um after
I was uh doing the ladder task I went
down to the zip line again after that
was done so I didn't really you saw
Kiara up there yeah I saw Kiara and
fauna up there and then after I was done
with the ladder I went down the zip line
and I couldn't see anything else aside
from that maybe someone vent I'm not
really sure cuz it's kind of a short
maybe
you I mean I
know I know G to give my alibi really
quick and I saw bio and we were alone
and she didn't come after me or anything
but I was in the Splash Zone in the
beginning I collected shells and then I
left okay where were you though at the
time of the
murder I went up to St Happ I reported
it immediately yeah I I know I went to
spash Zone and I collected the shells
and then I saw bioo and she didn't hurt
me and then I went back to storage okay
and then cron FAA and kiata were over in
Communications yeah so Watson where were
you I was at the
laboratory I I am s of am because Iris
was around me fa and Amy yeah I am too
and now so now I'm
s trying to vote someone off no cuz the
last the last murder the everyone who
was present we know that it wasn't fa
now and obviously iris is dead so it's
only you or bio but I know where bi was
of the Mur forgetting that the first
round I reported the body and both bio
and faer were with me and none of them
said that they bi even said that she was
following me the whole time but she
didn't see me kill anyone
huh CR trust me
me I trust you I
trust who are we voting for
iort self
reported no
what why are these boats yes oh my God
impost are
gone
byebye says no I don't know Kara is
really suspicious right now okay see you
later uh okay oh okay I got to go to the
greenhous a I have a pet AET
oh I couldn't pet the pet before Oh
man is this how they get you to want a
Pay to
Win how do I get in the greenhous oh
here we
go they give me a taste of what pay to
win is like and then they take it
[Music]
away oh I got to use the mushroom
door it's so
[Music]
quiet um 1 70
79 Bing
okay got to go up here where is
everyone oh I'm Different
again oh Pebbles I'm sorry oh oh Pebbles
oh I'm sorry
Pebbles oh please don't be mad this is
part of my
task okay
completed okay what else do I got to do
I got to go to Upper end oh Cara oh
oh she watching
me
uh uh-oh uh-oh uh-oh uh-oh uhoh uh-oh
uh-oh uh-oh uh
uh-oh uh-oh uh-oh
uh-oh I don't think it's Kiara
she's she she has every opportunity to
kill
me and then we made the reactor normal
I'm scared of Amy I'm scared of Amy I
really think it might be Amy I'm scared
I am scared of Amy
I do not want to
get me me me me I really I really I
really don't want to I really don't
think I think
S I should I should check I just I'm
going
to I'm going to oh oh oh
oh oh no Weis I wanted to check if
anyone and re dead oh yeah I didn't I
was wondering too I I think Kiara is
safe yeah cuz we just did the emergency
thing together yeah and then I'm join
right when we think I ran away cuz both
of you guys are I thought both of you
guys were the impostor you were going to
kill me no I I really because the first
death was Iris and me FAA and Iris were
the ones that were closest to each other
and yeah well that's and now I'm scared
I know it's not Kiara because Kiara
didn't kill me or anything yes so yeah
okay I still have three tasks left by
the way wait so why did why did you just
call him eating because I was wondering
if anybody died cuz we're about to
finish our tasks and you don't want us
to finish our tasks you're imp quiet and
I was scared if anyone was going to die
and I thought like might as well chat
and right and look tell what were you
doing I went down to mushrooms mhm and
what's the last task you did the Sorting
the mushrooms into the jars and the
crystals Kelly has been quiet yeah she I
mean ask me any questions you want but
if you talk too much you get sused out
too so just ask me any questions and
I'll tell you am what's the last task
you
did um I don't remember I was in
the shot I can't ask chat too because I
can't even look at chat um I know this
sounds suspicious but yeah I don't
remember I'm going I'm going to vote for
Amy I think with my yeah you're the
impostor you're just you called the
meeting because we're so close to
finishing our tasks that you're scared
no [\h__\h] I'm scared of
dying aren't we all I mean I saw cie and
she didn't kill me and I was running
away from you guys cuz I thought you
guys were going to kill me so H that's
my defense yeah okay we vote okay oh you
guys if you guys vote for me you're
wrong just so you know uh oh I'm gonna
vote for
Kelly
or she seems most sus cuz I saw you I
saw kiar and biu together and you guys
didn't die so unless you're both the
impostor no we're not uhhuh that's
exactly what an impostor would
say well if there was two imposters
alive we would lose by now so there's
only one oh okay that's true so one of
the previous was well crony I guess was
the one that got knocked out right so
wouldn't that be yeah yeah H I don't
know I don't
know no I say we just Skip and continue
doing our tasks unless you guys are if I
was the impostor I'd try to vote one of
you guys out right now and then I'd
probably
win so I'm going to skip you guys are
wrong regret your decision I love you
I'll miss you yeah
right no you
burning are we winning please what all
right how many more oh sorry
sorry
oh it's not this it's not this it's not
this it's not
this let's freaking
go
g that was wacky it wasn't me god well
played well
played that was wild I
[Music]
wish Hur house she was quiet oh you
turned into fun I see see we thought
Kelly somebody was quiet too but F
thought [\h__\h] I'm so sorry how do I ever
redeem myself to you it's too late it's
too
late can't even believe me I toally wasy
too my God I'm not a real Amy
goling I tried to protect her and now
I'm the one that killed her
I can't trust anymore yeah I can't trust
T I'm sorry I can't believe I got
impostor
twice lying why is everybody good at
lying I've been watching professional
Japanese Among Us players
recently everybody's just poker the had
practice that's
why you guys you didn't listen to
me damn it and I still didn't get
impostor single time
man maybe next time we still got more we
still got more time right yeah there's a
little more time then let's go next
round oh I saw I saw by the way the
ghosts uh were going in their own
channel did you have
fun yes yes recommend it it was fun I
don't know why crony was probably too
guilty to Jo the dead voice C oh wait
there's a dead voice chat I didn't even
know voice chat I was like why isn't she
joining I was like oh probably cuz she
feels guilty oh no I don't feel guilty
at
all AB you don't feel any shame crony
just randomly get voted off too cuz I
don't remember like everybody yeah I got
voted
off
M K knew yeah cuz I told you yeah yeah I
told you to believe me see oh it was
actually good what I did thank God she
was right you were so right easy way to
tell easy way to tell if if Callie is
imposter she's quiet she's imposter all
right impost so I don't know bye you are
the impos
wait is that was that a fake
out is that a fake
out
[Music]
okay and then flash Zone I muted right I
M oh oh oh hello
everyone oh
hello
Callie I'm Susy you you might just be
standing there
oh uh okay green
house
Green House Green House
oh how do I get in
oh okay there's
Iris how do I do
this how do I how do I do
this
what
oh oh thank
you use the stairs oh we got to fix the
coms where is
El um
18850 check why is it so Qui
oh I didn't even see I didn't even see I
didn't even really see I didn't f wa I
didn't even really seeit she was just
there wait wait wait what what happened
was that wait who you see no no no no it
wasn't me I was where were you where
were you when you pressed
it who pressed it wa I I pressed it uh I
was oh my God I was so in my tangent oh
my God I went up to the top right to the
communications and I was just Tangen
thing and doing a task and suddenly I
see a dead body but on the same spot I
think I saw at least one more person
maybe another maybe two people so it's
Kiara Iris fuok and then I just came
into the room and I saw Callie
outside I just the moment I went up the
ladder all of a
sudden
Communications almost the same time and
then I was trying to go in the way to
the mushroom door but I got rid of the
mushrooms but uh maybe killed by
accident maybe it's just am him by being
silly
uhhuh wait
what I'm you there right when I reported
right my own no I just walked into the
room like after cie she was already in
there like alive and you guys were all
doing the power thing or whatever and I
was also starting to do the power thing
putting in the code but then you guys
finished it and then somebody reported
Call's body so I didn't even see it wait
so you're saying besides me there was
cie and
you there were like two other people
inside the
communications Iris how all in there no
one was on the other side of the
mushroom wall so I don't think they
could kill her on the other side of the
mushroom wall but I don't know yeah I
just went up the ladder how it went and
then all of a sudden report there might
there was one other person in there but
it was hard to see cuz everybody was
bunched up I think I saw purple yeah
purple was Call's dead body no no
purple's
be purple we do have something to report
yeah h we
heard okay you are the and the
mute we were thinking maybe this being
Sil you know that's thing that we we do
that I heard that I thought she was
saying it to someone else and now I'm a
trying can we have someone who hasn't
talked talk please me me me yes so um I
was at communications I saw a bunch of
people there and I was trying to like uh
do my task and like I was still on the
task when it happened so I didn't really
see anything oh so you were also in
Communications there many people there
okay wait you were there even now when
when I reported you were still
there um yeah yeah oh so you were one of
the other people I saw then but I wasn't
sure who am I seeing oh [\h__\h] I voted for
f well I remember this I will remember
this
but oh sh you
guys I a
joke are they going to go in the Dead
channel are they going in the Dead
channel they're not in the Dead channel
yet all time to do my choppy choppy
choppy
vegetables vegetables are so
delicious I like vegetables okay next
has
F oh
wow what wait wait
what
everyone like a crowd of people
communication wait did you did
you did you guys
people
yeah wow see The Quiet Ones it's always
the quiet ones I knew cron never hasn't
said anything but I was ctive last round
that's cuz I asked you to
talk we're both innocent I'm sorry I
thought you guys by AC when I thought it
was too B sounded
suing susing Amit right because of her
statement but it
wasn't kidding I said that on
purpose
we just being silly H the two imposters
would of course vote for
fuo I
see sorry
oh my God this is what happened okay
next we we got to go
next don't give it to the blue people it
to the people
n oh oh oh how do I do
this
oh oh I
see
WEA I go this way
I go this
way please don't kill me please don't
kill me please don't kill me please
don't kill me please don't kill me f f
don't kill me oh oh okay F oh we have no
f F can we go together F can we be
friends are you playing asteroids okay
let's go together F let's go
together go Oh wrong
way oh oh this
[Laughter]
way
oh oh
I ran up because of the communications
thing was down and she was right there
in Communications in front of the the
thingy was any I was at the other I was
at the other I was with but I didn't see
body I was down by the dock I was in the
labs oh me um oh yeah I just met crony
in the labs
yeah Iris and I are doing the other task
the power thing didn't kill each other I
think we're
safe pushing up some lift what
narissa where were you I was down by the
dock I I figured that you probably all
were going there and I wanted to keep
doing my tasks so I just went down and I
was doing a sand castle and then I was
checking since yeah don't the um I
passed I passed tasks yeah they
disappear but if you pass them you can
still do them oh okay yeah so I was
checking manually okay or if you just
still like remember where they were
before it went down
yeah moo
reactor reactor that's
it what task have you done what were you
doing at the reactor we're doing our
task doesn't want to use the map I don't
like the map I like finding the little
yellow mark on the the screen it's more
fun now you know
marow emping the
yellow I actually haven't done that yet
the yellow there's a yellow marow is so
cute little Among
Us
uh the marshmallow
yeah so in but what task were you
doing yeah the marshmallows are nowhere
near the reactor yeah so what were you
doing that was
yeah but what were you doing today huh
we were doing a bunch of in the Rea what
were you doing what were you doing in
the reactor yeah what were you doing the
reac kind of
[Laughter]
s skip vote for now I'll give you guys
the benefit of the D thank you please
don't kill us
[Music]
[Laughter]
again
I am sus of them Iris don't kill me Iris
Iris Iris oh oh I'm
scared
don't follow me no I can't check vital
right now the commas are
dead okay
okay IR don't kill
me
no one's dead
yet I don't think I should
oh don't hurt me who's that oh oh don't
hurt me oh don't hurt me oh don't hurt
me oh oh don't hurt me oh don't hurt
me okay everyone is still alone
live um oh I have to do this
one
oh
okay got to save the C so I can see
who's
[Music]
dead on the is here
kis is here should I check
vital everyone's alive oh I
can't it was Kara it was k
k killed don't believe
her I saw people kill amen I am medic I
am medic I can see people's
vitals yeah and I can see you kill am I
am I am medic I can see people's vs I
have three battery charges every round
to see how many people are alive this is
the first time I have many I saw Kiara
kill no people watch it no no it say
hard for me because I had just I had
just seen bibu and but I did not see
kiia and I was going down and she didn't
follow me so she might have realized she
was alone with a but uh bioo also when
she killed me self-reported and then
this is literally the first time I've
got this scientist and I have this is
the first time I play it so how would I
know that I have three charges of
scientist to check
vital where is the body time in a while
all the body is up the stairs by
Communications I saw K kill watch it you
probably just looked up some guide about
those no I didn't things this is the
first time I have whatever scientist
whatever I can check people's bi well I
was I was so often alone with others and
I didn't kill them so why would I you
know can somebody vouch for me cuz I
think I was Al Al alone together with a
lot of
people come
on I was alone with people for a while
but I was not alone with Kiara yeah I
saw Kiara for like a split second I saw
several times alone and I saw crony
several times I think alone and I saw
narissa like maybe one or two times
alone yeah it felt like um either Kiara
or FAA was going to kill me cuz like
they were just kind of walking around so
I stuck around one of them to make sure
I didn't get killed um it would kind of
check out if Kiara
was I saw the K I believe I believe wow
okay
sorry
goodbye forever thanks forever H what
was that I I love you or I'm
D thank you
forever
well somebody's not
voting I just accepted that you guys are
voting me me out but I guess you'll
you'll no you're running down the
clock it's so sad I I was always with
you guys
love
you goodbye goodbye I will go up like a
phoenix and I will rise like a
phoenix look I was useful I
helped I helped I was so
useful okay this is the same right yeah
that's the same
okay now I got to watch out and make
sure fa don't kill me FAA FAA don't kill
me fa I trust you I don't think you're
the impostor
B don't kill me b b don't do
it okay oh
Irish are they still good in there okay
are they still good okay they're still
good don't kill me
don't kill
me I don't want
die
okay I I really don't think it's fa it
could be Irish full moo came from up
there
okay everyone's here except for full
m office not
active Office active
oh
okay okay everyone's still
alive
I got to go to the
reactor I think I'm safe with
fa I don't want to check vitals too
often because I have a
limit um we got to go I got to go down
here
fa oh
[Music]
hello
the oh no I I because I I I believe it's
F what why when when we were going to
when comms were down we were going up I
see I see like um many of us were going
up I think it was like I think I saw fa
beu um I also saw I was also with crony
and narissa alone none of us killed each
other um and we were all going up to
comms but then I see fok coming down
from comms ignoring the fact that
coms do the bottom one first right we
just try to do the tasks and you know
you were at the Top If you were at the
top you would do the top one right but
we're just counting like we're focusing
on our task yeah you can't see the task
on the map when comms are down yeah you
can't but if you walk around you can
find them so that's did last time
too
% that's why I decided to call on and I
can't get
anything that's how we play Among
Us this time what's what's the task you
did what's the task you The Green House
Green House
doing why' you you you come came back
down from comms even though comms is
sabotaged all the way back down to the
greenhous greenhous is
pretty green greenhous is
pretty you got
[Laughter]
a who are the cutest puppies who are wow
look at the Little
Liars look at the Little Liars
oh
Li just bow bowing anding none of
us
[Music]
goodbye come on F cast your
boat yeah don't don't um delay your
death it's time yeah it's inevitable go
mhm what excuse
me
oh byebye
[Applause]
[Music]
puppies
funny
funny that was really good susing out
that was
impressive Awesome from The reactor too
even the last round when when we almost
voted them out cuz they didn't know what
they were doing at the reactor
was that made me 80% sure and then I saw
them going down from com so oh yeah yeah
definitely what this little we me will
do the
ex
yes I'm so sorry it's okay you were just
trying to survive I understand I think I
think out of this whole group of people
me and foku are like the worst Liars so
it wasn't a good
combination my your B
my we were so bad hard to lie
[Music]
Wasa makes me
laugh IA laugh too you see see I I had
the good the good life you know I did
the marshm was and then she goes oh we
did that last
time oh my god well at least I finally
got imposter do we don't want to do one
more round
yeah hide and seek for the last change
the hide and seek hide and
seek hide andek sounds fun it's like
hide and seek like how you'd really
think hideand-seek
would I don't think we have to M for
hideand-seek
there an actual setting for hide and
seek though yeah there there is there is
computer uh you might have to make a new
room though maybe um if you can't change
it in the settings um on the computer
yeah then you might have to make a new
room is
it yeah no I don't think you can change
it
here okay then I'll make a new
one
okay okay
it's kind of like it's pretty much like
playing tag yeah
cute um any preferred
map anything let's do the original oh
yeah yeah let's do oh
yeah
nice I'll send you the link in the group
uh the in the
group okay there this one's chaotic but
really fun I've never done it before oh
it's fun
and it's a short game too
so let's go
perfect man this scary this one this is
like the only time I actually want to be
imposter hide and seek yeah really fun I
never want to imp ever
again say we don't have the me for this
you said oh no I don't think so right
just try not to give location I guess we
can if we're
dead uh we don't have
to in this game
hey wait we can we can hide in vents oh
is there only
one oh is this like
zombies we can hide really slow tasks
timer go down quicker so slow do we have
three minutes to
hide three minutes to hide she's in the
med
Bay she's
coming what wait
what oh man is
she she she's what
color
wow everybody's clumping
together where is she right
now is that
call wait how does this
work name tags no do your best you can
hear the music come close to you when
she's close by that's
scary crony where's
crony oh that's fun that's so quick too
that was so
[Music]
w for both the impostor and the the the
the crew mates MH
can we increase the speed for both crew
mates yeah I want to but also I I uh I
think I have to make a new Lobby because
I don't think I can change the amount of
uh Seekers oh there's only
one yeah it's fine to leave it on one we
just need to speed up so we're all
running really
fast okay
Max W that this is how it should
bee oh
[Music]
boy yum let's
go wait do I get to go that fast too I
think
so I'm going to be Unleashed from my
you okay oh God I don't forget to do
your Tas do your task I think there's
task
task I don't see them I see tasks but I
don't know what I really want to finish
[Music]
that R I'm scar I'm scared I'm scared
I'm scared I hear I hear the base we got
to win we got to win this I can't find
you guys what the heck everyone oh it's
so
[Music]
fastk you guys yelling I'm not even near
you
[Music]
Terri it's like a horror game all of a
sudden on
where you guys
[Applause]
[Music]
go terrifying screams
here going
louder is so going louder and louder
yeah it's so chaotic get in trouble
maybe I show the moment you hear the
guitar Rift you're like
she
coming my eyes are
[Music]
spinning
who's you're going to be even fast final
round I'm alive okay should I do
tasks
hiding I need you to run around like a
chicken one more minute
to don't stand still because it's going
to show your location later on shows do
you guys know where shows location it
shows loation there's a there's a red
dot uh that indicates where the crew is
oh my have
on what do they have see dead bodies I
see dead bodies I see
[Laughter]
[Music]
de [\h__\h] does she see me from the map too
or only when she gets closer oh God oh
[Music]
God that was
soose
hard that was impressive IR that was
really good I don't know how I just
didn't really see her on the screen that
often so thank God everybody was so
fast that was teleporting across the
map yeah the couldn't even keep
track nothing is scary who is it this
time let's go who is
it go today I think she's going to have
fun run run
R does doing tasks do anything
like an early task win if we do if we
finish them all yeah and we could get
lucky and I was being very proactive
with the task hide it's hide and seek
you got to hide not not no I can't die
okay oh
no okay got to go got to go got to go I
was about to get the thing I'm
sorry I'm
sorry
I
was oh
no on you guys on you guys damn
it I I do wonder if doing tasks is even
worth it I know right I feel you
just my quick she ran past she ran past
[Music]
no she's going on going to the cafeteria
wait can we tell
her it might be a little
unfair oh okay I felt that was the wrong
direction okay you know what let's do it
tasks sque I'm too scared to move around
at this point I die whenever I use do
tasks it's
just
4K she only has only three
left what is the danger meter ah come on
guys one more one more
minute good hiding she she's going at a
good Pace very good Pace
oh
30 30 seconds 35
seconds that was a really good hiding
spot yeah that was a nice hiding
[Applause]
[Music]
spot so
loud oh no
[Music]
whoopsy yes everybody's so
fast on is there overtime now she's
now you have minute so fast I
can't got
survive no pressure oh
man go go you have 30 seconds left you
can
it what you do you're Phoenix press is
getting to
her get suck on the wall no
no you have 10 seconds 10 seconds just
live 10 seconds easy easy she won't get
you she won't she won't get you oh
[Laughter]
no
W one literally
oneit like millisecond
like though
that that was the clutchest
ever can't escape time at the end of the
day but is really slippery yeah really
slippery oh my God that was exciting
that was
so
exciting I'm I'm pretty exhausted from
that but we can do another one if you
want I'm down for one
more actually you know wait wait oh no
before Oh I want to I want to speed so
fast yeah it's fast oh good okay
never what you wanted how do you how do
you kill time um there's a kill button
so don't you worry okay oh my God no way
I don't want to be it no the she has
awakened she has awakened I'm coming for
you nobody's using my hiding spot right
oh oh no good idea don't use my Hiding
might go use it no that wasn't your
hiding
shoot he's on a rampage there were there
I only saw one
person
overl does the music get louder for me
too I feel like it does I know it gets
louder when you're near someone really
even for
imposter you little [\h__\h] get out of
there get out of there you little
[\h__\h] what's going
on
[Music]
where are
they my hiding spot oh I
[Music]
see oh no that's okay that's the stack
de bodies I still got time I still got
time I saw someone where is
[Music]
she that hiding
spot oh my God that was no no I haven't
found anyone in like ages
you passed by
[Music]
somebody someone's here no oh
[\h__\h] where are
you hello I'm all
alone no hints no help oh what was that
there was some button popping up there
the use button
[Music]
yeah in
time I could even see you that's lame
what the
heck didn't see you well I saw you
that's all that matters oh dang it
nice oh no run run
a oh one more one
more
run no no no
no there's still one more
minute they're literally right there run
run
run you can throw it through a loop just
R going going Circle
[Music]
[Applause]
wow that was again pretty clutch I would
say get into
[Applause]
theing after Mama Mia
that was wow that was fun yeah that was
yeah that was fun that was merry I'm too
excited to say anything so let's start
with the with the goodbyes from anybody
but me um am please do yeah this is
really fun I'm glad we could get
together and have like a little
Christmas Among Us
celebration perfect holiday SE holiday
game right for
real just red with
and some blood when I think of Christmas
I think of among usol and Among Us
ornament it's pretty festive the colors
you this makes me want to play this
makes me want to play on Project winter
yeah oh my
[Music]
good yeah I know
C wow than I'm sorry you died so often
I'm
that's okay still fun call what about
you you had some good good kills fun it
was nice getting to dust off the old
Scythe for once and get back in the game
for a little bit that was
nice yeah I had a great time with
everybody here everybody here is fun to
talk to fun to argue with in a fun way
really in a fun way yeah in a fun way I
guess that's about it we should argue
more often yeah let's do it let's do it
no no I can't maybe not yeah no we just
stay TIY but within among us we can
argue as much as we want right and then
outside of Among Us you know we're
different people among us changes us
yeah it Happ Among Us stays in Among
Us stays Among
Us
all right and please please tell me
about your experience today science
Rules science
science sciencey science science Rules
end statement next
great interesting interesting I don't
quite understand but I agree oh I don't
think Kiara knows about Bill it's all
right don't worry about
it don't worry about it
we'll tell you later we'll tell you
later oh it's a m okay
I Mrs Mrs Santa Claus Mrs CHR yes yeah
know this was fun I'm glad I was able to
lie better this time yeah yeah you good
lying we need to learn from
IR that suspect yeah everyone everyone
was great I love how bad F was at
L
yeah tell it's their you can tell it's
their first time you can tell it's their
first time my first time it was the same
as me when I played for the first time
wor firster is always like that it's
great I love it thank you very much that
was fun they were so lucky cuz like in
that one round they were about to be
voted off and I thought I was going to
be alone but then somehow somehow they
survived survived
right I couldn't save you so fun okay we
couldn't save each other even if we
wanted
to well thank you Iris and then people I
I was happy to be able to kill people I
wish I was able to kill more people but
I was satisfied the amount of people I
was able to kill this time it was very
fun that's the spirit thank you for your
service that's the spirit that's the
Christmas Spirits let's go let's
go it was some good reaping
solid good job again I'm so sorry P
okay a trail was it stays in Among Us
stays Among Us don't worry about
exactly well we l a lot of things today
we really good at lying right yeah that
was
it yeah and uh we have fun we we yelled
a bit screamed a bit and we do a lot of
lying yeah but most importantly we had
[Applause]
fun true let's
play when I saw I was imposter with f m
I knew I knew that you weren't going to
be good at
[Laughter]
lying we s yeah it's all good true it's
funny I had so much fun thank you so
much for putting it together
[Music]
Ki I'm sad I had to be the impostor I
don't like it brings me no
joy I know what you mean no oh but you
were so good though you were good at it
with was over right away me murderer of
blue women women are
scared blue women I always say it it's
the blue people the the avatars I always
say
it yeah thank you you're welcome I'm
glad you had a good time let's let's
continue this in the Mal Dives yeah
peacefully the other Blue Woman
Quon yeah it was a lot of fun I'm kind
of surprised that I actually got
impostor twice U because I never get
imposter yeah I never get these
roles yeah and thank you for organizing
this it was a lot of
fun I love
among I guess you know there was all
sorts of drama but like we said earlier
what happens Among Us stays among
wow wow beautiful
well said Thank You
Quon well yeah that's pretty much it um
but Christmas is not over yet I think
there's still members that have like
special streams upcoming so check them
out everybody and I just want to make
one quick announcement about the whole
Ian Advent calendar some people may
already know but the last day the 25th
day will be delayed a little bit so uh a
few days uh the it's out of my head out
of my power now but please check back on
it next week we'll all tweet about it
when it is finally up uh so stay tuned
stay excited and thank you for spending
Christmas with us viewers I say to you
viewers thank you for spending it with
us and thank you to the girls for
spending it also with us thank you for
getting together at this
time Merry Christmas
everyone chras
[Music]
had a lot of fun that was really great
and I hope everybody has a nice nice
holiday season eat some
cookies yay Yum Yum Yum Yum okay some
protein milk in my
fridge very Christmas for
Santa May Santa will come to to drink
your milk oh protect your
milk yeah all right I don't think that's
GNA make Iris like Santa
anymore no Santa is is literally the
tree now I'm the tree but I'm not yet
don't to drink the protein milk we can't
let him get any stronger muscles for
Santa no don't give him the power no the
cookies wait is it like in some
countries Santa drinks beer or people
give beer to Santa really
sounds German Santa gets drunk I don't
know I think so drunk
Sant I don't know if that's oh no oh
no just makes it worse that doesn't
really sound like something I would want
to tell my children over yeah okay with
that I think some people already gone
like fle is gone already so I guess
let's go
[Music]
everybody happy holidays to all in good
bye merry Christmas happy Merry
[Music]
Christmas