[Music]
going
OB
[Music]
don't
my you say I'm way toile
[Music]
just don't even know what do
said they could play A Part
[Music]
me me me me me me me me me me
ring do it this
[Music]
K Kitty key sorry about the delay don't
worry about the lag in the game right
now it's only because I am not tabbed
in
um
yeah
sorry I know
why it's not I mean they could make it a
bit clearer but it's not uh their fault
it's my fault but they could make it a
bit
clearer do you want to know
do you want to know what
[Music]
happened you still blame it on them okay
yeah we can so okay it's been a long
time since I logged into Battlenet we
obviously played this game before but
that was like ages ago and so it's been
a long time since I opened up battl net
m
and I I wasn't sure which account to use
at first so I just tried one email
address I was like okay this one's not
working I guess it wasn't on this email
and so on eventually I I log into an
account that existed and it had uh on
the top it says like World of Warcraft
and Diablo 4 like as the games that I
have and then it says for Diablo 4 I
need to update it
okay so I click update takes a while
takes a while finally it finishes and it
says
like you can't play this game yet and
I'm like
why and I try out all kinds of things
restart PC and so on but
no it says that it's up to date and it
says it's live and I updated it and
everything but but it says I can't play
it yet H
so what
yeah it was the wrong
account but why doesn't it say hey this
account has not purchased the game even
though it's like showing because I know
why it shows it it recognizes that the
game has been installed on the PC but so
you could misunderstand easily and think
oh the game is in this account because
it shows there because when I went to
the other account it didn't show World
of Warcraft for example in the top bar
but it showed like
OverWatch yeah but Diablo 4 also was
there yeah Diablo 4 was on both sides
for some
reason maybe I don't know I I don't know
why uh but yeah
then uh in the actual account I could
just play play it right away because I
already updated it through the other
account that that's confusing why am I
able even though I supposedly on this
account don't own the game why am I able
to update it through that
account you know that's confusing that's
why I thought oh yeah okay this is the
one this one has Diablo 4 it only wants
me to update it okay let's do
it I mean I understand the logic that
you know it recognizes the game on the
PC so it just updates it even though I
don't own it on the computer but still
it's weird it's obviously
confusing oh well oh
[\h__\h] oh so
many cracks
[Laughter]
[\h__\h] yeah yeah it us just the same
folders yeah yeah yeah I mean I get it
but also that's confusing don't do it
like that tell me tell me that it's on a
different
account I had to look through I have a
million email addresses had to look
through which one it
was it's been a while it's been a while
it's been a while um yeah today was sore
sore sore time again in
Jakarta let's see is there anybody who
just went to the
concert I know that had a couple of kfp
went there but I've also heard there's
like an after party so maybe you guys
are busy at the after
party looks like
fun yeah the world tour whole life world
tour yeah with some some of the whole
Live members no but Al see in Atlanta
let's [\h__\h]
go let's go
know uhuh uhuh it was a lot of aans I
know I
saw like I saw the group picture from
kfp the group picture looks like it was
like mostly people flying
in I don't know if there's some some a
lot more kfp from ID D who missed the
group picture but the group picture
really just looks like mostly flown in
people I heard seata life was also super
high I think it was yeah I did for my
solo I did Chimera which was really hype
everybody loved the moment the press for
moment
everybody went like
wooo once again and singing a
longy yeah I didn't do Mirage I wanted
to make like I I know I recently did the
the the tutorial on how to you know but
the set list was decided a while ago and
um you might see you know Mirage
somewhere in the future but for this one
it was already set that it was going to
be Kima um so I didn't want you guys to
like think oh that it has if she is
teaching us how to cheer for Mirage a
few days before the concert then now I
have to learn it because surely this
means that she is she's she's performing
in Jakarta I hope you guys weren't
thinking that and then like learning
hardcore trying to learn hardcore when
it wasn't even going to be performed I'm
sorry but sometime in the future you
know it's good to be prepared in any
case yeah yeah yeah eventually yeah the
game is lagging just because I'm tabbed
out don't worry I'll tab in and then
we'll be
fine more yapping less
lagging I I don't think I can combine
that yeah well well well well uh now
it's it's this December no it's November
but um this was the second stop and from
now on there will be a lot of these
concerts most of them are like packed in
this winter season so November December
so they'll be there they will be a lot
of uh world tour stops so maybe you guys
can check out one of them somewhere and
if not just letting you know because
I'll I'll be you know not available
obviously to stream stream during those
times
yeah yeah let's
go the game is just lagging cuz I'm
tapped
Out understand well we we have some okay
here uh let's write down some topics I
wanted to uh what the what was I going
to talk
about oh uh new New
Gen
uh wait
ah
Arcane
[Music]
and
cats I can always talk about my cats but
it it it's just as per usual nothing new
I
suppose
uh um
ah okay just a few new just just just a
few
notes for MOS deos MOS MOS
deos okay here we go uh wait can
somebody I I didn't have time because I
was binge watching something didn't have
time to update myself what the I what we
may have forgotten about the game does
somebody have a uh like recap but like a
quick recap in the form of text
Max background oh really there's such a
setting I was helping out a girl
really we needed something from him and
he said no who's he El
Diablo Lil is back and pl something you
need to find out what you e Flowers I
ate flowers oh I did the village burned
down I I remember a village and like
some people dying there's a demon that
came back named Lil mefisto
Meo
H that name sounds familiar Lil hot Yeah
Lil is bad she took that girl's
mom uhuh God guy didn't give his
Blessing to chase
her huh that's very
vague Lil came she put rose petals in
people's mouths we need to stop her
okay we put misto in a soul Shard and
Nel left with it
Nel maybe we'll come back to
us also how do I even play this game I
don't remember I guess I can only use
this when I'm outside um this is the
beautiful lady
oh right I can't like change the angle
ah oh I tried pressing W ASD right we
don't walk around with WD huh or do we
no what is this
abilities have I used all my points no I
I have one more
Point uh I guess I was going for fire
mag
uh I was probably too quiet for you guys
here
louder you can change it to that you can
[Music]
use why why have I not done it already I
don't know what to put my skills into uh
for now whatever we leave that one
point was this I don't know what that is
um okay what what pet the well- behaved
dog is that a main
quest this one this is a dog wrong
dog she walked to it oh the the the
audio sometimes cuts
off just like can what was that
game ah hey the dog is from an
update oh seven days to die yeah now
we'll see how much it cuts out
um is that my stash
o o i don't remember anything Legacy
item Legacy
item why does it say Legacy
item did I always say
that is it because I saw something when
I was getting into the game about like
SE
Seasons or I don't know and it was
asking me do I want
[Music]
to if I but if I want to go into the
server that has seasons I need to make a
new character or something like
that what do you mean Seasons like
winter spring summer autumn or Seasons
as in like anime Seasons
or why would why would they force me to
make a new
character I guess we'll just not do that
then we don't yeah we will we won't have
seasons then will I ever regret that
that's their game Model season pass like
a battle pass
huh you only want to do the story so no
okay oh I'm not missing much
okay uh well okay how uh how do I know
which one's my main quest unlocks mounts
cool priority Quest introduces
imprinting
companions uh there's no dog
here it's the golden
one this is a side quest gold
gold aha here it
is okay we're
remembering that's a dog oh it's not my
dog you wonderer I I know what you are a
vtuber how do you know ah that somebody
dos me [\h__\h] who was it I come back after
such a long time and people know who
where I'm from who I am Mama
Mia okay let's do it I I'm here to just
by the way if in case you don't know why
is she suddenly playing the 4 again and
why is she playing alone now didn't she
play this as a collab before yeah yeah
yeah yeah but our collab group you know
never continued playing and uh now the
DLC is out and I was like I want to play
the DLC I think
um so I will finish the main story first
alone so I'm faster and more flexible
and then maybe if somebody wants to play
the DLC with me they're welcome to join
and there was some people that were
interested thank you I I saw many people
uh
liked my thumbnail see that the kitchen
is ready for tomorrow's service I'm glad
everybody liked my Photoshop skills
Angels Above you've returned yeah
returned I have indeed returned
K PE Peak thumbnail thank you I I I
graphic design is my passion I need a
holy blessing to continue chasing
Lil the Reverend mother will want to
hear of this but she is away at corv
Valar seek your blessing
there everything is unfolding as inarius
foretold soon he will be free to escape
sanctuary and return to the heavens
where he
belongs okay just to
clarify in this game there's acts right
and I am almost finished with act one
how many acts were
there
free it not
anymore
free probably
free why are there so many different
numbers we're talking without
DLC six act total plus one act DLC oh oh
okay perhaps there is
six why did people say I could probably
finish the whole main story in one
stream if there's six acts that seems uh
not
possible that was a
lie
okay
interesting it was a funny prank
it's a lie they were wrong
okay okay no problem I mean I I would
have been a little bit disappointed if I
could have finished the whole story in
one more
stream uh okay they don't know how to PA
oh never mind it's not about them not
knowing how to PA it's just this is not
e etal
is this where I'm
going how do
I I do I have a path now okay wait I do
want to I do want W
[Music]
ASD keyboard
movement yeah let's
go my mouse is available to do anything
what whatever it Wass go spe I saw you
in
there you're so sweet I hope you had a
really good
time thank you for traveling so far to
go to the
concert did you like it obviously you
did were you surprised
by um we the the last song we did a um
wait that always mix up the
names it was SSS
right
[Music]
um it we did a special
remix
version that was hopefully
hype a sore
only I wonder if they'll ever upload the
remix onto YouTube Because as far as I
know it's just sore only
remix wow who are you I don't want to
interact with you although that's a side
quest right but we want to focus on the
main story I hope it's not a uh not too
bad whoa NY Miner I suddenly I've
collected 500 iron chunks that that's
all it took maybe that was 500 at once
what I just collected diligent
minor okay
cool where did we left off K are we in
act we are almost done with Act One
apparently but you you should not ask me
where we have left off I do not don't I
don't know
anything I'm asking you
guys I am asking you once again to give
me a
recap this perfect I'm in the snow I'm
I'm standing in the snow I'm asking you
I am I am what's it what's it exactly
again I am asking you I am here to ask
you once
again to teach me the recap of this
game of the story so far I I am I am
once again asking you to remind me of
the
story please wa don't don't don't you
dare sound don't do anything anything
funny hey I want a mount when do you get
a mount in this game I I I saw there's a
quest to unlock mounts should I do that
first what is B
oh can't decide don't ask me level 30
okay I'm still far from that after act
free I don't think there's all
Paca what the what
how do I attack I don't remember okay
okay well this is good this is good this
is good this is good what what is that
is that mine stop stop
just I have dragons coming from the
ground is this this one Hydra
sick I thought the enemies became
that um hello sir Cromwell sir Cromwell
what are you doing here shouldn't you be
with the tutors
listen
carefully I haven't much
time one of our men Lord avitus was
failed in the ancient city beneath the
mountain we carried his body to the uy
but he
arose thirsting for blood I need more
context I
escaped please
you must slay him what he said listen
carefully but I didn't listen very
carefully I just listened very
carelessly the should I do
it what is this what is this what is
this you
sound you sound like
uh like AI Keandre
what is this though what on my map I
have to do something here inspect the
ancient Obelisk
why is this a random Quest that you get
when you walk into a
certain blood is the key stand on the
pressure plates to S satiate the
Obelisk uh is this only possible for
people or who
knows is there an
order oh
no oh I have to wait
okay I see and then it stays locked
in
yeah oh my Hydra are still doing their
best from far
away okay am I doing this right
well there's a lot of
fire I like
it very dramatic still a what what am I
doing
[Music]
wrong need to wait for the diamond
symbol to just stand even longer oh my
God yeah okay there's even more mobs
h a
shield you are
immune can't get you there you're so
smart walking into my
UI you are smart
cookie okay round two bring me the no
we're starting from the
beginning oh
no W what was that ah those are my my
blue
skills I see I see these these ones are
for that I
guess okay not a hold yeah there there
was a mix of attacks I I
see left click I I was using left click
but right click I I forgot about what
the life St dancing pretty thank
you did you have fun
on ID
Bros had an MC with
[Applause]
Ina oh I did
it MC with
Ena and I did the
kuo kuo song again I mean with
kall that's always hype because I think
it's really easy to follow along with
the
su su su
su what the hell
who and then oh yeah we did we did a
cover we did some cover songs this
time I think we didn't do any cover
songs last time but this time we did
some cover
songs yeah we
did not
[Music]
wow so it's it's
yellow so yeah a few covers for the unit
songs
perhaps this will happen more often from
now on who knows who
[Music]
knows who why are you so
glowing I couldn't even hit you before
not fair am oh my God why am I tanking
this should I really be tanking oh my
God what is
this how do I pick up these things the
the the pots on the
ground are they just a
mirage ah I have to use one up and then
I can pick them up from the ground I
see by the way is there anything better
than what I
have
[\h__\h] oh whoa hey they even look really
sick I got some rare boots Courier
charge look at those fancy
tips 14 intelligence maximum oh and a
rare
amulet uh wait what's better
uh
ahuh uhhuh my new one is
better this is a legacy item what's
what's with's the Legacy item understand
wait this also
oh Critical
Strike I kind of like the stats more
from the left
[Music]
one but it is supposedly better
so okay wow look at everything looking
so
[Music]
golden outdated stats
H
okay well are we getting there oh yes oh
yes we're going up the fractur
Peaks so when I logged
in uh into this account and went into
the character selection menu I noticed
something that I don't remember maybe
you guys remember
this
um my my there was a character that I
didn't
recognize I was like did I make this
character she's like a lot better uh
leveled than
my
Keandre yeah yeah yeah oh you guys know
do you guys know about it I I feel like
I don't remember her like telling me
but she probably did and I just it's
been so long it's been probably at least
over a
year yeah her account is up there in the
character selection I was
like What if I show
this can't show this now can't show my
character selection anymore because well
H but she must have also not played for
a long time but she was higher leveled
than
me
you level 29 or
so should I sell I should sell okay who
can
buy can somebody Buy in here can you buy
yeah okay okay don't
need uh
wait okay
also don't need this
hopefully is this my weapon my main
weapon yeah don't need don't
need
mhm good price m
mhm mhm
mhmh
MH this is
like
uh wait what's the word
again my legacy items
are not not secondhand uh what's the
word oh I should wear this but my top is
so sexy
but I know you can uh make out make like
armor parts look like others right very
nice yeah I can transmog
them and I was going to say oh my God
that's so expensive oh maybe not wow
wait the helmet's kind of
cool maybe I'll buy
it thanks
okay now it looks kind of
dumb now when something is
like old and fancy and fav
special uh something you find in
secondhand stores what do you call it
again vintage yeah my legacy items were
vintage
antiques what's the heart thing on the
map
ah you you heal me thank you no need I
guess but
than I leveled up yeah what am I going
to do okay time to
think um I could go down here and
activate something down
here we have a firewall inner Flames
metor I'm just going to focus on the
fire attacks summon a meteor that
strikes a Target location dealing 30
damage burning the ground for 11 damage
for yeah okay
cool
cool are
these like right click
attacks I think so right cuz it says
Mana consum
consumption thank you
GD these Skillet trees are not the same
from when I played oh really did it
change might just want to follow a guide
can you guys follow a guide and tell
me they go on the freea this one
really firewall is amazing could spam
them okay a wall of flames are Burns
enimies sure
okay sure okay and now it's on my free
spot okay cool sick do I need to
activate
this there you go
nice okay moving on not wasting too much
time here in The Refuge the bear tribe
Refuge
Refuge I see now why they are called
bear tribes I don't want to attack the
Arctic
bear really to attack me oh I was going
to leave you ah because I'm sure you
have a daughter or son and I don't want
to take his mommy away or dad D I was
going to leave it alive
no I didn't want to do
it I didn't want to hurt
you oh
man oh man oh my God there's more
there's so many wait you can't let you
can't make me fight real
whoa so dramatic can't make me fight
real
animals make me fight
monsters wow Flame for was lamentation
choker perfect for
me incinerate splits into free beams
wait is that an attack each dealing 120
for sorcerer this is perfect for me
legendary OMG why do why do I get that
so
randomly why is the game throwing things
at me so
randomly maybe specking to incinerate
what what
right is that a skill that I can learn
huh
ah my mom wrote me oh you can play with
my character if you want to no I got to
play with
keandra have to continue the story as
keandra
my friends will not recognize me as
another
person woo
firewall
firewall well if my enemies get bothered
by it I will just tell them to try
turning off their
firewall but then then I'll have even
easier access I'll I'll hack
them
hacks am I still going the right way
almost
there thanks for the membership renewal
welcome it's so pretty the game is so
pretty probably could be even prettier I
don't know if I have the graphics on
Max okay we are
here yeah the snow is so pretty Looks So
Soft okay let's go State your business
uh Reverend mother pra expects me mother
open the gates Mother where are you
mother let me enter I haven't been
mothered for a while
Reverend
mother please help me you were good
soldiers worked hard fought
hard drank hard she been waiting a long
time I know I'm sorry I got distracted
by other games
sisters I hope you find peace in these
Flames Veo oh what are you doing here
voice so you
lived I came clean to
prava about taking that woman's
bribe it's looking bad my ass is on the
line might not have a job when she's
done with me hey you're here for her
right let's go together mhm maybe she'll
go easy on me if you're there you think
I have such a soothing effect on people
we'll see
let see if that is true Oh wrong
way ah thank you not many could bear
your
sins thank you for representing
kfp in
Jakarta are you guys at like this after
party or is it already over did you have
fun if you went did you go did you not
go hold she's expecting
us let me in
we go who good luck how does he do that
nobody's here door is open to the
outside magic have the new Watch
Commander replace the forces we lost at
the mine so you've
returned vgo here tells me did you have
fun
today V not no vgo unfollowed me says
vgo is no longer following you V hates
me V why is it phrased like
that V please follow me again I'm very
parasocial it upsets me whenever one
single person unfollows me but like I
mean if if it goes unnoticed then it's
fine but if I notice it then it really
bothers me please follow me
again
please I need a divine blessing to chase
L first you will be made worth worthy of
a blessing a holy war cannot be one with
faithless
troops make no mistake makes this war is
Holy Lilith has brought the Eternal
conf and in narus will deliver us as WR
in Prophecy bless me make me holy until
then we have our parts to play make a
pilgrimage to the alabaster Monastery
cleanse your spirit I am Unholy then we
may discuss a
blessing sorry just thinking of the song
may as well make myself
useful come by the ruins south of here
me you talking to me we go you want
something from me even though you
unfollowed
me no
right uh Quest
complete wait but this was what's the
next oh no he I don't I do think he
meant what he
said
okay you're holy to
me
well I am your
goddess # not
cult you will stay good good choice you
have no choice but let's give you the
illusion of a
[Music]
choice
destroy what is
this
nothing okay up
[Music]
here aim
huh
Hil was it ever an illusion if I always
believe no it's always been
real hold your ground College of light
okay talk to the wander wait what to him
or what no what does he
want there's a shrine west of here here
Bears A Relic I'm told it takes on your
sin weighs you down Body and Soul Beats
the hell out of you it will cleanse you
prepare you to stand before the
father I hope you don't have many
regrets friend this kind of thing is a
lot deadlier for some than others watch
out all right fre I'll find you at the
end freaky
what you not coming with me no I'm not
ready not by a long shot even if I could
survive the trail there's no telling
what would happen in the end you though
you have a solid
chance well
okay I shall do it alone we are playing
solo after all what are these
footsteps oh a hint to go
up it's pretty in here I like this
place oh nice wall painting here with
some
gold books books
books books that I'll never
read hello wander be careful
them off please who fend who
off
oh that's
it are you following me now who oh bats
okay I know that's still very manageable
oh Revenant
what what is a
Revenant now he's a
skeleton had a nice sword though El
squiggle
sword oh a painted
Revenant HRA go get him go get
him your midnight snack
verman
more survive and ah there's there's
several enemy waves okay okay okay y I
hope
uh here if we put a wall there
I hope she can survive cuz that's the
most important and they seem to go for
her make a
wall make a wall make a
wall oh my God that's a lot I will not
fall oh no I have in fear oh no no no
come back come back come back no way I
can't see her
W
move leave her alone it's over
[Music]
you made it that's a little bit uh
scared there for a
moment but all is well the wander I know
I know The
[Music]
Wanderer a rare
wand um I'm using a dagger right now
should I be switching to a
wand maybe
yes I
don't more yeah it's more
damage in any
case but the the dagger was my mother's
knife how can I ever replace
it okay these are
nice my mother's
knife oh no
okay
um what are we done here are you just
going to stay
here can't talk to her let me
investigate the place a little bit
more is
this
oh Mage Clan signant
I mean I see the map is already telling
me to go to another place but is that
really all I had to do in
here that's just an event what the
oh the fight we just had was just an
event I I was confused cuz he did say
something about going West and I was
like this isn't even
West I'm confused but I will just follow
my quest
marker whoa what
the can I set that on
fire no okay wow what is that
though why is there no lore oh one on
one off Zelda has taught me why is this
not
working this is supposed to turn
on I am severely disappointed this is
supposed to make a chest appear or
something H okay I shall be taking my
leave then another one here
too is it a sign
is the
sign
bye okay down
to down the hill why did we go up there
in the first place then if we if that
was just an event and I didn't need to
do
that I guess the pilgrimage just wanted
me to go inside and that was it
yeah give me give me all you
got I love the trails I'm leaving in the
snow damn my feet must be
freezing I don't think I'm wearing
proper shoes for this if you want to
walk through the snow like this for as
how long I am walking through the fixed
snow I really shouldn't be dressed like
this I mean I'm a fire Mage okay I can
warm myself up I guess but those shoes
are not made for a snow and the rest of
my clothes aren't either my elbows are
exposed yeah I need some ski skiing
boots
or
something something more
suitable Relic
what does that do again these things
nothing inhale
what did I
inhale oh
hello yeah walk for the fire wall if you
really want to if you think that that
would be
smart
foolish foolish ambitions
must be put to
rest it let me up okay it won't have to
go
around
berries fight
berries W who
who to the center interact hark creature
of Darkness for you have wandered beyond
the reach of the light lift your sins
breathe deep the cold air the path to
Redemption lies before you if you have
the facei to walk
it oh okay heart creature of Darkness
for you have wandered beyond the reach
of the wait was that the the the pil
part of the P breathe deep the cold air
the path to Redemption lies before you
if you have the Fai to walk it
oh oh why is everything so red what's
going to happen bring me
out the idol of the faithful to the
altar of
martyrdom okay not too far can
do my health is slowly going down
oh must be really
strong is it waste of time to
fight I feel like I
must the trials that are be being put
ahead of me I need to clear
them or else I am not worthy
my HP looks fine
anyway I I keep on thinking like that's
still enemies left on the
field they should retract themselves
when we're done with a
battle
[Applause]
wo
nice now definitely fire Mage is
fun they know how how to make a class
fun with
distraction oh what is that bowl around
you it's a shield how do I break it oh
broken go hydas go
hydras where's my loot you don't have
any good
loot and this is early game already fun
with early game The Sting of your wounds
let the ice into your
bones welcome your pain for the agony of
the flesh is the first cleansing of the
Soul make your faith stronger than any H
is this a
masochist
religion okay
next I will die froze into this mountain
heavens above I can hear the voices of
angels and they are
laughing thank you for the red super
chat
wow thank you thank
you what does it say is it your
[Music]
birthday why does the balloon say
20 or 20 of Super Chat
oh how
20th Super Chat YouTube thinks we need
to celebrate that
so thank you for the
support well this path was
easier what the heck
[Applause]
MH there we are
oh what's going
on Welcome to the membership
yay I hope you will enjoy our monogatari
watch longs look around at the mountains
towering over you feel how small you are
tomorrow we're continuing Embrace
humility accept your place in worship to
the father for he has shown us the
way he knows the
way do you know the way he knows the way
but I also know that
way so guys I V watched
Arcane at the most perfect timing ever
because uh I I think I I started
yesterday and I finished the first
season
already and now I already have the
second season at my disposal and I
already am
through
uh the first episode I definitely
watched of the second
season maybe um
in the middle of the second episode or
so yeah there's a second season it
literally released
today
today what I chose the perfect
[Music]
timing maybe it was smart that I waited
to watch Arcane for so
long cuz if I watched it when it
actually released I would have had to
wait free 3 to four years for the next
season which is a long
time now being able to watch it all in
one go feels really nice cuz it leaves
it it continues exactly where it left
off it's really
really nice to have the immediate
connection yeah so perfect
timing and yes I like it very much
much uh I must say I found the
lesbians they are very gay very very gay
indeed super
gay it is very cute I want to be called
cupcake as
well please call me
cupcake no actually don't
please
don't they're no longer lost
well they were lost until they finally
ke they have to
kiss
wow what the hell jump scared
me no don't run
away holy [\h__\h] scary what is that huge
axe what is that Mama
Mia okay big demon guy very
scary right let me check some stuff here
first
oo Spirit walking
stick uh-huh it has instead of 19 damage
per second it has 38 wait why does it
say minus
one oh because I have to ah because it
takes up both
slots
[Music]
ah both this and
that I don't know that might not be
worth it in that
case you don't use one hand so it's fun
it oh
okay I guess I
don't okay
oh
okay can you call us cupcake no no
you're my chickens are you not happy
with
that 2
five I
mean no I think I prefer my ring
still okay uh let's listen the end near
Pilgrim look into your
cell find your faith feel how it fills
the void within you why remember you are
nothing without faith what even does
that mean hold fast to the light Chicken
in a cup and
remember it's not a cup it's a it's a
bucket bucket
chicken turn
around well so anyway yeah uh definitely
Arcane good show it's very pretty and
it's
I I don't have a problem with 3D
animated shows I mean I I watch Disney
movies the like new on stuff and I'm
sure I watched other 3D animated stuff
before
um but I will say maybe it depends a
little bit uh cuz like I didn't really
like the
style of like horin
Kuni that much to be honest like the the
way it was
animated
so it depends but Arcane is really
pretty I actually really like the art
style and wait what did I forget my idol
I forgot my
idol
sorry UN based on yeah I know H noi is
very popular and I did like I did like
the story and I watched um some of it I
don't think I watched a full thing
but I I think I don't know when it comes
to anime I prefer just the Classic type
of
anything but then it's like okay why
can't that like 3D anime stuff be in the
same category as arcan be seen as that I
don't know it because it's
Japanese I don't
know what's with you guys there's so
many of these
now H must be the idol that I'm
carrying but yeah I really liked it and
um so I never played League of Legends
before but
uh a a
few maybe already in the second episode
like in the beginning they start off as
like small and unrecognizable mostly but
I did realize like pretty soon like oh
wait could this be she calls her
uh I already forgot
powder yeah powder um but could this
turn into a jinx oh wait she has a tiny
little braid on the back of her head
maybe she will become Jinx one day oh
wait this makes sense she's starting to
lose her mind oh I
ah wait there's a jinx in the opening
movie wait a
second and then I
understood that's pretty Epic
[Music]
wow yeah yeah yeah yeah so even as a a
someone who never played the games
before I recognize the characters like
some of them at least and even the guy
that later on gets the hammer he did
feel like somewhat familiar and then
once he got the hammer I was like oh
wait I think I've seen that hammer
before
somewhere yeah yeah I think def so uh I
I was like more and more realizing wait
I've seen these characters cosplayed at
conventions and also VI I think even
before she becomes the adult VI I think
I've seen cosplays of her younger self
too
[Music]
yeah uh the the lady that Jace is making
out with is really hot really pretty I
like the golden accents
good stuff so I like playing cards
doesn't make me a sinner I felt with
that bribe good soldiers died on account
of what I did so bad for Jinx is that
the kind of man I am I kind of always
feel bad for Vine I just damn it I'm
praying why isn't this working also
enfor our girl is super cute made that
makes one of us at least you heard from
pra I will soon but enough about that
you're about to meet father in narus
himself not everyone comes back you know
you'd better I I owe you a stiff
drink yeah um like I understand why
she's going insane and all that she
she's like super schizophrenic I guess
hearing voices around her
and yeah well the problem really is that
she got brainwashed really hard by that
[\h__\h] it's kind of cute how she sees
him as a daddy but then at the same time
it's like girl please come
on but she had so much time to bond with
him at a time where she was really
vulnerable so she gr so attached to
him yeah Sila was a really interesting
character uh but uh what was his
name
uh was was it
Vader
um that was just a
typical de flag Vander death flag
character like obviously he had to die
huh
cuz it was just so set up so so sad oh
man they have the mentor that they all
look up to and are attached to but when
they're growing up they have to like you
know did unattach themselves from him so
he [\h__\h] dies and makes everybody lose
their [\h__\h] mind look at all these
Footsteps in the ground
ah it was so
clear no don't say that quina
Kina you're going to make her feel even
worse but I feel so bad how she how how
she's been like made in such into such
an experiment she's so [\h__\h] up she
might really be lost after that like
Resurrection she she might really be
lost for good but no probably not but
again like I feel like now now that
silico is is gone like she's the the
number one
like big enemy but also ah okay I'm not
going to I'm not going to bring up all
my theories I shouldn't
but
um she's so cute though but she's so
insane and she's like she lost her mind
we need to help her guys we need to fix
her
H but why why so
cool they're all so
[Music]
cool I don't know it's a nice
story and it's like you you constantly
like watching and thinking like oh my
God no misunderstanding no guys just
just talk to each other come on listen
to each other no you must understand
like she she has voices in her head
please give her some time no don't give
up on her no she's like super brainwash
but she's still somewhere there come on
no don't misund understand why she's
there the V isn't there for the blue
stone that's that's the other girl why
is really just here for you don't don't
misunderstand and also no Vice Jinx she
didn't replace you no that's just like
her girlfriend come on but that doesn't
mean that you're not also important you
know you're very important to universe
and she's
here there's
just you watch it and you're like ah
cool misunderstanding
Corner sounds frustrating no it's not
frustrating it's just um keeps you on
your tippy
toes
yeah big misunderstanding Corner they
need to sit down
maybe just talk about
it and this thing was at the first
pilgrimage stop and I was like whoa but
it was there was something on top of it
in the middle here if you
recall you
remember on the first stop of the
pilgrimage
she's giving the the ultimate you mean
at the end of first season you mean when
they were sitting at the table and she
was like me or or Caitlyn but what what
why does she
why that's different different kind of
relationships one is Sister one is
girlfriend don't make her choose
like what do you want you want to be her
sister and girlfriend that won't work
it just kneel before him and remember
you are small wonderfully
small I'm not
small small Wawa not here
today oh hey that guy what's his name
again the
statue inarius
inar is the creator was that really his
name this world is a temporary one we
were born into sin and Corruption on
sanctuary and it is only through the
good works of Father we shall be lifted
to the heavens
above wow
going our father andar has laid down
this ground opened up the sky and
created The Sanctuary from the Bounty of
the world
Stone
oo sounds like a cult to
me o the falling sickness claimed her
childhood but father gave her a new life
the Reverend mother prava is but one of
his many BL oh she's alive because of
him cast down from the heavens but
prophecied to return our father inarius
will Ascend to the heav and on his wings
we will be
redeemed so much
lore oh wow that's
beautiful that's really
nice the father points the way to the
light but the order of the knights
penitent was founded to carve out our
path to it what sorry a little bit more
Arcane though um I really like
how they are very aware that what
they're creating
can make things much much worse if it
goes into the hand of the wrong people
and if you if you use it too lightly and
so they they have this like constant
back and forth uh and I'm glad that
they're resisting so
much but okay at some point it reaches a
point of course
where they will use it
for all kinds of things but
M
yeah but you got to fight the Shimmer
stuff somehow if it's that powerful I at
that point I don't blame them at all for
making use of it of their little magic
thingy I wonder if there'll be more lore
someday about the guy who first showed
Jace that magic in the first place like
who is that and if if like where is he
from why can those people use it so
freely maybe should investigate on that
find out where where the where the Blue
Magic guys from that just teleported
them away in the in the
snow
place Aran rocks have a sad backstory
originally
rise is that the name of the
guy I guess maybe he comes up in League
of Legends
lore Arcane is focused on Z and P
over it's a theory a game
theory the theory is that he is rise
okay that doesn't tell me anything I
guess when played League of Legends you
would
know and now my problem is I want to
play League of
Legends even though I'm sure I would be
[\h__\h] at the game it's difficult
and yeah yeah that is a you guys really
wanted me to watch Arcane this is what
you get my desire to play League of
Legends
now wow it's an angel is how you choose
to approach
me how you dare to approach me forgive
this intrusion but tell me what you need
I could be your angle I must Traverse
the black leg or you dead and that
cannot be done without your
blessing my me and my P if I've learned
anything during my time here it is that
what we're looking for and what we need
are rarely the same things thing there a
jrpg league of legend been I once
thought you could find an end to this
but there has been no resolution only
more
pain everything I've done has pulled me
further from home from the place I need
to
be this world we made was Bor to be
impossible and yet like it creators it
rots from the
inside I I don't understand Lilith has
entered the ancient city with your
blessing I can pursue her
okay but more J your kind are weak and
this world has been wasted on the
Crusades of the Unworthy I can stop
her you sound evil
bro this audience is concluded it's cool
that you can just meet him here here
nice meet and greet place so easy I
thought it would be diff more difficult
to talk to this
guy he's just chilling
here thought maybe I would have have to
pay some money you know expensive meum
greed H have seen a cut scene before
[Music]
no self-absorbed jerk
there's going to be an
MMO play DotA DOTA why
do good game with talko Community good
with friends yeah yeah yeah I'm sure
it's toxic I can imagine I'm
scary I don't know I just um I guess
probably the game wouldn't even give me
what I what I desire
except more like I can actually play
with Jinx I guess but I don't know I
know I know you guys would react like
that but
but
but lore video watch alongs is there
lore videos in the game I can probably
just watch them on
YouTube try it out with gigy yeah maybe
I'll try it out I'll probably be so [\h__\h]
at it and Drop It Anyway don't
worry they are only on YouTube anyway
not in a game oh I
see please
don't why you guys bring up DOTA does
that have League of Legends characters
in it I don't understand the connection
is there a connection
no just because it's a MOA okay but I
wouldn't play League of Legends because
it's a MOA I would play it because of
Arcane I would just accept that it's a
MOA for the sake of it being
Arcane see I've I've immediately been
absolutely consumed
and just
addicted watch the Netflix
show and it's like propaganda to make
people play League of Legends even more
than they already
do it's it's a
curse one that I do not wish upon
anybody else but watch Arcane it's
good yeah good gloves Maybe
oh
pretty we have my little
thingies
exposed oh same item power
no no
intelligence nah I'll keep the current
ones
honestly what about the rest that I have
here ferocious iron St ferocious f f
ferocious iron
stuff
sta
okay yellow orange beige only okay
okay speak with them can
I want to be closer Maybe
[Music]
okay I maybe I should sell some stuff
while I'm
here SK of leather and
steel gently
used good
price good price says
you I'm selling to
you are you gaslighting me
this is really a good price I haven't
really P been paying
attention very
nice
okay Salvage
ah Salvage items to sell to to got the
new
look right I forgot whatever it's okay
we'll find cooler things
still that is just superficial stuff eh
you return for why are you telling me
that I have a oh return because I oh ah
my would would my return portal be here
where I teleported from I forgot that
that's how it works no worries G
game feel free to close
it
[\h__\h] oh there's
more oh my God
wa that Tru that's your
name ow I I like how this game gives you
all kinds of little like random battles
throughout the whole map but they're
also different enemies different
situations so versatile it's such a good
game
honestly good storying good
graphics they should make a Diablo
Netflix
show we need more shows like Arcane like
good shows for good games
agree honestly a Diablo TV show Netflix
show would be so
good so much
potential come on blizzard pay
up yeah I mean there's all I think
generally like surely there's some
Netflix shows where Netflix has kind
of messed
up the premise of a show oh that feel
for me I've been happy
with most like everything
on when it comes to like adaptions or
adaptation what I didn't like of course
is [\h__\h] Emily and Paris worst show
I've ever SE seen in my life you guys
might be uh
surprised cuz I I will be the first one
to tell you that Jo is so [\h__\h]
cringe the only good thing about it is
the outfits I did look up Emily and
Paris outfit several
times to see where I can buy the same
clothes never ended up buying anything
cuz it's always like sold out like hard
to reach but yeah it's such a cringe
show such a wrong depiction of French
people and just cringe cringe cring CR
cringe cringe cringe cringe cringe
cringe cringe cringe
cringe don't understand how it got more
than one
season
inexplicable and you guys make fun of my
taste for TV shows and stuff armor
against the encroaching I have have
standards
and based on
res I do have standards and and and I do
also Rec recognize that like and
like some things that I like I see why
you don't like it and I'm not saying
it's like the best thing ever but I'm
still enjoying it for like what it is
and for other reasons and so on you know
anyway what's going on
here hello ah you've returned yeah while
let us speak inside out of the
cold
what D it you're so
[Music]
mean shut up about rings of power
I understand that it's like that's not
even I just like anything that happens
in that universe and it's not the worst
thing ever it's definitely better than a
show like Emily and
Paris thank you iron
later yeah season two
improved on season one and I understand
that things aren't so accurate and all
that and and that's really like
unfortunate but if you ignore that then
the production value of the show is
pretty
good and it got better in the second
season and I just like anything that you
know plays in that universe so leave me
alone leave me
alone I I I've seen you guys like a
while ago talk about oh you know hiana
just needs to know that it's okay to
like bad
things
bro that's not that's not the right
sentiment in my
opinion because maybe it's bad to
you but it's not bad to
[Music]
me so leave me alone
it's okay to me
wrong yet you stand before me
unscathed I know his
ways that is approval enough for me I
see so I've been blessed by not being
killed I bless you oh thanks May the
light flow through you and keep you from
corruption and
sin our Victory is prophesied in the
heavens wait yeah wait what did it
already start I saw some
footage and heard criticism of that
footage that it was like
unfitting
yeah we were kind of hyped about it but
um not sure
I don't think anybody watch it so wait
so it's
out was this on Amazon right I should
watch it but yeah I've heard things that
it's kind of out of character and like
too too
happy like yippe
yay I guess I mean I don't know I should
watch it to judge it because I feel like
there are some like dorky happy moments
in the Yakuza games that give it the
cont interest between the sad moments
and the darker
moments no I just saw that one clip of
the music playing when they arrive in I
don't know was it
kuko and they're playing like this this
music and the criticism was this just
doesn't
fit the fight corer which you would
assume would be the
high I see
see maybe the writers only saw the side
quest no maybe maybe my impression of
the critiques were not complete
anyway it's generally very
goofy
[Music]
really okay I got to watch it once I'm
done with
Arcane and see what the criticism is
about
I
do I I do have some good knowledge about
Yakuza played a couple games so far
so I'm not completely clueless compared
to like
Arcane where I don't know
anything I've seen I've seen some
characters before but I don't know
anything is any of the Arcane story ever
like this discussed or like hinted like
is there any hints of it in the League
of Legends game or or does the Arcane
Story come as a surprise to League of
Legends players
too H they made it Cannon after the show
oh so it was like completely out of
nowhere and now it's just like okay
that's the story
now
interesting what is this
characters don't really have large
lore where were Vai and Jinx considered
sisters before the show or was even that
not a
thing yes
okay it was hinted it was a theory a
game theory it was a fan
Fury so also not very clearly confirmed
[Music]
H
interesting speak with
no so far are you kidding me I wonder if
I can reach like by walking kind of like
straight towards it but I'm like there
oh my God maybe maybe I should teleport
to youa
[Music]
or at least teleport
here accidentally confirmed that they
they accidentally confirmed
NY damn
must some kind of NDA
fine
afterwards it was obvious that they
scissors how is it obvious their hair
colors are so different
I would more so think that
Caitlyn and Jinx are
sisters but I guess it's not just about
the hair
color did you finish watching I finished
the first season yeah I I began the
second season all of this in the span of
one and a half days or two days maybe
which I I spent a lot of time on on my
bed with my
cat my neck is
stiff cuz I must cuddle and watch it's
difficult it's a difficult balance
ow I felt
that SL the knock back you guys walk
from me leave me alone I'm just passing
through oh there's only three episodes
out so
far oh
no something is stopping me from my
binge
watching how dare they I've been
Unstoppable so far
now it's the
end eat them up Hydra eat them up good
jobn't that
yummy oh so
yummy thank you Keandre for the yummy
snack thank you for feeding us
always you're welcome my
babies is it like
weekly one episode per week or two more
weeks for
everything that's not too bad if it's
two more weeks for everything to be
out free per
ooh ah does it have nine episodes again
I wonder when one piece is
coming
really kind about one pie
well one piece was so
good next season of oh yeah oh my God oh
there's just so many good shows right
now when is it yeah do we know Fallout
just came out this year right so it's
going to take a while but one piece is
going to be this year I'm
sure you don't have to wait for the live
no no no no no the problem is that
there's plenty there's too plenty of One
Piece content out there
I
see but see the Fallout
show wait no I already played Fallout
before Fallout show but the Fallout show
made me want to play Fallout even more
it made me feel even more of like a
motivation and passion it's nice to have
like a little other media to enjoy
boy on the side am I getting it mixed up
really oh I played after okay but I had
plans I always had plans to play Fallout
but watching the show made me really
want to get into a
ASAP mhm but don't play League of
Legends okay but also Witcher Witch is
also one of those cases where I was
thinking of playing it at some point
right
but uh then I watched the show and I'm
like okay now I really want to play
it oh yeah now I'm just waiting for the
new
season pretty
much so long
yeah I'm sure it's a long
game but maybe worth
it but yeah I don't know I don't know if
it's if will be a good stream game for
me long RPGs and it's really depressing
my mom says my mom says nah
it's not good
game oh it's an event don't die oh my
God oh my God I barely saved him bro
what's my
reward talk to me
[Music]
Diamond
fragment very loot very Grim very
[Music]
long it' be a goodish stream game for
you I think because you seem to really
enjoy character driven stuff and which
is very character driven yeah I do and I
also like RPG games in general but this
is a little bit different I guess from
the RPG games I normally play I
guess what's going on
here ah this stuff again okay let's do
it blood blood
blood blood for the blood
C hello
what my God
wa we
done should use my skill point again
also stream fall blood yeah fall blood
reach 4 million and
and goodbye declaration reached to 7
million or
[Music]
SOI oh my God oh my
God oh he's poisoning me but don't I
have to stay up
here I think it's done
though okay I have 30 seconds left for
two more waves you kidding me I'm not
going to make it
if only I could activate them all at
once but they take so much time to even
like spawn the next
[\h__\h] are we done okay please
please raction time what do you
mean bro
oh can I not
retry oh okay ah for Mastery it takes ah
it's only for
Mastery wait that didn't
even that didn't even spawn like the
second wave what the
heck oh well Gus objective
okay no
really thank
you I remember last year for my 3D
live I finally performed it like in 3D
in my members only that that'll be
forever precious you guys should rewatch
that I should rewatch it
[Music]
what this keep sake
M nothing to good I
suppose uh one point by the
way can I still improve something of the
ones that I already
have after critically strike your Hydra
gain 30% Critical Strike chance for 3
second Burns enemies for an additional
100% of its base damage dealt over 6
seconds sure we should improve those
shouldn't
we can I turn off the chat somehow by
the way
at least I'm covering up most of it
but you have it as your
ringtone are you so
sweet you
legit didn't even what I mean nothing
really they're just like can you help me
what do you
mean at least they're not spamming evil
things
I like burning
things I must be I must have some kind
of connection to fire I feel it I feel
something the fire is calling
me
something
special what could it
be what's this
place I know I don't have to go here but
I'm going to check it out I'm going to
chicken it out
hello okay can't really check anything
out abandoned but the light is on let me
in maybe it's l for later for
Quest could be
[Music]
Necromancer no Necromancer is more like
C style come on I can't take that away
from
her neck
romance how about the new class what I'm
committed to my fire Mage now I'm not
going to change now but what's the new
class that sounds interesting
Spirit Ah that's the green green looking
thing that I saw on the
banner Spirit born what does that
do maybe it can bring Spirits with
itself which is probably just like
Necromancer but with green things green
green floaty
things Animal Spirits ah
dead speed lurking
[Music]
now do you ever get
enough I'm so motivated to check out
every single corner but I really
shouldn't
look at my babies look at them
go look at them doing a great job or is
this a
village the Pine
Hill I have
[Music]
found
shelter wow More Strangers in the camp
stranger danger no
I am good
person
Shino try reading the short stories they
wouldn't ruin the show for you since
they were handled well and then make an
informed decision if you want to read
the rest D is best
why do I have to read the
book
why
o but um I might
read
um the first load of the Rings books
book
soon because I'm going on that little
spot trip
remember and I I I have the first book
or like I don't know does I think it's
just the first
book but my
brain I can't read so well I have to
like sometimes most of the time I I try
to read things and then my brain doesn't
register it and I have to read the same
line like five times what's wrong with
me yeah Sparks I'm streaming Sparks
Spar don't stop don't stop just go your
own
way oh yeah I should get the audio
[Music]
book that Sparks was useless
hi Nal what's the plan even more like
that than normal books because of yeah
right it has a difficult writing style
so like how am I how am I going to read
this it's in German though at least I
think I think it was in German was it
I'll explain on the
way yeah I do have an audible
subscription I should I
should you'll explain on the way
[Applause]
What if after your explanation I don't
want to do this anymore but hey wait
isn't this we I was here
before
huh is this a place you have to go in
again or am I was my progress not saved
before we weren't we here before
you think I've done all of this
before I don't know how to open my quest
log okay okay we go here again I
[Music]
see h
uh but I don't know I like the the
thought the idea the visuals of having a
book while I'm relaxing in my
bathrobe on a lounging
chair next to my sister who will
probably be reading something as
well just like I don't have anything to
fiddle with if I just listen to the
audio book
going to start fiddling on my phone
reading social media and stuff and then
I can't really listen to what the
audible is saying to
me
no which is my own fault because I could
just like not fiddle with that but I
need something to fiddle
with Lil showed me the ugly truth of our
Cosmos the Eternal conflict angels and
demons have battled over control of all
creation for all time to what end I
asked and she simply laughed oh what a
[\h__\h] book and yeah I could try do they
do they really say the exact same things
in the audible
versions as what is
written yeah
interesting no he's Reviving stop
it okay what's the right path to the oh
okay over
here rma's description of the ritual was
difficult to understand and the notes
weren't much better wouldn't recomend I
think I know how to talk with my mother
again
why don't know if German AUD book is
good but the English one is amazing H I
would probably prefer to listen to the
English one
too I don't know maybe German can be
good actually for audio books for TV
shows no but for audiobooks I actually I
want to give the German one a chance
maybe
for the sake of my focus as well how
sweet this taste Lili asked me to Aid in
a ritual sacrifice a priest from the
escort he had no fight he just prayed
I'm an audible right now he just prayed
as we made his blood useful forgive my
hand I'm still shaking power dances
along my bones I walk the path of our
maker now I walk the path of our maker
now should I should I read all the
drinks for
you and then get a um
then get
sued get a lawsuit cuz I read it to you
I just want to be your
audible I don't want I don't want to be
your angle anymore I want to be your
audible unarchived reading
stream I'll get
fired coming from the Black
Lake do you feel it no let's hurry this
is just a game I can't feel air until
they figure out how to convey such 40
experiences sorry girl can't feel
it yeah I remember this place this where
her mommy died and there was big ritual
and [\h__\h] yeah it was very
dramatic now we're trying to revive
her it's
working mother mother please can you
hear me my little Magpie it's you I can
save you from this mother I promise I
can learn how to
stop I can't be saved from my own
mistakes this body is only a
husk my spirit must pass
on and you must let me
go mother
no I need you you need to move on my pie
without me but I can help you one last
time before I go
you have the divine
blessing your blood necess
bro is she okay
W NRA you were so
loved
mother Standing Ovation Nel
the way is open we have to
go
but do you think Lilith is even still
here it's been so long if you choose to
be the Necromancer you still have to
learn how to summon her mother Spirit
yeah that's um a gap of logic take care
of my mother but it's not over
yet not for
you theith was after
rosma find him learn
why I'll be back at the Vault all
right wait
so she
Nel had to
learn is that what we've been doing we
taught her how to necromance or
something what
what still my really I'm actually very
interested in a cuz I already watched a
couple of lore videos on
it you can't follow L up so you're
trying to find ways to get
through this chocolate is so good
ow this place is full of Lilith's
[Music]
hatred he's so good he's so good
hello you are the last visitor to my
sanctum though you come too late just as
L did before
you oh my
god ah
holy
[Applause]
[\h__\h] actually making me use
PLS kind of
crazy
bro it's getting difficult Maybe
just raise your Hydra and run on circles
is that what you
do I don't know I like standing around
cuz if I if I keep on like you know
doing this I can't
move but is that the real Strat for
Mages to just bring out their Hydra it
started in
dreams I do anyway of the end of
sanctuary
should have done my class Quest great I
don't even know like where that would
be and so I went to visit
him my and the Serpent's thoughts met
too long in the fragments of future not
aware of what I need to be
doing I need to destroy the tumus to go
any further
Oh e e
mag everything looks like [\h__\h]
insides of some
body oh that already did it on the other
side
okay ew e ew
nothing here but yeah we've been here as
well before we've
already invaded this
far what what the
[\h__\h] what that sound
where do I go destroy path looking the
path
four
four where are the
others I must have missed something
I don't see any tumors
here but maybe
here
okay
oh whoa the music is intense that's
where it came from
yeah the white triangles I get it but
some of them I wasn't able to reach but
here probably yeah one after
another miss that
one
okay now we can go up
[Music]
here
okay those guys did
you watch all the new
debuts of the new
girls yeah I couldn't watch you know
during when it was happening so I just
skimmed oh my God I skimmed through some
of
it they're all
cute one of them has like a really
strong strong strong canai
accent the VII girl the kikil laala
girl I used to speak Kai dialect too
there's still some traces of it there
were others that knew maybe she can
revive my couldn't understand the nature
of such a thing but
yeah they deut
we're partially pretty unhinged that did
was about
him he saw himself the way they
presented themselves piercing hatred
heart and
Hell slightly
concerning but very nice very nice the
blue Kaki girl I can't tell yet if she's
a kusogaki
but she seems to be really into dancing
so maybe she's like the the Bono of her
gen yeah
s she's
cute other than that I don't really know
like the in their in the their debuts
from what I've seen was there
anything
like
common interests or so that they
revealed I don't really I didn't really
see
much I see how I playing the Trump that
was
crazy wait I already did that she played
the freaking trombone there's just
something so funny about someone playing
a
trombone she's really good but she was
nervous right so sometimes she got some
tones wrong and it just sounds so funny
with a trombone when you get a when you
don't play Everything really
confidently the sounds that come out
they're not like d dude anymore they're
like just they're so funny trombone is
so
funny she did such a great job I didn't
expect that at all
crazy how do I get to that one over
there maybe from
above waiting for you to have a
saxophone that would be
Unthinkable that would
be oh my
God ah
oh my God they're [\h__\h] killing
me
bro the hell these
guys oh ah accidentally ah what I
accidentally drank a pot give me back my
pots don't be afraid to run away
[Music]
temporarily I don't want
to I need to Stand My
Ground we get a ho
forra hell yeah
H I think I like
the uh I think I like
ni voice the most like so I locked the
it's kind of unexpected too it was only
a matter of time before Norris would
discover what I've done and come to I
haven't heard the covers but the only
song that seems familiar to me is uh sha
evil days anyway
is she calling her fans niik I saw mik
Sen's tweet something about nias and ni
PE finding it out or
so already locked in with the orange me
too
thank you and you should and you
should finally I got them
all
Yi SL the final tumor of hatred to fully
uncover the exit oh hi you refuse to
give me the
key you stand in the way of the
Savior the holy blood in your veins
should be boiling
I it now nothing you did will change the
future I
saw cat
energy I create my own Destin cat I love
cat all you must understand can't be Den
once I am victorious in Hell the High
Heavens will welcome me home where I
belong okay
C this place you I'm being
followed yeah I heard those steppies
again is that narissa getting in her
steppies she's a demon off the wallet I
wouldn't be surprised if she was
here
oo
nice maybe there is says Lil's daughter
I don't like these steppies those are
some really heavy
steppies narissa did you gain
weight
[Music]
Lam okay I'll try to run around a bit
more this
time I just don't want to waste your
chances
damage but going pretty well oh yeah we
fought this with everybody before here
no maybe not little slamming but we
fought something here on these
Battleground get out of here wa what's
that what the oh I need to go
there oh he's a good bro
oh
wa okay wow going really good going
really good ah ah I'm
coming I remembered how to dodge this y
it oh look at all that loot holy [\h__\h]
wow wow wow
take it take it pyromancy aru argument
argument nice that was a good
fight who are you night penitent Dawning
father's
Grace
wow
oh
reveal hello
nobody inside or just way
lower there you
[Music]
are holy [\h__\h]
V who did this oh my God V all that was
asked the pain is gone now what the
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] this was it just
punishment who put you in there stronger
men with have refused vard's
bribe
Nel Nel is she safe yes she is
[Music]
safe our meeting is no coincidence I
came here to
help will you give this to her for me I
should never have taken it
is so dark I have
repented do you think I was too late no
no not too
late the light has come to carry you
home do you not see it friend yes yes I
see it now they have come
repent for accepting the bribe that left
[Music]
Lilian he a that nar's Mom you didn't
need that armor to prove your worth
friend
interesting resource cost reduction when
hit while not healthy a magical bubble
is summoned around for six
seconds okay sure I'll take it
um
mhm
ah I think I'll keep the current ones
cuz they got intelligence and it feels a
bit more important
oh uh oh no never mind I'm wearing the
orange one which is probably better
yeah
oh this one's
better 221 item power resistance to all
elements and Chad resistance maximum
life vulnerable damage cool cool cool
this also better but no
intelligence but forns and Dodge
chance I'll take that
one I Over You
Blue
oh should I replace
that
yeah need something better up
here
soon
what yeah yeah two slots what keep the
other ones
you mean the wise
ring what do you
mean horns are only useful when you get
hit
uh okay I do also like the
intelligence I could agree with that the
key to hell I will not ask
again no answer you don't need
to I saw a vision of the king lifted
from my corpse under the watchful eyes
of the Great Serpent in my
sanctum if you are chosen the
conversations are so slow it's too quiet
where is
she
hello
liily
do don't scare
me don't jump scare me I'm really bad
with that kind of
stuff is there anything to find
here
no is that him
is that
rathma L's blood
petals
uh-oh
uh-oh so if I find rose petals in my
bathtub later
tonight should I not enter the bathtub
is it is it a present a greeting from
Lil
wow remind the shadow reminds me of
Maleficent I don't know if you would
have chosen that's to stand beside me in
this new
world
RMA but I would have saved your place
just the
same and
now all that you might have
been has been stolen from me who's rfma
again
stolen if evil Li Haw her first
child did we kill him
this key unlocks more than the doors of
hell it unlocks our PA to the
Future a future made possible because of
the price you paid look like she's from
Star
Trek your
sacrifice will not have been in vain
oh core memory unlocked level
[Music]
yipp I can only S one upgrade oh okay
okay
familiar should I should I get him
familiar or is it not
good still haven't uh
chosen actually I could still upgrade
that
too is a good
spell may have up to six familiars
Active at a time seeks enemies and
periodically
explodes sounds pretty
good it replaces the
hydras what I can't have them both out
at the same
time
no no it doesn't one
guy one guy thank God I would have
immediately regret spaghetti
okay interesting wall
painting
whoops speak of wait
what do I have to walk out
again can I not teleport
out T okay thank God but where
K where are we going
where is he bringing
me oh
here probably so maybe I should go here
[Music]
the main quest splits into free P so you
can
choose okay so is this already me
choosing one
path cuz I do see more over here
but those are so far like why would you
go for
those to exit the current
dungeon it a roulette will pop up when I
press e this is what pops
up with di menion
to this
one okay we'll try it next
time it picks up money for
you should get a pet
but I have to be in that City for it
right maybe next time I'll go
there I'm pretty happy with how I've
been picking up everything pretty
efficiently Let
Me Wait if I have my familiar out
outside of the
battle does it just live forever until
it dies oh there it goes It immedately
goes to the enemies
nice okay okay
okay very chaotic but I like it
protection shrine
but didn't I have to be level 30
somebody said I had to be level 30 for a
m
x
free oh wait this region is also we've
been here before too haven't
we feels
familiar you know what else feels for
familiar my
familiar thank you guys for trying to
remind me of the
story I think this once I am forgiven
for not
remembering it's just been so
long and honestly when playing it as a
the collab of the others I'm not
sure was was I really taking in the lore
back then maybe maybe not oops fgo
wanted you to have this now you guys
also for
Gore he was a good
man
seemingly was she even there did you
meet her not really already gone by the
time I vision of
her there is more I can see that Lilith
took a key to hell off rathma's
body then it was all in
vain she's the only one who got what
they wanted got plot armor
Nal she came seeking the haradrim of
Legend seeking hope
she found
neither but her part in things was far
from
over in truth we would need her more
than she needed us didn't seem that way
at the time though her walking enemies
for
anyone inarius proved to be just as
unreliable as I had feared his
self-obsession had driven him to murder
s and from the corpse left behind Lilith
had taken a key to hell oh my god well
would she use
it we could only depend on ourselves to
find out
interesting this voice is oh
extreme complet it I completed Act
One what that's so anti-climatic
it ends like that I thought it would
have like a cut
[Music]
scene it did have a cut scene no I mean
like it uh L is the cut scene you the
cut scene of her walking up the stairs
that's not really a cut scene to me I
meant like a Lilith Vision level cut
scene
[Music]
that wasn't the real cut scene to
me okay
okay uh so is it here where it spit
spits where it
splits I only see two places where I
could
go
um we got to go to SC Glen or you can go
to k is that these
places I'm guessing so scull Glen a yeah
scull Glen dry steppes that's not what
you said but I guess it's
just you're just showing it
wrong or this one place is called
that I'm not trying to wake up right now
upgrade your potions how do I upgrade my
[Music]
potions SC going lead to the mountain
okay kill the shot down the Ser thank
you oh my God we have some really
knowledgeable people in the
chat okay let's the potions and K shot
and then we'll go
towards the next
place and I guess we could do the Pet
Quest is is all the pet does uh pick up
things or does it also
[Music]
fight are you the one find somewhere
else to get warm I was here
first oh maybe inside the house here
[Music]
oh
ver uh Alchemist ver gle's hot what do
you
need here atar Vera not
Alchemist uh
ah
ooh aha it costs 10,000 gold and I have
to be level
20 okay
than appreciate
[Music]
it who are you a
cultist imprinting don't know how this
works
um I'm wondering I in in my stash I had
some little itty bitty diamonds and
stuff I wonder can I use them to put
them into my
armor like these ones oh yeah for sure
for
sure maximum life okay for armor it's
like give Max maximum life let's put
this and maybe willpower into my skirt
skirt can I just
like slot in in like like like just in
this inventory
wait where did they
go where where did they go I can't I
here how does it
[Music]
work
cool cold is this light is there
anything better for jewelry
resistance to all elements oh but that's
diamonds fire resistance poison resist
okay it's just like generally element
resistance and then on the weapon I have
one slot we can have damage over time
Critical Strike damage 12% 50% overpower
damage ultimate
damage uh vulnerable damage basic D
basic damage sounds good too
okay let's put that in there I don't
care and
[Music]
then jewelry H I can always take them
out again right so wait this is also a
gem 250% uh plus 250
armor oh this also has
something 250 armor that's pretty good
no let me put that in there cool I
didn't know you could put that in there
too just go to the jeweler okay I'll put
that in here too I have 500 armor extra
now don't
I
[Music]
yeah
sick okay
sick yeah that's huge from 180 to
[Music]
680 it tells you how much armor you need
for your level to Max
damage as long as you have that you're
pretty
tanky oops it's my keyboard no don't
disconnect okay nice uh and then is the
is this one the the dog
Quest
hello hello is that
it how do you do this ah well now I can
talk who's a good
dog okay
you have received a pet equip your pet
and modify their look in the wardrobe
pets Auto collect gold and materials
while you play interact with your pet
using the hello
emote follow
me why won't you follow
me ah visit the Wardrobe to
equip um
H
wow I'll keep this one right
now cool I'll keep this one hot I don't
even remember transm moring that I think
I just got that for some other reason
where I can change the
color cute
[Music]
cute
cute that's
matching
[Music]
cute cute I like okay where's the
dog where's where's the dog did it say
dog
here
cat acquired the vess Patrick
purchase are you kidding
me look at that that's that's
ni a little tiger it's
N I need to buy the DLC sooner than
expected h
oh okay
bye-bye I have dong why the [\h__\h] cat cat
people are so disadvantaged here why do
they force me to take a dog with me when
there could be a
cat they're gatekeeping the
cats it's so mean I didn't save my
outfit
oops actually it looks pretty
sick damn I look so cool maybe not made
for uh
such a region that is so cold and snowy
but who are
you what are you
doing are you making me jealous because
you have a mount who is
that I'm here to slay yeah but I could
just teleport here what am I
doing inner fire yeah but I'm sure we'll
get out of the snowy region now look at
her wow
slayen okay now this
way should I sell some things though
before I go haven't been
selling bless and thank
you # bless this staff is strong than
mine
but it's blue fine deal we don't like
blue things no
no wait was that bad should I no we
could
probably broken down for ah with symbols
on on the top
right oh ah ah here that one okay
oh that one's a little bit
better but I hope I can soon get a
yellow one so I can put something
inside something with
slots oh are these slightly better too
no because I want the intelligence
what is this magic temper
manual can't be sold anyway
okay
ahuh there's some chance for a Firebolt
protectors to cast tries for Fireball
proor to cast tries metor to deal double
damage use item to unlock a new recipe
okay I'll take a look in a moment very
good thank
you oh I had this already
should I keep
it is this should I keep it for some
reason you should break those items down
at the black breaking down just for
Trans
Morgan and for mats oh right uh
yeah okay
okay uh but like maybe only the the like
valuable looking things or even the blue
ones even
blue
well okay I learned the recipe I don't
know how to do anything with it really
but maybe we'll figure it out sometime
so blacksmith this place has a
blacksmith I think in
here
uh or not
yeah how
work should I just are these are all
good to
[Music]
go wait this ring is good is it really
better than what I CH is level seven
wait
intelligence oh I should switch it out
with the miners but it has a mask on it
the thingy I put that on
there can you take it
out can he take it
out do you get this I get it back when I
S it okay cuz I think
this one's I mean even look at the level
this is oh no never
mind that's the one I wanted to switch
it out with don't mind
me this one's fine this is the one I
wanted to switch out and this one
doesn't have a slot
anyway
okay I'm scared of doing this
wait this
[Music]
one
let's it
hurts oops unlock legendary aspects for
salvaging legendary items or clearing
dungeons the Codex of power will always
contain the most powerful version of
each Salvage legendary item uh-huh press
y to view your current legendary aspects
in the C of power in the collections
menu
why visit the CST to print legendary
aspects onto your equipment
uhuh the potential power of most
legendary aspects increases with higher
difficulty not does anything need repair
no
okay okay that's all I'll
do oh I could also Salvage these
things wait what oh no I think I put
this here because I wasn't high level
enough now I would
be but it's
actually we
no it has it has less damage per second
but some other things are nice but I
should probably get rid of
it oh this one with level 25 might be
good later I don't
know you can imprint a different aspect
on what's I need to still get a feeling
for what an aspect even is
can equip a focus of that one so overall
it could be
[Music]
stronger
uh I don't know it's a too much for my
brain right now I'm just going to move
on
weak I'm wasting my
time I'm on a mission run run run run
run run run run run leave me
alone now I'm just baiting
them CED out accident as if I am gy in
Eden
Eternal n h sometimes I forget that I'm
using W ASD to move now and not
left
click where's
my there you
are I missed
you oh my God where did they come
from 100 cage is close to
completion or some kind of achievement
for killing many enemies or
so
yippee leaving no stone
unturned let find a special ring
underneath
move on space bar what how do you know
what direction you're going
to if you moving via the space
bar what's that at the top right of my
map looks interesting
a
dungeon is it like an extra
dungeon maybe I shouldn't go
now
yeah keep on walking
towards my destination
did you guys
know Destiny and
destination
sound so much
alike
coincidence I think
not you might find your destiny at your
destination or you might find your
destination
at your
destiny no the other way around so it's
better oh the snow is
[Music]
gone uh is that the world boss okay but
anyway this is the place where I was
supposed to go yay I've arrived
GP will it always be raining cuz I don't
like that
[Music]
light's blessing if you have needs check
in with the Watch
Commander over
here hello are you my quest
givers who are you aunti you I'm looking
for aadum named donor an old friend of
his sent me at this hour I'd wager he's
in the keep check with a guard at the
door you talk like me when I make an
accent for
people is it really your accent or is it
fake
accent I could be voice acting this game
oh where am I going they should hire
[Music]
me I totally forgot the story too no
worries we we are relearning
recollecting our memories just like in
Ian
REO Ian REO now in Diablo 4 he's
upstairs in the Great Hall with his son
keep it
quick
okay oh that's the
de looking at the floor mosaic
in honor of the great Horadric Mage
Donan and the brave Druids
AR and nap who vanquished the demon as
of and ended the days of
Ash
not I
agree and I don't understand Dad I need
to be out in the field with the other
Knights Dad I need to be out in the
field with the other you know I I found
some of my old Horadric tones stay here
and we can go through them together I
can take some with I want to play with
my homies a
visitor I want to play games with my
Xbox with my homies I want to
play fortnite this discussion is not
over is there something you need I have
a message from
lorath well there's a name from another
life has the old man finally come down
from the mountain with a
warning an ancient evil walks the land
the demon
Lilith and you know this how did you and
lorth discover something of
Interest perhaps this is all connected
to what you saw
father yes did you I was just getting to
that it looks so there was an incident
at my
estate uh probably best if we discuss it
there mhm go and have a look around for
yourself I'll meet you
shortly and then we can talk
more as for your
request get to brace de and be careful
stay close to the other night's penitent
I will don't
worry too much fortnite
careful okay he wants me to go
here can I go from
here no got to go down okay
you don't think Diablo is in this game
Diablo equals
Lilith
maybe but I'm sure Diablo is in this
game in some
way he comes one of the come what okay
he'll be DLC Diablo in a game called
Diablo
4 Diablo will only
be meetable in a
DLC then you can't call it
Diablo spare some kindness for an old
Soldier no look at those fat birds
now you know why people are mad
nah no way what the hell we got new
enemies we got danger noodles snakes and
some what what the hell was that the
flying stuff those are some f snakes
what have they been feasting on probably
the
birds could eat those
snakes make a snake out of it
could make some nice Sushi snake Sushi
h i mean I don't like sushi but snake
Sushi sounds interesting you think you
could is that is that a thing has
somebody done that
before snake
Sushi
interesting yeah raw snake is that safe
to eat people eat anything raw these
days
snoy
[Music]
snoy that's so
cute welcome to firebreak Manor
travel I'm here about the incident Donan
gave me permission to look
around
incident that was all he
said guys he must be referring to his
study something unsettling transpired
there help
me it's almost end of the week and on
Monday I want to do a stream where I
announced
something but I don't know do you think
it's fine to just do a
normal probably normal gaming
stream and then announce it at the end
of
because I was thinking more of like if I
have wouldn't have done already like
kadas recently then I would have maybe
done a
k yeah I probably should just do a
gaming stream whatever it doesn't really
have to be anything too
special why is I don't want to go down
there it's kind of crazy looking I feel
like I need a mask to go go down
there a playing incription I don't know
I mean it it it should be
something where I can kind of freely
decide when to end it so that I'm not
stuck in the middle of a
inscription
fight
oh why is that here why has Lilith been
here that's the reason why he wanted to
talk here the
incident that is quite an
incident oh look here oh look your w
been out yet on Monday I want to do this
on
Monday I'll think about it but if it's
just a game I can come up
something
easy sorry I didn't get a nap
today been it's been a day
what the
[\h__\h] it's a
mirage no
bro what are you
doing if flesh
curtains what the
heck what this can't
be I know who you are and I I know
you
donut
old
tired each day a struggle to live up to
your own
legacy what do you want with me
asteroth she's dead asteroth cannot die
she s mommy not by your
hand what have you done with him away
demon I deny you you have growned so
stay strong
Soldier stay I can make you the hero
he's so
strong what a beard return to the
darkness from when you came I said away
[Music]
that just gave me reflect reflect Vibes
I had to like think about it where where
I heard that
before return to the a shark is all
you'll ever be that that just I thought
he was singing
reflect a signal
horn who's playing the horn wrong
Melody not playing it
correctly a large to and tile grim wall
of
Ash Ash
catch them catch them
all the pages are filled with or wa
that's not his last name is
it this reminds of Hell's fire demons
one passage is about
as
Satoshi a stack of papers bearing the
title of the fall of ASO it appears to
be an unfinished Chronicle of dlan's
battle against the demon numerous lines
have been crossed out and Rewritten
I keep on thinking it says b and not
[Music]
book what the hell what what why is
there
enemies what happened that's why they
tooted the
horn you're being
attacked sorry sorry about that can't
control myself
sometimes
fine everybody wants to be my
enemy s everybody want to be the
enemy eny
all the
misery everybody want to be my enemy
[Music]
oh the
misery I already knew that song though
way before I watched Arcane now now I
finally
Fon
goatmen they've never dared had come so
close to the estate before Scout man
perhaps they were drawn by Lilith's
presence I saw a vision of how L imagine
drwing yeah they do what do you mean a
vision I don't fully understand how but
it isn't the first
time full of surprises aren't you sorry
no wonder you caught Laura's
attention well now you understand my
predicament the daughter of hatred in my
own
home crazy she must be furious I cast
her
out that painting on your wall who are
the others in it where do you ask Lilith
seemed to leave after seeing them the
fan and
arida The Druids who helped me slay
Estero m i i i saw that yes I think
you're on to something I resisted her so
she might question them about the demon
next there are Knights stationed in
villages near The Druids if Lilith
passed through they must have seen
her surprising with how powerful she
seems to be she can't so
easily
seduce people maybe Donan is just like
extra strong but I thought it would be
an easy quest for her to get people to
do what she wants
H aha
uh so this is the one that was there
before already these are
new these
[Music]
are these are like the two different
people's
locations so
far he rolled a 20 on his w
that's what this act is all about oh
really about resisting the
seduction ah
wayo I wonder if I missed some others
somehow they don't stand out to me when
they're not
glowing I would fall
easily I would be very terrified okay
she's really scary
she's so
scary please mommy don't hurt me I'm
sorry
mommy I'm scared
mommy
mommy well this is
pretty it's still raining but it's kind
of nice this
region danger sake corpse window
F snacks are so
fake they kind of they
kind you know I I recently my
algorithm uh these past couple days has
been recommending
Me a Channel
dad has
like several Millions like free millions
or so subscribers so you guys might know
it but it's some
guy who has a like his own big plot of
land where he keeps a lot of like
rescued animals he rescues them like
crazy ones he's got like
kangaroos he's got yeah Urban Rescue
Ranch yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah he's got like every [\h__\h]
animals he has got he's got copy
buts um it's got like
everything kangaroos are
funny
mhm but uh I don't know why I'm bringing
it
up I'm very confused as to how why when
and how did he start
that but where does he get these from
these
animals where do they come
from but I find this way of filming
funny cuz he does this thing where he
fils what's like he walks around he
films what's in front of him and if you
watch the channel you surely know what I
mean but then he like tries to show
himself a little bit but he like leans
over to the camera front but you can he
only does it for a short moment always
and you only see like small part of his
face that that seems like on purpose to
me because it's so funny somehow how he
always fails to properly properly frame
himself it's chaotic yeah it has chaotic
energy
like he wants to address the camera
directly to say something into the
camera but you you on the very edge of
the frame you see his face for one
second but like only his cheek and a
closeup of his eye or so and then he's
gone again like
bro that's not how you Vlog your face
properly but it's kind of cute how you
do
it yeah it seems to be
a popular Channel with a lot of people
watching what he's up to never heard of
the guy
before yeah 3 million
Subs got some interesting
Antics now he's got these
cats what were they not links they were
um h b Bobcats Bobcats
pretty cute not going to
lie not as cute as smovie and
chers yeah baby b
Kats one one moment that I thought it
was kind of funny is like he was going
through all of his animals checking up
on them and then there's this like water
container this big water container for
some of the animals and he just finds a
random dead squirrel in there
and says oh yeah this is like pretty
much every day I check I check the
container every day and this happens
every once in a
while and then he makes a a a joke
or maybe not a joke and I would
understand if it wasn't a joke because
like if you have so many animals and
then you randomly get a dead animal like
a squl it's easy food he makes a joke
that no this is perfect for this animal
Beast it was probably no joke it sounded
like a joke when he was probably
serious it's locked open
up where do I get the
key damn did I need to bring a
key yeah it's probably not a
joke reasonable honestly a fresh dead
screw
roll on your plot when you have so many
animals who like to eat
meat 10 oal per key I need to bring keys
with me
[Music]
huhy
my everybody I just want to do a Koke
where I sing that song that's all I want
to do starts on archived Koke sings one
song
leaves I'm tempted to do
it actually why has nobody done that
before uned Kad stream titled I just
want to sing one song sings one song and
stream as promised leaves
I guess because usually you want to sing
more than one song but I just want to
sing one song right now I could sing one
song
like 500
times crazy I was crazy
once that would be you
guys if one song can make you
crazy
hello the [\h__\h] after singing it a
million times it's that
song I mean one song only one time
though
hey burn baby
burn I have one skill point where should
we put maybe I'll make my firewall
stronger
almost got Inferno the
ultimate my ulti I have an
ulti you're so
knowledgeable somebody get that man or
woman a freaking
membership unless you only watch t out
unless you only watch when I play Diablo
maybe then has away
[Applause]
[Music]
ears earns ears
earns you going to stream it more yeah
of course I want to finish the story I
want to finish all apps and then I want
to play the DLC with some
girlies yay membership gifts as if I
didn't kind of ask for them yippee
thank
you who are they going
to I watch your other streams too but I
have a softw for Diablo 4 oh really
specifically Diablo 4 or also like
Diablo 2 and so on cuz like most people
prefer like Diablo I the
most and Diablo 4 is like okay pretty
good Diablo 3 sucks right that's like
the general consensus and Diablo 1 also
well well liked from what I
know mhm but everybody hates free
right so the tier list is
two one 4 three or two 4 one
free for most people from what I'm
getting I really like Diablo 2 too even
though I was always too scared to play
it when I was a child
2 one for
free free I like free the most free what
I like free
more wait I don't even did I play I
don't think I played Diablo 3 right
hello
chicken I don't remember it look at
those what the hell hippos or what oh my
God they look so
[Laughter]
shiny they look so funny
are those [\h__\h] hip BS or no wait
they're
pigs I don't know I rarely
see non pink
pigs I mean I would have been a small
hippo I thought it would be so Random to
have a hippo here obviously pigs makes a
lot more
sense why is there [\h__\h] Hipp
here oh
I don't even think they're covered in
mud maybe it's a light too cuz now it
looks a little bit more
brown but the the nose kind of looks
like a horn to me from this angle are
you sure you're not a
hippo I mean look at that
body look at that
bod they look
amazing ah wait I see a red tint
maybe maybe you are
pink but I think black pigs exist though
I think I've seen them
before
right they do they do yeah
yeah
Kudo Peak shaped hippo
no hippo shaped Pig
I guess no I believe it's it's a hippo
to
me who are we going to talk
to I guess I guess I guess we just got
to walk
around you're the Great
[Music]
everybody wants to be my
enemy spare you pick a fine time to
visit bra wonderer maybe that's what
I'll do tomorrow to announce my hearts
are
pounding sweet music for a red day Donan
sent me at least you're not another
night's penitent not tomorrow Monday at
least it is us who will protect this
village with our lives let it
be there is an ominous fog uphill mad
Spirits emerge from it they'll be here
shortly are you here to help us off I
seek a demon who passed
through
so that's what it
was she looks like me more than I look
keep getting better doesn't it the demon
went uphill to Aid's domain but unless
you want to join the
spirits I wouldn't go there why have to
remove the AR best you stay with
us I can lead you to erida out of the
question
I'll be safe Don puts his trust in this
traveler so shall we all trust me bro
tell me when you're ready
to trust me bro mind what looks in the
fog and return as soon as you can Donan
will have my head if anything happens to
you tell me about I do she's a legend
one of The Druids who fought alongside
my father to defeat asteroth
I was raised on stories of her wisdom
and
courage a resume of the new
members you mean new chicken
members you want a resume of them what I
should be getting the resumes the roads
are thick with fog so the fastest route
to the hills is East hopefully we don't
have any spies getting in here in
accidentally got to be careful these
days you
know is there a waypoint
here that I'm not
seeing it won't
no how is sparring and training with
dummies supposed to prepare me for
fighting ghosts you sound so Irish or
Scottish what if they turn me into
one how is sparing training with dummies
supposed to prepare me for fighting
ghosts for fight fighting ghosts what me
one what if they turn me into
one on the
map
ah this
thing I must have really missed some
probably for sure I
[Music]
did okay okay okay keep an eye out for
this sign now in the map wherever I go
wherever I
go you look like someone who seen the
world hope I can do the same one day waa
B bear this [\h__\h] grizly Bear Down
you've seen how he
is blood
keep pleas
s
take
oh I want speed Shrine give me a speed I
want to move I want to zoom
speed oh God is this
Florida snck speed that where where's
the alligators there's rain there's
swamps isn't isn't Florida the land of
the
swamps my God I saw video I saw Florida
man video on my Twitter maybe you guys
saw it too cuz you always see the same
things as CU I do but um it was a video
of a Florida
man he was in some like you know water
with an alligator or or I don't know is
it an alligator or is it a purple I
don't know but he was dragging it out of
the
water holding its mouth open because it
had a little doggy a puppy
inside his own puppy supposedly
apparently and he was trying to get the
puppy out is the puppy Okay because I
need a follow up he he did manage to get
the puppy out but like I can't
imagine it it still looked alive but I
can't imagine that it just like was
completely unscathed after that like
surely the alligator was
already how do you
know how do you know the puppy is okay
are you the Florida the Florida
guy for sure the oh my my God the
alligator already munched a bit on the
puppy like how why would it not it was
small it could have probably eaten it
already you saw a news article on it oh
okay so Flor the puppy it's probably
fine yeah the video is probably old man
they post so
much uh like there's so many reposters
of old meme stuff because people just
want clicks and stuff but then there's
so much [\h__\h]
spam did you guys
see oh what is going
on did you guys see
it the
claim I'm sorry but I I I I that's just
like pure [\h__\h] so I have to bring it
up but the
claim that
Twitter is now more free of spam Bots
and stuff than ever
bro it's the worst it's actually the
[\h__\h] worst it's never been worse what
are you talking about are you trying to
like Gaslight people into thinking so is
it's so apparent it's so obvious there's
so many like every tweet will get a
million replies from random
dudes like uh like it's AI generated
they will like generate a proper reply
according to like sometimes it can
really make you think it's a real reply
until you notice that there's like 50 of
them oh there's just so
many can't believe
it h the
cop the blatant
cop yeah they look too similar that's
how you notice it like if you have too
many of them same
similar replies those are very much
spams where are we
going a bario K up ahead up ahead up
there that's the entrance to the K's
ahead mhm wait why is the passage wait
it looks like I need to speak friends to
enter it's so
bad the B are cling replies and DM DMS
too oh I wouldn't know but I'm sure they
would yeah
H speak French no speak
French we
we that's why I rarely use Twitter no
I've been using Twitter like my whole
life you know that's why it's hard to
let go and it's like you know very
connected to my job now
too
so
yeah I don't think we can just like we
behind it's sealed but there's writing
they look like old Druid rooms wa that
literally the song of wind uh friend uh
what was it again um oh no they're
coming TR speaking
friend all right m
a
[Applause]
[Music]
a there's something coming out of the
waters
the chant will open the
W light protect us hold them off see how
there's
actually oh no this is not
Meo close
enough the army of the
Dead is this Game of Thrones or Lord of
the Rings I think wait Army of the Dead
something like that was a was a thing in
both shows both BL of rings and Game of
Thrones right
game
Rings it's Meo bro I told you what are
you yapping
[Music]
about get it get
it take a while for him to
understand
melon watermelon
shall getting there I believe in
you oh they're getting closer they're
spawning closer to
you oh this is like a boss that's why
he's stronger okay and now he must
die son
suddenly it worked something's rousing
the spirits from their rest we should
make haste within yeah let's go in I'm
SE
[Music]
in don't mind the poison
puddle it's
comfortable let's go finally something
new to explore
cuz those other places
where we've been in
[Music]
before I'm going to get copyright
strike I'm going to get
idid the dead are stirred here as well
you think they'll ID me AR's absence
gives me greater
concern I saw the first called heavy is
the crown is song in the episode they
still use the same song in the opening
yeah but they changed
the the visuals
they'll ask me to do the cover maybe
next time there's something with RI
games maybe maybe next time I can be
part of it to here now that I watched
Arcane only through the stories he told
yeah season 2 is out and all the rest
was dead didn't finish it yet it's only
three episodes I watched the the first
one oh
hey you was that a levo Jenkins moment
for you bro you good coming out there
without your Bros this doesn't seem
right yeah no spoilers that's not
spoilered season 1 I probably spoiled
quite a bit by
now fangirling about it but I couldn't
hold back I don't
care premieres on Twitch what Netflix
what do you mean
I mute every time I hear the word arcan
no wait why the
how arida would not have barred the path
of the Dead like this the spirits should
be free to roam within the Earth the
premiere was aired on Twitch
Lilith
strange the door is locked with an earth
and
seal what was it my father said about
this how's your contract with stones
Netflix if you bring me one from the
nearby K I think I can open the
way open that
way
um W
Stones find and place the missing Ward
Stone within the room ahuh
into that thing but where would it be
can they open this path oh now they're
opening it
okay oh why are you escaping stay here
are you also muting me whenever I sing
that song I hope
not brain rot too
strong well but then you must have had
me muted for like 20
minutes previously or do you not watch
the
did you watch this the first season so
you don't care when it's about the first
season then we should be
good I want to but you too
cute why would you want to mute
me haven't seen to yeah yeah that's
understandable
the show is made uh in like by French
people
right genius genius people
I wonder what else they
made what I could
know do they have some other works that
are
welln yeah by the same studio just music
videos oh and are they by any chance all
like League of Legends music
videos maybe I should hire them for
music I'm sure they're like so [\h__\h]
expensive but what if I just say hello
low budget so please low
effort imagine oh yeah I'm sure they
made all the KDA stuff makes
sense please make FL Wawa please please
uh European discount please thank you
I'm Austrian play
animate me like one of your friend
shows that did it yeah really want to go
God God God God God oh yeah right that
was League of Legends right God God
Gods God God Gods God God gods
[Music]
we're demonic
markings something's written on
[Music]
Yom want you
play sorry sorry sorry too many brain
worms today you just made that one
happen not my fault we could have gone
without it and pain we bear this flame
that must
remain dead eyes stained with Ash and
Ember cursed are we who must
remember ah an elery written by ARA
this this is a memorial to all who died
fighting
asteroth the weak
perish
oh
as forgotten sounds like jinx's voices
in her
head wait we we are not your
enemy enemy
oh the
misery
Lilith she must be bending these Heroes
to her will arida would never stand for
it
unless oh something has happened to her
uhoh we don't know that yet she got
seduced by the mommy
I know it
already
tackle sorry almost died holy [\h__\h] that
shocked me that scared
me I wish I could like uh set that at a
certain percentage you use a pot
automatically can you set that somewhere
face
tank no
no I'm running on H on the heal n no no
don't worri I'm
fine I'm chilling
this must be the K of the
elders so
much
defiled that looks kind of [\h__\h] up
demonic scars upon their grave and Druid
runes to Rouse the
dead what do you think
these
runes the delicate
touch this is arida's
work why would you be aligned with a
demon cuz she's hot I have seen others
fall under Lilith's control gay arida
was sworn to keep the dead at
peace doesn't matter what do we do you
got to do what you got to do oh writings
of I concern ahead not behind as father
says read a letter let me read it
h how do I read
it
huh I'm clicking on it canot actually
properly read
it what would the ancient there go
my people are forgetting the old ways
growing
weaker they look to the cathedral for
safety and protection even for
Faith and yet here I remain in the
shadows watching it all slip
away iita where are you
these
CES are
evil I I I like
the these skulls that are so perfectly
beautifully placed
in the walls with these circles around
them it's kind of nice
decoration kind of cool if it wasn't in
a spooky cave like this actually never
mind that would be even more concerning
but like if it was like made with fake
skulls as a as a spooky
maybe just an accent uh you know it
could look cool if you're like
golf maybe you decorate your house like
that
de be
decoration oh look where we
are
outside didn't expect that what the
hell
why did I but did I accidentally go back
I just bought the fourth anniversary
thank you so much you barely made
it I'm on the right track
okay wait but where are
we not here just got to walk a few
meters and then I'll see what
[Applause]
happens by the way did you hear that
something screaming in Rage ahead can
you tell me if it was left or
right no oh wait it's a above it's in
the
middle never mind
never mind but by the way
ooh the
[Music]
hell I keep on Y is no longer following
no he hates me
too returned to the worms may they find
rest rest in peace
harlo did you think we'd so easily join
the dead lad
how did you find your way up here
through the cares Warcraft direct
through them Mighty Brave of you and
mighty foolish do you I I didn't know
they even do that if they reveal A New
World of Warcraft expansion pack that
would be kind of sick actually to
experience that life but besides that I
don't I don't have so
much 30 year anniversary stuff
I wonder what they would reveal one just
came out oh
H I don't I don't even play the recent
ones anyway
so a remaster of
two do they remaster the old ones like
what like like like the blood elves one
and so
on rumor is Warcraft 2 must ah oh that's
what you mean
I thought you were saying they're going
to remaster two expansion packs makes no
sense
huh what happened Ida came through with
a horned woman not her normal they're
going to their
honeymoon
ah
Lilith they headed towards Solitude the
top of the hill the sound of idus tarp I
carried with the wind and then this
madness began people like the idea is to
follow them you won't get far with all
this fog it seems to be drawn to the
Risen remains we spotted others in the
Hills before this one tore from the
earth the way the I'll stay here and
protect these two um the fog is too near
to are moving there the stones defend
looks like a children's stage I remember
when you were still Al I'm staying
Arlo stubborn light your f
that will keep you
alive Ma how are you doing are you okay
have enough food to last his weeks
sharpen my blade too in case any Spirits
get too close hardcore you taught her
well not so much to learn from someone
like sper the truth is she's the reason
I've lasted so long up here
a
cute okay find and destroy the Risen
remains zero out of
two in that region
okay I shall go here
first I like these houses they're like
so
round beautiful
shape booby house
the blind weapons a the W you attack F
oh wa whoa
party bring me more like it all seems
like bit of a
waste these blessings when there's not
so many enemies actually
more more more more more more
more
yo let's
go I know it was just around the corner
but I looking for
enemies okay well let's go
back it's over here supposed
[Music]
supposely sorry Bros for doing that it's
light blue what is this what is this
indeed
huh even she doesn't know is it in my
bag no what is that
Cy what is this
H how do I open my
quest
[Applause]
oh okay I'm fine
map and then cute
okay sorry kind of stressful right
now kind of busy right
now what even more
oh level up okay but I think this was
the one right
Harvest found a cat sealed by powerful
magic to open it I must slay wildlife in
this area and feed it their Spirit
energy so is this like happening on its
own anyway if I kill
Wildlife suppose
so no they're still dodg but
W forget about it but I didn't forget
about it in that one important
fight ah we've been a Boer
go okay right now I can't go there but
after
oh my
God big tree
guy Wait no that's not the right one
what the
[\h__\h] where's the
obsidian staff
I mean this one's better too
but evocation onus Conquest
onus Beast baton Rune
horror it changes name when I pick oh so
I guess it is this thing
okay I don't have anything to put inside
right now
or do I no I should bring some socket
the bulls with me if they fit into a
different inventory but how come I'm not
finding anyone any
anymore when I had so many from before
weird intelligence Critical Strike nice
okay
cool yeah we have to we'll we'll Salvage
the staff eventually and then we'll get
the gemstone
back gemstone
drop what how did I get them from
salvaging
to press take a
jum
oh oh no it's okay I'm not dead it's not
that urgent
but thanks for reminding
[Music]
me Banshee jumping we should take the
Banshee Banshee jumping maybe then
she'll be in a better mood what do you
think this is pretty fun Imagine banshee
vtu go bun
jumping the jokes right
itself I wouldn't want it to be me
[Music]
first time on a life broadcast
welcome it's so in the middle of the
night for
you what are you
doing staying up so
late I'll now
it oh there it is
the fog is thinning I should check on
your all right did it done that binder
done
that show to
here can I just ignore
them it's absolutely really difficult to
ignore
enemies if you ever want to but at least
it gives us a lot of
[Music]
XP I'm more comfortable playing you
think so compared to the beginning of
today
sure but I'm also kind of
tired I'm probably going to end it soon
anyway to read some super chatos as well
and then make some
dinner got to eat some
food it doesn't feel like I played that
long but it's been 4 hours in 2 minutes
in 1 minute it's 4
hours the roads are clear now we need to
get to braack it's safer there we've
lasted this long and
survived no I'm probably youve fortunate
something better than a girl dinner
[Music]
sorry Arlo if lilth is here you are
still in grave danger because she could
put you into a grave if you're not
careful braack swarming with those
Cathedral
gobshites please Arlo just for now sopis
maybe we should go with him
dad well the a would be
welcome I will deal with aridor and
Lilith see them safely to br tag I shall
do it I will I am the
hero let me rescue you Apex of Misery
all the
misery everybody wants to play
Apex except for
me okay I guess next would be that but
okay okay we'll do we'll do this little
side quest and then
I mean that's a weird point to uh to end
it at maybe
but I want to clear it because it's
making this circle on my
map Wildlife right like these
beers
wa wao wo get into the more
sick uh things that fire
fragments okay wait I'm not getting
anything out of these
though ah is it you guys
a okay these actually count as enemies
too is that what they mean
no how do I harvest the energy am I
doing it
wrong oh wait there we go to run into
these
orbs the works
Town
town oh The Works count too I
think slain oh thought it said slain
minor poor
child what a weird way to put that into
[Music]
words they only show one more on the map
but I still need a lot more oh there we
go now there's more
they heard my
prayers I want more
Wildlife I want to eradicate all
Wildlife
please no more
porcupines even though they're so cute
what do I get for the side quest I
wonder if it will be worth
[Music]
it I need a
respawn give me
more here down here down
here speed Maybe
random gear okay maybe we'll get
something really good always got to
dream
[Music]
big a bit
more they want quite a
lot takes up some
time but it the quest was given to me
against my
will so I need to finish it
almost
there give me big energy please big
Spirit
energy o what's going on
here it is done it is done what have I
received XP and money no
item
no no really
really that thing or did I
receive this grant items on you a yeah
it might be
this wa oh we got these masks and the
sapphire oh where did it
go just fragments Maybe
no mine's better but looks
nice 7 through and
[Music]
okay oh wait this one's maybe better 2
20 n no want
intelligence I don't know maybe I don't
really need intelligence
but I
have made up my mind over it
[Music]
check stats and
materials
[Applause]
attack ahuh
oh this is what I got it was a fragment
so if I get a lot of
fragments uh can be used by the jewel to
craft gems
aha did I do that on stream before I
don't remember that like doing that
going out of my way to do
that oh they added
it was it
changed but it's good that this is not
like filling up my inventory like you
know don't don't have problems like in
Diablo I with like always full inventory
quality of life
baby we love to see it it's so organized
too it goes into its own slots where it
needs to
go
[Music]
yippee intelligence increases skill
damage increases resistance to
MH
MH skill
point
oh Inferno is this the ulti that you
guys were saying you may only select one
ultimate skill wait are there this these
are all ultimates obviously I'm going
for the fire ones pyromancy
baby where did it go had to
activate no space here or what
do I need to clear it
out
maybe maybe it's not a flame
Shield or can I make a second
bar oh it's not that kind of a game
where you can make a second bar no no it
will limit you and that way you have to
make smart decisions
I haven't skilled too much into flame
Shield anyway I think
so so if they say it's an ulti is it
does it have a really long cool
down
perhaps place with
Fireball really
you can talk off other spells
later I want to test it out on somebody
but everything's dead here I wonder
why somebody something some kind of
monster must have ravaged these
L evil I tell you evil is in these lands
nothing good is upon
us only
Doom
[Music]
impending it's a danger noodle who would
have fought oh 40 seconds cool down
maybe that can go lower when I put more
skill points into it
H instead of Fireball really cuz
Fireball I can throw out there like
constantly for now I'll keep it this way
and I'll go back
here and we are going
to
wait I always press B for bag but no
it's I for inventory in this game
M so we want to put something into the
Buton a
Buton let's look in my
stash secret stash don't tell anybody
guys just for your
[Music]
eyes a ultimate damage is for this
Inferno
now h
but I won't use it that much I think I'm
going to put an emerald into
it that's what I want to do so we will
do
it you
put my
intuition
hello that was an emerald
right my intuition I felt that is the
right thing to
Yum Yum Yum
Yum you don't turn blades oh I should I
should Salvage things not sell I do have
a good amount of money now anyway uh
Salvage
[Music]
guy uh wait you you
you go away go away go
away oh no go away
[Music]
going transmog yippe but I'm quite happy
with what I look like now what left you
ask oh was that not good
maybe what still got some good in it
did I get it
back they said I would get it back I
hope that was
true the
stone everything that isn't right yeah
I'm just checking even for the the the
yellow ones I'm just double checking if
it's not like stronger than what I
already
have I mean this might have
been uh this is really close to being
stronger but it's not
M vampire ring 3.5 3. this is supposedly
stronger but no it doesn't have
enough different
variety your crafted gems are in the gem
tab ah you mean she would throw it in
there ah yeah okay the salvaged
ones thank you thank you R rafy for the
membership welcome chicken no egg for
now you are egg m
go water Yum Yum Yum Yum
Yum okay okie
dokie that should be good enough somehow
it really feels like a short amount of
time this game doesn't make or it does
make time pass yeah
fast what do you guys feel does this
feel short to you you it felt short to
me went by fast it's so fast how do we
always feel the same
things we must have some kind of
connection this feels short right I'm so
happy I could bring out my little props
from Blue again so
cute the chicken
thing I actually used hand from that
prop for the lemon thing for the lemon
thumbnail if you recall maybe you can
recognize the hand and I put I cut out
the hand and I put the lemon in into the
hand look Royal yeah but never be
royals
[Music]
Royals orbs your
chicken this it's a Golden Chicken
uh just like in chat we have some golden
chickens it's you guys see can you see
how being golden as a chicken is pretty
cool now can you see it
now
[Music]
H you can become a weapon of Wawa the
Sorceress Wawa the
Mage it's pretty cool
I'm not there yet it's okay you'll get
there excuse me I'm
Christmas I'm glad you're confident
about it
now so we're in act two I wonder how
close I am to finishing act probably
still very
far although you guys did say the Act
One is like the long is it the longest
is it really the longest
tell me knowledgeable
people how long do you think where I am
now since you're so
knowledgeable how long how many streams
do you think I'll I'll need to
do 11 more quests here in act
two act one is long the rest are Crick
oh really
because you have no war points at first
ah yeah yeah yeah yeah have to walk a
lot really depends on your pace I feel
like I was really fast-paced today but
H yeah okay well I don't mind playing
this for a while next week we'll play it
again let me put it in my schedule next
week
Diablo and
uh maybe I should schedule another eat
Eternal stream we don't have anything
scheduled right
now Diablo Holo cure there was something
else I think that I wanted to put
[Music]
somewhere
inscription we continue to stay on the
darker
side so
maybe
H the thing is like tomorrow not
tomorrow Monday Monday is not tomorrow
yet but the announcement I'm doing it on
Monday right but it's not really like I
have
to announce it at a specific time or so
um but I kind of gave myself a Time cap
because I see in the
schedule that uh CC has a like her
birthday stream
planned and a specific time slot and so
I to like end my stream before that and
then that's why I kind of have a a time
pressure I don't have to there's no rule
that says I have to I can overlap if I
want to but I it's her first birthday
you
know so I'm going to try to end my
stream before that so that I don't
know inscription is
like kind of hard
to guess like if I play it how much time
I would want to give it and if like
giving it an exact time frame nah act
two pretty
short I don't know if I should put it
there and Diablo 4 Diablo 4 I can kind
of end whenever I want but it would be
kind of
early in the day and I'm not sure about
that either
M EUR
truck
[Music]
huh good do you guys think I'll struggle
more with the wheel in Euro Truck too
more than with my
keyboard I mean maybe it's fine because
it's just for
fun
okay your truck with wheel with time
limit maybe two hours and then I'll do
the
announcement yeah that's fine that
sounds good depends if you're sing no I
won't be singing in this one I'll just
be driving and learning how to drive
with the
wheel use home 3D model
uh you mean like full body
tracking maybe I'll do
like I don't know
again I can't use that model too often
I'll get bonked if I use it too often
has to be for special
special
[Music]
streams I wonder if I can wear the Mano
gloves
only I need to try it
out if that works CU I don't want to put
on the whole thing
also I'll just be like I don't know
uncomfortable we'll see isn't it isn't
it special if there's announcement nah
it's it's
no no I can't bring it out so
often the stream itself isn't really
special so I mean it is a little bit but
not special enough to excuse another use
of the
model maybe if there's like a little bit
more time between the last time I used
it it's not like they said anything but
I'm like just pre
precautious pre
precautious pre pre pre
precautious you should do girls talk I
can't do it so last
minute that won't
work pre yeah okay
prees let's go to here oh it's been a
while since I was in that room as as you
can
[Music]
see where am
I where am I
[Music]
here
hello H okay we'll do the non closeup
but I want to be there on by the by the
piano why is it not showing
me ah is it
because yeah
okay I'll play piano with
my uh busy hands I'll play it with my
[Laughter]
feet what a pro let me put on some
[Music]
bgm oh use this one
again I like
[Music]
it doesn't even have a piano in
it wait chat can
be a little bit more
[Music]
visible okie dokie
uh I wonder if GD is here because GD was
at the concert and should probably be
sleeping
[Music]
now do we know where we have to
read buil out
okay second Mario Party yeah we don't
always need we don't I'm always happy to
have GD in the chat but I don't want GD
to feel like she has to be
here every single stream every minute to
tell me where to read the super
chats that would be very unfortunate
especially if she like stays because she
feels like I need her to tell me and
then turns out uh uh I'm actually going
to sleep now I'm not going to read super
chats
imagine GD being
like why are you doing this to
me okay so
I can actually probably figure it out
anyway because if I look at Hyer I
see which Super Chat links are used
before yeah the the the second Mario
Party stream there we
go 4m. inart she's 100% asleep where's
the commitment these days
why are you not asleep py you were there
[Music]
too n it's okay I understand it must
have been really you know exhausting too
with so much
hype you're
covering are you doing shifts was she
like ah Psy I'm so tired can you take
over my shift of telling her what super
chats to read I I I'll I'll I'll pick up
back on the shift in the 5 hours okay
and you're like yeah okay
fine I'll do it and now you're
waiting for your shift to
end imagine chickens taking
shifts the aies
D all right let's read the let's read
the super chats let's do it take 47 D I
know
unknown unknown unknown unknown thank
you for all the super chats singing me R
it's in your head be faction thanks for
the pinky nice portal reference than us
Gamers am I
right where where did I do think the
title was a orange must Prevail this
time is that a orange a portal reference
or what when did I make a portal
reference
here is the title referencing portal at
all oh because of
orange there was some orange in
Portal oh Orange versus
blue ref faction I think you like portal
a little bit too much you're reading
portal into things that aren't portal at
all I feel bad now I now I feel like I
need to portal it up some
more If Only They would release it like
a portal free or something like that
wouldn't that be
nice if a portal free
existed then I could portal it up some
more yeah but somebody can't count to
[Music]
free maybe they'll do a portal
125 that's
possible and we'll be like where's the
rest of them what about three and four
[Music]
ter H Cruz D Pokemon d d d General
froggy D
cute cat what are they
doing
Ro happy birthday
Roar super chatting at work don't tell
anyone I'm on launch break hope team
orange wins Mario Party col are was so
fun orange did win in this one
yippee at least I I
did happy Bela birthday they made you
work on your birthday I made you work on
your birthday I'm so
evil but I hope your birthday was fine
anyway I hope at least your co-workers
treated you nicely on that day as you
deserve it you deserve it sorry boss
those up no it's okay you can
you can sleep it's
okay no we found our way don't worry
it's not so difficult to figure it out
myself
anyway you don't have to feel like
obligated I'm worried that you feel
obligated to be at every stream to tell
me what super chats to read what if I
don't end up reading super chats like do
you ever feel like man what did I stay
up for
please sleep it's so late you should
sleep you should sleep go to sleep I'm
not going to stay uh live that much
longer anyway it's good
okay make sure to get good breakfast
later a good Brey my Aussies need some
good
Brey Ty D KX MP dun dun mark p dun diply
but angry d
T star
Creator T time Jackson FB d a stray love
d a troll for fun
D GD D thank
[Music]
you na and coton thanks to the pinky hi
atten I got my froggy merch a couple
days ago and L behold my fan made happy
oh oh got delivered today looking
forward to wrapping my merch at the
Welter
concert let's go you're so ready you're
so
ready exciting you're going to look so
good you're going to look so
fly thank you please show me
pictures if you're not too shy it's okay
if you're shy though you can also censor
your face though I don't mind like when
people censor their faces it's still a
nice look into
[Music]
you know your
swag
ma fancy D rection D invitation
D fire the elements D Unwritten D fire
the elements D Tracy D fire the elements
D thank you a pinky as well and wait
it's a it's kind of a
rainbow thanks for the great collab
today dear wa what a great way to start
my birthday may ask you to sing Happy
Birthday in German oh sure thank you and
I I will keep supporting you happy
birthday to you a while ago but still
congratulations I hope you will be able
to hear this as I
[Music]
sing in
the fire the elements
congratulations I forgot the jam in the
shoe
sometimes it just doesn't work
out
yeah your own Mario Party on your
[Music]
birthday I hope you're healthy I hope
you're happy and I hope you stay healthy
and happy throughout the next
years yeah make the most out of it I
don't know how old you are or became but
good job so
far and Dr loyal
dun fried screw D thank you and then
that's this
one are we dead no I see
you no no you guys seem fine
[Music]
where's the
thumbnail weird why is
[Music]
this I save it somewhere else
I probably
did damn it I deleted it I think
okay good night thank you for
watching there we go hope you guys have
been listening to Pineapple Euro beat
every once in a while or at least once
come
on listen to it Hulan thanks for two
pinkies I've been waiting so long for
this to happen racing games have been
part of my life for over 20 years so
this week I'm eating good racing games
are so underappreciated and under
represented in the V2 sphere it isn't
even funny oh yeah I
mean I wouldn't mind if more people
played racing games rather than
FPS but I I can see why people are not
really choosing to stream it but then
again also we had a lot of fun um
playing it for a little
while so know I'm wor that racing games
aren't for everyone so whenever you
liked it or not uh thank you for bottom
of my from my thank you from the bottom
of my heart for giving it a try means a
lot to me that my comment should Tres
things that I love no I really enjoyed
it um it was just really rough with the
wheel I wanted to be able to do it with
the wheel but I
wasn't
but I mean who doesn't even if people
don't have a license who doesn't love
like driving simulations I don't think
there's anybody who doesn't really like
the idea like the feeling of driving a
car in a simulation where it's not so
serious whether or not you're really
driving properly or so I feel like
everybody has fun with
that I used to like it as a younger
child
too in the arcades especially so
you guys what are you saying you have to
love it what are you
saying my wheel was being too sensitive
you think so I think my my my gas paddle
and stuff like that was just
yeah a lot easier to control on the
controller and also the joystick easier
to turn
[Music]
enjoy the occasional racing
game same me too so yeah I did enjoy it
hello chunky chunky wony saying hello to
you
H
oh you want strings of power why are you
telling me well I think you did say that
it was okay thank you Hulan for the big
super chat I appreciate it I'm glad you
enjoyed the
[Music]
arc finish first season today oh okay
well but I did say like first season you
know is
questionable for many people probably
you know what are your thoughts
write it down tell me now okay second
season your watch yeah good take a 47 D
zly but angry D onion and D K thanks for
the pinky had a super stressful day so
I'm looking forward to unwind watching
my favorite Speed Demon burn some
rubber I definitely burned a lot of uh
wheel rubber because I was destroying
the wheels
when I was using the
wheel and Yokohama
Yokohama now I connect negative feelings
of Yokohama it's too bad because I
really like yokoh
before thank you though Kono I hope your
days were better afterwards you shall
not have any more stress no no no no no
no
[Music]
[\h__\h] youf epic manful
action big blue boy
h
g Black penguin n
swag Tanaka
[Music]
Del
H what do you mean you want what I
want camera than R
fre scientists
scientists
there you don't want to
no Buckaroo holiday Dark Soul Dragon nun
and common rider dun USS anime NCC dun
[Music]
for the pinky hi attentio today is my
birthday so I'm sending you a
celebration Pinky the highlight of the
Year for me was seeing you on stage in
New York here's another year of fun
streams and awesome classes oh my God
you were there too let's go
W I'm so happy for you happy happy happy
birthday happy birthday to you happy
birthday in your shoe happy birthday in
your pants too happy birthday
[Music]
bro a
man a man breaking dimension
[Music]
special
memories so
[Music]
this
sorry I see smooy walking
around they slept so much all day
because I've been
like making them lazy cuz I've been I've
been
lazy this yesterday
my cats are
too too lazy they're always lazy she
feels it going to end soon yeah she
[Music]
might she
knows she feels it in Her
Bones Ender
d uh no didn't have the DLC matric
Matrix tun murf laser tun
[Music]
we do influence each
other Mary Pippin thanks for the pinky
oh hey just noticed it's my
birthday it's 4:00 a.m. but I'm always
happy to be spending time with you like
this great improvements by the way
especially for the last run good luck in
the actual race thank you it was
definitely better with the
controller 4
a.m. on your birthday you decide to just
not sleep
but instead stay up for the Wawa thank
you so much I hope it was worth
[Music]
it and I hope your birthday was nice
happy birthday to you happy birthday in
your shoe happy birthday in your pants
to happy birthday Mary
Pippin yeah yeah yeah
yay I hope it was a wonderful
birthday yow
you only deserve the best
birthdays Leon scape D action it D Elie
Lain D and Chase Hunter
D no more tilt
controls except maybe on
Monday you're truck you a truck
[Music]
spofy is entering the room slowly she's
sneaking up on
[Music]
me she's going to her spot on the gas
bed she she she's like she found a comfy
spot she made um a in the blankets
before now she's contemplating for a
moment is she going to become snail yes
yes oh yes she's sitting
down she's fluffy she's cleaning herself
now oh good
baby yeah it's a little smoothy
Nest so cute I'm going to
die okay these are the last ones I'm
going to read
today play by
play Jacob
py step sings Thank You 4
a.m. spank time thanks for the red super
chat wow I would have
won won
what ah you mean the the race if it
would have happened no but I think I
would have done pretty
well um because I did practice quite a
bit with the controller behind the
scenes
[Music]
too and then when I was just a little
bit racing against the
others it felt pretty decent but as I
said before if the race ever does happen
someday then everybody will have more
practice time in total so maybe then I
wouldn't be so good
[Music]
anymore people might have more time next
time cuz some people barely practice cuz
they didn't have
time uh that could have been my
advantage
[Music]
but but then I can also practice more
right but I feel like I I there's just
like a limit of goodness that I can
reach I just I just like everybody can
reach that level
probably and some people can go past it
but I I just can't really go past it
probably so if people get any more good
than that we might have a problem
no I can't go further
Beyond just
[Music]
ceiling no no no whatever we'll see
we'll see at this rate I don't know I
kind of doubt that they're ever going to
set it up now that the merch is out
there I I don't think it's the
Management's priority to still get the
competition
[Music]
going they have a lot of other things on
their plate after
all but we could do it on the talent
side but still but yeah right we can't
really because the server has to be set
up
H and then I would be really pissed if
the servers
are like killed again at the time when
we do want to do it again so whatever
maybe it's better if it doesn't happen
Che 47 D soon SP time K fpp fpp Kell PP
I don't know why I add up F there thank
you D glad you enjoyed
Austria
Sean thank
you Choice
voicer
similar this is also on the switch H
thank you for the red chat this is for
your new phone my new
phone did I talk about wanting a new
phone oh it's because I was talking
about my issues with the yeah I don't
know I don't think I'll need a new phone
for it but maybe I should buy a new
phone no I want to wait it out even
though oh hi chunky won who just jumped
up on my table like that how dare you be
so fluffy in front of my face covering
up the camera completely
mhm yeah she's lying down so now the
camera sees me
again why are you girls
here smooy already looks like she's
falling asleep chunky
wonky wants
pets they want me they want me so bad as
gigy likes to
say let me pick you up going to give you
a hug
even though you don't like
[Music]
that you're baby you're such a baby
she's such a
[Music]
baby you she is your baby she she must
be your baby I think she's a baby yeah
you baby
you think you're a baby you must be a
baby yeah you're my
[Music]
baby would you you going to go now you
going to run away to the guest bed oh no
you want to stay on the table are you
sure I'm going to annoy you if you're
here just like how you annoying me are
you going to lay your head on my mixer
again oh
no oh yeah she disconnects my keyboard
when she lies there cuz she's lying on
the keyboard
cable the weight the keyboard cable
can't handle the weight of the
chunker baby
so thank you somehow you summoned my cat
Amazing Magic Fish
fgh thank
you Jojo's World D JoJo's World D um the
eigh king for the pinky I want to
compare something can you say the
following Kiki I have a heart is a big
burden Cali it's for science
did you purposefully misspell
[Music]
kikiki k a heavy heart is a burden
C is that how you want me to say it what
is this for
oh that's what Liz said to make a
impression of me
oh a heavy heart is a big burden Callie
here I say it I set it a bit more in
character I
see motion
d d tiny Delta D mental Jelly D thank
you
wow
wow already spent 1K on Sixth Fest I
hope you get the
ticket Dr Professor d
[Music]
sorry move my microphone Loi D happy
birthday
congratulations every de
[Music]
D thank
you Z the post game marks heart pie and
po
whoa is that so Jackson FB D the gamer
crate thanks for the pinky also a
birthday so many birthday super
chats and I what it's your birthday too
oza happy birthday usza you'll get your
proper reply later just like everybody
else gets their birthday reply later
much later can't be treating people
differently
now uh the gamer cre says it's my
birthday today yippee and I couldn't
have asked for a better way to celebrate
it then spending my time here with my
fellow fluffy chickens and fluffy
junkers by the way
and listening to our beloved C oi making
all of the cutest noises you could ever
imagine yeah that was a a fun game a fun
oneoff game I'm glad you liked the
stream for your
birthday
[Music]
congratulations ah [\h__\h] I can't type cuz
you disconnected my keyboard chunky
[Music]
wonky
ah I feel like I heard this
[Music]
before bro no iian Happy Birthday song
is a little bit too complicated don't
you
think I was going to sing it in
Norwegian for you is there a simpler
version of this
[Music]
okay
oh will be
[Music]
what she's covering the lyrics I can't
even read them
[Music]
on there you go whatever that's fine
that was good
enough that was good enough Tred to copy
what she was
singing Holy Moly that's quite the
birthday song don't you have something
more simple and
repetitive you didn't even ask me to s
in Norwegian for you but I I did it
anyway you must appreciate it it was
perfect no it
wasn't no not
really
what Norwegians don't want their
birthday song to be such an easy
challenge no no they want this to be
only singable by nor fellow
Norwegians
hm it's like region locked Birthday
song region locked Gat keeped gate kept
gatekeep girl boss
whatever I tried happy
birthday sorry sorry for screaming junky
sorry sorry sorry
sorry
yes Sky
[Music]
B Cruz than green bird green
bird
and
[Music]
baby she meowed while yawning I can't
delete the thumbnail cuz you deactivated
my
keyboard no give me my keyboard back
give me my keyboard
back there it is
no they weren't because of chunky Wy
chunky Wy did nothing wrong leave chunky
wony alone now it's her fault but not
[Music]
before she showed me her belly she
turned around and opened up her belly
for me
she's getting a massage
[Music]
you're a baby you're such a
baby go baby
what
[Music]
you
we could go on
forever trust me
she never
stops
you even if you're bunny kicking me you
never
stop
okay took the microphone away from her
she has too much power over
everybody Monday per
stream that would be just too much my
kind of stream it would be too
selfish it's so healing
yeah I'm glad you guys appreciate you
have been conditioned to appreciate
that I have I have made I have forced
you I have raised you to appreciate cats
you can still hear her yeah she's still
there purring just further away from the
microphone
she will never stop puring she's a baby
you're my
baby oh no don't try to eat my mixer
things okay no no Nom
Nom she tried to num nom my one of my
like knobs my volume knobs
today
cheeky I can't stop like fluffing her up
and squeezing
we're like the perfect Duo she can never
stop purring I can never stop touching
her volume Nubs not if she numb NBS the
volume Nubs maybe her purs will become
even louder maybe she wants her purse to
be heard even
louder maybe she's like Turn Me Up turn
my sound up I want to be heard people
need to hear my purs I'm not purring for
nothing here I'm working so hard purring
all day every day and yet I'm not being
heard I want my words to be
heard oh she's so her
tummy I need to touch her tummy
I got to I got to end
it I'm
unstoppable
okay sorry tomorrow members
only the first the last three episodes
of Ki mon make sure to prep
that and we're going to start the second
season
of maybe we'll be able to watch it also
just prepare
everything the last
fre and the whole second season of
[Music]
yep my throat and mouth feels really
tired so let me excuse myself
and
byebye you'll nominate me again for the
video I saw that happening yeah it's
happening again you can nominate me go
nominate me guys
H I want to win an
[Music]
award yeah I guess it's the the one that
fillian is
organizing again
right there's a vtu Awards Twitter
account if you look that
up um there's probably a link there to
go to the voting
German
representation okay bye bye hope do see
you or me byebye thank you for
[Music]
watching your outfits this year ah is
that about like having the nicest
outfits Miss
vtuber could be me
m
[Music]
a