[Music]
for
e e
[Music]
I'm go
hello we back we're still all five of
us let's
go chipkin are a little loud oh yeah
yeah I I made us a lot of chickens but I
needed it for the arrows and for food oh
true true
yeah I want to give you guys a tour of
what happened but okay yeah Kar did a
lot of [\h__\h] apparently can I escape from
the chicken pan it's kind of loud in
here oh oh get out of there get out of
there save they're aggressive chickens
they eat people now free them free them
I'm free how could you do that to them
chicken c chicken cop now in where there
were villagers before uh feel free to
you know deal with the chickens however
you
like Kill Them All
[Music]
hello
hiep hello scared
me wait come with
me as soon as my mouse starts working
I'll be right there K I ordered a new
one it's coming
today house
it's for future villagers
o blue and yellow it work oh wait it's
really pretty in
here come call
there's even a little I'm not going to
miss out a breakfast's literally so many
pandas what's in the bowls I think it's
oatmeal it looks like the yum
yums Grandma's oatmeal don't say
[Laughter]
it cool oh hello poke you like it like
coffee with your
oatmeal ooh I already have some I got my
morning
shot so real Annoying you can see we
have beds now because we found a sheep
we got sheep a single sheep a single
sheep can it like it's over here
mosis we have about
eight it's important we have to I need
each one of the Gold Line I
needit Harvest our meat G no no I'm re
can we I'm not asking permission I'm
just saying can
[Music]
we no yeah in terms of food no
impossible can I harvest these now yeah
of course the chest above has seeds if
you need more if you want to Pro oh wait
smart
B oh my god did you think of that or did
your chat think of that I thought of it
I know wo smart did your neck hurt from
holding on to that massive brain
yeah seriously though true true though
true wow wow
wow she's to and if you remember the old
I mean it's still the same myth house
but it has our colors now in terms of
beds and some more decorations oh I want
to see did you put my bed next to
sleep you don't want why did you no we
can no it's fine I fine I understand no
it's fine you got a corner pillow
yeah I got wait I got double pillows oh
no I'm fine with this I'm good with this
double
pillows what else did you make
K oh yeah if you go let's let's go
behind the um chicken house I have
something to show you I can't believe my
little Merchant pen became a chicken
house the chicken po oh
big in yet but we can go in today cool
don't we need some golden stuff though
good thing we saved all that gold right
I'll check that chest over here dang it
you already did it all right that's fine
all right that's okay we're fine we're
fine chest there's also the Eyes of
Ender that we need yeah turns out we
already had enough of the Enderman eyes
so I just made pearls I made some eyes
out of them so yeah yeah that's good
that's like the most important stuff I
did and decorating here and
there yay very nice very busy rain is
popping off rain is always super loud in
Minecraft oh my uh shaders aren't hold
on a sec let me get my shaders popping
off cuz I got shaders
Lads shaders shaders
oh do you want to know why you are a
genius without knowing it huh uh I was
like I was mining my own business yeah
yeah yeah um and then a creeper popped
up a creeper spawned right and because
you're so close to it automatically it
it goes off right I stepped back but it
went like and then bam and it exploded
in this whole construction that you made
and I was like y b it's going to all be
destroyed but the water took the
explosive
and therefore nothing exped
science okay it's as if it was on
purpose thank you Mr White yes
definitely
totally she's a scientist and she
doesn't even scientist all right I'll do
a little more
organizing I'm I'm kind of stuck what
the hell I can't get to organize all the
chest for us that's very cool of her
that she does that oh you're doing that
yeah I am take take this take all of
this then thank you oh my God yeah
you're welcome I to please I can't C on
some of these things I live to please oh
why can I
not why we going into The Nether I don't
want to go in I'm stuck we need we need
armor and stuff shut the
up wait what what do we do what what's
going on she be she be the weather down
F the weather to shut a pie is dead no
somebody down oh
no wait get a is there a trap door oh is
she
fine Stop opening it leave it
[Music]
open no I I think wait am I like
crouching but I keep on pressing to like
release it you got to come out this
way somehow I leg cannot move that way
oh thank you thank you Freedom y Yahoo
yeah in terms of armor um we don't have
that much iron I don't think we're going
to be that lucky I want to dismiss we
have a bunch of we have a ton of
emeralds um oh we have a block of iron
why not crack that bad boy open here
I'll crack that even then I don't think
we'll all have full iron armor but we
can we can like partially get dressed up
mhm sounds good to me is it still better
to have we don't have iron but we have
diamond
putting on the diamond armor now and
then dying in the nether true that's
going to be me don't give me
any 27 diamonds from a block of diamond
here so now we have over 64 we have 68
diamonds not bad Lads not bad oh okay 68
diamonds all right yeah 68 diamonds sick
mhm wait how many 68 diamonds holy moly
we we have a fat stack of them but I
mean I think it is a good idea to save
for later we're
rich rich nice money money we have more
diamonds than
iron ah yeah that really doesn't seem to
it's because I I used uh most of the
iron to make an
anvil oh that'll do it and tools we've
been making a lot of iron pickaxes true
okay but those are necess those are very
necessary they are they
are but yeah that's how it's been going
so um the the thing is we have already
enough enough Ender eye thingies uh to
open our portal so we're not going into
the never to really get Enderman or
Blaze anything we already have all all
we need but we're just going in for fun
and we can get more NE warts and blaze
rods because with that we could make
more potions that would definitely help
us wa what if we die though are we
risking losing
resources uh if we die there we drop the
stuff right risk of death that's true
just don't die in the maguma just don't
die just don't die oh should we bring
some should we bring some gold so we can
trade with the pigment that might be a
good idea was thinking that might be fun
but I looked at a sheet of like
percentage of what you can get and it's
like going to be such a waste we could
use the gold for Golden apples that
would make more sense in the end some we
have a lot yeah is what I was thinking
wowbo oh I made the W yeah that's pretty
cool that's cool K that's cool I want to
enchant something oh that was the bow
that was enchanted but broken but I
fixed it with the Anvil yeah I named it
wowo w
wow we're going to need F falling for
later if you die in the ne you should
receive a punishment oh good a
punishment sure can a one of for
endangering the team's
resources yeah what is said punishment
we should make um we should make a
diamond sword with a power three
enchantment oh go okay okay yeah we can
share it I think we should at least
bring a bow and some arrows so that we
can take care of guests I got good bow
and I got some arrows I have an idea use
infinite arrows if you die in the nether
you have to be slain on stream for Shame
by the Power Three diamond sword that's
a that's a good idea you die double you
die in the nether you die in real life
exactly in Minecraft SL for shame
Minecraft is real life in front of
everyone here people are saying that
power is for bow what if we just did an
Infinity enchantment on one of the bows
instead do do we have Infinity we do we
have do we have LEL
question that's excellent question can't
make a diamond bow right that's not
possible Infinity do s nice though cuz
we do have limited bow or Arrow
resources yeah why not both not maybe if
we keep digging we'll get um well it
would take a while anyways to level up
like a villager right that had the right
stuff yeah
could sleeping Edge though sleeping Ed a
sword enchantment yeah yeah yeah it
gives you like kind of an AOE a little
bit like a bigger bigger and there's
looting too if you want to get more
stuff with the Looting is always yeah go
for it go for it but we need ask what
everybody's listening
toet Sound of Silence
nothing nothing where where' the music
box go Minecraft bra I moved the music
box to the house because people told me
that parrots would dance to the music
and then I tested it out but it didn't
actually work even when I removed them
from the bed wait I want to see no no I
think it's like a newer version Oh wait
now it's dancing it's
in he
Dancing Yeah okay where'd he go oh he's
outside oh my God oh my God oh my God oh
my God
oh your own one oh
yeah like let them dance bring him into
the
disco dance
bird
cute your doesn't want to dance what's
wrong with do
something poke him with a stick do it
may maybe this tuna is just not it maybe
maybe different more exp to tune boogie
boogie oh yeah
he's doing created the Bodacious
bow arrows he wants to escape he wants
out so bad oh God okay a not quite his
Tempo not quite his Tempo let's try it
out
oh oh it does shoot Infinity let's go
awesome audacious bow bow should we take
that into The Nether though cuz we need
that for the end what if we lose it yeah
maybe not we'll store it in the weapons
chest important weapons at least bring
one bow and a couple of arrows though
for the gas I I got one bow and a couple
of arrows I think I think we should at
least have like
Stone weapons at the
very
definitely what about what about should
we do one piece of diamond armor per
person maybe maybe I mean as long as you
don't fall to Lava it should be fine cuz
it'll just drop whatever you're wearing
and stuff so
I'm so I got gold helmets for everybody
so let's do I don't know maybe the chest
piece
Diamond good idea okay I'll just make
some
Stone I'll make a ton of good weapons
for the end okay I'm going to make the
chest plates for all five of us so don't
don't take diamonds okie dokie oh uh
right before the stream I I I ate uh
some stuff that was sitting out for like
uh maybe almost 12 hours and now
I why do you
do what what was it a
snack oh no was it it was just a it was
just a single rice cake oh that's
probably fine but I mean oh
okay how do you say it
toi yeah oh okay maybe it's fine it
should we like meat or dairy right um it
had meat in the you in the
broth you're going to be fun you'll be
fine wait
[Music]
wait thank you I won't die I
promise I might die I might die I'll do
I'll do my best I'll do my best
okay everybody's got a piece I guess I
should make
some rainbow of Friendship with myth
it's a big ring the music is kind of
loud
now should make some pickaxes
too oh yeah mhm I have an iron one I
still think iron pickaxes are the best I
think we for normal mining we can use
the stone ones but if there's like a
resource like gold or something we can
use the iron one
[Music]
nice everybody gets a stone picka you
get a stone pickaxe you get pick I I
already have an iron pickax so I'm good
enough
food oh this is so exciting like we're
going on the
field y oh my God field trip so what do
we need from the nether by the way poti
nothing we going just going die
yeah normally there would be things that
we could use uh from there but we
already have everything thanks to mining
endlessly
so for is there like an inre chance of
diamonds or no no diamonds but we can
get more
gold golden app and we can get ne wart
which is a little little plant which out
of that we could make portions to help
us resist the dragon that we're going to
fight feel good what if we make we can
get blaze rods what if we make a portal
inside the nether does it go anywhere
like
if oh usually yeah you make one and it
goes further but I I feel like they
would have blocked it for this mod I'm
not too sure I'm going to bring some
obsidian to experiment okay there's a
fire charges in in the cool things chest
if you need the fire charge for the cool
things chest I'm sorry where the
obsidian chest
is right here oh
okay oh wait oh we don't have we don't
have sugar cane do we no fish no we
don't ow ow that might be something we
need cuz if we had sugar we could make a
lot of pumpkin pies that would be
nice Yum Yum Yum Yum nice idea wait fire
charge is that what I'm getting uh yeah
yeah yeah to zap it on it's only one
time used though okay okay I brought an
extra just in
case more iron more IR oh there's fish
in
herey fyy
fyy we're going to need more chests so
many materials oh I guess we shouldn't
do
that this is why your boy wanted a trash
can
listen we just have so many things
there's a lot of stuff in
here make sure you Oran is it properly
just because we have a chance to die I
think going in with half armor is going
to be okay we can help each other to not
die protect each
other
the so when that big floating jellyfish
man dude guy comes like shooting balls
at you and stuff like that you're
supposed to hit it back with a sword or
do you slay him with a bow and arrow oh
there's another bow here with infinity
Bodacious bow oh yeah I put that in
there that's oh that's that's okay okay
yeah it's just I'm making a bunch of
weapons to get us ready for the end so
we'll use it then just a Bodacious bow
yeah someone can use the Bodacious bow
when we fight the Ender Dragon what does
that mean Bodacious bow oh bod should we
at least make a shield oh the P there
Panda's fre is like I don't know if it's
a new panda
panda we should at least Pi a shield if
we can Shield oh yeah Shield would be a
good idea we should make Shields
it's like it's just one iron purse so it
should be
okay hi I'll make shields for
everyone okay
T yeah by the way K Bodacious means nice
body just wanted to Bodacious B dunk all
right then I should know what it means I
just
said here's your
Shield thank
you go here's your Shield Bo I up can be
excellent admirable or attractive yeah I
guess it is
good nice Dictionary look up
there here's your
Shield I see my pant before I go make a
baby make a baby W's make a baby make a
baby why you double shielding AO
oh it's like the anime with the with the
shield I didn't know you could do that
damn let's go okay I'm having murderous
try harder make
taking our
resources we could use that for
something but the pants are eating them
the bamb boot must is this urg to murder
what it's just a b bamboo look how cute
they are
Banda I love Banda that's for morale
boost all right we need that we're going
into The Nether to die can we even ride
on our backs like what if we could we
ride on them into the nether like that
be cool me me no no they're just
cute that's their purpose they whole
purpose oh all right my OBS died for a
second let's go
hooray come on OBS I'm make one more
stone pickaxe go mine has also been
dying OBS what's wrong with you is it
OBS or YouTube side OBS is drunk for me
right now that was obs CU often it's
also
YouTube need some sticks then we can go
I'm pretty
sure guess what I'm making after the
stream wait guess what I'm making um I'm
going to make a chocolate chip Skillet
cookie SS kind of Y what's the skillet
part that sounds like a like a steak
thing it's like a it's like a a a like a
cast iron thick heavy bottom pan pot
thing yeah put the cookie dough in and
bake it that way and then you put ice
cream on
topi puki we're we're invited
right no it's single serving
sorry that's mess up you can't just tell
us about to say you can't have
[Music]
any dough in so that it fills up the
whole Skillet like a pancake or yeah oh
it's like it's like a cake kind of what
you're making yeah little bit
yummy yeah that's a good idea give me
the recipe later please please please
please please do I need a skillet for it
my dad um I guess it would be easier
that way yeah okay time to buy a skillet
you could just use a cake pan probably
oh yeah yeah a cake a small one though
if you want singles in the oven or a
cake pan on the it's in the oven okay
yeah there's a restaurant that serves it
it's called they make they call it
Pazuki
Pazuki what they serve Skillet cookies
yeah it's like what they're known for
what the hell give me free string killed
him free
string oh the the chest is full that's a
lot of stuff a that means your boy isn't
doing a job okay hold on a sec call my
brain was like breaking yesterday when
you were gone and I had to sort things
on my own man that was rough rough rough
rough that's all right it's just cuz you
don't have the configuration down like I
do if you figure out where it all goes
it' be fine fermented spider
eye he handles it
though yeah I'm I'm useful it's just
it's just not super entertaining is the
thing sorry everyone watching my POV I I
don't really not really doing much here
besides organizing
okay does everybody have enough food by
the way there's still like a watermelon
and bread in the food chest if you want
yeah I got the
food okay you're having a great time I'm
happy take it take it take it take the
food I'm sure chat will watch paint dry
with with us if it comes down to it that
would be an interesting interesting
stream watching paint that's very sweet
yeah they would especially watch it if
it was drying on your
body good point a good guys we we got we
got a
situation situation where' everybody go
what oh
no [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] what oh
no
what what happened enemies
anyway good thing we got Shields
right damn that was like black face
Pillager I dare attack damn that was
super
unlucky out it's okay there's only like
four of them of me cuz they're scared
they're [\h__\h] what they came all in
one damn what that's why they attack in
a group cuz they're big
cowards that one crazy those stps
man mhm come here those traps
yo yeah the traps that the the Pillager
was like setting up while the really
yeah that was very I saw that in Full
full
4K I got C by one come here buddy smells
like chicken in Get
Him CH get down here
toor I feel like we're hitting each
other more than than we're the enemies I
think it's gone I think so yeah I think
so great job guys crazy are we ready
smelly I'm
ready that's go oh I need girl has to
get her 1,000
block purposeful
No don't watch your helmets with the
golden helmets oh they're in the chest
behind the house house here here here
here
at the portal
okay I think my mouse is dying but I
can't find the
charging oh that's why I only only use
cable
tools I used to but way I a lot of eggs
here we go those mouses mes mice are
littley wonder what it was I must
release my egg where is
it didn't see nothing
oh well if I die my mouse
dies let's go M let's
go okay okay so uh goal would be to um
find the Pillager just for fun did
anybody bring gold for that a villager I
mean not a villager a p pigin
piglin did anybody bring some gold just
just a little bit no no okay I'll bring
some well then I'm my friends I'm rening
space in time please dropping my bird
off a little bit of gold just for fun
okay um I'm playing dollhouse the other
be iing one of those for we should play
sometime G some Forest that has the ne W
or
potions and if you find a fortress that
would be
sick the
cord yeah what what hey don't joke with
me man no I'll I'll play play Barbie
dolls with you girl anytime dude let's
do it
barie I love dollhous doll house my
weapons are kind of dying I kind of need
to fix it can I fix it move my friends
around a little
more there we gos
moved one second then I'm ready to
go roll then yeah like 20 I don't know
another okay uh building should we bring
bring some building blocks to make paths
perhaps I think we'll be able to just I
I have some
Cobblestone okay I got some endstone too
like one one stack I was scared for a
second cuz it was like it went so quiet
for like 5 seconds I was like did this
cour
die no it it went super quiet for like 5
seconds on my and I thought this would
even like Minecraft sound died I was
like huh but no it's just me I'm I'm
just being scared of my
own H is
coming we're here okay and I think we
can go this okay I'm
ready
okay you're
ready energy ready to go wait before we
go in we can take a picture in front of
it sure if you say so sounds good to me
stand in line whose bird is this whose
birds are these they're going to get
in yours and mine I thought I thought he
was going to sit in the house we got to
get that cat out hold on we got
to guys I feel like we're going to get
zapped by Ze sority photo
sity did you kill it where'd it go I
don't know where the cat went
but oh got to get your bird where is he
he's in front of the portal he's going
to go in by himself oh no he knows not
what horror aw photo
B don't lose the bird in the never that
would be so sad hello have you seen my
bird he's about this tall he's green it
was on your shoulder last time I saw oh
there he
is okay sorry jumping no the other bird
the green one oh I jumped it's on your
shoulder it's on your shoulder guys I'm
scared come on come on come over sorry
get struck by lightning with the
bird wait if you get struck by lightning
while your bird is on your shoulder do
you get cooked chicken as the
idem that's messed up man like superhero
like the Birdman or something like that
the origin story is you were struck by
lightning when you had a parrot on your
shoulder and then you turn into the
parrot
Man
scary okay dark wi duck yeah something
Mo man thank you guys hurry for the wait
whose cat is that you let them sit so
they don't follow you into
NE oh [\h__\h] maybe mine yeah it's your cat
in the boat but that's the bird boat so
okay it's sitting okay all right let's
go okay
cheese hello hello wow leave it to you
camera leave it to you I got it
okay then what shall await us on the
other side we shall
[Music]
see let's go the donkey for me be
careful you don't fall there's a lot of
lava the donkey went in let's go donkey
already alive
donkey donkey Burns a lot wait is he
really
burning don't worry guys he's gone
tripping guys there's a spawn that's
messed up wait where are you guys are up
there why' you get up
there what hold on also it's super
dark you're floating for us who's
floating hold on I'm am I stuck in the
port wait let me try this again why is
the server so borked okay hold on mind
just let me go let me join my friends
okay I think we're oh there's all it's
all lava actually let me
that's the H care Kelly I'm here I made
it I was just count 1 2 3 4 had some
weird mushrooms too we're fine okay yeah
be careful of your paths you may not be
seeing a hole but there may very well be
a hole D should have brought did anybody
bring a ton of blocks I'll just go back
and get a big
stack can be
useful okay we can make a bridge
some oh there's Soul Sand over
there we need those for uh time to be
useful nether
growing we have Soul Sand already I
think yeah we do have a lot of Soul Sand
but more NE wart would be nice and
finding a for we got NE one a little bit
yeah oh then we can totally grow them
already we should have we should have
planted them on the soul stand oh we can
duplicate them okay well then don't
don't take away the things the few
things that
okay now we're good let's keep an eye
out for the Fortress oh wait
coordination Cords Cord it'll slow you
down what are the cords I took a
screenshot of the
cords okay wait one two three four it's
not a very nice
spawn we're missing call I'm here back
yeah okay okay here should we go that
way to the next platform
oh you're facing here wait I think I
found
something you find it's a fortress
already are you sure it's a fortress how
do you know yeah you see to op the zoom
in with optify it's breaks no way the
Fortress wait where over there over over
where I'm
looking we should go this way first and
then turn go it's a [\h__\h] foress right
over there okay well now we have a goal
so that's we need to make a path over
there let's go I'm at the Builder okay I
don't have a lot of blocks though give
you if you need more blocks let me know
I've got a ton guys I hear a gas I'm
scared it's okay we are I do need more
blocks they might fall off here if you
give them to me oh yeah sure here you go
here him he sounds
hungry thank you he does so hungry
that's okay it's right over there it's
right over there it's totally going to
see
us it's okay no it's fine it's fine we
got to also remember um how we got here
I have the quartz no worries and I mean
the Fortress is so close I think we're
going to find our way back fine we're so
lucky he
goes so lucky man I'm I'm glad why did I
oh okay I didn't get any of those okay
making the path a little
longer or a little wider wait if you dig
another what is this red rock with a
stone pickaxe do you get them or do you
need iron you should get it it's just
like dirt basically it's this this
realm's dirt in in
Ence Ena does this remind you of
something being here I feel like I had
more gear last okay hold on past
them okay did YouTube die again for
anyone that's why I said I made I made
it really
bad we'll fix it when we come
back
yeah you're not fine falling down like
that on the one block pth where the
other side is
lava I didn't die you're not fine you
scare me
yeah no my God it's fine it's fine it's
fine no worries no worries I mean to put
that there
m you have a
flashback
the
example it is a fortress no way yeah
lucky us that's nutty looks like the eye
of
shuron oh goodbye load of the Rings
watch along let's go oh full extended oh
oh yeah I've done that actually before
with members oh
well remember when I got sick in Japan
when we were doing our 3D watch along 3D
uh debuts I uh when I got sick I did uh
lot of the Rings extended version watch
alongs with my members one after another
oh my God F eight hours four hours yeah
they good stuff a little stairway
make a little stairway can you catch me
I'm actively making it worse okay hold
on I what can you catch me oh you made
stairs you're too heavy that's a lot
less
romantic in fat tonight oh let's go fun
I helped I did one black wo
rotk
Ronin RK stands
for oh how do we get into the we have to
go up dig yeah I think we got to go up
it's an M from
Moy oh
Moet Mo we can't go in through the
bottom I I think we'll have to go up
like this is just like the the pillars
of it yeah the pap seems to be above and
then the main part seems to be further
uh over at the end of the that those
pillars there all right well if
everybody mines some uh nether rock then
we could just like boost ourselves
individually you know what I mean sure
oh yeah like a big like elevator yeah
okay I didn't bring a normal pickaxe I
only have the diamond pickaxe just in
case so okay well we can get some you
girls to to mine yeah I think I have
enough oh dear easy I'll start to make a
bridge careful there's like lava
right yeah there's
a
everywhere yeah careful there's lava um
all over the place
the wi will we W
everywhere I think I saw
her I saw her no really where you
go her blind's going to kill us
blind oh I can get some levels from
this oh she ah are you making like a a
circle circle stair a for you guys to uh
build up to it took about 40 blocks or
something like that okay can somebody
also give me blocks then okay I've got
quite a big stack I'll give you 64 Kara
thank
you do you want me to go in and Scout it
out yeah we need a scout go but then if
we want to go back we
went just I guess we get rid of the
blocks we made up I
guess yeah yeah that's how the elevator
works we'll figure out M our way down
again mine your way down don't worry if
you have to use a diamond pickaxe to get
down it's fine no no no I'll I'll use my
hands you're some dudes it's okay
they're friendly we have gold they
respect us why not just build
stairs right somebody says make a spiral
staircase yeah right that I'm already up
here so you know I'm good all right I'll
go then right beneath this is kind of
scary this hope this enough blocks yeah
it should be fine wait race you race you
you know race you oh God it's so have
any
more I have 10 okay I got
30 I it here oh yeah thank you you just
okay just should be real careful
okay making me nervous here with these
open edges back to me wait let's you
drop the stack yeah wait wait wait let's
go over here then I'll give it oh so
this is a
fortress I like the sound of the
stairs what NE so do we raid it is that
what you're supposed to do here yeah
we're taking it over be careful though
very dangerous very dangerous dangerous
can we fight them with stone swords you
think we'll
win if we find a blaze
spawner it's going to be a little bit
rough we rush it we don't give it a
chance to spawn and then we rush it yeah
yeah yeah sounds good okay we just need
a few blaze rods just for fun we don't
need to you know make the whole spawner
our
ours just you know oh yeah if we if we
end up getting wither like two more
wither heads we can spawn the
wither Quest hoay know
about I don't know about this ooh more
poisonous mushrooms for poison mushrooms
oh
sorry where you going dude sorry left or
straight uh girls Democratic vote please
left or straight stra are we going to
get
lost um uh I have some
torches me to me too should put torches
like on one side each so then you know
which way to go
back oh yeah good idea we're going in a
straight line I think it'll be okay okay
that's a good way to Mark oh but
actually straight is a dead end we could
oh never mind left is good okay come on
come on we're going this way it's so
quiet in here so far did you just say
that God bye Kara this a big one there's
some stairs here I want to go
up W what what possibly could go wrong
it's so quiet here this is a calm before
the storm photo photo
where is that we we death flag where are
the skeletons oh I like skirlington this
is may also dead end do they have like
chests and stuff here to
raid uh yeah they should have some
chests yeah oh sorry treasure my loot
Goblin
uh-oh run back run back
inside Retreat Retreat Retreat carry
it just yeah you got
[Music]
waiton anyway go tell him to e [\h__\h] I
want to hit the thingies don't risk it
for the skillet
biscuit it won't kill you hold on I'm
just trying to hit it wait yeah do it do
it girl
where dang it it should have die yeah
let's
go fall off your horse yeah you yeah
yeah yeah we got it
okay back
down and then the this
way
YY it's so empty but the bricks are so
nice I want to take some bricks
home somebody else choose the path but
this seems to be a good
section this stairs straight oh there's
a thing there a spawner there's a
spawner there oh nice rush rush a rush
it's
scary if you block the fire should be
fine you just put a torch oh just put a
torch on it right go Ena go go go am go
Callie oh he's very strong oh he's very
strong oh he does not like
me the potato oh no it's spawn behind
you too okay got it kill him kill him
nice well done lady
that was easy did he drop do we need to
more oh nice uh I mean we can just take
the torch out it w spawn more right oh
or we can build this thing where it's
like you can like block the line of set
and just hit it from like down here M
that would be nice if we know
to know how to do it if anybody has the
torch you can put it back on now
nice you're on fire nice hit oh I got a
blaze rod too let's go be nice many XP I
guess but they're kind of we need more R
for the eyes of we already have all the
Eyes of Ender chat that we
need come back we're just doing we can
take the End Dragon now I don't have any
more torches if somebody
wants I mean we could
but give a little more diamonds yeah a
little bit we should go in with a bit
more armor at least
I mean we have enough Diamond to make
armor
for I think so everyone don't you think
we we have like a
stack Tor no we got to it out at least
one more day come on yeah torch guys
torch oh you pushed him into
me sorry I said it wasn't
me okay no torch just Tor today is never
day and the next time we can do I don't
have one so
I don't if we're so eager and I used all
mine
yeah oh okay oh yeah yeah you listening
kill the
Endor oh but I I thought we want to
fight
more oh yeah sure did we get what do we
need do we even need it just it's just
you know for fun it's okay we finished
Minecraft Minecraft and then we just
find a different different thing to all
do together fine
am I using the wrong oh sorry this is
the wrong I'm such an idiot don't know
how to fight it's for I was doing
potions basically the more of these
things we have the more potions we can
make like OverWatch we will not be
playing OverWatch
together decision no I don't think it's
bad either it's just not what I want to
play play with you
guys why
not why not OverWatch hey is this what
you need this
ooh skin tags wait where are you too are
you where are you and some red stuff
Widowmaker turned to left I'm a sniper
where did everybody I just free
lava free lava oh yeah this good yeah
pick them up good good someone's going
to have to D this out here no clue where
we
are didn't but where are the skeletons
is it like bugged why go
spawns in the
Fortress dead be through in my chat oh
here
skeletons
there I should have brought milk damn it
why did we forget about
milk de oh oh oh no oh no oh no first
one that dies get spanked by the diamond
sword go go
go why look like that where are
you uh I was a little I I was one hit
away from dying oh there's another
one yeah oh and there's a place too I
think I I
die that's not great did you find my
stuff yep yeah I Pi it up okay good
bring retreating is a good idea
okay yeah those those the the curses
they put on you they're no joke yeah I
was really surprised by that I can't
believe I survived Ena behind you Ena
behind you
[Applause]
I just want to get the chest o nice
chest no please I'm sorry
armor
nice worry all my all my moves are
calculated got it all oh bowl is oh
there's more nether here be fine a
blocks I had to build my way up a I got
to build my way up again oh
a nice uh if you follow the path uh I
started building oh I guess you don't
have any
blocks I'll be fine I'm bringing
blocks but no gold armor I have no
shovels should be
fine a ladder over there I want to make
a ladder
now nothing in there okay here we found
the entrance if you guys hello where
where is everyone I lost my I was
looking at that chest over there by the
lava but there's nothing in there oh
really okay
yeah already looted it wait can you
backtrack okay you guys come back come
out of the chest area oh okay does he is
he going to attack me hello yeah the the
entrance is here but there's also this
unexplored uh part here go
deeper must go we are away from oh it's
just more chest it looks like oh is on
that more chest to be looted iron horse
armor gold have a lot of
horses a quite a few to ride into battle
valiantly don't get lost guys I'm
standing at the
staircase scared he won't does he not
care about the gold tell me tell me chat
tell me
chat all right I got everything in the
chest okay we're going back up let's go
get Kiara
[Music]
you're going to get me yeah you're
alone I thought I was just going to go
back to you can
you do we need anything here I feel like
we got everything oh you want to leave
already what what I thought we were
going to do the Ender Dragon no we're
not doing the endon no
not no today's never day don't end our
beautiful time together so early
yeah wait what if we made like a like a
like an arena and we have one each one
of us has to fight the Ender Dragon one
at a time that could be fun and we watch
we sit and watch you just watch and die
yeah and back seat each other damn oh
what my sound fine oh
uh I think it's a good
idea oh boy I might indeed need help to
get get back up we're going the
Coliseum Coliseum sounds good
huh yeah I do Coliseum do you guys think
you could beat a bear in a fist fight
speaking of Coliseum no no
no can you there was a there was a thing
like that in like a game called M noi
it's like you can get a title for
beating up a be when you're 10 years
old wait I think there's that in in
Witcher as well
you fish fight a
bear can you start oh you don't have any
blocks I got nothing I have a few a few
I was going to say you can start
building stairs up there's a gas over
there guys I don't feel very safe speed
it up speed up speed up we got to go
Watson I'm
trying Ena you are the
distraction I think it's
Z okay okay go go go go go go go
go okay maybe I can help build two maybe
not there's two of them we're almost
there we're almost there
guest speed
speed we here careful
girls I should have bought like a slime
or something just jump down down okay
emergency boat oh I do have
boats I don't know if I can do it with
this ping though right now we just still
stairs up why why why do I not have
problems with the Ping I'm so
lucky okay what if you're coming back
then I guess hello we're here oh we're
here we're right up here okay let me see
hold
on you can get in the boat and dive off
the edge oh all right that's the
thing okay can we tand them what does
that mean uh two oh like a tandem
bicycle oo oh girls I got to go like AFK
for a second but I'm just going to log
out for a
moment okay I'll I'll be don't be gone
too long I miss
you hurry up okay all right I got a I
got two
boats
nice are we are we just going to boat it
let's try it let's try it let's try it
yeah that could be
good okay if you say so okay aim do not
aim for the lava I wait am I in the
front oh F dri Drive I can't see I can't
see the bottom I can't see I can't see
going for it all my houon you're clear
clear W clear for
launch here we go oh nice oh it
works wow we
live I mean I knew itoo you didn't doubt
me for a second did you of course not oh
just joking jokes jokes
jokes oh W looks strange on the screen
hold on a
sec did it work I'm just going to put
them oh oh oopsies okay we
good get out of
way I have Mario Kart DK Mountain on
Loop I'm losing my mind nice oh in the
background
yeah it is pretty highp battle
Tunes battle jungle music so hey now
that we're here and ki's AFK we can uh
test by putting um a obsidian portal o o
where are we going um going SP though I
wonder wait that's what you titled your
stream isn't it title drop title
drop title
drop but if it's one block on the other
side then what if we spawn
do you need a
pickax well then I have k diamond one
I'll just use
it
oo I'm
[Music]
telling don't be a tile tail girl is
this is this tall
enough uh two three I think think I made
it too
wide is this three it's okay it's going
to be 3x3 it'll be fine
okay hopefully this works those are
weird noises who wants to go in
first H be careful you might spawn into
nowhere wait maybe you should leave your
stuff
first I'm not going
anywhere oh I guess it doesn't work yes
it does oh wait no it just uses wavy and
then it just stays like that forever oh
oh wait
what
ooh ooh wibbly wobbly where did you guys
go I'm going to barf I'm going to barf I
don't know everything I'm I god I think
I'm in heaven no no no do you guys have
any blocks um there is nothing I just
see call it Sky Block I'm I spawned
underneath the portal and there's like a
little obsidian platform that catches
you but there's nothing else blocks I
have some blocks I'm getting bar some
blocks I can't really go
careful okay just chill everyone don't
walk
off I have to walk off no no no don't
don't don't walk off don't walk off is
really wobbly um let me see if there's
so shift is wait you made another portal
oh uh don't don't come in might not be a
good idea to come in it's just really
hard to place a block right now you did
you did you did you make a portal and
you were like in the middle of the
sky yes we're in the middle this guy
right now oh that's fun that's so
fun can you can you get up do you have
do you have blocks I don't I don't have
any blocks I got some okay drop it on
the other side drop drop happening I
want to
see come through come through okay we
have enough enough platform this to stay
okay all right I'll just mine some of
these bottom block oh never mind Saving
Private atin
what's happening
here I've got five blocks to help you oh
my God wait
so um what's the plan to be here what's
the purpose of I'm trapped restart the
challenge you're trapped restart
restarting the chall we're trying to
save
Watson wa what if I what do you mean
she's there what she's below us she what
wait where are you at um there's a
obsidian platform underneath that they
fell onto
it I don't
see what what does it mean you see
that okay I just made another portal at
the bottom never
mind
what okay back into the are you going
back yeah I'm already on the other side
there was enough blocks to just make
another portal you guys go first in
comparison okay I'm coming in
hello hi
well that was that was good for science
right so we know that if you make
another portal you'll be again in the
middle of the
sky yep here can you give me back your
stuff hold on I'm going to I'll break
this portal so we don't go into it again
mhm
yeah why not what a strange silly thing
all right here you go
this and this one oh I didn't pick it up
I guess that's our portal over there I
think you have the chest plate now is
mine now I'll wear two chest plates no
mine what do you need two chest plates
for why not one for Monday and one for
Tuesday
a all right so are we going back in cuz
we I think we pretty much got
everything why well I mean yeah we can
go back but I'm not letting you go that
easily can I make all my friends really
wide wait what if we drop the dragon
into a portal like what we just did and
then he falls into the sky push him out
yeah I think he we build can you build
another portal in the end I don't think
I don't think
so but then we can break the portal and
he's stuck in the void
forever oh oh you can't build a portal
okay can you not is that what CH says
yeah the dragon kind of flies though so
won't have fall
damage not a nether doesn't work in the
end oh oh that's too bad okay then let's
go back to the to the to the real
portal and we can still do some stuff
though we don't have to end it here that
would be so sad we still have to collect
materials though K we have near enough
golden apples or weapons and that kind
of stuff so yeah we need to mine
diamonds let's just endlessly mine
because we need some diamonds and we
need maybe if we find a villager that
would be nice and I mean if you want
something to do you could build
PPP more organizing doesn't Okay do do
we need that well we need nothing really
but um we can build together this time
I'm going to be a weapon Smith I can
help build together yeah yeah hell yeah
all right I'll look up a guy together
sounds fun small child did we trade
gold we didn't do it but we could it's
not these though the it's like the
normal
[Music]
pickling welcome home everybody my Pand
hold
on are the pandas okay yeah did they did
they uh perish so
sadly they're okay dang it they're
starting to get so many you might need
to expand their
territory or call some
a cute sound if you need me to execute
your pandas I'll do it for you why are
you so eager well there's one loose
Panda that's not part of the pack
right what I'm going to put this
hor armor on a can I put on a
donkey I I don't think so sadly where
did all the horses go oh there's one
horse all right I shall do some
organizing that's a donkey
so that we can mine more wait did all
the horses
die I guess there's a skeleton
one he yeah we had like so many zombie
hes I know that one is like
underground oh a broken music disc why
is it
broken um I'm stuck in the all right
guys I'm watching a zombie spawner farm
tutorial let's go can I help I want to
help we me to work yeah let me absorb
information first absorb it okay learn
and then
do ton of dirt blocks by the way if you
want to expand the forest I don't really
think expanding the forest has much of a
meaning now though but I mean we can
still farm and get more trees oh we can
get more apples actually from the trees
oh yes yes apples would be nice
really you can take that as one of
yourself side quests cool okay side
quests yay nice nice nice also there's a
ton of coal in this fuel chest over
here kind of
[Music]
coal yeah all right expand the forest
then I'm going to grab some dirt and
then we're going to expand the forest
have fun I'm chopping down the forest
NOA no don't call
the it's okay just you're chopping it
down to make it bigger
it all has a purpose it all serves a
purpose I'm not quite making big I'm
just getting more
app good that's fine too uh how does how
does one plant apple trees oh apples are
a random drop from these
leaves you got to punch the leaves yeah
you can punch the leaves and or just you
know let them disappear on its
own the trees as the sa I'm going to
create a forest that branches off from
where we're planting a ton of
wheat it's going to go this way here's
the path to the forest go
go come here help me where are
[Music]
you putting you to work goba oh okay
either or mine oh not Birch Oak Only
wait the oak trees okay yeah I'll sort
I'll sort have
fun I'm was going to get a
snack um just so you know in the storage
room area I've uh I've separated things
by how the chests are actually labeled
so if it says nether chest that's blocks
from the nether if it says ocean chest
that's blocks from the ocean oh yeah so
they're already like pre-labeled that
way nice
yeah and then the ones that are in the
regular storage area have signs that say
like the top chest has these things in
them the bottom chest has these things
in them that kind of
thing yeah oh good job by the way go we
got some heart of the Seas but it's like
so useless I thought you could use it
for Atlantis but you got to make a whole
ocean no I just need a little bit of
water I can put it I can build a conduit
and and it's cool but yeah
yeah it's useless yeah so
sad but it's
fancy I can build it anyway
oh yeah if you're up for it I mean it's
useless can you build under not
underwater or is it only underwater
go looking at your chat for the
answer
um only water or under
water try to make it in the fishing
pond or in the dolphin uh
pool I can do that water is
necessary can can swim even faster if it
has the conduit he's not allowed in the
he's not allowed in the conduit pool he
stays down there in the stinky dolphin
confinement Zone a that's where he
belongs yeah he bit me what oh yeah okay
he bit me yeah true he's a little [\h__\h]
yes little into the
aquarium I'm stuck again I feel like the
grass should spread from there do John
yeah that guy sucks well I guess yeah we
hate do
John it'll grow
okay I can't go that way what the hell
Chey all right start mining cou cuz we
need like a I think we have a that g
made
right how many what we need what do we
need how many one second one
second I'm making the myy myy you guys
all right we need 20 stacks of
cobblestones one stack of trap doors
okay okay we already got a
couple do I get paid
overest let me check how how much
Cobblestone we have in the other chest
wa this this is I don't know if I does
it have to be
Cobblestone uh I guess it doesn't it
just needs to be 20 stacks of something
oh then we should have enough stacks of
things right all right let's we'll make
a stack cobone stack torches cracked
stone bricks stack chiseled stone bricks
stack I can't ride zombie
[Music]
horses they'll fall apart they're in the
chest by the cobblestone generator I'll
put um put like full stacks of stuff if
you find any okay 20 you say 20 yeah we
need
20 we're so ready for this there's so
many stacks in
here
torches make a
Tor 1 2 three Golden Arrow spectral
Arrow 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 there a
zombie 11 12 St
sorry my fault a lot of zombies are oh
there's really a lot of spw okay I'm
going as fast as I can man I don't think
you need to mine at all we have enough
stacks of things I think you forgot to
light up the new
area that's what I was going back to do
I'm
Sorry's okay we just need two more full
stacks of something when you left oh
okay than you we're
done okay now we need this many look how
much two zombies Max wait wait but
there's only 42 on that one you need
more no no no no that's enough this we
have that's not a full stack no that's
it needs to be a full St sorry full St
dead beat I swear to God dead beat I
know I know I've seen the error of my
ways okay I'm sorry you did all of that
wa sand is going to fall although I
guess that's no it should be okay we're
just going to be stacked up okay okay
okay I have too much stuff look how
efficient she is
trees getting why is it so slow anyway
can it not be faster come on it's my
[Music]
ping always
cursed ping pong ping pong oh where's my
chicken there what the hell get out did
you spawn there oh I have a new family
now put a little fall down
how so
close count count the stacks go try
counting the stacks why don't you count
them for me why they over 20 you count
them yourself I need to complete this
one
stack okay let me it's for your own
character development right let me
finish has let me finish it's unpaid
anyway do it for the satis okay there
okay what 3 69 12 15 16 17 18 19 2 2 23
Stacks but at least now we have extra
ooh
yeah because what if somebody dies who's
died the most here who turned on that
music it's a broken one scared me it's a
broken one I don't know why what it
is oh God fter
no why do you do that hey stop coughing
get that cing cover your mouth cover
your mouth spreading
germs it's like an audio book it's a
voice pack it's a voice pack I don't
like this voice pack I didn't buy it I
want to refund my money
back that's not quite my tempo
I'm
scared he's running faster Kara run run
run behind you behind you stop until he
kills
you yumy that's how do I get into this
dolphin Center I think it's over where
is the
dolphin it better still be there he's
gone I think he di no
way he must have despawned or so because
like why would he die we need four
carpets four carpets oh yeah yeah he did
oh my god oh speaking of I should
probably go share the
Sheep again it's fully
grown but uh four carpet should already
be possible with the stuff that's in
there yeah the only thing is I don't
think we have enough iron cuz I need I
need five oh wait what is it four
hoppers we only have 11 I think we can
only make two right now then we have two
Hoppers
now oh we do somewhere oh yeah yeah okay
we have enough then I wait for the
forest to grow I'll organize but there's
a chicken in there I got to use the rest
of the iron wait Dolphins can
drown
yeah
what air I guess they do go up for
air I feel so stupid right now but I
think they
do yeah IM being a seaal and
drowning couldn't be me that couldn't be
me okay I got the
CET oh there's a Sher box there no
generator are you perhaps
steal I say sounds like a Gil issue
oh good one girl one he's
happy he's happy that he met with the
one and
only Nick's mommy come on chicken let's
go consider yourself blessed come on
chicken come on time to go it's time to
accept the new world you're
in come
on get
moving he should be grateful we're going
to be like feeding him and stuff yeah or
killing him oh no we're going to be
killing
want to hear that you know just giving
him free like hope before you know the
end well yeah that's how the meat gets
really good is that you don't tell them
that you're going to kill them you know
when we're done with this series I
promise to my chickens I'm coming back
to the server every day to feed them
every day I will every day Comm I might
not stream it but I will open the server
every day and I'll more dirt I could
have made the forest so much bigger
isn't the server going to get shed down
though anyway I'm going to pay to keep
it open just to feed the
chickens all right well I'm ready to
start if anybody wants to help uh I I'll
come too I learn how to make
it okay I'll still work on the
trees is it like version specific this
yeah yeah it said it should work for uh
version 1.14 and up oh oh wait I got to
ask chat a question question chat should
I build the um mob spawner XP farm uh
should I build it like at the end of
this Atlantis
Road or uh cuz it's close to spawn right
or should it be further away from
Spawn close to spawn or Far Forest needs
to be bigger far away is better okay
well we might uh I have slabs we can
build a little bit further wait how many
blocks away
Tod is bugged no it's not I just changed
how they
look what what did you do to
us manipulated your images a little bit
it's fine don't wor about
it
60 oh is this your Forest expansion
pack K we yes it is MHM I'm working on
the my myy it's going to be a really big
wait you can put melons in the my
my it would be correct the melon
Mor I got some here SS good oh hell
yeah mhm damn you should make like if
you ever do like a charity stream again
or so maybe plant some trees to make a m
oh that's a good idea yeah every every
uh Super Chat that we get for charity
plants a tree in
Minecraft
Minecraft yeah wait what we take the
Mone then we take the money from that
and then we donate it to plant real
trees okay yeah okay real trees real
moris we want them real moris really
breaking Dimensions with that one it's
like freaking the
manions bucks for one
tree all right I'm at the end of the
Atlantis uh okay if anybody wants to I'm
coming is the only normal one well yeah
she's the only human out of all of us so
I thought
I would leave her image untouched is she
do is she she's
British
anybody I can make them for you for
car yeah oh wait we have it we have it I
see it
shulker there
[Music]
there wait where did everybody go wait
hello any can somebody bring extra slabs
cuz I got to I got to extend this place
a little it extra slabs I can bring
slabs okay go I'm here anyway I'll make
them nice I can't believe you can just
make a PPP that's so cool yeah what the
heck imagine having the brain capacity
chat I know I don't just make PPP your
name has to be also Amilia Watson true
only she is capable oh I made a lot why
isn't it the the pap then I don't
understand
previously on his property because it is
previously true there was already a PPP
and I guess that was
P should we just talk in abbreviations
from now on thank you
why is then yes
why stop that would be maybe a joke
stream idea just only talk in in
abbreviations
could be fun sounds
hard
BRB LOL getting more mushrooms too
lol all right I'll need you guys help in
a second but hold on I'm just R this
really quick maybe we can expand the
forest in time to go watch how the PPP
is made almost done
FR F FR F
FR for real for real for stop just doing
it they're actually oh my God I'd never
last that kind of stream
SMH I can't think of so many need to
make some
notes TG ladies please W it's not Friday
though it's not
tgit pleas T TG M TG is it I is it
Monday Tuesday wedn
Friday it's w i just rot
[Music]
the let's see what she's doing wow we
here going to fall
down can I make a wall around here am
yeah maybe fences would be good or
something or wall
whatever um
GTG okay I will pain that horse back to
him I still can't write this horse it's
just the donkeys maybe I'm just not
meant for
horses a no horsing around Ena no
horsing around
donkey
donkey full myth Shrek watch along
when oh man we've seen it so many times
k k and I have seen it together right we
watched it we did a one and two watch
along need to get the others in on this
yeah we watch both damn got a little
Marathon at my place yeah in the
beginning honestly so I know
sh shre I'm always down for a shre watch
along why is his name Shrek what do you
think you're M now donkey could it be a
reference to a German word of surprise
which is I'll look it up right now
I am surprised I
am why is he called sh I knew that was a
it's girl related to the German Shrek
meaning fear or fright
wow you hit the nail on the head K oh my
God that's why I brought it up cuz I I
thought it kind of sounds like and you
know ogres they surprise you right with
their look so you're like
shre oh Shrek lure new Shrek lure just
dropped Shrek lure yeah years later
we're still getting new Shrek lure what
a
word e that makes me so happy that that
I speak German wow you were
right me I'm dony or no I I the donkey
okay good nice how tall is Shrek Shrek
idiot Shrek is probably like 8T tall
block of iron oh yeah he's pretty big
he's a big
guy yeah hi wait Shrek is based on 7 ft
Fiona would be 510 as a human and 6'4 as
an ogas oh she be
ogis they call ah female ogre ogis hot
not g NGL
NGL hot what in what way Kiara would you
like girl
wi yeah where's our ogris in
whole no no be cool
she got like an alternate form she
changes at night oh for all the night
streams okay that's cute yeah yeah yeah
see see see some people in the in the
chat are like
hot see there's something for everyone
here
spicy you guys like an ogre lady
huh I think they don't not like an over
lady why not what's there not to like
okay I'm going to make oh yeah you do
bunch of iron bars you're just joking
you're not serious about it I'm going to
put you in front of an ogre lady and
you're going to be
like help Kar out like that don't out
them like that
kiar be careful here cuz I got to build
down somehow I don't know how not a post
ogre see they're fine with
it with water that's why they're myy
fans wa ogre outfit next who's going to
do an ogre outfit not me
ogre onesie with little Shrek ears on it
Callie it's got to be you come on you
have this whole like Shrek
thing for your whole streaming career
here no not really it's it's just a
little
joke just a little te hopefully I don't
die doing this go go go go we cat you
Boulders gate three ogre Kell oh yeah oh
man Boulders gate is so good I wish I
could have played the full game yeah
have you not played it on your own no
well I I did a little bit right like
simultaneously when we did the collabs
but then I felt like doing both is kind
of rough and then I left it to the
collabs only but then you know you know
what happened to the collapse so I was
like ah I don't know continuing now
alone is a little bit felt a little bit
late I didn't realize that we had
actually finished act one oh yeah we
kind of did yeah M we just didn't like
we had to do like one thing and then it
would have been finished I think right
yeah well oh maybe I thought we already
did it and we didn't realize we' passed
act one we were in act two oh for real
yeah that's okay
though yeah it's hard to do a really
long balers gate play play through just
a long game narissa yeah narissa she did
the whole thing she's crazy I respect
played it like several times I also have
a friend who's played balers gate six
times with
mods six my God
sheh oh you can play it differently
every time that's the amazing thing
about these kind of
games I love that have you guys ever
tried now I'm ready for the part where I
need to get this help okay what do you
need uh hold we're going
to wa I need to build
up just grab a stack I guess we can do
sand for this one because it's fine
we're going to I'll build up 20 it do be
fine 20 I'll be right back okay any of
these like Corners
thingies yeah good at going AFK now that
we need
her boss please put me in charge of
golden apples I promise I won't let you
down wait uh oh yeah am I the boss yeah
well I kind of figured since you set
this count count count 21 cuz I don't
know I I counted but I don't know if
it's right if I block is 64 and then is
403 at the end of it
cuz I didn't count wait is there water
down there how are we going to get down
oh oh you got the water oh this just
temp area oh that shadowy spots a little
suspicious hold
on oh I can go up with
the with the
water wobbly water oh sh funny free I
was right
okay nice
[Music]
uhoh I'm going to go to I'm going to
shoot it maybe we should sleep you want
to sleep s yeah let's sleep all right
good night oh God gaur is out in the
open though oh AFK G we have to defend
her I'll try where is she okay I got a
bow at the future PPP I got an I got a
bow but it's not coming closer right now
where are you you at the future yeah
they're over there oh Bey on the pandas
gotcha ooh
cool I can fight him too I fight
him going to waste these arrows like
that we have we can use infinite bow
yeah nice good idea I'll have it at hand
so hit him try hey okay yay now we
cancel Arrow cancel okay it's fine it
doesn't matter let's go sleep yeah
doesn't it not matter oh I guess a
majority of players can sleep okay
yeah Chad how do I cancel an arrow if
I'm like about to shoot it no it's not
majority but uh so this now we we'll
await G our okay we started having a
sleepover party without
[Music]
you no no a okay
switch item oh okay thank you chat not
much of a bow Smith but I'd like to
become
one
cool
oh see move did I
imagine yeah back with the abbreviations
it's not really an abbreviation I
guess I wonder why it's like why it's
like ZZ for sleep like where the
[Music]
question yeah not much of a
bon I feel like at least G is one of the
few ones of these on which are which is
like the same all over the world like
you know how for example uh bark bark
and woof woof they're like different in
different languages but that de is like
same
everywhere it says it uh since
1918 it's become yeah it's it's been
used to symbolize
[Music]
snoring who decided who who decided it
uh no one really knows but it just
started appearing I guess in Like Comics
and newspapers I suppose H oh I guess
it's kind of like you know like Comics
have like the Zoom and like those kind
of things
[Music]
zap so now we're just like chilling here
goo's back goba can you like sleep with
us in our beds sleepover party come over
gooa oh sorry sorry it's okay okay cuz
it's because uh one of those Phantoms
spawned and you know we want to be safe
up there when we work uh wait you didn't
protect me what if it came from me we
did we did we protected your honor we
killed it and then we ran away after we
killed which means another one could
have spawned
[Music]
totally you are we all sleeping in the
right beds oh I saw
you
[Music]
okay
with did the forest grow did the forest
grow chicken dang it oh this grass is
really
slow is there a way make grass grow
faster
everyone grass grow
faster ah the grass you need to connect
it to other dirt blocks and then we just
got to wait for this cuz it's going to
start going yeah
okay well I'll wait then oh man yes see
you a lot yeah thank you so
much bone meal bone meal is for trees
that's what I'm going to start doing to
get apples uh afterward after the forest
is ready let's go to the PPP while we
wait we can go watch them we don't need
the corners we just need like to enclose
this water area kind of what I mean wa
can make a clay
bre clay we have a t yeah I was thinking
we should use some of the clay stuff
that's a good idea yeah feel free
there's
tons yes yes go
ahead make pretty
bricks wait did I make too many no okay
you got to cook clay oh it
requires yeah we oh we could pick up
some lava from the never so we can have
endless you know no coal for the thing
but instead just use lava true good idea
yeah lava Farm kind of thing that was
one good thing about going into the
never at least let's
go yeah a long
process I put these back in
here so this is the
PPP yeah that require me getting more
buckets I was kidding I guess we can get
rid of this oh there's like one side
that needs to be sealed so the enem is
fall here goodbye fish
all I'll do this one more right one more
oh yeah I got it oh you got it okay she
got it she's got it h Fight Club yeah
looks kind of nice actually as if we
purposefully made a nice pattern nice
design good design skills
yeah totally on purpose M premeditated
Le I could give it a hole
M
nice Temple of
PE uh I don't know we need to do
something eventually
canel so I'm just watching watching
nature do it
thing H what does that
mean how can we help now Amy uh I'm just
waiting for this water to dissipate hold
on oh wait I have a spawn
it's wet it's go it's gone already okay
well now we have an extra
bucket oh sorry where did all the other
buckets
go all right one second I got to watch
this video more sorry you guys just
waiting for me okay it's okay it's just
cool to look at to be
honest I'm so excited does this count as
react
content must be you're not streaming I
think uh making a video we got to react
to it
live some video but then what about
watch alongs wouldn't by that metric
watch alongs not be react content cuz
it's not on stream
yeah has to be showing on stream oh no
no no I don't mean it needs to be
showing on stream but I feel like you
should be at least
uh we have to go back up there somehow
oh shoot we need ladders I think content
for us ladders we can make yeah I shall
make we need like 20 something
okay let me guess you make it super dark
in
there uh yeah we're going to we're going
to build a platform up there
[Music]
cool live myth reaction yeah I should
have checked out how a
ladder damn it wait wait wait wait
wait okay okay we're good we're
good I me eating like rice crisps
they're pretty
good oh are they covered in chocolate or
just sour cream and
onion oh I was thinking of different
kinds I think okay I got a I got uh
almost two stacks of
ladders
okay going to throw them at
you wait wait here uh uh oopsie uh
[Music]
scolding requires string doesn't it I
don't think we have that much
string oh think we need
scaffolding I mean yeah this should be
okay okay up she
goes and we are looking if you guys grab
some uh some blocks we need to make a
platform on each side so it'll be like
uh four platforms extending on each side
I
have eight yeah at the top I have some
what are they called half block
slabs do it like how I did here but on
each
side
tutal oh sorry blocks or slab blocks or
slabs oh um blocks blocks
huh
H I got blocked wait too it w work I
thought that they don't spawn on slabs
uh no don't use wood just in case if you
don't have any other oh Callie uh
jfyi um that only counts when you put
the slab at the bottom of the block for
example cuz you can put them both in the
top and the bottom position so just for
your Minecraft knowledge thank you do we
extend it this
way I'm trying the bottom right
jfyi jfyi I didn't understand what you
meant there for a second but
now how far is it again
uh eight blocks long two two
wide
five 5 six seven eight nice this is some
real Sky Block kind of [\h__\h] let's go now
this is
[Laughter]
Taun feel the danger oh you want some
walls too Amit with
that uh yeah yeah we're going to encase
everything in a two block High wall for
now s you want a side of walls with
that yummy walls go back down for more
blocks oh shoot speaking of going down
put water down there I think it looks
like a propeller right now like
a helicopter yeah what did you put water
down okay give me a second I think
there's water in the uh in the chest
over here the Sher box oh oh wait I have
water never mind she's doing the water
landing oh I'm just I'm just making a
little elevator let it can just make a
water elevator Minecraft's insane oh
there goes
the Torches torches
uhoh wait could we make an actual
functional water elevator we have Soul
Sand right what else do you need yeah we
can I don't think we really need a I
mean unless there's something else cuz I
don't think this needs a water
elevator oh oh
okay we got so much I'm going to go down
so I press uh space right when I jump in
the
water uh yeah shift is it shift if you
want to go down it's shift yeah gotcha
it's up for oh yeah
yeah some whatam call it torches on the
fences maybe
help are you coming back to finish the
wall or should I finish the wall oh yeah
I mean I was going to get more block but
you can finish it go ahead okay I going
to watch the rest
[Music]
video I have two
torches this looks cool I like this PPP
PE we should give it a new name I think
P was actually
cool what does it stand
for previously am property oh could you
if we have enough buckets uhhuh I need
three more buckets of
water I have one I don't know where all
the other buckets went I have all the
buckets because I filled them with milk
thinking we need them when I went back
but you mind if I just I'll I'll go pick
up some water watch out I'm coming up
you mind if I just I'm on the
lad mind me you I actually kind of want
to make a Whatchamacallit a
carpet sorry I'm just a
little I'll put it back W wo no how many
put
PL what okay two okay cuz I don't like
opening
doors
get we need four buckets of water care I
have one can bring one uh I have four
too oh okay you can bring can't is silly
guys you guys are silly we're going to
what did you guys do
okay now we're going to um line with
trap doors I said what they were saying
I just said it out loud now you're
poting started it so we're going to do
it like this and then close it
gotta the one of the other sides and
it's going to be on both sides
okay oh my okay
ah I'm coming with the buckets I just
went up the ladder and realized there's
no opening there wow perfect now no
delay in going over
fences beautiful hi are we pouring the
water here in the middle uh no no no
it's going to be at the end of this of
the Halls that we're standing in right
now but uh now
just I think we can't make the W CL
until we get another sheep we only have
one this is not a sheep
actually this is a sheep oh it's getting
dark it is a sheepa don't tell it
otherwise he's going to cry don't let
him
know it's very much a
sheep oh c
okay it's white it's thick it's
fluffy mhm honestly I didn't even lead
it there it just like went over the
fence somehow and suddenly was
there it really wanted to be with the
Sheep I wanted to give it some
company I need be
can I make this jump yeah we're supposed
to both sides pocor sorry if the water
pushes
you who if you fall you dig out of there
sorry
heart hey not bad that's that's how it's
supposed to work it's like exact amount
oh so so that you can kill it zombie
now nice test see here I just tested it
for us sorry I'm putting more water so
if it's going to push you go to watch
out ah watch out don't worry I got
washed away shouldn't break the sand I
think she's not kill
us
meow is car stuck down there no I'm I'm
made my way out oh is it
here so the hopper is already working I
can tell you that you got your stuff did
you die I didn't die but I broke a block
and it went into
nice see waa tested I did did waa
approved it was on purpose according to
Kaku can we get a translator note thank
you thank
you ni
o w the view from here is really nice
you can really see what we all made
together
a damn it's pretty big wa oh I can see
from here too mhm it's
posing be a shame if yall
SLI she said
TR she's not going to push me off I
couldn't
reach points
[Music]
finger oh it's
working kind
of wait don't spot him in yet I'm in
here s enemies wait
pause the game wait pause the game I got
to figure out how to get out of here
doesn't matter what side I
did taking down the water elevator oh
please okay wait it's working wait what
it's working oh yeah go down go down go
down go down go down over there go down
go down in the I got to put the water in
they won't go down unless I do that is
that a skirlington
oh
no maybe it was a bad idea to use sand
[Applause]
yeah
guys
your wait did all the Hoppers and chest
blow up oh just there The Hoppers okay
okay let me go grab oh that's K oh I got
to eat I got to eat I got to eat oh God
have a bucket of
fish oh God oh God oh this going to need
some repairs for
sure that was so good I saw like good
die and then I saw the sand falling and
then I slipped and I fell off with the
sand
falling cuz you put it and laugh at
me yeah I I got it it's
okayed about in the middle Midway
is it's okay it's okay I'm staying down
here
man can't blame you for that one not
going up there pppp giving
PTSD sounds about
right but hey you know at least we know
it spawns
monsters karmod kod I'm not K this was
fun I I enjoyed every single millisecond
of
that I think it exploded in the
middle so maybe need some repairs in the
middle yeah that that creeper would have
either exploded up at the top or at the
bottom so maybe the top would have been
better maybe yeah we just need to fix
the sides the water's out now uh
yikes I'll fix I'll fix the bottom if it
could light up first maybe at daytime
might be a good time D yeah maybe we
should s fix up okay well more more
stuff will
spawn what really I'll put torches up
there right now okay okay just well it's
a work in progress iess sleepy my time
yeah sleepy my time the beds are being
used sleepovers are nice see I miss
sleepovers see
all right there's already stuff up there
spawn so I'm just going to go to sleep
and hopefully they'll die monsters
nearby so we can't sleep oh there's
zombie oh hello kill him idiot stop
watching while sleep you creepy weird
hey you hit my panda it's fine he'll
live oh wow okay wow all right he
punched me back so you know what we're
even we are even
St even Steven even Steven who's
Steven I know the even freaking weird
freaking weird zombie outside watching
us fall asleep
yeah did anyone pick up The Hoppers or
maybe you need
I'm I have I have your stuff cool do you
I have the Wow Bow Wow Bow oh no the Wow
Bow sorry excuse me yeah I think wow B
sounds nicer
so it's or you say
let's just call a wo bow like wo this is
a bow it's called a bow it's not called
a bow who okay so it's a wo
bow yeah okay oh there's Hoppers missing
and we don't have any
iron I think we should have some iron
missing yeah I only found one hopper no
they they br oh no so recently I split
up an iron block that gave nine iron I
feel like we should be able to make some
more yeah we have 17 ingots so we should
be able to make a couple more yeah let
yeah it's just five per Hopper so we
just need 15 iron and then you put a
chest in the middle if somebody wants to
build it yeah okay sure should I The
Hoppers how many Hoppers do you
need uh we need three three we have a
million chests so just take one we have
a ton of chest yeah oh okay yeah there's
plenty I'll get these trap doors
you got the chest Cena or do I need to
grab some I got the chest I got the iron
I'll leave it you leave it all to you
and uh let me see if I can I want to
mine a little bit I'm going to
mine we we'll find some more
iron Japan
bro okay her shiku well actually if we
make pppp our iron is actually kind of
soft cuz some of the zombies or
something drop iron bars too so oh oh
yeah temporarily we can get more iron
too yeah there's some a lot of good
sides to so I think it's good that we
get
it okay I'm bringing the Hoppers
[Music]
over more iron yo if we could make an
iron farm though that would be amazing
but isn't that really hard to do yeah we
need at least one
villager at least two would be
nice right and I was to get one
yesterday I was like mining endlessly
but they just don't show up they've got
to show up at some point so I'm going to
keep I put the hoppers in the the Sher
box nice thank
you nice
Hoppers hippity hoppity you are now am's
property yeah me yes sir no the hopper
oh oh Kitty see that's a good sign we
got a kitty cat wish you were a a vill
villager but that's
okay new cat
baby more cats is it this white
cats oh I wish I had I wish I had
fish let's go fishing Ena go fishing do
we have a fishing rod there's a fishing
rod we have string to make
one is it is the fishing rod broken the
one we had before uh no there should
still be one
okay bucket of
salmon tight what
thanks TI is that oh is that German yeah
it is it
means oh Health yes just Health be
healthy
dummy can I get your help over here on
this side yes so all the sand fell cuz
the bottom ones o so we got to reput
this sand I got to
give this Panda's freaking pissed at me
may we won't use sand just in case it
breaks again
yeah we got other
blocks we have
Str should be
good 6 hours
later oh there it's car a stick that's
not a fishing Rock oh wait there's a
fishing rod beside it is the top like
blocked off or can I still get like
buildt up there no you can get up there
there's a a letter to get
out
wa wrong block here wait don't start
from the we got to get up
here honestly I feel like I've learned
so much about mft just from this from
doing this even though it's not standard
oh yeah give me one
oh oh like I didn't know about the grass
thing right guys but what grass thing
you know that you need to have like a
grass block connected to dirt that like
leads to the you need to have like one
grass block and then it makes more grass
blocks I didn't know
that Speas at the top I didn't know that
either uh just knock come off I have
like no weapon because you got my things
but I'll try oh yeah I put him I put
them in one of the chests down here when
you back okay is a glistering watermelon
slice bed
oh I'm so sorry that was you're not
allowed to go back up
there banishment she just attracts them
she attracts creepers can't be
helped was there no uh Diamond chest
plate within my things
oh I have it see have it oh let's go
thre it I'm going to take it
off I'm put my diamond chest plate into
the final chest box oh that's a
spoter moner more string give
me to God just die monster what if I
don't ow look you don't have any armor
on you don't have oh
[Music]
no oh no you don't have any armor and
you oh no please have
mercy please oh my god oh thank you
oh you know next time I I see you IRL
I'm going to do the thing where I hold
something high above you and you will
jump and not be able to catch
[Music]
it okay I uh I was trying to fight
something and I fell let me pick up
those EXP M it's okay Watson you're
doing God's work don't worry about it
it's all good we here to assist feel
like there's um there's a lot of
obstacles in the way and uh by a lot of
obstacles I mean
somebody you
mean work space what what do you mean
what nothing nothing it's fine we're
doing good it's a hard head Zone not a
hard head Zone hi
cat all right
I shouldn't die again but I'm going to
fall to pick up my stuff oh well it's
gone ah I took it the it wasn't really I
think yeah you're diamond armor is in
the other one I
you oh you can't eat it okay I can't see
you I can't go where are you point
then wait I have your helmet too
wait I took a different helmet thank you
that's actually I think that is possibly
not even my helmet but yeah okay T
please if you put torch under sand it
breaks automatically
oh
speed
H how are you supposed to get it
underneath the sand cuz it keeps falling
good question yes yes go for the fish
fish yummy fish where the bone meal
go we have no bone
meal maybe somewhere in some chest still
I can't see the cat guys Kelly Kelly
Kelly in your light colors chest cuz I
see the water them there than light
colors there's nine bone blocks that you
can turn into bone meal oh okay cool
yeah know that's supposed to be end
chest but I guess you don't get those
things in the end never mind yeah like
the sandstone
was just your light colors chest
whoopsies okay chy chicks uh it's time
you know it's time there's many orders
all made by me
so oh hey I can stuck in my head with
this okay never
mind
okay myth is hungry dang it feed us I'm
oh no I just keep falling all
right the temporary
brid sorry kfp love you though love you
right you know I love you
right I'll also get this
CLE are you I can save I need seeds why
are they running gr gr why are they
trying to
escape I'll get you out of there C I got
to leave in 20
minutes has it already so long maybe
Le it farewell how long has it been 2
hours oh God it's getting dark again
okay uh
SLE Tores do you need any okay take your
time let me know when it's ready for
sleepy
time well stuff will spawn while we're
sleeping right yeah probably
but yeah I'll put
torches I mean if you leave if there's
no water it'll just
burn oh yeah but the creepers don't burn
do they do creepers burn uhuh uh
wait do they not I've seen them walk
around during daytime yeah they don't
they don't
burn and spiders also don't burn I think
I got framed for a chicken Mas yesterday
what did I do yeah well y I was like you
know slaying some chickens to get
feathers and then the chat uh like I
can't see the AI chat thingy but the
chat told me that the AI was saying that
Mory K be brutally murdered the chickens
and that's why the isad
I had nothing I mean if it died it
probably had something to do with it but
not the way that are trying to make it
seem like it oh my God it's not me are
you girls in bed someone stole my bed
what who keeps on whistling by the way
what the birds yes the birds so
loudly are you waiting for me yes
just dropping some eggs really quick
wasn't
okay no no God damn it chicken
chicken are chaotic okay I'm here oh let
me take a
picture when when morning comes I need
all of your guys' help to just finish it
quickly that way we can
okay we shall
do all right team why you got to do
cson uh we're going to connect all the
corners to make to right now it's like a
cross right but we're going to connect
the corners to make like a big
platform and then uh yeah so we'll need
a lot of stacks for that we have
materials wood right I'm going to stay
we should have enough materials just
don't use sand cuz it's going to fall
wood someone use
sand well probably not wood ah
okay yeah we can make here though
Cobblestone
right uh no not slabs I think it to be
full BLX
yeah
thought is it safe up there right now
okay hey what's the percentage drop rate
for apples guys okay low we just got to
wait so we got to make it into a
platform yeah so connect the corners
like uh like here I'll do like a little
sample like this all the way to the next
corner and then fill it
in yeah oh the
window right we'll get to planting
then you good to go by you're trying to
say
something no no no
no oh
if if anybody has uh if somebody could
go down and make more cuz I I ran out of
platform or um trap doors I don't know
where they went the rest of them oh I
got some oh okay yeah we need to put
them back make some more well it was a
full Stacks I don't know probably like
30 okay I got you am I'll make them now
I'm already here okay thank you
yeah let's see okay doors teamwork all
the wood I can find
[Music]
cute 30 or
so
okay trapo
cute piure
time
okay what did you photograph us I you
have more blocks without my consent
there should be more down there uh
I'm going to sell
it to the highest bidder did you get my
double chin you might need more no I
took it from quite above so it should be
flattering
okay don't worry I'm also worried about
my double
chin make a one it it doesn't matter
what kind of wood it is right
Amy uh no okay
AIA
AIA stop stop that okay B whatever it's
called paparia paparia Pizza papaz
Pap what
else uh okay we're just waiting on trap
doors and then hold on I'm watching the
rest of the video to see what he does
thanks it looks so beautiful looks
so patchwork this whole island is
Patrick all right I'm going to just like
us
y all right so now we're we're doing the
wall it's going to be two blocks high so
if you have more blocks we're do this
more oh I didn't bring any
uhoh yeah go down
too I think maybe maybe an apple will
drop I've almost got enough we got 21
trap doors I'm just chopping some wood
because we do not have enough wood
I
thought I'm Mory I'm great at Anil sorry
that's
wrong what I feel I I made a one to
early I think I'll replant
them
okay I just want to see if we can get an
Apple just one apple get those apples
those apples
oh I guess we leave opening there yeah
it seems like it okay I got to help so
that should be
enough an
opening do we need the openings oh wait
maybe
not no we we'll close it all yeah I just
need you get
yeah okay so I have 30 but it's 10 of
each different type of wood so it's not
really consistent but it's enough
it doesn't matter cool I'm coming it's
crazy how much more efficient y'all have
gotten at Minecraft compared to when
myth first started yeah we Pros we're
pro Gamers now we' got better okay so
now we're going to seal it but it's
going to be like this hold on like this
and then we don't we don't need this
extra block up here really doesn't want
me to okay guys how do we swim it's
shift right you guys can start building
off of mine if you want to you don't to
put another block I'm going to get
blocks hold space sorry sorry thanks
guys but yeah I was such a noob I played
Minecraft for the first time after I
joined Hol for the first time I think I
played Minecraft before but it was back
in like what
N or something really really early
Minecraft here you
go Pocket
Edition I have another Quest For You c
yeah let me know what do I need I need
more torches to light up above the what
we're building right now I got it oh
yeah I'll
gra here mind you can go up top for now
and just put the Torches down up there
here I'll drop them just light up the
what we're building right now like what
we're putting down that way stuff
doesn't spawn up top this Pocket Edition
on the iPod Touch
[Music]
ouch I watched recently where somebody
got uh Minecraft running on a
calculator no way yeah that was the
first time heard a Minecraft zombie and
I
cried sced me so bad that's cute I never
had an
iPod a
jelly
oopsie see torch I only had normal MP3
players the ones with the USB a lot of
torches it's okay we'll never be low on
torches again
do you want to know how many torches I
made many I made about 400 wow what are
you doing I don't know if we need that
many so we'll never need torches again
they're all in the wood they're in the
wooden box but I'm going to give some to
Amy okay I'm out of blocks
again call said how many yes when you go
down there can you can you close up on
the back of the at the bottom yeah you
know that one there's like one
uh wall that the tall wall That's not
finished yet okay it needs to be
finished and then check it out
yeah ah that one
okay okay here you
go here your torches oh two walls
actually thank got a few more blocks
actually we're out of let me build up
once
again yeah yeah no wood it's okay it's
okay I'm getting something else Quest
failed
successfully what the apple quest too
many but that's okay oh no no no the
Torches yeah I did make too many don't
finish it all the way cuz
uh uh should we okay no it's okay I
don't think stuff will spawn in here
hopefully not well I guess I'll make it
fancy put some torches for now
okay all right now apple
quest it's going to be so
colorful should have had should have
made the whole thing in those fancy
terracotta
blocks oh yeah I don't think we had
enough though yeah he okay I'm going to
make the back side like that um just
going to wait
for just needs to finish there's like
a here l uhhuh
you see there's like one wall That's not
there's like two walls that aren't
finished down
there oh boy
I'm sorry it's okay it's okay it's okay
nothing much has been destroyed uh the
chest and Hoppers are still there yes
yes that's what's important I thought he
would you know die in the water such was
not the case okay all right well we just
need to finish the yeah those tall walls
down there I'm on it I'm on it I'm on it
I'm on it okay upstairs is
lit light on your on your way up there's
like one that's halfway built if you
could finish that one too I'm on it
okaying the and then we'll be done
pretty much here you guys probably want
to move out of the way cuz I'm going to
start putting well actually I'll wait
till she's done to put the water so she
doesn't well oh no no do it now funny
you won't die water right oh wait k look
look to your left there's I don't know
if you can reach it but there's like a
little Gap there oh okay I can reach
that too oh they're watching
wait judged okay I do a good job
watching there's one more one more
block trash on
me oh another one yeah there we go nice
and then I don't know how you're going
to get down uh good look fly I won't be
able to place these last blocks though
cuz like I need to I think we can place
it you shouldn't die if you drop from
here I don't think oh we me let me get
over there first in the middle and then
I'll like replace it and you don't have
a pickaxe nope oh wait maybe now I do
I oh
thanks I'll go here and
then and then I guess I'll die I have
ligh here no no no here I guess I'll
die that works that was a really genuine
guess I'll die jump bye wait did you put
a ladder
I you can dig out just uh I'm just
waiting for the death the death text to
come up at the bottom all right if you
guys want to get up here cuz I'm going
to we'll take out the Torches but now
I'm going to put the water so don't want
to get in the way oh it's night time and
do I sorry whoopsies I'm going to mine
my way out and then I'll fix
it
yeah wait wait don't take the Torches
out yet not yet oh sorry sorry sorry
sorry no not a single go dog on oh okay
okay okay wait
chest are they in the
chest no okay I'll bring some should I
use shears on the trees you guys shears
no it doesn't work for apples like uh
shears are the most efficient to get rid
of leaves but it will not drop apples
when you do that I see so I should just
use other random things yeah just a a
sword your bird is up here me yeah Bye
Bird Bye it's go
wait it should the water shouldn't be
flowing all the way down I don't know
why it's doing
that we can sponge it up
maybe yeah oh if you bring up some
spudge use a
hole which chest is the Spong I can find
it I can find it but I'm just replacing
the chest really quickly break it just
as fast oh creeper creeper watch out no
this
Sil we got to put the torch down over
there
St we got to put torches down up
[Music]
top oh oh it's okay it's not it's not
too bad it killed my parot oh oh there's
zombies just log out just log out I
understand I'm out you know going to log
out and then should I go to sleep okay
I'm out yeah everybody else just go to
sleep sorry just got an apple
okay are we good oh no bird dead oh no
all the parrots are like going instinct
Dead all right I'm going to sleep Simon
Watson's
bed
Instinct that's not how you say it in in
English okay you're good you guys can
come
back we can come back extinct extinct
are we good mhm morning probably going
to be mobs there still oh yeah oh yeah
it's
working zombie zombie be like two apples
I'm starting to get apples
nice all right she on that Apple yeah
she love apples we just got to finish
this wall again and uh need sponge cuz I
don't know why the water actually I
don't need sponge I just
yeah o
drown drop that trident baby come on oh
yeah one of these
days I think do we need extra blocks to
fix the
ceiling uh I might need a couple more
blocks I have a couple but I don't think
it's
enough yeah I can go get more wait I
have I have uh some maybe this is enough
nah it's not enough okay I'll go grab
some
okay who died up there di oh yeah bird
why' you bring your bird up here he
followed me oh
no well now he'll never follow you
again rub Sal in the wound block of
should be enough I think I don't see
anything is it
gone gone oh so if I farm the wood the
leaves drop the stuff on their own like
apples and whatnot oh okay I didn't know
that we do need more wood we're going to
have some colorful
ceilings
yeah oh
oops it got picked up yeah yeah yeah
yeah what you doing goall oh I should
this one SI I didn't want to go over the
edge but it uh yeah
oops okay yeah hopefully I'm going to
try plug this hole here
no what is it hole it
SP uh not yet hold on
okay I left the Hole by the ladder so
you can get up
here sponge oop found the sponges all
water but do we have to place a sponge
at the source or just no no no I don't
we don't need it it's okay hey SpongeBob
spam cob SpongeBob spam cob
SpongeBob German version
spam yeah let's go how oh in English
it's Square Pants right in German sham
cop means um sponge head
oh SpongeBob SP uh could you close up
did you close up this water I have trap
doors like just put blocks here to get
rid of the
water oh my Lord
Bob what where are we putting blocks to
get rid of the water where top no no no
don't worry you know just got
it all right I have some blocks oh I'll
take these
okay B
Spong sponges Bob
you in practicing German I'm fine I'm
just
TI cool no feel continue continue to
prac this is probably like 5 minutes
away from being done and then wait I
must I must
leave I must make my grand exito
no wait
gooa let me sing to you
[Music]
quick
SpongBob there you go that was for you
sp thank
you okay that was good
y night see you
later are we getting rid of torches are
we getting rid of them yeah we could
just make a bridge like
this how
can I think we're done let's go do we
need this wood down here maybe you can
get of it now so I'm going to have that
empty chest
here and the one
below actual wood not just wooden is
there something below okay no there was
a hole but okay we're good all right uh
she go place okay here yeah yeah I have
enough to seal it
okay okay I think we
have all right should be
done yay
fine now we can Farm
exp thanks for working on that guys
random stuff let me check the rest of
the video just in
case what about this water though it's
going to go away yeah it's going it's
going
down there's one chapor that's not
closed
what should we
check what what was it chat says there's
one chapter that was not closed but not
sure
I thought I closed there's one what that
was there already stuff there uh I mean
chap well it's working I don't want to
go up there yeah it's it's working fine
[Music]
creepy are they going to be not
exploding okay uh they shouldn't I don't
know good good oh yeah oh we can get gun
pow from here and then with the gun
powder wait wait back up back up back up
bombs and with the TNT I can get us some
um never
Rod wait I don't know why they're
exploding or not exploding but they
they're like making the noise that
they're going to
explode are we saying can we put a trap
door maybe and then like put it
up I don't know I think it's okay cuz I
I I uh I think it was just seeing us cuz
we were too low
oh
okay not working this there's so many of
them w we get a lot of bows
[Music]
too this is going be super helpful oh
get away oh so scary but it seems
fine just make sure you're not make sure
you're not standing on the Rock but
actually on the yeah
nice ah the carpets are gone are the
carpet supposed uh are carpet supposed
to be there on there yeah H where did
those go I have them in my inventory
where' they go well oh I can place them
in the on I can
try
difficult difficult but it's working
without them what the carpet's
for I think it's just supposed to help
like push in the fall or make it look
nicer
a it's kind of difficult from this
angle uhoh I think I hit you
sorry no I think it was the it felt like
it was I'm pretty sure it was me okay
damn damn it's
crazy so um maybe no carpet is fine
maybe oops Dad do we need the carpet
it it's working really
[Music]
nice oh carpet is for the EXP to not
drop into the
hopper oh and so creepers don't see you
when
explode is better enemies are higher and
don't see you as
easily okay so it's like two two
different me how are we even going to
fix it I don't even think we can right
now all right maybe here here you keep
somebody keep H give me the carpet
oh
witch yeah from the higher angle you you
could place it probably we can get
really good weapons now cuz of the EXP
Farm
yeah we can get the EXP and then enchant
things yeah I it oh you put you put a
carpet up above okay all all four I did
no I got rid of it I got rid of it oh
okay yeah I think we got it nice nice
completion good job thank you Amy for
leading us through it yeah thank you for
your help actually I think we should
block off the side a little bit because
there is a chance we get hit and then
fall off which side like the just on the
side like here on the on above the uh or
we can just put fences cuz yeah yeah
yeah oh okay come check for apples
later you naming this
one
uh uh I don't know chat do you guys have
any ideas spider
claw oh it's
spiders
[Music]
oh okay something dropped
nand
n yeah I saw in the video they said you
can put um like carpets inside to stop
too many spiders from spawning oh I
don't know oh pretty I like the design
work p should you want to call it PPP
ppp2 or pip
or um put myth mob maker somebody
says mob M M M I feel like it's hard to
say previously Lost am's Property you
guys just want to say p l a p no M
what's m come on please MIT mob maker
okay M mob maker I like mm cute I like
it it's just ours no one else is well it
was working great until the other day
weo oh nice maybe they'll despawn if we
go away yeah let's see back
yeah goodness for that Yay good job
everyone nice job team yay oh yeah we
should add that power three enchantment
to the Bodacious bow true I've got
enough
exp all right sleepy
time things have gotten a bit
disorganized here though so I might need
to fix
that I kind of want to make an
enchantment table but we would need
books to to make a powerful right M
probably but it's it really that hard to
find but leather I feel like is not too
hard to find well we have plenty of
leather cuz we have our cows and stuff
we can breed and then you know but it's
a paper take them out of this I haven't
really gotten any paper like things yeah
how do you make paper I had like three
pieces of
paper that's it here it's working cie
look I'm test it oo y my turn ooh okay
I'm excited go reap some Souls G yeah
yeah yeah I've been waiting for this oh
there's a bunch of them just don't
Crouch when you're hitting them cuz the
creepers might see you a gotcha so so
don't Crouch gotcha yeah oh there's so
many time to die
dummies oh there's so many there's so
much that we can get she's reaping oh my
god well I think uh they saw me all
right this is I there there goes the xp5
waited no we'll fix it and as long as we
just like stay get out get out just get
out just get out just get out just get
out oh no I hit Watson oh God it's it
never ends we we just got to as long as
we were like one step away and and
killing them it was fine so we're just
going to you know safy I don't think we
can fix it because don't you dot dot dot
me it should it should be able to you
should going to keep spawning it's okay
it's okay call close that's how it's
supposed to work so it's okay it's a
design
flaw Power Defense game now I'm glad I
tested it before someone else hurt thems
okay well what we can do is block off
the area and then just like build kind
of around it so we can hit them from AF
far that's the best we can do if they
keep spawning yeah but somebody has to
go in and like fix like we we can block
it and then I can fix it if can get
blocks in there to seal it but they're
going to be constantly
spawning yeah oh I have no arrows that's
why
the sure are a lot of them it should be
one XP uh or one HP one HP I mean this
is one way to farm XP right a different
way all right just every oh here uh who
here I'll Trust Ena to come in and uh
fight them cuz they're one HP I just
need to get in there and put block
on my
way yeah
B all right what are we
doing Sho you a shield yeah I yeah yeah
I got to get in there so just go and
we'll kill them there should be one HP
except for the spiders creeper it's okay
they're they're low okay
okay probably get one hit
go all right just keep keep getting them
as they fall I'm I got to seal it it's a
shooting range yeah all right all right
it's it's sealed for now it's sealed for
now oh we not okay okay we good I wonder
yeah is it supposed to be kind of lower
do you do you think um like cuz I feel
yeah they saw me and I was like as I saw
them I was like oh I bet they can see me
but it was too late well we'll fix it
one
hoer I think it was working fine when we
were standing like one or two steps
behind like further
behind maybe put like a fence or
something so we can't get too close
by
yeah yeah okay here's the limit where
you
should no
can't that was good stream
console well it was my turn to blow it
up and everybody had blown it up before
yeah we did it exploded up several times
in the process wor bonding
experience uh I need the Hoppers but I
don't know where they went I think
they're gone no again
destroy I bet we have I I had one so I
put it
in okay I'll see if I can find another
one I need like a slab or
something I have 60 free slabs if you
need them I just needed it to
two IR only
two well let's see is there ore and
we've only got two iron but let me see
if I can find some
more iron block would be nice come on
Minecraft Gods we really been testing
the team today give us an IR
block yeah there's a hole in the side
it's up there like get
it let see
see up there up there
[Music]
oh oh got one y I think I placed
it oh cuz there's a slap okay I see now
hold up I'll just wait
Clos this is Thea feather falling four
nice that's really good then oh it's
loud uh so if we put Gates right here
well we need we need to make more
Hoppers I don't know if we have any more
yeah it's okay we we'll work on that
we'll just leave this for now and then
yeah I'll find more
iron uh we'll fix it carpet is
easy yeah yeah there's there's a block
right above so we can't put the carpet
there
yet okay let's just go get the uh just
need the Hoppers and then put
the put the uh should we get rid of it
not yet not yet you just need the
Hoppers and then we can fix it up okay
okay well yeah leave it for now iron
iron
iron we thought it was finished but we
finish it a second time yeah and new and
improved yeah oh yeah we learn you know
it it's okay slow and steady all work
slow and steady it do win the
race oh oh know where El I'll mine a
little bit to see yeah well the box is
full right now um cuz I was trying to
find some iron this the one thing
there's so much stuff obviously we're
going to get so many blocks we don't
need
mhm need like two fences or three fences
that we can make it safer but we don't
have any wood
wait we don't have wood we should have I
just farmed a bunch of wood actually um
I'm going to put it there's a a storage
chest um I have see which one is it in
here I'm putting all the wood put in the
wood chest here iron trap doors are more
durable and can handle a Creeper
explosion guys there's a problem with
that we need
iron yeah we don't what do they mean
like cuz we already finished the top
part we don't that's not a problem then
floing up there there's no trap IR we
can't really make our trap doors yeah
that's the main
thing that's why we got to make an IR
need a Viller we need a villager please
if we could get a villager that would be
a game
Cher only two villagers that's the game
changer two yeah need to get lucky
twice yeah
it's okay we'll we'll we'll be fine in
the end yeah we'll be fine you just both
yeah we'll just need to get some iron
from freaking
sponge I
got does this also drop
water bow is
awesome let's see trying to use up some
exp before I inevitably die use it all
what is that all right I'm look for more
apples for now I'll let you guys do the
M I really should organize those so they
can do more mining please pleas
Ka please oh
yeah oh yeah whoopsies I am carrying a
lot right now ah one
moment let's
see sorty op
sorty all right
here's my
dirt let's see cute pe oh PE well that's
kind of nice cuz we don't have any pigs
oh let me out of there then come on come
on yeah good
job good job who's a good piggy you are
yeah you
are I'm not sure if I can drag this into
here
you need help or is it too full yeah if
you can get like if you can grab like a
wheat or something and then like drag
them or leave them was cut off but I
think as you said wheat yeah just just
bring the cows to the other side so they
don't come on follow
me yeah they seem they seem too thick to
escape
anyway okay we sure do all right we're
good we got the pig
oh freaking random ass zombie oh but
this one's did you come from the nether
oh I think it
did oh oh no so I'm going to introduce a
new mechanic we're going to have a chest
that you guys put things that we don't
need in there like rotten flesh and such
and then I'll take it and I'll throw it
off the side when it's
full yep that's what we're going to
do free gold
more gold for
example I don't know where to put
it here so if you don't if you want to
throw things away into one of the
Sorting chests oh wait I can't throw it
off the side never
mind you can't unless it was a Sher box
such a dummy yeah just put it in the
Sorting chest it's fine okay it would be
such a good idea though or trash can
this is why I wanted to make a trash can
we can't though we can't because that
would be Iron soft M and everything
that's fine they can visit
us let's see visitation hours are
currently open you don't want it just
throw it off the
side guess high
is five five iron per Hopper right me
15 more sorted
[Music]
put it next to sand then remove the sand
o that's a really good idea actually for
a trap can I love cuz we have a
gazillion chests like too
many iron please please show
yourself the good thing is that at this
point where it's All Phases combined
sometimes there's iron blocks like iron
blocks yeah just like how there's iron
Emeral blocks sometimes so you know we
can get lucky sometimes there's always
that
possibility feel like my inventory is
very full even though I'm dumping
everything
[Music]
SEC
okay no don't put that in there
[Music]
one
one although the more we mind the more
pickaxes we're going to use going to
just mine with stone pickaxes I guess oh
I've just been doing that unless there's
a like block that's hard to get
M yeah it's definitely the best way I'll
do it too after this one
breaks get a standand
all right making a trash can we're going
to try out wait is so wa maybe chat was
saying that instead of carpet we put
trap
doors I don't know if that has the same
function on top of the hopp
first I guess the trap doors are a
little bit higher Maybe not maybe
Sandstone they're a little bit higher so
I suppose they would we we would be
lower but I don't know if that really
you know helped
yeah unless it's iron of
course but we have so many fancy blocks
but no iron so much terracotta and okay
diamonds are nice that that egg yeah
what was
that it's like a zombie something egg
not here what was that I want to
see drop just throw things off the side
use this as fuel I'm trying to trying
desperately to make a trash can I need
to just give up all right uh let's
see what was that hold
on I think it was like a zombie
something egg oh I got it zombie zombie
villager spawn
egg I mean we could track hearing it but
we would need like a potion of weakness
or something and then a golden
apple we have plenty of golden apples
but we need a push of weakness side side
quest side quest side quest get the
potion of weakness the spawner we it
spawns several of them no just one okay
but then let's say let's spawn it in a
safe environment in the air G
be okay I'm going to put this in the
precious goodies chest sick just hold on
to it twist I didn't know they included
these blocks or items it was in the
chest so like I guess the chest can
spawn extra special things let's go
let's go let's go nice one is a game
changer there the trash in the nether
that's also possible
iron I'm cooking one
[Music]
IR diamond and gold I mean if we found
the uh if we found the like a normal
piglin we could have totally tried to
have uh traded gold for iron bars and
stuff but
[Music]
we
yeah thanks yeah those piglins all those
kind of yucky like all of them were
messed up yeah they're kind of
dead
groy oh this a random
chest
okay yes are you okay I'm stretching oh
cute stretch sounds nice right about now
oh more sugarcane
stretch we finally got sugar cane all
the game changes the game is changing
forever
now let's go this game will never be the
same now that you f those we can ench
enchanting
table eventually but you know there's
some work that leads up to
that ah sponge stole the water yeah I do
happening often it do be happening often
cannot speak Engish finally sugar cane
let's go we can make pumpkin pie too
yeah
exciting y Let's go
Team a win for us finally at
last it's it's the it's the bad one it's
the bad
one oh yikes okay um he's dead good job
but the the vexus are still around all
right we got to kill
him chickens protect me hey dummies come
over
[Music]
here nice thank you kfp got it for being
my
more man got your Stu sorry I Pi up come
here
no where you go yo why is he allowed to
just face through the freaking
floor I have TR oh there he is okay can
I have
my need pickax and sword pretty much I
think this is your
sword and then did you have an iron
pickaxe cuz I also have okay here you go
you can just have it and then thank you
you
go else Granite oh here's your
granite and your torches
oh thank you that one is so I didn't get
okay I'll just make a stone pickaxe oh I
gave you I gave you an iron
one no I didn't it didn't go oh it
didn't hey where'd it go then no that
was okay I just I'll just make a stone
one oh wait I have your iron one on oh
you picked it up I have a block of iron
I have a block of iron nice got
nine I love that we're celebrating wait
what happened to the water that's what I
really like about this game mode because
we we start from the simplest things
again and you know we can't just use all
these farms in Jaan I'll cook these two
IR
or okay how many is that 14 oh we just
need one more
for a hopper yeah I wonder if we can
decompose the iron horse armor that' be
nice that would be cool if you could
break it down you can do that with our
own armor but not with the armor of the
horses
yeah
sad oh yeah it would have only been a
nugget H I love nuggets but not those I
me still it's more than
something
yeah also cuz we do have some other iron
nuggets
probably need to check these more often
these
trees Tre
Tre how long does it take for the apples
to despawn if they fall I wonder long
long long minutes oh no oh despawn oh
despawn may be not so long oh I see keep
an eye on it check mhm okay I'll start
with
those maybe this one
5 minutes okay I'll be careful I'll keep
checking on him wait this used to be a
stone box what the
hell all right now I'll put
wood actually I'll make a chest that's
just wood from the
forest okay
now the sponges shouldn't take the water
I think
oh another Improvement
made yeah
shees what did
you how did you do it might need some
bread I just put more trap doors and put
the water block a little bit
[Music]
higher oh oh
iron we can fix the fix the
Hoppers yay
okay guess I need to break some of these
leaves down all right I'll make them oh
we already have enough we already had 16
oh wait really I thought we had 14
math y math is all good math is hard for
myth always has
us math math class with myth we released
an English language book before now
we're going to release a math class book
oh
yes oh is there any oh wait we can
already make a potion of weakness cuz we
already have fermented spider egg or
spider eye oh yeah what you mean oh but
we need a yeah yeah but we need a potion
making thing I don't know what that
requires oh like a potion table po
mixing table or something what is it
called h h maybe I should make a fence
around the uh around the forest I wasn't
really holding anything important I
don't think a brewing
stand oh we can totally make one okay
yeah what did you lose key uh I think
the only important thing I was holding
was maybe two apples which is is too bad
but is what it is
Dam
cob a couple of chests too oh well all
right let's start make some new
things it's not like we don't have
materials to make new things yeah
okay cob
Stone so I got a cool potion that gives
plus one luck very cool yes all right it
was just two apples do we have any uh
carpet or wool to make carpet oh there's
carpet in the uh sheler
chest I should put some in there okay
okay thank
you okay okay make the brewing
stand
nice put I
here okay we have
glass oh have
glass Kelly were you still wearing the
diamond armor no I put it away okay cuz
I think way to just in case no I put
mine away don't worry okay but it was a
good reminder for me to put mine away
too yeah
can happen at any time I don't know
where mine went
water it's somewhere for sure for sure
probably yeah I just put it in the final
chest that we're taking to the the last
battle I've been hoarding stuff yeah
good idea I'll put it there too and the
golden
hel make we have the Apple see I already
get new
apples where's the Sheep I need like two
more
fermented spider ey to water bottle it's
the only potion I can without
Nether I'm so excited Ena I'm so excited
oh hey we got a potion maker oh wait we
need to
get no problem we should have some we
got that
[Music]
covered okay and then I to make it a
splash potion
M I learned recently how to make potions
too gun powder we got gun powder from
the the creeper I don't know I a little
bit
yeah I I
put there's how many do you need there's
four here oh okay here
those thank
you are there children playing outside
please be quiet and
I'm so excited I'm so excited this is
not how I expected to get a villager but
it's it's a cool way where are we
putting the Villager in the in that
house you built okay
yeah I'm making sure they can't get out
right yeah yeah we'll close it off okay
we got three of them so if we happen to
have more down the line we can use it do
you want to make it now or do you want
to
wait I I want us to make it now
as soon as possible need golden apple
right we have plenty go check the final
chest behind the uh the chicken C cuz we
can already give him a job right and
then we can already have him start
working on we can actually give him a
job that gives us iron trade with
Emerald oh yeah yeah
yeah it's it will be the the the problem
solver for
everything when if we can get enough
iron we can change his job to much more
things they can open doors can they open
fence gates I think so the farmers do
that right no do they open
them what's a good way to do
this they buy iron they don't give iron
am I thinking of like the merchant ah oh
okay we'll put it in a boat the merchant
e oh I have a boat if we put him in a
boat is he going to restock them not
going to make we we can put him in the
boat for temporarily just to fix scks
okay okay I think we have more sticks
let's
see are you are you here Kara are we
doing it I am wait wait
wait yes I'm so
here all okay let's
go that should be enough let's find
out Co cool he already has a job does he
wait wait they they kind h
hard okay and then you want to get out
of there it's a splash
potion okay and then you cure me from my
then I throw this right guys do it do it
want to see it right
Chad he's a map maker a splish lame job
okay I also got weakness and then Golden
Apple wo oh Magic oh he's evolving he's
shaking he needs a hug my gosh you
called there buddy once you are not a
zombie anymore we'll give you a
hug first stop stop being so
green don't press
B he's dead he's dead oh it may take
free to 5 minutes okay oh oh really okay
we'll just stand here right I mean we
should put we should also get can you
get a name tag just so
y you going to name him yeah what are we
going to name
him
uh I don't know Shrek Wait no that's a
bad idea he won't be green never mind we
don't want we can have a legally
distinct
name that is not
Shrek everything blew up everything ble
up pocket are you
okay what's going on are you
everything's
fine don't worry about it guys oh no I'm
good okay I made I made I made a
name I need help again the same thing as
before I'm anticipating can try to fix
something small and then uh you got you
guys watch over the Villager I'll watch
him I'm a good
babysitter I'll I'll make another axe
cuz mine's kind of like
half durability
oh he's ging me aack he's got a name now
at him what his
name shre Li G can I make it with d and
then we we should make another one and
also call that one shre oh so we can
have
shreds shre together yeah
shre love shreds come on get over it
already walk it off walk it off shre
look at him come on oh I like his mon
he's fancy [\h__\h] boat yeah get him
shant good idea shant hey that was Chad
not
me okay they'll have shreds together you
ready I'm ready I just need to seal it
off again so need one
more
training I will kill what's there and
then
oh I want to see both what I do what I
do and I want to see
both
oh sh creeper watch
out also there's a piglin oh they're
falling off right now got to seal off
something a piglin no yeah oh that oh
creeper creeper oh
yeah oh even if it loads chunks does not
load people I wonder uh there's a hole
there on the side
shoot it's okay just keep keep at it
keep at
it come on do something they're not
taking as much damage uh falling Keep
Falling on the
sides he looks like he's really
struggling I'm going to go get some soup
oh that's a lot he's super constipated I
bet he's going to trans my G I know we
need to back up it's
fine yeah might need to eat come back
yeah go get your mushroom mushroom % off
go get it now okay fall back fall back
all right Retreat Retreat Retreat I was
able to fix some of it but I couldn't
see it all the way
okay I guess I'll borrow a bow and some
arrows I can shoot down the creepers
from the side
power three she's a regular B he's
nervous that's okay he's got performance
anxiety I killed some of
them not while people are watching it's
a freaking Battlefield damn crazy it's
okay just give him a minute girls if you
need help let me know yeah I think we're
good I got it all right yeah
okay you think it really work
for sure yeah it's the because he has
the swirly fers around it
worked can we it's okay it's okay a damn
it why not the other way around don't
let me out no leave bed I want to talk
to
shre but he's got to change his job hold
on I ran out of uh stuff to seal it with
I need to work how to make it what job
shall we give ready I think the armor
would be ni we can still switch his jobs
afterwards he noice though he's got to
get
better well now yeah his his uh current
job is kind of useless you good I'm a
all right no I'm going to die oh you
can't change the I can't change the
job okay I
can't there's like one hole on the left
I got to seal up but walks into a job
they
say when we can
help um like in the
back of Pap oh wait if we trade with him
you can't
tring okay but so you're saying now I
can still change it once and then once
we start trading we can't anymore so now
we can yeah we haven't traded with him
what's the tool again for armor um
makers what's the work table
thingy what was it a blast oven probably
needs iron right all right uh we need to
go around the back I got to seal up the
left side all right maybe if you if you
go in the front like on the left you
where the see where the purple blocks
are on the left side yeah and then I'll
go around on the other side to seal it
maybe if I make that it will teach me
how to make a blast some triming got get
the creepers
first I need
some there we go
[Music]
there was a lot more than I
thought that seems not
good wait was mine
defeated okay I was blowing up so my
stuff should be around
uh I had a totem of life but I blown off
I was blown off the edge
damn okay we didn't lose that much stuff
it's just like junk that we lost at
least for
me
okay wait was Ena wearing the diamond
armor was I don't know if it's still
there cuz I technically was blown up by
a creeper and then could still be
there yeah hopefully first Death Watch
there's just like one hole that they
keep coming out of that I need to like
seal it but I can't get to it
M M M it should be at the base of the
farm if it didn't fall off already how
do you make it into a blast furnace
[Music]
oh there's a skeleton over here smoo
Stone void claims another not feeling so
good get him
what's up oh I heard where did that come
from where did that come from that
didn't sound good there yeah there's
like stuff spawning back here somewhere
oh I think I know where it
is looking for Cobblestone oh here I
have
torches I think it's back
here I'll be be okay okay
things haven't spawned here in a while
so
Wonder bring cat against creeper can we
bring
cat guess could it' be nice to have a
cat sitting by those chests cuz that's
where they everything spawns right there
I I think I fixed it cuz there was uh
one block behind the wall that didn't
have torches
I got
it ding yeah bone meal guys sorry I lost
the bone
meal invisibility
potion o would that
work one potion of night vision and a
fermented spider we don't we don't have
any more fermented spider this how do
you make ferment too can you make fer
spider
eyes a like if you have a regular one
one
maybe regular spider eye and then do
something to
it yeah Brown mushroom sugar and spider
eye oh we have brown mushroom I remember
I bought some from the from the nether
plate oh
yeah oh yeah we have seven or eight okay
so we can make this and we got sugar
from the sugar cane
now nice
cool okay and then spider
eye I'll just go over there with some
blocks and like a you know like kind of
like a suicide
mission invisibility potion and some
blocks and I'll just seal it up okay and
then potion of invisibility finish the
fight need a potion of night vision
which
is
uh potion of
[Music]
Vision nether war and one golden carrot
we do have golden carrots right yeah we
do yeah we do if you check the chest
behind the chicken C
so one nether w we have lots of nether
W sand oh we do need more water bottles
fall W up you be
quiet need
one okay we'll make three three just in
case we need more layer
down
[Music]
three and
then three NE
wart makes awkward potion and then we
add the golden
carrot was it was it uh glow stone
powder that made it last longer I think
so
right no we have plenty of that if so
yeah you know for the extra
cautious you know stay stay invisible
longer oh yeah oh glowstone amplifi oh
it's Redstone that makes it longer okay
okay we have plenty of those too oh
plenty of both of those yeah
somewhere there's redst Des here a lot
of chests around okay okay we
got got award potion so we add golden
carrot the awkward
potion what the that's a weird name for
something yeah it's a it's pretty
awkward what the heck why would you ever
want eat use that
ocean
Panda hey you when you're invisible oh
uh shoot well I'm going I'm going with
just blocks
and that's all oh what if what okay I
got an idea since the blocks blocks the
the place you have to block is kind of
up above right so why don't you build a
bridge like up above so the mobs can't
reach you and then you go get to the oh
get to the get to the
hole
Yeah I go
work that's by Archer well we'll have
we'll have
a
uh maybe if I can make a
shield I can tank some of the mobs I was
able to close it except now just the
side parts are are open there's some
side Parts open I was able to close the
bottom cuz that exploded
again um yeah I Can Build a Bridge I'll
just just build a
bridge hunting time you joing an apple
hunt oh I realized I have to go soon the
Apple hunt wait that's not one that's a
be h
come on come
on don't fall off there we go and
now they should start despawning on
their own once I kind of okay I have to
go soon so I'll quickly try and help out
before I go okay uh what do you mean you
try to help out you've been helping out
all along no like like last like get
on the oh yeah stuff you know I'll just
seal it for now and then we'll fix it
another time yeah I dropped um ladders
if you want
to I just need like a form of
Defense yeah okay I still can there's a
ton of them right now so yeah I get
you all good it's cuz they they don't
spawn until you're close enough
for apple apple I have no idea where
it's working
another now we've got
three you are wait what do you
call a lady that has an apple farm and
collects apples isn't there a nice word
for that an apple
farmis no nice your
word an apple
princess
yeah no no that's not what I'm thinking
of I'll figure it out someday okay
anyone in chatard well okay Orchard is
probably the the pro most proper word
for it an
orchard well I guess Arrow would have
been better huh I just got to um get a
pickaxe cuz I I can't get in there to
seal it
okay see this this Forest is really good
okay at least the zombies are burning
once we get here that's good right guys
oh that's a lot of
creep there's more
really good Jesus oh you're swimming I
was swimming for a minute there it's cuz
my Forest is so
Bountiful Apple
Jack they'll also get a ton of wood at
the same time
too
oh I need to make
axxe it's okay at least I brought my
cat yeah y cats keep the creepers away
um a cat's not doing anything with the
creeper yo do your job it's like when
you want your your cat to chase a
cockroach or something in your house and
they won't do it yeah just because you
command them to if you're not there
though they'll do
it oh shoot I forgot to make slabs it's
okay okay sit down here
cat that's more than the pandas are
doing all right it's sealed off for now
so the ones that are here are the last
ones that are going to the one the I
feel like they're still spilling out
from somewhere is this just my
imagination like on the right like where
they're standing uh no they're just
standing there they they can't get they
can't uh fall that far down
okay an
apple you guys still added oh my my God
this is no we're almost done though
we're dead for now this
[Music]
ising okay I'm going to go bring a
bow that's okay it just blew up
[Music]
the Apple no I didn't have any items
that was just uh that was my Suicide
Mission
okay y Apple there's only a really good
bow left oh use it use it it's okay yes
oh my inventory is not full I di with
all the weapons huh maybe I need the
infinity
bow yeah Infinity bow would be good okay
I have one Arrow so I can probably use
Infinity
B you
like yeah no it's destroying everything
maybe we should build it from scratch
again no we don't have to build we did
have to build the base again but yeah uh
everything else should be fine
yeah oh no no no no no no no
are I don't know how there's still
stuff's fall I'm probably going to die
right now but oh no why have you no
mercy why why why that's
cruel there is a hole there is there I
Mission but you know I'm going to there
is a hole yeah see going to why are you
doing
that uh
together we'll like you know snipe
everything wait is the Sher box gone it
blow up I think so oh no this hurts so
bad I want the
Apple this ghost
Apple okay it's been a day full of
different rough Adventures but I'll be
late yeah all the you got to fill
everything in right g a top just a
couple more oh
no I should be yeah it's it's done for
now build it using obsidian we do have a
lot of obsidian not that
many well at least the base
maybe like the first couple of blocks in
the bottom could be obsidian even if
it's obsidian The Hoppers will still oh
yeah the base could be obsidian wait
isn't there still a hole over there we
have to fill that in move it with water
you think that'll work I it's because I
sealed it you see where the Bri Bridges
I sealed it right there Ah that's why
they kept spilling out no no stuff can't
fall past that the hole where the
bridges uh the ones that were here in
this chamber I think they're just um
they were just a lot that had
accumulated
okay yeah yeah all right guess I the
right let's go cat put this apple I mean
do we even need an XP farm for something
I mean it's already finished basically
and there are definitely uses good uses
for it I would say yeah it could be a
temporary iron and bow and stuff
everything yeah and forting does anybody
have a pickaxe I can borrow so I can fix
the base at least a
put pickaxes no oh if if there's
obsidian though we'll need a diamond one
right no I'm not a mining well unless I
mess up if I mess up I need a diamond
we're in trouble here you go well I got
to head out for now
okay bye Ena thanks for
playing
survive we'll try also our our house is
open I don't know oh it's cuz of the
creeper oh yeah hey do you have any
torches Cara um we need put torches Tes
oh wait I got the shulker box guys I got
the shulker
box here you go oh nice okay now I can
leave
my job here is done do you need torches
on me okay
yes thank you
by byee
byebye
okay all right thanks for watching the
stream guys have a
wonderful
okay byebye
[Music]
that