[Music]
n
I
[Music]
a I
n
[Music]
okay I'm
ready oh sorry I that was a oh wow I I
un I unmuted you immediately when the
kiky key stopped oh oh I'm sorry I I
wish everyone could hear
it wait did you do that on
purpose no it was completely by accident
I was trying I was struggling for the I
was struggling to unmute it no problem I
generally always feel so bad about when
I do collabs about doing my Kiki because
it's like a it's a morning call right so
it should be filled with energy but like
I can't just be here and like
K right that's like please do please do
no worries honestly I need a little like
morning cockadoodle D you know to wake
me up cuz right now I'm feeling it and I
have no caffeine in the house woo good
morning
sunshine good morning ladies oh my God
you're dancing morning ladies how are
you that looks really funny yes yeah
is 144p for you too yes oh I'm looking
that bad over
there here let me see one sec it
shouldn't it shouldn't be like
that was good for a minute and then it
was good for a minute I just leave it
like that it's a stylistic choice
Aesthetics okay they're already are
messing with us right now that's why the
streaming quality it'sing mental state
all right I'm going to change it to 720p
instead of 180 oh that's better
yeah no need
to0 yeah yeah I'm going to catch you
720p oh oh there go oh there she go oh
there she go oh are we looking crispy
again crispy oh good fried
chicken wait should I should I stream it
call should I stream it to them um is
that okay are you cool with that I think
I I think I am what color did you use
green and it didn't mess with your
feathers really which green is it can
you tell me like when you go into the
just the default green I got to go back
to the loading screen two seconds
everybody go back to the loading screen
I wanted it looks fine on my stream but
I want it to look good on yours so um
you guys still here though it's the
default I'm not even going to I'm going
to stay on the screen but I'm just going
to hide uh our bodies maybe let's see
let's see let's see
the the B hide the B wait my my brain is
just really slow right now so okay wait
so GRE that green never works for me
though I'm surprised you say that works
oh my it's just the
default just the default green do even
my do do even my my my feathers look
good to you yeah okay one on my side as
well one second I'm first we need what's
happening um they're trying to they're
trying to do some stuff and some stuff
chy well I
[Music]
mean uh yeah well we're doing some stuff
oh what you know what you know what
that's okay that looks okay that looks
good I think I'm going to stream it to
the
girls okay we can oh yes I know I've got
you
unmuted my sweet sweet Discord John
thank you for existing I don't want to
leave you guys alone what would we do
without you that's all right you don't
need to leave us alone just bring that
sentiment right into the game with I
have to say though my internet is also
not really the bestest you know European
internet is [\h__\h] so
uh how does it look like
girls oh I haven't seen looks good
really for
now Discord likes to lie to us
[Music]
um uhoh are we cre me
again that sounds
bad someday we're all going to be able
to get to the same room I'm telling you
this is that bad
really it's okay everything's fine is it
worse than when cie streamed
it we're not even moving over yeah you
you guys are not moving on my side now
by the way Kelly are they moving on your
side hello
yeah oh maybe because I'm streaming I no
oh wait how does that no you have to
have the you have to have their window
open at all times see here this is the
stuff that we can't actually check
before stream for stuff that happens
literally during the don't wor
about reload it refresh it fine and then
we started streaming n they don't they
don't move for me when I stream to
them now it's just black to
me dead um also Callie stopped moving
for me too uhoh Kelly uhoh Kelly Kelly
Kelly wait a second Kelly is she dead
is De
dead de is
dead well we found their
ghosts all
[Music]
around I find it kind of sad
B Mad World Callie is dead oh she back I
hear
her okay what did you
do sorry are we okay now guys no uh well
we're going to have to work fine okay I
fine okay I think it was better when cie
streamed it cuz I apparently like it's
[\h__\h] and I also don't get the others to
move
anymore Okie doie then leave
try Kelly one more time leave it to me I
got this
boys one second here go live frame rate
is
30 now go we've got time we're just
going to roll with this cuz I want to go
catch some gos I don't let's cat St for
the rest of this street please no it's
time for spooky it's almost Halloween
anyway thanks for coming to our stream
and now we end it just kidding ha just
kidding we're going to play the game now
can you do me one
favor um yes can you end your stream
once and then open it
again
yes wait it's not happening before you
do that yeah before you do that let
Callie go to standby okay go you can do
it now okay okay
okay is everyone ready to see the 144 P
yo it's okay it symbolizes the ghosts
you know when ghosts around technology
doesn't
work that's true G break
technology they don't want us to hurt
them okay yes obviously thank you D from
on the bottom of my COC
doll anytime anything you need this is a
nice
ear what ear ear yeah I have an ear
right in my face you have an ear I don't
know whose it is though WHo's
ear very highly rendered hello hi oh Bae
looking good I'm inside of your head now
I inside of your mouth scary oh here
want to see it again
no check out these moves I can
do so I think the scariest out of of all
of us today is ba like the the one that
who who's the most
scared I don't like ghosts I don't deal
with ghosts okay they ghosts they're in
another dimension I like to live uh the
the Rat Life in this Dimension okay it's
scary can you tell me how you're dealing
with scary games that this thing that
you told me before the Stream
of
OBS how hey hey
I'm tell him tell him ba tell him I
don't look at the game screen when I
play scary games I play the game by
looking at the small OBS screen that's
kind of smart though how small is I
you're coming from on that when it gets
real scary in Resident Evil in the
basement sometimes I've been known to to
look at
OBS what job we should I'm really
surprised that I'm not the the the
biggest chicken in the room and it's ba
actually hey I can play other horror
games kind of not
really paranormal it's just paranormal
stuff that I can't handle oh I see
really yeah by look at these level
should try Resident Evil we're all [\h__\h]
at this
game yeah we're all not very good at it
but we're going to try our best here
options guys we
have yo I have 62 dream what do we need
dreamers we haven't introduced
ourselves we didn't do that doam should
we start from the co eyes the the
councils can go first I'll go first
hello my name is s FAA I am the hollow
council's keeper of Nature and I am
extremely good at all horror games why
did that my
life I didn't click any I'm going to
find all the ghosts thank you very much
WoW confidence confidence
like do anything my I can't I can't get
no are you okay
no maybe it's just five of me and
cie okay okay um what's up everybody
it's B he guys representing chaos from C
so what's up hope you're doing good
um we we stolen I'm going to stole for
as long as I can okay what uh we're
going to catch no ghost today um what do
you don't need to
stop I'm scared okay why did you invite
why did you invite us to play this game
then B because I know you guys like the
game it was B was from Callie's side no
Bae invited me to play uh fmo and you
invited me and she said who would want
to play and I said Kara like okay that's
the team then I know it's because you
like the game and fora likes the game
and I was like who do you mean with you
with the first you who did you mean
Callie yeah oh play a couple times I
think it's fine I've played it a couple
times in the past it's it's spooky I was
like I to sacrifice myself it's good
hallow hallow hallow weeny game wait so
you're saying right now you sacrific
yourself so we can use you today as a
sacrifice for the ghost like a testing
object whenever we need to you know see
if the ghost is going to attack we're
just going to leave you in the room and
we stay in the track yeah we'll close
you in the room that's okay with you
[Music]
right you need to need to Haze the haze
the new the new
girl I'll protect
you the way ba the way Bae is right now
that's how I'm going to be this week
when I play [\h__\h]
Outlast oh that's right that's fun
that's that step up from phasmophobia
I'm so not looking forward to it it's
the worst thing that's happening to me
this whole
year yeah it's pretty rough I two
screamed a couple times playing that
game M yeah who's nextar you want to
take it away of course um hello my name
is takana from Whole Life English and I
have set the game's voice recognition to
German on my side so I will be talking
to The Ghost and yelling at the ghost in
German today thank you very much give
him a little lesson
littleon it's me
yeah all right I love that okay last
last and also least my name is Mor I'm
the first it's okay you you don't it's
it's all right you can just let it
happen I'm the first Apprentice of the
Grim Reaper himself which means I'm
also uh when it comes to dealing with
ghosts really bad because usually it's
my job to make humans into ghosts uh
when it comes to dealing with the ghosts
um
it's not good and I'm ready to face I'm
ready to live up to my family name and
face full life consequences I'm excited
let's go my specialty in this situation
when it comes to being part of the the
Scooby-Doo crew um Scooby-Doo crew is
taking a bunch of items into the house
that I don't know how to use and have no
reason for using and then leaving them
there so uh let's see how that helps us
out don't don't leave everything that
we're all broke as hell in the game you
got to put it back into the track ler as
much as you can do we even have enough
money to buy flashlights for every I I
we have one flashlight I can I can buy a
little bit we already have one though
you have money how many do we need do we
need one costs
$40 pretty expensive let me buy
something I have 74 bucks okay I have
62 we can hit the dollar store I'll get
us a flashlight okay I got some stuff I
got some stuff here you go and okay we
got we got all flashlights now we got
four to four awesome here we go we got a
Fator okay what else could we need
therometer we have a ghost riding book
yes it's in there yes great okay we got
a Spirit Box a UV light video camera one
of the six photo camera camera one out
of three EMF
reader I'm $1 short for thermometer guys
but we really we already have one we
have one oh excellent okay great um
think we're good do we need another
video camera or something perhaps fix
perhaps glow stick why do I need a glow
stick is there a party here ghost riding
book um it doesn't look like we have a
ghost riding book it's a zero does
anyone oh wait we can buy why did I buy
four we flashlights when I could buy one
strong flash flashlight what yeah I know
right and oh wait I have oh I have some
stuff here oh I didn't realize what the
hell wait what this is all my my
stuff yeah oh my God wait oh what does
have oh wait no no I have nothing uh I'm
going to add salt two times that's all I
had okay good idea two times Salt okay
salt
salt I'm going to add everything salt is
always good oh yeah add everything you
got I'm
contributing yes
salty I don't understand this how this
game works
y yes cuz now all right well this is
fine equipment list is looking good so
let's just go with
it all right ladies here are the jobs
that we have what's this got Edgefield
Street house allow me to narrate
recommended team to a two-story
six-bedroom house with a basement we
have recently received information about
a possible haunting at this location get
there as soon as you can and gather
evidence for the ghost removal team
we'll have more Intel when you arrive
location is small recommended items
thermometer and this difficulty is
amateur yeah let's start with amateur
something easy go easy easy is best
ready up ladies Ghost
Hunters I'm ready let's do our
best have you noticed SpongeBob looks
like you have three onon today yeah
pleas
baby rat little baby I need baby rat and
three on Sons oh I a quick grat oops
sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry that's
okay sorry
s feel like I had
something oh by the way guys when we're
talking to the ghosts and you're
listening to our stream like on our side
um why are
we I'll start it um and we start the
game uh hold on okay when when we were
trying to talk to the ghost you'll hear
us speak double because we have to input
our voice into the game we're not
actually using the dark
to yes yes I alone why am I alone oh
there you
are wait wait wait oh that's not money
thought it was money what my game went
full screen for a second I don't like
hold
Onre is not to
is possibly Frozen oh my God loading
also this is not loading
either waiting for fauna I bet a it says
loading game 90% that's how it was for
me for a while and it was a long time
until it finally why is B sity oh just
kidding everyone's
s come on come on come
on my has been angry with me I kicked it
out of my my CL closet that I stream
from my PC is angry now received at the
nor Lighthouse Road there we go all
right we're here equipment and prepare
accordingly before starting the Margaret
Anderson this ghost seems to respond to
everyone you should be able to use its
name to anger it and get some Paranormal
Activity I don't like this this game is
making my game full screen when I don't
give it permission to cuz you're
supposed to they want it to play
play it that way well Margaret you're
going down is that bleach can we bleach
the ghost oh a photo of the how I pick
up it again there
go salt all right ladies so let's maybe
split this up and someone should use the
camera someone should use the EMF reader
someone should use the salt I'm taking
video camera and
salt wait can I take a flash how do you
use things I don't know what the
controls are someone tell me e e for
picking up
items and then you can squirrel in
between those items I think like three
items is
maximum okay where's Thea I want the
can't pick up anything dang it did I
change my but you're right Chader drink
go drink some salt
milk want the
EMF oh I have the EMF reader hold on
dang it I want to be useful oh my God
pick up anything how don't put it down
just looked at the OBS screen and I
thought the the S how put things down I
don't know attached to the
girls weird pick up is D for some reason
I have it as Z drop is
X flashlight is C got oh this is for me
this is my personal settings oh ah we
going someone open the door okay let's
go open
it flashlight
knock knock G we there someone the key
is in the in the in the truck
now it's really dark M
take I got
Dr oh thank you I appreciate
it is key in Italiano oh no this is the
the wow there we go there's the I have
so we're fine wait what was the name of
the ghost wait I forg Margaret
Anderson margar Margaret
Anderson I saw can't say
[Music]
anything what all good we just got to
figure out what oh that is very creepy
that picture is very creepy let's turn
the light on for the beginning maybe
yeah I don't have I don't have a
flashlight can you wait there wasn't a
flashlight for you yeah there was only
three flashlights I think no no weird we
brought four right here maret Margaret
Anderson give us
a are you okay my double voice SP you
yeah it was so
loud Mar Anderson give us
a no could you just stay in your house
please
yes okay a dirty dirty ass woman here
living here oh man oh 19 clean up your
apartment come on yeah kind of nasty
guys it's colder upstairs oh she must be
upstairs then the EMF I don't like that
oh that's disgusting
stairs
I let's turn on a light that picture of
the child is a I'm
panting where is everybody through
that's a
beautiful
um oh wait who wait no downstairs it's
downstairs it's downstairs downstairs
are you B it's like in this
wall you like right here it's 14 degre
right here oh okay maybe she here sneeze
sneeze do you see like um like
cold like fumes and stuff that's not
cold enough okay yeah yeah it might not
be cold enough okay okay okay let's go
here got to check every room though babe
because very clearly sorry the plant
looked like the hand oh my
God how about
kitchen margetson give us a
sign give us give us a sign 20 not
here the laundry oh my give us a
sign was it door is this back backyard I
can't open it I don't know okay um I
[Music]
found give us a sign sign I feel bad
where I don't want to basement guys we
have basement swear in
J where we open it oh just Kidd being
very needy today so I might have to go
AFK from time to time oh okay
it this doors locked have you guys been
upstairs yet yeah yeah we went up there
but we didn't go in every room is the
thing hey come with me let's go check
out every room I have the EMF reader so
we should work
together I heard a sound I heard I heard
a phone uh vibrating I heard a phone
vibrating me too the I didn't hear
anything is scary how do I put the salt
down baby
room no
oh children's
room no give us a
sign I heard breathing in my
ear it's okay it was
great okay I braing in my
ear mean not like it are we all just
like really really bad horror game
players it might be give us a
sign hello hello what was it f Margaret
THS great
placement this
area here yet what's here this a big
house this
bathroom oh Margaret th no this
20 what was it it's not here CL it I'm
just going to put salt everywhere you
always got to put salt everywhere mhm
very important I room we haven't been
was someone breathing like yeah right I
heard that too before yeah wa was oh was
that
you I'm just maybe in
here he is the real ghost
H we I think s six where where they're
often in the
basement my to check the basement I wish
I had a light on my shoulder instead of
this teeny tiny light it's so small
where did go to 6 the light went out
and I'm I out of
Sal guys the light went out I'm going oh
no
uhoh you sure
B I'm hearing
some the the ghost was a little bit
active it seems yes yes I I see it oh I
see I'm not getting any EMF so it must
it must not be a ghost that responds to
EMF you got to you got to call it name
out more more often to angry Margaret
Thompson Margaret Margaret Margaret
Anderson is the name get out here are
you evil Margaret
Anderson oh Margaret Anderson Margaret
Anderson that's the reason why the ghost
hasn't showed up where
you by the closet guys is by the closet
[Music]
bring some more
salt a PlayStation V oh boy I got EMF 4
time to leave
baby it's not going on right now in the
activity there's no activity no activity
all good yeah there is
activity don't worry what is this thing
I have in my hand by the way
EMF 4 ladies how do I I'm going in I got
to you know make myself stronger for
Outlast yeah good idea should we put a
oh that now I got a cross dot projector
po ladies there like a party in
you guys at the entrance why is it's so
cold cuz the door is open you you
little no I'm serious K so cold I was
just kidding I want to put this down
here but in the I want to see if I can
get how can I turn it guys help me chat
how do I turn this literally like a
party down here does that mean it's in
the
what how do I turn it okay that's
cool Anderson is it recording I think
it's at the door it's recording right
yeah the ghost is at the entryway guys
perhaps yeah it's marget
Anderson Margaret Anderson L come
[Music]
house that's a weird sound yeah I hear
spooky breathing I I don't hear that my
s box
front it's definitely you might want to
turn off your flashlights perhaps I
think for maximum
activity I'mma stand at the door so I
can just back out that that
is okay okay okay it's 7 is that who is
doing that noise someone playing with
something a
ghost that sound that
sound I think
what is this it's the light switch the
light switch wait is that you who CH
that you're playing the light s stop it
the ghost has gotten the light switch
stop it oh man that's you oh no stop it
oh no the CR stop it oh man that's a
spooky ghost playing with the lights
let's got got to check off playing with
the lights
J got the door
get um Bae you're such a chicken bae
down here I thought it was not I'm a
badass Margaret Anderson [\h__\h] you okay
it'sin
Anderson get
[Music]
him Margaret Anderson
comeon
maret maret okay it's definitely this
front room Margaret Anderson CL
I don't want even want to know what
she's
saying nothing too bad wa wait wait can
we set up a
camera I set up a camera video camera in
the um in the entrance room but I guess
dark it won't you won't see anything I
swear to God Bloody Mary Bloody Mary
Bloody Mary Bloody Mary Bloody Blood
Mary Bloody Mary Bloody Mary there is
activity I'm running away yeah
something's happening we just got to
quit being little cowards and got to get
deeper into the house I bet it's not
just the end that's the entrance are you
sure did you see the ghost no but it
went down to 3 oh okay well then maybe
it's a room close by yeah what what's
useful here what is
that you can't really see anything
Margaret Anderson that this really the
best place is this really
video
camera marget Anderson [\h__\h] Margaret
Anderson over
there yeah get
her I'm no coward I don't like swearing
in
ger Margaret Anderson
come Margaret
Anderson you scared the [\h__\h] out of me
my dude me B is that you it's it's the
ghost oo
can't get me if I'm outside I'm I'm
outside the house
ask Margaret Anderson how v
p Anderson V
pistol oh wait what onet Anderson V
pistol get inside okay give us a sign
where is everybody over is that
something good Margaret
Anderson keep Margaret Anderson
keep oh it's 4 4 oh my God it's 110 is
that is that good I don't know I saw
Prince in the garage oh is that is that
so Margaret Anders pistol V pistol how
old are you give us a
sign please no I'm so scared no we're
fine B don't worry
this ghost is a little coward the
numbers mean nothing did you hear
that what do the numbers mean yeah you
you suck I'm to let's go to the
basement yeah oh yeah basement oh yeah
basement basement you can't open it for
some Reas I don't want to go that must
be the
ghost we get a cam coming no way wait
the ghost is hunting probably oh guys
the door closed the ghost is totally
hunting
the I'm not here I'll be watching I'm
not here the the door closed I'm dead it
was
me I heard I heard her laughing
no is someone
dead I'm dead really Wait f you died
I've died really
congratulations I didn't see anything is
the activity over am I
safe um activity I can't tell did two
people die I heard a door who's doing
this I can't open it who's do stop it I
can't open the door you scare me which
door are you trying to get out or in
front door yeah trying to get out oh
okay there you go don't open the door
you open the door wait wait wait for
Mead wait for me wait for me okay y I
survived want to w
f is dead though no we got to find her
body nice oh my God our sanity is all
very low except for B which means we got
to send Bay in
again B you're the bestest I was uh
really not doing good in there what did
you guys see on the camera did you catch
anything no cuz the camera wasn't
positioned correctly we got to move the
camera I positioned it perfectly are you
telling you Senai didn't position the
camera correctly are you saying that I
wonder where fauna was when she died
uh where where where did you put the
camera wait what on the on the on the on
the little table on the
entrance on the little table on the
entrance on the little table huh yes on
the little on the little table on the
entrance what yeah right at the door on
the right
side there's weird stuff on the
car oh wait do you have the um the other
we need the other flashlight you know
the purple flashlight that you can yes I
have yes yes I has on the car you have
where do you need
it the door closed again oh no oh oh God
that's bad um the the door is locked
um
I'm I took the headphones down I'm not
listening to
[Applause]
this I'm not I hear someone
Shing ah stop it all right okay I'm back
I'm I mean I'm dead but I'm back well
you can pick up my items they're all at
the door I got a I got a photo camera
and the purple why only you killed
because I am okay to kill yeah also uh
here uh who is that woman
character is that b oh no is that fauna
F oh that's me even as a ghost you got a
torch light on your shoulder ghost we
can see each other oh I got to go put
someu
it's you and me now you know do you want
to know where the camera is the video
camera it's uh is that you hold on let
me put some stuff away b b stay where
you are look to the right to the right
that's where it is the video
camera that's all the green
one why do you carry a picture with you
uh FAA is that you are you
doxing someone with that not me who is
that who is
that door locked oh boy why are you
screaming oh
God oh God what what what what is she
being
kill oh no it's just getting
[Music]
strangled just let the ghost pick us off
one by one think we're failing this Miss
ladies we are really not doing great I
knew it I knew it well the ghost
definely around this area how do you
open the B the wall I guess the main all
right B it's up to you now
um Journal any fingerprints fingerprints
I think freezing did you guys find
freezing
temperatures no all right so maybe no
temperatures I found fingerprints at
least gotcha okay
fingerprints all right according to Chad
Chad found it not we got to see we got
to see if there's ghost riding okay if
you go into the van you can do it
actually I put the
upstairs oh
God out oh my God the ghost coming the
ghost coming get out of get out
[Music]
of wait C still alive I thought I
thought is is bae getting killed for the
second time
what is happening here guys I don't I
literally don't know what's happening I
think we
lost
yay oh my go how was a scary GH she was
Downs noise oh I couldn't tell who was a
human and who was um all right well
let's try a different job guys was
pretty
bad we have lost all our stuff
recommended team size one how about that
guys a small three bedom single floor
house with a basement recently received
information about a possible haunting at
this location head there gather as much
evidence as you can so a ghost removal
team blah blah blah blah blah blah blah
all right let's go get some ghost
guys add some stuff um oh salt is I can
afford things now I want a strong
flashlight want money yeah
Insurance wait I didn't have insurance
oh that's weird I'm
just you always regreted later on that
you didn't get
Insurance um head mounted camera should
also be good I'm going to add a
tripod required level eight so we can
put the video camera on it yeah nice
idea what was that green Doty thing that
we pl that I placed in the hallway
candles yeah what was that motion sensor
right really did that tell us anything I
thought it was no how do you should we
candles again yeah I want to see if I
can light up some rooms next time does
someone have candles otherwise I'll buy
some a DOT I bought two don't worry okay
we have a lighter already salt never
have you can never have too much salt
but I think we have
plenty uh do we need a
thermometer always good to have just to
check yeah let me buy one unless someone
has
one I'll go by I'll add all right
Street house now we're fully equipped
again and we're probably going to lose
it all again no we can we can definitely
do this I have not die okay chat we need
your help at least I need your help come
on
please we can do it we can do it the
green one was the dot it g crosses
through it I saw that happening actually
I saw the green dots like dim a little
bit oh really and like yeah and change
before I
died you can see the ghost in it a video
camera
ah do projector is the green thing so
you should always be like combined with
a video camera the dots projector okay
well uh ba I know you're feeling not
ready but you should push ready in the
game all right I'm going me I'm start
here we go ghosts have been known to
Target those who staying in the light
too
long oo okay we got to move into the
darkness is taking her time again that's
okay no wor she in the the world
ladies all right here's what we got
is only respond when people are alone
that's
fun James Moore James Moore isn't that
the name of some famous
person only one torch wait why would we
only have one t oh you you already took
one oh blow out a candle we only have
one no we have two I got one oh you got
one too there's one on the floor one on
your shoulder cand oh one on the floor
okay okay I got the strong
flashlight we have a
p so James Mo this goost also seems to
only respond to people who are alone you
know you heard that bae you got to be
alone where's the head C where's the
head mounted camera I think Bae is like
mentally brained
de did I not put all my items in the
game babe did you lose your
voice oh all right
B bae you heard me B you okay B yeah you
good so quiet like a
mouse anyone know where a lighter
is uh lighter lighter lighter yeah I
could have sworn we had a
lighter
there now it's not this is really weird
I saw it in the no wait no I didn't see
it in the list actually never mind it
was there last time lost all our stuff
yeah but I bought new things I guess so
wait but then that means we can't do so
we can't do [\h__\h] with the candles don't
wor we just just leave the candles in
there then so that we don't lose them
okay going in I have the ghost riding
book with me and a torch and that's all
I got all right I got fingerprints
there we go ech
hello
James hello do we have a thermometer
still or uh there should be like we we
definitely brought one I brought one but
I don't have in my hand okay I got the
therometer Bae has the ther let's
go a
bone chicken bone give us a sign bone
where's the bone where's the bone go
take a photo go take a photo here here
okay let me go get the camera let me go
get the
camera
something maybe I just have a regular
old camera I would like it to be in the
kitchen that would be
nice okay let's go in
here Moy
M set James Mo where are you vist James
Mo
vist I could just
e everything I touch h ni someone taking
a photo I took a photo of the bone
Jam hold for
the N
here you didn't even walk in James Mo do
you want to exchange letters with me
ooh give us a sign I always wanted
someone to exchange letters with when I
was young pen pal yeah ghost pen pal
that sounds kind of cute actually wait I
found the o o o board oh my God board I
just thought there was someone here but
was your shoes I found the
board where is it I have it in my
hand o is it upstairs I heard something
I'm coming up with it right now here I'm
coming to the kitchen it was in the
basement how do we how do we use this
are the doors locked no I heard
something know the door oh I heard
something I don't want to hear anything
please this is cool is this like a rare
item heard something I heard something
did you pick up that don't use it
that that painting give us a this yeah
this is the Luigi board oh my God I'm
scared I want to leave right
now get the B well they gave me the sign
I wanted the Luigi board I have the
Luigi but I guess we can only use it
inside oh did you
have sign yeah the lights flickered in
the kitchen
oh what's that sound there's some
running water what that found how do I
use this [\h__\h] how do I use it how do I
even put it down figure it out well
there's dirty water in the sink is that
one oh yeah temperature just went down a
little bit
give us a
sign no don't give us a sign for God's
sake take a photo of the dirty water Bae
is that three it's it's it's not drop
activated ask a question okay drop it do
we have
theer thing how do I activate it always
falls I have EMF I'm not getting any
signs hold on let me take a picture of
the sink God damn it I'm coming
is out of two
out went out what I can't turn my torch
off there we
go I'm not get anything EMF was the
ghost stabilizing okay
good we can't even clear amateur stuff
wait where where's my o board where I
think it's safe to say no EMF someone
stole my ja board did someone take my
old ja board did the ghost take my old
ja board get the bone how do you get the
oh I got the bone he's
gone pick up the bone get money
apparently is this you my
dude maybe it's the basement okay okay
okay
no Del like reply to the O board like in
the correct room guys or anywhere
someone give us a sign
all right guys anywhere where are James
Mo [\h__\h]
youu I don't think James Mo would like
that blood Bloody Mary Bloody Mary
Bloody Mary Bloody
Mary PA can you come to the bathroom
with me uh oh James Moore how old are
you James MO is that you where where are
you uh maybe in German James
vbody come here he's in the bathroom
he's in the toilet he's in the toilet
toil
it's James Moore where at aist James
Moore VI pistol confirmed in the
bathroom James Mo VI pistol oh my God
James Mo what should I ask
him are you okay I'm I'm using the oja
board the question thingy the Ouija
board yeah the game can hear me I tested
wait I want to set up a camera in the
toilet James but it's a yes or no
question
James who has the video camera um me I
do oh wait the door closed you guys are
in
trouble
run oh the is he got me no he got me
as I ran I ran right into the
ghost it really turn my headlight off 10
wow you asked him a really personal
question I shouldn't move right I
shouldn't there's safe now it's safe
it's safe it's safe now it's safe now
all right I'll be lookout for you guys
where did you someone come back ba come
back in you little chicken I'm trying to
get the can someone get the tripod I
want to set up I want to set up the the
camera I the bathroom you can pick up
the camera where I died where are you
vist
v v
b by the way the tripod the tripod is in
the truck you guys oh where it's in
the are you getting reading emf2 in the
bathroom
EMF do hold on a second I'm pressing me
okay I'm going to do something terrible
I'm should I move it for him no one come
in here it only responds when it's
alone sity zero oh [\h__\h] oh God oh God
what I heard it I heard said I heard it
I heard it I heard it oo
this is it it
hunting no the door's still open you're
in the clear okay I want to get here I
need to get out of here come on Mommy
here Mommy here
uhoh I got out at the right moment it
seems
oh the
closet
board in the closet did you die there's
two oh no fa what are we going to do I
have zero
sanity um sanity pills are necessary all
the stuff though at the door you should
probably grab it go to the van and then
we just leave and make a guess a how do
I open the
door wait I'll try to open it for you
it's hunting again oh no oh I see it
it's at the door it's at the door the
door I'm dead
I'm why does this happen every time yeah
this is like I swear the ghost never
before oh I see it it went into the
kitchen be careful wellit I'm the only
one left alive I'm just going to pick up
some items and put it in the
truck yeah get out well we got we got um
look at my dead body maybe not that
Spirit Box really oh yeah the Spirit Box
work I don't I'm scared to am I supposed
to be able to see the other
ghost I Lev though who are you what
about fingerprints ghost or do we get
freezing temperatures
what's happening hey what was the lowest
temperature you saw B uh it was
[Laughter]
11 you guys good is everyone dead Bae
that is the demon crouching oh it is the
Demon's got the flash me that's
scary this is the demon
crouching oh it is why does it have a
flashlight what is that a flashlight
wait oh in this is someone is any ghost
in the truck right now can we can you
tell me like what the activity is I'll
go into I'll go into the truck I thought
you the ghost go into the truck the
activity is low it's not it's basically
non-existent right now okay oh no that's
a dead body oh that's the that's not the
ghost I thought that was the ghost
oh this is that's SP his body
oh you can't save items wait what you
you you don't have to pick him up you
lose everything
really every single time you go that
does that we really should get a right
guest here and not keep on losing our
money but what do we what do we what do
we know about him no EMF level five I
was everywhere up in that [\h__\h] with the
EMF reader and I didn't get level five
so none of that I put the I put the book
somewhere does anyone know where I put
the
book uh get ghost
riding let me just try to find if the
book
again if the book isn't written in then
it's only two it can only be one of two
Okay C you put it in the basement oh
dear let's see if I can make it to the
Bas I'll be your Lookout with zero
sanity you Callie is this you I can't
tell who's who I'm now ENT fast oh God
oh
God okay all right no worries we got
this wait but before let's just
uh I'm just which one are you guys going
for I want to choose something before I
go in so that I at least have something
here oh who is that someone's by the
door I'm at the door but I'm outside of
it no no no be okay so
far oh no I'm in the basement is it
hunting someone is oh did someone die
here you died just believe
I'm going to go with
um wait what did I do let let me read
what does a p guys do uh R to spread no
it didn't really do that Call's dead
budy all right okaying life may Yokai
Spirit Spirits are very common ghost
they powerful passive only attacking
when they need to they defend their
place of death to the utmost degree
killing anyone Spirit can temporarily
stop
SM okay well Spirit sounds like it could
be it J I can check the book guys I can
check
the with you could be a phantom three of
us Dr your sanity take a photo of make a
t ah commonly summoned from o I mean I
did speak with the oja board a lot but
he never answered me so it's not a
phantom I think where you put the Bol
where is the Bol H in oh wait I guess
the ghost can go look too huh H it's in
the basement in the basement I put the
book like pretty close to the like it's
it's like on the on the other side of
the
room on the on the bottom on the ground
mhm the ground I can't see anything on
the ground yeah might not be able to see
it you
[Music]
guys Journal
oh I didn't even know this was a thing
uh oh
well other side I
see Ghost can see the writing nice try
though
okay uh ra I want to see what the ra one
of the most dangerous
ghost oh there's nothing in the book RS
oh there's nothing in the book yeah but
apparently ghosts can't see it anyway
even if like you ghost and dead dead
players can't see it a that's annoying
uh I'm just going to go with
uh spirit cuz it's the most common and
we're playing an amateur game I don't
know my Logic No but those was freezing
temperatures what there was freezing
temperatur really there was was there or
was it just freezing is below zero oh no
there was no freezing temperature okay
um G can see the right there right I
don't think it was the
spirit oh you can do this no EMF okay if
there's no EMF level five it's not a
spirit
oh we got Spirit Box though oh no say no
ghing just because soter guys Phantom
orai okay well I think maybe a
Yokai I'll choose Phantom just to be
contrarian okay okay you got a common
ghosts that are attracted to human
voices they can usually be found haunted
family home strengths talking near Yokai
will anger at increasing the chance of
an attack we did constantly talk lot to
that maybe it is
maybe yeah yeah let try
it yeah let's try that although it does
say EMF level five is one of the
evidences but I crossed it off for the
evidence I crossed it off yeah me too
but it comes up doesn't it mhm well
let's let's try that's it I don't think
so I think it's just spe box and
projector it like like this cuz I didn't
see
it should I do it like this I'm not
going to lie
guys my my hand is stting to turn
numb are you
okay I like how this ghost is called
Hunter because that's like
hunting cute
put your guest in the book I
did did
i
j I did and then what do I do then you
click on uh you can go to evidence go to
the evidence tab oh I did I put yoai
okay good then you're fine let's leave
I'm going to go
out let's go look at our super
professional van and we all just suck I
love it oh it's Indonesia
really unlucky whenever I played before
the ghosts were never so
violent it was a
mayor so we messed up some evidence but
it's fine we got phone evidence and
photos at least we got some more
money I took the
photos I took the
photos see I don't know there's
something good job
no all right we're really horrible at
this one one more I'm bad at this game
let's do one more game if that's okay
with you
guys Redemption I'm going to get a first
writing book we have nothing
anymore yeah you can watch our oh I got
my items I'm going to add a Thom meter
and a tripod that's all I
got I'm buying a
strong level three that's so rude um
I'mma buy I don't know what I'm going to
buy what do we buy um do we T of stuff
oh uh a a light a lighter okay now we
have a lighter and the candle
camera strong flashlight we love one
more candle if possible guys got money
to I will buy I will buy I bought
candle good stuff now let's see what
jobs we have how about we do The
Farmhouse cuz asylum in prison is going
to be no way The Farmhouse isn't that PR
you
pink uh size recommended size is two
it's a two-story 3bedroom Farmhouse we
can do either that or the prison
recommended size three and Asylum
recommended size four those are scary
can you like refresh that to give us
something
smaller yeah no unfortunately doesn't
work what no it's so beig I think we'll
be fine Farmhouse then yeah let's do it
uh got an attic nice all ready wait we
only have one out of four flashlights yo
and one St
oh should we have more I'll buy more
yeah I bought a I buy one you buy one
Bae okay I cannot afford one I can
afford exactly one and then I'm out of
money oh my God in someone all right
someone just stay with someone who has a
flashlight you can stick with me going
to it's fine have now we should have
four yeah we have four the four and one
strong
one actually then wait wait wait wait
wait then let me can I
how do I get rid of one damn it cuz we
don't need five
flashlights oh well let's just leave one
in the truck go go go B you got to ready
yourself up no okay noise start let's go
we can do this guys I know we can let's
just believe in believe in each other
and we just got to test out everything
okay I don't believe us careful it hide
we got to hide yes go in the
closet you got to
believe I don't you got to
believe George Robinson seems to respond
to everyone you should be able to use
its name to angry against some okay we
don't have to be alone for this
ghost smudge stick I didn't bring SM
where's the strong flash SM we have
smudge sticks
right uh do we I don't know
we didn't bring
SM oh two TR how did that Happ damn
it and candle and lighter actually I'll
start off taking candles and then I'll
leave the ghost riding book here for now
if somebody else wants to use ghost
riding book I'm going to light up some
candles in the house oh yeah I I I'm
bringing the ghost riding book cool and
the video camera uh can anyone bring the
tripod
anyone got some free hands
um otherwise I'll leave the book behind
here someone someone get the camera I'm
going I'll get the tripod oh okay uh
well I uh I put the book wait that makes
no sense then I'll put the book down you
take the tripod and I take the camera
and the video cam
okay okay let's go I got the keys strong
flashlight oh no I don't like this I was
never in this one before
yeah this map is definitely
scary like IAD which is the strong
flashlight is it the black one or the
gray one uh the black one what's his
name again George
something what was it George
George George Robinson George Robinson
flashlight
sucks what got
you I think it's the one that you put on
your shoulder we go all right we're good
no I I put the weak one
away okay
Georgie my dude is winded after George
Robinson George
[Music]
Robinson 13 UHS
16 where are the lights o how do
I that's
scary if you find something sus tell
tell me I want to take a photo of it go
there's the candle one candle go get
another
one I'm just going to follow
you I'll check the
activity okay are you safe yes I was
shooked by ba yeah nothing's really
going on right now I can't tell who is
who gas profane gas
G
is I
need saveen sink so
scared you'll be okay it's okay not even
I'm scared and that means something no I
don't like being in the dark without
being able to see and I don't like
ghosts there should be a here another
candle I'll put one upstairs just a few
jump scares doesn't hurt nobody EXC me
it hurts the
soul you'll be okay it's a bit colder
upstairs I found nothing suspicious
yet yeah I have no EMF yet wait we're
not playing Among Us here I'm not
looking for anything suspicious am I I
left the tripod hold
on why is the tripod there did I leave
that there apparently you did
accidentally placed
it uh breaker is in a really easy to
find spot
where this
door I can't pick it up why can't I pick
it
up bedroom nice hat oh do I have to be
holding it the whole time oh I
see I understand May clock uh George
Morrison where are you
V George
Morrison where' you guys go morr give us
a sign where' you guys go hello in the
bedroom George Morrison
[Music]
pistol George Morrison give us a sign I
don't want to go upstairs with myself
it's okay I'm hearing scary ghost noises
I don't know um I saw something flicker
downstairs guys interesting oh maybe my
dude was giving us a
sign how nice of him to help us progress
in The Game Attic I'm going to go to the
attic that is very brave of you yeah
probably should have put a candle up
here I I see a sign where would I see a
fingerprints I want to see something
usually the ghost is like on the door or
the window or something weird sound yeah
I hear that too what the hell oh that's
you B sound like go it's just a table oh
it's one more floor up there a
sign kind of scary give us a sign okay
who turned the light off everybody me me
all
lights if you
turn the
breaker okay
um oh oh give me a
candle for the for the fingerprints you
need the the purple
flashlight yeah ah okay
okay give us a
sign George George where are you it was
that room you found the room you're
you're good at finding the rooms which
room I found the room which floor one
you're right here right here yeah which
floor the second floor okay there's a
bone on the floor oh I want to take a
phone where is the bone second
floor
[Music]
my wait the second floor is bom
cand second floor bathroom Okay where is
bathroom a here
ooh nice got it thank you nice okay
tripod wait wait wait wait B put the
tripod down where you think it is the
ghost though okay I love the tripod at
the door CU I didn't
have a breaker there it is at the
entrance door light pick up the bone
pick up the
bone hey you got to grab that bad boy
get that money I can't I got full hands
man all right I'm in the kitchen I
uh is he really up here I'm not getting
yeah how how do you think so
ba I can't see anything George Morrison
wo pistol why would George Morrison give
us a
sign I'm going to go gra George Morrison
giveit wait can someone put the camera
on top of the tripod here maybe in the
hallway when he comes out maybe have no
ghost writing book so let me grab this
oh wait I could take it never mind I got
the bone okay uh wait wa where did you
put the tripod it's right by the stairs
stairs stairs on the second
floor uh on the second floor stairs down
to the first floor
okay God it's so dark I don't see
[\h__\h] yeah I thought I turned on the
lights
but there we
go uh I turn the light on it's on is it
is it filming do you see
it are you in the truck I'm going to go
to the truck and check okay give us a
sign Chad says they went to EMF 3 but I
my candle's out I did not see it or hear
it
where F
you there's not
much okay camera's on camera's on
camera's on looking right in front of
the camera
what someone is right in front of the
camera okay okay
okay nice nice nice nice
give us a
sign what do we do with this cam we need
a light or are we going to uh s um all
of the candles I lit up are blown out oh
what does that mean should we take a
picture of that does that mean something
cuz he did something Wonder Maybe I mean
I probably should be witnessing an event
there's no activity at the moment can I
we haven't found the right room
therometer wait I swear it was the
bathroom do you want the thermometer
here yes please let's maybe go back
upstairs
then okay I'm
[Music]
coming candles do go out on their own
eventually hum maybe we should put a
candle upstairs did you put one upstairs
too I brought one with me
upstairs wait do you have the sign oh
gohost Rand yeah I do can you light this
one I brought it here where right next
to the
book yeah there we go oh start a fire
today she did it she streamed Sparks
shining your give us a
sign
B I don't know if yeah we got to talk
more to the ghost I don't think it's
reacting to me at all I think the game
doesn't pick up my voice but uh okay
well I'm going to go downstairs and
check on your sanity and just look at
the camera because is this is this
normal I'm eting out of here sign hold
up let me have a look all right
well nice bathroom is what ba
said put the video camera down in the
ghost room yeah apparently that's where
there's a little bit of activity but
everybody seems okay hold
up I see nothing give us a sign except
that stuff here wait was it the other
bathroom is this the same bathroom no I
think it's a different bathroom one
under the George Morrison
I thought you said door is closed and I
got I did too I got scared give us a
sign George Morrison Jes Morrison Geor
George I can't tell George
Morrison is that an orb there an orb
George
Morrison find a ghost
orb George Morrison get
CH we're experts at this guys George
[Music]
Mor George Mar Vision oh George George
Robinson sorry George Robinson we
freaking names wrong uh the name is
George Robinson everybody yes sorry
George Robinson sorry sorry
dude George
Robinson George robs who
that take a little
break's
shy keep on mixing up those names shy oh
here y bang you little chicken it is
pretty what's up um let's I'm going you
got nice sanity going on there it goes
you had nice
sanity yeah no I want to try to see move
the camera into like the bathroom maybe
George and give us a sign wait FAA found
it what F what I just found the cold
temperatures oh okay very cold freezing
oh three and that's for me fcking lights
oh no fcking lights licking lights
licking lights I think I'm dead oh oh oh
oh oh fre freezing fcking lights okay
flickering flickering indeed it is
flickering flickering flicker is a
hunting is that what it is
it's h I'm dead oh I'm dead
[Music]
again it was
me they always go for FAA she's a easy
target Among Us Always die first wait
okay so we got do we get
free well I still can't manage to get
any ghost riding so I think it's okay to
rule that
out temperatures no freezing
temperatures I thought it was freezing
temper it was just cold but not freezing
what was the EMF EMF
just three oh come on all of these
evidences are useless or no no five no
five we've we've narrowed it down to
three it's either a phantom Banshee or a
yo-kai and how do we do we have Spirit
Box what do we actually have ghost orb
and something
else um I don't know if there's a ghost
orb I couldn't tell didn't someone say
we have a ghost orb I'm going to take
this or was there orb
I can't turn on the light why oh it's
walking around
upstairs it's in the Attic
e lucky
spooky it's walking
downstairs it's walking down no it's not
wait I don't know it might be in the
Attic still are you in where are you
CS how do I turn off the
flashlight right click it that's bad I
can't find my flashlight anymore okay
that's that's not good no that's good
that is good man holding a
hatchet please I just want to get I
opened the door if you want to get great
I don't know how to turn off the
flashlight L uh t t t is that you oh
that's you call come here come come come
Kelly oh I see the light come Kelly come
Kelly where here come here come here
come here behind you
behind I think I feel like a
soft all right so let's regroup and
figure out what we know nothing you know
there's ghost orbs apparently yeah what
um maybe let's see okay there's
definitely no ghost riding because I was
everywhere up in that [\h__\h] saying that
dude's name he didn't he didn't come he
didn't do nothing okay so no ghost
riding freezing God damn it I go in and
it closes okay I'm going to
die are you kidding me
Kara you can try to run
hide see in who oh we see you in the
window we see you in the window it's
going to kill me oh he's coming he's
coming for
you are you taking pictures B yes I'm
taking pictures are you taking pictures
of K getting no no he's done he's
done okay but I got interesting photos
while he was
hunting you really why there what
is oh you guys I why are you looking
we've been here though save me for God's
sake
the no open it try opening it now please
oh my God oh my God I survived I can't
believe
it we just watching as if you in cinema
for God's sake wait did I see
fingerprints did we see fingerprints did
we see fingerprints because I was
running around with this purple light
wait what did you what did you take the
photos you took uh I took some cool
photos yo oh y I don't know if they
count as anything but they're funky
photos wo fingerprints on the w we can
add fingerprints guys apparently the
chat sees everything that I don't see
for me it's apparently a banshee if we
really saw ghost
orbs who interesting what does a Banshee
do whoa did it stop after you took the
photos because apparently don't wait
don't Phantoms disappear after you take
a photo something wait wait wait wait
wait taking a photo will make her
temporarily yeah it was about to hunt me
no and I took photos into the air and it
disappeared yeah waa that was a smart
smart choice for me to
take heck yeah wait what wait it was a
phantom I'm not sure if it actually
disappeared cuz I saw it in the kitchen
well I don't know it like didn't go into
the room where you were in it went into
the kitchen inste no but it was at the
door
right um no it was it went down the
stairs and then went to the
kitchen uh ghost UPS oh no sh yeah no it
has to be a Phantom cuz there weren't
any ghost orbs there were no ghost orbs
there were no ghost
orbs I thought you saw a ghost orb
someone say said that right oh okay oh I
think I saw a flashlight so one day I'll
leave you a
phantom need you in the sum uh only
finger the only thing we have is
fingerprints then what is this game but
that means that but you can you can
cross out you can cross out stuff in the
journal if you click it more times yeah
yeah I did I did I did I did that's not
so we have Phantom wait that's a phantom
not how you idiot give need uhoh I'm
going to die what no go back inside I
just wanted to put down some salt I was
feeling
salty yeah come and get me behind this
salt idiot
ha it's not a people say it's not a
phantom where are you I don't want to
know one day I'll leave you a phant did
no he's still alive get out of
here is that you Kelly no that's Bae
that's me KY okay safe now Kelly is it
hunting no finished you come
out I open Open Door come here kie come
here come here oh where are you guys
there's so much salt down here who put
all salt in one SP I want to bait him I
just wanted to bait him why that's a
what if I walk over it okay yeah it's my
little salt Garden you guys like it oh
my oh wow I'm so scared the Triangular
sh I'm saying Phantom the secrets of all
these world this world is the secrets of
the world are they're written here in
this triangle is
that can we go guys yeah okay I'm
scared just making sure guarding the
door the door Mak one
day you got the door I guess so okay
where's the door where's the door
where's the door uhoh here okay here
here there's not a lot of activity guys
I think it's fine I think
us you guys all guess Phantom wait one
last thing let me check the
door is it on the inside or on the
outside I don't want to go inside
anymore it's activity is going up a bit
okay I'm leaving okay
byebye okay on on the door or and light
switches oh well once again that was a
very uh was eventful at least we didn't
we mostly didn't die 75% of the party is
still here
somehow I 3 for three right
now that means we won't lose the items
at least at least the people
who what is that the people who didn't
die okay so are we really going for
Phantom I guess I don't know what else
we should go for yeah just got to Hope
and Banshee
apparently sorry maybe we should
split I'll pick Banshee okay wait why
would it be
Banshee because because the game always
is right and we always wrong it did
Chase me up the attic even though there
were other people
downstairs bansi targets one person
specifically interesting but wouldn't it
have said in this description something
about being alone because here it says
everyone usually when it's like that
just means I will talk to you the box I
see well I'm going to close the door now
everyone make your
decisions all right I'll just see what
happens I'm I'm joining the black parade
today okay we see what happens
[Music]
go bye-bye weird house fingers crossed
yeah you suck weird
Farmhouse that dude was really yanking
our chain for for a while
mhm no it was a yo-kai what the [\h__\h] we
were all wrong I don't get it I don't
get it this game is we just got to get
good we just got to get good at fasmo
it's it really started it became really
difficult after that stupid
update yeah it used to be last time you
guys played it you also couldn't get a
single win exactly exactly and we had
some some decent Ghost Hunters I would
say decent is this just a game for like
really Elite game Lords I fine that's
great games like that should exist um it
just means that we maybe have some
trouble update coming out tomorrow yeah
yeah that our timing was just a bit off
well maybe that was for the best yeah I
think it was for the best I want to play
it a come on never playing
again oh
no way I love spending time with you
guys so don't get me wonderful a game
come play DVD another time I mean I'm
I'm I I personally wouldn't mind not
playing it anymore
either I feel like I it's only fun cuz
you guys are here yeah me too I I
enjoyed having uh you guys around and
spending time with you guys cuz I I
haven't had much time or like
possibilities to interact with the
council members
specifically unfortunately
sorry my heart is still
pumping pumping will you get your
heart I've been trying I was going to
ask you how to do it because I'm not
kidding it feels like it's coming out of
my uh coming out of my chest I'm not I
can't feel my arms I can't feel my legs
is this am I oh my gosh that's really
intense I didn't know it was that it was
like that you should have a good rest
why would you suggest this game bab
there's so many other games that you can
play four people we could have play
Mario Party Bae Mario
Party it was still fun but I want to
make sure you're okay I'm okay did you
guys have fun you can say you've done it
do it
again yeah I feel like I'm getting
braver at hor again there are no
monsters under your bed okay should
should mommy for now check under your
bed
tonight yeah
oh my
god oh gee yeah tell him you tell
him I still had a good time though I'm
extremely hungry but I still had a
really good time hungry guys I actually
have to I'm watching horror movies quote
unquote hor movies got to get some
popcorn what's your favorite popcorn
Cali movie theater butter butter salty
butter yeah extra buttery oh i' I've had
a time where I only wanted to eat
caramel
popcorn but now I'm I'm back to like I
don't mind eating any kind like salty or
butter or uh caramel popcorn I don't
mind any of those yeah you probably get
sick of that real quick huh no I I love
the when it's like the more caramel is
on it the better it on it the more
caramel the better yeah agreed yeah F
what's your favorite
popcorn I like classic buttery as well
oh okay good choice got some good taste
what about B what's your favorite one
bals the question what's your favorite
popcorn um I like cheese you like cheese
popcorn I've never seen makes sense
you're a r I've only seen cheese popcorn
before in Japan like I I wasn't as store
where there's like uh 50 different types
of popcorn and they're they all sound
weird as [\h__\h] oh yeah like um like
seaweed flavor and stuff like even
crazier than that that's that's still
super normal for Japan seaweed flavor
still I guess
so yeah but it was really weird stuff
really interesting cool at least at
least they got different types red red
bean
flavor oh yeah that's right and like
spicy super hot strawberry flavor they
had that too banana flavor they
definitely had banana flavor popcorn a
that sounds yummy
actually Pizza like pizza Goldfish
oh yum
yummy sorry nerding out over popcorn a
little
bit I'm glad you're also a popcorn fan
Kiara I wouldn't mind whenever I go back
to uh Japan you know what we should do
we should find that store and then get
like 20 different types of that popcorn
and do a a taste testing stream yeah
blindfolded you guys can't look at it
it's a good idea yeah I mean would be
nice to look at it but I guess popcorn
all looks the same most of the time yeah
you got to guess the flavor that's the
fun of it
all fun on day are being quiet sorry
sorry B oh I had to go you had to go my
cat was again I
check on him can you give me a cat fact
of your
cat yes he's 21 years old I mean more
like an Insider give me an Insider cat
fact cat old man what's an Insider cat
fact like uh like something weird about
him that he
does um he sees into the spirit realm
that's cool and meows into Mir mirors
that's adorable oh my whenever I pet my
cat um my cats on like the part right
above their tail they lick themselves
oh cute yeah always without fail it's
very cute F do your cats follow you
wherever you go like as soon as you get
up from a chair do they like run after
you not really well I have to go
grab you know what what my one of my
cat's uh smoothie you know what what
cute thing she does um you know when I'm
talking on my stream like I talk pretty
like like constantly right so when I
when I'm done streaming I immediately
stop talking and smoothie every time I
swear every time I'm done streaming she
immediately comes into my room because
she knows I'm done streaming because I
stopped talking she walks into my room
she says me out and then she falls down
on the floor and she rolls around and
says hello like Mommy you're done with
streaming no play with me
so cute yeah she recognizes when I'm
done streaming it's so cute he's
probably figured it out by now yeah yeah
definitely when Mommy is loud she goes
to different room to sleep and when when
Mommy is quiet she comes back and says
hello cute Bae do you like cats do you
have a good relationship with
cats yeah yeah you are a rat after all
you ever get chased by
cats yeah yeah that's a good
answer have you has a cat ever tried to
eat
you okay I think Bae is brain dead for
real now yeah I think
so oh well that was fun ladies thank you
for inviting me I'm C I was caling down
it's okay thank you for inviting me K
and B a fun glad you guys had fun at
least I want to I I just wanted to I
don't know I I just wanted to play time
we play something not scary it's Howe
week we got to play scary
games exactly that's the thing it's just
this game because I can't deal with
paranormal any other kind of horror game
is not in the dark I can I can somewhat
this like pretty much every horror game
in the
dark it's fun which horror game is not
dark de by daylight dead by daylight is
it has some not very it has some not
dark levels guess it says daylight so
it's
bright I mean yeah there's like a winter
level that's like pretty bright outside
I don't think it's I don't think it's
the type of scary game that that you
would freak you out ba so I think it
should be fine I'm excited to play dead
by daylight yeah it'll be fun don't like
first person perspective that makes it
too real
[Music]
unless you're the killer but then why
would you be afraid if you were the
killer so yeah you'll be fine you'll be
fine don't you worry about it Bae we're
going to have a great time all right
okay with that being said guys I guess
we better sign off huh okay all
righty it was fun yeah it was fun thanks
for having
me see you
again see you at tpg me doing nothing
yeah that's
right TG going to be spooky too this
Winkler um maybe we'll see it might just
it depends on how you guys approach it
because people think I have a grandmas
plan but it really is kind of up to you
guys that you come up with is like up
until now it was always very scary and
spooky so it's like it's always
Halloween in your
TTG oh I'm I'm glad you at least think
that because right now I feel like
everything is very clownish and very
well yeah but that's also scary to a lot
of people pretty scary
yeah yeah well I hope that you enjoy the
next installment you guys looking
forward to it yay gath gath it's going
to be fun um anyone else got
announcements that they want to shout
out no we have a chance schedule is out
look at it
yeah some coming out on Saturday yeah I
hope it will I'm sorry I'm still trying
to find the feelings in my arms um I
hope you you guys will be there of
course I'll be there it's a very cool
thing mhm I know I can't wait wait did
you say did you like spoiler what you're
what you you know putting out there no I
just said special release something
anything special like not not not that's
it that's all you said Yeah Yeah hold so
I know I know more than the
audience
do you guys do yeah yeah
I might gorilla stream tonight oh maybe
what you going to
play mcraft Minecraft oh of course very
good for gorilla that's a gorilla game
[Music]
yeah hold to say something oh I don't
really have
anything I'm taking a little break
because I streamed a lot this
week okay amazing
yeah love
you thanks everyone will be out soon for
members
else bye bye bye bye bye all
I got out excuse me just a moment what
about I'm gonna ask ask maybe I'll read
some super chats you know what I want to
read some super chats you guys stay stay
stay
stay I think I'm going to actually stay
uh streaming and read some super chatos
girls okay whatever you want to do
byebye I'll talk to you later then Kiara
okay
oh There She
Goes didn't even have to do anything
well wait stay guys we're going to read
super chats I don't I don't feel like
leaving yet just a just a little bit not
too much not too much not all of it uh
moving to my office I hope it's clean
feel like it's not
clean oh no it's all
right I'm too big too big small small
uh I could turn green screen off now
huh let me uh turn uh green screen
off
okay and here here I am again now I can
get rid of that green screen filter also
I wanted to do the the heart rate
monitor for today for fasma but honestly
even if I would have used that would
would have barely been interesting today
I think that was that was like I don't
know I'm I'm I'm like really bad of hor
stuff but uh oopsie uh
yeah
fast I I was scared of things that were
not even ghost related like opening the
door and seeing
uh the like a dead body in the door like
that's the kind of stuff that I'm scared
of and
here
chat all right so chat you're here and
yeah the volume for the microphones yeah
yeah yeah
yeah the monitor didn't work no like
there was a there's a battery in there
like from the get-go and like I I
started like uh setting it up and it was
beeping on all the time I guess cuz I
kept on touching like the little turn on
thingy I guess um so it was beeping and
it was it was green and all that but
once I finally put it on and was ready
to connect uh it turned itself off and
then it stopped beeping and apparently I
guess maybe I need a little bit of a new
battery why would you send a battery
with the thing if it's going to be empty
anyway huh oh we need a BDM okay
about and close fast mode why the hell
can I just never win in fast
mod why is it so impossible
I sh old battery they probably didn't
know batteries can be like that if they
get too
old can't ship full batteries it's
illegal
[Music]
what did you know fasma has a tutorial
you guys need to play the
tutorial wait did it did it not have a
tutorial before
[Music]
I guess that could have
[Laughter]
helped let's read some super JS can you
play pacifi no well I don't know if you
guys have seen the schedule for this
week but there are a lot of horror games
or like scarying games on there so you
got to satisfy yourself with that
because I'll be honest me playing
Outlast I'm only doing
this for the sake of you guys and I'm
not doing this for myself if it were for
me I would never play this game ever in
my whole life and it's that's a pretty
pretty bad horror game like bad in the
sense of it's pretty intense
so uh that makes up for one year worth
of horror games I would
say
right I think that's worth one year of
it but I don't know how long I can even
stand that game maybe it's only going to
be like a 40 minute stream who knows
maybe I'll get a hard attack because of
my high
[Laughter]
cholesterol yeah good eyes is going to
be there for mental support I put the
schedule out you know have you guys seen
it it's looks like this no break
day well fmop phobia is right now and
basically for me right now it's it's
almost 3:00 a.m. of
Monday the rest of the day is basically
a day off for me
so it's it's it's basically a day off
don't
worry but the rest of the week is
busy should you really be reading super
chats this late well I have been up
until 8:00 a.m. last night so I'm not
going to be able to sleep anytime soon
anyway and I don't I just want to read
some for for like maybe an hour
okay where did I stop last time yeah I'm
playing Alice madness Returns that's the
that's the first one
right isn't that the first one Mech G is
the the second one
right that's the second one oh [\h__\h] is
that going to be a
problem is
that first one is
oh no okay cuz I think I already bought
it um I mean I wouldn't mind buying two
but you can play Madness without Mackie
okay me G okay first one is included in
the second but it's like a really old PC
game yeah I think I like barely remember
it wait you know what that means there's
going to be a cat in the game right
the um the the the what do you call it
in English what's it called in English
again the
cat the cat with the ba ba smile ches
cat yeah ches
[Music]
cat cat cute
don't I'm so happy that you guys are so
excited about the game cuz it's like a a
really old game and I I I always liked
the idea of that game like I I I like
the Aesthetics and all of it um but I
didn't think you guys were were so into
it I didn't expect that kind of positive
reaction I thought it would be very
unpopular
nostalgic it was an excellent game well
retro that's not retro you call that
retro I don't mind playing Nostalgia
games but like you know pixel retro
games that's not my thing but I
mentioned to you guys a lot of like
nostalgic games before and and all of
those I want to kind of play give it
give them a try but it's a lot of uh
abandoned wear somehow or like companies
that never
reply there is a fake kiata in the chat
mat what where
really Super Mario World I I do want to
play some kind of um 2D Super Mario but
I'll be so bad at
it anyway where do we read did I read
the Among Us members super
chats did I read those help
me kind of surprised you manag to get
perms for Alice it's EA Games EA Games
we have all the per
thankfully EA Games is chill in that
regards easy Among Us or H talk no I
didn't read it no okay did I read the
ones before that wait what was before
that what was
before Wario did I read Wario whereare
I'm guessing no
[Music]
you caught up with Wario okay okay good
then let's read um members
amus
ji uh
thumbnails here we go sassy buaka
members trying to prepare
myself we becoming
impostor which never happened
[Music]
okay okay I'm gonna
zoom danin and J mod danin oh wait I I I
still didn't really get to fix the the
thing ah wait a second is it even active
right
now uh
[Music]
weird I read those oh I felt so like
when I read one one of those super chat
with the gazon heits I thought so okay
okay
okay that means
yeah it was the G one
yeah okay H Tac H Tac with
aqu what a freaking cutiie
pie oh my
God she's such a cutie cute
[Music]
onion I I I still don't um quite
forget uh quite
understand the whole weight
thing
um the question like I asked it because
it seems to be a
meme and I know where it comes from from
the game
but what what what was it with the that
the numbers
changed is she getting teased because
she gained like a half half a kilo or
what I don't understand
teased for being
small well I mean that that's all
obviously jokes because it's like her
being so tiny everyone loves that that's
so adorable no one dislikes
that the tinier the
better oh she lost weight oh dear
well well okay I don't
understand she didn't want to tell her
right but later in the game show yeah I
know that
part I I know that part
yeah she tried so hard to hide it that's
why it's a
meme oh she lost 0.3 well that's nothing
that's like when the difference between
morning and nighttime
she tried so hard to but we instantly
figured out anyway it's kind of weird
yeah
okay I guess like well it makes sense to
to her community I guess uh like like we
have weird things as well that no one
understands I
guess what what's the kind of weird
kfp meme joke that no one else
understands if like other people would
look good
kfp uh the usual room I I feel like the
usual room is a bit easier to understand
though we have I think other things that
are
weirder oh cat yeah we have we have a
lot of things a lot of
memes
daddy FES and ties okay yeah if if I I
want to explain something what's so
funny about that they probably wouldn't
understand huh bye y
me I wasn't sure what you guys were
riding when you were riding bio I was
like what do you mean like a organic
product what do you
mean oh
biomi oh
[Music]
all the Australia thing but I feel like
all a lot of these things are just easy
to explain and I feel like the joke is
easy to
understand maybe maybe something like
you know my my my broken shoulder or so
would be a good comparison
[Music]
all right I need to read those Super
Chat and Petri d p d Mr K Dan kak Dan n
Dan for the red super chat fire B is hot
oh I think I was in pre-chat when you
sent that Super Chat yeah thank you
[Music]
nich I mean that's a pretty obvious
statement fire bird being
hot it is true it is true you're stating
a true true facts
here than for your support Mr kbig thank
you for the pinky am I late yes you're
late fun fact your on sister was one of
the first H live girls I found along
with M and Kon thanks for adding the
pairing tag past Kata and keep being
your fabul fabulous Phoenix self future
Kata you're the most awesome Burber
around right there thank you
unfortunately I got rid of the um the
tag you didn't say I I needed to keep it
uh also I wasn't sure which one was good
enough cuz I had so many ideas of the
writing should it have been onions with
like zero2
zero n z or or just onions normally
onion sisters oh oh oh no
oh oh o h n e e e or o h k n e e o h n s
something
oh oh there's so much to choose
[Music]
from oh
Neons I couldn't make a decision so we
ended up with nothing but I generally
just stopped adding those um couple t TS
because it took up too much space and it
it's like too many tags too many
hashtags like that also makes it
difficult for like searching afterwards
when people don't use all of them just
one of
them then it's I got to go through three
different tags which is so
stupid have fun with your
classes #b # y exactly that's the only
hashtags you
need Elis D NCH d m d looking for the
top danan Elvis danan kakun danash for
the I think that's a red one right
danan hi T there are two things I need
to confirm first I heard there's gravy
on your uniform can you zoom in on
yourself a little I'm not even wearing
my uniform secondly can you jump up and
down a couple
times apparently the floor is your
office is pretty old and we need to
check its safety it's not old this this
office is built newly very recently
2021 actually only like a month old so
no I know exactly what you're trying to
do
here I I know no no no I didn't miss the
joke I know exactly what he's trying to
do
and I'm not
complying not so so easy shouldn't you
be in the usual room you don't get to
make these kind of requests from the
usual
room sit down and get your
treatment I released you why would I do
that go back go back in
there it's a oh it's a your heavy joke
not I want to see your booa moving joke
oh then I did miss a joke if that's if
that's true then I did if that's is that
so
I thought it was a let me take a closeup
and you your bouncing
booble
like like
that see you don't hear any any cracking
noises on the ground do
you for God's sake for God
sake
ridiculous I like that name that's so
nice word play on
andur
[Music]
nice D I don't know how to say
this thank you for the all right Super
Chat is this how onion flavored fried
chicken
made
ah jokes asigned aquaa was probably the
first H life member I knew before I
jumped into this Rabbit Hole oh really
so I'm absolutely excited to learn more
about her
oh well then it was the perfect episode
for
you you're the second one to kind of say
that so nice yeah apparently got a lot
of people into the boat into the rabbit
hole hope you enjoyed the episode I
thought it was one of my best ones even
though I I was uh a bit clumsy on that
day thank you
Felix thank you for the r Super Chat
M # Hol
talk yes yes
keep on using the Hol talk uh hashtag
everyone Aqua MC neor Awards
[Music]
oh I see oh I think I know what yeah I
think I know what you're talking
[Music]
about flaming pants D to D Soul Gundam d
p d Ty D booty slaps d p d MVB D blue D
thanks for the
pinky hi K I noticed that you had three
streams in 24 hours from the 24th to the
25th I like your stream but I hope you
take care of yourself more I love you oh
thank
you free streams in 24 hours yeah yeah I
think I I know what you're talking about
M it happens
I don't know if the taunting the ghost
in German even works worked to be honest
I don't know they never like reacted to
me did
they anyway yeah uh thank you blue I'm
I'm I'm
okay um this week is very busy but uh
first week of November I'm going to
definitely take two days off and also um
I'm not not going to give too many
details just yet I'm not going to tell
you just yet where I'm going but I
booked a little trip I wouldn't call it
quite a vacation it's just a weekend um
trip inside of
Europe and I'm I'm going alone but the
where the place where I'm going to I'm
meeting with a girl that I know there
who I've never actually met before but
I've known her for like a long time
through like social
media through
like uh before her
life uh why would you say Amsterdam what
what gave you the idea that it must be
Amsterdam how how why why it's not
Amsterdam but um I will tell you guys
when the day comes closer and I will
take lots of photos again for you guys
to give you a report afterwards
[Music]
yeah I'm looking forward to it I I um I
wanted to go to a place specifically
where I know someone who lives there so
that I don't have to invite a friend to
travel with me
again yeah I think it I think it's
happening in the second week of
November I'll still be streaming like
five five five times a week I think
probably but yeah I already booked a
really nice
[Music]
hotel and I booked the flight today
really spontaneous and quickly I was
like yo I'm so excited to do this now I
I'm I need I need to I don't know
booking stuff like this looking through
like hotels and all that it gets my mood
[Music]
lifted what do you mean
yeah it's it it it makes you look
forward to
something there's there's a specific
reason as to why am going to this
specific country though so um yeah why
would I meet Ariana
grand you guys are so weirdly
specific to get married no
no no I'm not going to
get I don't do that I'm not going to
Amsterdam to get
[Laughter]
no even if I Wen to go to Amsterdam I
wouldn't do it to get
no I don't even want to say the
word
marry no her mus music is great but I
don't think I would want to marry
her she's a cutie and I love her music
but no marriage no no no just looking at
the beautiful Aesthetics I appreciate
the beautiful
Aesthetics
of of of of the beautiful
women are they finally making you the
Kaiser
what that's M natal don't M ah I
wouldn't mind marrying that's
D I wouldn't know how to handle her but
I could not turn down Natalie Dormer if
she were to propose to me who who could
say no to Natalie Dormer no one
literally no
one
mhm I mean look at look at her look at
we got to read super
chats uh S7 befriend to
D Emily 89 Alexander chin
11 d
h Dan crispy Dan S7 b42 Dan counting
chickens Dan J
swack I'm glad you enjoyed it thank
you Mustang
[Music]
talking about early Aqua activity is
very impressive I respect her because
she always tries very hard on game
singing and communication yeah yeah the
way how she's so good in any video game
impresses me
too we'll definitely miss you T you're
not going to miss me cuz it's literally
I'm just not going to be streaming for 2
days in a row that's that's it it's like
really a short trip I just want to kind
of like go outside and meet a human
person and look at buildings and stuff
and eat in a nice restaurant and stuff
and walk on a ground on on pavement and
touch
grass yeah but I'm not going to get no
no
no well we know we know I just want to
touch some
grass I want to connect with the Earth
and
not only my
apartment the cousa the
cousa no I'm not going to get with the
grass I'm not interested in such
activities
beeping it makes the worst
[Laughter]
no
you K is straight edge
[Music]
Idol Tracy
D oh Korean
[Music]
translate Korean to
English touch nature touch
pH
ah guys tell me when I'm missing on a
red or pinky please tell
me got to ask the gra for consent who
asks grass for
consent D number three
[Music]
D air support
101 every time
[Music]
Danel oh wait that's it hold talk talk
over I talked about the whole talk of AA
Senpai in my members only stream before
this stream uh quite a bit
um I just want to
say it was so much fun talking to AKA
and we have another collab already set
in stone so look forward to it it will
be on her Channel but um I'm going to
notify you guys and it's going to be in
Japanese only but but yeah if you guys
want to watch some
T please look forward to
it I I was I'm actually really surprised
cuz I said it in the mry but I didn't
really think that we would get along
that
well I guess because I thought he was
extremely shy and maybe doesn't it
doesn't really feel so open to make so
many new friendships you know but she
was so excited when I said I could show
her the Ian server cuz she was asking
for someone to show her around and I
wasn't sure if she she was serious with
that but then I kind of like lowy
offered myself
she was like yes please oh my God I'm so
happy thank you thank you thank you I'm
so happy yes yes really are you sure
really she was so excited it was so
cute so yeah I'll I'll show her around
even though she already saw parts of it
but she was wandering around on the
server and apparently getting lost so
I'll help her out this
time yeah I'm taking taking all the
all the big big names of Minecraft Japan
server and showing them
around I I had the the boss of
uset and the boss of uh
shet and now I'm showing around the boss
of uh uh uh me uh wait what's what's
what's her construction called again
what's aqua's construction Aqua Aqua
yeah wait oh my God aren't
those I mean veryy good at no she didn't
really take over let's let's be real I'm
I'm showing around all three of big CEOs
the big
free
what wow all the big
names I thought this stream ended a
while ago I left early well well well
you can never leave early in a kiata
stream I felt like talking to you
[Music]
guys I felt like spending some time with
you guys I used to do that well you
shouldn't I know you you regretted it
didn't
you not even 8 hours in you two hours in
only bra to short thank you
Rea it's not a break you can't even call
it a break though it's just two days
where I'm not streaming yeah that's
nothing that's just a
normal a pretty normal
week I'm not even taking more days off
than normally I mean I mean it's two
days it's like 2 years
oh that's called a weekend yeah it's
literally just a
weekend I'm planning to leave on on
Friday but I'll still stream on Friday
cuz my flight is kind of late and then
Saturday Sunday I won't be streaming and
then Monday I have a flight back home
and then I stream when I'm home it's
nothing
chill yeah I know you'll be fine don't
make me feel bad about it come on I'll
come back with some nice stories again
that's also one reason why
I'm doing it to get some some nice
content for my
stream
yeah Sak
[Music]
love the spooky background thank you I
love it too I love it very much also
since it's Halloween week I'm going to
be using Halloween fan art for all the
thumbnails this
week so if you guys are drawing
something for Halloween please get it
out there early so that I can use it not
going to be using it after Halloween I
think unless it's like something that
could be used even after Halloween
[Music]
the battle armor of used Halloween fi
what do you
mean s orus yeah okay let's read the
super chats for
uh this
one look at the
thumbnails I was I was first like
thinking
um like I was really thinking how should
I align
everyone and first I was like I guess
I'll just align them like you know like
in a simp simple way like like for
example where is an
example like like this
one this was by the way the inspiration
for this collab um because we Ed the
proximity mod in this
one but then I was like nah I want it to
look more like graphic design and
something I that I can totally easily
do and I was looking at like fum nails
from previous Big H life
collaborations and I I thought that
something like this would look really
good and simple to recreate so there we
go I'm proud of it but it took me a
while it took me like 2 hours to make
those stupid thumbnails I don't know why
it took so long because uh uh putting
everything in
position and then switching it around
and I don't know it took it took really
[Laughter]
[Music]
long it looks simple but it's it's not
like you can switch everything around
with one Mouse click no
oh they turned out nice thank
you yeah alignment and having the ones
in on the side like in about the right
size and I don't
know
yeah I like them though I I like looking
at
thumbnails like as in like looking into
a photo album to see like what I've
streamed you
know it's I like looking through
it it's like a photo
[Music]
album okay P Mr Jim Tracy
D oh thank you looking for the top D
looking for the top danion I saw that
yeah I saw that
[Music]
hat clip of her looking at our kfp
employee making fried chicken on video
and her being like Oh kfb is our rival
we got to destroy them I'm like what I
was here first with my
Resturant we'll see about that h
we'll see you about
that yeah it's funny because like she
kind of like at least used to work for
us I think like I fired her but in her
mind she was still uh she was still
working for us I think there he
is representing kfb in conventions in
other streams on Twitter on YouTube you
know what I I I don't this like it
you're doing a good job promoting
KF thank
you you go to conventions with that
apron I [\h__\h] love it thank you for
that uh I saw that you're going to go to
yon too according to
[Music]
Twitter very very good go promote kfp
please kfp kfp kfp kfp
PE Jacob
flirty seeker of Love D uhuh thank you
for the pinky what is this now boss I'm
trying to flirt with a girl but I have
no experience please give me your
opinion or suggest
improvements is this good enough to
charm her I came up with the following
hi beautiful eyes nice boing boings very
very
respectable G
number that is 100% going to work you
should give it a try yeah yeah yeah yeah
you should give it a try that is the
best way to pick up a
girl easy girls are not complicated at
all that's you just got to you know tell
her exactly what you
think lpnt d a
d d Justin B Miss
Monkey oh you're also going to come to
[Music]
what GD D thank you gecko man 414 D Tai
D ja 47 D not l
d this is French isn't it how do I
pronounce
this wait you know what let me put it
into
Google I don't want to make a fool out
of
[Music]
myself
reol reol re
easy the mole of the revolution is what
it
says
[Music]
what Sal
the magic D 17 b42 d p RM kfp
d
c mind of the quill a parting tip for
our champion k for setting this all up
thank you I'll have the cats the
archives you girls all have fun good
night yeah that's correct good
job thank you Felix sty thank you for
the red super
chat did you get to watching live huh
nice the collab is a blessing and I'm
crying in Joy oh thank
you it was it was pretty good I would
say I agree I agree I um I'm very proud
of that collaboration I'm glad I
organized it and um it was it was uh
worth it because everyone had fun with
it not only the viewers but also the
girls yeah
I know forand D Gator Gator sour yeah D
thank you K you're the best I have mad
respect for you keep grinding thank you
for shining so brightly and honoring us
with beautiful light thank you yeah the
grind never stops to be honest I'll keep
on looking forward to a time where the
grind stops but it doesn't stop it's
like I can't stop I can't
stop S7 B for the2 Dan big house danan
for the pinky have to go to work so I
will have to catch the Vault great work
setting the sub potential glad to see
everyone having fun thank
you it was a little bit of a process
setting everything up make up making
sure that everything works therefore
needing um testing sessions uh looking
into how the M works and
uh explaining it to the
girls and uh making the
thumbnails and me staying up until 300
a.m. oh no until 8:00 a.m. for it that
so that the other girls have it at a
convenient time and finding a time slot
to begin with organizing everything yeah
it takes a while but oh yeah and the
logo the logo as well got to give a big
up to Spirit snare again he captured the
essence of what I wanted again very
nicely right from the first draft like
that he sent me it was already pretty
[\h__\h] perfect I only made some small
changes with the
colors and but he nailed it from the
GetGo pretty much
yeah he he gets what I need
you can reuse it yeah this one I guess I
can reuse
yeah that is that is
true okay uh Char 1765 D Char 1765 dun
Andrew Garcia Dan Tai Dan Mary Pippin
dun is is 2,500 PHP a pinky or a red one
I think it's a red one
maybe do you guys
no a red one okay today is my birthday
and I couldn't have asked for a better
present than this thank you so much for
organizing this amazing collab from
scheduling preparing fil news holding
practice sessions and fighting against
the in law you've been such a blessing
in my life thank you that's very kind of
you thank you for acknowledging my
efforts and uh supporting me with my
Endeavors and happy happy little bit
beled birthday to you
yay happy birthday to you happy birthday
to you happy birthday dear marry
Pippin wait marry Pippin is that the
name from one of the Lord of the Rings
Hobbits happy birthday to you it is
isn't
it oh yeah yeah it is right
it's both of their names yeah Mary and
Pippin oh Mary pippens you got good
taste good
name me
liking I love Lord of the
Rings but anyone who doesn't know for my
birthday this year um my fans one of my
fans
organized um got me a got me um a
birthday video message from the actor
from Sam
SC I'm not fxing at
[Music]
all Mar pipp GD D Bob business D LP d m
d MF
D oh my God Miss fist I know exactly
where you learned that because I feel
like I saw you you in the chat
there pretty sure I did I see I saw a
lot of you in the chat over there mhm I
I see you there
uhhuh it's all right it's all right
she's she's I mean I'm there too
so
no
sure just um take a seat uh in the usual
room and uh I'll talk to you
[Music]
later thank you for the pinky so much
for woke Yol exactly so much for
that I don't I don't want to you guys
can do whatever you want okay but I'm
I'm not going to I'm not going to deny
that I might be a little bit
jealous when you guys go somewhere else
but it's okay you can go anywhere you
want it's not like I can't
but no I don't care I don't care go
wherever you want I don't care just just
come
back and and come back with some milk
for God's
[Music]
sake bre the [\h__\h]
air you are first for me
boss but am I
the am I the only one that's more
important there they go there they go
with their
ass no
I don't care I don't care
whatever
[Music]
whatever fny
this not like I care not like I care I
don't care I don't care I really don't
care you do what you want to
do I don't care a little bit I don't
care I don't
[Music]
care I need a lawyer I'm your lawyer I'm
your lawyer and I'm going to put you
into the usual room that's that's your
[Music]
sentence not thank you for the pinky I
thought for sure it was Watson last
round uh I don't know which one round
you mean did did am I ever getting Poss
she didn't right yeah she didn't but she
was doing a good job of being detective
she was very
active I mean I mean I say she was doing
a good job but she kept on susing me
even though it was never
me so I guess uh she she was
trying uh Petri ch
action ity thank you for the Triple red
Super Chat oh my God thank
[Music]
you hey C I just wanted to let you know
that even if I can't Super Chat you or
catch every stream sorry I'm still die
hard for you a hear that guys hear that
that's that's that's a good example and
I'm trly grateful for who you are and
the work you put into your streams
today's my birthday and I don't
celebrate it for reasons but y all made
it fun
oh you should celebrate it come
on love you and all my toyful S
bu
why thank you and happy happy little bit
belated birthday is always a birthday at
any given day
yay I'm glad we made you birthday
enjoyable m
let
oh let me sing you happy birthday happy
birthday to you happy birthday to you
happy birthday dear action
ity happy birthday to
[Music]
you nailed [\h__\h] should get a gramy for
that happy
birthday thank you so much for the
generous donation is way too much but I
do appreciate it really thank
you I'm glad you like my streams and
me love to you and much happiness and
health Ginger Ranger 13 D sh Jacob 47
out thank you for the pinking why are
you always on your out by the way what
happened to your not out to you main huh
what
happened it was my birthday too happy
birthday
Bianca H even with the Scuf this was one
of the craziest collabs what scuff are
you talking about I've seen in the while
what a frail I would say the scuff is
not even worth mentioning it was it was
it was too good it was all good no no
scuff at all no no no no no no no when
we look back on that collab we don't
want to think about scuff we want to
think
about the perfect collab it
was counting chickens d e thank you for
the red super
chat great job on organizing another
awesome B collab Tel thanks for being so
hardworking you amazing fire BB thank
you it's my
pleasure um as I said many times before
before um I I would be glad if uh the
other girls also sometimes maybe um
invite me to
collabs um but if they don't then I'll
just invite everyone to collabs and I'll
have I'll always be the party uh leader
I
guess uh but I enjoy doing it
so yeah
[Music]
do more unexpected collabs like
Minecraft with know well you were
suggesting that to me but suggesting an
unexpected collab is like how that's
like well it only happens randomly and I
in order to really have those like
random Minecraft collabs I would have to
start later than I normally do and
that's just going to mess up my uh
expect you
unexpect it's going to mess up my whole
like normal streaming schedule and my
sleep schedule and everything and yeah
overlapping with Ena is sometimes
possible if I stream pretty
long um but
yeah have you tried telling them to
invite you more that that's such a weird
thing to say like
no that sounds so desperate but no it's
like a lot of the collabs also come
together just by some girls in the
Discord being like hey I want to play
this game who wants to join me you need
four people um and yeah so recently for
example for the Halloween week they're
doing that and and it's just games that
I either don't want to play or actually
my schedule is already filled up and all
plan out so I can't add anything anymore
it's like really last minute so I I
don't really uh it's like too late for
me to jump into
that yeah but today today I was happy to
be part of that collab even though Faso
is kind of boring to me at this point
and I think it would be more
entertaining to me if it were a bit
easier to catch those [\h__\h] ghosts
like what why is it it didn't it wasn't
always this weird weirdly
difficult I remember playing
phasmophobia a long time ago and it was
it was manageable back
then they changed something and now it's
so
difficult you just don't know how to
play h
[Music]
name calling for like 20 minutes to get
the ghost show
what you have to do that that's so
boring name calling for 20 minutes are
you kidding
me yeah and there's so many more ghosts
now yeah that makes it also
difficult I don't know Bae was so scared
today so but she says it's only like
with a game like this but like aren't
all horror games kind of like this
I don't know she should play Outlast
huh it was too easy for some people yeah
but they could have just I don't know
added one like difficulty grade why
would they have to just make the whole
game that much more difficult like from
the GetGo why couldn't they have had a
diff more difficult
level for like to choose as an
option huh
I can no I'm not I'm never going to be
anyone's emotional support for horror
games
no that's I'm not the right choice for
the she suggested it yeah well she just
I guess she thought it would fit into a
Halloween week and uh it's a good game
to play with four people if you know
what you're
doing which we didn't know and uh I knew
it from the beginning that it would be
like
this
yeah yeah I mean look at our levels we
all haven't really played the game much
so it was to be
expected if I ever play Fast Mo again
I'm going to promise you I'm going to
play that tutorial and try to get good
on my own but I don't really plan on
playing it anymore anytime soon
Leon scape thank you for the red super
chat in Great British pounds I rarely
see a Great British pounds donation here
on my channel thank
you thanks my close by
neighbor over the sea I see you over the
ocean that stream was a lot of fun can't
wait for the next one thank you what do
you mean next you mean the next H in
Among Us
it's going to take a while I don't want
to I don't want to push it on to them
too early maybe in like a half a year or
so
[Music]
yeah pounds aren't all that common of a
sun
yeah yeah I don't ever see GBP
donations interesting I I don't know do
do do the British not like vtubers very
much is that it I have more Euro Nations
but I guess EUR is in more countries
than GBP
huh that that is true yeah oh what we
good Chaps in it I I don't know I don't
know about that I don't know boot
that 3:00 a.m. for you well it's also
3:00 a.m. for no it's almost 4:00 a.m.
let's
go uh FL flamable d
D for Dan GD Dan for the pinky good day
hot wings GTS K thanks for arranging
this collab it was so fun Sasa collab
Queen thank you I love you thank you
thank you thank you I I had a good time
was a good memory we are here oh where
were you
hiding get out of your hearty
holes yeah yeah we show you have as uh
two two even and you're telling me that
we were not able to find anyone in
Europe
who
fits fits into whole live of English for
real
us come
on thank you here you go
L thank you see I love I love the
British I love their accent and yet they
barely flock to me
they barely flu to me I don't know what
it
is I love them but they don't love me
very
much I'm British but I'm never here
that's a lie I see you here all the
time next gen all EU that would be fun I
would I would like no matter in which
country in Europe they would be I would
travel to them every [\h__\h] month or
have them travel to me or meet meet all
up meet all together up somewhere in one
country I would do that constantly
traveling in Europe is so easy that
would be so much
fun yeah we could do so much stuff
together I just honestly I just want to
travel buddy that's all I want I just
want someone to go traveling with me for
[\h__\h] sake someone with the same job
would be so good because like they have
um the same like I don't know they they
can adjust their schedule to however
they want we can talk about the same
things we can even if we want we can
stream together on the vacation and
stuff like that we can share each
other's stories in in the streams and
all that it would just be so
cool yeah what cons would that
have I want a travel body yeah
are you lonely maybe a little
bit I mean I just kind of rather than
feeling
lonely it's more
like
uh I just haven't been I don't know I
feel like I'm losing connection to the
real
world yeah kind of isolated yeah from
The Real World but also maybe a little
bit from the virtual world as
well interestingly enough oh thank you
more UK gang yes there was a yellow one
too poor show chaps show does L the good
Queen stamp I'll reach you across the
waves why are you guys finally showing
up now why why did I need to call out to
you guys
specifically mobile enough set to enable
you yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I already
have that I mean I have my gaming laptop
now I could even do do proper gaming
streams overseas although with one with
one
screen now doesn't sound very easy but
it's
possible I've been here the entire
time yeah I know I
know have you considered collabing with
UV Troopers outside of whole love yeah
kind of
yeah
M it's just like uh a bit more easy with
like
[Laughter]
K ke you can stay but I guess I'm still
in your room huh I I guess it's I should
get out of here sorry Callie wait I'm
going to get out of
here wait sorry sorry I'm still in her
room that's the thing
[Laughter]
all right okay I I
left that reminds me of that one time
when I I think I was yeah Ena I was
still in ena's room like a year ago when
I was playing Fire Emblem it gave me the
biggest heart attack yeah when Ena
joined my screen I was like where the
[\h__\h] how how how
how I think that was the same principle
anyway it was nice seeing you
that was nice big surprise I completely
forgot what I was just talking about oh
yeah I wanted to say that like the good
thing about
um collabing with like in comparison to
collabing with someone from not whole
life to someone who is in whole life is
like I can be open about you know stuff
like management stuff and rules and all
that and application stuff all that kind
of stuff like organizational things
things so with someone from outside of
whole life I kind of have to be
um very secretive you know
very
very I have to hold back yeah there's
there's a filter that I have to keep on
and it's just I don't know kind of a
bummer you know
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah yeah but still yeah I'm
not completely saying it's not going to
happen anymore the last one was like so
long ago I just don't really have um
much interaction with anyone outside of
whole
life
um I I asked to collab with someone
specific I'm not going to name any names
but I was turned down and I'm not going
to say bye who who or why or whatever
but yeah that's not happening so that's
unfortunate like the
one yeah what yeah well I'm yeah that's
it that's all I'm going to say James
blackberg thank you maybe in the future
maybe in the
future um so many technical things had
to go right for this collab to happen
you and you nailed it bus and under time
pressure too yeah thanks for the great
stream bus it was awesome to see your
big brain on overdrive thank you I'm
very happy very
proud um I uh I'm I'm I think I can uh
write that in my book of
accomplishments I don't don't worry chat
it's okay it's okay it's okay it's it
was a very sad for me but
um
yeah cuz I really like her you know I
feel like there's a a
[Music]
connection
wellow and thank you J slurg thank you
so much I'm glad you enjoyed it yeah and
I hope I could kind of make kfp proud
you know that would be lovely if if
through this
collaboration kfp can be like yo that's
my tental who organized that yeah
thank you Sean R also thank you for the
pinky thank you for the hard work on the
collab Super Chat for your troubles
thank you it was a pleasure my pleasure
I enjoyed it thank you sha I'm glad you
enjoyed the collaboration I hope you had
some laughs I hope it lit up your day I
hope it started a fire today for you in
your heart thank you soon thank you Chad
yeah it's a bit uh weird uh ma D thank
you JC J G GC k e d more proof of your
British F oh thank you Scottish Scottish
wonderful I can speak in the language of
the Scottish people I can you you
understand me don't don't you I I I
can't I can speak Scottish very well you
know but people when can I try to speak
British or whatever people say it sounds
like Scottish
man I'm I'm not even trying to sound
like a squat but you
know it is Scottish they told me
before put put in my mouth I of my PO
fish and chip
I just want to sound as beautiful as you
do I aspire to be uh
as Divine when speaking English as you
this and now the now the UK people are
leaving you see them leaving they're
like oh God this girl [\h__\h] up for real
now did you bite your tongue
it was not that bad come
[Music]
on after the
[Laughter]
dentist when you speak Spanish it sounds
like a French accent when did I speak
Spanish it's we who burst and
it I admire how much you commun toate
I'll give you
that thank you ban H hit hitner hitch
hitch H
hitner how do I say hitchner in a a
British way British
H I
can't I'm just trying to
sound like you guys it's so beautiful I
love those
hitchn hitchn
H it it it without the H okay oh when I
said Kaz Deo it sounds like
French ah because of poo it was po well
I've learned that now de po
[Music]
what what do you
mean Camp is way
better thank you that is
right that is
right I'm not a
[Music]
chicken
drent thank you for the red super
chat thanks for organizing this
absolutely awesome you're welcome we
need some big events like this every
once in a while
right right we need some stuff like this
to look forward to and and connect and
get those funny interactions from the
members maybe even interactions from
people who usually don't collab with one
another
M you're welcome thank you for watching
and supporting and watching my point of
view thank
you thank you n yummy thank you m a and
mck mck mik gr junor thank you
D
OD Anon m
zero
X zero
[Music]
X thank you for the red super
chat to our young and beautiful oeno
this was very fun collab lots of funny
moments thanks for arranging this thank
you for
watching I'm glad you enjoyed it I hope
I hope you had a lot of fun watching
it thank you so much Among Us RNG is
based on
PING
what no
way does that that Mak sense wait wait
so what the one with the lowest ping
gets uh
impostor
yeah a cron is
spy that sounds
stupid where's the proof
[Music]
Ena Kelly Bay and but Ena is is not in
Asia we were on the Asian
server but she's not in Asia that makes
no
sense Iris okay Callie
[Music]
okay ba I guess
okay no
you know shows as Japan and Amica that
has absolutely nothing to do with that
you can s your country to anything you
want in Mario Kart in the Nintendo
online store flaming pants d g shell d z
Snow do d r d hi smoothie I'm not done
yet baby hi I'm almost done I'm almost
done mom's almost done
baby baby baby almost done I'm going to
just read these super chats and then I'm
going to end it as like zombie d and
Bruni a sf2 d wandering worm D motion
for the pinky be proud of yourself tent
you really organized this entire event
and it went perfectly while also having
a stellar whole talk within the same 24
hours yes that's also something I'm
really proud of it was kind of crazy of
me to put um both Hol talk and this uh
event on the same day for
me uh cuz yeah for Hol talk I had to
prepare a lot and uh then for among us
as
well it was a bit um crazy but I didn't
want to have H talk in the week of
Halloween because I didn't have time for
it and same with among us so I had to do
it beforehand
M oh thank you Son thank you for the
pinky are you going to make a
rainbow thank you so much I'm glad you
like that Fire Emblem stream back then
tan oh wait I didn't finish reading your
hard work paid off and we got a great
collab none of this would have happened
without
you I guess
so thank you thank you so much motion
yeah hard working T always hard
working look at my schedule not a single
day
off n don't worry the Monday is kind of
a day off now
[Music]
t for
for
[Music]
thank you s SC de D naked chicken d c
chicken Dragon firear
KF Jolly d k sleep schedule bye-bye D
winner guy D S7
B2 Luka
umbr K
[Music]
cats Papa thank you for the red super
chat I can see the End by the way
T I always believe in you thank you for
organizing this wonderful stream you are
really the best I love you mama and get
some rest thank you thank you for
believing in
me
than means a lot to me thank you for
your sweet support Fafa I hope you
enjoyed the
stream I hope you had some laughs and
some good
moments thank you for watching my stream
supporting it and for your generous
donation I give you a
kiss I appreciate it thank
you again
and
and we are
[Music]
oops all right then I'm going to go to
bed now maybe eat one more one more
small
snack rest of the super chats are going
to be read
and maybe after Alice if I got time I
don't know for how long I'm going to
play the
game actually I wonder how long the game
itself is cuz I wasn't planning into
making it as serious but madness Returns
playtime oh it's pretty short oh my
stomach what the [\h__\h]
it's okay I'm already f it was just for
one moment a big like
ouch uh main story average 14 hours Main
and Extras average 16 and a
half H we could finish
it we could kind of finish it I'll see
what you guys think of it when we are
done with the first
stream I don't no
[Music]
I'm okay I'm okay I'm okay oh my God
smoothie is sleeping under my desk she's
so
cute she's like sleeping all the way
stretched out like not curled up but
like like a long
noodle she wants belly rubs yeah that
position means she wants belly rubs but
she's in a dangerous position because if
I move my chair I might roll over
[Music]
her this is special because normally
when I stream she's far away but now she
chooses to be here
I think she likes me more and more
recently she she's been like cuddling
with me and and um kneading while I'm
cuddling with her every day and today I
was when I wasn't able to get out of bed
I was chilling in bed with my B bathrobe
doing some stuff on my laptop and
smoothie was sleeping next to my hip and
suddenly I feel something massaging my
hip through my
bathrobe it was smoothly kneading my
bathrobe and it felt so
sweet it was so cute her little paws
going
like so
cute it's so cute how they like neat the
movement with their paws is so
cute I remember back in the day in the
day it was really rare to see uh her
kneading but at some point she started
doing it more and more first she would
only do it with my clothes on the ground
but now she does it on my bed the whole
time even with
um you're not no I mean of course you
always lose to cat even with even with
like fabric that's not even like fluffy
she still does it now like she's really
happy yeah display of affection right
yeah it was never a competition
[Music]
exactly either it's because she's
getting older because she just got used
to to the environment and she likes me
more maybe I'm nicer to her
n I've always been
nice yeah I was so worried that they
wouldn't really remember me when I would
go back after Japan or like I mean they
definitely would remember me but maybe
not like me that much anymore be like
attached to to someone else or not find
a way to attach to me anymore but
thankfully that didn't happen
yeah okay I'm going to go now it's 4:00
a.m. so good night and I'm going to
sleep hopefully 1 hour earlier than
[Music]
yesterday good night guys I love you see
you see you in Alice madness
[Music]
Returns
boohoo spoopy Halloween week starting
from today
woo
wo
wow so scary and enj when we say us in
trick or
treat byebye
[Music]
for