[Music]
[Applause]
Look to your left, look to your left, smile and you're ready to go Start
running Do
n't look
back
Look forward If you're hungry
[Music] Get a
rice ball Dessert Strawberry and be happy
You come too and enjoy
the world
[Music]
Happy  Right
[Music] It's
begun!
Yoyo
3rd Hololive Movement Meeting I guess that
means yes. No, the
opening was great. It
was great. The video
and the song too.
So yes,
thank you to all the viewers for coming.
Thank you very much. Thank you
very much to all the parents and guardians for the sports day this year as well.
Thank you very much for your support.Also, I'm
late in introducing you, but I will be serving as MC this year as well.My name is
Mio Wolf and
Miko Sakura.Thank you very much.
Please, thank you for your support this year as well. Let's do our best. Let's do our best. Let's go.
Let's do our best.
Let's do our best. And this year too. You're
working hard as a little bit of support.  I
would like Subaru Ozora to be in the MC seat until the opening ceremony is over. I
'm Subaru Ozora, and I'm a member of the sports day executive committee. I
'll do my best as the yellow team. Thank you very much.
Now, I
'd like to start the opening ceremony.
[Music] That's
it.  First of all,
let's get the players in. Well, they
lined up
properly. Thank you.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] [Music]
[Applause] [
Music] [Applause] [Music] [
Applause
] [Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] Let's get
along and get along and get along.
[Laughter]
That's why  Well then, let's have another team.
Please invite them. That's
it. [Applause] [Applause] It's a big deal, but that's right
.
[Laughs]
Okay, first of all, let's talk about Miko Sakura, the executive committee chairperson of this live sports day.
Please give your opening remarks.
Thank you very much for all your support and practice today.
Thank you very much, despite your busy schedules. I'm very,
very happy to be able to gather here again like this, so today I'm
going to take  I
hope you enjoy it. Please have fun. And
by the way, have you noticed that I opened the black box in the back?
Look, I've
checked that over and over again, and
now I have 54 Holonile members.
So, I'd like to make a little fan mark for 54 people.
[Music]
[Applause]
But I'malso
grateful to all the fans who support me,
so let's
all show the good things to the fans today.  Let's
go!
Yes, thank
you very much. Thank you very much.
Next, I
received a message from the company name of the president of Cover Co., Ltd.
Yes, please give me a greeting from the company name. Thank you for your
hard work.
So, I
remember feeling proud that I didn't
end up in last place. Did you practice a lot? Please try your best so that you don't have any regrets.
Also, please prepare early for today,
Miko-san, Mio-san, Subaru-san, and help out.
Thank you to all the Hololive members for your hard work. Thank you to
all the listeners. Thank you for your continued support.
Thank you very much. I
hope that the organizers and listeners will come together and make the sports day a great one.
Well, I'll change it to my greeting.
Please do your best, everyone. Thank you very much.
[Music] It's
okay to sleep. It's
okay. It's okay. All of a sudden. Is
everyone still? Yes,
OK. Well, we've finished greeting the business names.
The meeting.  Yes, the
players will be sworn in.
Red team
Fubuki Shirakami,
white
team
Amaneko-san,
yellow team Ozora Spy-san,
please wear super leather, please.
[Music]  This
is my friend A, the venue announcer. It's the
7th of Spring.
Thank you very much.
Please come to the voice channel for the three athlete-teacher figures and the contestant channel.
For A-chan and Nodo-chan, there is a
voice for everyone in the competition.  Thank you very much
for being in charge of making announcements about channel changes, etc.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much
.
Sensei, all of us, the players, are
here
November 6, 2022
[Music]
That
Nekanata Ozora Subaru
How did this happen? The
three sworn players,
please go back to each group's channel. That's
why.  Thank you very much, you
are a wonderful athlete teacher.
[Music]
Yes,
this concludes the opening ceremony.
Everyone,
please move to the fencing PvP venue. Please. So, everyone,
let's move.
Yes.  Yes,
while we were on the move, yes,
I would like to explain fencing PvP from my house. Please, yes. What is
fencing PVP? It
is a competition in which three people from each team are selected to fight one-on-one.  The players
fight one by one in the order of the mid-ranking generals on the other side. The
winner gets 10 points, and
if it's a tie, 5 points
are added each. Yes,
by the way, if you
hit three times, you win.  I
feel like it's necessary, so I want everyone to
do their best.Well, it
's too hot for a draw.Well,
what's the point of this game?The
winner of this competition gets 10 points, and the draw is 10 points.  Um,
we both have 5 points here, yes. Ah, hey, I'm
sorry, I
might have gotten a little natural.
But the point of this game,
or
rather, the point of this game.
also
Is it reading to each other? I read it
aloud. I wonder if that side will rush in first, or if it will become a town. The one that rushes in is also pretty strong, so I see. Ah, yes, yes, then just read the front and say, "Let's hit each other."  That
's right, I'm looking forward to it. Well, first of all, was
there something like which is the right
or the left?
Which is which? Over there,
looking from this audience seat, white is on the left and
red is on the right. Now, let's have them move like that.
[Music]
Can you do it? Everyone, you can't. Of course you can. You can
do it.  That
's great. The
right guy is here. We're having a strategy meeting. Hey,
let's have an
interview and
ask him about his enthusiasm.
Well, I think I'll start with the red team now.
Yes.
Nyan Hello, I
think Ah, can you hear me? Is it the
red-red team?
Yes, so the red team in fencing PvP is Azu-
chan, I don't know who is mid-ranked, but
Noel.
Everyone, I would
like to hear your enthusiasm,
though.  What was your
enthusiasm? Will it be one person at a time,
or will it be
everyone?
Everyone
will practice together, right?
[Music]
It's the feeling.
That's
right, let's do our best. It looks
like we're having fun.
Why are you giving it up?
Hey, I'll
go. I'll
come back. You
were strong.
[Laughs] That's what
I said.
Thank you. Thank you.
[Music]
Thank you.  Now, let's move on to the white team.Okay,
everyone from the white team.
[Music] Are you
being beaten? You
keep hitting me, aren't you?
[Music] I
would like to ask the three of you how you are enthusiastic.
How are you?
Yes,
how are you? On the other hand, what do you think? Leader: It's like
we don't like it. You know, we should practice.  Chan: It
's strong, and I'm
going to talk about the bonds.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Thank you very much.
[Music]
[Laughter] It's
scary, it's scary, yes.
Thank you very much, everyone in the White group.
Thank you very much.
Now then,
White Team,
Red Team
[Music]
How would you like it?
White Team, we've had quite a few
meetings, right
?
[Music] It
's the first class, so don't put too much effort into it. Well, I guess
it's a little bit.  What is it?
Thank you, Kanata Amane, America.
[Music]
But that's right.
Well, I'd love for you to use it.
Wow, that's right. I'd
like you to keep the White Team, too.
[Music]
But I don't know what you think, but from
what I saw yesterday, Watamei and others
were really strong, and
ah, that's right, Dodo was crying, and Iroha was also
really strong, right? Yes, hey,
did you complete the move? Yes, I
heard you.
Yes, I can hear you. Yes, I can hear you.
Also, could you please right-click on that entry button?
Yes, it's
done, yes, it's here.
Thank you. Then, see you there.  The
person on the other side asked me to enter the door.
Yes, I
understand.
[Music] That
scary threat from before was amazing!
[Music]
This
has become so easy. It's
even easier to get in. It's even easier to leave.
Nno
[Music]
Congratulations
[Laughter]
[Music]
Thank you very much. Well then,
thank you Azuki-san and Kanata-san. Next, let
's move on to the mid-career selection.
Mr. Watanabe and Mr. Lamy are both contestants.
Please move to the channel. Please, do your
best.
No, it's a bit different from practice, and the
tension is amazing. No, it's already
decided. This is how the match will be decided.  It seems
like it's hard to get ahead. It's
like a hardcore mode, isn't it? It's
amazing how the announcements come in. It
feels
authentic. The players have no choice but to enter.  It looks
like you're all set. Now,
please come to the channel, both of you.
[Music]
Do you both look like you're ready?
Are you nervous? Just a little more.  I
think I'm going to treat that sheep a little bit like this.
[Laughs]
Okay, everyone, please get ready for the start.
Okay, then,
let's go to the
mid-ranks. Let
's
start. Okay, let's start. Okay, let's do this together.  It's
time to stop.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] I
'm coming. Please come in the door
.
Thank you. Yes, Sand. I'll
go. Please. I'll go
.
[Music] [
Music]
[Music]  ] I
can protect Genghis Khan.
Thank you for this decorative animal.
[Music] Thank you very much.
Yes,
thank you for the Chukyo Line. Now, let
's move on to the general battle. Mr. Noel, Mr. Iroha, please move to the contestant channel.
Please, yes, so it's a target match. It's
almost time for the mountain.
So, I'd like to reward the White team for being 1st-see.
So, will you enter? What do you think? Hey,
Irohaha, I've already entered. Yes.  I'm
here. You
pressed the entry button here.
Hey,
as someone who wields a sword, I can't afford to lose
.
[Music]
Okay, so
please press the button to start the match. Okay, let's
go.  It's a
symmetrical battle.
Excuse me.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Yes,
[Music] It's a
competition, right? That's it. The
competition is,
uh, how many teams and how many teams
? Next up.
White and a little more
red vs. yellow. Red vs. yellow.
Looking from the audience seats, the
left side is red and the
right side is
yellow. The
red team will be moved to the opposite direction,
please.
Well then, let's ask the yellow team if they're really excited.
Hey
[Music]
Well, if you say yes, let
's move on to the Golden Team versus the Red Team,
so let's play the
Golden Team's
fencing PVP.  Is that Aki-
chan? Yes, and Yo-san
is different.
Subaru is
the middle-ranking officer,
and my father is the general, so I'm
glad to hear that.
What do you think of the group's enthusiasm?
Even if you say no, you
can really do it mentally and physically.
[Music]
[Music] [
Laughter]
[Laughter]
[Music] I guess it's
like moving, thank you.
How about the next battle?  The
next battle is going to be a battle, but
everyone wants to win.
But things
are starting to get a little more fuzzy than before, are you okay?
[Laughter]
[Music]
Sports Accountant
Please give your friendship to the contestant channel
Well, it's the big round. Red is a bit
too strong and I hope it doesn't become a bit one-sided game.
As a white person,
That's true since they fight once, right? No,
but it was a little fluffy.
Compared to the first time of the Red Team, the
face and other things looked a little different.  It
started to feel like lunch.
[Music]
Basically,
everyone is pretty fluffy,
so I guess that's it. So
what was that wow thing you mentioned earlier?
[Laughs] So,
everyone,
get ready.  Are you sure?
Please press the entry button
Yes, please, thank you. I
have an entry. I can
hear you. I can
hear you.
Thank you very much for standing in front of the door.
Pochi: I
'm nervous. Start: I'm
going to reap Azuki-chan's life.
[Music]
But you see, Leader Shirakami
was coaching Neka, so I see
.
That's a replay.  Yes, it's this year.
It seems like you can now enjoy longer replays on the sponsored Neane screen. That's
great. Yes, thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Hey Ozora.
Subaru-san,
please visit the contestant channel. Please come to the contestant channel.
Good luck.
Subaru Ozora, member of the sports day executive committee. He's
talking. He
looks terrible. His
eyebrows are definitely going to get thicker. Is this
thing that withered this sheep okay?
I'm not there yet. I'm going to fight with the ducks.
[
Music] I'm going to fight. Thank you. [Applause] [Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
Thank you, thank you
[Music]
[Laughter]
Well then, let's
move on to symmetry, Mr. Noel Shirobane,
please move to Tokoyami and the morning contestant channel.Yes,
333, so it's the first mountain.Yes
, the yellow team is also looking good.Here we are, oh
my,
Towa.  Thank you very much, Mr.
Zero
[laughing]. I
think he has become much stronger.
That's not the case. What is this music?
[Music] You
may be thinking about various things, but the leader...  I'm
going to go and say something as
usual. I see. You
say you're thinking about it, but I'm not
thinking about anything. That's
true. So,
please start your business. Mother, please
enter the door.  Please stand in front of me. Ah,
thank you for being there on time. Now, let
's go to the final match between Red and Yellow.
Yes, that's
fine, since we just made red bread.
[Music]
[Music] It
's done. That's
fine. Congratulations.
Thank you.
and
A while ago, Red got a shutout against Red and White,
but now we're wondering if
White, who was shut out, and
Yellow, who has a 2-to-1 advantage over Red, can
certainly compete to some extent. That's
true. What do you think of this?  For the white team, but for the white team,
well, this fencing game
requires a little bit of luck,
so I
think there's a chance that they can win.It's
like 3 questions.
So yes, I'd like the right side of the left foot to
be gold, please.
[Music]
So, are
the Staminers gathered? Are they
gathered? Well, let's start with the interview.
Yes, yes. I think it would be
better if the colors were white and yellow. Both of them.  I do
n't think it's the side that has more experience in fighting, right? I
didn't buy either the right or the left, or the right and the left,
right? Let's
hope for the best from the white team.
Well, first of all, let's go here.
White is here. White is here.
So, let's be serious,
and we're going to be a little bit nervous. I
wonder if we can beat Yellow. We might have been more serious.
Let's
try our best.
If we're destined to lose, we'll win. We're the
strongest.
That's why we say yes, so please do your best.
Thank
you.
Next, I'd like to go to the yellow team. Please
[Music]
[Applause]
This is an interview.
It's an interview.
[Applause] It's the
third and final round.
What do you think of the yellow team fighting against the white group?
No, I'm sure you'll say what you always say, Mr. Netowa. We
'll fight at high volume
[laughter]
No, Towa-san, please say what you always say. It's
mental and physical passion.
[Applause]
[Music]
[Applause] [
Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] I
have physical power. OK, leave it to me.
Do your best.
Okay then.
Hero group vs. Yellow group.
Front line.  I would like to go, Kanata Amane,
Mr. Aki Rosenthal,
please move to the contestant channel.
Good luck. It goes by so quickly
though. It
feels like we are saying things like this to each other.  It
's really funny, and the
fireworks
made me realize once again how good it was that we were able to implement it.
[Music]
[Laughter] [Music
]
[Laughter] I'll
save the gorilla this time.
Thank you.
[Music]
Thank you.  Mr. Start, so let's
start the front line between the white group and the golden team.
[Music]
Start
[Laughter]
Well, it was a great battle.
Thank you, Kanata and Aki.  Well
then, I'd like to go to the live broadcast.
Lamy Snow Skin, Subaru Ozora,
please move to the joint secretary channel.
Yes,
no,
yes, there may be three from here. I
think I'll start getting into that mood if I buy that one earlier.  Yes,
that's true.
If that's the case, everyone would be
jumping up and down with joy because the white team won.
[Laughs]
That's right, that's the kind of spirit you have to win.Then, crush them
with your high school mentality and physicality.
Start
[Applause]
Yoshiyoshi Ikenami
[Music]
[Applause] That's a
shame. [
Applause]
If you say yes, you'll be found by the Subaru boy in the sky. He
was just barely fit.  It's
okay if you're being poked a little bit. Good luck, good luck. [Applause] So
let's move on to the next one.Okay, now let's move on to the general battle.Moiroha-
san VS
Tokoyami Towa-san
Please move to the contestant channel. Please.  The
competition here is also a bit heated.
Well, the Sensing PvP has finally
reached its final battle.
[Music]
Anyway, I'm in it, but it's okay  That's
right, what's going on, what's going on, what's going on?
And
where did Kakogawa go? I guess he's not here yet. Please move
to the Airohada Voice Channel.
[Music]
That's why I bought it.  I'm going to fight.
That's right. That Iroha sword is really
sharp, so it's okay. It's okay. I
wanted to bring it with me
just now. So yes, it
's a little yellow.
Although it is strong, white also won once,
so I picked up the section chief once
and said yes, Miko-san, are
you okay with that? Yes,
Shi's PVP fencing against yellow is, well,
this is the final match.  Good luck
everyone. Let's
go.
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] You
did your best.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you
. Excuse me.
[Music]  I
feel like Towa-sama is unstable.
Ah, that's right. I said yes,
and the first competition ended. Yes, that's
right.
[Music] I
'm thinking of having it displayed. Yes, that's
right.  No, I don't care what happens.
White, you
did your best, right? Well, the White team did their best. They did their best, didn't they
? The
next thing they did was to show the leader's stubbornness. They were
fighting each other. Wait a minute, the
white hairs said, "Stop it, stop it, you guys."
Stop! What are you doing? [Laughs] It's all good. Well, I guess. [Music] The part where you're training is OK. So it looks like you're done.
OK, now that you're in the prefecture, there's no space left. Let's go and
visit.  I'm
going to make a specific announcement.
[Music]
[Applause]
Please, please, please
Alright here,
boat race contestants,
go to the voice channel, the contestant channel.  I would like
Thank you in advance.
Could you please move the voice channel along with the venue move?
[Music]
I would like the voice channel to be moved as well.
Red Team:
Fubuki Shirakami, Omar Polka, and White Team:
Crying  For the six Ayame-san,
please go to the contestant channel, the voice channel, and the contestant channel.
[Music]
Thank you very much.
While we are on the move, I would
like to explain the competition. Yes.
Please, yes.A
water boat race is a competition in which teams of two people
ride boats and compete for speed.Yes,
one team from each team will participate.
[Music]
Divided into operators and hindrances.The
hindrances will be fireworks and darkness.  You can use your attacks to
hinder the opposing team. Yes,
it's a competition where 1st place gets 30 points, 2nd place gets 20 points, and 3rd place gets 10 points.
[Music] This
competition requires a lot of manipulation.
Everyone seems to be practicing fairly well,
so I
think that being able to use the controls well is going to be very important. Yes, even during that practice, you
know, that competition is golden.  I
had various members help me make it, but
today everyone also made it, so I
made some changes,
so at the time of practice, there were only two.  There
was no exit, but this time there are
three, and there are
no more dead ends, so I
wonder how it will be affected by the game.It's
quite difficult, so I don't like this maze.
That's right, the name is Cat Tunnel, and
if you were to encounter that dark attack, it would be quite difficult,
so I'm wondering how it will turn out.
Timing is also quite important, right? So, let's talk
to each team.  I'd
like to have an interview with you.
Okay. Well
then, let's start with the red team. [Music] I'll start with the red team's interview. Can you
hear the red team? Alright,
good, good, yes. The
driver is Fubuki Shirakami.  And the obstruction is yes, the
obstruction is that pom-pom.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Yes, the white team's control is Hosho Marine,
and the
obstruction is everyone and Aqua.
Yes, Aquamaringo is complete, right? High price.
Kill the base. Next,
try to beat him to death from that polka.
[Laughter]
[Music] In
accordance with sportsmanship, let's go to the
Kigumi interview.
Next up is E-
Kino.  As for the group,
there is a lot of control, and then there is
interference.
Thank you very much. Well then, please,
let's
get over it with some mental and physical passion.
[Applause]
[Laughter]
Isn't this a bit of a yellow card
?
[Laughter] It's
been two laps.
Yes, it looks
like all three teams are ready.
I'd like you to start.
[Music]
That's
fine. Let's do our
best. Start. Good luck.
[Music]
[Applause]
[  Music]
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Music] I ca
n't ride it alone I
designed it, but I can ride it
[Music]
Yes, I'm the first one to come today
Hey.
[Music]
I guess you'll be the first to find this song even if you can't catch it with your butt.
[Laughs] Well
then, red hair in first place.
Please tell me what you think.
Nyappa, it's the bond between foxes. That's how we
practiced the day before.  That's all I was able to do,
but that's all I could do. Do
n't try to appeal to me the day before. Please
stop trying to appeal to me when you two practiced together.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
White team, how was it?Aquamaringo
Well, in that maze, which is so exquisite, there
was just a disturbance.Who
threw the disturbance over there?
Excuse me.
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Music] It
was good during practice.  However,
when I was interrupted a little earlier, I
didn't practice which route to take, so I
guess that's when I was discharged from the hospital. I was a little confused.
[Laughter]
Yes.
So that's it.
[Applause]
[Music] Here are the
highlights.
Well, if you're on the contestants' channels, please
go back to your respective team's channels. Thank
you.
Sunday was over in the blink of an eye.
Hey.  But by the way, everyone,
please take your time.
Mio-san
said that it's already her birthday.
But now, that
amazing lap time is
perfect. Is it
true? It
says 15 minutes after the boat race ends.  There is  I've
been winding it for 10 minutes. It
's true.
[Laughs] It
doesn't hurt. It's fine.
It's fine, Michael. It's
great. It feels good. Thank you. Thank you. So,
did you
score?
Red.
Group 7
has 30 points, and Yellow Sea has 50 points.
[Music]
[Applause]
It seems that they are in the lead.
What do you think of the red team's 70 points? Everyone
[Music] [Music] It's pretty bad, isn't it? But after all, it was these three who made the fencing decision, and they interfered at the right time. [Applause]
-
[Music]
Thank you very much.  But isn't Laplace drunk
?
Next, I
'd like to interview the white team, which is in last place.Yes, that
's right.Hello.  There's a
white button.Yes, I
'm going to win.I'm going to win with Daruma-san, and I'm
going to be unrivaled with everyone.I've
been practicing a lot, so leave it to me.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music]  ]
No, but we showed the strength we could muster, so I want to
pass on this strength to the second half of the team and
work together as one to aim for the championship.
Please.
Now, it's
almost time to get ready. It looks
like the members aren't here yet, so I'd like to ask you to wait a little longer, and I'd like to connect with you by telling you a little bit about us. I'd like to see what you think so far, Miko-san.
After all, it's the
same as usual. Well, it seems
that there
was almost no practice time for the first session. It was the
night before, or rather, it
took until the day of the day, so it
was pretty much completed.  It
was a little difficult to get them to practice for the competition, but
this year they thought they
had to make it really early and the practice period was long.
[Music]  There are
members who wanted to participate today but couldn't.
[Music] There are times when we
all didn't have time to practice together, and
that's the case, but the
other day we tried to find a time to practice together, and we
practiced quite a bit in the village as well.  Looks like he was doing something like that
Oh yeah, that's really what happened
. It's amazing that this result has led to this result.
Everyone is serious about the video. I can see that this year will be particularly different.
Also, the competition itself is pretty good.  It's powered up,
and with gimmicks and
things like that, you can do some really interesting things.It's
really
amazing.In the first
half, I thought I was creating a competition that was pretty much based on entertainment.  I'm
sure the
team
[music] was
really happy about what we've been waiting for.
So, it looks like the preparations are complete, so we'd
like to welcome the ID members as guests. Well
then,
everyone, go
home.  To all ID members,
please enter through the entrance gate. Please come. It's
open.
[Music]
-
For some reason, Mel-chan also entered with us.
Well, I'd like everyone to gather together,
okay?
[Music]
Well, that's why this time, we're
inviting members of the ID group from that house as our guests. Each of us will
introduce ourselves to everyone.  I think I'll give it to
you. But first, let's
start with the red team. Let's start with the body.
[Music]
Okay, so what's next?
Hello
[Music] I'm
the Beast, and I'm risking my life today.
Thank you very much.
[Music]
Hello everyone, Hard Live ID.
The key to the key is the frog.
Thank you.
Please. I
have a lot of elytra.
That's why Minecraft is
amazing.
[Laughs]
That's it.  That's amazing,
that's amazing, yes, that's why I'm going to ask these three
to do their best.Yes, and the white team will be the first.Bay-
chan,
yes,
Dr.
U.S.A.
Scary, sorry, that
's a lie.
[Music] There were
also illustrations.There were a lot of them.
[Music] I
'm Iris from English. I'll win today.
Thank you very much.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Yes, and the
third member of the white group will
be next year, next year. Yes, I'm Pavlia Leine, a 2nd generation member of Peace Sora Indonesia.
I'm going to run hard today.
Thank you very much for your support, Go Go Lighting Aichi.
Thank you very much.  I
would like to introduce
Takanashi from the yellow team. I've
been practicing the relay with Muna-chan.
Thank you very much.
Yes,thank you.
[Music] There you are.
[Music] I'll
be waiting for a moment. The
thread is being transmitted.
And finally, it's
Nyamamu Village.I'm going to raise a horror fidlin car.Thank
you very much.
[Music]
Hey
That's it.  I would
like these nine en and ID members to join us as guests, and then the second half of the team to join us and move to the venue where Daruma-san fell.
[Music]
Yes, then, the
second half of the team.  We're also going to
start broadcasting, so we're going to be on the
move for
a little while.The competition time is going to be a little bit
later, so I
guess I'll take it easy.I'll probably
take a break as well.Okay,
Daruma-san is going to fall.  At the Dano venue
While we're picking up the cat, it's a bit late. I'd like to
talk to the second half of the team. Is it
okay if I ask them? Yes, I
understand. Then, I
think I'll make it feel like Red Chain. Starting with the red hair, I would like to interview the second half of the team.
[Music]
Can you hear me?Yes, I can hear you,
but please wait a moment.I'm
going to call the second half of the team back from completion.Thank you very much.The
universe is
about to press the button.That's
right.Yes, I destroyed the button yesterday.
So,
Survival Moo-
chan hasn't
done anything for a while.
[Music]
Hello
[Applause] I
'm sure the team will start streaming soon, but I'd
love to hear your enthusiasm and thoughts on the first half.  I think I'd like to ask you something,
but what do you think? The
second half of the Red Team is up
to this point, and
Laplace is thinking about something. I
hope you'll do a little bit of that while you're preparing.
[Laughs]
Well, I watched the second half of the show quite a bit. It seemed
like it only came out just now. I was
watching the show while everyone was sulking and asking if Laplace was drunk. I was
worried, but it's okay. He's been taking a break from time to time, so he seems
to be okay.  But it's still okay.
[Music]
Well, with 70 points, the list
is number 1. I
want to carry on this. The
Red Team is in first place. It was announced that they are now in first place.  It's been a
long time since I've been in the middle of a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time since I've
been in the middle of a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time.  I'll
do my best, I'll do my best.Okay,
thank you.Okay, let's go.Let's
move on to the next white team.By the
way, everyone, here's what happens next.Well, after this, we
passed the preliminaries.
Those who passed the preliminaries moved to the contestant channel. The
flow is that they
go to the contestant channel.  Everyone on the team, no, I beat them all up.If I told them they
did a good job, they probably wouldn't do something like that.I felt like they had some kind of malicious intent. [Music] I don't know if they were on good terms or not.
It's good that we don't understand. We're good friends. Yes,
I think it's the white team. By the way, please
don't talk, just watch. The points are quite
high, so if we
can dominate the top spot, there's definitely a chance for a reversal. That's
right,
Daruma-san's white.  I'll show you the group. They're
losing quite a bit right now. Isn't it the White group?
Finally, let's take a look at the end. Please cut a little.
[Music]
[Music] [
Applause] [Music
]
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter] We
said let's do our best, so Mr. Nedaruma fell
down. He was wearing pretty big shoes, so everyone.
Okay.
Looks like we can start the competition soon.
[Music]
Okay, so we'll
start after introducing the competition.
Yes, yes.  Well, this Daruma-san fell down,
but this is a
competition for all members.When the
sign says ``Yes, yes, Daruma-san,'' he
heads towards the goal.
If you move with the sign of falling, you will die instantly.Yes, so the competition is for Daruma-san to run as close to the goal as possible by 321.Yes, it
is a competition to see how fast you can reach the goal, but be careful not to die.  I guess it's
important to act accordingly,
right?
Even if you get a lot of points, it's
all about the goal.The
first thing to do is to have everyone gather together and get the results of the preliminaries.
After that, the top 15 players will compete in the finals.Yes,
and there are no points in the preliminaries,
but
yes, points will be distributed to everyone in the finals.So, we
will start with the preliminaries, in which everyone can participate.  It's
nerve-wracking. It
's a tense moment.
This year, we've added a little ice smile and things like that. Well, it's
changed a bit. Yeah, that
's right. In the ice area,
if you stop quickly, you'll be skating smoothly like this.  It
feels like instant death,
and the difficulty level has increased a little bit.I
mean, last year, the
judgment was quite high, but this year, we have
made sure that the system is even more precise.  So, I'm pretty
serious, but I've been practicing.
Well, yeah,
well,
before we start the competition, I
'd like to say a few words to everyone that the
competition is about to begin. But yes, I'd like to hear from that announcer, A-chan,
etc.  Can I do that?  Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaahhhhh
Is it okay if I say a few words ``It's about to
start'' I've
got it all right
Everybody
[Music] Are
you ready? Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaahhh  I
think they're doing things and making entries, but
Fubuki says that they want to chat when they get started, so
they all ran out of golden apples and
probably ate them.I see, that's what you mean.You're a
glutton, aren't you?I
can't do it.  Because I've been eating it  You're a
very greedy person. You
're angry. You
're angry.
[Laughs] I
don't know what you're talking about. Are you
ready?
Well, this Daruma-san spilled the beans. However,
everyone participated, so it's quite a
house.  Okay.
[Music] Well,
let's get started. Yes, OK. Here we
go. The
preliminaries have started. We're
all here, so what's going to happen? It
's begun.
[Music]
[Applause] It's been a
success. It's
been.
[Applause]
[Music]
Thank you in advance.
[Applause]
[Music]
I would like to make an announcement. Well, we'll
start with 15th place. Okay.
Employee Iris.
[Music]
Button.
Okay, and 12. Um, and then
[Applause]
[  [Music]
[Music]
Yes, that means the 15th place winners
will advance to the finals.
Mio-san,
will you interview the top three? Yes, that's right.
[Music]
Sui Ishinomaki, starting with the 1st place.
I would like to interview Mr. Kanata Amane, number 1 [Music].
Hey, it's here. It's here. It
was really easy to practice today. I woke up really early in the morning.  I
practiced and
practiced,
but somehow I got 1st place,
but I
couldn't hear the voices saying that there was no point in qualifying.
But do you get points? Do you
think even the lowest place counts as a point? Well,
there's only one piece, so if you're
someone who wants to eat, there's meat in the box at the back.
[Music]
Mercury Hoshimachi  Please come to the contestant channel.
Lost Hoshimachi is here.
Hello everyone. Congratulations.
[Laughs] I was
n't looking left and right, and I thought I was definitely in first place, but I
was definitely in second place.
[Laughs] I
won't forgive you.
If you say yes, next time I'll take first place.Since it
's over, it
's all about how you can stick to your own pace without being distracted by other things.That's
right, I
'll run my own way at my own pace.
[Music]
Now
then, 3rd place.
Yes, I'm 3rd place. My name is Tokoyami.
No, that's right. Next time, I'll take a gun and kill you.
Shut up.
[Music]
It's this bastard's turn in the battle between test humans.  There are
still 15 people left, so that's
right. That's right.
It's really, really bad, so it's scary. Thank you.
[Music]
Please,
please,
[Applause]
Yes, we can go. Well then, the
finals will begin.
[Music]
Do your best, try your best, try your best, try your best,
let's start! Let's do our best!
Now, what's going to happen?
[Music]
Good, no one died, no one was disqualified.
[Music] [Music] [Music]
[Applause]
[Music]
Well then, I thought I'd announce the rankings.
Yes, please
[Music]
Hey, it's okay. I
was nervous for the first time, but it's fine for now.
[Music]
Now, let's move on.
Well, I do
n't have a child.
Okay, 3 points. Yes, and
[Music]  Azuki
ranked 3 minutes, so I'm glad I didn't die,
and
suddenly Iris has 5 points.
[Music]
[Laughter] You
did a great job, and thank you. I'm sorry for the
excuse you made yesterday.  That's what I was
told. Excuse me. I'll
use this information now. Thank you very much.
Mr. Utsunomiya must be confused,
but I can't understand that.
[Music]
Next,
Minato.
[Music]
[Laughs]
I'm the winner of this game,
everyone.
[Music] We
look alike
. It was a real success.
[Music]
What's
up with you? The fact that you've been able to stay at the top without falling is something you
have.
Red has a good jump, so that's what I've always thought.In the
qualifying round, I was 4th
place, so I was 4th place, so I think that's
true.In terms of ability, I think it's really
good.I did my best in the good parts, and I can aim for 1st place.
By the way, yes, there was that.
Canada also came in 5th place, which is pretty average.
Button came in 4th place, which was good. I
'm glad to see a bit of a turnaround here. Daruma-
san's fell.  Well,
once this competition is over, the first half of the teams
will take a break. Yes, that's right.
[Music] Let's
take a look. This is this. This is this. The
red hair has 111 points, after all.
And the white team has come
back with 83 points, which was what I
expected.
Amazing.
And from here, the
gold team has 88 points,
sonow the
white team and the king are very close. It
's a red heat. [
Music]
[Music]
Finally  I hope you say hello to all of them and give them a
pat on the back. I
hope they take a break. I'll
see you all again at the closing ceremony.
Now it's time to move on to the next competition.
[Music] Let
's all move to the place where we're going to kill the mobs.
Finally, we're going to
kill the mobs, but that's right.
Everyone loves killing the
mobs. So that's the first half. Everyone is saying goodbye and stuff, so it's
a little boring.  I guess we can connect. We
need to use our conversation skills to get somewhere far away. Yes, that's right.
Hey,
Sakura Shrine Maiden has put a lot of effort into this decoration this time.
Well, let's put it here and there. That
's the story. This is this tree over here. This is the
hairdresser's tree. I, Sakura Nico,
was in charge of that, and it's
amazing.  When I opened it in the evening, it
suddenly turned into a Christmas tree. It
seems like I'm cursed to become a tree. Is
this what it is? Um, the
Christmas tree starts to be built, so, yeah, that's
right. And
then there's that cat.  Nee cherry tree Mone
Yeah, it's a bit like Nesou from Amikochi.
This is a project, and it's amazing. It's easy to think that it's cherry
blossom petals, but it looks like a strange vase. Do
n't tell me someday.
Hey,
it's a wonderful decoration.  The waiting room is also very unique.Well, the
red team has been preparing this TNT from the very beginning.  The
red team has been
building at an incredibly fast pace from the beginning, but it seems like it's not going to happen.
[Music] It's
starting to invade other spaces more and more, and in the end they
end up building all kinds of buildings in the spaces of the yellow and white teams.  The
group and yellow are surrounding themselves with glass,
protecting the mysterious structure they built inside, as if they are building something.
But
yes, by the way, this is from this year.
Hey, I just finished taking a bath.But,
yes, starting this year, if you've been watching until now, you'll
know that the reply video is
now available.  Yes, I
think it's quite interesting,
but in my free time, I
heard that I can watch some highlights of the reply video, so I'll
take a look at it, so please,
please reply.
That's right  The
video
is very important, so you
can see the faces of the listeners who started it,
so here
is the entrance scene.Each
one has its own personality,
too.Even the opening ceremony.This
year was the most sluggish.Well, that's
true.
[Laughs]  I
think I must have lost the script.
Yes, and then he said that PVP was pretty hot.
Well, it was pretty
hot. I think it was perfect for the first event.  Well, the
White team lost quite a bit here,
but yeah, I'll see
later on. The White team's Burn Sea drama has
begun.
Hmm,
at the end,
the fox said that it was the power of the fox, and that it was the
power of the fox, and
said that the fox was getting tired. He
was doing it, he was doing it.
That's right,
Neono.
It was great to see the boat race with such an experienced duo, and yes [laughs] The video from above is also quite easy to see
. I
still wanted to see this, but last year you
can see the lag.  I felt like it would
n't be possible for everyone to do it together,
so
this year, everyone participated in the Daruma-san song, and there
were quite a few crowns.By
the way, this event was performed by the
Gottomi 4.It
seems like people sympathized with it.  It's a
game that has been realized this month,
so
let's change the shape,
but I think it's interesting that everyone is acting like a cat and running with all their might.
[Laughs]
It's a game, and it's quite
exciting.  Yes, it was a battle, that was great. That
's great. It's not the same after all. The digest is also good. I think it's time
for the mobs. Yes, I want to kill the mobs. Yes, I want to kill the mogs. So I asked them to
move.
If you would like to move your voice channel,
please do so.
For the next participants, please remain on each team's channel. For
those who are not participating, please move the
members of the watching team to their respective color infection
channels.
So, I would
like to explain the mob-suppressing competition.Yes, I will.It
's a competition in which three people are selected from each team, and they work in groups of three to aim for the goal while defeating mobs.You
mean enemy, right?In each room.
mobs are springing up  Once
all the mobs are defeated, you can move on to the next room.Yes, there is
one person in charge of bows and two people in charge of holding K.This has been
discussed and decided in advance.Yes,
here.All three people who participated.
1st place will get 30 points, 2nd place will get 20 points, 3rd place
will get 310 points It
's a competition to compete for speed, right? It's
like RTA, really.
Well, since we're having a sports day with Minecraft, I've
always wanted to make a competitive game with Minecraft elements,
and this year I think we've
finally managed to create a game that makes full use of Minecraft.  I
think this is a very well-planned competition, and
it's quite a star competition, but yes, it seems like everyone has
a lot of strategy planned during the practice stage.
Personally, I think the key point is the person who uses that dream,
but yeah, the only person who uses it is that
one person.Well, it can
also be used as support, and it
can also be the main force.  That's right. Yes, I
have the impression that people have strong ears.
So everyone is on their own
channel. I'll make a side announcement.
Those who will participate in the next competition will
be on the main channel. The colored main
channel. Please remain on the red, white, and yellow main channel to
participate.  For those who don't  I'd
like to ask the infection channel, so it looks
like there are only three people in the red, white, and yellow main group.
Thank you very much.
Okay, let's start with the red team. Well then, I think I'll start with the red group.
Hello
everyone with red hair, were you
in a meeting?
Oh yeah? I
went to give you an enthusiastic interview. I
got too serious.
Please tell me the composition of the bow and K. Hi, I'm
Yumi.
[Music]
Hinamori no Tanga.  The person
in charge of reading and the
prefecture
are Comet Hoshimatsu and an unknown flare.
Funa-chan hasn't played much Minecraft yet,
so I think it would be easier to support her with a bow.
[Music]
Yes, I can't hear either.  I'm not good at it, so I'm going to go
.
This vertical part is just for decoration.
[Laughs]
[Laughs] I
'm really nervous about my enthusiasm, but
I'll do my best to support the two of you.
[Music]
From the practice dictionary, other teams have
been treating us as enemies, or rather we've been attracting a lot of attention, and we're
a little bit like that about the white team. I
heard that the white team was a little under 3 minutes.
[Music]
Hey.  I'm satisfied that it's under 4 minutes. We're happy. Yes, it
's really written here.
Lastly, some advice to the red group:
Just run all the way to the goal.
Yes, it looks like that. After that last stage,
when you see the code, run straight.  please
Hey,
please run straight through. It does
n't have to be that straight. It doesn't have to be that straight. It's fine, but as long as you just head towards it. It was too much. Yes, yes, maybe you've made it all the way to the final goal. No, that's not the case.
[Music]
Please keep this in mind. Are you
okay?
[Laughs]
So, I'd like to move on to the next team. Good
luck. Yes, you
dying friends, can you hear me?
What is the composition of the white team?
Well, the
reading is Sushiro Button, and the
sword is Amane Kanata White Coat Hiring.
How did you decide on this composition
?
Well, as expected, Shishido Button has strong aiming ability and is
good at any game.  He is a perfect giant, and I
forced him to do a difficult bow, and then I tried my
best to practice with the sword so as not to hold him back.The
two of us
practiced together.  I once
went there with just the two of us and it took 6 minutes and 30 seconds. It
took a long time. I
think the results will be good.
Yes, I
was told something, but
there was a rumor going around that it took less than 3 minutes or something.  It
seems that the
technology is correct, so it
's my 4. The
information is old, so that one is cut down to 2 minutes.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
[Music]
Good luck.
One
final piece of advice: Just keep running
straight towards the goal without looking aside.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Next, I'd
like to go and do my final interview.
Amount
Can you all hear me?
Yes, yes,
everyone in the gold group,
everyone on the gold screen. The
composition is, uh, the
dream is Natsui's Festival,
and the prefecture is Yozora Mail Tosuzu.
How did you decide? This is a
bow that only Matsuri-chan can do. I
want you to stand back and watch the whole thing and be able to support me and hope that it will end.
We'll just follow along.
[Laughter]
[  [Music]
[Music]
Run straight to the goal
There's a final stage, isn't it? Yes, I
thought to myself, now
aim for the gold goal. Why
don't you take a little detour? Is
n't it obvious?
So, everyone,
do your best.  Please
So, the
interview is
all over
. Now that it's over, I'm
going to start killing mobs. I see. Is it
finally starting? It's finally starting. It's
been a long time since I've been killing mobs. Well,
for all you viewers.  I'm sure the kids who drink it are
thinking that they're being a little careful about something, but it's
not like there are always surprises like this every year.
Please  I do
n't know, but
when we did that when we were rehearsers, we were the
most surprised, even though we had prepared it ourselves.
[Laughs]
Well, I'm really looking forward to it.  It's
okay to introduce a little bit of a stage,
but here it is. There are 5 stages. The
first one is the
stage where the early zombies and monsters appear.  Yes, the boss is now
Those slightly strengthened zombies will come out,
right? There are
quite a few who are discharged from the hospital. Once you
defeat them, the next thing to
do will
be this one in the water. Well, it's in the
water, so it's
on your skin.  The controls are difficult, and the mobs are a bit difficult, and the
fact that you have to swim to various places makes you
feel like you're losing time, so it's quite difficult.Yes,
and
here 3  Up to stage 3 stage
Well, this is the stage in the Nether,
so it looks like the boss
will have a ghast or something like that.There will be
flying enemies
called Pignin, and if you hit that one with one shot, you'll see a
bunch of them.  It seems like there are people who turn into four pieces and attack you like this,
but there are people who you can't catch, and there are people who
fly into the sky and
throw fireballs at you.
Well, it's quite difficult, but here you go. There's a
big mob called a gust that
appears as a boss, but
if you
hit back at the fireballs it throws at you, you'll die in one hit. That's
right.  So, I personally think that the
time will depend on how quickly you can return that fireball like this.Yes, the
next one is yes.Then,
uh, this is
umm, 8 days.  The
stage is set in a Western-style mansion.Yes, there are
a lot of
mobs like Luck Gaters and other mobs with very strong attack power.There
are also a lot of old married couples.The
boss is also quite strong, and here too.  It's tough,
but
yes, everyone is quite intelligent.
And this final stage. It's
not shown right now, but you
ride a trolley.
Mirko and the beautician are dressed as zombies.  The
skeletons are fighting.The
easiest way to defeat them is to take them out of the minecart and fight them.This is
where you need to aim quite a bit.In the end, everyone fights with a bow.
Yes, and now
this last part, please run through this area.That
's right, my
advice is to run through this area.Okay,
then here.If
everyone gathers, you will reach the goal.If everyone gathers at this red line, you will
reach the goal.  Yes, then you are ready  It looks
like it's done, so I
apologize for not contacting you.
Miko-san, the
number of subscribers has just exceeded 1.6 million,
so thank you very much.
That's fine.
That's fine. Thank you. Thank
you.
Yes.  So, please subscribe to the channel
and acknowledge the follow live.
Thank you very much.
So, at Mikochi, please press the start button. I
'll say it's about to start.
[Music]
This
water stage is really difficult,
is
n't it?
There's
one fish on top right now, so we
've overtaken the red group, but it's OK. It's a
pretty
difficult
stage, so we can go a little further here.
[Music]  ]
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] It's
not almost the same
time. It's the final and I want to do it again. It's
quite difficult, so here it is.
Okay.
Ok Google
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
Congratulations
[Laughter]
I guess I heard that the division of roles between the three of you was
really good.  I guess it
was because of the practice.
[Music]
[Laughs]
If it was my seniors, I think they would have kept TNT.
Thank you.
[Music]
Where did it go?
Where's the beautiful group?
[Music]
Hey, thank you
Thank you very much. I
really
think it must have been a little bit, since the final stage was in that country first.  I
lost some time. The result was a little unexpected.
But congratulations! Thank you
very much. It was very quick, and it was
really
successful.
Thank
you very much. Thank you very much.
Okay, let's do the last interview with the red team.
Okay, everyone with red hair.
[Music] I
thought it would be better to run straight, so
running to the left was the surefire way to win. For us,
yes.  Yes, yes,
but I thought there might be something behind it,
so when I ran in the middle, it wasn't there.However,
because I was reminding myself so much, I
noticed the presence of the creeper.I
noticed it, but it
was very plain.What do you think?
Hey, that's a zombie, isn't it?  That's right there  I
thought it was delicious that I missed it a little bit,
but they kept repeating it so much. They were
almost lined up, so it
was really close. I've
prepared an excuse. What do you say?
Let's go, sir
.
[Applause]  ]
Thank you very much. Excuse me. Thank you. I do
n't mean yes. Well,
here we are, the mob subjugation has
been decided, but yes, I'm going to tally it up for a specific person. Is it
finished? What do you think?
I would like to announce the scores.
But yeah, yeah, let's go, then please
replay it. Come
on, come on, let's go. I see. At
the beginning, white was the fastest,
but
on the Japan stage, white was a little behind.
That's right, isn't it?  The
water stage was probably good, it was
fast, it was fast, it was fast.
Yellow was moving pretty fast, and
red and white were chasing after each other at about the same speed.
[Music]
White and red were also wearing white and red to the point where they almost caught up with her,
so it
feels like the white one was able to make a complete twist at the end.
[Music] That
creeper that was being eaten was
attacked by the creeper, and Mel-chan was slightly attacked by the creeper,
and then she respawned.
At that point, we are forced to do something,
and the big point is that white is the
one to finish first, but here it is quite a bit.  They're
all just walking straight towards me.Yes,
yes, it
's been quite a plan from the beginning.Well, during practice,
there was talk of preparing this creeper,
but it's already the same thing, so
let's make it a surprise.  No, but I'm
glad it was a surprise. It's pretty interesting, isn't it
? It
looks like the bonuses have been tallied, so I'd like to make a specific announcement. Now, here are the bonuses. Is it
true that they're lining up?  Don't
turn it over in a relay. This is dangerous
. Is
this dangerous? It's a bit interesting.
Well, this is probably a possibility of a turnaround for any team. Yes, probably. If
red gets 3rd place,
yellow gets a cup or 121
points.  And the
white team has 113 points, and the
gold team has 108 points, so I
don't really know what will happen, but
only if the
ranking will be a little bit 2nd or 3rd.  I feel
like it's going to change, but it's
true, and any team still
has a chance of winning.
Wow, that's great. That's
great. It's a dead kit.
That's great. I'm really happy for someone like that. I'm
happy to see it.  It
's a fun problem.Okay,
so let's go to the last competition.The
last one
is the sticker drum selection relay.This
competition will be the very last competition.Yes, it will
be a relay competition with 6 members selected from each team.
Nice to meet you
Well, each player can go around the obstacle course one time and
pass the baton to the next player with a touch.
Yes, it's
simple, but this year's race is
extremely difficult, and it's hard to see how it will turn out until the end.  I do
n't know, it's a really fitting competition to
finish off with, but it's really this year.It's a
selection, so it's a little bit more difficult
than last year.  I
'm very excited, but
everyone has been practicing and getting really good at it, so it's
really exciting to see how it will turn out.And
1st
place gets 30 points, 2nd place gets 20 points, and 3rd place
gets 10 points.  Points will be distributed.Okay,
so let's ask everyone for the relay to prepare a little.You,
please.Yes, announcer, please.Next.  This
will be the second year of selection, so if you are
participating, will you be
moving to the third line?
Please move. Please leave the
voice channel as it is.
Please
line up and press the
entry button.
Yes, everyone, please press the entry button.
Everyone, it's just the last minute.  I've been practicing to the point where I have to stay
calm.That
's right, I'm
nervous, but there's also the fact that I'm going to lie down,
and after all, I feel like I'm in charge.That
's right.
Can I ask you to make an announcement, please stop?
[Music]
[Laughter]
That's right,
please.
[Music]
And the
white team goes to Sakamoto Kuma, and the
yellow team
goes to this shark, which is the tiara.  This
will be the first decoration. Thank you very much.
And then the
second runner will be the
red team, Anyan, and the
white team will be the empty one of Poki. And the
kino group will
have a red heart. And,
uh, the third runner.
The third tank is the
red group
Crazy and the
P group is
chest
you
yes and the
fourth runner is Tyler and the
red group and the white group
and the
fifth runner
the fifth runner red group is your Honoka and
you.  The group is my meow,
and the last one is the anchor.Yes, the
anchor letter is
Yuzuki-chan, and the white group is
Minato Open, and the golden group is Subaru
Ozora.  I'm looking forward to it, so no,
everyone is getting ready. They're lining up. Are you
lining up? They're lining up.
[Music] Looks
like they're all ready, so it's about time. Let's
start. Well, it's about time.  Let's
start the
interview.Okay,
can I ask each team to listen to their enthusiasm?Okay, let's
start with the red team,
everyone with red hair.  Oh no, no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no.
But what about the Red Team?
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
Choco-sensei, the anchor, isn't nervous at all.  I
woke up, so can I go
?
[Music]
I've been working hard, please. I
forgot.
By the way,
[Music]
[Laughter]
Until
[Music]
How are you all doing? Hey,
okay.
Practice.  But there might be monsters living in that performance,
so
I'll do my best not to lose to them.
No, they live there, they really do.
I hope they do their best.
Yeah.  Have
fun,
everyone. Hey everyone.
[Laughter]
[Music]
With everyone's help, I
'll stream Starburst. Please.
That's why I said yes, so do your best, Shiro Momi. Hello,
thank you very much. Well
then,
your group.
Everyone
[Music] This is the
last event, so please tell us how you feel now.
Mental Musical Pansion
[Music] I
'm really excited about it, but what do you
think about Akihara? I feel like I've practiced too much and gotten worse.
But
[Music]
Hey
That's right,
I guess I'm about to
throw up, but I don't know what the result
will be.In the end, I want to have fun with everyone and have fun.
[Music]
So,
what do you think of Pekona-san, the leader of the second half of the team?
Yellow I
guess I've been on a good ride since defeating the roasted mobu.The first half was really good too.Pyoko could have won yellow, everyone
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
Well, maybe
Subaru was too strong-willed and ended up reaching that point.
That's how I felt as a mother, so I was practicing and my heart was pounding.
[Music]
Please really check it out.
[Music] It was
destroyed.  It looks
like we've already started, but
please go back once. Thank you. I can
catch it.
[Music]
Well, please stand in line for a moment.
Please check the message from the shrine maiden.
That's right.
Please.
[Laughs] That's
right.
[Music] I
made a mistake. It's impossible.
Uh,
who's the first runner here?
[Music]  ]
Thank you
[Music]
Yes, it's okay. Yes, thank you very much.
Then, are you all OK with entering? Yes, I
think it's
time to start. Are you ready?
[Music]
[Applause]
[Applause] [
Music] [Applause] [
Music] [Applause] [Applause] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Applause]
[Music]
[Applause]
Everyone  I'm thinking of cheering you on.
[Music]
Now,
this
is all of a sudden.
[Music]
[Applause]
Hey, it's
a little smaller than it was at the beginning.
Masuhai
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] The
red team and the yellow team arrived at the finish line in 2nd place.
So, the white team, which came in 1st place, is
now in chocolate
[music]
Thank you very much.
No, it's amazing.
[Music] I
could tell from the time we practiced that we had been practicing a lot.
But I think we got some great results this time.
What do you think?
What do you think about the relay members
?  Was it?
Good luck, Cat, the
victory is a victory for everyone in the white team.
[Music]
How was it when we arrived
? We ended up in a tie.
Well, that's right. I guess what the command says is true.
Well, there
was a bit of a handshake dent,
and my Laplace was
scraped off. It seemed like I
couldn't press it properly, so if I couldn't run, it would
have been difficult to move.
[Music]
Congratulations!
Please look forward to the final results.
[Applause]
[Music] I
think so.
[Music]
Thank you.
But it was amazing. The yellow color at the end
caught up quite a bit and
made it into the moving suit.  I thought it was amazing
[Music]
Because everyone passed the baton,
but
everyone ran really well.In
the end, I was giving it my all, so I'm done.Thank you very much.Thank
you very much.
[Music]
Thank you.
Okay, so this is more than just an interview. Now
that the
competition is all over, I
would like to hold a closing ceremony.
Okay, so I'd like to tell
you
all about the members of the first half.  First of all,
everyone, let's gather together
and let's do the closing ceremony.Okay,
please give the announcer.Okay
then, we're going to have a lively closing ceremony,
so let's have the closing ceremony.  Thank you for
joining the Discord channel.
Mr. Subaru Ozora, a member of the sports festival executive committee, is a contestant. Please move
to the channel.
Thank you very much. Please move to the morning assembly table in Minecraft.
It was hot,
wasn't it? It was hot, you
know. But I
feel lonely. That's
true. Thank you for your hard work. I
don't feel like it's over.
[Applause]
This year, things went really smoothly,
and
yes, we had some really passionate games,
and I
didn't know who won or lost until the end, but I
think it turned out to be a pretty great game.
Thank you for all the games. Thank
you very much.  Seriously,
thank you. There are so many things.
[Music] This year
has been amazing, thank you.
[Music]
Well then, let's make a final decision. Okay, let's make a decision, so
we're all here.
So I'd like to hold the closing ceremony here.Okay, so I
wonder
if everyone's here.I wonder if everyone's gathered.It's a little strange, though.  I
guess that's what you're saying.Everyone,
now we're
going to have the closing ceremony.So,
first of all, I'd
like Subaru Ozora to give his correct greeting.Thank
you very much.
Yes, is this okay? Yes,
did you all have fun today? -
[Music] Looks like it was
fun. I think it's probably because you all worked so hard,
and I
think it's because you and the staff worked so hard to prepare.  It was a really great sports day.
Subaru had a lot of fun too.
Thank you very much. Thank you for your hard work.
That's it. Thank you for
your greetings. Thank
you. Now, let
's move on to the final award announcement.
[Applause]
Hey, what are the scores this time?  I've
found a prankster, so I
'll call you in order.
Hey, that's right.
[Music] I'm so
excited.
Today's announcement of Miko Sakura's special selection. Let's start
with the last digit, please. Yes, then, let's start with the announcement
of the last digit.
Okay, first of all, I
put my fingerprints on the red team.  Hey
[laughter]
Let's go. The
first digit of the red team, white team,
[applause]
[music]
Let's go. Now, let's announce the 100.
Please.
[Applause]
[Music]
[Music] Let's
go!
Red Team, White Team, and King Team's tuners. This
is the announcement. Congratulations.
[Applause]
[Applause] The
results are in.
[Applause] [
Music]
[Laughter]
[Music]  I would
like to say
thank you. Thank you.
[Music]
Everyone gathers around to film and finish.
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
[
Music] [Music] [
Music] [
Music]
[Music]  ]
[Laughter]
[Music] He
used it.
[Music]
So everyone,
don't throw during [Music] Please don't throw.
Please don't throw. Hey, I'll
take a picture.
Everyone look straight ahead.
Morning assembly table. There was a morning assembly table.
[music]  -
[Music]
[Laughter]
So, everyone, the
Hololive group is disbanding, but
thank you to everyone who was in charge of the camera for the second half.
Thank you very much.
Goodbye.  I'd like to have it.
Ah, bye bye.
[Music]
Thank you
[Applause]
[Music] [
Applause]
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] [Applause
]
[Music]