[Music]
and going under confus obession I still
wonder if I was made for if I could
always be oh
please make me
so perfect
[Music]
foring see what I want what I need oh do
you you for super
now me I to you I don't even know what
to do with
this good play part my
miror heart
[Music]
with I king queen of
you you see I you all me it like
everyone
around around
keep
my just I know sh
me you I want I need
[Music]
you you
super you I don't even know what to do
with me
good Play Your Part night around
[Music]
don't
me me
[Music]
[Applause]
one more
time wait only half only half only
half just just one more it's so good
[Music]
I can't believe there's two Euro beat
remixes to
[Music]
Mirage confused Obsession I still wonder
if I was made if I could only
see
please
upul perfect for you sending like it's
just for me don't think so live
life and yet I'm asking why you I want
[Music]
I you Me On A Mir I you up into I don't
even know what to do this
[Applause]
[Music]
he me
o i be the king and queen
of I'm beging you to see you
[Music]
me keeping me escape my way you say I'm
fragile I'm just your perfect Idol break
me sh me
you see what I want I
[Music]
you you s Me On A Mir it's all you want
the sh I don't even know what to do with
this mess it sounds like Eminem to
[Music]
me and on and on it's me I'm
lost did I say how I been full
song of
course
[Music]
bambo oh wait I'm so a
okay focus
um what do we want
today not sure what uh I what do what do
we want
today do you want 3D or 2D wa but 3D is
just like not full body tracking
but uh I don't know can I uh
the
frey okay okay I can make that
happen probably
[Music]
can you can
you it's probably
fine one more you want to you want to
listen to it again while I'm setting
this
up wait
no it will distract me
though no it's okay you saw me on a Mir
I you up the I don't even know what to
do this me
[Music]
m
okay okay probably
[Music]
okay oh oh
oh oh M say
she oh yeah
K it is yours
truly
Tak uh here
to be be your your
boss
um
[Music]
um such fancy light
right oh yeah this maybe this is too
purple okay yeah
yeah um um
um Kitty ke how are you
guys I'm I'm uh I slept a little bit
wow let me tell you re Rec readjusting
okay ah I wrote down my
tangents uh so that I don't don't forget
them so that I can tell you wow genius
but okay we're going to play Holo cure a
little bit more before I
go cuz I'm going to be gone for a few
days very sad very sad very sad
but uh uh I have many tangents so we'll
see how it goes if I die from my
tangents ah
off screen I managed after that uh one
time that I streamed Hol cure recently
where I failed the endless mode by like
a few seconds before Yago came uh I did
it off screen I I was like unsatisfied
with that result I knew that I could do
it I was pissed off at myself so I did
it off screen uh I did pretty well well
I will say the only reason I I revived
at uh survived at the very end because I
had a couple of Phoenix feathers but
before Yago came I only used like two of
those at the very very end in the last
like 50 seconds and then Yago came and
he kept on killing me and I revived and
then he killed me and I revived and he
killed me and I revived but I guess at
that point it's okay to
die that was quite the suffering not
going to lie
but before we go into holoc cure um I
don't know if you guys watch the gosu
stream or the VOD uh of me with gosu in
fredd you should watch it even though I
feel embarrassed about it I don't know
why man like from the clips that I saw
they're like
okay somehow is still feel very
embarrassed not yet okay okay when are
you getting to it huh tell me your
schedule I hope it's in your calendar
and appointment to watch the the
vaud um
the light source don't don't worry about
it it's I'm I'm here out outside
streaming from the
outside uh you know like natural
lighting um but yeah I was going to say
uh I mentioned uh I don't know if you
caught that but I mentioned that I
made um a different presentation a
different uh PowerPoint presentation
uh because of a
misunderstanding probably just because
I'm
dumb like I think like there was like
first it was the idea to introduce
ourselves in uh our language but then I
don't know then the the idea came that
we introduce each other like I
introduced gusu and she introduced me
but then that idea was gone and and we
ended up doing the just introducing
ourselves thing but when I was making
the the PowerPoint presentation I was
still very p p p p uh even after several
times like confirming with the
staff I still did it wrong and and made
a presentation of go go instead so just
so that it doesn't get lost I shall show
you here really quick it's just one
slide oopsie um
there we go all
okay they said that I should just make
it roughly and they will like graphic
design it into something nicer but I
still wanted it to look something like
decent cuz I I tried really hard cuz I
don't know how to use these
things I feel like I'm more useful in uh
Photoshop than in PowerPoint but yeah
okay here let me teach you okay in case
she didn't know yet who is go she's a
cute very cute live streamer from Korea
you can tell how cute she is by the
moving images above yeah yeah right now
she streams on so maybe it is pronounced
soup is it pronounced
soup I think she pronounced it
soup uh which was originally Africa TV
that might sound a little bit more
familiar to you Africa TV U but it got
renamed and it's like
uh even though the name sounds like it's
like from Africa uh it's like very
popular uh among South Koreans for
streaming yeah the side has been around
forever I think they I I think I heard
something about the reason they renamed
it is because like so uh Korean
streamers can't stream on Twitch anymore
since this year and I think from what I
heard is they renamed it just like for
like the sake of their image like the
website CU now so many Korean streamers
went over to the website and in order to
make it also more like uh overseas
friendly just to like the not like I
don't know not that it's not already
overseas friendly but it's like I think
uh calling it Africa TV gives it like
the impression maybe that it's like it
belongs to one country or so and and
then it's like quite the
misunderstanding because it's from what
I know most mostly Koreans on
there it's in know kind of weird so they
changed it for like their image I think
from what I understand yeah yeah yeah
marketing
uhhuh the
continent shut
up yeah yeah yeah now it's
soup and she's part of is Idol which is
you know
[Music]
like I wouldn't say it's
I guess I guess it's like H life but
then is like your idol is like under
another company just like how Hol life
is under
cover yeah yeah and they have more I saw
they have like a big lineup of YouTubers
and content creators uh on their website
I checked out their website they have so
many
yeah and yeah it's a vtu group that also
makes music and they perform live and
they have concerts too and I really like
their own kid but I also like superhero
oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my God
and then they have another song I forgot
the title um but it was like for their
visual novel a magical girl visual novel
thing yeah I listen to a lot of their
songs
now and it's very K-pop style too so you
know I think there's some Synergy there
and she's a funny girl with cute
expressions and Good Humor good her main
language is Korean but I think her
English is very good also her job
wow wow so good and the way we met if
you remember is through the be Awards we
were both nominated in the same C
category so I talked about her and then
she saw a clip of it and then I saw a
clip of that and like she reacted to me
on her stream I reacted to her on my
stream and on Twitter Etc and like went
back and forth back and
forth and then I think I went to my
management um and I asked hey can I get
perms to uh collab with go good because
when we collab with outside people we
have to um yeah check can't just do with
anybody at any given
[Music]
time um so yeah I did that and then they
pretty quickly said yeah okay and then
you know we started getting the ball
rolling but it took a long time because
first we we were trying to figure out
things and I was still trying to figure
out that was like yeah around that time
is when I started figuring out my exent
equipment but I was still very new to it
and I was struggling with it and like I
still had a lot of issues with it I
wasn't so used to it now I'm like way
more used to it yes yes yes I've used it
a lot since then so yeah less troubles
happen it always works pretty smoothly I
used to always have some error setting
it up or the calibration didn't go
nicely or whatever or you first I also
realized I can't like I only can record
but not live stream like it was weird
yeah I've become so accustomed to it
yeah so this and so then then after a
while I was like kind of ready but then
we got too busy I traveled so much
especially in
summer but now it finally happened
and
um yeah I have some thoughts and
comments and I will share I'm during my
gam playay but yeah that was my extra
homework the PowerPoint presentation
that I didn't have to do U extra extra
this Frey so Peak thank you so just I
don't know if you realized but this is
again different from the one that was
used in the goo
stream go stream Wawa was like
uh like default model adjusted by them a
little bit I don't think it
has as many BL shapes no the mouth
shapes like for example I wasn't able to
do like this
mouth I don't think I was quite able to
do like stuff like this I don't
know my eyebrows were a little bit
different too I you could tell really
really I I told you I have like so many
different versions of my models
now oh yeah I don't think I can do
triangle mouth so I want to redo that
vtuber face expression
challenge um with this
model and with my triggers cuz I wasn't
able to push the triggers this is all
like without triggers right but I do
have some triggers so I want to like
redo it with the
[Music]
triggers yes make a short yeah we'll
make a Youtube short but I'm not sure if
I want to interrupt The Mirage challenge
YouTube shorts uh for that and I I think
think maybe Sian still wants to fix the
crying face I'm not
sure tell me Sian otherwise I'll just do
it
without Chestnut mouth my beloved
yeah I love triangle mouth I love
it so yeah just so you know different
wow different
dimensions okay okay let's see
apparently the greed sticker has
been uh nerfed
[Music]
why why he said on Twitter that it's too
powerful but like I have yet to feel the
power of it the full power not so what
what I haven't gotten that much out of
it either Marin was op a man then I
don't
know I didn't try M with green yet I'm
not getting a piece of the
cake hey someone got 37 million and
37 but they're Pro like that also has to
do with like game skill I don't have
that game skill I wouldn't be able to
achieve that would I I don't think I
would have been so so take that into
account only Nerf the green sticker for
good players and not not for
[Music]
me it's 20 million oh [\h__\h] okay it's
understandable that he nerfed it I must
say with these facts understandable but
it's not like I was able to ever achieve
that where is my PO can okay so the
people who already got the money so as
an exchange can I um get like a
injection money injection from caou uh
directly like into my account for the
losses I've made that I could have
potentially the money that I could have
potentially made if I had more time but
you know I'm a streamer I'm busy
please oh wait I think my P my pupils
aren't
moving oh man I missed out on the good
stuff I can't believe
it
no uh yes
sorry I'm fixing my
eyes uh
[Music]
sure okay yeah they're moving again I
don't know why they always do that when
I like don't completely reset all of the
see it's like better when my eyes move
more right doesn't look so stiff
anymore I know what's good let me
H that reminds me wait are you seeing
this [\h__\h] wait uh wait I don't mean it
so negatively it's like are you seeing
this oh my God this crazy stuff wait so
I just look at
this that reminds me of um Ricky and mor
Rick and mor what is this wait is this a
b or how did I not find this
before it's like when I pull down my
upper lip a
lot
what it looks good from the side from
here I didn't realize what was
[Laughter]
happening looks like a Simpsons
character hi
a no that's too that can't be it wasn't
like that before why the long
face seon we need to look into this I
don't know if I like it do I like it
it's kind of funny but maybe it's a bit
too
extreme sorry it's too funny to me okay
okay okay okay I'm once again
stalling no
maidens
okay it's
perfect she has a nose yeah dude did you
doubt it it's pretty apparent with the
light going on here to charm
Point okay okay okay I don't know how I
noticed that now uh Holo Q
are um
okay here we go I'm so sorry my
[Music]
mouth it does it so much
now now even when I'm not really pulling
it down that's so weird okay okay okay
okay well looks funny
[Music]
enough oh oops game
do oh no wrong
wrong woo
is this [\h__\h] border I can never get
it
right two
llas what yeah I have all of the members
now yippee I mean I did already at the
end of the last stream but now do you
see them at the beginning I can't unsee
it me
neither wa is it something I did I did I
did I what what did I
[Laughter]
do okay so yeah I I did a full run uh
money Focus but I I only got like I
don't know 25k or so so like I'm like
where the [\h__\h] are those Millions
um so I all I did was buy um yeah I
think I got 30k so I just bought like an
upgrade but the upgrades at this level
are like like all of that
money that I earned in one run
so
ah but okay see I didn't play with M yet
even if greed got nerfed I'm sure she
even with nerfed has someone tried out
it out already does she can I still make
good
[Music]
money get Max coin gain oh see yeah
that's also a thing like I don't even
have all the upgrades yet so that's also
probably why I'm like making less money
she's still in best money okay great I I
still haven't played her so it's a good
opportunity n we'll we'll try um I don't
know if I can pull uh another full
endless run I'll probably die especially
because it's going to be my first time
but
but I'll
try uh don't you have the Armory unlock
to turn off items you don't
need oh I guess you mean that I don't
like the chances are higher of me
getting the money related
ones is that possible how do I do
that I don't I don't know how that works
I don't think I can do it
you need to buy it in the store you need
to buy the option to disable it is it
free all weap to be disabled in the
Armory and will not appear allow F
50,000 bro
bro
bro n whatever I'll play normal I'll be
fine
man
so swings a short range sword in okay
close range I was I think I was doing so
well with P
because
like it ranged
attacks but okay while shooting a pistol
at the nearest Target ooh Miracle
Central Cannon oh continuously shoots
large Canon bells that explode into
Hearts okay boy boy and pig
I love trying you trying to explain them
horny that was a misunderstanding she
was saying hi honey but I didn't hear it
like that so I was like oh I'm horny no
no and then I couldn't escape from that
conversation
anymore okay I guess we I'll do this one
again and these things are
fine wait what did I have Dash on did I
have it on
C yes okay wee
all right then let's begin with the main
weapon okay it's a combination of distan
and
uh close combat actually like if the if
the cannon will always go towards the
closest enemy regardless of where I'm
aiming to I could aim somewhere else
you know like you know you know but you
know oh now it shoots Two
Shots
[Music]
crazy lost should I get it gain a lost
gge the gge increases slowly near
enemies or when
hit at Max gge madine reaches her climax
of course I've heard about this healing
20% HP and Deals 300% damage to all
nearby Targets wow
300%
H
okay okay but I'm going to still
increase the main
weapon does she have any wait never mind
I was going to say does she have any
healing skill yeah this one but only at
the climax how long does it take to
reach the
climax probably not that long it sounds
like it might not take that where's my
climb ah the bottom here oh there you go
it happened cuz I got hit feels good
huh look at that Dodge like a
[Music]
pro I don't even care I want to test out
that
gge oh my p is uh
ready was it
X does it even work on these kind of
enemies I feel like it
didn't it's not worth using it now give
me some more
enemies oh well here you go oh oh okay I
still have to aim it okay another hold
pirate Captain when collecting holoc
coins increase crit by 1% for 5 seconds
up to 10% targets hit by skills has uh
10% chance to drop additional Holo
coins oh okay sure all I heard was crits
and
coins
fine
oh oh where the sticker I'll pick it
up uh T oh I like this one I do like the
stamp actually
regardless of
it's oh that I didn't realize I got
censored when that happens uh regardless
of it's kusoo status because it's a
kusoo computer it's actually a good
stamp I think apply the stamp to the
weapon uh what life
steal May heal a random amount of okay
cool cool cool
cool
cool oh I need I need ra uh more
radius to pick up stuff oh
God
H this one's o they're both
[Music]
buffed okay Ian
Cur I did get a couple of new
collaborations also I think that I
didn't have yet uh in my one it was just
one playr but I finished it so proud of
myself I think I was so locked in and
focused like without chat I I do some
things maybe un not so ideal because I
don't have the advice but at the same
time I'm more locked in
so chances of me getting thir are
higher is the music too quiet by the way
for you guys should I turn it
up um if you have the M dagger get it m
dagger you mean in here it shows up
uh it's okay it's fine it's a little low
it's fine okay let's keep it the way it
is
then I don't know I've never tried with
Hollow before people probably say Hollow
H Hollow for money making but they
become
stronger 5% like up to what like if you
get more h
I'm going to
die 100% please don't give me hu
okay oh there's an anvil what the
heck didn't
realize
H
okay I wouldn't go for H until your
character sh are closer to being Max
right oh my God wait wait wait wait wait
wait looks at chat for one second
escalation those coins Yum Yum Yum Yum
Yum I want the tangent but I'm I'm
scared I'm too focused still
maybe it's just going to get worse oh yo
what the heck
sh drop some coins jle where's my
salary come on yo oh he gave me a
flower ah should I replace with
maybe the marking n Maring was pretty
good that I had that on my good run as
well maybe on the life steal stamp you
get paid in flowers yeah ridiculous
huh upgrade the life
[Music]
steal I think you need life
steal you think so we can have other
means of getting
HP minus K is taking damage oh well
okay I'll finish I'll strengthen
something
else where are you
guys let's see so okay here are some I'm
going to start going for my
tangents
um num
Uno was like randomly brought up uh LOL
I was quite
surprised it's kind of like following me
right now everywhere I
go should I should I
learn
LOL now this is not the first time that
like maybe it's
Destiny should I learn it for her you
know we could become even better friends
it's free I should just try it once
don't you
think are you guys saying you didn't
enjoy the the LOL collab that the girls
had the other day are you saying you
didn't enjoy it don't be so
T haven't seen it yet well it was a fun
collab dot dot dot there you go there
you
[Music]
go I'll think about it uh should I get
this sausage because it also is buffed I
wonder just in case or should I all of
these are good
choices yeah I do I do need to start
with M smell but it will come again
anyway okay if a Target is with an 80
pixel for more than 1 second they gain a
debuff that reduces death and speed by
20% after 3 seconds target takes 75 oh W
that's pretty good but I need radius I
need uh pickup
range look at all this exp that is
unclaimed Big chcken Boss
Yahoo
25 who the [\h__\h] had this idea that I I
should get hu if next step is 25 five
how strong are they now 10%
15% there's some weird circles around me
what does this
mean already
Max chicken MK murder woohoo Fried
Chicken for free for
everybody if you had elimon could remove
it now well I don't well I really
don't good money good
money okay so we we'll we'll oh thank
you we'll think about
the reduce I I'm not going to I'm not
going to do it I'm not going to do it or
should
I should I but like 30% I need I will
have to get pickup range then
heast stamp oh
okay wait there's also stamp here that's
the attack up
stamp well if we got the Hast stamp what
are we going to replace the haste stamp
for and then what should I not be
strengthening now because it won't make
sense to strengthen it or should I sell
I no I'm not going to sell it but I'm
going to strengthen something
right uh
H let me fix something really quick it
bothers me I think I know what I did
wrong let's
see upgrade life steal or upgrade
haste oh upgrade life steal or pain and
what about the other one that I already
upgraded once do is that not do you guys
not like that one
[Music]
it's not bad but the others are
better wait what's not working I here
ah it doesn't do it
anymore yeah I I see I
see
nice you're freezing yeah yeah cuz I was
fixing my face
capture
okay uh so what somebody said swap slow
[Applause]
but I'm not you mean with
haste this is not the haste yet so I'm
going
to
snake Okay snake I guess slow stamp is
unpopular even though I like it
H we shouldn't take cutting board even
though it's buffed
because it's not going to really do
anything special for M she's certainly
not uh
flat
reir a right it does cooll out with the
E anchors and I did uh learn it off
screen it was pretty pretty good pretty
damn good like
she
uh you can get to collab use it for
[Music]
collabs all right at least I know that
one so I know what like what to
expect oh I'm censored
okay uh did you guys see I retweeted or
did I ret no yeah I retweeted no did I
did I did I I know I oh my God leave me
alone
I wait I can't tangent I uh replied at
least I think did you see I replied to
the um to the person on Twitter who made
the uh 3D environment that we use
today should I get
[Music]
speed I didn't realize that they made a
whole environment from scratch for this
collab I just thought they used
something that they already had CU I'm
sure they have a lot of like uh
stages uh like rooms and stuff cuz they
do a lot of PRD streams they're like
generally just in PRD
uh and I thought they maybe just put
some like you know waa and
go items into the
screen but no they made the whole thing
for us what I was like what damn like
they put so much pre uh love sorry I'm
under pressure so I said pressure so
much uh effort into it and there was
like a l oh I didn't know they made a
whole logo and they made those like
slides for when the screen is like
changing and stuff like that and they
like when we needed to change the room
within the world they moved us around
it's was like such good service I didn't
have to do anything wow
wow and they they the even the outfit
changing was
automatic they took good care with me I
appreciate it yeah Big Ups to the
staff I didn't have to walk and I was
totally walk I was walking on the spot
okay that's also some effort from
me production was really good right it
wasn't like it wasn't like I I'm sure
like they can do even better like uh you
know like if they wanted to they could
probably
do like whole life
studio uh
collaboration uh quality
but like I'm so honored that they put so
much effort into it for just I I thought
it was just going to be a little silly
chaotic collaboration but they made it
way more organized
thankfully
yeah wait I'm scared of taking the next
box oh is it going to give me ow y y is
it going to give me whatever I can't
reach it right now anyway just going to
give me another cutting board I
think well he
would you guys honestly take
hu I'm going to die I promise
you would you on nah no nurse
horn okay gladly thank you for being
reasonable oh bomp okay I guess we're
working with the bomb now oh it has a
buff damage plus 15%
so so this
now maybe all the time was worth it all
the time waiting was worth it it gave
everybody more time to prepare
especially for me like back then as I
said I didn't really know what I was
doing with
3D so I'm
glad that I had more time to prepare and
now it's like we reached this we reached
this one year anniversary
perfect timing I wonder what I should do
maybe I'll just do nurse one now there's
there's animals around like there's
stuff around everywhere isn't there oh
yeah animals up
there go anniversary y you've come so
far yeah I really think like in terms of
technical stuff I've grown a lot in this
one year you don't need life seal
anymore what do you mean you'll see I'll
need
it oh hit if the player does not get
attacked by the
Target h no we're not going to use that
but okay here we go first collaboration
so early on oh relatively early I guess
it could be oh wait that was bone bro
wait a second what he that was bone Bros
wait I was thinking of a different one
wait is it always shooting in the
opposite direction of what I'm aiming
towards
Fu what's going on
[Music]
what's I don't like
that I hate
that is that the bone bro thing don't
like
it I watch the B thank you so much for
catching
up it choose both direction oh okay
sword beams go in front
Okay uh maybe I'll take the Anvil what
do you
think maybe maybe
not
yeah I really like the
an anyway I started and wow I get so
many like XP things that pick up
everything in this run I rarely get them
in other cases is there anything that
influences how high the chances are that
you get
it
no oh I'm just really
lucky super glasses oh well okay
no I mean something that uh I might be
doing right
now oh my God w Wait I'm seeing the the
sword slashes
now I I don't know it could have been M
and slashes too you know is what I was
thinking is there anything else on the
map that I'm not seeing that I didn't
pick up any anal I don't think so but
there's another one of these things what
the heck
why do they keep on appearing now they
look similar right thank you so an
official collab name for you in go not
that I know of but I saw people calling
us seori I think that has a nicer ring
than the other one that I
heard should I got headphones people did
say somebody said headphones good for me
uhoh
uhoh I don't feel strong enough for this
stage of the
run I would prefer something that shoots
more in the direction that I'm aiming
to okay I got in the right moment I got
the special in the right moment
and guess I'm going to
strengthen life
steel 13 well we got 1K well I guess
that's good we'll see how far we can go
I guess that's
good don't know if I'll soive but yeah
that's a good good amount to you know
even if I die
it won't make me cry what should I
collap the bump with guys what should I
be looking out
for [\h__\h] I can't reach all of
that I'm
horny potato or I never find the [\h__\h]
potato I tried so hard to find it off
screen I'll never a
I have to take it I feel like that's
only the smartest thing I could
do okay here we go
um oh myit I can use them twice so so
sick let's go that or Super Chat
time F super chat ah it'll come back it
come
back I might don't have the potato
unlocked Maybe
feel I saw it uh before in the choices
like a long time
ago oh because I I see what you mean
because I took the limit now I really
can't get it Ah that's what you mean no
okay cuz the yeah defensive items
are wait wasn't it going to be double oh
I guess it just stayed there and I have
to like tatch it again
so many good choices uh whatever bomb so
what did you say potato or what was
it potato chances are
low I I'll lead them a little bit more
further away and then I'll come back I I
go
back oh my God [\h__\h] it's already
time
[\h__\h] okay at least I get this potato ASA
Coco okay ASA Coco is more realistic I'm
a bit scared right now I'm kind of in
the beam and I can't Dodge away you
think I can tank one
beam get ready to dodge there's I think
there's a tree there so I can't Dodge to
the right I think I
can't to the left will be probably you
can that I think is my is it
possible okay we'll
see okay
jump scare this menu gives me a jump
scare okay nice nice nice I finally I
touched
everything well I'm in I thought you
were gone already wuki already nice
nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice
nice
[Music]
okay here I go another one the bomb I
expected
that yeah ground P those
bombs you should be defusing them girl
oh she de yay
woohoo nothing beats a ground pound I
don't believe that anymore lies lies
lies I beat a ground pound
P pgy bang
okay it's okay cuz I got the
limiter ah I need an upgrade item oh my
God collaboration
item
all
one okay speaking of bomb diffuse look
game I think I I I brought that up as a
possible uh gaming option like a year
ago I was like we were like talking
about okay what should we do and go was
like I want to do like a mix of
things uh and uh yeah great choice right
I thought if you if you do want to play
a game then I think I recommend this
game cuz I haven't played it in a long
time but it's really good for one-on-one
uh collab with communic ation problems
because that makes it more
interesting there we go I'm taking the a
Coco for the bomb that's the combination
right yeah and I think really uh us
failing so many times was not a bad
thing I was actually thinking oh this is
great
entertainment this is how it's supposed
to be
we got to struggle we got to be
struggling it's the only
way would be boring if it was you
know just a walk in the park going too
smoothly but what was with all these
like new things did they update with
those new modules and I've never seen
them before I
think love was a lot of fun 44 moms
thank you thank you thank you stay for
so many months and years and you get
rewarded with cool stuff for staying I
love you
[Music]
guys I'm on The Struggle Bus and I'm not
getting off all aboard The Struggle Bus
what is this what are you saying what
are you
saying what are you
saying was this some meme some song
e wa wait did I also in previous collabs
only play the tutorial or so that's why
I haven't seen those
but but no I must have finished it
though at some point because I had more
options I had more
modules so maybe a few times like my
first tries were tutorials
though but no I definitely uh came past
the
tutorial two years four years
woohoo oh damn those modules were so
difficult especially like what what the
[\h__\h] why were there different kind of
wire setups and and I didn't even see
anything about the twirly wires in the
manual when I was looking through
it are they mentioned
anywhere thank you aim sauce apparently
I'm still a decent character to use so
I'm glad to to know of that maybe not
the best character for like money gain
but just decent enough
for you
know
surviving I cleared stage four hard with
K let's
go wow I really strong thank you I'm
glad I didn't get too nerfed if anything
I got buffed once and and since then
they have nerfed me
huh near the end of the
manual bro the manual is too
big thank God go kept on getting like
the same modules thank God
honestly I feel like min's
ulti doesn't clear as well as certain
other ulties like oh God oh God what the
[\h__\h] where did I
go like for examp oh that wasn't so bad
for example like he has Alti clear is
insane not always cuz it's like a lucky
thing but
still but at least her horny thing I
don't know how to react in this case
Okay once once everything's right I'm
like wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
what's the logic behind
this well I get it you have to like
stay no I don't know I don't I don't
really
know I did it right this time but
normally I [\h__\h] up but it's it's usually
fine I
survive but I was going to say her her
horny meter makes up maybe for a less
efficient
ulti I would say oh I got the ulti right
back
again because the horn meter is is
pretty good I must say
also I guess maybe it's less about
clearing everything on the board and
more like about making coins from what
you do clear
maybe Marine Al yeah I was just saying
that I understand hug you kitties for
us
I so I I took a nap right after the
stream um after buying some groceries
and stuff and I I I couldn't resist like
I fell asleep while cuddling smoothie
instead of falling asleep on the Casper
pillow but I did switch to the Casper
pillow Midway through but when I fell
asleep on smovie I woke up at some point
like when I say on it's more like like
I'm like kind of curled around her right
and like my mouth like a little bit a
part of my jaw is on smoo's
butt you fluffy and you know I'm like
curled around her and she's curled
around
me yeah it's really nice she doesn't
mind cuz it's just like a part of my jaw
but I drooled on her I woke up and I
realized I like lowkey drooled on
her so I like swiped it a little wiped
it a little bit and then moved to my
Casper
pillow my new Casper pillow first try
first attempt at Casper
pillow oh uh no uh M
mhm ready for another ult oh my god oh
green
stamp wait what do I replace [\h__\h] I
didn't expect getting the GRE
[Music]
ST which one they're all maxed which one
do I
replace life steal maybe mark
all right I'll go with this
one ah wait I need
to too bad it only like strengthens it
by one level when you strengthen it with
something that already has been
strengthened feel like it should
strengthen it like double at
least what was I
saying I pillow so uh okay so Dr don't
smoothie I hope that's I hope um I hope
that doesn't like affect her too much
when she cleans
herself uh but yeah I just slept too
well I guess in my nap cuz I was only on
four sleep four sleep four hours
sleep uh what should we get next W maybe
wammy water I want to do something with
wmy water that I haven't done before um
what was it what can you combine combine
with uh for for
[Music]
Sleep ah the boys love book or the CEO
tears
okay I can't reach
it I'll lead them around in the
circle okay so the C oh my God it's like
so if you're not like on top of this
story if you don't like oh God no I'm
too scared I I had to still take a
little bit more distance [\h__\h] um I've
been like complaining a lot about my uh
problems with like sleeping recently
like i' I've been using pillows that I
used before and was like okay with them
but nowadays it hurts so much so I was
discussing pillows and stream and people
recommended me the Casper pillow which
seems kind of like a popular pillow in
America and and I found it on Amazon so
I did get it and it arrived today and
now I only use it for the nap so I
wouldn't judge it yet but for I think
maybe I was just like so tired that I
slept
comfortably just
automatically uh you got a mattress too
oh
cool but the nap was really nice I don't
know if it's because of the pillow or
just because I was really
tired so far the pillow is nice I I can
tell it's like like inspired by Hotel
pillows cuz it's just you know fluffy
but it's so big if I get a second one of
these to line up next to the one that I
do have now I won't have space for my
chunky wonky box anymore cuz chunky
wonky sleeps on a little box on my bed
next to my pillow these take up so much
space American size
crazy two collabs let's go
can't
reach I can't see my [\h__\h]
Mouse one pillow is enough chunk is man
is more yeah I
agree no I think I'm fine with just one
on my bed and the cuz so basically now
there's no free space anymore on the
waves of my bed there's from left to
right there's the chunky wonky bed so to
say her box on my bed then there's my
Casper pillow and then in immediate it's
like they're all touching each other
then there smoothy's pillow smoovie has
a pillow it's like a foam pillow that
she likes to sleep on these days for a
long time now actually I think she won't
change her uh priorities anymore she
really likes
that now there's like no space anymore
there used to be like some a little bit
little bit of space like a maybe more
than a more than two hands of space
still if you know what I mean if you can
visualize it I guess it doesn't matter
but it does feel kind of tight now cuz
the pillow is so big and there's no
space it feels tight what the
heck I've had good experience with Emma
and tempor products temper temper I
think yeah yeah yeah I think that's the
one I heard about I've done my research
is temper the one that uh hotels also
like to
use temper that sounds very fam familiar
to
me Temple or was
it I think so I need to look it up
again
Tampa thank you for the Super Chat uh I
just realized I didn't have these things
up
oopsie oh wait what the [\h__\h] forgot
where I was
ah we got both
choices
wait I've done this one
before haven't done the other ones at
all oh no wait never mind wait what I've
done this one uh this one the boys love
I've also done doesn't look like I've
done the CEO combin ation what tier
doesn't collab with it oh
misunderstanding huh okay then uh bo
love Yeah boys love okay I like it I
like the boys love collaboration with
wammy
water I'll take it
now instead of it oh that's cool that
could be some kind of expansion in the
far future but I don't know how that's
going to work uh character
collaborations oh that's cool
well there's got to
be I don't know
like beu
Kyla but Kyla isn't a playable character
yet right so and be NE see okay
uh I would say crony M
ah crony Mum would be cute I don't know
uh oh Kyla is oh my God brain empty
sorry
ah oh yeah Wonder one day if they add fu
is are they just going to add foru as
like one character or as separate
characters I feel like I feel like it
would be interesting if they added them
as one
character I feel like I I would want to
see that more cuz there's like more
things you can do with
that and then oh you know how Iris has
this thing with like uh her like
demon devil whatever side and um and the
angel side they could do the same with
like fuzzy and and
[Music]
fluffy
oh why am I why am I dying take care
take care
lava oh my God careful careful careful
too much hor me holy [\h__\h] but almost
side how to HDE switch oh yeah yeah yeah
that also sounds interesting careful too
much climax too much too many too much
too much okay too much
horny get that money before I die in any
case oh
40K
okay okay still kind of
yby I'm scared I still have a feeling
that I might die but it's okay I'm
getting a lot of
money oh there's some stuff there's an
anvil and
money a second I want
that oh I can use it twice but I I don't
think I can do it
twice I I'll need to circle around
again unless I don't want to
no bad idea ah circle circle circle I
tried to stay around to like touch it
again while I'm still
there we're reaching dangerous territory
I need to kind of be
careful oh wait I forgot I had this oh
my ulti oh my God sometimes I don't
notice that my UL is activate uh that
ready to activate
H oh knock
back dangerous dangerous dangerous
dangerous dangerous
dangerous I'm pretty slow I I would
appreciate like a speed stat buff next
time I see it I might get it oh [\h__\h] yo
I don't care right now
yo I'm
scared oh [\h__\h] the gold Anvil is in the
hoorde I'll go to the other anvils first
there's so oh my go
okay it's all about the money guys it's
all about the money wait what is that
a never mind I don't think there was a
golden Anvil what what would the golden
an anvil be here for I imagined
it attack
H [\h__\h] hell
the green thing is that just a
stamp I guess it's just a
stamp There's Something Blue
too do do machine
cell box oh
triple
no the H okay I'll take the water I'll
take the boys of I'll drop the
H I'll
yeah thanks I'm glad we
agree oh now it dropped [\h__\h] I I I'll
I'll upgrade the pistol cuz my golden
Anvil is ready yeah
I'm chill chill chill take a step to the
right dash away no my Dash isn't ready
but it's okay it's okay it's going to be
okay calm almost 50k even if I lose I
don't mind I'm not going to make it to
30 minutes that's unrealistic
anyway just take a step to the right
oh another one [\h__\h] another one I need
to get to the golden all right I'll keep
on upgrading
this I okay uh I'll I'll try to Circle
through the for this side oh what what
what did the Golden One respawn in a no
wait do I have two golden ones right now
no that's another another normal one
okay sorry I'm very nervous right now
oh yeah I guess I'll upgrade one of
these
too oh look at all that
[Music]
money oh my
God okay uh we can make another collab
what what should we do so should we go
with something that I have here spider
cooking tears
those two actually do collab huh yeah I
think I remember that I can only take
one though so I'll
take the spider C
now upgrade
it and run away keep for
later
yeah please don't be disappointed in me
and if I die I have hu on which I I
normally never do and and I'm scared I
don't have maximum stat upgrades and
[\h__\h]
either okay I'm so
slow Mir go that I even survived that
just
now
okay it's actually doing good yeah yeah
surprisingly surprisingly
let me look at my tangent list and see
if there's anything that is easy to
tangent
on
ah did
you uh like the sound of the mic that I
used I listen to the clips and it sounds
pretty
good I got
a road Wireless me
microphones they're called Wireless me
there's also wireless gold I don't know
the difference
but it's like people use those a lot
seemes
for yeah Wireless purposes not just for
streaming probably more for video making
vlogging and
stuff I really like them but I
misunderstood some stuff when I was oh
god oh I right they Disappear Completely
I forgot what's happening what's
happening what's happening I don't
remember what's happening okay
it's okay I appreciate a feather but I
can't get a feather now I guess I just
got to just got to skill my way out of
this oh oh oh difficult difficult
difficult what
the they're bullying me tears are right
there oh
[\h__\h] it's go for going out on location
no no actually like both as I said like
there's no big difference go and me
they're both like you can use outside or
inside um but yeah I really like them I
I okay I'm I'm scared to step out right
now but I also got like uh like the set
so it's a receiver and a transmitter and
even the receiver that you connect to
your PC if you want to use it for
streaming that one can also be used as a
mic so I have those two wireless
microphones right now uh and then I
bought an extra lavalier mic that you
can connect
also I don't know why I bought
that it's like a like these things are
like rectangular little boxes that you
clip onto your shirt or whatever but I
have I also got like a cute little white
lavel ear mic I have too many wireless
mics now took me so long to figure out
how to properly use them
also yeah I got so much stuff now so I
was thinking I was thinking I I also
bought a shotgun mic a new shotgun mic
for cooking streaming cooking streams
um to like aim it at the frying pan for
example so that you can hear the
sizzling nicely and all that um I was
thinking I could
combine two mics I could use two mics I
could put the shotgun towards the food
and then still wear my uh wireless
microphone and walk around carelessly in
the kitchen without me sounding distant
amazing goated setup my my setup I also
got a shotgun
no they're they call them shotgun
microphones I don't know why because I
guess they're I don't know do they look
like a shotgun not really
but I'm so scared to step out of the
[Music]
screen
MH I could use them for the off collabs
that I'm going to do with the girls that
are visiting
me that I got the idea to get those mics
because when I was at ena's place and we
were collabing just because the mics
that we normally use you got to get
pretty close for the radio Sound and if
you're too far apart it won't sound so
nice anymore I guess I mean it's
acceptable but you know so she had these
uh microphones that I
bought now I have so many too we can use
them I like the closeth sound me too
podcast m
okay I'm going to do
it where do I [\h__\h] go for my
experience at least like this isn't too
bad even if you do get hit but right now
I feel like I might be in a bad
position
okay everything looked really red and
danger
us oh that oh oh no
no that was ridiculous that that is what
got
me no I stumbled too much well 20
minutes yeah and 60k that's that's um
good really good and I get a little
bonus okay good good good
[Applause]
good I don't want to buy the item thing
cuz I don't think I need need it really
I'm going to buy um maybe
speed a ENT the
coins
20%
[Music]
buy buy the fan card
unlock fan lettuce you
mean a oh I ran out of money again just
got to do another mod and run
spend the coins and get coins a refund
something
no but here I'll get more another money
gain
[Music]
okay okay I think I'll go with for
another M run if you guys on M that was
actually pretty nice
okay
okay that was really an unfortunate
accident
me escaping the big red and then just
like I really felt like I was stumbling
over my own
legs unfortunate it is what it is I know
should I still get in this
run 3,000 extra
coins H not that
much usually better to just stay boxed
in you can kill the bumb or use Dash
through the
wall yeah yeah I I often Dash through
the walls didn't I actually do it
anyway color is not for the extra coins
oh then it's just for the the risky
feeling or what you want to get me in
trouble guys
huh he wanted to get me in trouble I see
how it
is no
more stop getting
hit okay what was I talking about
microphones uh speaking of cooking
streams I'm surprised I have many
tangents speaking of cooking streams uh
did you guys
see I don't understand why they didn't
announce it with a video cuz it feels
like a big deal to me but they low key
announced in the
picture my ramen in the v
collaboration my Ramen so yeah I can say
now I of course the V collaboration
comes with a Ramen because that's like
their main thing and you can already see
the packaging of it it was in the last
email too yeah
I want to show it can I take a moment to
just show it sorry sorry sorry before I
forget it it was in the last email yeah
I just saw the tweet I didn't look at my
emails okay here we
go oh Jif it's a Jif again
so
Koto where the heck did it
go I can't see it in my folder I
here my I swear my hongo is better than
that but like when I speak it for the
first time in a long
time it's like what how to
speak so final launch date when you can
start ordering is 25th of
November sorry I'm picking my eye cuz
those cat ey cat eyes cat
ears cat ears cat
hairs so
confused um yeah uh there's
still one two three four five six seven
shouldn't there be two more
things I know I can't think of one what
was the other one um oh yeah they
definitely should be at least one more
thing released 1 2 3 four five six seven
no eight nine
oh yeah yeah there's two more things I
guarantee you there's two more things to
be announced
um I don't know when the next one is but
I think I'll be not streaming cuz I I
won't be
here two dos oh both at once in one go
tomorrow ah man [\h__\h] I can't react
to sad hope you oh sorry that was my hip
hope you guys um keep an eye out on it
but yeah my Ramen
it already says chicken pyan I think is
that what it
says P does that make sense P python
yeah lav so generally I don't know I had
to like I had input in it and I was like
generally my favorite flavor is tonot
ramen or miso Ramen because just because
it usually comes with buttered
corn um um but uh I thought it's more in
character uh and they Rec recommended a
a chicken flavor Ramen um so actually
just uh today no yesterday yesterday I
picked up samples I didn't get the final
packaging package stuff yet but um I got
like samples like unpackaged stuff from
their Factory directly uh it's
like yeah the noodles and the broth and
like extra like
crispy uh uh chicken skin I think and so
I think tonight I will have that be my
dinner cuz I bought some green onions
and I'm going to make an egg on top and
I got some corn yeah that's what I'm
going to top it with hopefully it's
going to turn out good hopefully I don't
mess it up how can you mess up uh
instant Ramen you might think but I
think I've messed it up a little bit
before
I've had V Ramy before and it's really
yummy uh so yeah the boss uh was as far
as I know a Michelin star Michelin Chef
star Michelin star
chef and um so he's really into this
stuff he's really studied it yeah Tim
and he yeah like he knows what he's
doing he makes really good uh Ramen FL
FL and other stuff and is really good
ingredients too so I hope you guys will
like the wobble Ramen you got to buy it
in bulk it has really cute packaging too
I'm so excited to have
this yeah so full launch uh 25th another
update on the two remaining items which
are let me tell you those are exciting
ones
tomorrow in ex exactly
23.5
hours make sure to check your emails and
stuff
[Music]
tomor for the coins do one sure okay
can you even kill these
dudes wa you guys kept on saying Super
Chat super chat but you don't mean the
membership right because I don't even
understand how this should help me make
money cuz it makes me lose H
coins the green one
[Music]
okay all right and so yeah raming
tonight raming tonight yippee a there it
is romance Y what are you guys going to
eat tonight huh
yes to membership together yeah yeah not
in Hol here but in in YouTube
yes
oopsie I'm hungry this stream also won't
be too long because I still have to
clean because I'll be gone from home and
uh you know I need my home to be
relatively clean for my cat sitter
[Music]
I'll wait for an item that has a buff I
guess but I want an item soon
bro I need to clean I need to pack but
packing shouldn't be too
crazy and I need to uh what was I going
to do I going to do something cook yeah
cook potato sausage nugget crab that's
what you going to eat craps and food wow
what what a
lineup who's taking care RBF and uh BFF
although I don't know like
BFF she's probably too busy to show up
so it might be just RBF I don't
know and then when I'm back I'm going to
try to uh have RBF help me with a few
more things like like hanging up a lamp
and stuff before my guests come I want
to I want to do a few more
things before it's too late want to make
a good impression with my home I wonder
what they'll think of
it cuz I've seen you know I've seen uh
one of their homes and I've seen a lot
of other Hol members
homes um but
I don't
know
European home little bit
different okay we're working with an axe
now um I wonder if there's any
collaboration that I didn't do before
with the axe anything
new I do like the classic one that I
always do with the
axe Axe and Dagger I still haven't seen
this Lade dagger maybe I need to unlock
it hasn't shown up a single time for
me it's an unlock how to unlock complete
stage five stage five is this stage
four what I'm doing right
now [\h__\h] sorry sorry wait you I I might
die I'm going to
y it
hurts okay I
survived I survived because I I I I I
dashed out of it and I get one second of
invisibility this is stage one hard you
need to complete the one the cannonballs
what wait stage five ah the
island I suck at the island
[\h__\h] can you guys log into my account
and play for
me and finish it for
[Music]
me uh heal back up
please food food
food you could you
could you must overcome it m maybe after
all of these like money runs after I
upgraded all my stats then we can go
back to the island and we'll have a
better chance I
guess y
it new super collab of hopa oh that's I
haven't seen yet wait what uh Axe and
the boys of yeah that's like a
classic I to maybe I'll go for
that why you so mad at me Jimmy why did
you grow so much I must have fattened
you up too much like in uh Diablo like
in the prison
cells sorry I I I totally not my
intention you're imagining it we didn't
fatten you on purpose not at all what do
you you're a little bit of a
psycho it's all in your head Jimmy we
were just feeding you well you didn't
have to eat things that we put in front
of you wasn't forcing you at
all see all these angry chickens trying
to kill their boss no respect
they ain't got no
respect couldn't be you guys right you
you guys have respect for me for your
boss of
course I hate when they move like that
it's like not the most difficult thing
but I'm just just too dumb for it when
I'm like
running can't Dodge
them oh yeah barely dodging a
[\h__\h] hey do it always have this buff
isn't this buff new
well I'm not going
to not be moving and I'm not going to
keep this stamp I think so I think I'm
going to sell
it she knows an no no I know the Buffs
but I didn't
realize no I also know that you can get
the Midway through but I wasn't sure if
that was the first time I had it on that
one
for upgrade F oh true but I'll be
selling them anyway at some point
whatever
that so much
choices
ow but you made me climax
thanks for that you hit me but you hit
me
good killing me killing me
[Music]
good since I'm singing it reminds me so
so I was so
excited and her viewers understood
the the one Yong dance you guys already
don't know so one Yong is a pretty
famous uh C- up idol in Korea um she's
in the group I now but that wasn't her
first group that's not where she started
out but she's now in the group I and um
she's really popular and she's known for
being really cute and beautiful and long
legs and really
slender and and she does really cute AO
ago that is so good that it pisses
people off partially
makes them
mad um but yeah uh when when she dances
choreographies she dances them you know
in her style like you can tell her charm
I wouldn't say like she's my OSI or
anything like I am aware of her
existence and she's cute and and all
that and I like her groups songs but I'm
not like a huge fan or something um but
yeah I
definitely know
her um she's cute and so I saw there's
like this thing a while ago this is like
a K-pop meme I guess she did a move in
the concert like it was filmed with a
fan cam thanks for the memberships she
did this move that we copied H where
like she takes a step forward while
turning and like swinging her hip in a
nice curve and that became a big topic
you know cuz it looked so smooth and
elegant when she did it yeah so I'm glad
I'm glad they got it cuz if I would have
told you guys in my chat maybe two
people would have known that what I
talked
about which is fine too you know I'm I'm
fine with that I'm fine with us never
understanding each other's memes me
always asking what you guys are talking
about and then the one time I pick up
memes that you guys know you're not
happy with it you don't like the memes
that I pick up like skiy and brizer and
all that stuff I don't know why
I'm just like picking up what I'm
hearing from be boo I
guess yeah the contrast so I'm I'm Sorry
by the way for bringing it up I I'll be
honest like I was nervous and I
just cuz you know I don't know I really
didn't know what else to come up with
when she asked me for like a flirty sexy
line first of all and second of all I
was just nervous and and and what I came
up with was making her say stupid [\h__\h]
that can get
clipped I mean entertainment brain you
know was hilarious
okay but I'm so bad at memes I didn't
even I don't even remember these phrases
I have to ask chat to remind me of the
full phrases I'm such a
loser conted brain while yeah
yeah she said it's so great like I I was
honestly delighted by her saying fine I
guess we I'm a little
part it sounded so cute when she's said
it I think we've all been blessed by
it she really said it
nicely was
cute it's an old meme
but a funny one I guess I'm sorry about
the skibby toilet but she knew that one
surprisingly I guess not so surprisingly
I guess that's pretty
famous I guess that is pretty famous
is uh can I combine one of these with uh
the sausage or the
axe or should I
roll no
roll everybody he wants to be my
SK Hast is
[Music]
good okay there we go there's everything
oh this one has a crit damage plus
10 I think I should just first work on
what I got
unless those are not going to become a
collab anyway although I feel like there
should be an axe sausage
collab just attach the
axe to the sausage you know what I mean
swing it's like a really flexible axe
like
a wobbly axe sounds
fun congrat on the last stream was worth
staying upward thank you so much I
appreciate
it all right I'll just um how does that
relate to H I would say I know it was a
stretch but I actually can pull
something out of my ass there and tell
you I would uh connected with that one
like PP game that b played weren't there
peees harmed in that game so Axe and
sausage to
me I could say that's a reference to
that
game yeah
see not the one you guys might want to
see
but sprx can't always be according to
your
liking but uh but
not I can't reach anything I need to
pick up radius
oh well okay uh what about these uh plug
type and cuz I don't have everything
here yet so ah okay I could get the
meteor with the Axe by getting the elite
lava
bucket but we were also considering
getting the wait no the boys love x
super collab I feel like I already did
that before but I could do it again
sausage boys love that one was so
funny I mean it's here so I might just
get it should
not I COC and sausage that's a
thing a yeah I had that one too was it
that good though
is any of them buffed no they're not
buffed okay let's get Asa for the
sausage
sure
fine ah another sticker in the same
place time to clear up a little bit I
feel like it did really too much
f fck y
it yeah I think because I invested so
much into the Super Chat I don't have as
much damage output as I had before at
this
point let me go
here oh
nice I'll take the limiter
[Music]
okay
okay keep healing yeah oh I finally
reached the stamps increase damage by 5%
for each okay that's not going to work
for us [\h__\h] another stamp I
don't I couldn't leave it on the ground
but oh and
[Music]
H I guess I'll just get boys love for
the
axe so use it for
[Music]
now ah ah oh
triple is that
membership take
I know it cost of enhancing is reduced
by 20% and amals
appear should I keep
it I guess that's
okay
um not what I normally would go
[Music]
for not my favorite yeah drop okay we
don't want to like hog all the space and
then not be able to take other things
that we might
want um headphones okay
what was I talking about ah the the
memes
yeah and and and and not just like that
one one young meme but just generally
like talking about dances like doing
little dances K-pop dances that uh go
recognizes I need to bring up more I I
was wondering like if um like generally
I want to make uh like YouTube POV for
you guys but I was wondering if we do a
collab that's only on her side di uh she
can she seems like she's allowed to play
copyrighted songs as much as she wants
so they often do like K-pop dancing
streams where they just play all the
popular K-pop songs and they just dance
along to them I feel like
maybe if we do a one-sided collab on her
Channel we could I could make use of
that privilege of not caring about the
copyright and Just Dance my ass off
because I could I could only do that in
an unarchived stream but even for
unarchived I'm not allowed to use the
original audio I would have to you
know use uh instrumental that I have
permission for so that's you know not a
big library to choose
from you know those are just some of the
things I think about but also I already
have like from today I'm so inspired
like I have so many ideas of what I want
to do withy especially when I come to
Korea I won't share all of my dreams
hopes and
dreams oh oh I didn't know that was so
decent um because what if they don't
come true because I said them out loud
what if I jinx them don't want to jinx
them um but one thing that I could
say that's not so much in Jinx danger oh
10 minutes oh [\h__\h] is um
where's
Pula wait I want this
box uh oh sorry it's like going for off
the lab in Korea and to K dream I want
to do Koka
stream together in
3D that would be cute
and and uh dancing off collab dancing
stream cuz today I mean it worked out
pretty well but there was some delay I
think in how early each of us heard
maybe a little bit not too much though
because uh I think staff s played the
music I think so yeah if one of us would
have played it there would have been
more delay but staan played it
so I feel like there was a tiny bit
delay but not as much as that could have
been but also not ideal like if if we're
together IRL that would be even better
you know
yeah can you tell I'm really
excited about like
interesting collaborations see I I I
wanted
to like say that I know there's some
people who only watch like whole
live and and surely there's some people
who only watch like is ID
don't um but I think it's nice to do
some networking and especially after 4
years um it feels like also kind of
refreshing and fun to connect with
people outside of my bubble cuz I
definitely feel like I'm I've been like
staying a lot in my little safety bubble
I
guess bubble bubble bubble bubble bubble
bubble bubble pop
pop and staying in my little bubble is
nice and comfortable but every once in a
while it's nice to pop the
bubble and try out some new things meet
some new people and it kind of I feel
like it gets the inspiration going
also you were interested in is concerts
when I Shar it with you yeah yeah they
look really fun and they upload them on
YouTube so you can watch some stuff on
YouTube run run run
run so you
know I hope you guys don't
mind but yeah speaking of like popping
the bubble and stepping outside of it I
was definitely very nervous about that
too
because uh like I think there was a lot
of like a a b big audience watching
today especially on Go Side the like
from people who don't normally watch me
or maybe even saw me for for the first
time ever so that made me really nervous
I wanted to make a good impression but
uh how can you make a good impression
when you can't communicate
right but I help it it seems like like
yeah Stan also told me yeah you you made
a good impression Korean fans really
enjoyed it and F was cute and fun okay
okay
okay lightning
Wier I'm
glad feel like I could have made a
better impression though but I was a a
hot
mess I hot
[Music]
mess it's
okay I'll get I'll get used to it
hopefully
I'm
super chill and like oh God familiar
environments but even with h life
collabs I sometimes still get nervous
like I still get so n oh my God nervous
for every single uh holot talk
episode every
time every time when I do Hol talk I get
so nervous that I need to like urgent
urgent
pee like suddenly so suddenly I don't
knowwhere it's like oh God I got to
pee you never detected nervousness
really really in h oh definitely is
um cuz I always want to do them Justice
you know I want to do the whole talk
uh guest
Justice that feel makes me feel very
pressured who would be a guest I would
make you nervous all maybe maybe Ian
members
generally would make me less
nervous for am I think I was still a bit
nervous because it wasn't you know
special
circumstances uh what should I take
should I take the chicken feather just
in
case I wouldn't mind it taking up a spot
in my
lineup you chill of IDs too yeah I think
I would be pretty chill of ID too
although oh
no okay we now have a bomb wait does Axe
collab with bomb at all I don't remember
how do you guys know all of this by
heart
[Music]
anyway crazy
Lads no
okay I stop
give me give me give me I hate
this
a never played this I got the wiki
pulled up okay you're honest that you're
using a cheat thank you I appreciate it
that way you guys can give me quick
answers m
what should I collab Hollow bomb with
then I'm still looking for the boys love
book which probably showed up a couple
of times until now already and I didn't
take it uh but yeah boys love for the
axe and then for bomb potato I will
never find the potato maybe I really
don't have it unlocked who knows how do
you unlock the the
potato how do you do it
uh playing as coron oh I think I yeah I
did play as cor before but do you also
have to like finish a stage as
her I definitely saw the X potato
before I am so
certain survive 10 minutes oh
H I don't think I used her outside of
the stream
but you got to say hey guys to the chat
that's the challenge that's how you
unlock
it wait do I want to keep any of these
stamps I feel like I'm not getting the
stamps that I
want pick one yeah that that one is
okay we love
explosions
power will I keep it though should I
keep the
[Music]
flower ideally we keep a spot for the
greed later
you can check out this game if you
unlock potato nut okay
just want to say hope you have a nice
break thank
you I'm excited to
[Music]
chill GRE don't call
this I got the boys love y
are you going to stress out who whoa no
why would
I I'm
fine this is stressing me out and having
to clean and cook after the stream is
stressing me out
too a little
bit might as well get hope soda oh okay
when I see it I'm kind of blind most of
the
time okay no hope so
that sucking all the coins in like a
vacuum
y well I have a feather in any case I
would be fine but I don't want to waste
it sit here I hate this I hate this like
wibbly wobbly
Wiggly why you got to be like that
thanks for the
raid okay what are we going to combine
with the bomb I I I I I want to do new
things that I don't have here yet do you
see anything that I here I have The
Cutting Board one I have the asako tail
one I
have yeah that's it is there one that I
don't have yet that I didn't do yet
potato [\h__\h] yeah right we've been
through
this [\h__\h] potato music
music bomb and music did I not do that
one
before the the this
one does that collab bomb and music bomb
doesn't go with music
okay yeah I know this only shows what
that's why I'm asking
oh oh wait oh my God they're doing the
tole thing [\h__\h] but it's not too bad
[Music]
yet I was so stuck what the
[\h__\h] yeah the fence I thought you know
dodged the train but then there was a
fence that was literally not visible
anymore at that
point of all the
enemies I definitely feel weaker than in
the previous run but MoneyWise we're
already at 44k
ooh how far did I get 20 minutes right
last time 20 minutes I made 50k okay
that's actually not such a big
difference you hear that cutting cutting
cutting then
Mommy Mommy oh the trees are shooting
the the PO balls aren't they
ah yeah right no greed stamp ah [\h__\h]
considering that it's decent
income can't always have great St but I
feel like it will still show up it will
just be really
[Music]
late where what what drop what where
something dropped I don't see an
arrow am I blind something made
blop stamp oh
okay okay this is the spam that like
disappears at the 20th minute right it's
going to
[Music]
Sur keep on
Surviving thank you for the Super Chat
America here you're going to America
oo I have another exciting tangent can
you believe it the tangent Factory is
going
strong but before I tell you that should
I get one of these for our future
collabs did we decide what we're going
to do with the
bomb oops
see it
should I just get the
feather
yeah let's survive longer okay so
something
absolutely unexpect unexpected
happen or is maybe going to
happen this is an IRL
uh topic please
enjoy so as you know I used to be in art
[Music]
school and I didn't finish it I did two
years but the two years are First Years
just repeated just
twice right I told you this
before so I'm not super proud of it I
try my best but I fail it m
okay yeah
it w it's so bright it's blindingly
bright well nice
clear don't die again
ideally uh there okay it was going to
all disappear in a moment anyway all
right okay W this is the one where it
gets kind of crazy with all the red in
the
moment let's try to survive without
using the feather
oh this diagonal is working okay stay
here I I I I can't I can't I can't it's
okay it's okay this is really more
survivable than you might think at first
oh
God I thought I could walk through
that sorry but we only have 50k and we
got one more revive and it clears
everything yby
I could walk through
it all right the the last one we didn't
make it to the
boss oh no oh no oh no why I forgot it
does the to
thing okay okay okay okay
okay uh wait I'll
I'll get back to my dent
maybe maybe after the bus I don't know
should I get nurse
horn I know I can Dash really the well
but I didn't have a dash available I
think at the
moment I generally always try
to okay I'm try to continue my
I'll try to continue my
tangent okay so I um from that
time
I uh didn't really stay in
contact with anybody besides a Senai
that I had back in the day that wasn't
in my
class
um and and one girl who used to be
like my best friend uh in my
class um but with her I
think we didn't initially stay in
contact um we
only I think we once I was so Random I
was like in a hospital when I still
lived in a different
city and I was in the hospital and I
randomly met her there for the first
time in
years and that's I think when we like
reconnected via like social media like
we told each other our social media
accounts I'm too [\h__\h]
dumb greet them oh I'm going to go
looking for
it right
there might be the end of me
I don't have any more revives
right so late and the greed was
greedy
mle it's hard to reach ah risky I'm kind
of inside of the
enemies
risky
okay okay have big more C I'll be more
careful now so yeah we reconnected after
we met
years uh I think like she also even
already graduated so it was like
way way
past but yeah H and since then we've
like not been talking regularly but like
she she likes Japan so she also like
when I post something about Japan she's
like you know sometimes she comments on
it and all that
and
so uh what do I
get [\h__\h] none of this works with the
bomb I think except maybe the bounce
ball but I don't like that collab I had
it before spider cooking reall
Dam it I could take idle music Idol song
and collab it with something
else horn
okay so okay here comes the thing thanks
to being connected with her like she
finished that school so she stayed in
contact with a lot more people I guess
from her class uh thanks for being
connected with her I have been
invited
to a
reunion I never thought this would
happen first of all because I didn't
finish the school and I was only in that
class for one year that was my first
class uh I didn't think it would ever
happen also because it's been so long I
don't know like reunions don't feel so
common in AA I think like they surely
exist but don't feel that maybe it's
just because I don't get invited cuz
never finished at school that's why it
feels uncommon to me but I got I got
really excited because like even though
I didn't um stay very long with them
that one year made a big impact on me
more than the second year honestly like
my friend circle from that I gained in
the first year with that class before I
repeated the year and end ended up in a
different first class High School um
that first class had more impact on me
and and closer friends and
um yeah I I'm excited to see them again
especially my my particular friend
Circle that I had uh yeah well I I'll
have to travel for it and take a day off
for it um or maybe two the like cuz
travel time is kind of long um but yeah
I'm I'm I'm excited I I never thought
this would
happen yeah I'm also I guess feeling a
little bit weird about catching up I
wonder like you know word goes around I
wonder if they I don't think so though
like I don't think they would know what
I do
nowadays but if they ask oh oh I'll say
uh I don't know I I'll come up with
[Music]
something I think
my uh that one friend that invited me I
think she maybe knows I don't think I
told her but she might
know I mean I don't
know H I'll bring ndas and make
everybody sign it just
kidding ah oh it's so cool I can't
believe like I can't imagine how that's
going to be cuz um this is actually so
don't even think about the math but this
is a 10year
reunion 10
years and when I was I was invited to
this WhatsApp group and I was looking
for all the profile pictures and some of
them had like like pictures of them in a
in a wedding dress like with their
partner and so on
and yeah and not everybody had their
face as a picture I was like oh uh this
person no I still remember all their
faces pretty clearly but some of them
that did have their face on their
picture I was like oh wow they're so
adult now I haven't seen om since we
were teenagers this so
crazy you don't live in the same country
as them anymore a that's too bad but I I
honestly I would even travel for
something like that um across borders
maybe not across continents but across
some borders I would do
it okay oh look at what we got we got
[\h__\h] coins are you kidding me oh
because it knows it
can't no you could have filled up with a
defense
item interesting that it gives me
cl don't take the next weapon if you
oh wait a [\h__\h]
second well I got
two are are any of these capable of
collabing with each
other uh oh well we already have two
collabs oh
well we already also have 60k almost I'm
satisfied look how smoothly I slide into
that
my
invincibility but yeah that's exciting
have you guys ever been to a school
reunion the class reunion
I was such a weeb at the time and I I I
think oh god what the what the did I
just run into
y whatever we got
60k
uh they didn't invite me what what the
[\h__\h] maybe I just didn't have your
contact info I was glad to get out of
high same but I'm I'm still kind of in
excited excited about like seeing them
again and just you know and I really
wasn't close of anybody except for that
one friend Circle and I felt really
isolated from the rest of the class cuz
like my friend Circle we were like kind
of
the maybe not weirdos I don't want to
say weirdos but you know what I mean
like more the we had our Corner we we
were five people out of a class of like
30 or something um and we we were
definitely the
weebs not not all of our people were
weeps but there were a lot of like you
know cuz I was in art school everybody
liked like art and all that but uh all
the girls that liked drawing like manga
related anime stuff were in our group
and yeah we were definitely very Japan
culture uh yeah we were the Japan
culture click I wouldn't call us a click
because that kind of sounds like we
wouldn't let anyone else in
uh and that's not true we weren't so
clicky but we were holding strong
together
and I think there were some drama too uh
every now and then U between some of
like the girls but I was I really liked
my group and I was so
sad like when I had to repeat the
year like I just I still met them in the
school quite
often but it's different like like you
know cuz they move on in class and they
have different [\h__\h] to deal with they're
busy with their subjects and all that
subjects I mean the school
things so it was just sad that I saw
them moving on to the next class and I I
felt like a failure first of all I felt
like a big failure
like
yeah oh my [\h__\h]
I felt so
stupid but yeah I just was sad that I
couldn't be with them
anymore just seeing them move on while
you stuck and left
behind yeah I've come so far that's true
I've come so
far I
did I proved that I didn't need the
school at
all yeah okay tears in my eyes go away
go away we don't need that but
yeah what was I going to say
though oh yeah I was going to say like
in the previous schools like in junior
high school and all that I got kind of
bullied I was like yeah people ignored
me and and made fun of
me um in art school I was still kind of
like in in an isolated friend Circle not
one of the cool people but also not like
bullied or so I was I guess I was
tolerated by the pool
people I was definitely kind of weird
cuz my bangs were so long they were like
covering my eyes
partially and I always dress like the
most like
Japanese fashion like everybody dressed
pretty normally maybe there was like
somebody that was kind of like Punky but
besides that most people were like
pretty normal in my class but I I always
had like um uh over KNE socks and skirts
and like you know
so I stood out that
way I was very shy I was so shy probably
because of my experience of getting
bullied and not having many
friends cute
CH kind of cringe but also
cute why 2K no NE I don't know just
Japanese like I was trying to imitate
like Harajuku cute
style with what I
had embrace the CR yes yes
yeah I'm not going to play the game
anymore today by the way I'm going to
read a little bit of super
chats kind of like mentally tired from
this game my head hurts a little bit
again and I want I want a tangent more I
talk
more look at everyone say they like
anime
now when I say cringe I don't mean it
like that
negatively m
yeah but for people who hear this kind
of stuff for the first time I do want to
like uh note that yeah I didn't finish
that High School uh after that like
failing the first year for the second
time I I took a little break from school
so to say and and did some
work uh traveled moved away from Austria
did some work etc but I went back to
Austria afterwards and I went to Hotel
school for 3 years with which was uh
like kind of like kind of like high
school um and I finished that and I got
my degree so to say so it's not like I'm
a complete failure who didn't get any
kind of school graduations
whatever yeah trade
school which is very common in Austria
like 50% pretty much I would say go
after Junior High School they go to
trade
school like whatever they choose any job
cuz they have that in any kind of job
branch and then they go to the school uh
like two months a year and the rest they
work for a shitty salary shitty as hell
salary I bullied a lot in middle school
but I'll tell you wh sounds hot as
hell hot I'll tell you nobody had the
hots for
me I definitely have had like like maybe
one Crush I remember having a weird
crush on
a on on like somebody was like three
classes above me I think who was who
seemed like a big
nerd but it was so weird I don't even
think we talked more than once or
twice and something about mil schnitten
connected
us I don't know I got a ask my at that
time bestie if she
remembers M it's like m is a snack that
I liked to eat a lot at the time I still
like it
now just a little
snack did you drop your notebooks no
like no nothing really it was like
nothing I
stayed very isolated and
shy proud my whole school
life but it's kind of fun to think back
to school life now and yeah yeah yeah uh
I think I I was talking about this
because of the Super Chat like when you
get like when you don't feel so
connected to them or so you don't want
to like you wouldn't want to go to a
reunion but I don't know I definitely
want to go but I don't know I I don't I
don't know I don't know they have like
weird date choices and the the people
that I want to some of the people that I
want to meet can't go to the date that
they're seemingly choosing so my at the
time BFF is like offering uh a separate
date uh just for our friend Circle to do
a reunion and I'm think thinking well I
don't want to travel there twice in one
month um but I might just go for the
smaller reunion then cuz that's those
are the people I really want to see
again it's going to be so nostalgic oh
my God oh my
God
yeah yeah sounds
fun I hope it works out either way I'll
go to one of
them either
way how a cute little friend CLE K me I
wonder if my other class will ever do a
reunion but I have actually zero contact
with any of them I don't think they
could they would even know how to
contact me so
whatever I don't I never really felt
very included in that
class so no
need at least you're doing fine you mean
LifeWise
yeah they just got to drop a
Supa no I don't I really don't think
that that class or anybody knows what I
do so
impossible so okay here let me finish my
tangents I was going to ask you guys why
is it always the small and blue
girls what is this what's going on like
why do
I it's not on
purpose I don't aim for them it just
happens it's a coincidence I think it's
a coincidence it's a funny coincidence
though blue women in general yeah cuz
waya also blue Nai Mama also
blue crony also blue but then you could
say that about other colors too
maybe let's
see a p also blue narissa also blue
true like if we talk about like
pink there's actually not that much pink
I would say nanora mikai Iris would fall
in the pink
category but yeah not like that crazy
connected to them huh a m
too c ah Cy
yeah
H maybe there's just a lot of blue too
it's not
fair qu true I was actually just looking
at this screen right now as reference so
clearly isn't on here so I didn't I
didn't really consider
it heck even H is
blue yeah but then it doesn't always
apply like I'm not close to Suicide
Senpai not that close like I haven't
talked in a while with k stand byai for
example and yeah you know doesn't always
apply need more orange girls true
true I did drop n a message
recently couple days
ago we haven't talked in a long time but
I know I felt like okay I'm going to do
it
yeah I think she appreciated
it she wrote
back yeah wrote her a long
message
tried
orange
orange so what else was I going to say
uh I had a in my nap I had a
stream I had a dream about the stream
right
after
like is like interesting it felt so real
cuz there was also like uh cuz I was
mirroring the stream when we were
dancing I was mirroring it in OBS so
that um uh I could do I have to explain
why I did that for dancing for like
knowing which hand to pull up and
whatever you know what I mean right I
was doing that and so that reflected in
my dream like so apparently apparently
there was a part according to my dream
there was a part of the map that we were
in the enir
the frey environment where if we walk
through this portal the whole map or so
or the footage will be mirrored and
that's like the mirror world of it and
we forgot to walk through but it would
have been there and we could have
mirrored everything it would have been
so much
easier yeah they had that
feature yeah and also like was kind of
weird at the end the stream generally
was fun but at the end of the dream did
I say stream the dream generally was fun
but at the end of the stream in the
dream
uh it got kind of weird I got like
interrupted I don't know it was weird
not worth
explaining but yeah it was fresh in my
mind so I dreamed about it comfortably
on my Casper
pillow while drooling on smoothie
yeah what else oh yeah I want to learn
more of the dances did you like the
little taste of kiding that you heard in
case you haven't heard the full song yet
k
k want to learn more of their dances I
feel like I should be able uh to get
perms
to like use their songs and karoke
streams and stuff and maybe for YouTube
shorts I could cover their songs should
be fine like I already used it in my
stream got perms for that so maybe we
can add that to my library of usable
songs in archive
streams yeah maybe when I'm done with
the Mirage challenges I'll upload a
kidding uh YouTube shorts too a proper
one you go are a really good picking up
each other's cover thank you it was just
so confusing in the beginning because uh
I was still looking at it like on
mired and so is like using the wrong
side of my body a lot of the
time very confusing I wonder like she
seems to also do that and try to adjust
in her mind with it that's it's so
difficult like you got to try that one
time trying to copy moves so fast when
they're mirrored and your brain is
trying to mirror them too while you're
looking at it
it's so difficult it's like you're
playing twister with your
brain but yeah I invited her also to do
um miras challenge like properly with me
like I asked her to send me raw motion
data so that it will be nicer it looks
better than cuz we can clean it up in
post edit and yeah she has then a little
bit more time to uh
uh learn it maybe if she wants
to clean up that motion yes motion
mention I think that's kind of
it yes yes yes yes that's kind of it I
was so cute today ah se oh my God were
you here in the beginning of the stream
I found a funny thing if I for lip
syncing I noticed that's how it happened
for lip syncing if I choose not the
hybrid mode but only the uh pick up by
voice I can make a really funny weird
[Music]
face you got to check the archive
later but it's uh I'm not going to use
that mode anymore anyway I use it by
accident if I use voice only my mouth
won't open when I open it without a
sound so
but you got to check it out it looks
funny I could like pull down my upper
lip and be like no [\h__\h] or something
like
that to me it reminded me of freaking
Morty or Dr Seuss I guess yeah not
really what it reminded me of but you
guys were reminded of it
[Music]
okay let's read some super chats in 20
minutes I want to like not go over 3
hours cuz I need to give myself some
time to clean and uh pack and
stuff and
cook maybe 30
minutes yeah but I have a headache um
um can you guys bring your own bgm to
work today I have a
headache I feel like over
stimulated am I like developing migraine
or something like that could that
be I don't know how that works
[Music]
so let me find
myself there I
am how close Clos are you from the
screen well what be close
obviously do you feel feel sensitive to
light right now I feel
yeah like my
screens no I don't mean like I have a a
migraine now but I'm wondering if it's
like something you can develop like
slowly if yes then I feel like
like maybe that's what's happening I
just have a lot of uh headache these
past
days it's
weird yeah you
can uh do we have an Autumn version uh
only like a Halloween one and I I I
guess I could switch to the winter one
that also I think only comes with
Christmas
decorations I don't have it ready right
now so it's just going to be cherry
blossoms need more electrolytes M drink
lots of water I've been
trying maybe I should drink more like
sports
[Music]
drinks before we seen Christmas
decorations still go for it I guess so
but not
now remind me when I'm back but the girl
talk room has Christmas
[Music]
decorations just water would be better I
guess doesn't have electrolytes
though gigy is going to play Fallout New
Vegas uh soon nice I I'm going to play
it also again sometime you know it's our
little comeback anytime we want game
so return of K's balls
oh I don't know do you guys want
to I've been working on the Advent
calendar I can happily announce uh we're
working on
it it's looking
good and we figured I figured out a way
subconsciously how to lessen the stress
on our artist Pon Modi we're going to of
course go with the same artist um but
yeah we have a new
system you got the domain back yeah
should be fine the old ones are also
still
up silence yeah I have a headache please
get your own music
uh turn on your own music if you wantan
to while I head for
it apply
cats yeah it's nice to just sometimes
like we are always forcing music on you
guys who knows if you like that music or
if you would want to listen to any music
at all at that point so I think it's
actually good to give you you guys you
option to either not listen to anything
or listen to your own music I think is
generally
good it's nice for a change yeah okay
let's see Diablo back in
Hell uh super jets
[Music]
Lu
this keep on reusing this thumpnail also
for holo cure I reused the thumbnail too
cuz I didn't want to spend time making
another
one and it looked cute
anyway ah here we go take it Monkey D
take a 47 D Cruz
D can I say how gorgeous you are pretty
stop
Cruz D Tracy D oh s million on goodbye
sing
[Music]
noise such a cute song so
nostalgic I forgot Japanese
[Music]
for
spanking thanks for the red super chat
I'm always ready for cat
yeah have you also drooled on your cat
before important
question thank you disy yeah you know I
I like being more expressive and you
know because my life Tod doesn't really
have teeth that's also one big reason
why I like using this one because I mean
it does have teeth but like barely
visible it's nice to be able to
smile that's like like the big like
upside to
it you made me think my phone was going
off humming goodbye declaration I could
tell the difference you have goodbye
declaration as your ringtone but like
the version with instrumentals
right will 3.0 have teeth I asked for it
but probably
not cuz that I think
they maybe have to add something to the
art maybe that's too much to
ask I don't know they're still getting
back to me on that
one like 3.0 is finished but I was like
oh oh I feel like I asked for teeth
oh more visible are you guys going to
like still do it and they were like oh
we didn't get any like that I was like
oh ma oops oh I thought I sent that
request I'm pretty sure but oh maybe got
lost can I still get teeth even though
you already like seemingly finished
working on it and they're
like I don't know no
reply well I'm still waiting I'm still
waiting give me some teeth yeah please
please I want more
teeth cuz I really like how YouTubers
look when they have teeth and they
smile I'm jealous they look
happy yeah I'm a tee trans yeah she
doesn't need her teeth anymore does
she how morbid let me take her teeth if
Amma ever comes back you know for
something she'll be without teeth is
that
okay I mean like who's going to use a
more me
chiku for her
gums how would it sound chikaku with no
teeth I don't know how do you sound when
you have no
teeth like that
me something like that well that's just
how it's going to be from now
on H you
impression that's a bit
extreme oh buy is that
how if I wanted to do it that's like the
direction I would I would
go you sound like
shooting okay okay thanks time ghost fix
with pinky just wants to say thank you
for the wonderful performance in I saw
you I was particularly Blown Away by
your vocals they were so good I got
goosebumps
a your stage presence is top tier I'm so
glad I got to experience it who are you
standing next
to tell me like I saw like two kfps
right next to each other pretty sure one
of them was
you just
curious because I need to identify my
chickin identify
yourself for the folder mhm
mhm talk to but I think ghost be not
here right now so I won't get the answer
I
guess
H the kfp records have to be maintained
yes but not I'm just kidding I'm not
actually like adding it to any folder
I'm just just
um writing
down a
tendency no for real
though I'm too lazy to keep that
going anyway I'm so happy you enjoyed it
go f make sure to get back to me about
my question uh any in any case thank you
for traveling to check out the concert
for me I appreciate it my Australian
kfps sorry I I I would love to you know
be in an be at an event in Australia but
that's really up to the events I
guess one day one
day Supernova d d d for the red super
chat H just want to say your performance
was Bloody amazing Blown Away ah yeah I
saw you
too yeah you were like you were standing
um like close like in front like like
there was this like row where you can
walk through where there's no no chairs
right you were like really close to that
like space where you can I don't know
what do you call it a corridor no uh a
path yeah I know you stood there mhm yes
yes you were in the front line H like
almost in front of that empty aisle yeah
I
I see I remember I saw you guys I
registered you in my brain you looked so
happy oh Wicky was with you like right
next to you
or
wiyy Vlog do is it up yet I haven't seen
it yet I feel feel like my algorithm
would show me
[Music]
path
was I
[Music]
see
M need to
check
again from what I have
in my my
archives and what was that yeah thank
you GD Blown Away press for
Kos I'm so glad you got to experience
that yeah feel like there
were like feel like I feel like almost
like most of the kfp that we there
traveled from
Australia thank you so much M Australian
mates so sweet of them Psy than soon nin
diesel thank you for the pinky boss your
stage at ID sword was fantastic I'm so
happy to be here and appreciate your
stage today also happy to chant eating
toita again yeah but stuned at the ID
part by the way though the ID part oh
when C KO said something in Indonesian
right I had a very good time with whole
life fans and K because of you thank you
all thank
you I think it went better this time
though met some met a few Indonesian
thank you that's sweet to
hear there were some I we met there
though
a I'd like to hear that give me their
names give me their names give me give
me
now name them spell it out spell it
out I'm
[Music]
waiting oh well thank you thank you
thank you n diesel I'm glad you also
could go there
yeah thank you Ito very
fun Ito was originally for
the
uh the the de extra
stage not uh honeyworks extra stage um
so it's great that's getting like so
much usage even way after even over a
year over a
year wait maybe not wait was honey works
this
year huh
it feels like over
here oh how many Works was this year oh
[\h__\h] ah oh you meant it sounds like
something sh would say true true true
that's
true well me c might be more similar
than you thought but maybe I can
generally um hold back those similar
phrases like like maybe it's in my head
and I just I just lock it in there a bit
more than she
does longer than a year for real it
does I'm surprised but yeah so as I said
I'm glad it's getting uh good mileage
usage that song
yeah world
tour let's go
[Music]
it's
F she doesn't even attempt to hold back
exactly I love that it's
amazing more of that
please need to eat a meal thanks for the
r chat K thank you for always inspiring
me have a great day thank you a it's
very nice very sweet you too you shall
also have a great
day me D Bill Wilson D lunchbox d
SP D dong and certainly thanks for the
pinky I have an idea about the witch
books try reading the short stories they
wouldn't ruin the show for you since you
since they uh were handled well then
make an informed decision if you want to
read the rest do is speci as
English wait was there a followup don't
see a
followup do I still have credits I I
bought so many things on Audible
going to be listening to them this
weekend but it's all Lo of the Rings and
um Game of
Thrones so oh no okay cuz you ended it
with a dash
minus Witcher continuation
wi
Do Well for now I'm so glad I I I was
struggling with like having nothing to
watch a while ago and now I have all of
breaking bed and then Better Call Saul
and still I have Arcane and by the time
I finish watching all of that I'm sure
I'll have some other new stuff to
watch yeah I got a good
backlog met colol is so good I'm excited
follow season 2 is that going to not
take a while longer that feels like it's
going to take a while longer Breaking
Bad tangents dle yeah I've been holding
back today um I will say I've I'm I okay
I I try not to spoiler I I'll say it
like vaguely but I'm at the part now
where the wife is
in which is
surprising she's in
wait that does sound kind of spoilery
she's not dealing drugs I'll just say
that
okay the T part no that's not what
that's not what I mean with
in she's on board no oh
yeah yeah but damn that that Hank
episode was so stressful I really
thought like this whole episode he had a
death flag over
him wao and then the moment when
hospital and then Walter Walter is like
in front of that
door and then that guy crawls towards
him bleeding over the whole floor holy
[\h__\h] holy [\h__\h] wow I I really thought
things are going to
like get
out
also some where in those recent episodes
there was a hint um from the Tuco
side
uh was it the guy he said something
about
having a
relative in
o over there and like something
foreshadowing like someone perhaps kind
of like
uh
um that's like
secretly you know and I think so you
don't have to tell me anything don't
actually but my
my
uh
what's ah ah yeah I guess that's what
they're called wait adjusting
my guess is cuz this would be a huge
twist and very disappointing and
shocking that it's
Hank's
partner because isn't he
Mexican something in my
throat Gomez yeah I feel like it must be
him because that just makes sense like
the way they're foreshadowing it and
like it feels like something will come
up in the
future shut up
[Music]
lunchbox um but yeah we'll see we'll see
we'll see I we'll see if my Fey is
correct I do think this really
nant in German we say Nahant
dip it oh that seems like seems like I'm
I'm on to something okay let me read
super chats Justin lamber Pion D unknown
D spankenheimer
in all these birthday super chats I
remember that it's my birthday today and
I'm also just a few days from my four
year KY work anniversary yeah I'm
looking forward to many more years of
this oural and the great community
you've built thank you awesome so you
must be at four years by now maybe yeah
probably or are you yeah
maybe congratulations thank you for
supporting for such a long time and not
getting sick of
me I appreciate it and happy belated
birthday happy birthday to you
in the H say happy
[Music]
birthday
congratulations thank you for the
support I hope you will continue
supporting and hope that you'll stay the
way you
are cuz you're
lovely my birthday tomorrow too oh no no
no no I'm going to miss it cuz I'm not
going to be streaming but happy birthday
in
[Music]
advance coming up on one year
already something is in there thank you
oh my God one year got to appreciate the
the somewhat
newbies thank you for being part of
kfp you were my most watched streamer
this year according to statistics I saw
lot of those pop up here and there is a
bit overwhelming because a lot of is
going on like with also things in my
algorithm with K
so haven't really been paying attention
to it but oh mint got me too I was your
number
one she never shows up in chat
though does she just not watch
anybody and therefore watching me for
five minutes or so is enough lurking why
the [\h__\h] is she lurking why mint prove
your number one stateus and comment in
the chat more
often I'd love to see
that God damn
it this
girl going to write her strong worded
letter
now where is
she girl what the [\h__\h] I am your number
one
why do I can't see what I'm
writing
why do you never comment and show up in
the chat
girl make yourself known and
seen talk to
us she want wanted do you think it was
her plan she wanted that all
along oh she
wrote she WOTE back to
me girl she says no I just like to lur
not
acceptable at
least every once in a while you got to
say
something I'm giving up on
you she doesn't want to derail the
Stream
I
mean I know that like when somebody WR
something in the chat was like I
wouldn't say it derails but like yeah
everybody's like oh hi me hi me hi me hi
or whoever is there uh and yeah maybe I
don't know I I also worry about that
sometimes when I chat but I mean like
one comment every once in a while
couldn't hurt and I don't mind like her
showing up anytime you know I would love
her present that's what I don't don't
worry about it don't worry about it I I
just want to see you there I didn't know
that you like me this much that you
actually still watch my streams like I
didn't I didn't think so no it's nice to
know you know you know how that feels to
me like
very happy see I didn't know that if it
wasn't for
that like
statistic yeah it's affirming
feels good
[Music]
man need a good confidence
boo tell me tell me that you love me
like okay don't tell me but like just
you know show up sometimes I wouldn't I
don't mind I want to see you please
derail my chat der rail my chat do it do
it do it do it do
it yes it it helps my brain
worms it helps
me I'm
hungry got to make my Ramen soon or like
now time is up guys Cinderella time
coming a little bit early
[Music]
today going to make that Robin yeah how
do I make
ramen inant Ramen like I feel like I
know but like they they wrote me like
instructions and it it feels like it's
kind of over complicating
it
h let me let me bring it and you
interpret it for me
so as I said I didn't get like package
stuff I got like
testers so it's like a handwritten
instruction instruction boil two cups
water and cook noodles for 3 minutes or
until desired texture I'll do three
minutes at the end mix in the powder
Sach okay okay
and then top with Aroma oil okay so
that's fine but then there's a separate
note that says a thing that confuses
me please use leftover noodle H2O think
that means water that's not the
confusing part to add to the
satchet and then in
in the curvy marks boil in two C cups h
t
H2O why why don't just write water okay
so says please use leftover noodle water
to add to the satchet you mean do they
mean the aroma no wait powder satch to
add but like when what why don't
understand like this is the different
from the original instruction
do you understand
this like at what step do I do this
before I put the powder satel into the
ramen
maybe cuz again first just boil two cups
of water cook the noodles then at the
end mix in the powder satchet and step
free top with Aroma oil but the the
other note says please use leftover
noodle water to add to the satchet so it
I yeah and ah okay wait I I think I see
the connection now boil in okay so
before I add the powder Sachin I should
add water to the powder
satchet but why would I have left over
noodle
water I'm not removing any water from
the two cups of water that I'm cooking
the noodles in maybe just a little bit
maybe they just want me to take a tiny
bit cook the noodles remove the noodles
put the
S put the s in the water and then add
the noodles back I'm adding noodles
back I take the dles out see it doesn't
say that that's an important Point
that's missing here in the instructions
I take the noodles out it doesn't say
that let me confirm I think I think this
is a a time where um I would get a reply
um can you ask something for me I'm
about to cook I'm about I'm about to
cook and the
instruction is low key confusing me um
text
um so ridiculous I feel pathetic no I
would have just I would be fine making
making it with the original instruction
but the extra note is like adding a lot
of confusion here need text support
video yeah I would love them to send me
a
video
um
so the main instruction is okay but they
added an extra note that says please use
left over noodle water to add to the
satchet
do they mean
to remove the noodles after they're done
cooking then put the powder into
[Music]
the noodle
water uh pot that doesn't have the
noodles
[Music]
anymore
boil ah I guess I wouldn't even put the
noodles back in they probably probably
just at that point they expect you to
put the noodles into a bowl finish
cooking the soup and then top the
noodles with the
soup but like why are they not riding
that boil and uh then top the
noodles with the finished soup up
that's 5D chest yeah I think also like
once the real product is out um the
instructions will probably just be these
these simple
instructions the free step instructions
will probably be on the package but
maybe this is a hack you that you guys
can also
use based on the
sounds like you need to strain most of
the water but save some to mix with the
dry
s strain
strain yeah but I'm not pouring it away
right I'm still using it because it's
Ramen it's not yakis
SOA I'm a waiting a reply I will
probably get it soon so I'm just going
to go and prepare it by cooking an egg I
wish I could
make how to make I'll just make a normal
egg it's not the same it's not the same
but it will do and butter corn and and
uh spring onions that'll be my dinner
hell
yeah no come out and go into a serving
Bowl mhm then mix the satchet into some
of the
water
some but I I do think it it's not some
it's in all of it
because it says here uh please use
leftover noodled water to add to the
satchet that sounds like you're adding
the water into
the like in in a different container
just let it li like a little bit of
water into the SAT powder but but
underneath it says in uh uh these like
uh uh curve marks clamon yeah it says
boil in 2 C H2O the C is probably for
cups so don't we have two cups of water
cooking in the pot already so that
sounds to me like I'm not adding water
to the satchet I'm adding the satch to
the water parentheses yeah
brackets you know what I mean this
sounds like
yeah why why is this so pathetic I feel
so
pathetic but I mean you got to give it
to me like this is a little bit
confusing Jesse we need to
cook Jess I'm Jesse is kind of sending
me through a
uh a roller coaster too by the way
because I was liking him um but now he's
doing things
that make me unlike
[Music]
him like I understand that he's unhappy
with the cut they're getting if you
think about how big their cut
is
but him resorting
to trying to not just anybody on the
street he's trying to make money
with the people that are in his um group
uh the the trying to stay away from that
[\h__\h] group that's really not cool yeah
the rehab
group that's not cool but I will say a
lot of people told me they stopped
watching and and lost all their hope for
Walt after that one scene where you know
the girl you
know um but honestly first of all I said
on Twitter that it was other scenes
where I lost my hope for him like when
he did uh when he forced his son to like
get [\h__\h]
drunk uh in a really aggressive scary
demeanor but after that scene that a lot
of people are saying that's when they
lost their hope and perhaps even stopped
watching after that I Feel
Like Walter had a lot of good
person moments
like I don't know
like
[Music]
he I don't know he watching it all now
fresh I don't know if it's like like
this in your minds guys but the
following episodes are more UPS than
Downs
yeah and like for
example I don't know he's just not doing
so badly in those following
episodes yeah he doesn't seem completely
evil so I don't know like I'm I'm I'm
actually again warming up to him now and
then unarming with Jessie because Jesse
is being a [\h__\h] right
now not a full turn no it's it's not not
even that it's
like he's doing like he's he's not
scaring the [\h__\h] out of me anymore so
it's like he's not on the same course
right
[Music]
now slow train wreck
happening but they somehow changed their
course is what I'm feeling but I'm sure
you'll go back to being on the train
Rack Route again both Walter and Jesse
do change a lot for I I I I don't really
understand I was praising Jesse's
character
Arc it seems out of character for him to
sell to the rehab
people that feels so
[Music]
dirty H don't like
it at that point it feels out of
character maybe previously it would have
been in character but at that
point yeah he's in his villain Arc again
broh he going through a lot he seemed
like he
really at the rehab point at that point
when he starts selling he seemed
pretty healed
of course not completely but like
decently
healed over that
incident but yeah well thank you thank
you thank you for the membership renewal
and for the huge Super Chat EDF
fencer thank you wordless what the heck
thank you is it bugging out or is it
really
wordless thank you so much Mah MW Mah
EDF fencer EDF EDF EDF EDF
[Music]
is it really
empty your interpretation is right my
interpretation is right
guys you guys some of you guys were
saying I I take the noodles out and then
put them back again no no no no you keep
them out so I was right with that I'm
not that prophetic after all my
interpretation went the right way okay I
think I'm ready to make my dinner now
nice
okay Sil wish you and Iris played EDF
one time
[Music]
a would have been
fun oh we need to cook I'm okay
okay okay but first the fly in the room
contamination
bro Walters saying the fly let's use a
whole episode but I understand I
understand once again I am very
intelligent in
understanding the implications and
emotions in this show
I know why that fly [\h__\h] is going down
it's not a filler episode it's because
of
Hank y y
yep I'm an empath thank you unlike this
stream is trying to make you think when
it comes to Breaking Bad I'm an
empath that's the proof thank you I I I
you know couldn't bring it up on my my
own but you bring it up
yeah doesn't make too much of a
difference either
way when boiling be
done main difference will just be
texture of noodles since they'll be
spending different amounts of time in
water well maybe I'll take it
out how much of Breaking Bad have you
seen can I catch up I think I'm almost
done with season
fre you know what I'll be want some
Arcane over the
weekend so you get some extra time to
catch up but I'll also be watching
Breaking bed most
likely so let's go whole year fast yeah
I think I'm like at episode nine or 10
of season
3 they're going to release the last oh
okay okay while I'm away Arcane phito
phito I'm probably going to finish it
while I'm gone I wonder I
wonder yeah I'll never catch up at this
point would it help you if
I don't watch Breaking Bad at least not
past this third season and instead start
watching better call all but then I
might want to a tangent about better
call has characters from the other shows
show up as
cameos maybe I have seen that before but
just didn't understand it until now no
no don't do that but I've been told that
I can watch better call
SA um cuz it plays before it just merges
at the
[Music]
end but okay okay I was told wrong what
okay
okay okay
fine
okay you guys are like Walter in the car
now screaming at
me don't do it I don't know what he's
gonna I don't I haven't seen that scene
yet
right also Netflix [\h__\h] spoiled
me Netflix has like previews playing
right when you like hover over a show
uh and I don't understand why it showed
me that because that seemed like
something really far in the
future but when I was about to turn on
Breaking
Bad it showed a scene where Hank had
hair again but judging from the
situation he was in it didn't seem like
it was the beginning of the show it
didn't feel familiar either
and the scene seemed like something that
would be at the end wait
what and not Hank I mean Walter of
course
Walter he does get hair again right cuz
that scene implied
it
right don't correct it she doesn't know
it could be a flashback
but the content of it seemed like
something like the end of the
show I'm not asking for spoilers but
like I'm like why the [\h__\h] are you
showing me this
Netflix pretend you didn't see it I
tried for
be don't overthink it just keep watching
well all good things come to an end you
know
so it's all a
mirage I rais this tangent don't think
about it it's not my fault it's Netflix
fault can't believe it no fa only ramen
yeah I'll go do that now and I I have to
really I have to really
go byebye thanks for watching in German
we say Al in and two streams today very
muchos muchos Grande fun hope you had
fun too I'll be gone for couple days
I'll be back next week and in the
meantime tomorrow is the reveal of the
last white items so please keep an eye
out on that
and what else I don't
know take care
guys thank you stream Mirage
oh yeah I might have a YouTube short one
or two coming
up while I'm
gone byebye
[Music]
byebye byebye
bye-bye
[Music]
byebye
byebye ah doesn't did I say it oh now I
said
it okay okay I did okay okay okay okay
okay okay
[Music]
wait do you not hear any music am I the
only thing that you you here Oh I
thought that was at least some GM
[Music]
son
what is that a is that a meme for that
song how people mishar the
lyrics I need to cuz there's a member
called
s
oh it's a twice fan of Mee oh I didn't
know now I listen to it again with that
in my mind thank you bye-bye