[Music]
foreign
hold on
hello everyone welcome to today's stream
which was supposed to be yesterday sorry
for moving it but thanks everyone for
being so spontaneous and uh adjusting
with me and cooperating with me and
waiting for us
for the revival of tacoma because it's
been a while like
right our last collab it has been a
while like two weeks or so
yeah last time minecraft wasn't such a
hoe
yeah i don't know what was going on
that's a bs
though i was heated you all saw i got
real angry that was stupid
we did everything we tried it's real
rude to you rude game but seems like
it's fine
let us bury the hatchet as they do yes
hopefully uh i tested it quite a few
hours before the stream like constantly
and i tested it with
uh ina like being on the server as well
to like see if that's a problem or
something but everything's fine so
it better stay that way not jinxing it
no no no no no not at all
yep hey be fine we'll have
we are going to like go on the journey
but before we go into
the journey we we of course we gotta we
gotta
look back on our spa
day ah yes
yeah that was the thing that happened
actually my much well needed rest um
resting time uh for you for you and i uh
many things were going on and so it was
good to
lay back kick back relax get get a
massage and
feel chill kind of laid back vibes and
don't get the [\h__\h] chill chill kelly
chill it's all good you can just be open
about it okay
there's nothing wrong with what we did
there's nothing wrong it's just
we just had to have a relaxing day but
if you'd like to
have some context actually
uh around the time where we had our
debut
maybe i should turn on some bgm for this
part at least uh around the time where
we had our debut
uh i callie was already working like
crazy before the debut
so i noticed cali is like the type of
person
who is not very good at like one second
let me turn on the museum
yeah who is not very good at like giving
herself a break
wouldn't you agree with that oh
no i can't i can't say that you're wrong
that is true
that is a true fact yeah i i enjoy it
working is something that i
enjoy it's just yes i do take it to the
extreme sometimes
so then i thought i told we actually
made that promise i cried
a while back i i told kelly once we're
like one month in or so
we should go on a spa day together
i remember that yes i remember making
that promise yeah
yes i recall so finally
yes the day before yesterday we have
done it
we have i i um i wanted to take off
as much as stress as possible from
my dear kelly i wanted to her to chill
and completely relax
so i i booked i made it like a
whole day plan so i booked lunch
we had we had teppanyaki do you guys
know what te panyaki is stefan yaki is
like
like how would you explain temporary
there's like a huge uh
platform yeah it's like it's like a
thing
that you put the meat and the vegetables
on and they
they put it on fire for you it's a grill
kind of hmm
and the glue does it yeah it's a fancy
one i didn't know what it was until
until you introduced me to it actually
oh yeah that was your first tip on yaki
right
yes yes it was so i also know that cali
loves meat a lot and there was a
a choice between having like uh seafood
tapaniaki
and vague beef
[Music]
i actually have i have approved approved
by manager i have photos of our food
gallery
so let me put there was like a starter
like some veggies
[Music]
uh that was like he also grilled those
on the
on that big what you call that i don't
know is that a
grill a metal plate okay okay and you
gotta eat your vegetables everyone
vegetables are important unless you're
trying to meet me wink don't do that
it's not like i want to meet you guys
super early or anything eat your
vegetables eat them
yes yes what that was actually
there's like sweet potatoes i don't know
what the white thing was
but it was also good and then the the
thing in the front i don't know if you
see it
like but that was like some kind of tofu
thing right or what was that
yeah yeah that was tofu and i ate all of
it
and the thing that looks like
spaghetti sauce that was like some ankle
paste right like a red beans paste i
think
yeah it was great and i think it had
meat in there as well i eat it
it did i didn't i didn't eat the paste i
just ate the best i noticed that you
didn't eat it
i noticed that and i thought to myself
um
that was already a good a good start
so then then the most important part
happened like
in front of our eyes he started like
grilling
this really beautiful piece of meat
really a fat piece of meat
the thing in the back is salt by the way
rock
[Laughter]
and uh like actually i guess
in the end it wasn't really that much it
was kind of a small portion
right yeah i mean they can't give us
they can't give us too much right it's
so very expensive
but it was so good it was so
good and she cut it into little pieces
and then ah
i can't show that that photo but he
he made like a at the end he made like a
fancy huge firearm
you were excited about the fire i
remember that and you were very excited
it was i took some really good photos of
the fire but those were not manager
approved unfortunately
i wonder why too dangerous for
everyone's eyes maybe
but it looked really cool and got really
hot for a second
yeah that was really nice really fancy
effects and he did it several times
because there were some other people too
and every time that he would do it i was
like
fire it was very nasty it made me think
of you
it made me think of you and how you rise
up many different times oh thank you
a warm and familiar feeling indeed
yeah so i'm not surprised that you like
that part the marbling
in the meat looks indeed very beautiful
doesn't it let me let me
mark can i do a close-up let me make
that bigger for you so you can
see look at that high resolution
baby oh yes do you see that guys
this is so tasty looks beautiful it was
amazing
it melted in my mouth yeah
oh i want to eat that again so
then we ate that meat and then what was
that what for what came after that oh
yeah oh oh no no that secret that secret
that comes later
yeah you showed it you showed the tasty
burgers anyway so we ate that meat
and then we had uh we also had some
dessert
right yeah we did it was delicious it
was not unlike anything i'd ever tasted
before yeah it was like a
a tea ice cream tea flavored ice cream
but like roasted tea it was roasted tea
um i remember specifically
some lipsticks like roasted green tea
with some cereals
i think and some maple syrup or
something like that yeah it had some
syrup on it yeah
ice cream so that was lunch time
and then after we filled our cute little
bellies a little bit
we have we it was time for a massage
i booked uh i booked for us
the longest the bestest massage that
included also
a facial because if you want to be an
idol
you have to upkeep beautiful flawless
skin yeah right yeah which yeah
you already have to begin with yeah well
i only have it because i'm death
uh so and i got this body uh for free
and uh it was very nice
um it was they so whoever um my mama
she made sure that my skin was naturally
very beautiful yeah your skin is so
white though yeah actually she
the the massage the massage person
commented on my skin and said wow so
beautiful and i said really
i was very surprised and then after that
um they got they got some of the uh the
facial cream in my eyes
oh yeah we were very nervous about that
but i said it's okay
they might have been nervous because i'm
deaf uh but but
people get people have it they have it
twisted uh just because you do something
mean to me does not necessarily mean
that it is your time i obey i okay how
time works with people's lives
okay listen i love you that's very nice
of you
i mean did you tell her that you're a
reaper but on hiatus
i think that she could tell okay
somehow like they get scared when they
hear that you're a reaper right so
i hope they don't get scared off of you
because you're like a really nice person
i don't know i don't know about that i
don't know about that um true it's true
you can also you can be nice if you want
to
i also but because i obey the laws of of
who should die at their time it also
goes the other way and that
just because i like you doesn't mean
that i'm going to let you live when it's
your time
gotta be fair right exactly the true
neutral
is me i'm the true neutral so so we did
that facial
and uh that was like an hour and then we
did an hour
oil massage how was that for you kelly
did you ever have a
massage like that before um so when i
was
mostly uh in the underworld right um
i would get occasionally a massage with
hot stones
oh so
yeah those are quite popular in the
underworld but i actually hadn't gotten
anything quite like this before
and it was very nice because i haven't
had a massage in millennium
i actually was in the charges i go a lot
because i i have like quite some
problems
with my body because i've never been
like are we born so many times like
stuff goes wrong here and there
i almost i got so tired i almost fell
asleep
at the end i went out after the massage
it was like
i'm so [\h__\h] tired i'm like kelly
aren't you tired and kelly was like
what no not at all that didn't make it i
took a nap
that's because i took a nap during it oh
you did
let's take naps yeah so i took a nap
during the massage i can't even remember
most of it you fell asleep
yeah of course what yeah
it felt great when i got up i like when
i i don't wanna
no matter how relaxing a massage is i
don't wanna fall asleep because i wanna
be like
uh actually like experiencing how good
the massage is i wanna experience the
feeling of it
but the feeling of it made me feel so
happy that i went to sleep that's good
but wow
oh yeah actually it wasn't there there
was like they gave us a choice of
free aromas that we could put like under
uh like you know the hole where the
head goes in and the right places place
it there
and there were free choices which one
did you go for there was yuzu
and there was sakura and there was sand
sand what's it called sand
i think it was that one i didn't get the
the yuzu or sakura
oh we went for the same one yeah i think
so i also went for the sand
sands and sandalwood sandalwood oh yeah
sandalwood is that what it was
yeah it smelled lovely it did smell very
good
i find that i choose it though i think i
chose it for the effects that it had
oh that's why you took it yeah it was
like um
i i'm not sure totally i can't even
remember now really i think it had it
was to improve sleep
i think oh yeah yeah yeah there were a
few effects for that yeah
so now it smelled really good we had
that and under our nose the whole time
while we got the
the facial and the and the what the
excuse
just keep on what you ah you haven't
no this is fine because it says you have
been idle for too long okay
i bet it happens no problem no problem
okay
thank god thank god this was not the
other ever okay
okay i can see that that's okay that
makes sense
i've just been i've just been idle for
too long okay that's no problem
haven't we all got em
all right
after that massage we uh
wobbled out of the massage room both in
our back ropes
underneath pretty much naked
and we sat down in like a chill
relaxing room on some sofa
thingies how do you call them
hold on uh sofa thingies uh what do you
mean
wait where in the in the relaxing room
yeah yeah lounge chairs oh yeah oh yeah
yeah so we chilled there and we we dang
we drank some hot
tea and we were watching like a
beautiful
sunset yeah the sky went like rainbow
yeah it was it also started raining but
then it went away again
so that was okay but yeah we were we're
just
trying to wake up from that beautiful
massage and
looking at the sky looking at the clouds
move and
talking a little bit about how beautiful
this is and how nice
and how much cali deserves the [\h__\h] out
of it
anyway that was really really you
deserve it too i'm not the only one
that's been working hard hey
yeah give yourself some credit geez but
then we realized oh my god it was
already getting
dark so quickly so so i was like kelly
kelly kelly
we gotta change into our swimsuits now
and go to the pool
because that place had
also a pool and a hot tub and a sauna
and like a uh what's it called a
whirlpool
yeah a hot tub yeah so then we went to
the changing room
and um yeah and we changed clothes and
nothing else happened
yeah nothing happened nothing happened
no not
it's not actually like for real nothing
happened
because yeah i had i had the chance
to like when
i actually i got too embarrassed
she's watching her words very carefully
right now
no actually like even i was too
embarrassed to even like
like have you see me when i was in
dressing
and when you were in dressing i also was
i was like
god can't look no no i don't know why
you're so worried about those kinds of
things it's just a body
you don't so you don't mind if i see
your naked body
i mean if it's in the right context
right would you when you go to places
like onsen no one cares
right well because it's you hold on a
minute because it's you though i might
actually have a problem
if it's a bunch of random random other
ladies that's one thing
but if it's you
hey kelly come on
but like for example i i personally i
don't like going to onsen because i'm
too embarrassed that people see me
so naked and i'm too embarrassed to look
at other people being naked
so that makes me very you should well
you shouldn't worry about me seeing you
naked because the in the right
context i i don't care you see because
it is me
i don't care if i see you that way
you shouldn't worry then next time i
shall don't worry about it i shall show
you my full naked body next time fine do
it
okay do it empowered i dare you
okay okay oh yeah
so we got into our swimsuits callie was
wearing quite the cute swimsuit i was
quite surprised i thought you were gonna
come
out with something like more i don't
know
dark or something edgy dark colored like
sporty or something but you came out
with something pretty adorable
yeah i mean i guess that that is what
what people refer to as as the gap
i actually like white i like mm-hmm and
you wear
very light brilliant your bottoms wear
like in some in some pastel color
uh grand radiation yeah
and very yeah yeah yeah and very weird
feminine
yeah very cute i don't uh i don't like
sexy type swimsuits they're not for me
did you think my swimsuit was sexy yes i
liked yours it was very bright colored
like you
it was ganky and had much energy uh like
you like you do
it but would you call that sexy i don't
think
i don't know about sexy um i think it
was also cute
but it did it did dip down a little bit
so maybe it did dip down
down away what does this mean you know
you know like you have it was kind of
like a v a v shape
right um i guess so like i wasn't
looking i wasn't looking or anything i
just noticed
i just noticed that it was like that
listen
okie dokie that's all right
so we went we moved on we moved on we
went to the pool area
and uh we went straight for the outside
hot tub there was like a
a hot tub made out of stones like really
big not
probably not really can you really call
it a hot tub like when i imagine a hot
tub
i imagine these things that people have
in there in their garden
like a really small one but you call it
a hot tub
i don't know it was rather big it felt
just like a mini pool
but it was wine but it was very well
yeah and it was
yeah that was really really really nice
because we were still watching the
sunset
with this nice city skyline and and
there was like water as well there was
like a
some kind of uh uh
[Music]
cava yeah what's cavan
um what do you mean like the
the one yeah what about the water there
was that
there was that there was a
comma cover
yeah so he was staring at that and the
beautiful lights
and the the airplanes
yeah yeah and then and then when it got
dark all the
all the uh the lights the buildings uh
lit up
and um it was like there it was like
being surrounded by a starry sky except
it was buildings
yeah that was really nice and we kept on
talking about lots of stuff but we
cannot tell you because all these things
are
secret
wow that was really nice we had lots of
time to talk we went we
we were in there for like if you include
the lunch
we were together for like for like nine
hours or something
feels like nine hours maybe not nine
hours but it feels like it
so again after a while in the hot tub we
started feeling a little bit too hot so
we went back inside
and kelly chilled but i went for a swim
swim
yeah that's right i'm not a big fan of
um of public pools
it wasn't really quite like every other
uh pub public pool that
that you may think of when you first
hear about it but that wasn't really
public
it was mine but i just wanted to lay
back and watch
do you kelly can you swim
yes yes i can well i can dog paddle
dog paddle huh is that the is that
what you call the crawling one yeah so
you put you put both of your hands in
front of you and you just kind of
move on back and forth um to stay afloat
oh that's not swimming callie that's not
swimming
i mean i guess i consume but i've always
had problems with water getting into my
nose so it's just hard for me
i get that i understand that but
normally if you swim
correctly you shouldn't really get water
into your nose
oh then i get i guess i'm pretty bad
did you see me swimming i'm not that
good either but did you did you see me
a little bit i looked for a little bit
so i'm also not very good but
like can you swim as much as well as i
can
i don't know about that i don't know if
i'd go that far
not to drown okay listen that's all you
need that's all you need
i like water but i don't like really
being in water for too long
like that it was actually nice because
the water was also not too cold
but now since i did that after the
massage
now i have sore muscles again so i
should go straight back there again and
get another massage
what will happen to you
so yeah and then uh after a while we
chilled a little bit more
and then we went outside to the hot tub
again for a little bit more soaking
and then we both at the same time
started feeling like super hungry and
low-key sick
because it wasn't that the lunch wasn't
very much
yeah we were starved yeah so
we went to some like a burger restaurant
that was kind of like hawaii themed
right
right yes exactly yeah i am burgers
good and they played like all these
nostalgic like
uh english tunes that and we both
started like singing along them the
whole time
i was surprised that you knew them to be
honest i know that we both have existed
for eternity but i wasn't sure exactly
where you had heard them
uh those are like super mainstream all
over the world not only like
english-speaking countries yeah so i
love them
we kept singing together
and let me show you which burgers we got
oh
they were so good um but yes um
that's the guy you got the pineapple yes
i knew that you would choose that
but i i love pineapple on pizza and
burger but in the burger it makes it
like much
like you don't taste it as much as on a
pizza i would say
but it makes it more refreshing i really
like it it's really good
pineapple burger is awesome
[Music]
yeah i'm not surprised that you enjoyed
it the burgers were so big like i
it was so hard to eat yeah we were
hungry so i
i almost ate all of my almost
it was really good oh yeah cali
cali got a dessert after that i usually
i love desserts
but i can't eat that much at once but
cali got
pancakes after that i got pancakes i was
so
hungry they were great of course they
didn't finish them though
yeah but i i like to take a bite of of
everything and just kind of
it's so wasteful i need to fix it no
it's all right
i'm gonna worry about it i'll eat the
rest next time
okay promise yes
let's just share our food oh that was
that was really good oh but then
afterwards
we uh both parted our ways and went home
after a nice relaxing day and i was
i just hope that this kind of like
took away all the all the
stress from you at least for a day
well i mean it'll never erase all of it
but it was
a nice uh escape i would say and then
the following day i was able to sleep an
entire day
so yeah i actually also i had sleeping
issues
recently too but after that spa day
i i i fell asleep so quickly
oh that's good that was right sleep is
important
yeah all the
i really enjoyed that thank you for
going there with me kelly thank you for
joining me thanks
thanks for pushing me to do it i i know
i should do more things like that
we will do more we will do more yes
let's make it a regular thing yeah more
girls that
i would say i really enjoyed because i
don't i don't have many friends
here in in japan and
so it's good to have someone to like
just you know do
stuff like this together and talk to
each other right
yeah that's true i also don't have many
many friends in the underworld city that
i live in
so it's nice to hang out come up to the
surface and chill for a little bit yeah
yeah
yeah that was our spa day all the other
details
shall be
mine oh i can tell you one more one more
titty thing
we shared one one hair brush
you sure did yeah that whole situation
was interesting
we were like after the pool we took a
shower
and then we were air drying blow drying
our hair and we kept on taking turns
with one hair brushy
i would say this is basically as if we
shared a kiss
what nothing nothing nothing completely
different
that doesn't make any sense
all right now we're done with that talk
hello i'm here welcome
back in my house well looks like you did
some nice things with the place
congratulations yep i have like a
memorial here
and you're you're if you did you read
the sign above your bed
i didn't let me read it now i am
dreading it but i'll give it a look
where is it let's see calliope mori for
whenever she comes back
that's nice and look next to you there's
a chicken
oh so whenever you come back and you
sleep on the bed
you have a chicken next to you because
you don't like sleeping right next to me
but this is basically the same thing but
i hope you don't mind this
this chicken that's great can i get the
egg
uh you can't really i have lots of eggs
that i can give you but actually
actually i wanted to check something
could we sleep for one night quickly
sure what are you gonna do i wanted to
check
something like in your no funny business
did you spawn in your cave when you
logged in
no i spawned here oh did you notice
anything
in your cave area come with me
hold on they might be gone
oh you mean all the chickens yes
actually as a matter of fact i
i did notice them yesterday
prepare for the club that did not happen
i noticed the many chickens
where are they now did you kill them i
did
was they not supposed to well actually
that was a funny thing like
on halloween i i realized i had way too
many eggs
and my chicken farm was overflowing so
since it's halloween
and you didn't give me any any retreats
i thought okay then she will get tricks
so i spammed all my eggs on your on your
cave
and basically at your house but there is
some
some chicken's born by the way where
what is this
it's my pool oh spa time again
right now i can hold them whenever i
want except this is annoying me there's
this one
right here where the water will not go
ah you have to put more water there
but how minecraft is kind of weird you
need another bucket and then get water
from an endless source
and then pour it over there so that the
minecraft
people also don't get like problems with
their ocd or something because people
are very picky with that
for real though when i was building my
wheat farm i was like
making these these water uh uh
how do you call those like well whatever
i was making water
and then they were like hey you gotta
fill every single inch with one and me
even though it would already work why do
you listen
i didn't i ended up not really listening
so anyway callie here we go
we want to go on a one hour journey
where we find some new lands so let me
give you a stone sword
thank you i have more in case you need
more lighter you can have a stone
pickaxe
you can have a stone axe thanks and wait
do you have food i have lots of food for
you
oh actually let me give you
probably this would be better let me
give you some baked do you like baked
potatoes
i love baked potatoes you're awesome
right go take them
uh i don't have any spares but you could
make
can i make it tell me how i can make it
and i will make it uh i'll make no i'll
make you some
armor one second uh everybody does
things for me i wish i had played games
you need to play more minecraft you're
like you're living in the
hole but i guess i kind of i have more
time now from here on out but
too many other games i want to play
that's all right that's all right you
don't have to force yourself to play the
game
but i also want to be elite maybe i can
just be like a rogue
being just wandering the land with
nothing just using my hand to carve
things
i like that at least one of us is like a
total noob so it's not me it's you
that's awesome oh i can make you feel
good in that way then
okay callie up also take that bed take
your
take your bed okay you want me to take
it with me on this journey yes
we might have to sleep just a left click
a few times
oh yep okay okay
ready i think we are ready
i have absolutely no idea if there is
anything interesting close by
oh by the way look i built this while i
was uh
trying to test out if the game works
properly before the stream
it's not done yet but this is becoming
the kfb restaurant the first one in
minecraft
i built it right now it's nice you did
this right before this stream
yeah i started building it jeez
i couldn't wait anymore i didn't like
the the black foundation just being
being there and nothing else so i had to
start building
looking good old leaf yes
yes what are these cows whose cows are
these no that's your sheep my sheep my
sheep
oh my god yes you can't let them live
like that no this is
uh this is still fine i gave them more
space than they had before
but that's not a life no no no that's
the same thing i said when i saw
anna's farm you have to look at enos
farm enos farm is even worse than this
oh jeez dude oh man that's fine because
that's the exact same thing i said when
i saw you
yeah all right
okay damn it
sorry i couldn't get off the i couldn't
get out okay kelly
now i think we should try to mostly
go into one direction and not get too
much off course
so i have uh i have um
some methods so we don't get lost we
could either did you just kill a chicken
i mean yeah why not okay we could either
you could either um i was thinking to
build like
a huge not huge but somewhat big pillars
everywhere with cobblestone
and then make them so big that from
every certain distance you see one
pillar and you just follow the pillars
and eventually you end up being back
here
okay that's pretty easy to see or i
could use
torches but um i feel like
we could always get uh stones somewhere
so
okay well yeah i mean i have cobblestone
for days as they say so
we can just use both oh hello doggy
doggy you wolfie come here
you need a legion stuff to get him to be
your dog
oh yeah anyway
is there any direction you feel like
your heart says we gotta go there
hold on let me lick the finger
see where the wind blew
it blows
on um how about over that mountain where
the lava is
oh [\h__\h] okay uh
yeah that's gonna be fun your little kfc
and um the goal is to stream like
until half an hour before kelly's collab
stream so
right even let's go practice with the
ladies yeah even if we don't manage to
make it back
in time it's all right we'll just make a
little cave and we can
try to come back off stream or whatever
next time
so yeah we might get lost but that's
okay
we will always find back eventually
eventually yes okay the key word being
eventually
oh yeah kelly kelly kelly we both posted
our
schedules today we did and uh we both
playing yakuza tomorrow huh
we sure are both playing it tomorrow
hope you all look forward to it many
many people seem to be excited which
surprised me
oh [\h__\h] i [\h__\h] out my back i'll be right
back and steal my clothes if i got my
beds i forgot my bed
wait right here no problem
but your yakuza is like um it's in
jrpg but i have no idea what to expect
at all me neither it is also my first
but from what i've seen it looks very
fun and like my type of game so
oh i am excited i anticipate it
it's like really it's like really
popular and everyone keeps like
there's like this baka mitai meme from
it right
oh yes
something like that i'm getting a dmca
stricken
maybe cut that out afterward it's
getting clipped right now
didn't expect that to suddenly happen
i actually see that your voice quite
well
[Music]
yeah i was just playing around if you
haven't i'd want to swing it at a higher
key
if you ever do a karaoke stream you
gotta sing
[Music]
i can't sing that low that's really nice
i want to sing
be able to sing that low where are you
did you stay where you were
yup didn't move okay okay i
am back
i brought my yellow bed
oh we are kazuma curious here kfp
sim oh yeah that's right you heard
correctly
all right so do you want to go that
direction oh yes okay
let's go i should i should start by
already making some
i'm going to start with no okay i'm
going to make pillars first i'm going to
make pillows first
okay can i help um no
what you want me to do is this hang on
is this how you make them hang on
actually wait i'm
probably gonna wait i should make them
yeah but stop stop stop stop stop stop
stop stop stop stop stop stop wait why
should i stop because
if you jump down here it's better to
make it by the water so you can jump
down without taking damage
oh okay so it will i fall if i fall into
the water it won't hurt me
yep i see no makes sense now i got very
excited
so we're making that oh here's a good
spot
okay i'm making it
i want to make the next one okay
let me take a second okay oh
splash sorry if i got you well
go and jump down kelly i will catch you
[Music]
you didn't catch me the water did
imagination
oh it's getting dark we should uh
already like find
a spot to sleep it can't just be a
random spot because there's no enemies
out here anyway yet
oh the sun is going down the stars just
like on our spa date kelly
yeah well it does kind of remind me of
that huh nice
i think we're already going uh all right
let's just sleep here
here okay just drop the bed yeah all
right click right click
all right on the ground okay got it hang
on
did you already forget like all the
controls
yeah i don't know how to play video
games yeah when i don't when i don't
play minecraft for a week i also forget
everything
don't feel bad okay
let's keep on moving moving okay
we're probably gonna get lost oh well
it's all right we have the coordinates
from home we can always find it yeah
it should be fun
[Music]
that's raw meat free oils oh we can cook
it
i have like a [\h__\h] ton of chicken meats
at home
cali i have so much i don't doubt that
it's like too much like i'm overflowing
with meat
i don't like this there's too many trees
here
yeah there are quite a few huh all right
okay let's go whoopsie daisy hopefully
find something new
i want to find like uh uh there's like
these uh
big um witch houses i guess
i wonder if oh it's more like uh there's
witch houses but there's also like big
mansions and that's kind of what i want
to find
ooh a mansion yeah i want to find a
mansion that's got all kinds of treasure
in it yeah
then we can kill the mansion boss and
take the mansion yeah
pretty much oh i think no boss there's
just a lot of enemies in there
oh oh we're going alongside the water
huh
and i kind of stopped making pillows we
could make one here i mean it's probably
going to whiter in my turn
okay my turn will turn i'm gonna make it
i'm going to be useful
hold on leave cali alone although
aren't that your friends yeah i love
bats
a lot of them where i live doesn't have
to be
i mean that's a good height you could
make it even higher how many stones do
you have
an enderman under this under the sand
actually over there um i have
14 13 12 11 10 9 8. okay jump jump jump
five okay whoa the view is amazing
i can see everything i can see where the
world ends
but it probably doesn't end there kelly
if you don't think so
you know the world is round right uh
yeah
no i didn't know that this world was it
was
oh oh that was fun so you're not one of
those flat earthers
what is that people who think the earth
is flat
that's the thing people think that oh
yeah oh this is where i smell the energy
oh creeper skellington ashby
oh god hold on cali follow me
cali cali calico
you gotta follow me don't get lost
and get into danger okay
gotta be more careful i mean i guess it
doesn't really matter we're both eternal
so
no matter how many times we die who
cares very true fact
what is going on there that's small
piggies that looks interesting
oh please as if someone was here before
yeah that is a bit suspicious a little
suss am i right
sas very sus sus that is what they say
should we jump in the water uh i
actually i think i want to make a small
tower here just as a
another sign okay and then we jump
okay
[Music]
oh no it's all in the water hang on i'm
in the in the first spawn point where we
first spawned
hey it's a good thing that you made
those pillars right yep
but i didn't make them i didn't make the
path from the spawn points to our
village yet but i think i
i probably kind of know how to get there
could you pick up my items for now
yeah i'm i'm swimming through the water
gathering them now okay
that's right i totally forgot that when
you sleep somewhere else and then you
pick up the bed and then you die
then you automatically respawn at the
spawn point because you destroyed the
bed
god damn it so there's this village here
that i remember very well
maybe we need to figure out a new uh a
new strategy with the beds then
i mean we can't carry them with us right
no
i mean like that's just how it goes
that's just
i don't think there's much you can do
where i hope i'm going like
in the right direction oh my god come on
i'm where am i going where am i going
uh there's uh there's someone in the
chat
no the village coordinates
from our home hold on maybe press
f3 yeah but i want to know what you
might
want if you want huh your card oh yeah
that's an audio
i guess that's a good idea all right
let's see
let me find them okay x y z
first negative 154 100
100 x is 100 minus 154
yes x is minus okay wait a second minus
so god damn it
so that way that way okay leave the
other
coordinate for now
100 actually tell me that dude
tell me the last of that one okay
uh the why that's that oh the z okay
minus 501
[Music]
okay i think now i'm going in the right
direction
what do you think chad am i going in the
right direction now
by the way kiara apparently you reached
four hundred and forty four thousand
subs
which happens ah wow you're right
before the stream i was like oh i'm
getting close to cali's favorite number
it was meant to be wait that is wrong
that is wrong
but one second one second oh yeah four
four people
completely opposite so then i guess just
turn around and go the other way
no wait okay so what i say not on the
scene of a village
uh what was what was that again minus
yes minus 501.
uh yeah i think now now i should be
going in the right direction right chat
now it's right i think let's do your
best
now it should be right okay yes okay
just go
keep on going straight kiana just keep
on going straight
kelly do you also have some problems
with orientation or is it just me
i just don't i just don't use the xyz
coordinate stuff
i just take a long time to figure it out
and then that's how it is and get over
it
oh i see my restaurant well there you go
interesting that's progress why
but didn't wait didn't we move away from
the restaurant
okay i'll just follow those towers then
what the hell
good that i made the pillars very good
oh my ah
ah now it makes sense i have i have
found my
center of directions again wonderful
talia are you alive uh-huh just hear
slam pigs
actually thingies actually tomorrow
i'm um i'm gonna visit you
yup i am aware i'm you're going to
probably interrupt my yakuza stream
probably yeah i'll try to be as late as
possible so i don't interrupt too much
don't worry too much if you have to drop
in you have to ding dong or anything
it's fine
if i have to ding dong yes ding dong on
the doorbell
okay be careful by the way don't let any
demons feel like i don't even know where
you live right now
don't tell me i know yeah i know all
right i got it
i'll let you know later it's in the
underworld just be careful getting down
there it's a little
spooky it's been a while since i last
went to the underworld
yeah i didn't want to see it again that
soon like but
in that context of visiting you that's
all right
wait am i still going in the right
direction
[Music]
i haven't seen uh i haven't seen a tower
in a while
no pillars gone too far
i'm going oh am i going in the right
direction now
i wonder the piglets don't really like
me very much
because this is what i do to them before
they end up there
what are you doing killing figs
is this the right way sending them to
the nether
oh yeah i love bacon
go right five minus five oh
i went a bit too far uh
i hear i think here okay okay
sorry callie i'm almost there it's okay
but i think um i was a good example to
how you're not supposed to do it i mean
i did try
i almost fell into the water but there
was a tree i landed on a tree cave
need cave oh i see my tower where i fell
down
i think that'll go or is that the one
where i still survived
might be that one because we did make
several yep that's why the sun's going
to all the sunset's beautiful here
i don't have anything to protect myself
kelly you better not die
because if you die then all the items
are gone
that's a true fact okay
what was that what was x again hold on
let me check
i have to leave the bed hang on uh x is
uh now it's negative one six six
negative one six
oh okay with with that i'm there
but with x negative 166 but i'm not i'm
going the wrong way
go toward the sunset yes yes
i will find you at the sunset
at the end of the sunset isn't that
poetic isn't that beautiful
sure i would say so i'm taking a little
nap
though
[Music]
it's getting darker kelly i'm scared
where's my tongue
oh that's right you don't have a bed huh
yeah uh oh hurry up
it's right i'm almost there i'm almost
there where where are you where are you
hold on minus 100 something right
66 166 i'll put your bed down for you
okay so you can crash land into it hold
on
log out oh smart
i guess i guess that's smart but i'm
almost there
so put down your bed next to mine okay
thank you i mean it's it's decently far
away but you know wait where am i right
now
am i going the right direction still out
here
[Music]
me trying to find you oh huh
this is fine we still got some time i
don't see anything
okay they're telling me to log out
because then the night will pass
okay one second
oh that skeleton's on fire and there's
some spiders too is it all ready today
now
uh-huh okay picking up my bed finding
cali
no problems i'll be waiting here for you
[Music]
ah it's taking its damn sweet time right
now
it's okay let me see what i can see
around here let me
in i'm here with a crossbow cool island
i kind of want to go over to it
let me in
let's try again sometimes it works
better the second time
yeah god damn it minecraft
why won't you cooperate with me oh here
we go here we go
there you are okay so minus
minus 100 something
no so many trees oh my god hello pig
kelly i'm waiting yeah i don't like all
these trees
i'm not the biggest fan either but um my
last name is forest
so oh yeah right that's true oh yeah
yeah yeah
don't be too insulting please
okay i'm sorry i love trees i love trees
very very much you don't have to take it
that far you just need to not dislike
them
trees are my favorite thing and i think
this just seemed like yeah
it doesn't need to be it's all of my
tower
and i found probably you didn't i
where are you wait a second what is that
not the tower
is that the other that's another tower
goddamn wait a second then up here it
should be
you know i thought i just found the
tower that we made at on the sand
now the one that you made i think so you
must be getting closer
yes i'm almost there
i'm almost there i'm almost there wait
for me kelly i found it
yay are you down there
huh are you like here hang on are you in
the vlog
hold on no so i'm not in the water you
see me
okay now i don't jump in the water
because i'm just okay oh please please
don't fall
oh god just just be careful as you come
down okay
it's very difficult here to not fall
i think i have to jump into the water it
should be fine
please
damn it chiara
um
i have another idea
because um uh we don't have some
oh cali
huh it happened it happened again
[Music]
just try again maybe it's fine
all right welcome back i have a bad
feeling
no no bad feelings just just just make
your way over to me
do you want me to leave and come back
and then well i have all your stuff but
i wonder if i would spawn do you want to
come back to the
to the village because i have an idea
yeah
i don't think this is gonna work hang on
it's happening again
i have all your stuff why let's see
again
why it was working literally all day
what is your download speed
limit check oh darn it i spawned
i spawned in the same place i left at
okay wait what
what do you mean a spawn did you kill
yourself no
no if i do that i lose all your items
yeah
i'm not going to lose all your items oh
yeah oh yeah
downloads please
uh download f word off and get some new
stuff
but i literally just got it i know but
they suck
i'm on my way back are you not able to
enter the game at all
ah nah uh probably yeah but uh
probably just gonna you wanna play the
ghost game instead well we only have 30
minutes so i mean it's
i guess it's also finally stopped
minecraft at this point
okay that's fine too
um but one second let me see again if
it's gonna kick me out again probably
yeah but let's
i'll just hope for the best come on
minecraft come on we probably could
have time for one ghost game if you
wanted to play okay now it's not
happening
and i'll hold on to your things until
later
thank you uh if you could put them uh
in i guess you probably need some time
to go back but okay just
keep them for now okay yeah we'll figure
it out later
um
would you like to or do you want to just
talk instead because we can certainly do
that
uh yeah i think i could also just talk
because i'm not sure how to set up the
whole fast model thing because last time
good i did it so i think i need some
time if i want to figure it out
okay that's fine okay
well minecraft you disappoint me once
again
uh you really need to thanks for nothing
if you need me to talk to him i'll talk
talk to him into them yeah if i talk
some sense into them i mean i will beat
the [\h__\h] out of them
[\h__\h] rude sorry f wording sorry
excuse me oh children watching
f wording rude but i'm starting to think
that it's not minecraft i'm starting to
think that it's the internet demons and
i won't come and fight
but you know that this never happened
before the update
[Music]
very strange i just started happening
once i had
the the minecraft update but oh well it
doesn't matter
i'm sorry was this but at least we at
least it worked for an hour
uh during stream at least not
that makes it difficult because in the
future if we ever want to do like
minecraft collabs even on my
even on my end right uh that's a
difficult situation we will find a
solution
eventually we need to play other games
i heard though that um you could we
could
possibly move our ramps server to like a
proper server and then it works better
but i don't know i'm fine with that i've
established nothing in this game
but the others might be a little
hesitant
that's true yeah you don't have much to
lose but i i think
some people said that you can like
transfer the whole world over there but
i don't know if that's true
i don't know that's interesting i think
a way out looks like a fun game that we
could play i know that amelia and gouda
played that game together i wonder if
that would be interesting
if it's specifically meant to be a
two-player game
you could do that if it's with you
i i will play anything i think that
could be funny
maybe let's do that let's organize that
as a collaboration a lot a lot of chad
is saying yes do it yes do it
so uh all right oh they're getting
excited they love that game huh
yeah they really seem to like it but
tomorrow is like basically
pretty much like a collab which is we're
playing the same game on the same day
just different times like a few hours
apart
true true indeed you can talk about it
later
oh yeah looking forward to to yakuza
do you have some i feel like i feel like
cali you would get very well along with
those peeps i think so too i think that
we would be friends
yeah i also really love i love mafia
movies i know it's a little bit
different
oh mafia i love the whole world yeah i
never watched the mafia movie before
yeah i reck we should we can watch them
together some do you have a favorite
i've never heard of
oh what what is that
it's a japanese muffin movie oh that's
your favorite one
not my favorite but i like it what's
we have to be good fellas have you ever
heard of that no
i don't know any maybe yeah you can
introduce me to your favorite
mafia movie weekend
is good but everyone talks about
godfather and scarface so i've never
heard of any of that
godfather says nothing to me i'll
educate you don't worry about it
it's cool you'll educate me
sure why not i want to know i can help
you thank you
[Laughter]
sounds good sounds good to me we'll plan
on it
i have some i have a little more time
these days everyone
oh yeah i'm holding on to it for as long
as i can
yeah it's relaxing i mean it doesn't
really count as real work when you're
relaxing and having fun with everyone
right i mean it's work
but it's not like not like other work
that i do you know reaper job stuff
right
it's different we put jobs but i thought
you were in hiatus
i am but that doesn't mean that your
reaper duties just stop even if you're
on hiatus from killing
damn that's totally whatever job you
gotta do damn you never get a break from
dad huh
nope never ends yup
just keeps on going and going and going
really
oh netflix and chill good idea callie do
you know what netflix and chill is
i have heard of it before i am aware
it's literally
just what it says in the word it's just
netflix and jill
yeah you you watch you watch the the um
the
the tv programs or the movies together
and and you chill
so to speak yes i am i'm aware i know
how it works except i don't get a chance
to do it but i am aware of how it works
i
i i know i know let's do it sometime
i'm educated man listen okay
okay i'll do it i have some time now
let's do it let's do it oh okay yeah
okay we could even do it tomorrow oh
too bad i have to after i visit you i
have to go
back home and play yakuza too
you gotta say hey yara you got work to
do go
good excuse for me to you know okay for
my house next year you can't stay there
for too long no one can stay there for
too long
i'm excited to see you please
as i heard you where you were uh
unpacking a lot of stuff today
yes actually that is that is what i was
doing uh before this stream
and before the following stream uh i
made sure to get a lot of my unpacking
done
because i actually hadn't gotten it done
uh before i finished my recent freelance
work
um i had many boxes many boxes
in my home and now they're finally i i
focused on clothing today
and also in the kitchen so i can start
cooking again because i have a real
kitchen now
so you can cook oh i want to cook for
you in that kitchen
because i kind of have a cooking party i
promised you to make french toast for
you
do you actually are you do you fancy
yourself a cook no good
not at all me neither me neither so we
both kind of suck so this will be
this won't be like an enlightening
experience where one of us is the
amazing chef and teaches the other
the other one how to cook we just kind
of suck so it'll be a nightmare yeah i
mean there's a few specific things that
i can do well
like french toast or pancakes
or i can i can do some fried food and i
can do pasta
i can make curry and rice oh me tell
our special our specialties why don't we
have a cooking party sometime
hell yeah sounds good sounds good
make some nice food and then i'll
serve some that nice sushi on
a special plate called kiara
what you can eat it
off yeah never mind making it weird
i'm making it weird you like sushi
um yeah i like sashimi
[Music]
yeah i gotta be honest not the biggest
fan of sushi really
um that's so but i like it i can kind of
believe it i love ramen though
oh ramen's the best
[Music]
but can you slurp around forever can you
slurp ramen noodles can you slurp them
i mean i can if i try i didn't know that
that's something that i should try to do
that's the normal way to eat wrap i
can't do it by the way
i can't i can't slurp it but you're
supposed to slurp it because then
apparently it's easier to eat it
oh yeah i didn't know what kind of ramen
do you like
i like tonkotsu
oh yes oh yes with that with corn in it
[Music]
i wish i knew how to make ramen my own i
mean i kind of tried before
with some ingredients from the
supermarket but it's just better when
you go to a ramen restaurant
well yeah because the i mean at the
ramen restaurant sometimes they they
train for years and years and years and
it's like an
art form to them right much like killing
is to me they really put their all into
it so
it's it's not quite it's not quite as
good as it could be
right if you're just doing it on your
own you know free ball in it exactly
exactly oh we got to go on the ramen
date
okay i'm fine with that not a date robin
party party between two
people you know kelly
a party between two people is a date
what it's nothing bad about it
uh i don't know what that i don't know
how that stuff even
works well yeah do you have to really
have those kinds of intentions
i mean if it's between friends then it's
not a date right
i mean it can be a friendly date
a date with between friends it's not not
that's not a weird thing
i guess
kelly
come on a little bit to my side
oh come on oh come on
you always make it weird i wanna
i wanna
what are you trying to do why why are
you making those noises
what are you doing i'm snuggling
no why do you do things like this
because you're cozy
what does that mean how is how how can
someone be cozy
explain to me your flowers
you're soft cali you're so shocked what
is
what though everything about
your hair totally not
did nothing yeah only your hair totally
only your hair
well i do use some very premium quality
shampoo and conditioner
no i use gravy that's
that's just kind of weird man that is
actually like really smart because then
you can wash your hair and at the same
time
you can like like drink
it that's what that smell was i was
wondering why did it smell like um
like a turkey dinner do you want to
smell on my hair try and try it
come on i'm good really i i'm gonna pet
i mean i can smell it from here so i
really don't mean
i don't need to do that
jeez
oh come on man look okay that's just
putting your head on
the putting your head on my shoulder
fine
it's just a greeting
is it yeah huh really
in many countries over the world giving
someone a kiss
on the cheek is just greeting
oh yep especially where i come from
we give each other kisses on the cheek
on the right side and on the left side
sometimes even double
right side left or right left head like
that well i mean i've heard of that
before but
i i don't know i feel like if it's you
your intentions are a bit questionable
no that's not true there's nothing
i don't have any wrong intentions it's
just a politeness
i'm just being polite
would you like to would you like to
try out uh this foreign greeting
i'm i'm good i'm just gonna stick to my
usual underworldian coldness thank you
very much okay
okay i respect i respect your ways
thanks fine
i can respect them casually thank you
they are the kfp
ways
fine are you looking forward to
being suspicious and among us i really
want to finally fulfill my destiny
yeah rape some people yeah
exactly but do it smart be stealthy
use the vents oh wait how do you do that
oh yeah see you probably
um you you you probably don't really
know much
about being a reaper in that game yet
huh that's right i haven't done it a
single time
don't do it like me and kill uh a body
in front of
everyone who try to actually do that
and not not really on babies i killed
someone but then
the room was empty but right after i
killed that one second later
the whole crew came into that room
but in that room there was events so
what i should have done and what you
could learn out of this situation is
after you killed that person in that
room use the vent
and then go somewhere else try not to be
noticed but the thing is i haven't even
used the vents before but i've done
quite well
later on with my remember that then yeah
it's kinda you should if you're gonna
practice anyway you should try those
events i hope you get
i hope you get to be reaper i hope so
too
i really want to fulfill my destiny i
feel like i might actually be good at
the game if i do that
yes oh yeah and you and uh
i think you and if you vitan you might
have to like translate because i'm not
there
i'll have to flex my casual japanese
skills that are very rudimentary but at
least people will be able to understand
some words
i think your japanese is very good
i thought it was so cute you were like
telling me that you were doing like
flashcards
i am i'm doing japanese flashcards i
want to speak japanese very well for
everyone who supports me
in japan i want to learn from you it's
really like
uh i still don't know the word in
english but that's very ed
yeah i know what i means but i don't
really know quite a good translation an
admirable kind of but
it's it's not quite admirable it's like
in between admirable and like oh you're
doing like a good thing like that's good
of you to do kind of thing it's it's
hard to um noble yeah maybe and i
because i'm generally way too lazy to
actually study
actively when i learned japanese i
didn't
i didn't study at all
you said that and that actually gave me
some hope actually when you said that i
realized
wow um kiara hasn't studied japanese at
all but somehow
she is fluent so if i try then maybe i
can be fluent
soon as well yes you just have to talk a
lot anything
keep on talking
okay i will you can do it come back
i'll try um
it's important it's important so i want
to make sure that it works out that i
fully learn japanese
i'm trying to be careful to not use
yonah too much
i think it's so cute how you say that
though
like when like when when i'm
in the onsen with cali
you haven't gone to the onsen yet yeah
but in the future in the
future you said you don't like those
kinds of places
yeah it's also so hot like the water is
so hot
yeah well i mean they also have um but
they also have pools that have
cool uh or cold water as well so what i
like to do is i like to jump into the
super hot
then jump into the super cold and java
is super hot super cool
you're hot super cold super hot super
cold and then sometimes they have like a
cool uh
like a cave that you can go into that's
full of hot water and then you jump in
the cold water
oh i love monsoon and then and then you
just lay you just lay
naked in the wind and you let the wind
go over your body and if it's snowing
you let the snow fall on you and then
you get into the hot water that sounds
very exciting you you're like getting
really excited about that damn
i love the onsen onsen daisuke
cali and kiara onsen episode coming soon
question mark well only if you want to
i know that you can't get over the
nakedness factor which is fine if
there's like
if there's maybe if there's less people
because the last time i went to an onsen
there was like so many people it was
like really packed
um but if it's like less packed i think
i
i can't get over it i guess
all right you just have to have your
mind not in the gutter because
if you walk into the onsen with your
mind in the gutter then you're doomed
from the start
oh yeah that's not it that's
you i don't
[Music]
i was just really nervous about like
like them looking at me because they
were looking at me and i also didn't
know where to look at because i was like
if they if they notice that i look at
them because there's nowhere else to
look
because there's so many people then they
might think i'm rude or something for
looking at them
okay kiara listen here's have you ever
heard a saying that says
um it's kind of like it's not awkward
unless you think it's awkward yeah
yeah with my existence it's it's the
same thing in terms of this
it's not lewd unless you think it's lewd
and no one thinks that it's lewd except
for you
right so you're making it loot if you
think of it no no i'm not thinking
it's slow it's more like i'm embarrassed
about my body
well that's understandable too but you
just have to realize that no one cares
when they're
looking at you there you know because
everyone is on this because if they
if they cared then they would be
embarrassed too and they wouldn't be
there
um yeah it's just hard to get that
that way of thinking out of my head
difficult because it's not normal like
where i'm from
we don't have this culture of going into
a big bathroom naked with
well we certainly don't in the
underworld either
it just depends on your personality i
suppose not not everything is going to
be comfortable for everyone right
but if you'd like to enjoy an onsen
there are also ones that allow you to
wear bathing suits
oh yeah i saw that that would be much
more comfortable for me
yeah well there you go i did see that i
wanted to go to one of those this year
but
didn't happen didn't happen
well maybe eventually um you should go
someplace snowy
yes yes snowy places
with an outdoor onsen oh yeah that
sounds
relaxing
sounds good but i wonder when it will
snow in japan
it's kind of um probably probably not
pretty soon
do you think so sure i mean it's been
getting cold hasn't it right
occasionally when i go up and i i i
stick my my hand out to feel the
overworld temperature
you do that it's a bit nippy you go out
and stick out your hand to feel the
temperature
oh sure why not it's fun to take a walk
when it's cold
yeah yeah you stick your big toe into
the into the bathtub to see how hot the
water is
sometimes i stick my my little finger
out into the
overworld to see what it's like outside
decide whether i want to take a walk or
not
cute scare some humans you know
what did you scare some humans on
halloween
maybe a little bit i mean i can't help
myself really you know well
they're they're all chilling in the
graveyards and trying to do their their
you know
silly little silly little high school
teenager games right i gotta come mess
with them just a little bit oh yes
it's fun be respectful don't do those
games on the graveyard what the hell
that's right
it's rude excellent
[Laughter]
show them show them who the boss is
yeah that's right get out of that swing
and do a swoosh swoop swing swing swing
switch
i'll come out and start swinging with my
side of course i can't actually i can't
actually really mess with them
like really i didn't like to take their
lives because that sensei would be angry
oh yeah
just like be like could you please leave
yeah could you please leave me
please go home children you're like 13
14 go home
give them a good bunk give them a little
i'll i'll i'll come at them with the
scythe
get ready to swipe at them and then i'll
i'll do a little 360
right with with the site and then i'll
bonk them on the head with the with the
dull side
360.
it's trying to make me think you're
athletic or something
i mean i am oh really oh really people
to kill them well i'm looking forward to
your free dw then when you're going to
show me your athletic
skills callie larry you'll see i'm going
to break dance
oh okay okay write that down everyone in
her freaking baby she's going to pretend
should i get a breakdance
we'll figure something out we'll figure
something out
i'm looking forward to okay and you know
what since you're gonna break dance
i'm also gonna give you a special dance
then
oh i'll show you my dance skills as well
okey-dokey dance battle
let's do a dance battle
okay i'll do a dance battle with you
hell yeah hell yeah
that sounds like fun i'm looking forward
to that one day one day a challenge
in 3d we shall do we shall do a dance
battle
all right i think i'll let you go to do
your practice now
yeah i gotta go head out meet up with
the homies and uh get ready to
definitely
definitely be the imposter at least once
i'll be watching you
callie one time just one time let me
slice something up
i'll be in the chat and help you out if
you need some help
ah deadbeats cheer for me and share it
loud
monkey i'll do my best
you can do it i believe in you just
don't be suspicious
that's the one thing and don't get
caught
don't get caught when you kill someone
oh i never do
sounds very cool
[Laughter]
just made the crowd that's for sure all
right sounds good well i'm gonna go
ahead and
head out oh oh the collab in german we
say
at the end is thank you no
we say i'll dance thank you
of zane yes
thanks for watching everyone sorry it
got kind of uh
cut short again but yeah
alright later guys bye bye bye see ya
[Music]
you