foreign
[Music]
thank you
faith
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
assistant
[Music]
foreign
wow
whoa
whoa whoa sogoy
new layout let's go okay
oh my god I've been using the old ones
since
bazillion years
I've been using that forever
yeah this one's kind of like generally
darker
and maybe more
um relaxing to the eyes also
it takes up less space like uh compare
this
whoa
it takes up way less space I mean the
chat part takes up a bit
but yeah besides that wow
yeah more gaming screen so I'm thinking
normally I play tltk with um
you know no layout but I want to show
off this new one because it's pretty so
I mean I don't know if I um
we'll see how it looks like because the
chat box might cover up
uh some like I don't know
layout uh from the game or so but yeah
this was basically given to me for free
uh for I guess my birthday
from Fayette
[Music]
f-e-y-a underscore
Kun
who also speaks German I think
amazing yeah it has nice you know my
nice colors um the other one was more
focused on turquoise and this one's more
focused on the Reds and the Blues
[Music]
I especially like how the how the
hashtags are like burnt into the chat
box so yes it looks nice
um it's a little chicken and I I like
the colors you know it's a nice change
right
yeah okay
so we're gonna be using that I'm sorry
for being late I've been up to some
things wait
let's go behind
I've been up to some things
[Music]
what
like here
eh
oh it's because on the left side it's
higher than you know on the right side
that could maybe be should maybe be
changed I might request that
to have the left side you know next to a
chat box the left side
uh as low as the right side I don't
think anything will be lost by doing
that
um but besides that now it should be
fitting
um
[Music]
now let's see how it looks like in game
oh
see
oh oh space for the game logo true
that's what that might be
[Music]
um
that's okay that's the only problem I
see with it double audio
because like it being different sizes
might be kind of weird for games where
it's important to see everything
you'll hear double audio are you sure
oh yeah you you do you do
oh
it's been a long time no recap now we're
doing recap although I don't know if I
remember what I did
it's been a long time
this weekend we're gonna we're gonna
finish
the game I think
I mean I could still drag it out longer
and longer but people told me I can
finish it and I feel like yeah for the
sake of my channel
you know we should move on maybe
um
okay what do you guys think
should we play like this today or should
we say sorry new layout and play in full
screen
oh yeah we can do the laurelin village
Quest so I kind of like started
something there to be honest
uh This Land Is Fun new layout full
screen don't mind
I like the new layout yeah I mean you
know I like it too I'll be using it but
the question is do we use it for Zelda
today
oh no blood moon
you can full screen tomorrow for the
finale or maybe I will okay it looks so
nice nice
it's nice to have something fresh
I think normally I would like apparently
put the like the time
the time maybe my time
up there on the top right we'll see how
the colors match
link
oh wait no she's gone now
no more all right let me skip it
uh yeah but for now I'm covering that up
because I mean it's so tiny you don't
even see what's going on but uh
I want I want to advertise
is it bigger here
no
it is so tiny
oh well put in the bottom left no it's
even smaller there
you could put it where I am
no no no
um okay let's see
I took a lot of accidental screenshots
so
a lot of them don't mean anything
uh
I've been playing I think only in the
airplane
like once
so I didn't do
a crazy amount of things
where did I even
I remember telling you guys about this
did I tell you about this horse
I think so oh yeah yeah I think I told
you about this and this yeah that was so
pretty and I told you about that and
that
I told you about
did I tell you about this I think so
a gold ruby yeah
uh accidental
this may be new
uh
um maybe
wow that is quite a screenshot
no we did that on on stream
yeah okay maybe I'm from here okay
okay this screenshot looks accidental
but there is a reason to it
um because I I got this boat recipe
right and I was just like exploring on
the right side of the map and I found
out that if you use this boat you can
grill fish like kill them on your way
and then just pick them up and yeah
it's like a fishing boat
s
yeah it's the defender boat
yeah and I went to some
I went to this island
um
which is where there's this quest with
like three enemy camps yeah
and then there's a after you after you
clear the free enemy camps you have to
go to the back of the island like
there's a little cave where the the
pirate ship goes inside and you have to
yeah
kill all of them too and then there's a
shrine that's what I did yeah
oh I got this as a reward blue main
Lionel saber horn let's go
[Music]
and then
uh I went into a chasm
Colosseum
and this one was easy but you get
Madness helmet which is so cool
foreign
princess
it's somewhere at the corner I think
around bottom right of the map
um then I walked around a bit more to
see if there's anything else there but
there really wasn't
it's kind of cut off too you know you
have to I think you have to enter from
that chasm
um then I oh yeah I guess the Chatham
was on the island yeah yeah and then uh
um I I did this little quest which was
too easy first try right in the middle
um and then oh yeah then I tried to fly
as far as I could
um to the other side because I think I
was going for the for activating the
the tower
um
and then I did a shrine on the way I
don't know why I took the screenshot
I think it's just accidental all of
these are accidental
I don't know something with my fingers
on that day
here oh I got a lot of fairies here
and oh
I think this is accidental too
I just went up to one of those islands
that's I think accidental too but you
see that I got a cool Bowl
[Laughter]
I got a new heart I was upgrading a [\h__\h]
ton of armor I think until they told me
they can't do it no more I need to find
another fairy who can upload upgrade
even more and another accidental
screenshot yeah it looks like I didn't
do that much I guess
no well as I said I really just played
on the uh airplane a little bit
the line don't know that was for free I
didn't hunt it
uh where am I right now oh yeah cause I
was checking I was visiting all the
fairies to see
if they can upgrade my stuff but I guess
I really need to find like one more
oh and I did end up um getting the
the
[Music]
Tower
no I didn't do the Lino Coliseum no no
no no no no I did I think it was
um
what are they called the lanky ones
oh
it doesn't say right it just says lone
Island Coliseum that's the one I did
oh
so cut off
ah
was it a [\h__\h] it might have been
horrible ones yeah
you and your girlfriend love me thank
you I love you too
that's an island in the sky above oh
what is that looks interesting how do
you get up there
how do you get up there is there like
pieces falling down
yes
oh great
ah great good to know
is that the the the apparently there's a
king glioc is that the one
steak
you have to get a hover bike to get up
there oh
yeah no I have it on my thumbnail
um
that's the I don't know if we're gonna
get that one that's supposedly the most
the strongest one right I feel like we
should start with the linels and maybe
we should start by just finding one
normal one
but at least you can save in between the
liners right in the Colosseum
no no no we have to make a plan we have
to make a plan okay
um
we don't immediately jump into lionels
and gliox okay
we I think uh first we do a couple of
shrines okay that I haven't done yet to
get some more hearts
at least two more Hearts which means
eight more shrines depending on how many
I have now
uh
foreign
like this one
so six more if I want two hearts
[Music]
um
yeah it's a plan I'm making a plan Tony
is
yo I got so many bananas on this island
it's crazy
well and I mean where are those friends
it looks like we barely got any shrines
in the Garuda desert maybe I should look
in the Gerudo desert
or we go in this area because this is
the only one I haven't found yet that's
actually maybe a good idea
I should do that
yeah and then maybe also Gerudo desert
um
oh wait this Shrine did I actually
finish this shrine
does it say on the map because I have a
feeling that I maybe didn't finish the
shrine
is there an indicator
on the map that I finished it
it's finished I'll close the blue okay
okay I had a feeling that maybe I didn't
finish it
where is the Tower
no idea
where's the tower
let's go up this mountain and maybe we
can see it
to the south in the mountains South
mountains maybe like here
oh
okay let's go
ah the sucking noise I feel like that's
something
that maybe I got
from Japanese people from like
being around them a lot
because they do that when they're
nervous
nervous or when something's like not
going well or when you're like oh [\h__\h]
I'll be a bit
do you guys not do that
Japan yeah yeah chill chill we have like
eight hours
I'm probably gonna stream eight hours
oh see look at my upgrades these are at
like 22 now apparently
wait where are the left eh wait it's
only one oh never mind it's not that one
this one is on free these ones are on
free that's set and then I did a couple
others but
um
this is so cool
so cool
yeah you get too many outfits though and
this game is confusing
climbing climbing climbing
I don't think you do it
wait who does it who do you do it do you
do you do you say make the same noise
yay
yeah based on easy to upgrade that's
what yeah why I've been upgrading that
one the most
because you know some of them like the
fire one I'm like
that one's so specific why should I
upgrade sometimes extremely rarely
um
there's like a
something there
but this stream you know I'm I'm very
ready to do a long stream
I had like a sandwich
it's one of the fattest libertas I've
ever had before because she just cut
that
huge ass slice
I didn't want such a huge [\h__\h] slice
wait should I go that way
yeah here in the supermarkets you can
get a libacca stand semi which is liver
cast it's like kind of like a
kind of like a sausage
um
but cut like a cold cut but it's warm
and like really thick
usually salmon is a very Austrian word
for bread
specific type of bread German
austrians say semi [\h__\h]
sounds like spam no no we do not blend
it
you crazy person
it's not just the bread roll a Kaizo
yeah yeah Kaiser because Samuel is just
yeah a short way to say
um
yeah yeah and I usually get it I used to
always get it with guacal
um pickles but
um different pickles than the one you
have in burgers
what do you want
nanny nanny you're scared now huh what's
gonna get cold
um but yeah recently I like to eat it
with Peppa Peppa honey but not the spicy
ones they're not spicy
spicy
[Music]
similar to Bologna
want to say so should we take this piece
go up really high
it's been a while since I played the
game
I hope I can impress
hey what the [\h__\h] is that
oh there's a chasm
I still don't see a tower
I think Leo fell and a big sword wow
what was that
should I check it out I want to see the
tower first
there's like a parrot wait is that what
is that
have I been there before
what gliok is this anyway he's he's
sitting
baby ice ice
I mean they all eventually will fly up
right
I'm I'm just gonna count on
um Arrows with eyes
he he chose a really fancy place with
that sword
is he gonna notice me
see you later
hi bye bye don't fight me
back thank you but where's the
uh
where is the the tower
ah he doesn't even what's AIM dokle
oh he's taking off
pass the clinic to the South
so maybe like here
I really can't see it but I see a shrine
oh my god there it is
[Music]
I bought new pc stuff do you wanna know
what I got for my PC it cost me 1 600
Euro yay
you want to know some more details about
it
let me tell you
I'm I don't really you know I got advice
about what to buy
um
so you know RBF and BFF were visiting me
um and we also went
out a little bit to go swimming
but let me see let me see so
um I am getting
uh RTX 4080 16 GB
because it's white it's white I got a
white one OC Nvidia
gddr6x yeah 4080 baby
um we weren't considering
um
I think it was what was it 7900 XTX or
something like that we were considering
it but then
um RBF watched some videos and came to
the conclusion that for streamers the
4080 is better
um
oh first move on we're gonna we were
gonna take the 7900 but now we're going
with this one yeah and then also we're
adding
um what is this
Samsung and set
three seven S one t o b w SSD
970 Evo plus one terabyte
we're adding a terabyte because I my
space is full
and we're adding a Memoria g-skill
ddr4
3232 GB c16 is K2 2x 16 GB I think this
is Ram I think this is RAM
I downloaded some more RAM and a new
um net style I don't know what it is in
English be quiet pure power 12 M 850 B
and 344.
power supply exactly
yeah so in total that's like a thousand
six hundred Euro
yeah so we're upgrading RAM and uh disk
space and the power supply and the
graphic
board card thingy but the rest he said
the rest looks fine and he thinks that
the graphic card should
fit into my PC
it should fit if it doesn't work just
gonna buy a new one too but he thinks it
will fit what was the memory uh uh
Memorial
G scale ddr4
232 GB
c16 I8 keys
no no if I order Kelly's PC case it's
gonna take a million years probably to
arrive and who knows if they even ship
to Austria
and I I want the white PC case unless
it's kiwawa on there and it's like fancy
and red unless that then I want a white
PC case
yeah 32 Ram
we're going for the good stuff I think
[Music]
I think everything will arrive next week
middle of next week and then we'll try
to put it together
and see if it fits
and
um then we can use
[Applause]
finally I got that done and we tried to
fix my printer but my printer is
apparently a lost cause
yeah
like my my best friend she was just
lying on my bean bag and watching
and my uh and her yeah my RBF her
boyfriend
um
oh
oh test that the printer tried to open
it and all that but it just did not want
to work
yeah
the rental boyfriend
there we go
cheaper to buy a new printer yeah
it's ridiculous I didn't have the
printer for that long but you know the
problem is it like
interesting Garuda attaching material
greatly enhance the materials power
doesn't add as much durability
[Music]
um what was I gonna say
um
the the printer basically my problem
I tried to print something and then like
the paper doesn't get stuck
the paper doesn't get stuck it just
it just doesn't really it doesn't seem
to like successfully grab the paper in
the first place and it goes like
yeah and it just gives up on it it just
doesn't go through yeah but there's
nothing stuck from what I can see inside
nothing looks like it's stuck
and printer yeah it's so weird I don't
get it I didn't break it nothing I don't
know what I did
[Music]
it's so annoying because I have to print
out some things
clean the rubber parts of alcohol maybe
plastic GoPro and what should I do
should I bring it to like people who
repair printers
I wonder how much they charge excuse me
where is the entrance
is it stuck in the snow
is there a dude somewhere to tell me
what to do
or do I have to go to the top with this
and see maybe he's at the top
look for a cave oh okay
I think I saw something
here
bunny
ah
thank you
guys it's so bright
depends on how entrepreneur is it's
really not that old
it's like one and a half years maybe
oh that was quite a lot that I got from
a few pokes
what's in here
truffle
oh wait maybe we read this
billson's records
50 years old in print eh
I know that Laser Printers will never
have this issue apparently but they can
only print black and white right
maybe I should get a laser print but I
don't want to get another printer
it's such a bother why did I get the
first one
they're built to die fast really mine
wasn't that cheap either
[Music]
oh they can have color too really
they might be a really expensive
I'm going to keep a record of my time
working on the Skyview Tower and the
Garuda Highlands day one we've arrived
at the site and started construction
unfortunately I have a snowstorm blue
and as soon as we started we had to stop
and take shelter in the nearby cave good
news the cave is warm and safe we
decided to use it as our base camp for
the rest of our project Day free the
cave is bigger than any of us could have
imagined we explored Inside by following
a water Downstream when we were deep in
the cave we heard some hammering I don't
know how a sound from outside meant it
that far down okay I will stop breathing
now because I I guess they were down
over there
and we'll go look for them
ah chest ah okay no chest it's not like
I wanted it
I don't want the bomb but okay I I would
probably die
oh
um
I will catch you on the flip side oh
a wing please
[Music]
ready ah
nice ah wait is it gonna be
very difficult in the water
oh
there's some ice fruit here
bomb flower
over there it has just one why is always
only one out of the three growing
what
hello
how an interesting path
maybe that leads me to the
um first floor of the Tower
or not
just to a chest okay
pause
[Music]
oh is this just behind the waterfall so
you could have found it also if you just
investigated the waterfall
oh
foreign
yeah so
um printer is [\h__\h]
uh PC is getting upgraded
generously
very excited for the 4080. I don't know
if I really like
I'm gonna
play games where
that see that difference will be so
obvious to me but wait where are these
people maybe I should have read the rest
of the text
or
Maybe
maybe I have to ascend here
to get into the temple
oh because I'm under the Tower Temple
Tower
a bit
undo undo Diablo 4 you think Diablo 4
gonna run way better
hi graphics
you should no doubt
is that all I needed the new graphic
card
it'll make me laugh less often
[Music]
um
look I'm not going there I want to go
there
I want to stand on
wait
Ascend here
or here
um
let's go
ah I see for a little bit more fresh
fruit that's why they had ice fruit
there
um no one here even though where did the
people go
[Music]
what happens then
you oh
well the tower just never be accessible
from the outside is this just how it
will be
lots of yawns yeah I didn't get as much
sleep as I wanted to because of smoothie
I do have an energy drink for tomorrow
because tomorrow I realized I have a
long tutk stream planned and then at
midnight a three month Callie's Channel
but I prepared something
for tomorrow
well
I mean yeah
wow
and no I think I will be fine I can
finish it tomorrow oh yeah mama told me
so that's the thing like she was gonna
come but uh then I realized oh
oh I have a stream at midnight
so I wrote to her and I'm like Mommy
oh no
um
so she's now not sleeping over
just it's okay she was she wasn't coming
for me
anyway
she she was gonna come for something
else
what do we do
we're in the shrines
let's explore
[Music]
let's explore oh Diablo yeah she got so
addicted to it
and then my brother was also playing it
on my PC
because they first the first half was my
mother taking care
and then the later half was my brother
see a temple the ash right there
and one there okay good
let's do those two
yeah and when my after my mom was gone
she wanted to play at her place but I
guess you can't when my brother is using
my account
um at home at my place
then my mom can't use it at her place so
well
they tried
uh I think my mom got pretty far my
brother too
although I think my brother has his own
account actually yeah yeah I feel like
he told me about
doing stuff on his account
what's this
oh are those
I know there's
oh what's that worked oh yeah
because he had eyes first on his back is
that why that happened damn
I want to kill this one though
he's throwing what is he frying
fry just throwing it at the mountain
letting out his frustration
[Music]
thanks quick judge
yeah let's go
no way
huh
you thought you could get away with that
eh
why um do I have to melt it
oh
wait yeah
don't lose it also what am I wearing
[Music]
oh it's a trap poke oh this is an OCTA
Rock too oh [\h__\h] him
that's why I can't
hold on
we're exploring we're just doing side
stop today
[Music]
nice jump
oh
great
lots of eyes
I moved so slow in the snow
and no no no
no no the finale won't take so long I
heard so many people say that I could do
it in like six hours
but today I'm purposefully just dragging
it out and doing side stuff
oh afterwards we could make a
sled
see my Pro Gamer moves there you see it
seven at worse right yeah so I think
it's no problem I mean normally my Zelda
streams are minimum eight eight hours
nice flips are ready for liners I hope
so yeah flips are very important for
lionels
now
yeah
what blessing for what normally you only
get blessings if there's if it was a
challenge or something
thanks
that was easy
oh this is challenging and you mean the
gliac but the Glock felt like it was
kind of far
and even then I feel like it should be
a bit harder to get to the blessing
shrine
it's weird maybe a Lionel oh I wanted to
practice on a solo Lionel anyway
okay let's see what it is maybe it's um
straight ahead
pretty far really I was gonna go the
other direction though because there's
never Shrine there
uh this way I think
I'm so slow in this
let me make um
why am I why am I actually I'm pressing
uh next to that
long too strong I guess
because I'm activating my
thingy uh
I don't think I ever made a sled before
diagonally oh perfect I think that's all
I need or maybe oh wait it's the other
way around oh yeah
I don't think I ever got a recipe for
this now
you know part of me wants to like not
finish it tomorrow because I feel like I
could still make
a lot of content
out of this game and but after I finish
it I can still like go back on another
save file and and play more right
um put my own private time
no I don't want to finish it tomorrow
because I I want to
um
next week
start
Final Fantasy 16 I guess oh there's a
Lionel
but to be honest you know a part of me
is like
not sure
about
playing Final Fantasy because
it's longer than tltk is it not hello
stop moving
is that up
is that a silver one or a black one or
which one is this
probably notices if I take a picture
the white one
white one
those are really strong 40 to 40.
it came longer huh
yeah white one great great practice
perfect practice no I'm gonna [\h__\h]
die he's gonna take all my fairies
I safe now and if I lose all my
favorites I'm gonna redo it
um
no I can't
unless I take something with
freezing
maybe that's worth it because
do I still have something with freezing
protection
cold resistance five minutes
and this one two seven
Thirty
I prefer having more
that wasn't enough
it doesn't have to be two stars
they're all one star
but then it should be enough to at least
take uh like one more piece of armor
right
so
this is okay
and then
I haven't used this one since my last
Lino fight but it's useful this one too
to have higher chances of you know
getting the shots in
and then we can
maybe this
higher my highest damage is
these ones Maybe
wow it looks so cool
that weapon sick
um use it to five free bombs oh no oh
God I'm scared
let's go I don't I don't know my my
fingers are butter and jelly
[Music]
laughs
how do you
[Music]
know
can you not mount in that moment
oh
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
that was that that was that was
unnecessary
get out of the snow
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
from behind it works too
wait
[Music]
all right
sorry Rush McFlurry oh
baby
[Music]
all right
nice nice not it's not so bad
it's not the worst really
today
yeah the jumps the jumps the jumps he
doesn't jump so far
does he oh fairies we're gonna have to
go
get some fairies that would be nice
because
uh how many do I have left
where are they two more
I wanna I wanna go get some more fairies
before I go to the
before I go to the Coliseum
what
[Music]
let's go
uh do I remember how to dodge oh he gave
up on it okay maybe I was too far away
at that point
for him
look what's that angle is my what's
going on
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
I had a big explosion that's what comes
after that huh
[Music]
said a small Ledger
small ledge
yeah let's go
Savage Lionel balls someone that shoots
five times right wait we should combine
wait
um
get rid of that take your Royal Albert
and maybe combine the Royal hellberg
improved flurry wash that that would be
really good what's the lemon sword
um I don't know
I must have picked that up somewhere
randomly
um
that was not so bad for my first big
enemy today and it's been a while since
the last time too
uh the horn or this thing
which one should I fuse
this thing
wide made Lionel Sable 44 [\h__\h]
and then we can in theory fuse that one
too
but I think all our weapon this one
strong Fusion
okay this one when I'm on the back that
way because the durability it says you
know generally they don't have much
durability but it's durability up to but
I would use that on the back maybe and
this one
um for flurry rush if I Dodge
90.
Chase
to your singing
[Music]
that's a lot of damage yo
yeah works good for the back because the
the door built in
doesn't go down when you're on the back
I know all the tips and tricks what's
inside here I don't
I guess I'm not gonna check it out hello
bear
hello brown bear
or this is a black one I don't know
what's this that looks like there's a
Kodak oh yeah
um
up on this tree
[Music]
167 168 holy [\h__\h] is the maximum
oh yeah they keep on telling me I got a
lot of um kodaks off screen and they
keep on telling me to go to the forest
so that's the thing we can do today
where's this other Shrine oh they have a
cool
please wait
[Music]
please stop moving
pathway
no I don't know where we're going I
think the the next Shrine was like below
this level
I think the one that I saw I am here
here here
these things don't break
Forest cool place to visit
Norse
I have been my cold resistance ah this
thing is gonna disappear when I hmm go
on song
feel bad
let's go in and that will be our uh the
fourth one
then we can get uh already
a
heart
yeah I'll just make it again with auto
build I know I know a road for a ball
huh
we balling
hey
I don't want to think I don't want to do
shrines
and we can fly up here alone
oh I guess that's that's where we have
to bring it but
first we have to find it
oh there's the ball
found the ball
if you get good you don't need more well
I think though the Lionel if we bring a
lot of food the Lionel Colosseum my
not to be so bad
because I just
want to believe killed a white one
nice
I don't know if that was the intended
solution but yeah
and a lot of fairies oh yeah because I
lost two yeah but that was still one up
I was still you know
warming up
trying to live the amount of Hearts I
had
yeah but you're probably better at the
game than I am
can you ascend through the ball
I'm just gonna guess yes oh my God
okay oh wait this is not the ball that
we will need
is it
do we actually need these ones
and this ball was just a way for us to
get
this one
and learn more about balls
ah I see
a little bit too but that works
I learned that from a different shrine
where they used the same technique
um
absolute genius takanashikiwawa
okay about here do I just
yeah
yeah that doesn't work do I attach it to
the big one
seems so
I wonder if it falls down oh they're
gonna respawn it for me here haha
okay
it works it works it works
it's easy not so much thinking required
after all
oh
hey guys
[Music]
hey I don't have my phone here how am I
gonna tell you all my tangents
I'll have to get my phone
because otherwise my I mean I think I
could think of some but
I would have to think really hard
[Music]
I know a certain grown man stream on
that I'm sorry my God
cow carrot I got familiar to that one
that that guy I did not know him before
I had no idea
that this guy existed before
hmm
oh wait one
yeah
um very very entertaining I mean I think
like first I was like when I just
watched the clip of uh Ahmed
um
[\h__\h] it's so bright
the clip with the Army comparison I was
like you know I was first of all feeling
very proud of Amir
because it put her in a really good
light yo
and and she's not even you know the
greatest gamer of them all that's me
just kidding
okay
yeah and um what was I saying oh yeah
yeah so first I was like yeah that dude
what he's like
so stupid and annoying like how could
how why do people watch him I just
didn't understand it but then
after watching a bit more
I realized it's the fascination people
probably watch him because they're just
laughing at him
about them and they're fascinated by how
you can be that stubborn and that angry
and that cynical
about everything and blame everything
like maybe it makes you feel better
about yourself
this is chat Dad hello
is it broken again that happens a lot
these days huh
it's okay I'll just continue talking to
myself
as I always do oh hi
guys
[Music]
I'm just running around trying to find
shrines and and just find anything
really
Shrine thingy on it should be on
maybe I should go down here
uh-huh
you heard something from my Shrine
thingy and there's probably something
down here
some stuff to go back up
um
yeah yeah so I think I think I
understand why
there is some popularity there I guess
I guess it's like comedy
but I don't know like watching him
regularly might make you very cynical
too
I feel like that could
um
oh chest up here I can't watch people
like him
you you don't even know why brain
melting hate watching I wouldn't say
that it's necessarily hate watching in
that case I think that's a bit different
huh
I think it's just very it's not hate
watching but like you're not doing
yourself a favor
by watching him are you
because apparently he's
done for years and years and years oh my
God we could never
talk about games like that we would lose
perms immediately doesn't mean that I am
like dishonest about my opinion on games
I would say that I
I have some moments where oh
I should probably
not have said anything
not that I ever
it's not that I ever you know had uh
consequences but
what's with this frogs
I'm pretty honest yeah I just don't want
to like you know when a game is like
very obviously having some issues
I I don't want to act as if it's not as
if it's perfect because I can't
that's just nah
he
is that better yes
this is an interesting area
and yet there are no shrines
oh the shade helps
Shrine nearby
but for him that he has to study
stream of audience
mm-hmm
the other way but it just started
pinging now
well that's that way pings less
well it's really like in front of me I
see it
let's do that one next oh it's been it's
been protected
what's that sound
that's quicksand
do I what do I do I want to die do you
drown in quicksand
oh I I you just run out and that's it
oh
hello
oh nice shot
whoa
foreign
[Music]
[\h__\h] hell
um
I'd reload just for that kind of what I
want to do too yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
but no we'll just we'll just go to a
couple fairy Islands I'm not sure if I
remember where they are but they're
always like round Islands right with a
pond
we'll just go find a couple of those
they refresh right and get new fairies
right
mmm
[Music]
yeah it'll be fine you know I'm drinking
water out of this Atelier rise up oh
wait is Italy Ariza 2 this one oh I
didn't realize a stainless steel cup
um
and I feel like it's making my water
colder than it was when I first put it
in it's amazing
it's amazing
yeah I actually I went to Japan last
time with one empty suitcase and one
full one
oh no it's a big one
um
yeah
um because I
I knew that they had some stuff for me
um
actually a lot of stuff
and the stuff that I brought back is
like by far not all of it
honey
we're not even
huh
it's all cut off
[\h__\h] do they want from me
so I make a bridge
what a stupid solution
can't ah they could send it to me but
I know it would I don't want it to like
arrive and then I have to pay like 400
bucks of taxes even though it's supposed
to be a present from the company
um
because it's it's gonna be a lot of
merchandise and unpacked and all that
just sounds like it could get really
annoying so I just said leave it at the
office and I'll pick it up whenever I go
to Japan and
um so we started by taking some stuff
apparently there's like one pretty huge
can't reach that one
one pretty huge figurine
from ryza
it's not like I collect figurines
so I don't I don't even know what to do
with it
but yeah I mean free stuff let's go
is this how you guys did the shrine too
I hear enemies
not really yes something like that
that's what you did okay
okay
[Music]
okay we can make a bridge maybe no not
quad
um
[Music]
here we go
yeah
and then and then oh they have them how
not hoverboards but
some kind of board
over there
and we don't have to make stupid ass
Bridges all the time anymore
okay
what's up here
uh-huh we need a ball
apparently a little
fall out of here
[Music]
okay
that didn't activate anything I thought
if I wait then maybe it'll like land in
a
place like this and activate something
no okay
also it's kind of gated close but I see
somewhere where I could ascend
so I guess we'll go over there and then
we have to maybe bring the ball back
here
because that's also where the shrine
ends
the place
but I need to go there too
all right and then when I come back I
have to make a bridge to get up huh
I could make it now
I want to heal oh no no no no I'm fine
no
annoying
[Music]
okay did you guys see Nina's graduation
stream was 18 hours
that girl
oh my God I watched a bit of it
especially like the end
ending two hours or so
I think
how do you handle
not enough
like yeah
now it might be
yeah she took a lot of time to talk to
everybody one last time
all of her
niji
colleagues she took the time to
carefully
talk with everybody and I was really
sweet yeah and she just she talked even
about like very
could you say mundane things
like
you know what are you doing what are you
planning on streaming next week and so
on I want to watch and blah blah blah
very sweet
pretty unusual as far as graduations go
I guess so yeah I don't know I just
thought it was there we go
really like
it showed how much she cared
about the the company
um really sweet
did my line will break
[Music]
that's so sad but I have two of the five
shot bows
I where did the ball go
wait it must be here oh there it is
oh wow
I'll get more when I do the Lionel
Colosseum so as long as I don't lose
more than I make
it should be good
here
okay
this is a one-time thing
or does it close again
no it stays okay
remember you can repair the bows
with OCTA Rose oh yeah I've never done
that before
are we just gonna ignore the
[Music]
hey
what's going on
what what are you doing
huh
should we just let it blow well we're
gonna fall
oh oh now we can make a crap yeah let's
go well that was weird
though
should I you know what we'll we'll do
the ball first
and then if we feel like it will get the
[Music]
okay
but Nina said she wants to visit me in
Austria
in the summer
I mean she has another reason to
apparently to go to Austria
but yeah would be nice
to meet her again I've met her before
and it was really nice she's she's so
open and sweet
and caring and a lot just so welcoming
hmm
she wanted to kiss me for Pomo
well I I just wanna
oh nice
can't rip it though huh
great
okay not not a big issue
birthday's next week oh [\h__\h] oh yeah
right oh
[Music]
not working
she told me and I guess wait you were
listening
why were you listening
when were you listening to our private
conversation
all the birthday Colin
ah I was like when did I last
have a public collab of poor that you
guys could have listened into
creepy you must have heard my private
conversation
hold on there
I forgot already
[Music]
and see a big free heel
that's why I don't heal myself
also I gave my best friend one of the
leftover Gods
rewards that I
got from trying to get the right from
the right the right one for pekorda
senpai
what's that thing over there
bye bye
is it cold
Mamma Mia you're hot and you're cold
you're yes then you know you're in and
you're out you're up and you're down
yes
we'll make up
you don't really want to say no
you don't really want to go oh you're
hot then you're cold yes
[Music]
yeah you associate the song with Alvin
and the Chipmunks did you give her the
one no no not I don't think I ever got
that one did I I don't know
no she got the one that looks like a
lion
new jeans released a new song guys I
know you don't care but I just have to
let you know
they released a new song
and I don't know it's kind of cool kind
of chill
[Music]
oh look
it's an interesting interesting song
yeah well there's some people who know
it actually wow wow
and I was like just a surprise a lot of
as a lot of other new jeans fans who saw
a tick tock or a YouTube short whatever
form you saw it in where there were five
girls
dancing but they were filmed from above
you couldn't see their face clearly or
anything but people like they were
saying oh this is new jeans filming
their new song and a lot of people were
like no no way that's not them
you know the leak too
some random dances filming a dance video
oh it was real so everybody's like oh my
God that video the leak video was real
oh my God that was really damn let's go
and they filmed it in Portugal
apparently Portugal they were so close
they were literally right next door
um
these statues must mean something
new jeans
[Music]
why do I bother with these I don't even
have to fight them
[Music]
what are these weak weapons
hello Bo broke again Nani
[Applause]
I dropped it
was it a good bow
where did I drop it
oh what the [\h__\h] why is this thing so
annoying Royal
where did I drop it
[Music]
ah
well it ain't so bad as
dontendo just casually when sorting his
inventory dropping
um the dusk ball or the light bill or
whatever a [\h__\h]
when I got shocked by the guy outside
can I still get it back is it far
and I dropped a decimal
oh nice toolin
yeah but still it was stupid because he
he was like just like mentally not aware
of what's going on
he didn't realize that that that's what
he was doing
okay but I can't carry any more Shields
that was so useless
um where is it now the Royal bow
ah it's right there
I probably have dropped it ages ago
[Music]
I have never been to Portugal
maybe I should go I've Been to Spain
before
not the portable bomb bit okay that was
a cave let's go maybe there's a shrine
there too although then then it would
probably activate my shrine
thingy
um wait how do you just place I guess I
could place a time bomb
because I never use them anyway
let's go
Billy where's Gerudo Underground
underground ruins
oh sounds very interesting
[Music]
oh dear
maybe iFood
bring out you know bow
in the bow
oh
the music here makes me sad
interesting though
oh wow it gets pretty nice now
the what's that instrument
these two can break it too whoa
really
whoa that
that instrument what is that it's so
cool
piano Shield I don't think I have a
cannon
but yeah I've seen it in action it's
pretty nice
thank you
[Music]
well that's fun maybe a seat Tower yeah
uh what was I gonna do oh yeah I'm gonna
I was gonna test with Rudy too
does her Panda break the stones
what's that called
oh not all of them in the only way I
shoot
[Music]
that is very interesting though
yeah I didn't know that either
you switch between the two of them
that's a what I'm doing now yay
we think alike
I saw I'm was did this like super
interesting stream
right the anatomy stream
where she had uh
skeleton model of herself
that's so cool I love her ideas
I love her I did hear by the way I
listened to the archive she did say I
love you I'm very surprised
is like a
let's say cold but she just doesn't
really
say or feelings much
she's she's not very she's not she
doesn't show her affection
much right so
I I was like I was in disbelief like did
she really just say that what
um
okay there's nothing here
okay
she says that she means it
hmm
she loved me
oh does this cave have something to do
with those statues oh yeah and it must
be
there's probably a side quest right that
has to do with this
[Music]
oh hello
number one Gosling
proud number one Gosling
nanny
you wanna fight
me
and this time I attack with a better
weapon
so that you don't waste my time
got it
another girl to claim one
Julie Julie wants to
break some Stones let's go I did I had
no idea
I would have never tried this
if not for you guys telling me that this
works damn
I thought only unable can break
yeah it's not that
you know ball
breaking up rocks still slow yeah maybe
I should check if I have a cannon
maybe it's worth checking
uh let me see a Canon cannon that's a
water hydrant that's a frost do you guys
see a cannon I don't think I have
cannons yet
no I mean I have Rockets but no
no cannons I think
yeah yeah I know you're supposed to use
these swords and all that but in the end
I feel like just switching between you
know bow and ariju will be faster
[Music]
oh sorry I didn't want to smell your
armpits lady
non-canon Wawa
where does it continue is this the right
way
I'm not sure what I'm looking for no
news
this these ruins are very ruined
indeed
Polo wear statues point oh okay okay
even in here huh
[Music]
trying to get through but
is non-canon Huawei single
so I am
I am dedicated to my my cats
in my job
were you asking that so directly
you guys never ask me so directly but
yeah yes I am
[Music]
very very very very very single this
suit
this is your first time watching me live
thank you hello
and I am also not on the lookout
let me tell you that
I know I just don't have any interest or
desire
for a relationship the only times where
sometimes I feel like I wish
I had someone it's like when I'm like
like really in a lot of pain and I wish
I could get like a just a quick 5-10
minute massage
from you know someone who would be here
or when I have trouble with my PC or
when I don't know when I'm sick when I'm
sick that's really rough when I'm sick
then I feel like damn I wish somebody
could just go to the pharmacy for me the
last time I was sick man going to the
pharmacy was so rough for me
remember that time
well I wasn't sick for that long but
yeah I went outside and made me feel
really
weak and Sassy
yeah so for times like those I'm really
like ma'am
but
I mean I'm not gonna like force it
because I don't have any interest anyway
and
um I think that's better like I think
it's good for me that I can focus on my
job I don't think I
I could even like make anyone happy when
I'm like
I would have to
sacrifice a lot of my time
that I am currently using for my job
I think like I can't imagine keeping up
my current schedule
and having a relationship that just
doesn't
it just doesn't mix
unless it's someone who really doesn't
give a [\h__\h] about seeing me but then I
don't know that it's barely a
relationship probably I don't know
let them stream from me
um no thank you
yeah
I don't I don't know I'm fine really I
don't brilliant um feel like I need this
except as I said those times honestly
for those times it's just even having
rmt around would have
would have been great it doesn't have to
be
relationship but you know I'm alone I'm
all alone
I'm all alone I'm alone
[Music]
it's not like my my friends
like I I asked like oh is there anyone
who can bring me something from the
pharmacy but then
they replied too late so I just went
[\h__\h]
I just went on my own after that
felt like [\h__\h]
friends my friends were busy
that's okay
it's okay to be busy
people have jobs and stuff
rmt and BFF sound perfect for you
we are going on a trip soon
our trip is happening
soon
this month
right after my next Japan trip actually
it's like
oh I I go home
and I asked to like let have them let me
go back home like a day earlier or so
because
now I have like I think like one day
and then I go
to London
and then from London we travel further
something like that although I don't
know we also gonna check out London
probably
last time we were in London it was also
have rmt
[Music]
um but it was really cold
during those days
during the London days I won't be
streaming I'm pretty sure but I might
have some
some content
to upload anyway
it [\h__\h]
[Music]
sounds like a fun trip yeah I I hope it
will be good because we're gonna watch
The Lord of the Rings uh
Musical
suppose it's a musical
oh
Nani I think we reached the
the special
treasure oh okay well cool
cool I guess so
yeah no no know they um just created a
musical it's just about to start in the
summer
but I think it's like officially
approved or something like that I mean
they have to write to get like a
license and stuff
oh now they're carrying swords
took them a while to make one yeah I
mean I don't know if like a musical
that's kind of sounds
weird those are rings musical sounds
weird but we'll see we'll see although
no I mean Hobbits you know when they
were celebrating they were singing too
so them singing on its own is not the
weirdest thing I guess
where do I go now there wasn't even a
shrine in here
[Music]
also I'm in the Garuda desert now the
highlands weren't that big
I guess I'll jump on this thing and see
what I can find
boots yellow what
visit did you
foreign
no it turned around like chunky wonky
so cute
it doesn't like me what is that oh is
that
close to the town
I want to be productive
what is there to find here there's
probably a quarter cup on the top of
this thing
you send anything yeah
[Music]
there we go
yeah they had their twinkle pointed
concert I didn't watch it yet um I have
a cold to watch it maybe I'll watch the
VOD at some point but now the Virgin the
fifth gen and the first gen
had their own concerts right
am I missing some generation
that's really cool and it made me think
if if myth could ever have like their
own concert instead of the whole Ian
concert
could we could we ever have a
like our own concert
um
I don't know
maybe I should ask management but the
thing is we just finished it Ian the
full Ian concert so
um
foreign
[Music]
I
haven't talked about the concert yet
right what should I talk about what do I
say
what is there to talk about
um
[Music]
uh ow
it was really not like that books it was
really nice how everybody was uh
screaming not screaming but like
chanting
and yelling during Sparks yeah
the camera
the camera work
um
I don't know
uh I guess it could be improved
I mean I'm just expecting
what am I doing I am I'm expecting an
inevitable Blu-ray release because every
concert so far I had a Blu-ray release
right
so I'm thinking when that happens
we will be able to request some
different angles
and then we'll be happy oh yeah but
Kelly did mention something about my
dance break being just
that visible
and watching it afterwards I have to
agree that was kind of disappointing
because I put a lot of energy and and
like I don't know power into my dance
moves
during that dance break because I was in
the center for the dance break
and I wanted to make sure oh
that I
shine during this
dance break
well I mean what I found really cool
though
is
you guys maybe noticed too I I don't
think this was a thing with
[Music]
um
with the four Fest looking back on it
you know how the camera and the
close-ups
it had a
like a blur going on
like for example if they're a close-up
is focused on the face
oh the blur would be like in the front
hand that is visible
[Music]
and that looked cool did it not
ah
oh hey fire
[Music]
sweating
can you not eat my friends
what's it what did it eat
[Music]
[\h__\h] I can't
why are they so annoying why am I
bothering with them
[Music]
oh my nose is so itchy the whole time
a bear
he's dead now
yeah my nose
cat hairs please
where's the chest
thank you
aha why is there this fire
why
oh [\h__\h] funny
where am I
oh
it's ah this is the end of the map it
doesn't look quite like it
okay
it's best yeah it's like thank you you
know my last uh Korean lesson before the
lesson I was like really stressed out
because I brought all my study things to
Japan
thinking that I will have some time
to study
and then I didn't at all I was like so
busy
recording practicing rehearsaling and
stuff
yeah so then I didn't have any time and
I brought it back and then I had a
Korean lesson like pretty soon after
and I
I was like stressed out like [\h__\h] I
didn't learn I forgot everything again I
have to do my homework
um
yeah
so then with my homework I was having a
harsh time really
but then
I got some help
and then I watched the video I found a
channel
where this dude he explains even the
most simple things and also very
difficult things
three different levels he explains it
like all really really well really easy
to understand
what's the channel I don't remember the
name right now but it's some like uh not
a Korean guys like a foreign guy
he
he's a great job boom
explaining everything and really helped
me understand the the yo form
which saved my butt at the Korean lesson
I I just watched it for like 10 minutes
and it clicked and I'm like oh I I
understand this actually way more than
when my teacher first told me
yeah and so I proudly presented my new
skills
to the Samsung Nim
did I never do that Shrine over there
maybe I didn't no no I didn't it's
outside
and she was impressed
no
Trina Hall yeah she was impressed she
was very satisfied that I
understood it yeah
actually I only have I think free
more lessons with her
I think
um so it will be over soon and I'm
thanks to finding that channel I think
I'll
you know go through the whole Channel
to first remember everything the lady
told me
and also made me extend my knowledge a
little bit
yeah
any YouTube channels explained better
than paid courses I mean I'm not saying
that my teacher was bad at all
I think she was great
foreign
that was a big Miss but it worked out
anyway
you don't see me
yeah yeah go to the big explosive box
how much damage did that do yeah
you're trying to shoot
it wait wait wait let's make it fair
I'll go over to you guys if I can make
it as
oof
is there an entrance somewhere
or do I have to make a bridge
it's foreign
yeah but at some point it was just
overwhelming and you know
I felt like
the knowledge is just
being pressed and pushed into my head
and I'm not really learning anything
anymore unfortunately
wait
now
I don't know I I I I wish I had I would
have had more time in between the
lessons to practice everything
no but I was busier with work than I
thought I would be
that is obviously too short
this bridge gotta be huge
eh
I'll bring those back please
use the shields too glad the tooling
okay
pulling my eyes I'm so tired
oh man I'm losing HP the whole time
oopsie Doodly Doo
oh those work too
whoa wait they look like they would make
good materials for building a sled or
something like that too
if it's still not long enough
then we just I'm just gonna yeah okay
I'm just gonna hold it like this
and then fly off
go go go go go
all right
oh God there's so many explosive apps
oh it's time
go go
how long does it take to explode oh
there we go
[Music]
and I want to use my line of weapons
right now
my masters were I never used a master
suit
[Music]
he's so lanky
such a lanky boy
let's go
oh
I thought
that was a silver white one
now let's get to you I'm just gonna
probably throw you down in the sand
[Music]
what about all the materials
can you make it go off faster
no
there's any damage
hi Michael my mother no no
where does it go
does it just come back into my inventory
when it's like Reloaded
[Music]
yeah okay
they got quite the nice setup here so
I'm actually suspecting
that the shrine will be a blessing
shrine
even though you're not a really
contractually obligated I guess
[Music]
to fight
all of them or are you
someone down there
no so well
let's see
[Music]
the show
the Thai social
see me give me give me a blessing please
wait one second
it's been two hours so far by the way
drink more okay I drink more oh
it's not a blessing shrine
after all that work
on
naked
oh wow these are actually kind of fun
always
they're not so bad
but okay
can I go below
okay easy
no kind of lonely
okay we confused a stone
and we can Ascend and get the materials
will we be seen by the others
confused with the
corn
get the bow
oh there's some spikes down there too
to fuse with one shot yeah easy
easy peasy lemon squeezy
oh he saw me or he heard me
construct stays completely seen me now I
guess
you could set them on fire I suppose
let me use this
take that oh they look strong
what was that I I jumped back but I also
hit him
oh my focus
oh
my God
so night long sword okay that is at
least effective against them but there's
nothing fused on it oh it's still the
strongest and I have yay
you lost your weapon too
it's over you [\h__\h]
Get Wrecked
of course
[Music]
oh yeah anyway what should I talk about
about the concert it's already it feels
like it's already been so long
my memory because my birthday happened
right after so
I don't I know my memory isn't fresh
anymore
uh oh yeah I I was very honored to
be placed
in the middle
for like everything
I I I was very actually confused about
that this decision
um
I I don't know
I was well honored like I don't even
know why
um
but I'm I'm I was very happy not gonna
lie
yeah the Sparks reaction was amazing
oh 16 lost
yeah I mean
the MC is um
some of them were maybe a bit uh awkward
[Music]
I just realized though you know that the
last speeches do you guys realize it was
a kind of a reference to
I think I think it was the first
Japanese concert
um
but the last speeches you know they were
a reference I mean they were
purposefully kind of like more
awkward as a result because we were
doing like the emotional speech thing
just like Japan Gumi Japan group did it
in their first concert they also just
popped up out popped up out of nowhere
was so loud suddenly
yeah they pop
up out of nowhere in one line and just
one by one randomly gave these like
speeches
but
I don't know it was more emotional for
them somehow
um intentionally unintentionally awkward
yeah you did notice the similarity um
yeah
oh yes I I advertised I took the
opportunity
because I didn't know
what else to say I thought like a lot of
things would already probably be said by
the others anyway
um you wanna go there
I don't know if I want to bring you
there I don't care much about courage
but we did another Shrine wasn't this
one a temple was oh yeah
that is where the temple was and it's
like really dark everywhere here
should we go to the korok forest where
is the Kodak Forest
I like the content of the closing
statements nice
you did a great job at SimCity thank you
next to the fairy at the top
uh
uh fairy
is it one that I didn't find yet
is it this one
oh yeah
I was wondering about that because
that's I think where there was this
weird
um fog
okie dokie
yeah also I mean I think
one feedback that I saw from a lot of
people that uh I understand but I also
understand why it wasn't the case this
time
[Music]
um
I saw a lot of people like
um who are hoping wishing
for
um like units because we only did like
math virus Council
and
um
you know the Japanese ID groups on their
own and everything and we didn't mix
anything and you know generally I'm like
a big fan of mixing
everything around shuffling units
because I saw that a lot with like hello
project concerts as well
but I it's our first concert so I do
understand that they wanted to keep
probably that was their fault I think
they wanted to keep a certain like order
and system and keep everything clean and
organized for the first concert and then
if we'd ever do a second one that's
where we can go crazy you know
we just gotta you know go very basic
this time and then
in the future
we can do whatever
are they gonna come for me that's fine
Bring It On baby
or are they going for oh
I I did not expect that
[\h__\h] off
I went for him understandable right yeah
I think so too
give me that meat
oh dear the trees are angry
I hope the place where I'm going now is
an entrance a proper entrance
my favorite performance besides my own
oh
mume was crazy
mume's singing was sheesh crazy I think
so emotional
[Music]
um
that was something
that's quite something
and
maybe Ina no also Cali because holy [\h__\h]
Sasuke Kelly
as expected of Cali like she just
[\h__\h] sets the stage on fire rocks
everything like damn
the song that she chose and she had the
guitar
I don't know that song is really hype
wanted wasted
it's just really hype and I really like
it
yeah I mean you know it's it's she
doesn't have like much of a choreography
for it but did you just follow these
rooms
but I don't know it doesn't feel like
it's lacking anything right
how does this work and
there's someone there hi
so bad real bad the last one just aren't
right anymore no matter which way I
enter the fall comes and gets me and
then I'm right back at the beginning I
can't return to Chronic floor is like
this I want to go home I did hear that a
big hole opened up and mentioned was
kind of scary and she wants
do we have to light sorry
um sorry
inside
sorry let's talk let's talk can we talk
God damn it
how
just wanted to talk to the guy
can we talk from here
he won't talk to me
why
I know that in breath of the wild you
had to follow where the Flames are like
pointing towards
now he will talk
uh what is these weird vibes oh are you
an adventurer too You Feel The Vibes
right the strange Vibes in this air all
around here oh I mean fog in the forest
up ahead the Forester head has Lost
Woods and it's always been pretty weird
if you got lost you'd wind up back at
the entrance but now the fog in there
has gotten even thicker take two steps
to the forest and it'll spit you right
out not too long ago you could at least
walk into these woods but now you can't
progress at all oh
oh
he did mention something about dementia
wood so maybe I have to go into the
chasm
then find something to ascend up to or
so I don't know
yeah
[\h__\h] yeah
makes sense okay
hold up I want to get out
I just want to go out
this is not the path let me go out
please
thank you thank you thank you thank you
good intuition
big brain
big thanks to Carefree who printed a
guide for fan chanting oh yeah it was so
cute I saw videos of you guys like
practicing
beforehand he was cute and also did you
guys see like you know there was this
big German convention going on at the
same time right dokumi and over there
hey Dave rent is a movie theater
to watch the concert
for like I don't know how many people
several tens of people hmm
that is such a cool like
way of gathering and watching it because
like the thing is also like even if they
wanted to watch it
um
in a hotel room or whatever they
couldn't because
it was like three four four a.m I think
for Europeans most Europeans
and
yeah you can't really be loud if you
gather with a lot of people
you can't like cheer and yell
so they managed to
uh rent a theater amazing
got it
amazing
[Music]
yeah but everybody who wanted to go
there had to provide a code like a legit
code of them of their streaming spawn
streaming code
as proof that they already paid for it
so it's not like you can just go there
and watch the concert for free
oh there's a there's one over there
um
basically probably
there's something to ascend either in
the middle or
earlier on
love you and connect thank you orange
yes
it's the other way follow the stairs
down and find the first you know
and Friends
are scary here it's so dark and there's
creepy spots on the ground maybe this
was a bad idea
oh
I feel like I see a path that goes up to
the root
should I not follow that
you can see
what
did you not like maybe activate them
first or so
maybe that's what you have to do I don't
know
we wear docomo the room it came crazy
when you appeared
it's nice that we have
our own concert for the first time
so far like four Fest was better but
like third Fest
uh
oh yeah protest was the first time right
where we appeared
and we were just guests
and then four fence
we were at least you know like kind of
treated normally like in units and all
that
um
but still
I'm going the right way okay
but still it's nice the Lost fog oh
yeah I'll fix it don't worry
it's nice to have our own thing
that we can be very proud of that we can
also invite the other
um branches to
yeah and and I mean I mean no I
understand the sentiment of you know
people wishing that there would have
been like some
you know the Japanese or ID members
singing with us together I get that too
but as I said I think it comes back to
you know first of all the fact is our
concert
is our concert if we start like mixing
in everything I don't know
would have been nice to see of course
but maybe that's what the the four Fest
Etc are for you know
half taco
we can still see many of those
combinations in future big festivals I
think so yeah
and who knows we might do it
the root lights
yeah I want to go there too but there's
so much red on the ground
ow
but yeah who knows maybe in the future
we'll also try something like that but
I think it was fine the way oh wait a
second
the way it was I think it was fine
wait that resembles
the trees they had in breath with the
Wild and the Kodak Forest
hmm goopa
you're listening listening
[Music]
how you doing
man I swear I probably have some guba
tangents but my phone
so far I should go grab my phone
goodbye
a life stronger
a stronger day but they couldn't grow up
no it's not wait no can I get out of the
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] oh no
no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no
no please leave me alone oh thank God
terrifying
[\h__\h] you guys [\h__\h] you I don't want to
fight you go away
go away and leave your clumps for me
yeah there they go
gopa helped me so scary it's like um
the horror game that we played out last
um so scary
I wanna play happy games
in the rain
did she say that
we're playing against that hell though
wait we hugged in the rain I mean we hey
I mean we shared an umbrella
Ella Ella
we hugged in the rain
I mean we hugged a lot did we hug
specifically in the rain
oh we weren't really considering using
instead of umbrellas using those dorky
um
rain colds then she doesn't have to
carry anything
but I feel like
I don't know then we would make
everything wet yeah the ponchos would be
cute though I don't know they're dorky
and cute at the same time
sharing everything no it's hard to share
a raincoat
I think would be a bit tricky
can I tell
can I say it can I um
roughly vaguely
talk about
the the not a success
I did ask jenma by the way and she said
oh it's fun
let's see what Kuba says I leave it to
Cuba
just just vaguely uh
it's good that you're here you can give
me you know your your thoughts
[Music]
my DMs are open too by the way do it oh
okay okay
so you guys know that uh maybe you saw
it
did we even talk about it in the Twitter
space Maybe
that there's like a clip of
collaboration
with
some big cup company crepe crap
yeah uh like you know Harajuku takes the
streets there's like if you go down
there there's like so many clips
and like one of the biggest companies
there that do that is called Marion I
mentioned this no I talked about getting
the ass
I don't think I talked about these clips
crepes
should I go to this
should I should I should I
okay I don't think I talked about this
yeah and and and I love first of all let
me just say I love Harajuku craps so
much
because they're like they're pumped with
so many like things you can get like ice
cream and so many fruits and they don't
they don't hold back you know
they put so much stuff on there you can
have cheesecake on your cup
and other things cookies and whatever
cream and a lot of cream I I prefer it
to be not too much whipped cream
or custard cream I like normally my
ideal crap is like custard cream uh then
a scoop of vanilla ice cream or whatever
and a fruit like strawberries or bananas
um yeah that's it I don't want like too
much on it but you know get a good
balance
where was this
way maybe
and yeah they they basically
they don't make you know typical French
cups no no no no they make oops [\h__\h]
stop it
they make Japanese japanified
French cups
how do I get past this
okay it's fine
yeah really yummy yummy you should try
and it's like were they typical to eat
them in Harajuku but you don't have to
it's not necessary you know you can get
them in other places too and now let's
get to the point so there was this uh
collaboration right
and
was it first gouda's idea to go
maybe she was like oh I want to go
what's this
it was probably her desire I was like
all right I will fulfill your desires
I think yeah there was one thing I
really wanted to do
and then gura wanted to go eat the
collaboration Crips and I'm like okay
leave it to me I will do the research
where will we go
I'll check out you know which ones
we could go to which ones are like
probably sold out immediately
oh I'll check it all out all right and
then we'll go oh
and I found
a good one a good location because
there's like several locations not
halajugu actually actually they didn't
sell it in Harajuku at all
um
are you her mom
no I see myself more as a sister
big sister
you annoying
get out of here
yeah so I don't know if you guys saw the
details but they have uh first in the
first phase they have a Aquino Senpai Uh
crap and the fubuki said bye
um
and they're both
very very filled with whipped cream a
lot of it
um
and they also sell like merchandise if
you go to one of the
places that have these cups not all
Marion crap locations have it oh
yeah yeah yeah so we went and uh I got
the Aquino the crap and Guna got the
fubuki crap of course of course and we
got like a little bit of merchandise too
um and then
this was my breakfast by the way I was
looking forward to a club for breakfast
but yeah honestly
we we both thought it was Emma was there
too by the way but she didn't get a cup
but we both want it was a little bit too
much whipped cream but it was still
yummy mine had like a a cheesecake
topping
and I think like one waffle
um and I was I think maybe banana
caramel banana
and gunas had like these you know those
chocolates
um that you know there's like this uh
takenoko and kinoko chocolate in Japan
right where everybody's like are you
talking to cool team or kinoko team and
the taco
it's topped this this crap the Saluki
crab is topped with that to kind of look
like her ears and it's so cute it works
so well actually it just seems the place
to be to the place to descend by the way
so I guess I'll go
yeah it looks so cute
um so it's supposed to create these ears
right and then
Guna sits down
you had custard though too yeah custard
yummy yummy I think maybe mine had a
little bit of custard I don't know
and she tries to start to eat it but
then one of the ears fall down
good at first was really like sad about
the ear falling down yeah but she made a
uh or two I don't know one or two burps
really happy
like attacking the ear and like throwing
it around
it went places
she fed the birds it all
goes in the circle you know it's the
circle of life
um
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
don't even attempt it I think you're
gonna get sick hmm
the ear never had a chance
did you even take a picture and go down
because damn
it looked so cute I took a picture of
mine I think
what
if you didn't take a picture that was
that that was very unfortunate
but I guess you can find other pictures
of the same crap out there ah you took a
picture after you lost it oh yeah and
they said you should just Photoshop it
because now there's like this AI
Photoshop where uh you know it auto
fills things I tried it before it just
uses the Photoshop uh library of stock
photos so it's very very ethical yeah
yeah I was saying just try to autofill
the ear
can do it for you legit I didn't I get
in photoshopping for you if you
hahaha
yeah but you know worth the experience
it was it was uh worth it getting cute
cups I kind of wanna try the other two
as well
I don't know if I have a chance to do
that
maybe because I think it's going for
a whole month at least
I might have a chance to get the other
ones
I got like some random merchandise that
gouda for some reason didn't get this
I don't know why I bought a keychain
and for free I got like one
like Place collectible random placemat
like I made out of paper
and it's like first covered up in an
envelope so you don't see which one you
got and I open it up and I I had polka
looks really nice it looks like one of
these papers that you have like when you
order something at McDonald's and on the
tray the paper they placed on it or kind
of the paper that they wrap around the
crap I guess
one of those yeah like a just a
placement yeah but I got porka yeah
and good I didn't get one anyway so
because I was before her I was ordering
before her the question was if maybe I
got the last one maybe because I didn't
ask for it I don't know they just gave
it to me
hmm
but she got a bit more merchandise than
me
right she got a key chain and something
else
and then and then because I bought the
fubuki keychain too we both had the
fubuki kitchen which is really cute it's
like um packed into a cup bed a bed of
crap and then we showed it to furuki
said but
we were like look for bookies then bye
ah you got the acrylic stand nice cute
yeah yeah nice
like oh wow you got it thank you
yeah yeah yeah
it's so cool that Japan has this kind of
like collaborations so many
collaborations only in Japan what
happened to the dick at the victory
no Yahoo
it doesn't even say yeah
what never have seen such quiet kodoks
before
yeah they don't even move
they're like Stone they don't even
breathe
are they dead for real
wait we'll talk we'll talk and we'll
activate the shrine
they going through something don't
understand
the grimace
the Grimace Shake struck oh yeah gura
told me about the Grimace Shake in
detail
to me that thing looks like it's like
out of Sesame Street
oh maybe a reward trap no okay
it's not
does it not look like it's like straight
out of Sesame Street to you guys
really
[Music]
that's it
wait this Shrine is really easy huh
oh wait okay okay okay
this one uh maybe we attached the the
big block to it
that was super difficult totally
so difficult
oh by the way I was really hoping or
like planning to get a um a collab going
with like an aqua lab going with Gouda
while we were there we really wanted to
but I was not able to get like the only
studio time that I was able to get in
like a streaming booth was for the one
with Lapu Castle
the other two days where I had time and
I think gouda had time too
was exactly the two days where I
couldn't use it
so that was unfortunate another time now
we'll have another time hopefully surely
what's going on here
um
should I cheese it
cheese
[Laughter]
yeah
yeah I don't care we got some [\h__\h] to do
today you know
so lame though that you can't cheese it
like that it's actually
the same they should not make that
possible
every Shrine that has some some Target
like that you can cheese it like that
yeah
I'm sorry that I'm telling you now and
you may rely on it in the future
so wrong yeah
it's illegal I agree
I only do that one specific Shrine trust
me everyone does it I bet on that one
that's insane right
um okay can we talk to the train oh
oh that one's pretty big you talk no
oh no they're so sad oh my God it's
because he's sick okay
hello
[Music]
we're in the inside of him
what the [\h__\h] there's a there's a statue
where we can get our hearts
grimace Grimace aftermath
they're really cute really really really
cute
um comic first I saw a sad comic of
Grimace and I liked it too what Grimace
was really sad that everybody disliked
him and his shake and then they updated
it they uh uploaded a new comic where he
was happy with all the comments of
people who said they did like it um
and then he was really happy
my heart Ryan yeah
oh that was awesome
uh Mamma Mia we almost couldn't get
another one
so cute oh and I was told I think Emma
told me because she tried it
that is lavender flavor
did this also happen on stream and I
just don't remember
I think lavender flavor it's not that
bad
it's weird yeah but it's not that bad
blueberry
maybe maybe it depends on like the
country
lavender lavender
I'm a Saturday Jack Fox there you go oh
nice
nice bed and like a bean a jelly bean
gouda jelly beans
let's go eat some more jelly beans
I'll make your Jelly Bean dinner
or some place to sit on oh nice nice
nice cave
eh
I guess I have to go down here to fix
the tree
wow wow
right way okay here we go mini boss oh
no
what am I wearing I don't have to wear
these clothes anymore right
have fun here we go friends
what do you say that as if good luck
you make it sound like it's so difficult
Nani
all right
um scare me
death ahead I know
it's getting hands in no
no I I did it before but I need some I
need to stand somewhere
you think this will help me a lot I
think it's the only piece that has Gloom
resistance
I think
[Music]
I have to go down
once the sword gives extra damage okay
should I fuse it to something I should
fuse it to something
what should I feel that too
I'll use it maybe to the the whole
I'm so scared
foreign
why can I not do it with the bombs
why
I can ah shut up
foreign
it's okay I have a lot of medicine for
this
uh
and that's the problem I have to stand
here
on this [\h__\h]
but after this the Ganon well I've had I
fought him before so
where are you guys going
oh
go on the ground floor there's some trap
Wings yeah I guess I could do that
um
anyway
see I have a lot of juice
I'm well prepared
just one left
so I'll finish him with some eyes and
there he goes
it's nice to see you again we meet again
how how beautiful how how happy that
makes me
where is he
I was trying to attack
link you little [\h__\h]
because I'm embarrassed myself real good
now he's he's weak
ah he's so weak what's going on he
barely takes Hearts from me
[Laughter]
weaker than the lionels that's for sure
[Music]
do I have to do it again no
okay
my Armory uh probably better than last
time too
and I didn't have the master sword back
then or I didn't use it at least
let's go yeah
yeah you tell me no longer court and
these suckers are happy again
what are they gonna give me
what could they possibly give me
um
nice clothes I want the bow too uh
oh this one's breaking
yeah that was easy
that was easy
yeah
went for all the travel just to wake up
to three just to be able to find the
master sword when you have it all along
is he the one
after you wake him up that gives you
like a like a hint
oh also do I
how do I get back
to the shrine maybe really and that's
what that's that's what he's for
I guess that makes sense because
um
but
I think there will be many cases where
there wasn't a sand spot
oh
I think there would be many cases where
people already have the master sword
on it
I may have gone to the wrong place
where do I go
this is why you got the master sword
remember for the wild so again expect
you to come back here to look for it
[Music]
I see that you know I get it I get it I
get it today's my birthday happy
birthday oh
[Music]
yeah
well atmosphere changed
it's happy
again it's been a while huh I finally
made it home foreign
[Music]
can I even extend my postage yeah no
I need more I could probably do the
shield stash but uh
uh where is the face how do I talk to
him
they have to go right up in his face
wakey wakey oh there we go
oh
foreign
[Music]
yes you went to Great trouble to restore
me
foreign
[Music]
won't link Trey goddess Master shelters
is
memory no I see yourself
Excalibur
[Music]
we attack noise
oh
yeah
it's a cherry blossom tree right now
this is
foreign
yes we're Fusion
that's Master [\h__\h]
done
yay
overlay was covering some of the
dialogue
you have to auto complete
you you are ah
you you appear to be faced with trouble
once more
when I see you have prepared the master
sword
that sword I sense a sacred power with
its status stronger than before what has
come to pass
take heed and do not rely solely upon
the power of that sword you must steal
your mind and your spirit as well
I am always here
should you ever have need of me you need
only ask
Ah that's so lame
so after showing me the memory he would
tell me where it is now
and I already have it
[Music]
um
is this pinging because of the shride I
already did
or is there another one right away
um
you know what's another one
another one
this way this way this way this way
okay
I need one more Shrine anyway
free in the forest oh dear okay
I know can you get lost again now the
same way as before
[Music]
um
I wouldn't want to get lost while
looking for the shrine
oh no
[Music]
there's some paths okay
where am I
ah [\h__\h] no no
I just got lost
I need to find the Quest for them
really
oh let me go here that seems ah
pranky
um
so pretty I found it myself I want it no
you can't have it no it's fine but if
you do something for me maybe I'll
consider it
the thing is I love garden apples and a
pretty stone is pretty but I can't
really eat it so if you bring me five
gold I think I have that
nothing
[Music]
apples okay take the green apple
ha ha
all right
so this must be a blessing Shrine right
also I probably shouldn't directly
follow the laser you guys said follow
the path
but can I go here oh wait it's right
there anyway
okay
okay yeah that should be a blessing
Shrine right
right
these things usually are blessing
friends I think
easy
yeah I literally fell into our hands
this one
oh by the way I did also check out the
did I tell you guys
did I write about it on Twitter I
checked out the the Shibuya Crossing
um advertisement for our concert
it was really stressful
because it was after the the crap
um
uh Adventure
and yeah we were like really stressed
because like we had somewhere to be
after that too
I tweeted about it yeah
that was um before we had to go to the
the stream and the the studio
[Music]
um
yeah so
we were already like I was like I really
need to go now because otherwise I can't
see it I don't have any other time where
I could go see it so I have to go now
yeah
so
we went we rushed that's why I was
walking so fast and Emma was saying I
walked so fast
well
well places to be at
the [\h__\h]
yeah
honestly like it was so short
but because it was like running like
basically every 10 minutes it was really
easy to catch it like we arrived and I
looked for a decent spot
where's the other Shrine Quest by the
way
I looked for a decent spot
um where I could see all the screens
because I saw in the picture that it
should be on five screens right
oh this way
five screens at the same time on that
big ass crossing that's like
huge yeah and every 10 minutes for a
whole week except for during the night I
think
[\h__\h]
yeah but the advertisement itself was
really short I didn't I didn't let
myself be spoiled before going I wanted
to see it with my own eyes so I didn't
watch any spoilers
so I also didn't know that it would
literally just be
um I think our version of shiny smelly
story playing
with our promotion picture for the
concert
video I thought they would play the
music video of of our original song
it was just like the picture playing
with some music
I kind of expected more but it was on
five screens and and so often like every
10 minutes on such a huge huge
a huge could you call it venue
that is huge really
um
that was cool and I the moment I saw it
started playing I I was like I think I
already had my phone ready and I started
filming
should I go this way
I started filming it but it was so short
and I I ended up not seeing it with my
own eyes because I was just
watching it for the camera
screen
that's the exit okay
yeah but then I had to go we had to go
we were in big big time pressure
why are they hiding from me
is this part of their their game
for the like this one
ah okay
[Music]
not in the forest there's a wide open
space and right in the middle there's a
green sword you can see an island
floating in the sky from there Maka
loves that place but since it's covered
in Lost flag only caught up getting on
there so you can't come with me but I'll
tell you where to find it could you show
me your map
in the sky or no
there okay
you can see an island cloning in the sky
from there I wonder if you could see
into the forest from that Sky Island too
yeah
it's not in the sky but it's a sky
island
oh I should go from the sky
okay
can I
had to keep
it's gone
do I have to talk them again
hey
unmarked it okay
uh
I can try to go from here
and then fly over
it was kind of far
mysterious
hmm
okay
should we play some cocktail while we're
here
what do you get out of this one again
shock light steering stick homicide
okay
[Music]
actually I'm not interested
the only good thing on or the thing that
I think is good is the
steering stick
no gotcha sorry
not now
I'm thinking
of
throwing myself
over there
I wonder if I can get to here at least
um
although maybe
maybe I should just fly
of a bike all right
uh
okay
or this one
but improved
with a steering stick why does that one
not even have steering stick
someone on top steering stick
[Music]
foreign
because often there's like three steps
lying around
anything
no
[Music]
maybe here
I don't see anything
wow
so cheap
steering wheel would be better
I don't know if you're joking but I
think it's fine
I think it's fine also I'm gonna add a
battery Maybe
One battery
that's hopefully not too much weight
okay
man the summer heat makes me so tired
oh man
mm-hmm
oh I can't take off
because it's not on a thing but can it
What if I
I would
wait don't fly away without me I
probably will probably
[Music]
of course
no I don't want to lose my my building
materials on that [\h__\h]
oh man
I mean I could use this too but um
how much does this cost 36.
Mamma Mia wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait what if I you know I never use
them so
let me take out
device device
I'll try to build it myself one two
three
um and
um the wings
uh-huh
let's see here free
it's free
more economically friendly
because I'm using up the thing if I'm
ending the game tomorrow you know
I might as well use up what I have right
after this
Coral chorus I guess we'll go kill some
lionels
I I don't feel so scared of the Linus
but honestly because I never tried I I
do feel
very nervous
about
the
gliox
I don't know how to go about that
I don't know
okay this is the perfect Construction
let's go
I hope I don't regret building this
afterwards but I'm looking good
where's my battery uh
because it's still using the that one
yeah that is depleting a lot
[Music]
Monday
oh
my soul Knight I don't have a donut
armor what do you mean sunlight armor
there's still night armor that makes
battery deplete slower
okay I'll use I'll eat some of these
batteries
there are so many armors
too many
if you ask me
do I have to go higher is it the one
that I've seen the very distance
we could also land in an island over
there and then charge
if we need
actually pretty fast
it doesn't look so fast above here
even if I
eat more batteries
[Music]
no
why
I am making a new one
yeah the glider what the [\h__\h] is up with
the glider
is this the one
don't fall down don't fall down
[Music]
take it all right
why is it still running stop moving
okay chill I made a new one we can
reload
yeah they all the five-star fell down
here perfectly I just turned around in
the right in the last right moment
[Music]
uh okay let's go
and wait [\h__\h]
it's that way
go wrong but I don't think he makes this
whole thing heavier
wait where am I going
it's because this island moved it
confused me
oh is it that thing
no not again
no
ah okay wait that was something else no
is it wait ah
nothing
oh that's so funny at least my Landings
are incredible
I mean come on hey hey
[Music]
huh it's bugged out
yeah they don't fall down
I'll try it one more time okay we're so
close
we're so close
actually no let me throw out one more
[Music]
what
why do they get stuck there
oh it like pre-built it even though I
don't
[Music]
um
I don't like fix it set it in stone yet
that's when I moved everything
forward for
come on
[Applause]
fine I'll do it myself
why are you moving
he's making me dizzy
waste of time
unbelievable
foreign
all of this for it to disappear so fast
why is the glider
so annoying let's see
can we get a battery too again
I don't know if it's really helping me
at this point
[Music]
no
I didn't even use it
it's a fresh glass glare
I didn't know
foreign
I wanted to give you a chance
I really wanted to give you a chance
okay
I really wanted to
but somehow destiny
does not want us to work together
yeah the spinning probably makes it
think it's moving or something I don't
understand
but I feel scammed
but oh finally into our destination
wherever it is
where is it
huh
I'm supposed to see it
down
how far down
it's in the forest why am I going from
so high above
it's hard to go down with this thing
am I going down
what if I just let myself free fall
does that not work
can I
what a [\h__\h] waste of my time
[Music]
okay
I want to go to the pond over there
anyway
I
question my life choices right now
[Music]
is there any fairies here
better be
hello fairies no fairies here
what about furries
sounds the same to me
no fairies no fairies how fairies
fairies oh [\h__\h]
let's get him
they won't know what hits them
wait these are the wrong ones
Chic is in the house
are in the house too
foreign
don't worry this time it didn't mess
everything up for once
now we got two fairies which we
desperately need anyway
or the linels
I gotta be really careful though because
what it's like five final fights
genius
I thought that a was for the fairy fairy
oh it's still here
five final fights Mamma Mia
Mamma Mia
I gotta go in with a lot of Hearts so
that we're not only relying on the
fairies
there's more though there's more
now we have three and that will be the
fourth
red blue white silver and armored oh my
God
there's there's cute hi
dad
[Music]
boy don't scare the fairies
very nice so that the it's in my bubble
no
very nice set of fairies
react less than the ducks
[Music]
now free fall
I hope it works oh I see a shrine wait
is that the one
oh
it must be
no
oh
oh meets good though let's go
ah
[Music]
you're right they don't only take my
hearts they also attack with Gloom
because they're the liners are on the
ground
yeah okay we'll have a good a good big
uh cooking session
[Music]
mighty constructible
no no need I think
yeah I just want this
a song I want
[Music]
um
five okay one more heart we can get of
course
noise
and this way we also got the the Kodak
Forest behind us now so we did some more
side content
places I haven't been to yet very nice
wanna talk
oh you found it
found it wow just like a cork
chosen
oh my God he just cloaked or juice with
me
there's another Shrine of the first
another one
hey
what you did
I think I'm good for now but
where am I there's probably one here
let me go grab my phone real quick y'all
let's get my phone
[Music]
thank you
what is the textbook collapse tonight or
tomorrow night
because my my phone just gave me a
notification
is it tonight
for tomorrow night tomorrow right fossil
of course I put it wrong into my
calendar
tomorrow night I thought so
okay
[Music]
what was that
uh
wait what was that ah
one more thing I just saw in my notes
wait lead me to the next shrine
I don't hear any bing bing bing bing
I mean
virus
[Music]
foreign
follow the lanterns Unturned
lanterns there's no ladder in there I
lost them
freestyle
ah ding dong
hmm
What if I if I go this path I will get
lost
probably
[Music]
what's tomorrow tomorrow collab on Cali
Channel
regarding the
English study book
there you are hey hey no you can't
no you're not a colleague so whatever
there's this thing Beyond here that I
can't stop thinking about I keep wanting
to go and check it out again
[Music]
you know that thing that showed up over
there it looks similar but kind of
different
mm-hmm
flowers are there to help keep you from
getting lost so don't go picking them
okay
but at least this one maybe
um so okay I I remembered one more
tangent about the okay
me third Wheeling meet up
you know when we came to the karaoke
usually Indians Japanese karaoke
you have to choose one drink in the
beginning if it's not a drinking drink
bar thingy system
and you have to choose one
in in the beginning and they'll bring it
to you and then you can still ask for
more later but first they want to choose
one right away
[Music]
here
yeah and so the staff showed us the menu
[Music]
um
there it is are you leading me around
the staff showed us the manual and it
was Japanese and there were so many
drinkers I would say at least like 40 40
drink choices Maybe
[Music]
and I was like damn okay I have to
translate this for good so she knows
what to choose to drink
so I start wrapping
every single non-alcoholic only though
uh item that I see on the menu do I
still have to follow the flowers yeah
and and try to like quickly translate
every single one I got like this one and
this one then this one and this one and
this one and this one and this one and
this one and this one in that tempo
there were so many what
Mamma Mia
there were so many
do I have to yeah
you have rapid translator and the moment
I finish
my wrap my literal rap
the staff member
pulls out
the English menu
it was such a funny moment
because I was so proud that I was able
to so quickly so spontaneously so fast
so accurately translate all of the
drinks on the menu for gouda and I had
this big doya face like though yeah I
did that
glasses sunglasses on moment and then
immediately after I'm done
the staff shows us the English menu and
also has like this smile on their face
come on but
the English menu had typos and weird
translation mistakes my translation
didn't have that
comedian stuff
yeah
that was funny
hmm
yeah I was feeling so cool so skilled
what did she pick
Ed I remember actually
I just remember I had balanced soda
because I always try to drink things in
Japan that I can't drink much
overseas well back home
I just caught
one of those tiny fruit flies in my hand
and I let it go again because I thought
it was dead already
or like
um The Milky one the Milky looking one
it was okay impressed by my rap
I don't know I think okay you only had
eyes for gouda anyway
thought
I I'm not sure how to interpretate this
tweet
um didn't she tweet in English yesterday
something like I will never forget this
day and it was a picture of only her and
Gouda
and I'm like
oh man
and it's a picture from the song cover
they did but the the way the sentence
just sounds like it's about the day they
actually met right so
I'm not in that picture
oh man
I'm just so irrelevant it's so funny to
me oh man but I don't know it may have
been about the song cover I don't know
it's kind of weird though if it's about
the song cover weird thing to write I
think
let's let's just say it was about the
song cover yeah yeah
ah man
why were you not there on that day
I really needed you
oh man
anyway
where is the Lionel
um
Colosseum do you know
don't my
yeah
where I would be fighting for Kyle
attention too but she always can have a
kind of attention I feel like maybe in
that situation she would have you know
been like I don't need it today
third wheel that's rough but hell yeah
up left from below kokiti Forest
under the surface Coliseum ah okay okay
yeah yeah wait where was that something
round
where is the surface Colosseum
[Music]
those are the mazes
West
this one maybe
that must be it
okay
okay but before we do that we cook
some things
ah
ah funny
we have to cook let me cook we have to
prepare well
[Music]
I would say you still have us but that's
not much so instead you still have Cali
Cali
um I mean
we get along really well but it's it's a
different kind of relationship uh Cali
has different feelings towards me than
for example
it would be nice to
have someone who sees me the way okay
I don't think there's anyone who sees me
like that
must feel nice what does another one
[Music]
what
yeah and you guys you promo
yeah that could get pretty close
[Music]
um
someone who
I guess what would you describe it as
maybe like a fascination
kind of like a like a fan
because I I would say that's like
yeah
adoration yeah adoration and admiration
mixed
could get pretty close
only I want to say only because it only
feels that for anyone
not particularly for me
um
no I would say that's different too
no no no lean and me that's different
she doesn't
I don't think she admires me
she possibly adores me
but it's different though
um
it's the same you feel towards Ahmed
oh yeah pretty pretty close
yeah
kind of
[Music]
yeah they should in future how long live
auditions or Halloween edition they
should ask do you do you adore and
admire anybody in whole life
[Music]
in an area with water even if it's
really real I want to see it myself even
the picture would do
it really water you mean the the big
whirlpool
that uh okay
eventually maybe I'll bring it back to
you
made the court looks really happy here
good for them wasn't there a cooking
space in here in the tree
uh
wait where how did I get inside again
was it here what
how to get inside here there
hi hi
you got mushrooms good for you
I am so happy for you
okay
and now we cook wow
I was reminded that we may want to cook
some things of sundelions
[Music]
no
oh
cool sword thank you
[Music]
four and six
yeah same thing
um
can I add another tomato
make it stronger
mm-hmm
that is a good one
foreign
not to get caught fighting Gloom enemies
without Sunderland Foods
would you want to try cooking any of
these recipes IRL well not exactly like
here
you know I would have to add some
ingredients but yeah
it'd be fun
there is one EU country that don't get
along with austrians it would be funny
if some new Hollow EU girl is from the
nationality or the cruel irony
no
no think so are you talking about
something specific
[Music]
no no we don't have any issues like that
but if anybody I mean
if we do then that's purely political
and not really influencing anyone's
no
there is no beef
nobody gives a [\h__\h] about where you're
from anywhere here
doesn't matter like if I hear you're
from any country in Europe and it
doesn't link
foreign I don't think
you could say any country and it would
make me feel negatively about you no
obviously it would be concerning
otherwise
with my truffles
[Music]
that gives extra Hearts right
plus four
hmm
um
Overkill
oh
comment is this plus nine and full
recovery
no point adding regular food to hearty
meals oh okay
six
that's five only wow
I was just reading the comment that was
probably with blight you mean this
uh-huh
not fly fruit fly go away fruit fly
oh well
it is what it is I thought I could mix
those
I was wrong fruit fly
oh nine
that's better than the truffles
hmm
do I still have space for more food
because then I'll make
one more
of this
foreign
let's see how's our inventory looking
we have a lot of
extra hard ones
and one two three four five six seven
eight nine
[Music]
ten
yeah 10 Gloom recovery ones I have space
for one more
here's a big one plus 15.
um maybe I can eat some
no they're all they're all good nothing
that takes up space too much I think
okay
would you say I'm ready to go to the
linels
I also have maybe we could go to one
more Island
it's only been four hours anyway we
could go to one more Islands to get a
couple more fairies because I have four
now I think
foreign
[Music]
useless
what do you mean
how is it used how could it be useless
well any anything would erase it once
you got once
insta destroys like what
okay then I can use it for the gliox I
guess I don't know what the [\h__\h]
yeah it takes away
I need a [\h__\h]
man
okay I'll I'll try to find one more
easily accessible island with fairies
um
I don't know what about here
I don't think that had fairies
um
[Music]
that could have fairies
I went that's where I just was
maybe here
[Music]
this one probably has fairies
and that was the water temple what the
[\h__\h] this one this one must have fairies
at least on one of them
no
Maybe
or this one
Skydive racing around
oh my eyes are so tired what about what
about this one
this one right this has to have it
oh free teleports and placed one by the
fairies
um
more oh the heart like I don't think I
went to the Heart Like yet
[Music]
Aries
please
this is not the one I just went to right
[Music]
where is this
uh they still show up until 5 PM
well they they're not around in the
night time
they don't shop unless I have for lesson
free
oh
oh okay
what okay
I mean okay yeah I get it because
otherwise you can like spam them
all right
so uh I marked this one that's where it
should be
I can go from here maybe
I'm gonna go maybe I should prepare a
couple more
weapons
[Music]
you can't have more than four oh really
okay
we wanna
maybe use this
I hope I have good base weapons left
over but
we have
um
the Gerudo one strong Fusion again
all right which one was Stronger
um blue white white must be stronger
is it or maybe
whatever
90.
and then
um
I don't know if it's so smart
to put it on it's all night weapon base
should I
yeah white is stronger
um
oh well okay I'll keep this one for now
maybe I'll find something on the way
foreign
I'm so nervous
ah
but I got good upgrades and [\h__\h] oh
and I can save them between
they drop weapons and strong fuse Parts
yeah
make sure you're safe yes
I will
yeah I have three arrows that can one
shot ah you mean
hey
I was gonna say yeah but I don't wanna
use them for this but like what else am
I gonna use them right
okay they also wash out the gliox
no way right
oh hoarding
it should ah you get no drops oh yeah I
do want the drops
I don't want the drops
okay
from which side do you enter
another light Road would be nice
South Side okay
I thought so
there's a weapon up there I think or is
it no no it's just uh
I don't even know what it is
[Music]
who wants
no
no I'll keep that one for
a while that tangent I'll keep that one
I think
well I have to keep that one
ah did I tell you
you may have heard
that she was dressed like super
not fancy but like you can tell that she
put a lot of effort and thought into
looking cute and edgy that day yeah yeah
if you heard from Ahmed uh
uh you know what her manager said
to me
oh
that she doesn't always put this much
effort into it and she kind of like then
then I asked oh wait is it for me
and it was a yes
try to impress me
and make a good impression cute
put a lot of effort
into her outfit and I must say it paid
off she looked really cute
the clothes she was wearing I would say
there was a time where I may have worn
something like that too that's a little
bit I know it looks kind of like
Harajuku straight fashion
but
I liked that too but I would usually
when I would wear a hard you could
straight fashion I would go for a more
like brighter look I think but she had a
more like edgy dark look
but I like that too yeah it's cute
I gotta go this way
I wish I was
um
I think she
enjoyed the
the collab I hope so and I let her
listen to my songs and she really liked
them and her manager also
like them
everybody was listening
I gave her I listened to two of the
songs because
I think they were both
like something she would like hey
horsies
lucky
um no I think that's only really lacks
my music which I'm really happy about I
wouldn't say that it's the
you know a situation like with okayu and
Kura
so no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no
I've been
here
free shot five shot though I guess I
would have noticed that
love Halloween and releasing free APS
all around the same time Oh you mean
because Bales and Cali
yeah but I mean Cali is always releasing
something
and I had no idea that Bells was working
on something honestly
that caught me really off guard like I I
heard about it
on I think the concert day
that the song that she was performing
was you know from her EP and that that
was
uh
yeah
being released
very soon
I had no idea
they're really edgy though yeah I really
liked the one she performed in the
concert
I was like what is this song
I've never heard it before
it must be a cover of another whole life
member
a yo
Where'd I go
did I fly down
I made my toy
oh yeah guys
um I saw that she's like doing uh like
merchandise and um
for the EP
and then I was thinking for a moment
like oh should I be doing that too
uh because like we didn't talk about it
me and Gemma and so on that that would
even be like a possibility or so and
then maybe I should do it we didn't talk
about it but I was like maybe if I do
that it will help me
get back some funds for the music videos
because like usually merchandise you
know we get a decent cut from it
but no
um
I'm even though that would probably help
me I will not do it because
um you know I just in this month I'm
releasing birthday merchandise
in September there will be Anniversary
merchandise so in between in August
where I want to release the album I
don't want to like
pressure you guys or burden you guys or
make you feel like you have to get
another merchandise you know
it's a lot that's like three months in a
row of merchandise I don't want to do
that to you guys
but if you want to support the mvs you
know
super chats are always an option even
though it doesn't go 100 to me and I am
paying 100 for the MV questionable
but you know there's ways
other ways than the merchandise
where's the entrance
should I go to the root first
foreign
I got the birthday merch list thank you
I missed the answer I walked by
spanking High I'm Skye thank you
thank you
yeah I don't know it would probably also
be kind of a little bit too late for
organizing merchandise now but at least
and also jenma told me like Bales has an
EP that's kind of cheaper than an album
and so you guys are already gonna pay
more for the album than for the EP by
default so
yeah I don't know I don't know oh I
think I see the entrance
let's go let's get Facebook
[Music]
come on
Come On Let's Get Physical
[Music]
dancing
don't make such a big deal
ass can you put the secret still okay
you don't know about a physical release
you don't know
no you don't know thank you oh my god
Slavic fellow thank you
that's a red one
my polish friend
can you can you just go here
yeah I'm pushing for physical for sure
um I mean it won't be in stores like in
persons doors
but you can order online a physical
version
so I have been
promised
thank you Jim Tracy yay
where the [\h__\h] is this entrance
do I have to climb up
probably
no okay
now
you mean the things that need the
special players no no we're not doing
that
laughs
[\h__\h] you
why why no weapon what
are you carrying no weapon
[\h__\h] off
[Music]
VHS no
no no vanilla no VHS
no I only sell practical things
thank you Derek thank you
MV funds let's go let's go
kanauru said
when I asked currently
can I get a discount for two MBS he said
yes
[Music]
thank you
thank you for giving me a chance like
honestly I'm so grateful I don't know
how much to Discount this but
motion for the memberships
yeah that is so nice
because
I really want to make two now
I need it for my own satisfaction
here
is this the red path
is it up there I'm so confused
I should just fly up probably
light across it's in the middle of a
lake
ah
is it not so elevated
as I think it is
I stayed on the map too but
yeah
uh-huh
water
or here probably
yeah
I I I I I I I I definitely chose the
wrong path to walk over oh
okay
you guys thank you
I also have been like bagging
the next time I come to Japan to just
you know get
um
10 minutes
of recording time because I already have
to go to the studio for something anyway
so I'm like can you guys close I don't
need a director I don't need camera
movement I don't need anything I just
need to somebody press the record button
and uh yeah let me record my
choreography
that I've been begging for that spare me
10 minutes please like I understand them
not being able to do
something where there's need where it is
here
need for directors
oh
okay
but I don't need a director Young
I don't need
some time and someone who presses one
button and I guess I need to put on the
suit and somebody needs to help me put
on all the things and all that but if I
do it on the day where I'm already in
the studio anyway you know you know min
max
quack quack quack quack
I didn't even get that much practice
[Music]
PGW 135 thank you what
curly fries you you straighten curly
fries
why is your job title not in your name
it's unclear to me well thank you so
much your rent money oh no and 502 thank
you oh my God you guys remind me of how
many super chats I have to read
um
oh I've landed right no not right there
ah
okay guys
I will [\h__\h] everything up because I'll
get nervous and I'll drop my spaghetti
when did you save like uh is there a
specific timing to save
like after
I know right after the Lionel but is
there like a specific specific timing
um thank you thank you
uh I was it's automatic
oh
but you lose the loot
eh what do you mean I lose the loot
they drop if you use that save
the loot they already dropped or the
loot they will drop
you know all the same subscribe to drops
in safe manual
grab the loot and then manual save
okay okay okay I'll try
let's go thank you guys for the super
chats please I already got so many uh
please stop I will never get to read
them wait wait at least waits to send
them until the first MB comes out okay
don't send them now
I'll never finish
we'll send them no
no please have mercy
okay
um
take it back take it back
take that back right now
I was saying this
yeah and then switch always to this one
perhaps
foreign
you little shits I swear to God for real
send them when the Envy comes out
man
I'll never finish them
okay I'll be fine I'll be fine I'll be
fine I'll be fine I'll be fine I'll be
fine I'll be fine we'll be fine I'll be
fine
oh yeah yeah oh yeah yeah how
intimidating
the Dodge
oh let's go
uh wait uh
okay chill chill chill
[Music]
maybe try a flurry Rush
um
[Music]
what
okay well
oh
nice Dodges though yeah yeah
should I already eat
it's not so bad yet
[Music]
foreign
shush
improved Larry wash with fresh weapon is
opaque
damn that only took one flurry rush and
one riding uh portion
he's mine
I think it's not worth eating just yet
unless I have a small one
eight plus no wait I have like yeah
these plus ones but they have full
recovery
ah what but what if I if he's already
out there like
[Music]
laughs
okay okay okay
really weak Lionel uh stuff so if I save
now that's fine
I can't I guess huh
I don't lose anything yeah apparently it
was the first time you killed a normal
one the most basic one
okay that wasn't so bad that wasn't so
bad that wasn't so bad that wasn't so
bad
Bring It On which color is this blue
[Music]
I don't know why I go to this menu but
maybe it calms me down
good damage good damage
[Music]
ouch
am I still pretty good HP is still
pretty good HP
wow
wow wow wow
I don't need to eat yet
[Music]
he's almost dead
okay
oh [\h__\h] okay sorry sorry sorry
ah this one should be good
thank you for the rest of my channel
[Music]
oh my God
easy clap
[Music]
let's see
[Laughter]
how many more free
more
I have still four fairies
three more a white a silver
and an armored silver one
at least I don't like in other
um and other cool Sims that at the end
they all send
them all at you but in this one I guess
they only send a
armored one I've never fought an armored
one before that's kind of scary
oh my God
where is he
had the right weapon right now
ouch
[Music]
I swear I'm dodging I'm trying to
this is where I catch Ross
hey I'm too late I'm just too late
[\h__\h] oh it's [\h__\h] me over
oh
[Music]
gotta go to the offensive sometimes
let's go
[Applause]
back to the normal weapon
[Music]
you [\h__\h] idiot sandwich
Mamma Mia
well that actually could be good but
um
[Music]
I'm trying to min max my food
that's okay okay I'll take the defense
up
it's just for a little bit but
no why I did so well before what's going
on
I'm stupid
I wish he would jump further away ah why
why why why why why why why why why
my food
okay
[Music]
yeah
I won't hold your bow yeah I keep on
like trying to switch back anyway to the
normal weapon my trunk
please
he was so close
[Music]
what is he doing
where is he
does he want me to come closer
fine
[Music]
what was that
what does that mean this did he like
like go so far outside of the Coliseum
that it counts as like I'm not here
anymore
[\h__\h] man
what's going on yeah he got stuck stupid
[\h__\h]
I can't go
[Music]
I'm losing all my food
I looked at the check
[Music]
thank you
okay why did I do that I don't know I
don't know I don't know
yeah
thank you hylia Shield
me a flurry Rush please
run
[Music]
all the explosion is coming
no problem I'm really far
[Music]
yes
[\h__\h]
[Music]
what a weird Fight Man the other one was
way better oh my God
[Music]
okay I shouldn't rely a bit more on
shooting him shooting them I guess
generally
[Music]
um
okay here comes full maximum Giga epic
damage
he should hopefully die
yeah okay
okay two more and those are really rough
ones how much food do we have we have
fairies also still
four fairies we have
um
wait ooh Gloom recovery we're not
looking good
but the fairies also of course recover
the Gloom right
um
I might have sold some crypto bones yeah
okay
[Music]
wait uh
ah one weapon
okay come on
I'll Focus I'm focused
scared he's scared of me
big Miss from you son
oh that was in the space
I'm so organized
[Music]
okay
risky touristy
touristy
[Music]
might eat that
or maybe a defense one oh three times
defense up four minutes
that's good
okay
get up
maybe after the fire I tried again
wait
uh what's our weapon that makes up for
that this one
I think so
that's a two-handed one though I prefer
a faster one but I don't have anything
already right now
um they're both that's basically same
weapon oh
63 on this one hmm
yeah
or Masa soy doll
it is still fused to the Buckle blind
horn
I know how much
like total damage that does though
but yeah it's better to against Gloom
right let's try a muscle shirt should be
not too bad
the fusion isn't too bad either hmm
60. oh okay that's decent
what are you doing
what is he doing
oh
let's go let's go let's go this is going
pretty well it's going better than the
one before I think
yeah yeah yeah
all right
I mean all these Dodges are like well
very safe plate oh explosion coming up
too low okay
it's almost dead though
when I'm dodging okay-ish
which is sad
oh
that's my chance
look at this and watch and learn
this is how you mount a horse
and catch him a lesson
about horsing around
master sword and Tyler Shield
very sexy
what's this yeah okay oh yeah
hi hi hi hi hi hi hi
not that yet
yeah that was pretty
proud
oh
I could not choose to quickly fuse
something but I don't like the base
weapons so time to save
yeah but the armored one like do how do
I do I have to get rid of this armor if
yes how
because like the armored block blends
muklins
it was a really rough I have to bump out
of him only once
and then it's gone nowhere
oh
hammers or uh-huh
so I could also like try to flurry Rush
with like one of these weapons no
okay okay
bomb Arrow until he breaks okay
I can try but a bit difficult one he's
always like out and about doing whatever
he thinks is best
okay but we got done okay give me your
fangs
quickly
hi hi oh God that's so scary
wait have we not fun I'll still want
either yet I feel like we did
[Music]
oh
I need I need
a spiked iron ball Hammer Mamma Mia I'm
scared
Lord help me save me pray for me
um
[Music]
maybe I don't know should I
just in the beginning until the armor is
gone try to steam
[Music]
you might one shot me I still have some
defense up
and I still have four you can't watch
like me I still have four fairies we're
good we're good
he's like he looks like he's going
straight for an attack man I'm so scared
okay
um
still like he doesn't get phased by it
he continues writing straight at me oh
whoa whoa okay
okay with a blunt weapon actually oh
yeah yeah
I can ride him too
oh [\h__\h]
is it now just just a white
lineup or silver one it's a white one
right
oh my God that was really good that was
really good I can't mess it up now
oh I have one that clears 15. hmm
no we can't mess it up now I have four
fairies okay don't drink it
he's got no armor but he's got this
scary spiky thing
yeah the weapon is huge so is dodging
gonna be more difficult
possibly
no this is the same hitbox
okay
hi
do you see how I always carefully adjust
the camera
time after sprinting
out
yeah
yeah okay
thank you
foreign
[Music]
defense is right about to run out but I
don't want to replace it just yet
um
what is that
man I'm such a gamer
ah he's leaving me an easy opening there
[Music]
cheeky Wawa I knew I would get
they travel for that okay well I cannot
feel that
only
oh was that tooling oh
she's tooling honestly
it's such a chad
say if we safe guys
all right
I can't make it
ah that confused me
whoa he was already getting back up
[Music]
no fairy
lost
time
I want to bring all the weapons
oh my God
that's crazy I did so well even though I
was panicking there was like I think the
second or the third I was like
scrambling
first one yeah no fairy one first try
but yeah this the last two and the first
one I think
generally there was just one where I was
like for some reason doing everything
wrong
and then I got a bit more like careful
and the last one definitely like damn I
I couldn't have
gone no
gone much better
I mean of course it could but
I want the bow
foreign
[Music]
what's to drop this is Savage Lionel
ball so 32
should I get rid of I have too many of
these anyway I'm not using them anyway
higher maximum number of parts
Drop The Demon King the duplex too
oh yeah it's only 14 I guess
and that normal line over I don't need
the normal Lino bow
it was lying around I I think a couple
more bows
the mighty Lionel ball
I'm space for Shields The Savage liner
ball
more line of freons
uh oh the normal line I don't need the
low normal
I think that's
everything interesting that I left over
wait what is this
can I use that his armor
it looks like I confused it to something
is that even good
[Music]
add to a shield
I barely used Shields bud
oh
ah thank you you have mod open the chest
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah one afternoon I
actually don't know what's inside
but come on this must be the most
difficult call Sam so it must come with
a pretty good reward if already the
other colosseums that I did had pretty
hype rewards oh is this Majora's Mask
[Music]
an eerie mask passed down from ancient
times wearing it makes it harder for
certain enemies to spot you certain ones
wait who
it's a rapper refined which one so which
ones
because there's one like specific ones
for each enemy type right basically but
basically all of them even linos
pretty much all
oh
non-bosses are lionels bosses
kind of aren't they kind of bosses
doesn't work with cases Lionel's just
for a moment aha
um
Linus can spot you from as far away with
that on oh okay so it helps a little bit
but
not completely okay cool
we got the cool ask Majora's Mask let's
go
so that is one of my goals ticked off
my next goal is to fight and kill at
least one gliac
there's no glio color Sandra I know
there's a glioc in the Colosseum but
there's no you know
right
what what uh what I mean
hopefully
kingly according
to die rules my rules
no no no no no [\h__\h] it's so hot in here
I hate it
go bust
nah
not oh
there's a glare gonna depths too oh is
it like a Gloom glioc that would be cool
ice Cleo has the best loot oh wait which
one is the easiest
because let's at least start with uh an
easy one
but I would assume that they're all not
easy
fire
couldn't I even wear the fire armor
while fighting him
does that block the fire damage
fire
doesn't work man
okay which one where is the fire one I
feel like I probably saw him before
I know
um
bridge bridge of hylia
is it is it this one I don't know
it's not this one
which of hylia
ah this one probably
my closest
to the stable
now look hot though
that was fun
like challenging and fun and frailing
I did not want to
fail
and thus I did not
replenish from food through yeah we
gotta make some new food obviously
we're healing back automatically at
least
yeah
oh yeah yeah yeah we always can come
back to farm little Parts I know I know
yeah but I mean my plan is to end the
game pretty soon not because I really
want to end it I could continue playing
this for like 10 more parts
but
try to end it
the series has been really good thing
thank you
all right
sure
I just want to say what you got
um damn
not interested thanks
would you guys say one glioc is more
difficult than the whole Lionel
Colosseum
I feel like maybe the difficult part
about it is to like you know I don't
know it's huge no
hmm
wait
it's easier
oh yeah if you don't know what you're
doing yeah exactly so like because they
fly around and I don't know
sounds rough
[Music]
that was difficult
y shot his eyes used to go okay yeah
yeah I was gonna use key size anyways
but I don't have so many anymore when
I've look his eyes
the aracuda ones work too right and
these ones well that's still even in
total not that much I feel like oh wait
there's a couple more here ah wait I
have elemental ones yeah
Elemental
it's Elementary in it
okay
hopefully that's enough
um
what was I gonna do I cook
oh
really
gives me some extra
sure give me Melania wait Melania bent
yeah is it only good for the horse or so
good for me I don't remember
[Music]
debut um
good for all okay
[Music]
what what's good for the goose is good
for the gander instead of saying
it's scary
black nun
I never heard that before
well not like you know ignore my extra
Heights right like the lionels would do
Gloom linels
so
we don't need anything gloomy
just normal food right
now
[Music]
I am just doing side stuff today I'm not
doing main story stuff
I'll take out the x-rays from the shoe
power alone no okay intimidating
um
interesting I'll make this
I'm gonna make some meat meat meat no
products are not my thing really
I love the game I love doing like side
quests and all kinds of exploration and
shrines are fine too but collects
[Music]
no if they're on my way and they're not
uh bring me from point A to B clock
then they're okay
too many and then there's probably [\h__\h]
reward if if any reward at all
[Music]
if there was a really good reward not
even then
it's working they're everywhere there's
too many it's Overkill
it's Overkill
I mean the good reward is until you max
out your inventory
but that's it
that I can tolerate
so true so true
what do we got
um foreign
banana one salt oh
try that oh yeah cause I got so many
bananas
one salt
y banana
I have to use up these bananas wow
I'm gonna do something wrong
because now it turned into something
else
or was it always this and I just didn't
I imagined bananas
I mean it's fine it's the same effect
or is it the order that I put the salt
first ah
you guys
have been mighty banana
no way
I imagined the banana I thought there
was a banana outcome
it's all in my head
God damn it
um
[Music]
why not
make a couple of these
and
[Music]
now there's one too a lot of I'm making
a lot of attack food
normally I didn't care much about that
but now I do how's it looking
oh one more
[Music]
um
wow The Omelette art looks so good
doesn't it
looks crazy good
[Music]
okay we can go to the
scary scary
big dragon glioc should I take my horse
I should probably take my horse take my
horse
bring out my horse
I hope it's not scared when it smells
the blood of dead Lionel horses
on my hands
because it's very similar I'm sure to
normal horses
blood smell
don't worry I would never hurt you
golden horse you're my Flex horse
I need you to flex
on people randomly oh I should make some
new weapons too though before we start
the fight
not now though first we
go put myself
is this a muscle horse
oh I talked with Kuda about muscle
horses my little cars
yeah one of the many random wait topics
in the car ride
I think we talked about like cars in
general what car would you want and I
talked to her about you know the classic
cars and then I
I talked about GTA with her about the
muscle cars I think she didn't know
I think I had to explain to her what
that muscle car was
felt
a little bit proud
yeah you don't know what the muscle car
is
let me tell you a thing or two about
muscle cars
don't worry I got you
okay how is this gonna
like go down
is there someone there
aren't you the morning you're so
refreshing isn't it I can't see that
floating island in this rotten weather I
might as well rest until it clears up
but you're not gonna talk about the
Dragon
there is one right oh yeah
no comment about the dragon okay
wait the rain is gonna lower his fire
damage right
or not
okay he he shoots at me and I have to
dodge okay well maybe that's a bit
difficult on a bridge but okay me
I just like Pokemon duh
and base weapon I have this one
increases power of Larry Rush
not that we're gonna flurry Rush this
dragon
but
what ifs
um
[Music]
what my strongest so night
thing I guess this one
okay
I have space for one more but I don't
have a base weapon no okay
will I even be using my normal weapons
like my my close combat weapons
we have many have many cases yeah a
decent amount
should be enough for fighting one glioc
let's save
um
they could stand on the ground oh okay
okay yes yes yes you want a good two to
spin oh okay
I was wondering what the best weapon was
in this case
I don't know I want to want to use my
Lionel's weapons
I guess I can sacrifice one
hi oh am I looking at its butt
oh I am
Savage all right Lionel and kiss
eyeballs yeah you're fun okay
let's fight my friend
should I already like
get to it
did I stun it
okay
where am I
[Music]
thought it was fine
the fighting stage is too small
redo redo redo doesn't count doesn't
count
yeah you know I know those weren't dyes
but eyeballs but he wasn't flying yet so
I thought well whatever
take two
one more try
it doesn't count because I didn't die
you know this is still the first try
I did definitely not fail because I
didn't die
easy
exactly
foreign
what's going on
oh
foreign
do I aim for
the heads
or anywhere
oh this is gonna so break my weapon
does he not fire up
oh there we go
a broke I mean honestly for this one of
the normal ones works too
[Music]
is it gonna come down
and miss
now we're talking oh that's crazy
[Music]
Let's Go full out attack come on
everybody
[Music]
don't stop
go away I thanks for giving me a little
push so sweet
the tooling gets one because I I heard
one
I don't even have attack on
this will even be much faster if I had
attack on maybe I should
oh very easy
oh
I skipped the third phase
cuckoo
cuckoo guess I'll never know
hey
Google yeah those horns are looking very
cool oh we got wings too but no eyes
sad I used um
a couple
[Music]
try the king
oh okay
okay oh
oh where where where where where
do
you're just trying to the people who say
I'm ready
and the people who are like kind of
taunting me are giving me very very
conflicting feelings Vibes
bottom left Gerudo dessert okay
like around here
I don't have enough battery to reach him
oh it's in a sky island
I have enough battery
super high up
[Music]
who's up
let me get out of here
oh dragon's X this says dragon's Exile
but he's in the sky
um
then how do you get them down if he's
does he just land like here for example
we can get there with Sky Tower and spam
tune really
um
a little island on the sky okay okay
oh shouldn't I see it then on my map
you guys
you guys it's the most difficult one
you're just you just want to see me
suffer what if I wouldn't phase him huh
you're gonna regret it all
are you doing so much
yeah yeah you're you saying that I don't
trust you guys you guys are just sending
me there because you want to see me fail
yeah
hmm
[Music]
wait so people said I should go to the
Tower
wait where is the tower on this one
no that's the highlands Tower
ah here yeah from here
is it this nah
so tiny this one
has to be that one
you want to give me a good fight okay
challenge mm-hmm
let's see if I can really reach through
the tower first
I don't feel I should go for the
highlands one
God damn it how many more times am I
gonna teleport
Highlands one
ooh my weapons
um
all right
that's a good argument because
I need
more more better base weapons
I mean I don't even know why I have this
one
[Music]
didn't oh look at Landing have decent
base weapons
[Music]
um
oh boy
what's that your farm of pony die again
[Music]
I have to read some super Jazzy I'll
I'll read maybe for an hour because I
need to cook too I really have to cook
today it's okay I'm relatively motivated
to cook today
yeah but I'm obviously not gonna get
very far I I have to do a dedicated
Super Chat reading stream
for the weapons on it oh yeah
well we have nice broadsword Poco Reaper
nine and seven
oh this one is already fused too
I need to go to the depths and get
something good there
post at you what's up the post statue
also how many
[Music]
I can get a heart
I'm cooking salmon for real for real
hmm
loot World decayed Royal weapons from
the he knocks um
yeah guys I don't know about you pushing
me to go to the king one with not so
many weapons
I I just
[Music]
hmm I don't know
sounds like a scam
boo coward
well let me let me try to find some
weapons
hmm
he was all the Civil I know horns on
some stupid dragons
so I think you are you want to push me
that way yes that's exactly what I think
you're doing
I'm gonna just go towards that light
Road
and hope I find
some weapon dude
on the way
all right
[Music]
away oh yeah true Garuda web weapons are
noise
he's gonna wait
before he sees me
ah well now I could also loot the camps
no
I'm I'm normal I'm just like you that
was just because uniball has a big fat
ass okay
don't mind me stop
following friend Eva I'm never fo no
friend
they heard me talking about looting
their looting their Camp [\h__\h] is it gone
now like when you attach something and
then don't use it is it gone
no it's not nicer
that's my last one
I see
po
I see no weapons oh wait no one's also
poke I think
wait
the root is up pretty high
[Music]
where's that go
oh wow
what bow am I using okay
well
there's a dragon in here
laughs
she's literally a Gloom version of
everything
wait what the [\h__\h]
done this
it's not the clean yolk you guys we're
talking about what the hell
oh they just go and chill down here for
a bit ah it's attacking me
[\h__\h]
I'm Fernando did Zelda not tell you
why are they
excuse me why are they attacking me
ah I see a weapon
hey boss monsters those are like random
low level suckers
oh
[Music]
it's a travel attack Plus
travel is spare
oh
[Music]
I'm ready
I didn't go to this Labyrinth huh
[Music]
I heard a goat
is it yeah goat where did the root go I
lost track of the roots
uh
thanks ghost dude yeah because
let me check my
what cool
are you fighting the Dragon
[Music]
I wrote down a tangent that I wish I
could tell properly but I can't really
tell properly so I don't know how to
tell it but I want to tell it
when I was in the studio
this will be very vague because I cannot
really explain the whole situation
but there was on one of my studio days
where I was recording things
um
there was not with me
someone else had an issue
with something
um
[Music]
like a tracking issue
maybe and I had a genius idea
dad first sounded like a joke and just
funny and like hahaha Kiara you're so
funny
but I'm like wait a second wait a second
think about it
if we try this it might fix our problem
okay
so just let's just give it a try okay I
know it sounds ridiculous I know
I think it could actually work
and then reluctantly and while laughing
they tried my idea
and then everybody was
super amused but also like oh my God
this actually kind of works
and I'm like oh my God I'm a genius
I need to like get the patent patent
on this
because this is like
the most genius invention
mankind has seen
since
I don't know what could what is I don't
there's nothing more genius than my
invention
smart and humble motion tracking genius
yeah and I would be so proud of me I
think I told her possibly wait
why is this something rude I lost track
of it but I got one weapon
or maybe else maybe I have to shrine
I mean there's one here I don't know if
that's the one I saw
hmm
I guess I'll go there
it's on top of the maze
oh but does that mean I have to like
actually go through the maze properly I
don't feel like it
yeah I found a workaround to fix yeah
and it was so funny but it worked
and I'm like please please go ahead and
use it in the future if you ever stumble
upon the same problem
just think back on what I came up with
and I know I know it looks ridiculous
basically like I I thought of an
assisting item to help with a certain
motion tracking problem
that maybe some some people may
experience
and it is such a simple
object
that is cheap and everywhere like it's
one it's an object that is already by
default in the studio oh
like not by default but it's one of the
things that the studio is equipped with
a cheap easy reusable and throw away a
ball item yeah
so it's just such a
great solution
attack Apple something okay good stuff
maybe one more would be nice
because for once I'm not being spammed
with weapons
marvelous
well I cannot tell you any detail
just wanted to say I had like a stroke
of Genius you know and I'm very proud of
it
tell you thank you
I don't think I can
they were like no
no you can't kiwawa
[Music]
but what if
wait I'm going the wrong way again
yeah I just wanted to gloat
okay what else is there something I can
actually tell
um
[Music]
this one's for later
um
[Music]
ah for um you know I had several days
what's that where I would go to the
studio and do stuff
and
I felt like I can't go without some
souvenirs right
I know I probably could have like nobody
would have like fought or something's
missing
but I felt like I should bring souvenirs
so again I went to get some noise
souvenirs
I already told you the other thing
though
and every time they had I brought
different one I had the milka one
milka chocolates
and which are really simple but I think
they're really good what the [\h__\h] is
this it's a tree
um
and I brought the Mozart balls on
another day even though I I told I
warned everyone though like hey here's
some fancy Austin chocolates but just so
you know like don't expect too much of
them because I personally don't think
they're that good
I just brought them because they're like
the go-to
souvenir you know
and then another one was added the Mana
waffles again yeah what a way to sell it
right I know what is that stuff over
there
go ahead
what is that
maybe a arena for a boss fight a redo
toothpaste alarm two-faced alarm
is this the glucliac away
Bulgaria wait isn't that wait isn't that
the wind temple one yeah
let me at least activate the shrine
I don't mind refining him
hi
you would be so proud of me if you knew
that because of me
some Thai fans went to donate blood I'm
also super proud
and in that moment I knew
I [\h__\h] up
please let me reach
this
now ah
not good
yikes
Chad are you dead again
what's wrong with you recently are you
not taking care of your health are you
not eating healthy are you not sleeping
well are you not hydrating well why are
you so unstable huh what did you do
maybe you should go to the doctor
there you go
yeah I think you should go check up with
a doctor
will you listen to me hmm
will you take my advice I think you
should
otherwise
mommy kiwawa is gonna be very worried
about you and your health
you going on Tuesday okay
a doctor in the house
don't rely on doctors in houses they're
also not doing well right now
go outside your house
no kfb doctors they're also breaking
down everyone's breaking down
what
let's go
did I finish the Yeager
Side Story
I think I got pretty far but did I
finish it I probably didn't
hi
no let me finish it
[Music]
maybe that's what I should be doing
um but it's already 9 P.M
[Music]
mmm
you know the thing is
I am so far behind those super chats
that it doesn't really hurt
you know not read super chats for
another day
someone really wanted you to get the
next main story milestone
oh
well did I do it yet
um
hmm
exactly
if I have a mountain what does another
Pebble matter
yeah just having a Super Chat reading
stream that's what I gotta do
um
don't remind me of the work I'm pushing
away
um
they're just salty but riffled
potato chip
um
what do I do
what am I doing
chasm in the chasm
oh it's like maybe an underground path
what
no
oh
yummy large donut yum yum yum yum
maybe so what about the eagle
should I
[Music]
um
should I continue it
I'll continue one of these I don't know
the king I don't know anything about a
king you mean the king of Hyrule yeah
yeah no not fight him we're protecting
him
no I don't care about Colgate
ah wait we also wanted to deliverland
um that's her dad
[Music]
um
let's go there
maybe I should do another side stream
side stop stream one more one more
but I kind of wanted to move on
but not really for because I want to
move on
it's just for your guys's sake
also finishing at 10 parts feels nice
foreign
oh my God
oh yeah I think I already talked to them
off screen
is that delivering Quest
or is there like another specific one
well okay
you're in the ending after tomorrow you
mean ending tomorrow
wait I don't know what exactly you mean
oh my God addicting
I think
um
how can you notice me I'm far away and I
have the mask on
hmm
oh will he like eventually notice though
hi
sniff sniff
I'm just like you
hmm
what if I just
openly attacked as one will the other
snooters
I I guess not
not for this one because nobody was
watching
where's everybody I thought this was
like infested with enemies it's not so
bad
hi
I don't care about hiding my intentions
I'm not a fake [\h__\h]
come on come here
hi where are you looking link we just
had some
oh my armor we just had a [\h__\h] ton of
really rough fights
we're supposed to be better at fighting
now
okay
let's eat one of the attack up things
blue one
is the chat dad again say hi check say
hi to Wawa it's a silver one oh you guys
are not dead holy man
whoa
okay okay
you wanna fight
hmm
it's on
why are they so so jelly
you can like bling them with the tips of
my finger across the whole island
wow it's a silver one wow
do you have to do this alone isn't this
like maybe also part of a side quest
where
um
you
get help from
with like other Fighters
I did it alone
no okay
bananas
hi hi
I will not
act actually yeah it even took off the
mask I just realized I finally still had
the mask on but
I will not act fake I am who I am
I'll give it to you straight hey
hey fighting you with a weapon that is
made out of your own horn let's go
you like it you like it maybe you should
actually cut off your own horn and make
your own weapon out of it because as you
can see it's pretty strong
but stream two two stream Duty windy
song everybody
stream it
um
potato chips yummy
no
no no no
where's the rest of them
squash two three and four
there's a
thing here well check it out later if I
don't forget hello
you're so mean to me
no my weapon bro
rhino
[Music]
I'll pick them up so actually that one's
pretty good right now
it's running low on energy I just took
it out
huh
God damn it
fire good
no speaking of the dude song
when we were like on standby and
rehearsing for the summer
opening ceremony stream
[Music]
uh that was one of the songs that
everybody kept on singing
everybody was like vibing to the song
and then
you know how in the in the summer theme
song There's this part that's where it
goes like and how does it go
where is it let me let me try to
remember the song
[Music]
foreign
so during the rehearsal several times we
had to listen to
um the songs instrumental uh and also
the sun version because you know it was
in the kind of teaser and it was also in
the 4D teaser that kind of remained and
it was also in the
um
fish
it was also in in the actual music video
obviously
so there were like many opportunities
where they would play it for us and we
had to listen to it just watch the video
again and again and also during the
actual stream
so every time because sometimes what
what did I say I didn't sneeze
every time when they would play it
like everybody would like pretty quietly
sit and watch but then every time that
Parts oh I took every time that one part
came up
how did I get in there
every time that one pocket came up they
everybody like every every time since it
worked the first time
and everybody was like oh that's so
funny that we all started at the same
time
they would do it again
so one time everybody's like
and everybody laughs like oh that's so
funny though we all said the same thing
just this one part
and then we did it again and again and
again because they played it again and
again again everybody was like really
loudly and like energetically funny
it was so cute
oh okay let's get some help with some uh
fun items shall we
are puff shrimp yeah yeah
oh I could have done a sneak strike wait
here
nice can I still do it too late
wait was there some explosives here
I think I wear some explosives oof
oh nice shot
he was about to hit me
oh no Poise man no pores you liking
pools you gotta put some stat points
into that big recommend
foreign
there he goes
oh nice weapon drops I can't
it's like wait
isn't this weapon
for future one of my special weapons I
don't want to lose maybe I should be
careful
it reminds you of ff16 the combat really
well I'm curious about that if you say
that
foreign
should I be careful about that one
no no no no no no no no no no no
maybe I keep that one actually
[Music]
hey give me that
push
[Music]
what's left only you no there should be
more
where's the rest anymore on though yep
no one oh it's a little selfless
oh
the duck duck claim I will love ff16 you
think so
well I hope so
I
the reason why I want to start it
specifically next week I I have actually
I just wanted to wait because I was
obviously traveling and everything but
there's another reason why I'm looking
forward to starting it next week
hey
but I'm not 100 sure
if it will work out where's the last one
no one up here right
now
in the well
ah can't wait to see you played
have you guys been playing it because
it's a good time to like get ahead of me
and then don't get spoilered
now is the time
why is it so steamy is there like a hot
spring in there
you're hiding because you're scared huh
you little [\h__\h]
you're letting all your friends die even
I don't know if you can even call it
friends though
you beat it what how can you beat it a
month ago PS5 you got a little PS5 oh
only PS5 right now
you're closing in on the end okay good
what did I get
for that trouble hmm
I haven't used my PS5 much so far so
that would be nice
they don't sell in your country you
couldn't find a copy of the document
but I can buy it in the online store
Ryan
let's go
get done this lone Warrior showed up and
just killed them all nice sick
mohawk
I heard he also just killed
um like a million liners and a big glioc
he's on the road
oh yeah the tropical version I love it
okay I'll go to the King Leon
[Music]
oh
100 GB okay
thanks for the warning
don't Dodge the smoke huh
yeah I should get more key size probably
right
I'm gonna go to caves
Maybe
Diablo 4
oh
I could easily do that
if I play alone
but the group I think it'll be very
difficult to get it together
foreign
[Music]
going to Japan again so soon and then
and then to London
so
um
[Music]
yeah I can't play the game much right
now
or any game for that matter
I'm coming to visit you you're joking
but I'm for real coming
do I not get yeah
a reward
yeah I booked your place at Airbnb don't
you didn't you see it
that was me
um
foreign
I have to help her building oh my God
[Music]
my mouth is getting so sore from the
salt hmm
restore the restaurant in a lucky
treasure shop
you enjoyed this okay
vlogs
and hiding rice ooh rice okay how much
logs don't lid yeah
stop it just take my help I got nothing
else to do except killing the King Leo
[Music]
um
foundations okay
15 logs
you don't want the palm trees
20 bundles of hat
sure wait so
I'm guessing that the normal trees are
kind of far maybe up on the mountains
though
I can like drop them maybe
[Music]
um
not far
oh okay
[Music]
um
like realistically speaking can you
actually not build like proper houses
with palm trees
[Music]
thank you
no the shape makes it difficult oh
wait so the logs I have to roll them
down can I I guess I could fuse them all
and then carry them down
or even make a car out of it
just drive it down and then disassemble
wow I'm cooking
oh
you did the same
ah
um
oh my God it's so salty
almost as salty as almond after she
plays FPS games
thank you
that is not much of a tree is it
there's two
and a couple over there
oh
um maybe at Mario Party
some logs at the shoreline but eh how
many
uh it's so salty
um
oh my God
I'm gonna die from Salt overdose
I should stop I'm sure you guys are not
enjoying this but I can't stop
okay I'll stop I stopped
[Music]
um
I stopped my cup
foreign
does this make an ax
it's so nice
no
why the stones around all of these trees
why don't you make them
into ax materials
why
um
foreign
[Music]
now
oh there's a interesting opening over
there and it must be
like to explore
trees grow back when I'm not looking
I'm not sure about now
not that fast
oh that's not looking good ah oh Faker
huh
[Music]
that's not very pog
but for that's the first time I actually
killed one of these trees properly
instead of just trying to slowly kill
them with fire because I thought that's
the only way for some reason in my head
that's the first time I made quick
business out of them
foreign
[Music]
that is
Seven Trees I think
how big of a car should this be
EP or I just I always honestly I don't
even mind look like carrying them
while walking
yeah we will make a Euro Truck Simulator
how about that what
I don't want to use out my new fancy
weapons for this
are we oh you can blast them with ridges
lightning
the master sword
does it work what's the message
is it safe to just drop them do they
like just
Fall Apart
and and crumble happy belated birthday
thank you oh thank you you were you were
at the theater nice
I'm sure that Santiago was there
and I mean surely a lot of other higher
ups saw it that they're like okay okay
maybe next time bigger venue
they just needed like a one-time proof
you know
next time we go big or we go home
also I
while I was in Japan
I uh
pitched my idea of
huge humongous
virtual us on screens
I pitched it to
um like higher-ups
who could maybe consider it
unfortunately I was looked at with
uh laughing eyes and I don't think
they're gonna do it
um
I doubt it will happen unfortunately one
can I like uh keep it in batches
mm-hmm
wait how many is this one two three four
five six seven
nice it counts as seven right not as one
eight eight okay that was eight seven
more oh
um here's some rice I don't know how
much though
seven more wait that was all the rest I
had enough rice
I got 20 bundles of rice
oh nice okay we just need some more you
guys said there's some
normal wood on the shore ah
that is oh there's a chest there too
foreign
please give me a weapon
ah five five rupees that's kind of a
troll
s
that's never chest though
if I walk too far
we'll just disappear
are there more logs
yes
cute oh that's actually wow well
programmed
that I walk away and he recognizes that
I place something close by wow
[Music]
what MSG sphere in Las Vegas that sounds
sphere that already sounds crazy
that sounds
really fancy
[Music]
let's fuse the student Master Sword
20K
MO
hmm 20K wow
wait how much was makuhari I don't know
if we can fill as many as you know in
Japan
okay
I think 10K no problem 15K okay okay
kitty kitty Maybe
okay go highly close
can fill 20K
are you are you sure
[Music]
makahari is way under that
but I feel like easily in Japan they
could easily do like 30k
I need those like three more logs but
I might go back to the OG spots
entire venue was packed yeah although I
think like not every seat was ideal wow
I feel like it's better to at least fill
up those seats that are not ideal
um from for like the view then keeping
them empty right but yeah I feel bad
that some some
uh seats may have not been so good I was
on the edge it was really good really
edge of the first floor
front middle back
people bought there were 10 cables
second floor Edge you thought the view
was good I was first floor Edge but it
was quite brilliant
because we were like a little bit
worried about that
wait the VIP was where where are those
too expensive they're way too expensive
like somebody paid but I guess more than
one person can
go in there right
so you can share the the cost
um still wait where's the dude where am
I
where am I
I'm lost
or maybe there
full of Hardcore fans
[Music]
you got special service
it got tacos what
600 700 per person in the booth
I mean
thank you
that's fine maybe if you really really
really want to be there and had no other
way to get a ticket
oh
free more come on
come on
better than paying scalpers true true
I don't know about 20K guys we gotta go
step by step I don't trust
me I feel like maybe it would be nicer
to go with like a 10 or 15K venue but
then do two days instead of one day
I would feel better about that
yeah
I hope we can do that next year
help
you can make that happen
2024 still so far to go
four Fest always happens like around the
same forfeit like the Fest always
happens around the same time kind of
right I wonder if in the future
ours will also always happen around the
same time
like close to ax
I think like obviously
putting the date and the location close
to ax there was obviously you know some
kind of thought to put into that
um but if we change location then we
don't have to go after the
ax date right
so
would you guys prefer to not be around
ax because I think a lot of people were
able to combine it at least and that's
kind of nice
if you already want to go to ax anyway
then it's a like a good way you can
combine two trips into one to come from
further away
but yeah
I heard a lot of people got covered from
Ax or other concert I don't know and and
and very crowded
and La I heard many stories my personal
experience was not so bad but I guess I
I I stayed in
say for every areas but I I heard a lot
of
funny
references on Twitter and so on about
uh
L.A
yeah I saw so many positive test tweets
I hope you guys are okay if you if you
have it then please rest well okay
take your time to rest
Milo
[Music]
um don't call me this year apparently
there was a lot of stuff going very
wrong from what I've seen so in
hindsight I'm like maybe maybe it's good
that I didn't go
because I wanted to go but the concert
overlapped and work in Japan overlapped
but yeah there's a lot of bad [\h__\h] going
on which
isn't always like this crazy crazy
[Music]
oh hello hello it's more than two rings
it was like five incidents that I heard
of
of like money being stolen
and threats of like
um ripping off wigs off of cosplayers
heads
that was beforehand not sure if it
actually happened
foreign
[Music]
this group of like pretty normal
like not really convention going looking
people
where I guess they found it funny to
yeah
do stuff like that so they that wasn't
apparently the first time that they were
threatening with stuff like that
um
a day uh
we're like threatening all over social
media
to yeah rip run up to cosplayers and rip
off their wigs
and but people shared it so much that I
think everybody knew about it and um
maybe they didn't do it I don't know I
didn't hear about it actually happening
[Music]
yeah because they didn't like cosplayers
and I guess they don't like they
probably see all of that as weirdos
[\h__\h] weirdos I'm gonna ruin their
time
thank you
foreign
going on
so I dodged a bullet
although I'm absolutely appreciate it
since we just talked about dates for
future en concert
I would appreciate it if it wouldn't
overlap
please
I want to go
um
and in my NYC that sounds fun
having a concert in New York sounds like
fun
it's okay there's only like really tiny
small bits left
I just want to clean out the bag
oh yeah that's East Coast huh
each clothes would be very happy
you don't get far
um
it depends on a lot of like
um more beginner cosplayers don't
um
what's the word they don't
[Music]
um
fixate I don't know
properly secure they're wigs that well
well like don't secure it at all
and then it's really easy to rip it off
and then others who secure it well
or like medium well
it's actually going to hurt because like
they got clips and everything connected
to their actual hair
and maybe even like glue and [\h__\h]
so
I don't know I don't I wouldn't wish
that on anyone
um
okay
foreign
I think if that would have happened then
you could have called the police on them
because that's assault fail
I would say so
okay you got the logs you got the rice
what do you want next
let me see if I can finish this Quest
[Music]
the guy that punched me that's seven
years in prison
[Music]
how hard did that guy punch you
seven years that's wow that's quite
something
nice Foundation can I get a house here
instead I want a house on the beach
instead of my house somewhere else I
don't know where it even is
[Music]
um
which building should we get to work on
establishment
um the lucky treasure shop sounds
interesting
or it's in a ship
that looks like it needs a lot of
materials
oh yeah tell me
okay though follow me
oh
all right here we are
hmm once upon a time a palm tree grew up
through the building's Second Story roof
it used to be wait I think I started in
breath of the wild Maybe
[Music]
oh
I'm thinking this will use a lot from
the palm tree as the central pillar for
the lucky treasure trap too but this
building is Big so rather than connect
the roof and the floor the palm tree
lock would go in the plant pot
on the second floor
and through the hole in the roof do I
have to do that like manually
it's easy enough to get a palm tree log
from the palm trees growing around here
but how are we going to get the log into
the plant pot and throw the hole in the
roof okay I have to do it manually no
problem though
yo with the master sword is like a one
hit
let's see I need to get it on top first
right
on top of the ship
um
easy enough
you're sad what you sat for the wood
what what what what
you sad for the word
we ain't no saplings
we're at kfb here there's no mercy at
kfp you know that hey wait that's
actually I can't get it through the hole
I can't get a higher
well okay that's fine I guess I gotta
maybe go up here
do it from here
we are brutal
at kfb but also very loving and caring
and sweet
we can be we can be very nice if we want
to
[Music]
but we don't always want to
go oh
he regulator noise
this Quest is quite well done
[Music]
huh
[\h__\h]
suddenly so manly
no more singing
I did that
the biggest building in this Village so
we're turning into its former glory
wasn't easy but the owner is gonna love
it
Cloyne
who's calling chummy which we're going
and came running I can't believe I can
open my shop again I never thought this
day would come this place means
everything to me oh my God thank you so
much holy macaroni you bumps
I made a boat nice boat nice boat so can
I buy Treasures in here
do I get these dresses oh is it like a
gotcha let go look you know like a game
like try each she'll try a treasure
chest and see what you get inside let me
do it let me do it
gamble gamble gamble gamble gamble
do I get a free try oh
left because I'm Lefty
what was the best price cylinder
ah
I got a red ruby
oh
are these the other things they're not
that good I prefer the money
it was the best one anyway
let's go
oh ah wait I don't get the rubies I get
the price oh okay
oh okay okay
the prices change
black modern home
[Music]
they stay the same
if they stay the same it's kind of lame
all right maybe change this every day
[Music]
oh
if you have Lionel parts that's more
interesting to me oh come back later
I got a roasted porch yeah you want it
that's a very specific thing he has a
real weakness for Rose's Porgy seeing as
he went so generous I'll bend the rules
and let you play again it
but for the same things
uh and I can only get like one of the
other two
gay
I want the second price please
blue
is that okay
okay well mohawk
um restaurants
what do you get at the restaurant
can I buy food there
what do we need
the Fishman keeps roasting porches so
it's always supposed to give him ah
um
I already showed up the buildings
Foundation using the logs you collected
for me if we can place a log from a palm
tree through the holes number five okay
and through the floor okay
oh
so we have to move the boxes first
I can do the whole question because it's
getting late
10 p.m now
I'm still not sure can I read
supercharge or should I just play longer
guys
what should I it oh wait
longer after me
um
yeah I don't know I'm not satisfied yet
but but but again if I
uh finish the game tomorrow
you can still do side stuff on my own
time right
foreign
just gotta go back on my save file
[Music]
um
no attaching no no
I
I eat okay go in there please
maybe if I drop it
what
hello
I usually spend that 10 times you think
no no if I only have so little time then
I will properly use that time to read as
many as I can really really trust me
do I not look trustworthy
[Music]
okay let's see if we can finish Laura
Lynn and then
tomorrow I'll finish the game
[Music]
that looks good
oh
yeah cause we're gonna move on
hey I want to do Cocoa too maybe
tomorrow we have some time
[Music]
yo that's blue shirt
he put on an iron chest wait is it the
last one that I saw in the water
or is there going to be a new one
actually
wait
if they sank it it's probably in the
water
that's that that's the chest that's been
there for a while
[Music]
so there's a sword there that might
okay another blue rupee funny
foreign
with this one
Rusty Claymore okay
under the ship
maybe I can reach it from there oh also
have a statue
the devs to be trolling you
meanies
how fishes
I've seen
[Music]
what is in a bag I think was it a stone
it was a raster Shield
that's not it
no I don't see anything else from here
under the ship
I'm kind of looking under the ship
other side
God damn it did I choose the wrong side
did you guys like
my recent Omen like shorts and memes and
stuff because I got more in the works
I had another idea for the funny meme
recreation in 3D
the Akita one was not my idea I was from
chege
for the next one
summer one killed
yeah actually so the thing is like they
asked us
what do you what do you want to do for
your summer shorts
like in a
in a form to fill out
and I did not even remember this but I
asked for
recreating a meme perhaps
[Music]
I thought it would be funny
uh ah oh cute oh my God one of course it
is cute can I keep it in the end I'll
probably be able to keep it right
anyway and yeah I entered the I said I
want to do any meme
and then that's why they thought of it
for me
and when I had to record it I was like
what am I the only one who's doing a
meme and they're like yeah actually yeah
also like a part of the other people
were also doing memes they're like no no
just you I'm like why
and then they remind me oh because you
requested for it like and I'm like what
I don't remember that anyway but oh I
guess I did oh my God
what so out of all of those shorts
only I am recreating a meme and
everybody else is just like I don't know
being cute
[Music]
I feel like they could have
yeah done some more meme Recreations
yeah they picked the meme they picked
the meme I didn't pick it either
and I I watched the OG several times and
then I practiced it tried to get it as
close to the original as possible so
that you guys can recognize it
you were cute though thank you that's
why you were special um
it didn't recognize it why
why
leave me alone
where's an old meme huh
I mean I feel like I personally never
fully saw the OG video before I just saw
it in GIF gift form I think like with
the guy with his smile and all that
I don't think I fully saw the video with
sound before so
me too me too
same or so many
[Music]
yeah I found it but you're gonna let me
keep it right because kind of
conveniently my size
but if you think about it some dads
shirt
who keeps it all the time
and kept it in a moldy old chest
and sweat in it and has [\h__\h] enough like
seawater on in it on it now he wants to
give it to me
think like a normal person would I as
the hero really want this used dirty
old shirt that's if you compare our body
sizes isn't even the right size
[Music]
but thanks
it has different value for me
nice
wait so the restaurant that did I finish
the restaurant is this a restaurant
eh wait this is such a nice house
so chill I want to go to the Maldives
do you make food
for me
special menu
46 rupees
[Music]
oh looks it does look special
food paella
it's hearts
interesting do they ever have like some
special
attributes I wonder
where's the guy by the way the Builder
where'd he go
on there
I read it right yep
mohawk
gives you new recipes you haven't right
registered oh that's so cool okay that's
nice
let's make a home
oh there's two
I'll make that one
oh
is it the same thing again
putting a palm tree in the middle
oh she's hellofresh in person
personified
hellofresh yes
[Music]
uh yeah okay it's the same thing okay
make sure it's a straight one does that
really matter don't they all come out
straight in the end
very straight
because the normal trees I feel like
they all come out as the same model
when you chop them if it's different
with palm trees
[\h__\h]
oh wait I go up
it was better I
think that is very strange
very not European
[Music]
thank you
solid joke I'm tired okay
I'm just tired
I went swimming today though and I
lifted a little bit just for fun
but damn those two kilogram per arm
they're really heavy
ah you're welcome guys
oh
it's nice for building it seeing it one
by one come back together that's
actually really noisy
[Music]
let's do the end
yeah it's a start yeah
I have to start somewhere
weakest night
I have noodle arms
mmm
yeah I have to do reps at lower weights
exactly
start small
[Music]
like after I lift them
you know I'm like I'm like in the baking
stream where I was um
um
[Music]
like leaning my arms on the table but if
I do it without
is a bit more difficult so I I can do
like
comfortably I can do like um seven maybe
and then I can gum value for a couple
more until like maybe 15.
over my head is a bit more difficult
though than just normal
don't don't laugh at me
it's breath okay
thank you thank you some people are very
nice
thank you did he say to clean up the top
this stuff how do we drown the
did he ask me to drown the water too a
bit I'm drowning myself
he'll handle the water okay so I'll just
get rid of them
easy
uh
isn't it also a word with d uh
isn't it a similar word
train is so similar oh
[\h__\h] I
must have kept those in
can I
ah
wait how do I reach the other ones now
[Music]
I'll recall
oh you know what I'll use ice fruit
or the choo choo Journey yeah because I
never do
I never use it
[Music]
ow
I wanna go on a vacation
I'm actually I'm for uh for now don't
worry I mean I know
I I have a feeling of
obligation and stuff
um
because I'll I'm gone here and there for
work
but
after that soon I'm actually planning a
trip with someone
hey hollow life member is going with me
on a trip
I'm so happy
I'm so happy I will not say any details
yet because we didn't decide yet which
country
and we didn't decide exactly when we
only decided the month but I Would Not
Shake any exact details but I'm so
excited to go with someone
um it's an it's an En member um
oh yeah we're going on a trip we're
gonna have some fun
okay
I'm so happy
I'm looking forward to it
[Music]
I would not say who yet oh
both fruit thanks I never use it
Oscar a nice place to visit nah I want
to go to beach
well this looks like
it looks similar to
the Maldives Spa
man I want to go to the Maldives but
Maldives now is not the season I should
go in like December and or January or so
okay we got one more for you maybe
arms house who is that armies armies
let's go
Australia Australia is so far and so
expensive to go to New Zealand too
like both I would love to go to
but it's just
expensive
you know
palm tree
no
I really want to see them
[Music]
not only for that but generally you know
Australia and New Zealand both so
beautiful
it's so expensive
ah
I have to do it from above kind of
Mexico
yo you'll see guys we have like a
[Music]
a consonant in mind but no country yet
I'm not high enough
ah what it works it works I think
there we go smooth
hmm
and Optical hello
hell no
I want a beach
that was the last one they all looked so
nice
what's up Grace I have been to Greece
before I don't know I I wouldn't mind
going again but then again
should go to new places is what I'm
thinking
[Music]
Brazil too I've been to before
times
I went to Brazil two times
once in someone once in Winter whoa
[Music]
please come again wow
I brought back happiness and peace to
Laurel Lynn Village
hmm
today the Pirates attacked and overran
the village I was desperate to get
everyone to safety
before I knew what our beloved home was
gone
after everyone fled
the only sound coming from northern
Village
was the sound of monsters
I never thought
never dared to dream I'd live to see the
day we could all laugh together again
like this
this moment right now
it's all thanks to you
and of course I'm extremely grateful to
Bolson too oh no no there is no need to
thank me after all when I first drifted
into this Village
you are welcome to me with open arms
didn't you
the work I did here is just my way
it goes away so fast Boston thank you
this Village owes you adapt in fact I
think it's safe to say that you are this
villager's savior
now I talked about this with the rest of
the folks around here and we do not have
enough money or treasure to repay you
for saving our home
but the treasure we do have well
it's this Village and everyone in it
so from now on we'll do everything we
can to share our Hospitality with you
hi
to have a little vacation home
even if I don't have my own home here
but I'll get free use of the beach right
a villager's savior I'll provide bed for
free anytime oh
you are also welcome to eat at the
restaurant as much as you like free of
charge
I already paid 46 bucks though
can I get those back
no I'll just say we may not need to test
this luck but I'm sure it would be fun
to play a treasure chest game once in a
while not for free though is it
please feel free to take anything you
find in the village
Mohawk oh I'm watching this emotions I
can't hold back anymore oh
look Lively it's time for the
dance
Laura Lynn Revival dance
[Music]
foreign
sorry
that seemed like such a good connection
as a joke
I want to see the dance
I'm sorry I don't think it was like
entirely bad you know I liked a lot of
the things that they did and I thought
the
boom because of the blur I did not say
that before in four Fest you know that's
really cool
[Music]
I can unlock one more place
I thought it was over
with whom do I speak where is the guy I
just see this guy now
was it so bad for mine too
[Music]
oh yeah the solo dance for non-fiction
yeah yeah yeah I would have liked to see
that like if they ask us ever like
camera angles they wanna I want to
change
I'll tell them where's the dude
anyway I want to open the chest too
are the instructions I like to see
audience shots though
I wanna see you guys
oh fishing harpoon oh wait let me try
that
because there's some fish here right
we are harpooning now wait where is it
oh could I not pick it up
Why not pick it up
no I didn't
I would try this
Pro lemon no wow I don't want to be like
those
survival YouTubers
that I was like really into for a
certain amount of time
oh it's breaks immediately
but I can just fresh swimming get them
fresh a lot too which is also something
a survival YouTuber would do
but that's really like high level like
oh my God
if you were able to just swim and just
grab them with your slimy hands
wow
that is impressive
well I only really ever watched one
specific one mostly and he seemed pretty
legit because like he's been doing it
since he was like a child
or really young teenager
I can't find the guy I don't know where
I would be able to do one more thing
[Music]
there you are a new attraction
what do you want
I like it to be some kind of
entertainment so I think everyone could
really get behind and enjoy you've
traveled all over the place haven't you
ideas
I think an underwater tour would be cool
but I don't know how you're gonna do
that
breathing would be a problem okay uh
okay
it's gonna be a water rally ride because
that's the only like thing you can
probably do yeah okay
when you in the like industrial map
where you had to
what are they called those enemies
I mean I guess there were several
actually
ah reopen the shop by telling the
shopkeep and look out landing at the
Village safe reopen which shop
this shop in the village oh
okay bloopers yeah yeah yeah
blue pity boopity
what do you want I'm tired
I don't think about the races here once
they finish your work there they do want
a real professional races will be
willing to oh oh
in Tarrytown I have to do the race there
first okay thank you
oh I'm tired ah
[Music]
eat
it's only been seven hours
I think I'm too tired to game at least
like mentally
physically
um
[Music]
make some food you know no excuses today
but I like
I cleaned everything properly
my kitchen is clean so I think it's
easy to start cooking
ah
tired from this game for today
just because of I think it's the heat
[\h__\h] I don't think it's even that hot
outside right now because it's like
night time it can't be
it's just the heat like saves it just
stays in my apartment
my apartment saves heat so
passionately
ah now my windows always open and barely
goes in
Minecraft
well I want to play Minecraft again next
week
Minecraft
ff16 and we gotta do member stream
yeah
I see I wish I I really want I say
small fan front of window
um
guys
I think I may have been overall kind of
low energy today have I
but I had a good time
had a good time I wasn't I wasn't
not really okay so that was just
internally
I I didn't 360 no scope on the lineup
did I
oh
man I like this new album
what the [\h__\h] is an outlet
what is an outlet
uh-huh
rain melting from heat help me
brain frying
oh man Spanish Outlet you mean a Spanish
omelette
have a Spanish friend who made me
Spanish omelette several times already
every time when we meet at like a
convention
it's so good
yeah and once I saw the process and I
was shocked by the amount of oil used
in making it cause damn it's like wow
wow
a whole
frying Pan's height of oil
and then yeah lots of potatoes potato
yum yum yum yeah yeah
what yeah
I mean by the time you add all the
potatoes and everything I guess but by
that time it's reaching like full height
[Music]
oil omelette yeah
it's really good though like in the end
it doesn't taste that oily and you
um I guess we always ate it like in
between some bread like a sandwich so
that takes away a lot of the oil too I
suppose
hmm
looks like a frittata
I guess so
what's ahicho don't know that
Linda polita
romantico
see
Senor season
you think you'd pass out as I said it's
like it just takes that much like
like it doesn't taste like the amount of
oil that it looked like
when frying it
huh
sort of snare
let me see if I have a
tangent to send you guys away with
[Music]
no these are for later
ah
a small tangent
um small tangent yeah one full of road
yeah
um
so uh because there were ID girls around
I've also been around like ID staff a
lot
um
they're also sweet and nice too
I talked to a couple of them
and so this one time
this ID staff was Lending
uh
me and another person their laptop to do
something and I know this
that
the cursor the mouse cursor
was like constantly changing
Star Wars faces character faces
um
like tiny Star Wars faces I'm like oh
this person really likes Star Wars huh
and then I was like hmm I wonder if she
knows the Han Solo song
really relate with liking Star Wars that
much but you know I'm a social person so
I always want to connect with people
right so I'm like hey hey hey hey manage
your son do you know the Han Solo song
and she's like no
so I'm like okay let me show you you're
gonna like this
so I put on on YouTube the Han Solo song
I'm Han Solo Han Solo Han Solo Han Solo
solo
and we were all like watching it and
vibing and like partially dancing along
no but she really liked it
yeah I made a Star Wars fan happy I
think
I did a good deed I think so too
um I'm spreading my knowledge that I
gained from you guys
yeah
thank you
you gave me a talking topic
with a Star Wars fan
Han Solo Han Solo Han Solo and Solo solo
hmm
I'm writing one down for tomorrow
I just wanted one but I'm not tell you
now I wonder what now you know
okay
okay I should get cooking
and thinking about
how can I get
things done officially tomorrow before
my stream
thank you I hope you guys have a lovely
evening too thank you for the crazy
super chats you guys
[Music]
um
I will
see I mean I have to I will see if I
schedule if I can schedule a Super Chat
reading stream for next week
and for next week I'll have a proper
schedule up
but for tomorrow
3 P.M or for half past 3 P.M just like
today starting time okay
and then at midnight I have something
too so I'll be drinking energy drinks
tomorrow
I got the same one as last time that was
so yummy
so thirsty
oh no oh yes
not unhinged no
just energized kiwawa
I need the energy save me from this heat
oh
help me
I can't survive
much longer Turbo
imagine if I would have taken her today
while killing all those lionels I feel
like hmm I would have panicked too much
or do you think it would have increased
my focus
I was already kind of kind of hyper
already
during that time
more panic
would have been too much
I would have gotten a headache oh yeah
maybe two
missing yourself I sweat oh
misting myself of eyes one
interesting
me and then I would need something to
miss myself with like a spray bottle
oh
Mama I love you thank you for everything
thank you for today
thank you for a great week
with concert and with Bob day
many things going on
where today's Saturday
a week ago I was on the official Channel
right
how
sheesh
so many things in one week
stress
an eventful period yo sheesh
my God
I haven't even used the Yukata yet on my
own stream but I didn't feel like it
would fit yet
um
we'll find I mean you already saw me in
high quality 3D moving around
so I think you guys can wait right
I don't know when to use it
oh sometimes sometimes maybe during the
Super Chat rating
yeah
also I want to do the the bingo I want
to do the Bingo
um
I have to think about how to go about it
yeah
bingo
okay and in German we say if he doesn't
I go cook some salmon now for real for
real forever I paid extra for that dish
shouldn't be
the difference
[Music]
can kiss my ass and the clean Ox too
I could have easily killed that kingly
up you know it ah
[Music]
foreign