[Music]
There's not enough, look, Ender
[
Music] Man [Music] Ah, there's not enough, Ender [Music]
Man [
Music] There's not enough, look, Ender [Music] Man [Music] There's
not enough, look,
Ender
[Music]
Man
[Music] There's
not enough,
look, Ender
Music]
Man
[Music]
H It's
not enough Look,
Ender
[Music]
Man I've opened it, I've opened it, Mikemashi,
congratulations, congratulations, congratulations, congratulations!
Display Are you in the viewing room? In the viewing room
Yes, okay
, okay, you're okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, oh
, is everyone here? Gather together, okay? Yes, gathering, yes, gathering, gathering, gathering.  I'm not a teacher, I'm
not a teacher, but I
just happened to be here. Hello, are you
all here? Is everyone there? It's
okay. It's okay.
Well, I'll go. Well, let's go.  I
'll go from A, I'm
hungry. I'm hungry,
please. Masu ja mule. Senpai, hello. Masuametepa. Thank you very much. A. I'm here. Kanata-san.
Yes.
Mui-chan. Hello.  chan
yay iinai tomeyou nai to
me
you kai ne ki soame chan ameame chan ah haime chan yayee ni o
Kaela
[Music]
yay  It
's so confusing. These members are on the phone.
They're the ones who will break up and become A. Yes,
yes, B's Hotenchoco-sensei is aww.
Oriyoi, Oriyoa-chan.
Hako.
[Music]
Please, Captain. Hello, Captain.  No,
hello, hello,
yeah, dalin, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
flow up,
I'll do my best,
look at me practicing, I've been practicing for a long time, so I'm like, uh,
let's do this here too.  Is it okay? Should I
go? I
think it's better to go. Should I go? Yes,
today, Raden-chan was
absent, but I'm sorry for not being able to attend.  I
was
surprised when Gozaru did it. I was surprised
because I thought he had come to apologize to me. I was surprised when I
saw Gozaru in my house and did something confusing. He said
that I looked like him.  We
would like to cover your writing as well, so please
help us. We will do our
best. Since you seem stubborn,
Raden-chan will appear in Home Hunting, but I will
appear in her place for a little while.
Thank you very much.  As a hunter, I'll keep going as a hunter,
and I don't know what will happen with the battle yet. I
guess it's a secret.
Kanata wanders around alone, looking forward to our time together.  I
wonder if someone will come and see if I'm working hard all by myself. Maybe they'll be watching everyone's cameras. Maybe they
'll tell me to do my best, hit them, hit them. There's a spy here.
What's the truth? You're acting
like a messed up spy. Matsuri-senpai is getting off. He's
telling you to leave. He's
here in the waiting room of the white group. It's the classroom.
Everyone is waiting here right now. Yes, he's looking good. He's looking good,
isn't he?  I
'm here.
Okay, everyone's gathered here.
It's good, it's good, it's good, it's
good, it's good, I'm glad everyone's here.
Oh, there's a signboard. There
's a signboard. Where are they putting it?
Everywhere is empty.  You can't put it up because you're using it, right?
Can't you just put it up
?
How do you use a signboard?  That's the
only way to tell someone that you're a selfish person. [Music] It would have been nice if there was a white sign in the house.  I
'm here. Everyone's here. I wonder if I'll go
scout somewhere else where the scout group is.
I can hear the sounds of people hitting each other from all over the place.Since we
were practicing, I wonder
if it's okay or if it's already started.The
main thing is that even during practice, the Rigros and the
others were beating each other up quite a bit.
Yay,
I'm sorry, I ca
n't take off the signboard I'm holding in my left hand, but I
can't take off anything that might be stuck on the signboard all day today.
Oh, I can't really get it, I ca
n't get it after all. Not only is it good, but it's true. It's no
good, but what a terrible thing to have, everyone.
It's too serious. Even if I hold it in a competition, I wonder if it's
okay. Maybe it's something I have. It's
easy to reset.  I thought it was,
but when I'm infected, my left hand
changes all the time, so I guess it's okay. Minecraft
As expected from one of the creators of Minecraft, it
really looks like it's going to happen again. I'll debunk it.  I'll do my
best
this time as a Debakuha for the Minecraft Sports Day, and I'll
do my best as a Bakuha, but I'll tell you everything
about it.So I wonder if there's any intrusion on the creators.No, no, no, no, it's true.Aho
Oh, that's terrible.Is this true, Minecraft?  Is it
true that there's a new version? That's amazing. That's
amazing. What will be added in the next update
?
But it looks like it's going to be like experience points. I do
n't know.
But I can hear it, I can hear it, I can hear it, I can hear it.
I heard a voice that sounded like Subaru Senpai, but I'm not mistaken.
Hey, I heard it. What's the internal broadcast that I heard? What's that? Well
then, I think I'll call out to you. Well
then, everyone in red,
please.
It's an announcement. Everyone's not in the red group.
So, let's go. Let's go. It's white. It's white. Merle. Meruru
is red. Meruru is good.
Merle is this way. Meme, it's over there. It's over there. Mememe.
Mel this way,
it's
all over, it's all down
now, it's
nice to be here,
this is it, this is it, this is it,
this is it, it's a genius, it's really lined up, the
red is lined up neatly, the white is lined up neatly too, let's do
our best.
Let's
make it beautiful Let's come together Let's
stay here with mom Let's stay here Hey, here,
here in 11th row.Would you like me to stand in 1st row?
Okay, so next up is the white team, please come in. Please. Yes, yes, that's true. The white team has a lot of connections. That's great.
Finally, I'll ask the yellow team to call their mother.
Okay. Next, let's continue.
Yellow, please.
Otaku-chan, it's okay. Kashi-chan is hiding, and you're
doing it too. There's something wrong with
me. Wait, I
realized this, but this route camera was
probably set up. How many
punches are they exchanging?  I
'm hitting on the
white group. It
's too serious. It's
annoying. Shio-chan is the only one with a Ping sign. It's true,
Shiono is the one who put it together. It's because there wasn't a yellow
sign and a white sign.  Well, I
couldn't even hold a sign and take it.So, first of all, I would like to
ask you to give a greeting from the Oro Live Sports Festival.I said yes, and everyone,
Hello, Nyanini.
Hello! Thank you so much for everyone coming together, despite your
busy schedules. I
'm sure the seniors and juniors have helped each other and encouraged each other up until today, even in practice.
But today is the real race, so
let's all do our best and win.
First of all, everyone should have
fun and aim to win. I
hope everyone enjoys it. Thank you very much for your support today. Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Yes, we have received a message from Mr. Yago, the president of Cover Co., Ltd. We have received a message from Mr. Yago, the president of Cover Co., Ltd. Yes, please take a look here.
For example, it's gymnastics. I won't do gymnastics. It
's not in the program. I'm
not going to do any preparation for today.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
At today's sports day, we cooperated with each other.
Let's encourage each other and fight bravely until the end.And
thank you very much to everyone who always supports Ro Production.Thank
you very much.I hope you will
pay attention to the hard work that we have been doing until now and support us.
This is Meba's
concern.
Hello, it's probably a mental injury. No, I
can see where the injury is.
Channel 1, please, sensei.
Good luck. Good luck. I like the slope.
Hand,
hand, youuchi's large-sided blank frame number 1.  Because I'm serious  Please make
sure I'm right, please, please, please, do your best, please, do your best, thank you very much, thank you very much, thank you very much.
Please, please, I'll come. I
wonder if I'll be able to come. Hasha, come on, come on. Come on, come on. Hasha, come on, come on, come on. Hasha, that's good. I think I can do it. Tsutsuo. Is it alright if I ask you to be the player teacher? Well then, please.
Masu
Sensei, as members of Hololive, all of us players have
taken over sportsmanship.
Sensei. Dodo Fighting is the best way to do it.
November 4, 2023 Red Team Representative Toku is White Team Representative Ah Yellow
Representative Haspels
Ye
[Applause]
Thank you very much for coming back.  It's okay.
Thank
you. I'm sorry for throwing the bread. Sorry for the inconvenience tomorrow. Thank you very much. It's a
special day. Now, everyone,
please move. Can
you move?  I'm
fine with this, please excuse me. The
white team
's dangerous voice is so loud.
But the white team's fugitives are the contestants of each group.
Please go to the white group's contestant channel.
It's kind of real.  The sound quality of the sports day
and the
feeling of it being played are so realistic. I
mean, it's like flannel or something. I guess it's the
first round of home hunting.
Only people who are in the first round of hunting can enter.  That
's right, that's right, that's right. Um, I'm
going to the white group contestant's channel,
so uh, Ame-chan, Kaela Nelisa,
hi-o. Please do your best.
Pre-
channel, do your best,
do your best. Good luck,
good luck, good luck.
Absolutely
[laughter]
That's
right, that's the third person. That's right. It's
Kaela. Her body
is so cool.
[Music]
I was able to go. All three of us were able to go. Is it
okay for us to be fugitives too? This is not okay.
So, what does that mean? Are we infected? The
white team is the hunter. The white team is the most
likely hunter.  It's like a hunter, so I'm
going to go and cheer for you.Other than that meba, let's
just cheer for each other.Eh, it's
not a fugitive, it's a fugitive.What group is this from
?What group is this from?  There is an announcement  I wonder if there will be any
announcements.I wonder if there will be any announcements.I wonder if there will be any announcements.I wonder if there will be any announcements.I wonder if there will be any announcements.I wonder if there will be any announcements.I wonder if there will be any announcements.I wonder if there will
be any announcements.I wonder if there will be any announcements.  Are you
referring to the three of us, or are you
referring to the white group of hunters? Which frame do you want to
write? It's not us yet, so it's white. It's not
red. It's red, it's red, and it
means that you can go to the other side with a book.
Hey, can I press
it? I can't do this.
I can't enter. I'm trying. I'm
getting too lazy. No, I'm entering. So this is probably better. It's probably already arbitrary.
That's right, with the power of God,
you don't have to press it. It's okay.
Oh, I'm sorry, I'll excuse Sado's announcement. Kaiha-san, Roboko-san, Nakia-san,
Amaka-san, and Choko-san.  I'd
like to ask the White Technician Channel to do the
opposite. What's going to happen to us? This
is the opposite. It's not because everyone is running away now. It seems that the
fugitives are moving, so the fugitives are on the
Contestant Channel.
Isn't it okay if you ask me? What number are you talking about
in the same place?
Yes, hello,
here, here, here, this is where it is. It's a
white group religion,
so the fugitive who runs away is this channel.  It
seems like it's become, so I'm against it. It's
difficult, it's difficult, it's difficult today, it's difficult today. I
wanted to practice this.  The
number one
thing I haven't done is the one I haven't been able to do.It's
true that I don't like this, but once I get over this, I
can do it.I see, I completely understand now, it's
perfect, please wait.  The
white team is
All of them will run away Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, that means we're all contestants,
right? That's why
our white group,
during the hunt, will be separated by the infected and the hunters.
Probably the three of us,
right? HAllHGoing
TEwhiteaMayB
All
has
Ogo A, right,
only the hunters are
on top, right?
[Music] It's
kind of like that, right? Only the hunters
are on top. Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah,
in the end, which one is the
one who runs away?  It
seems like the runaway defender/fugitive is probably set automatically, so
that's why that question comes up.For
example, if the hunter is a member of the red group and the hunter is a
member of the white group, then the answer is ``oh''.  I'm being targeted, so I'm
running away, and then I click,
and then I get caught with a rope, so
even if I'm already caught, I feel like I want to run away with all my strength.  I'm
going to South Korea, I'm going to South Korea
, I can't get out, so the back of the cage is surprisingly a hiding place.Oh
yeah, I'm a little anti, and
I'm a bit of an
anti.  I'm heading towards the cage, so I
have a hunch that there's no one behind the cage. I
wonder if that's the case behind me, too. I'm a little worried about that, right now. I wonder
if that's what the staff is saying. I'm
watching the text channel, but it's white.  set  There are
7 people who ran away as contestants, so it's the second tier,
but I guess I should go.
Well, that's not what Kachan called me, so it's a
competition, right? That's right,
so it's Hunting 1.  I thought for a moment that it would be better if
both people from the second game went to the other side,
but they are there. Even though
they were called over there, I guess they didn't get the message across.  It seems like
Raden-chan's part is right,
right? That's right. Yeah, I see. I
feel like it's something like that. Maybe I'll
just ask the announcer.
Thank you for this.
Ren-chan is there,
right? That's why he was called earlier, but I
guess things are progressing with Nemada Ra-chan joining in. I do
n't think so.  That
's right, that's right, that's right. So only
people who are not hunters should be
on this channel right now. I wonder if there's something going
on.  I
have the power of a god.I'm being coveted.I
just asked him.Thank
you, thank you.Are you
okay?I wonder what's going on.It's true.
Now that I think about it, I didn't hear
about the flow of the competition.It
seems like they didn't do the flow of the competition.I don't
think there were any materials like that either.I'm probably
reading the materials right now.  I
wonder if either of them will probably be able to take part.Other than the contestants, it's written there.Other than the contestants from other teams.  I
wonder if Terue will come back or not, but
everyone is going to be at work for a long time today, so it's scheduled to
be around 9 o'clock,
but I
feel like I'm not going to push, so it's
a bit of an atmosphere.  I feel like I'm
going to take a short break to save up some energy, but I'm also hungry so I'm going to
eat some food. Let's take it
easy. It's going to be a long time.
NemaThis is also the best part of the sports day.That's right.That's
right.It's okay to say that Daigomi is difficult.  I
don't know, it's a real thrill, it's a
real thrill It's called a real thrill It's
written in this book that gives me the answer, real, real,
thrill, real  It's a book, it's a book, it's a book, it's a book, it's a book, it's a book, it's a book, it's a book, it's a book, it's a book.
Ignore it now. It's
okay. It's not 7 people.
We're 12 people.
[Music]
34899 people, 9 people
.
Yes, thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Reply.
Thank you, thank you, thank you. Okay, but
1 In the first game, if Red is first, everyone will have to run away.
Yeah, it's true, it's
true. What's going to happen? They're the
same, just different channels.  It's
just the voice that says "Niyaru" and suddenly it starts to
rush. Eh, it suddenly starts running away. It's coming and it's
coming.
English members,
where is English? Let's
take care of the members and protect them.
[Applause]
One English member.  Let's protect it
English member, let's
protect it. Do
n't hide it, there's a dangerous Fauna in the back. You
can't protect it more and more. People are
watching your back. I'm not an anti behind the prison either. Let's
protect it. Run away! Run away!
Run away!
Change.
10.
Squat down for a moment, 149 cm. Let's make some mistakes. I'm
under 149.
What kind of person is this?  I
can't fit in because I'm a squid. I'm 149cm tall.
[Music] I'm 149cm
tall and it's
amazing. On the other hand, if you're small, you
don't run away, you look confident at all.  Actually,
who are you protecting?
How are you doing this
? Why is it happening
? Chan-chan, catch me! I can go. Someone tell me I
can go.
I can go. Chan-chan. I can go. I can go. Chan-chan. I can go. I can go.  You
can catch me
, yo, I
failed. Oh, I made a mistake. I was killed, but stay here. Hey,
whoever caught me, yo, it's
over. I
wonder who it was. I'm
sure Anya was different in no small part.  It's
like an awkward, awkward crackle. Hunter, please. There are 6 people,
so please write 6 people.
Yes, that's true, then let's go. Come on,
let's go.
Wait, Ta 6 isn't here. Excuse me.
Pa's 6 is here. All the fugitives of the White group.
Everyone who was just talking, White group.  ABB,
please move to the original voice chat. I'm so
tired of losing it.
[Music]
Well, it's over. I guess I can just go back. I'm off.
Bye-bye.
Bye.
OK. Is this like cheering? It's cheering.
Okay, Kaela-san, I wonder if it's okay, it's
aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa It's a good feeling that I
went without picking up anyone,
so I guess I should just stay in the weak seat.
Kanae was arrested and is still being arrested. I
can't get out, I ca
n't get out, I can't get out, I'm in trouble.
It's a lie in Ruri. The game hasn't come out yet.
It's probably someone inside or something. I failed to escape.
Well, I haven't been able to escape from prison. I can't escape from prison. I
can't.
And it's South Korea.
Oh, and Kihara-chan is also there.
Well, I guess I can't leave until the next start. Should I stay with Monene or something?
Let's take a picture.
Yes, it
's a country
.
Thank you. It's a prison where pictures are taken. My
face is covered in grass
. It's nice. It's
nice.
I'm here now.  I
got a successful jailbreak. I got out of jail. I
finally got out. I finally got out. The
hunter does his best. Let's
support him. Let's support him. Let's support him. I'm
coming. It's Korea. Thank you. It's a prison. I'll
give it to you properly.  It's kind of like
this. I
feel like I'm going to show it to the listeners too. This
is the best shot. Wait a minute. I
'll also download it. Wait a minute, it's
Korean, it's Korean, it's Korean, it
's true.  Their
faces are very close, but they
're very close together, and they're really in love.Wait a
minute, that's right, it's
Korea, it's Korea, it's so hot.Yo, you've
already escaped from prison.You've already escaped from prison.Yo, you've
successfully escaped, y'all.Entry
Well,
we've entered it, so we've got an infection, an
infection, an infection.  It
seems like it's amazing, but in the end, there are only 6 people, so I'll
do my best to look at it. It's
too big. There's one block for each person. It's
really big. This place is so big. There's so much space
left over.  Even though it's really big, you
can see the whole thing and it's definitely a nice feeling.Yayyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyy, I
wanted to get a seat close to Korea.
But it seems interesting.I
went to the dangerous yellow team that I made myself, and now I'm feeling
a bit fluffy.It's
okay.Hey, I'm back.I came back.I came back
because I had an interview or something.  It looks
like he went to the second match, I
see. I interviewed him enough to make him cry. It's
okay, Mu-chan, I'm just confused. It's
okay, it's okay. I thought it was funny.  I
lost, what are you going to do? You're laughing out loud. It's
okay, it'll be fine. It'll be
fine. It'll be fine. It'll be fine. I thought it would be fine, but
from the way the speech bubbles were flowing right now, it
looked like it was going to be interesting.  But I
was blowing a lot. It was blurry. I was blowing. My
chest was walking around. Let's do it.
Let's do it. Let's do it. Let's
do it.
Hey Shiro Team Chiro Team Shiro Team Chi White
Team Shi Team Shi White Chim Ah Shiro Team Pigeon
So that means we're not runaways either
Right, yeah, that's
right.  Oh, that's right
. Please wait a moment until the next escape. Yes, be
polite until the next escape. Yes, be well-
behaved. Yes, be well-behaved. We're a
team. That's right.
Everyone was so nice that white was lined up beautifully in the first place.Yes, they
were lined up beautifully, just like our color.Oh yeah, just
like our color, white, clear, clear, clear,
clear.  Power is clear and white power is
not. Clear is transparent and
clear. It's true that it's a mistake, but the residents' toys are gathered together. White
has colors. That's
dangerous, because there are two colors of white. Do your best,
do your best.
Good luck, what's coming next? What's the theme? It's
debuted
in 2021-22, so it's pretty recent.
Lately, I can't get into the Rocks. I'm
barely getting into it. I wonder if it'll be until the 21st Rocks. Holo is up, but
Hololive is really running away.
English's 2nd and 3rd generation, etc.
English's 3rd term ID Soja ID
's 3rd
term Yes, I see. It's a bit sushi, and
this is the summer of 2020.  It's
hard to find a name that's easy to find, even if I look hard. Good luck to
you. Do your best. Daiko's festival is going to be even more intense if you're here.  I
feel like I'm being chased, I
feel like I'm being chased, I'm
a little confused, I'm
not prepared for it at all, I'm still very anxious.  Is it
okay? Is it okay? Is it okay? It doesn't
matter, you can catch them all. If you're going to
touch someone, you'll probably have at least one bob.
Short bob. For now, there's no way around it.
There are hairstyles of different lengths. Touch, touch, go, go, go.
Where are you?  It's not really quiet.Why is it so quiet?
Everyone was making such a fuss, but Gura-chan is
also taking Gura-chan with her.Nice, nice,
nice.
Miko thinks Holo
kids, no, it's
good, but she thinks Holo kids, no. She says it's good, but Kanata is probably in. I'm
sure I'm not a kid. It makes me feel like a Holo. I'm
not a girl, but I'm a girl, too.
One thing's for sure, it's not you.
Anya has been arrested. It's true, Anya. It's a
scratch, it's
not a scratch, it's a
big sister. It's a big sister. Hey, that lucky girl is worried about this.
Well, I'm curious about this, but I wonder if he's going to fit in. He's not a bad guy, he's
not a bad guy, he's not a bad guy, he's got big boobs, he's
probably going to fit into the category of girls and kids.  Let's try to
run away, then me and the
leader will catch them, catch them, and
catch them. Yeah, let's catch them all. If you can't
figure it out after putting everyone in, just put them all in.  It's
much faster to say good, it's fast, it's
fast, it's not easy, the topic is interesting because it changes, it's difficult, it's not a common understanding, it's
funny.
Thank you very much for doing that. Bra-chan
might be a [ __ ], but it was already there. I'm
sure that's the case. It's
just my bad luck. But if it's a kid, who is it?
Naruno, I'm sure you said that. I'm sure you'll get into it. I think it's probably kids. It's probably Neki-ish. Yeah, it wasn't Noki, but it's being watched a lot. Hello, I'm sure I want to know the answer.  I
want to know about Mio-senpai as well. At the end, I
want to see a bar. No matter who you are, you'll be targeted. Neme-
senpai felt that way. She was locked on,
right? That's right.  I
feel like Nerisa-chan is like that same person. Oh no, I couldn't get that or that,
so I secured it. I'm so happy. I'm
worried because there were 0 people. Was it
difficult? It
's okay. It's okay.
Hey.  It was more difficult than practice at all.
No practice problems. No problems. The practice table is too easy.
Yeah, that's a big deal. That leader and Chiara
will cover it. It's okay. It's okay. I'm looking forward to it.
I'm
going to put everyone in, so I'm going to
put in everything I found, and it's
going to turn into a key. Please use your grip strength. Let's
move. It looks like it's moving. Is this going to move?
[Music]
Lo
wor
JAandlikeforforthe
shortcutdidONETRto
inforshortcutIcould
FindYeahbutThatShe
wasconsideredshort
butI
isShedefinitelyhas
shorthairIthink
Herknow
aboutdefaultONE
So-so
Oh, don't worry about it, it's
okay to be sad, no
prem
[Music]
Problem level,
nooblob, look, look, look, look, there are some
pitiful people like this.  I
want to do this so badly.If I open this door
and close it right away, something will happen to me.I'll
do this in front of the door when it's closed.And then I'll
go inside.  It
smells like earth. It smells like earth.
[Music] I
wonder
if it's exercise. It's
dangerous. The
contact is too close.
It was so cute when we were standing next to each other.  It's so
cute! Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's so cute.  It's
cute, it moves its head, it's really cute The
head meat han has been synthesized,
but no, yellow, yellow, yellow, yellow,
if you run away, you'll be fine.Let's run, right, run away.I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll
run away, I'll run away,
I'll run away.  I
want to go to Korea, but I'm sure I can't, I can't, I can't.
Only the fugitives
are the fugitives.  It's
already been entered, right?
That's right. It's called
Escape.
Run away.
2023 It's
not
Neri. It's nice. Nice people were also arrested.
I'm going to sneak around and cause trouble.
Kanata Fresh.  This is the most viewed
song. Let's go by my side. It's him. Give
me a cigarette. You're bald.
[Music]
It's amazing how many of you are saying that you're a sad woman. Hey, I'm here too. I'm here too. 460. Catch me. You've completely ignored me. There's no way I'm like that. Wait a minute. Use it. 158 Safe. Hide it big. 165 That's right.  I'm in charge of hiding it, hiding it, and
trying to catch it.  There's a lot of people,
but no one
will catch me. They've caught me about three times,
but I've talked about my concerns, but it's not Chuu. I'm not Chuu, I'm Chuu.
But there were people who were worried about me, but I
apologize for the inconvenience.
Nakaiha-san isn't neat and clean.
Even her screams are clean, so whatever she
does, she's neat and clean.
There's a lot of dissatisfaction, there's a lot of dissatisfaction, right?
Nice, nice, they didn't catch it, they didn't catch it, they
didn't. It's
true that
Azusa is definitely on the roster. She's definitely on the team.  It
was dangerous, it was dangerous.
It's so cute when you have a little bit of self-awareness. No, it's cute. It's scary. It's so neat.
You're absolutely neat.  You
should run away with Ei-chan,
because you're so cute, Ai-chan. You have to run away too.
Even though you're so neat, I
didn't think you'd get caught. The
yellow was really strong. The yellow was strong. The yellow one was strong. You
caught the yellow one. Pesu
was terrible. With this.  It's one more time.
Yes, Captain, you're not neat. You're running away again. You're
running away one more time. You've made an entry.
Everyone did it. At once,
Round 2,
Lara, you're running away.
But let's
run away.
When I was a strong, tall man, I
wanted to be chosen as the leader. I didn't care if I was an older sister or a sexy woman.
Well, I guess I didn't, but the
kid who misunderstood me, Polka,
misunderstood me, so I was feeling that way, so I
was able to get a little closer to the cage, right?  The
cage is so small, it's so hard!
If that thing is caught already, it won't be able to escape for the rest of the game
. That hunter
won't have to wait until the next game starts. Subaru-senpai, do your best
and don't run away.  Tonaja, next Mio-senpai is wrong, who
's thinking? Isn't Tamio the next one? Yes, that's right. Well,
that kind of thing, that kind of thing, that
may change. There's a possibility that things will change and be completely different.  I
want it though  I
want to be protected.
[Music]
All my shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes.  It's
a bit creepy that the slopes are about to overlap next to Xione Tepa,
but
somehow everyone is buried. I'm
stuck.  I ca
n't help but stare at it, it's so cute It's
cute how
they're standing side by side Cute Hey, someone please line up next to me too
Ah
reset reset oh it's starting Oh maybe we'll have to
do it one more time Let's do it again oh yeah Yeah
ok oh ok ok ok ok ok ok ok
Oh,
oh, oh, it doesn't matter at all,
but Subaru-senpai's nipples are gone. Yeah, I
said it was a lie.  I went
out of my way to chat with Subaru and
asked him how many nipples he had,
and he said, "Why do you have two? There must be more than two.
No, birds are eggs,
so I can't get them like that."
Hmm, it's become something like a specialty,
but it's so sad. What's going on? It
debuted in 2019. It's
so bad, it's so bad. It's
not included.
Oh, who is this guy
from 2019?
Everyone, please run away! It's a
shame. It's a shame. It's a shame. Let's
take a stand. The group, the leader, etc. It
was 2019.
Hmm, it's crazy, but even now, run away, run away,
run away, run away, it was terrifyingly fast.
Artists are gathering here.
Apparently it's a collection of artists.
It's difficult to say that there are more than 3 stations.I
had the impression that they were playing it.It's definitely on the top left.It
's crazy.Ah
[Music]The
person who was caught by the police was interrogated.Who
is he?  I've been arrested,
in a certain way
. I've
been arrested. I haven't been arrested. No, I have
n't been arrested. I have
n't been arrested at all. Surprisingly,
surprisingly, I have
n't been arrested yet.  I do
n't think it's possible for us either. I thought I'd fall asleep, but
I answered all the questions, but I ran away. No, it's
amazing
. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work.
Only three hunters are here.  Please stay and the rest of you
should move on. Goodbye, good luck, good luck, good luck,
good
luck, good luck, good luck, good
luck, good luck.
Yes, yes, it's Korea, but it's creepy. I'll give you this too. Oh, which is Korea? I
don't know where you're looking, but I'm
giving it to you. I'm giving it to you. I'm
giving it to you. I'm already used to it.  I lost this. I'm going to put
this out. Please give me this here and there.
The shot my teacher gave me in Korea is so
surreal.
This Noel-senpai looks like an ID photo, so I
get it.  It's
a shot of a guy who won a lot of money and is filming a lot of things.
Hey, I want you to do your best in the second game. Do your best, Naga. Let's go to the
cheering seats.
Cheers. Do your best. Wait, wait, I made a mistake in collecting drugs.
Wait a minute. My mouse is
soaking wet.
What's the matter with you? Why were you just in front of me right now? I accidentally fired a shot. It's
dangerous. The mouse turned out to be beautiful.
Live the mouse.
Oh no, I was just stroking
it. I was stroking it. I was
stroking it, but it hit me.
Hey
, oh, it's
cute. It's facing down. It's facing down. Wait.
Kochie is cute, it moved, it moved, it moved
, it's cute, it's cute, little, little Negura-chan,
that's a glass glass,
isn't Gura-chan going to appear? Are
you sure it's okay? Stay here, it's true.  When I
woke up, I was a contestant. That's
probably true. It said that I'm now entering the runaway. I'm probably going to be taken away
right now. That's
the one who disappears. Good luck.
Good
luck! A dangerous scuffle with white hair has begun. A cute book.  I didn't realize that.
Did the Subaru statue get taken away? Maybe it was
YouTube's aa? It was
just the one who took it.
[Music] I'll
clean up my hands.  It's
coming, it's starting, it's starting, something,
something, something,
there's a
lot of people
[Music] It's
not the first time I've come in. That's
fine.  It's expensive. Toa-senpai is hiding here.
Toa-senpai is hiding here. But Toa-
senpai is probably about the same size as the other one. I
thought he was hiding in a corner.
Terue, it's surprisingly different, it's a huge failure.
Sui-chan got it. Yes, Asu-chan looks expensive. It
certainly seems expensive, but it's
gone, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's
okay, it's fast. 3 people have already been arrested. Catch the gosu.
It's easy to understand.  Ruduru,
it's too early, it's too early, yea, Yomoko-san is
being arrested. Whoever she is, I
can't see her name.
Naekari-chan is tall, isn't she? She's tall, she's
tall, yeah,
ao.
Ah, the cotton was caught and the foxtails were swollen. I wanted to
go to the ears. I wonder if the people of the Kebo-mi tribe have
ears to catch. Oh yeah. I
wonder if they don't have them or if they don't have them.
Hey, that's right, that
's right, now just listen to your ears. That's right, that's right, Fana-senpai.
Those horns are not furry ears. There seem to
be a lot of horns or horns. It's
dangerous, catch them all. There are quite a lot of them.
That's right, there are a lot of blurry judgments. That
guy is good, he feels good, he
has a pretty good title. He's got a good title, he's getting really
into it. He's getting it really well. He's really getting it. He's
getting it even better. That senior is also stupid.
11  People aren't
all that great.
Meruru is definitely not like that.
No, I can't help but blurt out Mel-chan. Meru's
senior is really hidden. Mercury is on the right side.
Senpai is no, no, no, he's here. He
's in the red. Do your best, no, but it's
amazing, it's too nice, it's nice, it's nice, it's so nice. It's a
cow. That's the best record.
There's a best record. It might be the best record.  I'm
so [ __ ] up, it's
amazing, isn't it 2?
Nice nice nice nice go away
[Music]
Ah ha ha ha Ah, wow, that
one from
earlier Oh, what's going on? Wait a minute, chocolate. The teacher's photo is too good, isn't it? Really, wow, how good is this? I just
took it.  You guys are so good, let's just get along. I'll
send this to Subaru. This is really good. This
is really Subaru. This is too good. Kaari
was really depressed. Everyone.  I put a lot of
work into it on the way home.It
was really good.The beasts were
really hard to catch.At the end, they caught a lot of them, so it was scary.The ending was
mostly blurry.I could have put most of them in.Bobo's
floating fa was really amazing.Yasoke's
ears are surprisingly few when you look like this.  When
Nebame-senpai says he has furry ears,
it doesn't give me the impression that he's a little bit scared.That's
right, I guess.Everyone is a blur,
so they don't get too aggressive.
Maybe I don't like that blur, but if I
judge Mio-senpai, there are quite a lot of people who are dumb, so please come and
poke me in. That
's right, that's right, Mio-chan, Kamio-chan, it's
definitely
Mirando
Mirando, in a sense, it's a bonus stage.
I'm sure you can
run away, run away, run away, run away, run away, try your best, try your best, run, run, run, run, run, run.  It
was a little hard to catch it, it was a bit hard to
catch it, it was hidden, it was hidden, it was
hidden, it was hidden, it was hidden, it wasn't hidden.  It
's like a system, it's like I'm going to have a hard time, I'm going to get caught for a moment, but
Korea's waiting, I'm going to get caught, it's
okay, I'm going to catch it.
Cha-chan changed her mind
and was arrested. She was arrested. She was arrested
. I was worried
about her. She was so poor that she hid her blond hair. Her hair was blond. Her
color is too early. Ha, it's okay. I
'll protect her. It's true. She's
not a baby. She's blond.  It was blonde. It's
a little
weird. It's
a little the same. Sorry, sorry, sorry. It's
the same. It's the same. I want to
but it's
amazing.  It
's a shame that I have free time. This is free time. This time is
free. It's dangerous for me. I don't like
it, but my name is sexy. You can catch me in a little while. It's okay to come here. One-chan, one-chan. I'm sexy.  That's why you're so sexy, you
completely
ignore me. That's why you didn't do anything. That's why I'm a senior at a
festival, a senior at a festival, a festival where I'm a
senior. I'm not a senior, that's
not it.
No, but I'm here,
Chancha-chan. I didn't do it here either. I didn't do it. Nice, nice. Anyway, there were
14 of us, right? There were 13 of us. It
was dangerous. It was dangerous. Sunny, nice. No, it was just barely dangerous.  It
was dangerous.
I really escaped the sexy frame. I'm so
glad I escaped. It
was dangerous
. I really wanted to be a little surprised. I
could hide behind you.
Tami
White
Explanation The
person being explained is disappointed.
Chim, are you going to go back? Oh, okay, I guess it's
up here. I'm
back. I
think it's moving automatically. It
's moving. I see. It's amazing. Oh, seriously.  Yes, it
's true now. Okay, okay, okay. Oh,
oh, next time, Lomen hunting is
over. Is it over? Are you going to tell me the results now? I'm
sure there are points. How many points?
Well, at the beginning of the sports day, he told me, but he
couldn't tell me anything during the middle, so I watched it at the end.Yes,
yes, yes, that's
right.
Stop it! I'm
hungry, so I'm fine, but I'm in trouble. I thought I'd
end up in trouble, so I stopped practicing.
Today was the same. Yesterday was really good.  It's
okay, I was practicing with that person a lot,
and I bought a lot of them.It's really
good in practice,
but in real life, the actual performance might be different.No, it's okay, it's okay, it's the
same.
Well, they have the same shape, so in the first match, it's
Mercury-senpai and Biji-chan, who are really good at it, and the really
dangerous, dangerous first match is Roboco-
san.Oh yeah, but it's Roboko-chan.
I was trying to teach you a while ago and you were getting good at it pretty quickly,
but I guess you just started practicing today.It's so
good that I want you to do your best.It's a beginner's luck, I guess you can do it, I can do it, I can do it, I can do it,
Passion Passion,
etc. It's really scary B  Well, the white team is now
2, so it's really nice.
Nice, nice,
nice. I've
received a follow-up invitation.
Okay, yes, 6 contestants, 2 each,
please move to the voice chat.Are you going to do your
best?Are you going to go up?I see, you can go up to the top.  Is that the
one with the voice above?
Yes, the voice is the voice. Chiara is moving.
Yeah, Kiara-chan, it's her second match.
Are you okay? I guess I have another interview.
Well, I'll go. I'll go.
Hello
everyone, now that Chiara is
gone, I'm
going to say something that puts a little pressure on me, but
yeah, so many people have been looking at me like this for a long time.
Hey, that sounds like a big deal, haha.
When you look down, everyone is paying attention. It
's war, and it's hard for people with war phobia. It's amazing. It's
really brave, isn't it? It's amazing, isn't it?  I've
been practicing a lot, so yeah, that's true.That's true.Here's
a bit of a record.Even if I
fall short of practice, that's not it.It's a nice
fight, that's right, first of all, it's a goal.It
's amazing what I can do.I'm
really excited.  My
heart is pounding on my side, so what's going to happen?
Well, I've done this before in practice,
but I didn't end up doing it, and I only touched it for a moment,
but yeah, it wasn't difficult at all, after all, scaffolding.  I
have to figure out where the next one is and
decide to fly there next time.I
jump and let go of that Triden.It
seems like the flying distance will increase even more.Oh
, it's
quite technical.That's right.That's
right.Today's competition is like that.
Well, it seems like it's the most difficult one, but it's certainly the most difficult.Maybe it
was last year, maybe last year, or something like that.The
human one was
also difficult, but it's even more interesting than that.  That was a
moment of hard work, or
something like that. Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's a huge victory or defeat that is decided in an instant,
so in a sense, that's right.
As soon as you do it, it feels like it's over, whether it's good or bad,
but this one lasted for 300 seconds.  Let's
finish it 5 minutes 5 minutes 5
minutes 5 minutes I wonder if the deep side will do
its best I wonder what happened in the end I'm sorry
for the support that was dropped I
think it would be better if there was support for yesterday  That
's what happened in practice, so I guess that's what happened in the end.I wonder if he'll come
back to the team or not,
but he's parted ways with the contestants, so I guess it's okay.Bo-
senpai from A is right, so I'm sure he's like this in his heart.  I
can't see the upper part anymore
. I can't imagine how far I can see Roboko-san and
Chiara-chan's Isamu from here. It's
only 200 meters away.  I'm fidgety, fidgety,
really fidgety,
but this is Chiara-chan. If Chiara-chan,
Roboko Senpai, gets a good score,
Choco-sensei will give me something nice to eat. I
believe in that, so I'll make a hamburger, and then I'll
make a
tiara. A book about coming to Japan.  That's right, I said I'm in Japan. I'll
make
a basket. Yes, I'll make a hamburger. I
want to eat stuffed green peppers with meat
.  I'm running
out of appetite for meat, so I
can't help it.I don't know if I'll cook it for you or if I'll go to the restaurant.I
just
want to go to the launch regardless of winning or anything.I
guess I want to do something like that.  I
became a member of this group through a lucky draw, so I'm sure it's the white group.Let's
make a reservation at the restaurant.I don't know what type you want, but it's
not meat.I'm sure it's from yesterday.  My
repertoire was mostly meat, like
hamburger fillet cutlet,
ena yakiniku, shabu-shabu type hot pot, etc.
Oh, nice, hot pot, hot pot, nice. It's cold, and it's
getting cold, so Shide-chan comes, but the
other cats don't.  I guess I won't be coming for a while. No, that
's right. It's different times of the year.
I guess I should just go out to eat every time I come. I can go, Fuka Chico.
No, I don't think so. I'll just take the number of people who can go first, and then I'll
take the number of people
and book a store. I
can add more later, so I see. Oh, let's go, it's
going to be a year-end party. It's
true, these seeds, these
seeds, wow, I'm going to leave it there.  Is it alright if I
bring a load of amazing flowers? I'll go
and see you then go. That's fine. I
guess we have quite a bit of time. We'll
do each competition one by one.
After all, there will be gimmicks and interviews,
so everyone will
probably be enthusiastic and talk passionately about it.Oh yeah, it's true that it's going to happen, right?The close-up
is Minecraft, because there will be a lot of enthusiastic people.Hold
on,
so we're currently the second strongest.  Yes, it's definitely
past 9 o'clock.I
have a feeling that there are definitely some marks left behind.The
back of this one is a little off.It
might be that, but the wood line and the back of the fang line are a little off.  Hinanka
Hime and so on and so on and on and on and on and
on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and off and on and on and on and off and on and on and on and off in the spring and summer and the rele and the rele and the
end of it, I think there must have been five events, but I don't think I'll be able to do it at all.  There's probably only one voice,
right? That's right, so there's only one replay,
so there's only two of them, so yeah, I
feel like I can go there. There's definitely a follower line.
It's like that 3 It's like doing that 3 times I'm
doing it 3 times That's
how long it will take I'm sure it's the beginning, do your best,
do your best, ah, I'm back It's starting!
Hey, it's going well,
it's going well, it's going well, it's going well, it's going to be good,
Roboco, you're a woman who can fly.Rebiji-
chan is really good at it.But you get
anxious about how good you are.  There's
definitely a lot of pressure when you're there, so do your
best, Osan, you're doing your best. With this, if you
go all the way to 200m, you'll get points,
right? Or maybe not that much.
Points are determined by the last one or the last one.
5 minutes from Noe
Well, it's not like it's the earliest, so if
everyone reaches 200m, everyone will get the same
points, right?But
if it's within that amount of time, it's likely that they'll reach the final goal.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, so yeah, if you
aim for 200, you'll have to fight against yourself,
yeah, yeah, do your
best, yea, yea, yea, yea, yea, yea, yea, yea, yea, yea, yea, yea, yea, yea, yea, yea, yea, yea, yea, yea, yea, yea, yea, yea, yea, yea, yea, yea, yea, yea, halves, yea, yea, just now,
Chiara-chan was roboco,
senpai, yea, yea, that's it.  I'm a beginner,
so I'm just a beginner, so I'm wondering how I'll finish,
but I'm
actually good at games, so I'm very skilled.
Okay, okay, Roco-san is really good. He feels really good,
and there are all kinds of things.
After all, he participates in competitions and other tournaments,
so he must be used to things like this, getting attention. He doesn't seem
nervous at all. He's really excited.  It's
amazing
Oh, you can do your best,
do your best.
It's so fast, oh B-chan, you're so fast
Hey, you're good, and Roboco hasn't fallen since the fourth one It's amazing, yeah, you're so calm It's
definitely going to keep getting better This temperament is definitely
getting hotter and hotter
Hey, good
job, do your best  Just a little more, you
can go 30m, you
can do it, go ahead, Roboko, you've got Jet with you, you
can go,
just in case you fall 13.
Even so, I'm going to wind it up from the checkpoint.
That's about it. That's right. So,
calm down, 10 meters to go, 10 meters
to go, 6 meters, oh, go for it, do your best, go for it. Nice
goal. You're too nice. Sei-chan is
also doing her best. Sei-chan has just
a little more to go.  There's
something like 200 at the end,
Sui-chan, Asui-chan, no, there's
still 90 seconds left, so there's still more than a minute
left.
Even though Sui-chan is good at being able to relax, there's
always pressure in the actual performance,
pressure, it's my turn to do my best, so I'm
sleepy, yeah, it's irregular, this one is going to do my best, but the purpose of the game
has changed, but I still want everyone to cheer me on.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I
said it's a battle with myself, but
yeah, it's a 200m battle, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right.
Everyone has an equal chance of a draw.
Yeah, I'm nervous, I'm drinking water, I'm drinking water, I
'm looking up, but I
don't understand what's going on. Is it too expensive? What can I do? I
want an elevator. Everyone, 200m,
crackle, crackle.  It feels amazing, crackle,
crackle, it feels good, but this is
it.On the other hand, the pressure comes on the people on the second level.Let's
do it, do our best.  Good
luck, 39 seconds,
yes, that's quite a while. It's hot, right? It took 39 seconds to
climb. It's from Kiruko.
The second round is Kira-
chan.
Kira-chan.
Good luck, Choco-sensei's place is a place where you can climb up and see it from above. It's nice.
Here, here,
here, it's really here, it's pretty good, it's
getting a little closer
[Music]
It's okay here, now it's here, push it a little, it's warm,
it's warm.
Okay, it's true. You can see a little here,
yeah,
yeah, see. It's cute.
Tell
me, you're telling me, you're lying. Is this an infected person?
Is this okay? Where is the good guy?
The sign on the right is the
entry. Everyone was doing this, so there were
n't many people like this. Yes, the entry.  Is
it a list? It's the far right of the four signs on the left. Is it over there,
here? Really, I'm going to take this. No, it's
floating, it's floating, it's floating, how is it going to float? How
can it be floating? It's normal to receive that one. It's going to
turn into a severed head.  Seriously
, where's Tiara? Tiara, you're
climbing smoothly. It's scary.
Even the people around you probably
can't see this or that. They can see it.  I'll
never be able to climb up if I do that. What's with the obstruction? What's this poop-like thing? Oh, what's this? It's like soft-serve ice cream. It's really soft-serve ice cream. Ah, it's soft-serve ice cream. Oh no, it looks like it's climbing really smoothly. Wow,
wait, wait, I've lost sight of the character.
Tiara is the fastest right now The
checkpoint is coming, Kikiraki oh Oh nice, the
second check is fast Wow, I
'm just taking precautions
[Music]
Hey, it's good
Wow, the effect when something goes up is
so
cool Wow, it's really fast Everyone is watching
[Music] Wow,
we're almost halfway there It's so fast, it's
so early It hasn't fallen even once yet.  It's
nice to know that I can do this. Thank you, thank you. It's
totally
different from the three of us just looking up at the sky. No, seriously.
No, this is too fast
. I went up and it turned out like
this. It was going smoothly. It was going like this. I didn't know, I didn't
know, I didn't know. Put this on the spiral field.  It
's true that if you make a mistake, it will
fly away all at once.There are
colored blocks from there.It's true.It's something
like that.It's completely different depending on where you go.There are also
quite a few shortcuts, but it's
poisonous and tense.
Let's cover this a little more.Here, let's go over here.Here,
Katene-chan and I are going carefully.Oh, wow, how nice, can't you see us?That's right, we're floating right
now.We're drifting,
but everyone's floating around.Everyone's
face
is Geara-chan.  Wow,
no mistakes. No mistakes. I haven't fallen down even once.
Amazing crackling.
This means it's the final spot.
Yeah, if there was a scuffle here, I'd be dropped.  I
wonder if that was expected. I don't know. In the end, it's the distance we were at in the final seconds. I
guess it's
better to give and take for 70 seconds than to lose both of us.
I'm worried about things like that slipping away and falling. Saka, I'm doing my
best. Good luck, 50 seconds left.
Ah, I'll
do my best
to like it.
Oh, there's only 30 seconds left, go for it, both of you
[Music]
Yeah, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming.
I wonder if you two are going up together. Do your
best to catch it.
Do your best. Just 7 seconds left.
[Music]
Oh Ruo.
Yay tomorrow.  I
didn't make any mistakes. I was almost there. Hey,
okay, I'm going to go down hard. Wow, I was surprised. Suddenly, I fell
down. No, I didn't make a mistake.  It's
amazing, it's amazing, it's amazing, it's amazing. Good, nice, nice,
nice.
Chiara: Yeah, and the
next one is Kiba-sen or Kira-sen. Yeah, it's Kiba-
sen. It looks like it's
going to be busy. Poi chao. Some pairs like A and B are already together.
Yes, yes, yes,
yes, that's right, everyone on the competition channel,
yes, yes, yes, let's do our best, leader.
Yes, the group and Chico-sensei want to notice, Choco.  It's
still stuck in your ass, isn't it? I wonder if I'll be able to participate in the competition? I'll do
my best and do it three times. I'm
sure the
thing on the screen on the other side of the third message
is the point of the follow-up.  Then, the white team's
points are now 20, and they have the most points now, so they're probably number 1. I
wonder if I'll go or not, and I'll be able to catch up. That's a nice fight, that's nice, that's nice, that's amazing, Amada.  He
hasn't come back. He's back. He's still home. He
's still in the middle of an interview. It's not like that yet. The white team is the only one of ours who's
eavesdropping. They're both eavesdropping. They
're going all the way to the cat.
This is an interview with Idaki from the mountains. Maybe that's right. That's
right. He
played a high-level game. Hey, he didn't make any mistakes
. It was amazing. He didn't make any mistakes. That was amazing. That's
nice.
Nice, the White team is currently in first place.
It's a very close battle, but White has 40, yellow has 38, and red has 37.
Nice, nice,
nice 4 points, yellow, 38, 37 strong. Let's go, let's
go. Good, nice.
Nice.
Wonderful nice, nice, nice. Nice. The
princess and the dangerous princess.  It's dangerous if it's going to happen.
No, that's what it means. It seems like it's going to happen.
There's always something like protecting the general with a ray of fang.  That's
right, there's still a lot going on. Well, I have to
do my best. The pressure is
slowly building up. I don't know what I'm planning to do, but I don't like it. It's starting to
put a bit of pressure on me. Even with all the pressure, it seems like there's no way to find a pair.
Well, this time I teamed up with Ramen-chan, so I
guess I don't know what's going to happen yet.
Thank you for your hard work. I'm
looking at you, Mom.
Okay, so here
's the interim announcement of the general specification.
Here's the overall score.
So yes, 1st
place is 40, and that kind of money is quite a bit even before.
Yellow is the last, 63 points, white is 60 points, that
's 3
points. Okay, let's move to the next competition venue.  It was
announced
that there was a jump from there.I wonder what the score
was.  There
was a difference of 3 points
3 Yellow 63 White 6 and Chiara-
chan Nice Thank you very much
Good game
Good game Good nafa Nafa got off
Nafa 2 people It was amazing 2 people It's not good.  It
's too bad, it's too bad, Chiara, please do your
best and fight.  The main
character of Teruyakutsu is that candy.
Yes, the entrance is right. I'm going to go with this. I'm
cute. I made that. I
made this. I was so excited. The
orchestra started with Chanri-san, nice and
nice. That's cute.  This is so cute, and
what's more, it's okay to ride on top of someone.  The
general may be on top, so it's
the side that gets clicked. Don't enter.
Okay. If you've already entered,
cancel the entry and touch it again. When you
return, you'll be the general.
That person from this is here.
Will that person from my pair come? Is
that person there? Will he or she come? The
other pair is still wandering around Minori.  It's better to have
something ready and I want to eat it.I want some onigiri in the container.I want to
eat some rice balls.I'm hungry.I want to eat some
food.I'm hungry.I want to eat some rice balls.I'm hungry.I want to eat some rice balls.I'm hungry.I want to eat some
rice balls.I'm hungry.I want to eat some rice balls.
So youknow
how beagressive
OKGbeagoodhorsey
okuryoubetter
be
Gae-
sama,
where is it?  I
can't see where I'm going to see where I'm too sick here, which
is painful Either way, it's
okay to get off,
how do you stop the target?
Just
Nice Nice Nice
Nice Ah
Ose
Mumbling
What? Wait a minute, did you
go there dressed like that?  He
came in a suit. He looks strong. I
made a suit. He
looks strong. It's better to look strong. He looks
strong. It's okay. I
won't charge you a huge amount of money later. It's okay. It might be
possible. Oh porridge.
Senior.
Thank you very much, you look strong, you look strong. Did you
ride? Did you
ride?
Oh no! I rode so bad!
So Okayu-senpai will help you out as a pinch hitter.
Thank you very much for your support.
Thank you, Aoka-senpai, for coming.
Hey, let's get on. He got on
top of me. He got on top of me
. He sat on the chair for a little while.
Okay, leave it to me.
Thank you. I'm so happy. I
can sit on my fluffy ears. It's stuck in my fluffy butt. There
's a corner of a chocolate wire stuck in it.
That's right, leader. This is the horn. The
horn hurts. I do
n't like it. It's better if it's a bit irritating. I don't
like the stimulation. I
feel like it's quite irritating.
If I say so, Mio-chan might also be quite irritating.
This is Senpai's horn.
Thank you very much for your help. Thank you very much for your help. Also, I'm
going to let you participate. The
most scary thing is that there is one suspicious person.  I'm afraid I'm going to be
let go, so I
guess that's why I just learned how to do it. I want to lead Tan to victory. I
hope you're cool. Let's have
fun and do our best, everyone in the white group.
I'm going to do it, I'm going
to do it, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do it, I'm going to do it, I'm going to do it, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do it, I'm going to do it, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do it, I'm going to do it, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do it, I'm going to do it, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do it, I'm going to do it, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do it, I'm going to do it, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do it, I'm going to do it, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do it, I'm going to do it, I'm going to do it, I'm going to do
it
What's your strategy?What's going to happen to the white team
?Well, if you get the most successful kill, you'll
get 1 point added to it.That's
right, I'll protect you and probably
focus on the opponent you want to attack.  It seems like it
would be a good idea if we all just wake up the people who are
approaching that general.If you're the type, it's better to stay close to the general, but it
might be a good idea to keep coming closer.  It seems like a
weak person.I
want to beat up the weak person.I can see hearts, so I
might want to avoid people with 3 hearts.Conversely,
at the beginning, stay close to the general and
when you see 1 heart, attack him.
Okay, I think this will probably be the voice chat for that pair, so I guess that's right. There
are so many voices. Well, I think there's probably a name at the bottom,
so come to think of it, it's true.
Kanata says there's porridge. Minato, it's better to work together than to work together. Cooperation is bad. The general can't say "protect and protect." That's right, it's the big general. Let's do
our best. Let's do our best. It's true. It's true, we're in trouble for each other.  I'm being targeted for some reason,
so I guess I should go to Terutsu Cover.That's
right.When I find it, I feel
like I'm being attacked.Then I
think I'll probably have to move from now on.Everyone is moving.
Well then, let's go. Let's go. Okay,
please, please,
please. For now, we'll protect the back of the large book. I'll
go, but I wonder what's going to happen.
Maybe he didn't turn his head, or rather, he kept his back to him. He
might have been facing the outside of the venue instead of toward the venue, so if you think about it
that way, you'll probably be in a different camp.
Even though I thought it might be a problem, if the viewer moved, I
'd have to protect them, so
if I found one heart, I'd rush in.
But then I asked them to take a look at the leader's heart too, and
then I saw the leader's heart.  No, I do
n't know, so please just go. Okay, 2 or 1. If I tell you to quit now, then I'll
just run away. I understand, okay
.  Let's
set a goal for 3 times.I got 23 kills.Yesterday
's maximum was 3 kills.To be honest, I
can't give up on practice.I
thought I'd cut it, but I got 5.My goal is too high.  Well, my
goal is to get under 5. That's
right. That's
right, I'm going to try to target Amikochi as well. I
have a feeling it will start soon. It's almost over.
Wow, that's right, it's right here in the frame, right? The
white one, that's right, that white frame, that one in the middle. It's
probably going to go away once that start starts. Okay, okay, okay, ok, okay,
this is really evil. I
'm thinking, ``This guy is getting in the way.''  I feel like it was like that yesterday too, so it's okay to disappear. It's
okay, it's
okay,
it's the devil and Teshi, they're the
strongest pair. They're the strongest.
There's a lot of things going on in the game, and there's a demon
knight or something like that that's so powerful that it's
definitely the strongest, so let's
see if we can attack it once.Even
now.  I don't have a sword, so all I have is a book, so yeah, I don't
know the name yet. I
wonder how close I can get to it.
How about this? Everyone's going to practice, but
yeah, it's a sword anyway, so it's a continuous hit.  It's
important to shake each one one by one.It's important to make sure you hit them repeatedly.Alright
, it's okay to start at any time and it's okay.There's a lot of competitions going on, so I
guess they're preparing for it.Oh,
that's
weird.  Oh, I'm surprised you haven't changed. It's
okay, it's okay, it's okay. Just now, I
thought I had teleported for a moment, but it was just moving in a straight line so
quickly.
Okay, okay, okay,
okay.
Choco-sensei is in first person. Minecraft is in
other than first person. Is that F5?
There are various things after F5. It's
true.
Yes, it's true. In this game, the viewpoint was
not specified.  So, if it was like that, you can
definitely see better this way, so it's okay.Yeah, yeah, okay, okay, that's it.Okay, I'm
wondering what you're following, but I'm actually
practicing how to follow.  It's
helpful, it's helpful.
[Music]
Okay, but I'm a bit older than that, so it
's okay, but what if?
If you get drunk easily, do
n't push yourself too hard. It's okay. I've never gotten drunk playing chocolate games, so I'm not really strong. Yeah, I'm a
game that forces you to play for half a period.  I don't
think so. On the contrary, I don't get drunk in cars at all.
Yeah, that's right. I
don't really get the feeling of getting drunk in cars.  It's
easy to say that it's amazing, so it's easy to say that it's amazing, so I
want to have that feeling.I'm really serious, but even if I
ride a night bus, I'll fall asleep at night, so it's
better to sleep, but it's true that both men and women  It's because I get drunk that
I sleep and spend time doing things
like that.It's not like I'm
saying yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, that's right.  It's
starting, it's starting, it's
starting, it's
going, it's going, it's starting, it's going, it's going, it's going, it's going, it's going, it's going  I'm
sure,
even if I go one more time, Dajeon will still be one. That's
too fast, but I have to go anyway. If I
don't attack that, I'm sure in the end.  I
don't care if I die, before I go, let's go, let's go.  Okay, that's helpful, A-Sora-
senpai. So, Senpai, can you go? Oh, oh, Okay,
Okay, Ade. There's one, there's one, there's one, there's one, there's one.
But I also have
that, okay,
okay, okay, okay, well, that's it, it's a fierce battle,
and I got 3 kills, nice,
nice, nice, nice, ok,
ok, ok, ok, it's really good, 3 kills,
but red is strong, 5 kills, 6  I'm killing it. It
's true, so I guess it's okay.
Let's go from here. Let's go hard.
There are two more lines left. Yeah, there are still more,
so it's not good at all.
[Music]  We can make
a comeback, wow, wow, the
heart 1 members around here, you know,
even if everyone attacks right now, it won't hit
, so it's true, it's true, but it was just
barely.  I'm becoming a general. Hmm, what's
this? I don't know what TT is. I do
n't know, I don't know what T is. I do
n't know, I hit TT,
but I'll leave it at that for the time being.  Those who do
n't know anything do
n't understand I don't know what is T for the time being Who
said T? It's from Ani-
chan who called me this.
Okay, okay, I'll ask you to enter again,
but please wait a moment.  Wow,
there's a huge crowd of people.
The foil in front of the White Chico sign. Ah, that
's helpful. It's easy to understand. I got on. Okay,
Yoshie. That's nice,
nice, nice.  It's a
good feeling, but even if I attack at the beginning, it's
okay, I don't want to attack, but
it's a bit in the middle, and I'm getting beaten up by 5 of them,
so I'll just go fishing.
[Music]
All right, all right,
all right, all right, all
right
[Music]
Yeah, it's so unique that it's on my head.  It's a
strange feeling when I watch it on F5F5.
Well, it's nice weather today too. Seriously, no, seriously. It's
better than sports day. The
sun doesn't set, so it's definitely good to exercise. It's
good, isn't it?
That's amazing. What's that
? There's a lot of banging. It's
just different teams fighting like crazy.
[Music]  I'm sure you're
confused. Even though you're a different person, I'm
okay with you. Is that okay? I'm not satisfied. My boss told me to
get along. So, that's true, but that thing is gone. Don't want to be there. Even if you don't like it, it's
important to be
next to you.  Subaru is here, so I don't want to do it these days,
but that's it, Chiba-chan is also a [ __ ], but if you defeat him, you'll get a
lot of points, so I'll definitely do my best to defeat him. Shall we
go? Let's go, let's go, let's go from yellow.
Yeah, go around to the
back, Sky. Senpai is at heart 1, it's dangerous. You might be targeted.
Even if you die once, if the ball runs away,
that too will turn. Oh, can you go right in front of me? Nice,
nice, nice. You can still go
to the heart.  Heart to heart to heart to heart I can
go to the heart
Kao 1
Nice has been defeated
Uh I
'm 1 I'm
Ocho I'm going
Kao nice nice nice heart 1 heart 1 It's
right in front of me.
Hey, Sora-senpai, I wonder if I can
go or not. This is nice. This touches my heart. I wonder if I can go before. But I can go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, it's
nice. Subaru, nice, nice.
Oh, who is this?  Hey, how many people are there? It's 5 kills. Oh yeah, it's so
good. You can cut it down to 5. All right, you
're a genius, you're the leader. That's
amazing. That's good, that's good, that's good, that's the goal.  You're
doing it well. What
should you do next? It feels good now. It feels good. It
feels good. You're a genius. You can
do it. I hope you'll do the same for the next one.
But this is really difficult.  Even so, the
number of kills I've gotten is
higher than the number of kills I've had, so I'll make sure to kill them with my current strategy and
aim for 7 kills at the end.  I
said, Okay, I'll cut it,
but no, it's true that I'm already at the 1st place level. No, I can
go, I can go,
but I feel like I can go if it's Chicoset, so I
feel like I should head to Kigumi first.  Yeah, yeah yeah,
yeah, maybe that's right.
Nice, I got carried away.
[Music]
Okay,
nice. [Music] Nice. Okay, now, then, are you going to kill me again? Are you going to keep killing me
? Yeah, this is a little bit of justice, but the name of it is salvation, right?  I'm a
devil, so let's go.Save me,
let's go, let's
go.  I don't
want to score, but I want to kill the general too.I want to kill the general too.He
has a lot of hearts, so when I see something like 1 or 2, I'm
glad he just attacked me like that.  Well, I
was able to cut 2 and include other people, right
? That's right, so surprisingly I got
hit too, but maybe if the general's heart
had stabbed me when I was small, everyone would have been the general.  I'm
not looking, so I can get a good feeling
Let's go from the back
Yes, it's good, it's
fun. Hey, I'm a little happy. I've killed a lot, and I
'll erase everything. Even though your lives are angels, I
'm saying something. I'm a devil.  You're
saying something amazing, but did
you stop fighting? Are you
going to do it again? Well, let's
do it one more time. Tadashi is in the white race, and Obetsu, who entered the race with a good chance, is now riding.
[Music]
Okay, but if that happens, there will be white angels, devils, and knights. They'll be
extremely strong, no, they'll be strong. The only thing left to do is give
them a strong blow. There will be no samurai. We
'll go for the promised victory.  I'm the strongest, I'm the strongest
. I'm nervous. I'm here. Let's go. Let's
go. Let's do our best. Let's go. Let's go.
Rush in!
[Music]  Go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, it's nice, whatever, I could
have done it, but let's go, okay, once, I'm going to
die,
so I'm going to cut someone's heart,
okay, I'm going to cut it, and I'm going to cut it, and I'm cutting it all around here, finally, finally,
finally.  Let's
do it, let's do it, okay, okay, it's okay if the general defeats us.
Hey, nice, nice. I want to go to the stars, to the stars, to the
pigeons, my friends, my friends, this, this, this, my friends, around here.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, I
lost, but it's okay, it's nice, nice.
All right, finally, let's move this way, move this way,
move this way, move this way, move this way, move this way,
move this way.
Nice punishment, punishment, okay, no,
hey, I couldn't get enough kills, but, well, well,
well, well, well, leave it as it is. Well, I said, 4 kills, 44 kills, well, well,
what's more, I got 41, that's awesome, I defeated the general.
Hey, oh, that's really nice,
nice, nice, good, good,
good, good, good, good, isn't it amazing? The
last part is really high.
The points are being calculated,
and a lot of things have changed in terms of the total, but red was really strong, right?
Well, it's the first round and the second round, right?
So what's going to happen? That's
even a good feeling.
[Music]
What's going to happen to this?  This is it, isn't it? It looks
like we're about to do an interview. Wow, I
want to do it again. This is fun,
fun
[Music]
Oh no, nice,
nice
Well, it says go to A, so let's go to White group A.
White
Yes,
White,
thank you for your hard work.
That's right, Lisa-chan and Lisa-
chan. 10
And Ame-chan also got 10 kills. It's amazing. The
foreigners are kill machines and kill machines. Kills are better, it's
amazing. Everyone is scared.
Wow, I woke up at the end, that was amazing, that's
amazing, this is amazing. I was
able to make a comeback, I guess I had a lot of success. 41 Yes,
that's right, I was surprised because there was a targeted kill.
Taji de
Nice
Kills are big so yeah yeah sorry nice Nice
one kill nice nice kill
If it wasn't for that one kill I'd be at 40
Yeah yeah that's important.
Important
Nice Nice
Nice-chan is very strong and very strong. That's
amazing.
Roboco-san's pair was also amazing Nice. Nice and
naughty. I got 3 kills at the end.
Everyone did a great job. It's
amazing. That's amazing. Nice
Nai is amazing.  I wonder what's going on. I'm
quite curious. It's not good. I'm pretty good. I wonder if I've
gone far. I guess I've come a long way,
but I think I've made quite a comeback.  I
feel like I'm making a comeback.In the second match, I was number 2,
or 2nd, or something like that.It was 22nd.So, it wasn't
quite the first time.Red was also strong in its own way, so it doesn't
matter.I don't know if it was strong or not.  Lire is getting scared. Tamohime
and Hime are both shaking, and Shikihime is shaking.
Ima-chan, let's do our best. It's okay. It's okay.
We'll win. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
I can win, I can win, I was dodged by the yellow team
for about a minute and a half during practice, but the part
where they serve me that food is not at
all.This is a serious meta reading,
but yeah, an update has been released
for Holomen Hunting.  The contents have
changed quite a bit, so that's true. It's
possible that you're reading this mysteriously as if the menu has also changed a bit. That's possible. That's possible.
That's totally possible. I
want to win. I want to win. If I've come this far, I've already
come. How far do I want to go? Yes, I
want to go. I'm
starting to get a little greedy. At first, it's
about having fun.  It was like, ``That's good,''
but somehow I felt like I was
winning.I'm wrapping my arms around me.I do
n't have sleeves.I
didn't just come here.
Even now, I tore my shoulder to pieces. I
can't tear my sleeves apart. I
can't tear my sleeves. I've torn my
skin to pieces. Don't tear my skin. Don't tear my skin. It's such a
wild thing to say.  I'm muscular and
muscular, and I'm proud of my muscles.Misuiyose
last 41 kills.Oshimi-
senpai glue turned bright red.
Who was the one who cut it the most?
Kame Kiara was also amazing. At the very end, I'm
sorry, but I defeated Subaru-senpai
twice and Miko-senpai
once. I was being chased by Kara and Kara.  It
was amazing, it was amazing, it was
amazing, it was amazing, it was amazing, the White team, it
was amazing, but at the end, I would like to say
thank you very much Nekomata porridge.
Thank you.Please leave your thoughts.Yes,
thank you very much.It
was a pleasure to play with you all.I will continue to
support the white team.Yes,
thank you.Thank you.It was gone in an instant.It was gone.It
was there.Agent JintoThank you, Agent.  Really,
and thank you, Agent Oka of the MAGA team.
Thank you, me and my seniors, too. We've got shocking numbers of kills,
so it's
totally different. We worked hard.
Hey, thank you very much. It was so
much fun. It was fun. It was really fun. It was fun.
But the pressure of the competition after this is
different. No, it's
okay to relax and hope. There's still plenty of time.  It's okay, it's okay,
everyone can go, it's okay, it's okay, it's
okay, it's okay, it looks like it's okay, protect the princess again,
even if you have to protect the princess, she's still the princess, and even if you make
a little mistake, she'll make up for it with a relay, is
n't it?The pressure is so intense.  It
stings even the most dangerous things. It
stings even the worst. I've been practicing it. I'm
climbing now.
Everyone is climbing the ivy. I feel like I'm getting better at climbing
the ivy. Even now, I'm getting better at climbing the ivy.
Eggplant is difficult, isn't it
? It's difficult, isn't it?  I
heard that it was a good idea to run,
so I guess the scores have been tallied, so
I'd like to take a look at the totals for the three games.
Here are the scores. We did our best.
Red, red,
46 points, white, 38 points
. Red, 2 points. We were in 3rd place just a little while ago. I thought we had
made a comeback, so we won.
Hey, I know what's going on here.  We'll
see what happens in the second half of the race, so let's move on to the next one.Yes,
yes, then let's
all move on to the venue for the next race.  I'm looking forward to fighting Let's
do our best Let's
do our best We'll do our best We'll do our best We'll do our best We'll do our best I wonder
if everyone else is here Hirowa
Do your best muh Do your
best
[Music]
Masu
knowdone
all gujiguji
Nike
[Music]
Nice
Oh, do your best, White team  White team, do your best,
do your best, A-hime, Okatan entered the princess.
Hime-hime looks strong. If the princess is number 1, she's strong, hime.
Ichi-chan is strong, the power is the strongest, the
secret
is crushed, you go tight, I hope you go tight, I want you to
shake hands with me, do your best
here, ah, you're in an engine group, it's nice, you're
cute with the tiara on, hey, chiyochi.
Karao
Oh, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay
[laughing] I
thought Kaya-chan was crying, so why is she laughing? She
's laughing, she's laughing. I was
surprised.  I
was worried, but now I thought someone was crying, so
I was surprised. It's because
Himegacchan's way of laughing is so special.
[Laughs]
[Music]
Yeah, nevernoticed this
before aetlaughbutI
neverheard
likeWhenIlovesomuch
becomeslikeCrying
knowhappTearshapp
Cryhapp
Pipi Okay Okay Okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
Yeah, I wonder why Ka-chan is laughing like that. She's
just playing around with her own 3D image,
so she's laughing at herself.
[Music]
Hey,
Ah
[Music]
[Music]  ]
Patty It
's okay, right? Yes, it was supposed to be you. That's scary
. You only have to do it once. It's like a one-time match.
Ah, pressure, pressure, you're
nervous.
Do your best.The one who will be participating in this is Katan, Mei-chan, and Azuki-chan, Azuki-chan, Ka-chan, and Chan-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-d-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-of-d-of-the-menu.  I've done
it before, but yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I
did it, so I cut it, and I
had to do something, so I affirmed various things.  I
feel sleepy if I can't divide up the roles because of that. Yes, it's important to be strong when you have time to share. There's no cooperation, so much so. But on the other hand, Minecraft has been working for about three years now, and I think he's good at cutting vegetables.  Yeah,
I thought so too, so I thought I could cut it,
so there was an item for cutting boards that said knives, and when I
clicked on the cutting board to open it,
there was a knife, and when I put it next to it, I could cut tomatoes, etc.  It looks like you
can cut carrots, carrots, potatoes, etc., and if you add beef, it's minced
meat.  It seems like it's a
special edition for this time.
Yeah, yeah, that's
right, but it's
amazing to be able to do that. It's certainly possible for Minecraft to
be set up like that.  It's
amazing what they're doing.
But we're all so moved, but
Kara-chan, who's in the middle of her life, probably thinks it's normal. She's a little girl, after all.
Maybe that's why she's laughing. She
doesn't have the luxury to do that lol.
[Laughs]
Nocha, I
touched it. It's cool. Leave it there.
Thank you. It's starting. Do your best. Do
your best. Do your best. Do your best.
Do your best. You must have seen this on the street the other day.  You
came just in time. Hey, it's fine. It's
going smoothly. You're getting a good footing. I'm nervous,
but everything is going well. It's feeling good, it's feeling good. It's so
fast, it's so fast. Oh, it's
smooth.  It's so smooth, it's so
smooth, it's so smooth, it's so smooth, it's so smooth, it's so smooth, it's so
smooth, it's really good, it's like 1 or 2,
it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's
good, it's good  Let's go let's go Let's go Let's go Let's go let's go let's go let's go
let's go let's go let's go Let's guess what this is It's wood It's brown Yeah it's already made of wood Hey hey what what what what is this What is this This is already The
machine is new  So, I guess, what are you making?
What is this? Oh, oh, what is this? What is it? I
don't know what it is. No, I don't know from here.
It's white, white and pink.
What is this? What is this? What is this
? I don't know why. I don't know. I don't know. Share it with me.
What are you doing? What are you doing? What are you doing? What are you
making? I'm really curious about this. I
want to practice this.  At the time, it
was like Mishi's hamburger steak, but
Mishi's handmade hamburger hamburger
What is it? What are you making? What are you doing now? Are you
cutting it? Grilling it? Cutting it.  I'm
grilling, I'm cutting vegetables, I'm cutting vegetables. Do your best,
try your best, do
your best. Looks like it's going to be fun, so do your best. I wonder what you're making. I guess you're
making it. Let's go back later. I ate it. I
ate it. I ate it. I want to eat it. I want to eat it.  Hey,
nice, nice red, early, early, you're already up to stage 5. Oh,
good luck, but you're only at 2 right now. No, but
red is strong. Red is strong. But it's fast, fast, fast.
Hurry up, there's Wan Chin Wachin, I'll let Wan out! Go, dodge, go, go! This princess is a gorilla. That's right, she's strong. My princess has 50g of strength. So don't be sorry, do your best, do your best, do your best.
No, Wanchan.  One chan, one chin, one
chan, one chan, one chan, one chan, one chan, one chan, one chan, one chan, one chan, one chan, one waa, one chan, waaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa  It
's magic that doesn't float, but it's
really strong and strong. Just a little more. Just
a little more. I'm fine. I
can go. It's okay. I'm going to go to the very end. I don't want to be
bossed around, but I can still do my
best.
Do your best, just a little more,
try your best, try a little harder, try your best, let's beat it
Nice, nice, nice, nice
[Music]
Nice, it's a great piece, yellow
Onamaiga is nice
. That's nice. That's nice. That's great. Wow. I
wonder what they were making. It was definitely a daon. It
was a title. I'll
ask you later. I don't know what it is. I didn't understand that one
with the pink blocks and the white one at all.
But when I looked at it, it
was brown. I wonder what it was. Oh, I don't
care, but it was amazingly yellow.
At the end, it was almost brown.  It's all messed up. Hey
, it's not me. What's wrong with
that? Who was it? I
couldn't figure it out in an instant. It must have been a mess.
[Music]
Oh, I'm so nervous. This time is like a flower.
Can we go fishing? I'm here now.  I'm not doing an interview,
so just take a moment
and go
and go.Here you go, this is the air conditioner right now.  It's
hot in my room,
so I open the door and let's get out of the way.I can't live without an air conditioner.But I don't
have an air conditioner at all in my house in Austria.But what about heaven?Well,
in the summer.  It's quite hot, so I
'd like you to turn on the air conditioner, but houses are usually
built without air conditioners, so it's hot, just in case. I
can't think of anything, but it's hot. It's hot,
so it's dry.
It's different, but I'm not asking for it. Even if I'm told, it's not good for chocolate.
Even if I say it, I'll act quickly.
1 Even if it were now, I'd still be blaming it. Oh
yeah, with the air conditioner,
this air conditioner
love, love love, I wonder if the interview statistics are being compiled right now.
This Tsuji is the last one in the rele. Oh yeah, I'm nervous.
[Music]
Oh, I'm really weak at real performances, so it's okay. I
know I can go. It's okay. It's
okay. It's scary.
[Music]
Yes, I'm sure Nerissa will be the first
one, so I'm sure she'll be super nervous.
No, but especially
since she's the one who can fix anything over and over again, I think she'll
probably be the one who feels the most pressure, after all.
Iroha-chan is
probably the last one. I'm just going to go to the bathroom. I
'll do my best. I'll do my best. I'll do my best.  I'm getting
nervous because I'm going to have to do a reread reading, so I'm
going to hand over the baton to my senior, and I'm going to be in the
middle of this, so I'm not sure if I'll be okay, I
want to do my best, but I do
n't know what the actual performance will be, so I was able to do it.  No, I get
it, you
get anxious, right? I wonder
if the points for the relay are high after all.It's the last competition, and I
wonder how it will turn out.Even now, the red team is the best.  Probably
because we have a pretty good lead, right? Yeah, right. I think it's going to
go up in reverse. I
get the impression that it's going to be high at the end,
I understand. It
means that there can be a reversal.  Let's
take a look at the scores for the Koshi race. The
red team was in first place,
so it's 30 points, the white team is 20 points, and the
yellow team is 10 points.
Yes, the red team is a bit amazing, isn't it?
Maybe in 2023, I do
n't know if it's going to be strong, but I still don't know.
From now on, let's
move to the venue for the next competition race.  I don't
know what to do, I'm in love with you,
I'm in love with you, I'm in love with you, I'm in
love with you
[Music]
Oisho, Tireki-chan, it's so messed up, it was
flying off on its own, oh my god, it was flying off on its own, everyone, I'm here. I'm home. My
senpai is amazing. He was cooking really
fast. It was
really fast. What were you making?
Come on out!  It's lamb, lamb, lamb, lamb, lamb, lamb, lamb, lamb, lamb, lamb, lamb, lamb, lamb, lamb, lamb, lamb, lamb, lamb, lamb, lamb, lamb, lamb, lamb.  I was so sleepy
during practice and I'm glad I was finally there because there was even a high school.Actually, I'm
so sorry,
Kankatsu-
chan.What the hell is that?  The
contestant was blown away before the announcement was made.The
cutting-edge technology was so cutting-edge that it was said that it
was a moment of surprise.It
's easy to understand.  I'm going to
dash and
crawl. Go ahead. Oh no,
no, it's better to enter. Yes, you can enter and get a
book, so
open that book and find out what the master of White is.
I'm going to select the general and I'm going to go
ahead and right click on the entry list.
Niame
What layer is it on? It's somewhere in the middle,
like the leader of the memory group. Ame-
chan is on the 5th layer. 5th layer.
So I entered. I
wonder if it's done? It's done, it's freshly made. It's fine, you old man. Oh,
wow, my character design is shaky today
.  It
's okay, you can do it, don't be weak, it's okay Can you make it? Oanka It's okay Yojo It's okay, it's
okay, it's okay, it's
okay, it's
nervous at the end
[Music]
Have Aso
O
Iyaneta English was important  Yes, I've
entered, I'm done, but
I'm at 9, I'm at number
9.  The
order of the contestants is 1st,
yes, yes, next is Choco-sensei.
Finally
, it's nice to hear that
Minecraft is getting familiar with people like this, and
people who are used to it are coming in. It
seems like they're trying to catch up. Let's
go, I guess.
Everyone in the White group, I can hear you, I
can hear you, I can hear you, I can hear you, what do you think?
Well then, who should I choose? No, no, I don't
know. Well then, Iroha. When I realized that the anchor was floating, I
became an anchor, but the wind I heard was my feet.  It's early,
so I'm confident that we'll be able to do something,
so I'm going to do my best. That's
great. I hope you can come in first place, Shiro.
Please
do your best. Please do your best, Zhang. Thank you very much.
Well, that's it for the last time. I'm
back from Hana. I'm
back. It was just a while ago, so when Nerisa-chan was
confused, I
said ``Open Book.'' I didn't hear her say ``Open Book.'
' I was embarrassed to respond.  I'm a man. Let's do
our best. If we're at the bottom, we'll be able to go back.
That's right. Let's do our best. Let's try our best. Let's try our best. Let's try our best. Let's do our best. We're on the right. Ah, we've fallen. We'll
try our best.
Oh yeah, it's here. The water is so cute. Wow! Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaha  It's
okay, it
's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it
's okay today in Korea, I'll remember and do my best.
Yeah, it's the end, so feel free to do it for the last time.The
end is with a smile.Okay, that's it.When we're
done, let's go eat some delicious meat.Let's
talk to the chocolate line, Azuki and chocolate.
Yakiniku Owa Shabu Shabu O Ready to go Ready to go Good luck, Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Strive Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Do Do efforts Ready to go Ready for yakiniku Owa Shabu Shabu O Let's do our best Come on, we'll be waiting for you
Come on, let's calm down
[Applause] Come
on, come on, nice nice catch
Nice catch nice catch Bread
nice nice
Brett Nice bullet, that's what I'm talking about. Go go, leave it
to me, leave it to me, all right, all right, all right, all right,
all right
It's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's
good, it's good, it's okay.
There are times when there are times when there are times, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's
okay.  I do
n't understand myself anymore
[Music]
Hold on, this bread, bread
Hey, it's on the left, it's on the
left,
right?  I'm sorry,
do your
best, do your best, Noi-chan, do your
best, Do your best, Noi-chan, you can go, I'm sorry
, it's totally fine
,
dong-dong-dong-dong, don, do, it's
okay, you can go, you can do it, do your best, it's okay.  Let's
go, let's
go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's
go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.
Hurry, feel good, feel good, do your best, do your best, oh, do your best, oh, bad, bad, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, do your best, Ikeru-chan,
do your best, good luck, Kekaeru-san, do your best
[laughter]
Kai
[Music]
Gogogogogo
Do your best
My
[Music]
Hikore  Or are you going to get sucked in?
No, nice. Oh, it's finally time to give up. Do your best, do your best. Do your best, do your best, Aki.
Senpai, it's like you're going to
hit me
. It's okay, it's okay, I'll hit you properly. It's okay, it's okay
. Eat just yo. Yes,
try your best, try your best, do your best. Do your best. Do your
best. It's
okay. It's hard.
Please wait.  It's okay, it's
okay
, it's okay, it's okay, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.  It
was a fight, I was so nervous.
Do your best, do your best, everyone. It's
over. You're
strong. You're strong. You're strong
. I forgot what to eat.
It's okay. I'm
hungry. I want to be hungry.  Ah, I'm hungry. Let's
eat a lot when we're done. Yes, nice run, nice run, nice run.
[Music] Nice
meat, I want to eat meat, meat, I
want to eat meat. Let's go,
meat. Let's go. Meat. Meat.
Yes, yes, yes, my heart hurts.
Now, thank you for your hard work.
Japanese sub-sub-oun.
Read the food you want. Let's all eat shabu-shabu. Shabu-
shabu, shabu-shabu is
delicious. Shabu-shabu is delicious. Cute, cute. Cute,
soothing, cute. Let's
go, let's make shabu-shabu hot.
My Chiko line brat  The Chico line will take me,
take me
[Music] Give it
to me,
let's leave it all to Choco Choco sensei's choice is berry
Good super nice Yeah
Uh, leave it to me, leave it to me, Aiya, but you did your best. You did your best. You did your best. You did your best. It was amazing. You did your best.
Well then, let's ask Iha, who served as the anchor,
one more time. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
How was it? How was it? We're the best. We'll be
fine from the beginning to the end. We've
put together the cheese work. It
's okay, it's okay, it's okay. The result.  I
was able to finish in 2nd place, although there were many times where I was passed or overtaken. No,
it's amazing, it's nice, it was a
good fight.  Thank you for your
hard work Thank you for your hard
work Thank you for your hard work
Thank you for your hard work Thank you for your hard work Thank you for your hard work Are you mastering it?
Thank you for your hard work, thank you for your hard work, you did it! The color
of the 1st grade test. It
was really good. It made
everyone cry
. It was
so emotional. It was so good.
No, it's 2nd grade. It's
okay, you did your best, you did your best.  Tami-ya I
tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best At first,
to be honest, I
felt like I was having fun, and I was like, ``I'm going to do my best even though it's difficult,'' but I didn't expect it to happen.
Yes, that's right. I don't know until the end. Yes, the first result. I wonder what's
going on.
Yes, that's right. So we're going to hold this ceremony, so please gather in front of everyone. Let's go to the very beginning.
At school, there was a
wall that was not good for
us.We were surprised, and we were sealed away.Now, we
are all lined up with a sore throat, all
lined up neatly in white.  The
white team is fast, they
line up neatly in a single line, and
it's great.It looks like they were separated.Maybe it's because of the correct answer method.There's a lot of
excitement, so there are
only 5 of us, and there aren't many of us.It's
true, the dangerous yellow ones are fighting each other.
Look at the polka! Everyone lined up like a
polka. I've got some bread to cheer me up. Is it
okay? Is it okay?
This is it,
it's a little too much, so I'm yelling at you, but I
'm fine with that.
Yes, I say yes, so the closing ceremony
is about to begin, but what do you think, Mr. Yamiko? Is
this year good? I wonder how it will turn out.
To be honest, I didn't understand it at all,
but
yeah, everyone worked really hard and
worked really hard, and it was a close race every year, so I
thought it was really worth watching.
Yes, that's true, each of them
had their own drama, or rather, there was. I
think it was a drama, including the practice, but
yeah, I think it was really good. The
group that worked hard and didn't have it all together was
a bit like that group.  My mom couldn't come,
so Mio-chan was just talking to me, so
she came and asked me to get along with her.We
lined up a little nice, which was great.I said
yes, yes, so how about the ceremony?  I
wonder if I can do it? I'm getting ready soon, okay. I'm chatting with you, but that's just a relationship right now. I'll wait for a while. I think I'll be able to
go. It's okay,
okay. Well then.  Everyone, have you heard our voice?
Has it been heard? Has it been heard? Has it been
heard? Yes, it has been heard. So, before the ceremony, there
was a huge amount of chat chat because of the competition.  However, everyone  I
would like to say a few words to Sanne-chan, A-chan, and Nodo-chan who supported me there.Yes, yes, Ei-
chan and Nodo-chan,
thank you very much.The voice of heaven.Thank you for your hard work.It
is the voice of heaven.Thank you.Thank
you.  Thank you very much for this year, and for this year as well,
everyone's hard work and
individuality was overflowing, and
we were able to see all the hard work of the three organizers,
so we were very moved.
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you
very much for your cooperation Thank you very much for your cooperation
Thank you very much for your cooperation Thank you very much for your cooperation Thank you very much for your cooperation Thank you
very much for your cooperation
I think it was fun for all three of you to participate, so please come and join us.
Please do your best until the end.Yes,
thank you, thank you very much.Yes,
everyone.Then we
will now begin the closing ceremony.First
of all, I would like to give a closing speech.Yes, please give a greeting from Mr. Samiko, the chairperson of the sports day executive committee.Yes,
no.
Everyone had fun at this sports day.
Yay, I'm glad it was fun.
No, it was really good, everyone. Thank you,
everyone. Every year, we've gotten really busy, and
thankfully, Hololive has gotten busier,
but still, we've had so many people
come together.  I've seen everyone working together,
everyone taking the initiative to call out to each other
and help each other, and I'm
always so impressed by how much I've seen it all.
Thank you very much for your continued cooperation.Thank you very much.Thank you very much.Thank you very much.Thank you very much.Thank you very much.Thank you very much.Thank you very much.Thank
you very much.I would like to take this opportunity
to thank you.I would like to talk to you
about the newcomers and other members of en and a.  I
think it would be great if the number of Hololives increases and we can
all make Hololive even more exciting, so please continue to support us in the future.
Yes, that's great. Yes, please.
Next, Miyo-
chan, please. Yes, everyone this year.  Thank you very much for
participating, and you did a great job!
You did your best, you worked hard, you did
your best. Yes, everyone said yes,
so that's the end of this year.
Thank you
very much. Thank you very much.
Okay, next Subaru.
Okay.  As for Suva, I've
seen a lot of different things from different teams, and I think all the
teams are working hard, and I
think we'll see some results this time around.  It's
one thing that we all worked hard together. I
think the big baby will become a treasure, so I hope that you can make use of the bond we have in the future. It
was a lot of fun to watch. Thank you very much.
Thank you
very much. Nice speech. Nice speech. Nice
speech. Nice speech. Nice speech. Nice
speech. Nice speech. Embarrassing. Thank you.
So, finally, I would like to announce the general benefits.
I would like to make presentations in the order of 1, then 100, and finally 10.
Now, Mr. Samiko, the sports day executive committee chairperson,
please make a special presentation. Thank you.
Yes, then we'll start by announcing number 1.
Yes,
then,
please go ahead.
Whaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaahaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa  I'm
a little scared to announce it, but I don't know yet.No, I do
n't know anything yet.I don't know anything
yet.Okay, let's continue.I'll
announce about 100 first.Okay, yes,
here's about 100.Go ahead, no, no, no,
no.
Oh no no no no no no no no no no no I'll go last.
Okay, everyone, finally the announcement of the 10s.
Wow, that's
okay, so the red hair got 158 points. The
winner is the red hair. Good night,
congratulations. Congratulations! Congratulations! Congratulations!
Congratulations! Wow! The
first class hasn't passed yet.  I know it's frustrating that I didn't do that,
but the way I came out here was also reflected,
so it's dangerous. Let's get along, let's get along, let's get along, we're
friendly.
Please, please, be friendly.
And 2nd place was the white group with 138 points. 3rd place was the white group. 3rd place was the white
group with 106 points. You did a great job. You did a great job. You did a great job.
Yes, it was amazing. It was amazing. Yes.
Why should I award the award?  That's right,
yes, there will be an awards ceremony this time, everyone.First of
all, I'm Gio, who won the same medal as the yellow group.Okay, well then, I'm going to see the yellow group's players, and the
representative of the teacher is Hasbechanpe-
chan.
Please come to the front. Come here.
Please win. 3rd place medal.
Wait a minute.
Temiko-san.  We've
prepared it for you right now.
Hey, congratulations, congratulations, congratulations. Hey,
yea, y'all, everyone's on board. y'all, y'all.
Next, y'all, next is for real. y'all, silver medal for the white team.  This
is Geo from the yellow group, A-chan, please come,
come, come, come, come,
please. Well then, A-chan, you won the gold medal.
Congratulations on your gray hair! Oh, you're so cute!
Thank you for the nice job!
Congratulations!
Congratulations, congratulations,
Osa, and
yes, it's Ji, the gold medal winner of the red team who came in first place.
Stop it, stop
it, stop it, stop it, stop it, stop it, can't we just get along and pick it up? There were so many
diamonds that disappeared so quickly, right in front of my eyes. So that's
all for Holo
Live Sports Day.  Thank you to everyone who has caused 2023 to be a problem.
Yes, thank you, thank you.
What should I do?
Should I put it on the platform over there in the middle? Yes, please. Yes, it's
on the mobile platform. It's over here. Yes, let's move. Come on, come on. Let's move. Come on, let's
move.
Everyone, everyone, line up.  Line up, line up,
line up, please line up. You can get in too. You can
get in too.
Oh, I can't
see it. I can't see it. Okay,
everyone. Isn't there still time? I wonder if there's still time.
Wait a minute,
wait a minute, please. You're here, too.
Everyone's here, too. They're here, too. It's true. I'm so happy. I'm so happy. I'm so
happy. I've lost
my medal.
Oh, I don't think so. It's too
good. If I try it one more time,
I won't
get kicked out. I don't have any more. Oh, I don't have any more. I'm so sad. How can I give this to you?
Kanatakana-tan can't say anything. Yes, yes, that's it.  I
can't raise it, I can't raise it, wait a minute, tap,
why don't you touch it
? I was able to touch it by left-clicking. I'm glad I did it. I'm glad I did it. Ta-
hai-o, everyone. That right in front of me.
Where should I look at that?
Koro-san.  I wonder if I should
look at Koro-san.Koro-san.I feel like I'm looking at Koro-san.There's
a lot of things flying around.Okay
, you should look over there.The
villagers.The villagers.Look at the villagers.Ah, it's true.They're right in front of the camera.
Man Sune photographer here, here
here is
here, are
you all right? Is the
photo showing a little Mel Mel Camel Calcari
Please, I ca
n't
see the foot of the mountain. Thank you very much. Thank you very much. Thank you very much to
all the listeners who took a look at that picture. And to all the
management staff who cooperated so much behind the scenes.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.  Let's
get along a little, let's get along, but we'll get along, let's get along, let's get along.
So this time, I participated in the Hololive Sports Day, and I'm a white 2.
Yes, unfortunately I'm a 2, but everyone, I
had a lot of fun, and the chocolate was a lot of
fun.
So, I'm glad I got a medal.  That's how I feel. I'm going to
take a poop. I'd
like to thank everyone who took the time to watch me. I hope we
can do it again next year.
So I'd like to end this today.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Good job and bye
[Music]
Bye