[Music]
me I
jumped over that deep
[Music]
weee
[Music] I
had it
[Music]
Ah,
no, I was
n't planning on going to see small fish this time,
but I
unexpectedly caught a cat fly, so I'm sorry.  I
can't help it, let's have
fun. There's no book I've enjoyed as much as Jets. Let's
enjoy it. Well
then, last time,
that normal preliminaries. My
brother won, right? Hey
Nito.  Personally, I think we
achieved a good result because we were able to get first place for a moment,
so I think it's pretty good.I personally think that we achieved a good result.This
time, I hope everyone can enjoy the race.  I
think it's great,
Tadashi.Now that the shooting starts at 4pm, I wonder if it's because I'm so excited.  I'll
lend you your courage to play Soma Cartpyon.Ah, Nakatsuna no Kuni,
etc.Next
time, I won't lose,
Papa
, I wo
n't lose.I'll abolish the system where I can't lose in the way.If I
play against you, I'll become very weak.
Well, I'm really
bad at things like having to win or competing with someone, so I thought the best thing to do would be to have fun and
have fun, so I'm going
to have
fun running, Dad. I'm going to have fun running today.
Noel has come too. I
ran a little more when I got there yesterday, but
that one is the one that is strong in Snow Mountain.
Noel is
still Mao. I wonder if all the people around here are
just about the same strength based on the standard.
That's what I think, so everyone is
doing well and making dango.But it's
my first time, and it
was worse when I went to Mario Kart, and
that broadcast was a bit like that for my middle brother or about 11 years old.
Without my mother, I'm always in 11th or 12th place, with
no one behind me, and I'm all white, and
when I say everyone, everyone goes ahead of me, and
even killers can't catch up, and it's
like that all the time.  I
was at the bottom of the class, but being able to become
that dango means that you've gotten that much better.I'm really
bad at games like this,
but even so, I've been practicing quietly and
working really hard, and I'm seeing the results.
Personally, I think
that my sister and I can't play together with everyone else,
so I
don't really play Mario Kart.
When I say "Let's go," I'm like, "Where are we all?" It's
like, "We've all already reached the goal." That's basically what happened in front of that one call, like they were
interested in the entertainment that was waiting for them.  It
seems like it used to be, but now it's like my
brother is messing around and saying things like 6 is good or not,
and it's like who's better
and who's going to be in first place.By the
way, I'm like, 6 I got hit with coke b.  I
feel like I've reached that point,
and I feel like I'm amazing compared to before.I'm not
good at it, but I'm getting better at it.That
's why I hope I can practice science at my own pace and
enjoy it and get better at it.  I
'm feeling like, ``
Yesterday, I'm a rent
student.'' I said, ``How much did I do?'' I
only got 300 to 2,700g, but I feel like I
need to get to about 3,000.That
100 is crazy, right? Hey,
let's practice.  I
don't like the practice of memorizing the courses, but I think it would be better to fight in a national race to know
when to
use items against other people.  I
thought I'd be able to remember it, so I did it over there.
Hey, yeah, that's
right. It's starting. It
's starting. I'm standing here. I've
put on about 4 clothes. I wish the
items would shine. Hey, is that
Dameros' cheese naan?
Meow, Beaver  Meow!
[Music]
A park My mother is not good at it. It's
water.
It's urine.
Sa-san, Noel has chosen 10 mountains that he's good at
.
Ugh, I
like small bread, so this is a good start.If I
eat this one again like before, the flag will be a good start.It won't cause too much
lag.It wo
n't fall
off.It
's
quiet.Sawahama Moon
As an elf.  I wasn't
able to take a photo of the item.It was scraped off again.I ca
n't read it.I'll
remove the dark face.Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
This is how you can take a Nico item Yaba
Eie
rar
me
Why banana or 600?
Oh yeah, that's right, it's all right.
Or Maher deceptive stationery, it's a mushroom, idiot. It's
not Yarolid. What's the flower? It's
not Bach.
[Music]
can.
What was it? Mom.
Why, I don't want to
get in the way, there's no chicks here. There's
no fresh air here for the surfers.
[Music]
4 I
can't go back with a push pick. Wow!
I won't be dropped anymore 4 Honesty in the eyes of A 3 and coke [Music] Alright, I guess it's a good thing I went even though I was dropped Poon! It's a 34-shaku mirror car, isn't it? ko I used to be one too.
Hey, there's something about Weird 4 that made me become a dragon. No,
where's the color? I
wonder if I'll jump on the spot that the viewer chose earlier.
Bowser Castle -
I also chose to play Kikupocha, who is a no-no. It
's because I'm a social punchline.
Setup
, I'm sorry everyone that it's over. I
wonder if I'm a dad. I'm a sonar item. I'm a trash, and I'm going to win the baby park. I'll cover it up and say  But I'm not that strong
[Music]
[Music] I'm
going to make a rave,
that
kind of thing,
but I also
don't want to have one.  That's the
waiting room I wasn't supposed to use here.Bach Kokoko No, it wasn't
here.Ahaha, catch
more fish,
catch more fish, don't turn around.lana
Yeah, yeah, I'm
sorry, but I guess I made a mistake when I went along the line.But
everyone says Naru.  I'm
sorry for telling you to do it. It's scary, everyone.
Yeah
Then I'm stuck without 1 Oh,
well, I'm going to increase it by 224 and move it.
However, it was surprisingly good for me. Is
this an upset?
This is an upset. I
thought it was a small fry, but the number of customers who were pushing it. I'm sure there are a lot of
people who don't like Bowser Castle. Why
Walker Rose?  Miyase: Let
's go home together.
This is a betrayal. Let's wait a minute. We
had already decided to go to Bowser Castle together, but we haven't decided
yet. You didn't listen to me, Miyo-chan.
[Music]
Why the Dragon Lord?
Even if I don't care about it, I can't sleep at night. Ah,
that's the problem. If
I can't run, I'll do my
best. I
don't fall down very often.
[Music]  ]
Now is the best start. I do
n't want to be the first to be relocated. I
don't want to take the position. It's
indigo dyeing. It
gets damp. I'm
grateful for the points, but sometimes the
contents are distorted.  I
can do it.
Seriously, I
thought it was a bit of a misfortune, so I
was completely caught off guard. Wait, I'm letting my
guard down, and my husband is letting his guard down again and again. What the heck?
After all, it's not suitable for financial management for people who are no l.
Please
leave the flying parts for the end.
Now this kid can
tackle someone,
but there's a new item.
Hello!
[Music] I ca
n't see the demon Hey, it's a
pretty close battle.
Ah
[Music]
Damn it Sakura
hero 6 g
Move Hey,
wait a minute, I'm not going
Arthur-
uh-
uh-ah-ah-ah-an Bach Ah-wobbly, wobbly,
well, Kappa Castle is a no-go  Well,
hahahahahahahahahahaha, I've already gone to the Dragon Road.
I'm not giving up yet.
hahaha
[music]
Ugh.
Ahhh
Dragon Road Car
[Music]
Yeah, yeah, I
just took the LS and
saw it.
It was a customer.
[Music] I
got it. I succeeded once.
This is the first time I've had a square car.
[Music]
Streaming eggs once and six times.  I've never been successful.
Good, good.
[Applause] I
'm at a good place. I'm not sure
where I've been,
but if I'm in trouble, I'm not sure where to go.
[Music]  Once
again, thanks to that, I
was able to get it.It's
better not to overdo it.The world is such a bad place.It's
good that I threw it blindly.Part
2Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa than what
if it had fallen.
I saw it.
[Music] That's
because it fell.
[Music]
Dash mushrooms. It makes people crazy.
First of all, Komatsu's Nada-ism is not good. I don't want to
argue either way.
Which one is it?
[Music] I
thought I was overtaken by that last-minute L,
but that wasn't the case.
Red Papa. It
was a shame.
Well, you don't know the outcome until the end. Everyone
scolded me, and this was the end.
6 c 6 shards
4 days  I
was really confused about Soda Saikaku and Saara Kaiyo. I
thought maybe a heavier character would be better, but I guess I thought it was a cute reform like this.  It wo
n't lift unless it's raised.
Later, I said "Lido Spray" because it was not in English.  We're
all going to be picky, right?
At first, we
're going to look at everyone from behind.
After all, we're all in possession.
Together, we
're all white. Let's get along and spread the voices that everyone has dropped.  Karasa
Kitan
[Music]
ano
Sacher I
received a reciprocation
ni
[Music]
over moo Well, I
was in a place like that
bikkuri summer
Good,
now lightning has struck
This
is a place where there is no injustice
[Music] Will there
be sparks?  Hey
[Music] I
hung up my items. I went to the right.
Put it in.
[Music] I
love you. Eh, Ebi
Hisashi.
Show me how to wear it. This wasn't the time to confess.
[Laughs] There's
too little line
[Music]
Somebody will sell me thunder at the start of the game.
Hmm, yeah,
8 petals, why don't you make this 3-2?
Aaaaaaaah
Takakko
Sacchan
[Music]
That's it.
There's no such thing.Last
o
Last
? You've lost it, even the perfect medicinal herb.Well, you
already
have an opponent, so it's within your ability.You're a
genius, you're pushing me to no good.  It's
unusual for Big Blue to
choose Bowser Castle very well,
but Nami-chan's choice is rare.
[Music]
Medium
Mario Kart Star is different from the others, so maybe an
orthodox ending would be
fine.  You know,
I'm not good at this part,
but I don't do this part, but it
's that kind of fingering. It's a feeling that anyone can get good at. It's
difficult, isn't it? I have
n't practiced it until now.
But when I run all over the country, I'm often chosen unexpectedly.The
days are a little rough,
but for me, I can't let it go.
[Applause] It
's my fate that I won't get any coins.
Four companies, Sosa City,
wake me up.
Cart Buboo. Just
a little more. Just a little more. Just say the turtle shell. It's
my
cold. That's it. I won't give you this. I won't give you
this.  It's
okay to try shortcuts, but this is too much. China,
Zach, Vispapan, the
last fe
guy, by
Mach, was emoted. Well,
Noel stepped on it and kicked it a bit.
Ahaha, yeah, yeah, Mio's are overwhelming.
Papa,
Yada.  It was fun on the ridge.
[Music] I
thought it was the same thing as Jeb and I moved the same way. I dare to
say it.
Hello again.
Well, it ended in a middle-of-the-road place, which was neither good nor bad.It was
tough.It was so much
fun to see how exciting it was.  The
undercard is over, step bang,
Jajaan, the four guys, if it
was fun, and I worked really
hard. Thank you so much for the shrimp, it was that day. You
look hot and weak. Hey, that's
good.
Good.