[Music]
me
tell me
keep on um
[Music]
need to figure out the audio
[Applause]
one million
everyone thank you thank you thank you
very
much you thank you thank you
for streaming little tony listen to it
again and again
[Music]
trying to find my destiny
but they keep pushing and pulling me
[Music]
up
could you tell me please
[Music]
oh
i don't even know
[Music]
um
i promise i will
[Music]
what a banger what is this song it's
such a banger what the hell
i wanna if it's okay i wanna play the
there's a 8-bit cover of hinotoni
from fabulous reindeer which is a
channel on youtube
uh which was commissioned for apparently
an
upcoming kfb game from
airborne cat so i want to play now if
that's okay during
two days bgm i think it's quite fitting
and a little change of the of the
usual vibe that we have it's really cool
did you guys listen to this
[Music]
foreign
so yeah um this was unplanned i wasn't
going to
i wasn't really going to do a
super chat stream today but
during the club pinot tony reached 1
million because of everyone's health
thank you so so much so
a bunch of uh a lot of a lot of super
jets came in
which makes me scared because i don't
want to fall behind too much
so we're going to read some super chats
[Music]
and we will first of all however start
with
the ones from the way out collab
are we ready for that let me see
supers uh actually i
download the thumbnail
[Music]
and i actually after the halloween
collab i just wanted to go back to sleep
because i barely got any sleep after
yesterday
uh
i wanted to go back to sleep but now i'm
awake so whatever
that was the story let's start with the
stories i i i didn't get much sleep
oh which is my fault because i always uh
procrastinate too much with netflix
i admire you you can't you work so hard
and care for your viewers of course
i don't you guys are so important to me
[Music]
super chat
i don't unexpected stream but i did not
expect
to uh reach hinotori today
but tomorrow i keep on forgetting what's
tomorrow ah okay okay
tomorrow i actually have um a sponsored
stream at 12
uh japanese san anton which is like an
uh now
minus three hours we have a sponsored
stream
and a little later we have a member
a members only stream
and i was thinking probably for the
sponsored stream i'm not gonna read
super chat so i better read them today i
mean i'm gonna read them eventually but
not
right after the stream yeah remember
[Music]
tomorrow actually i'm gonna do also a
members only stream on christmas as well
because i want to spend some
some special time with you guys for
christmas
yeah oh yeah
what day is it is it saturday it is oh
i will also publish my schedule tomorrow
which means you will know
i mean the members already know but
everyone besides the members will find
out tomorrow who will be the next
holocaust
oh i won't be alone for christmas
finally yay
thanks to you guys i will also not be
alone
let's spend it together there was like
something really big planned for
christmas unfortunately it
had to be cancelled because of the
current uh
you know current situation
it had to be cancelled so i'm really sad
about that i i still want to plan
something else for christmas but at
least we have a member stream and i also
want to upload another
uh fairy tale reading for christmas
and so on yeah
[Music]
but maybe we it's not planned right now
but maybe we can squeeze in another
halloween collab
for christmas let's see
it is unfortunate yeah oh there should i
loop the music
is you can uh loop oh it's already
looping
no
down down okay so let's start reading
the super chat
stay back
oh by the way thanks for the flowers
thanks for the flowers by the way
[Music]
this card what's up discord
it's okay you can tell us who the next
guest is
discord do you want to be my guest be my
guest
now this card only if you become a
youtuber
thank you discord for coming
it's just a super chat reading but very
spontaneous but i wanted to thank
everyone for
helping me reach 1 million on hinotori
[Music]
discord thanks to you i can do holo talk
without you i couldn't do holo talk
discord the future but don't you have
you guys seen like every now and then
people
do like like personifications
of like browsers and applications like
this gordon's own programs you know
yeah i feel like probably someone
already made like a personification
out of this discord like a discord town
probably already exists
maybe just use that and then make a
video out of it there you go you can buy
my million dollars idea
i'm i'm giving all that business to this
score last time what
what what was the other thing i wanted
to do
didn't i suggest something to discord
some business idea
previously in in another halloween
collab
thank you thank you guys for the
memberships by the way thank you
for watching
official post exam celebration super
jack oh did it go well
i saw the best to relieve my stress
tension do you miss me of course i do
but you were always there anyway somehow
do you know who i am of course i know
you are vgamer
free loving you can't hide from me just
by changing your name i know your
unique profile picture i know a bunch of
you guys profile pictures
thank you i'll be at work around when
these streams are happening so i'm gonna
go ahead and drop these super chats in
both three chats now just to be safe
gotta think ahead thank you oh yeah a
bunch of those uh super chats are mixing
up actually
because i have them sorted by order i
can't sort them many other way they
sorted by
in the orders they can they come in and
not buy the order of the stream so
they're actually mixed sorry guys
thank you for the membership wow so many
new members wow what's going on
[Music]
i made friends with a local bird who let
me know about a service called birdie
eats now i can get food delivered using
my allowance for my uncle mickey
i'm now cozy and happy in my hidey hole
oh
[Music]
i don't know why i get so emotional
about this stupid mouse
oh my god so cute casper donkey shirt
another one did i say hidey hole i meant
casa casper
sorry oh my hidey hole was really
adorable just made me feel very very bad
thank you shane casper
so cute i love you i will miss you when
i move out of this house
i will miss you but also at the same
time i will not miss you
thank you thank you
thank you guys for the memberships
[Music]
thank you thank you guys
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you oh my god why why
all the memberships
thank you okay if you see my friend
oh another member oh you had
congratulations
um of course i read it i also read it
now
sometimes i read the message messages
quietly to save some voice
it seems that future wong one has made
an error in his calculations and has
been
terminated so this is future one two
that came to say congratulations for not
only hitting one million when you
eventually see this
but you mean your other channel got
terminated and this is a new new channel
what
tutorials johnny does in the chat please
help us i've been trapped here for three
months already and we aren't allowed to
leave there
are armed guards everywhere can i force
us into 24 hours shift wait please no no
no no i'm sorry
oh stop complaining also thank you for
the membership
thank you soon stop coming yeah it's uh
the outro of the i'm playing it directly
from youtube
so it's the outro of uh
of after hino28 bit is being played
thank you for the membership an airborne
[Music]
and then better than most things pop up
i don't know the melody
why do i not know the melody what the
hell
god such a banger
[Music]
because i said i played only one stream
a way out on one screen
is a bit difficult one thing that
confuses me in a way out because i use
the mouse and
the keyboard is that when you're in the
screen you don't see where your mouse is
but
but but you kind of have to go down and
up sometimes with your mouse and then
eventually at some point your mouse
accidentally leaves the window because
you
don't see where it is and then you tap
out and accidentally kind of sucks
[Music]
i should get another monitor no i refuse
thank you for the membership oh thank
you for having me
i i don't think i'm gonna get it oh my
god guys yesterday
yesterday i wasn't calling at kelly's
place
her tv is huge
[Music]
her tv is
huge did she ever mention how big her tv
is
did she ever mention it in her stream
did she say it i don't know like
interesting stuff i don't know man but
she did yes yes
it's huge when i went into like
the last time i went
when i visited her place she didn't have
the tv yet and she didn't have the couch
yet
[Music]
so i went i went there yesterday it's
huge
holy oh
and you guys remember how i think in
yesterday's dream
i told you about i told you
about like that that that program in
japanese tv
every new year's eve and they have this
um
[Music]
they have uh they have this program
that's uh
24 hours cocky no sky
[Music]
you remember how i mentioned that so
yeah i asked kelly because i was like
i thought that gallery doesn't have a
normal tv but you can actually listen to
normal tv
watch normal tv in her place so i asked
her if i can come over
for new year's eve so we're most likely
going to watch
it together on new year's eve at her
place
song name is literally there
kinotori it's just the 8-bit version of
my song
i i don't understand how people are
asking for the time of the song are you
guys for real
are you guys for real how could you miss
the title of the song
how what people keep on asking
what's the song name what's the song
[Music]
so yeah i'm happy that i found a place
where i can watch
um dad's program for new year's eve
yay
[Music]
and i think that time i might actually
sleep over yesterday the taxi ride
i had to take a taxi to get home because
it was past midnight
holy that was expensive that was so
expensive callie even had to borrow me
money but i'm
giving it back of course and i got sick
in the car
because i was staring at my phone the
whole time got really sick in the car
never do it again next time when it's
after midnight i'll just have to sleep
over
such a waste of money to
spend on the taxing so much holy
that taxes plan yeah damn
but i wanted to get home quickly because
i had to sleep in order to be awake for
a way out isn't there uber
uh there's the uber app but it just
sends you normal tax scenes
so it's like expensive there's no
typical uber like you guys know it in in
japan
it is there is an uber app but it will
send you normal taxis
now
[Music]
so unfortunately that's bad
how about buses not that late no no no
no i mean
depending on where exactly you live
there might
there's there there can still be trains
after midnight
but not not that long i think there
wasn't any
i think there wasn't any other train i
don't know i don't know i didn't even
check
but i just went straight to the taxi
also let's continue a little bit jeans
tv dancer
[Music]
foreign my birthday makes me feel both
happy and blessed happy birthday
wee happy birthday nice birthday
the last airbender thank you thank you
tbc studios thank you shannon and urban
cat thank you and complete my tanki
i hear the 505 is really difficult but i
think you got really
up until now the game didn't seem
difficult at all
would be weird if suddenly they really
upped the difficulty of the game
[Music]
dude
team
[Music]
sorry i got congratulations uh or
hinotori reaching 1 million
[Music]
in the discord
will you guys ever do a face reveal what
do you mean i'm revealing my face right
now
what do you mean hello do you not see me
open your eyes
this is me this is real
this is me i'm exactly where i'm
supposed to be
now what do you mean
confusing me what the hell
[Music]
i fell off i fell off a lot
okay i feel like in the way out collab
today we didn't make
much progress there were too many games
to play
there were too many pl games like
basketball darts
baseball uh the the one with the
horseshoes
l trotsky thank you and dark weep thank
[Music]
stand so i can't go into the basement
again
are you okay rocky dancing
real doll i love the i love the humor
that we have going on
and the the funny jokes that we have
going on but please always remember
i would never do anything bad to you
guys i will never do anything to hurt
you
okay i just want the best for you
for real i love you
i just want to pass for you
[Music]
frs kfp overused mob thank you
never heard of the rules
yay the usual room my favorite tyreke
duncashin
run while you still can
you guys are being way too open recently
about what's happening in kfp do i have
to remember you
what stays in kfb oh no what happens
when kfb stays in canopy
messed it up i messed it up
thank you what happens in kit if he
stands and gets me got it
[Music]
are you going to kill me i was looking
for jim and i couldn't find him is that
going to be
me pumped are you calling me mom that's
so cute
thank you thank you
yes it is too late to quit what the hell
thank you it's monkey
and
[Music]
this fish catching scene happened the
exact same way as it did with amangura
really
was one of them not able to catch a fish
and the other one was which one
which one caught the fish was it ahmed
and then gura was just eating the
fish i meant caught i can't imagine that
[Music]
i recorded it i knew it i knew it but i
struggled hard i knew it
yeah makes sense
because is the fish
she probably just felt sorry for the
fish
[Music]
thank you thank you for the red super
chance
what can't you hear some money i don't
have milk though
what thank you thank you for the red
super chat
oh wow thank you for the support
i i think i remember somewhere in the
stream i was jokingly asking for money
and callie was asking for milk
oh yeah yeah when we were going to that
house
thank you thank you thank you well who
will give kelly milk then
she said my name i can die now don't die
you're not a phoenix i don't want you to
die just yet
[Music]
hello fellow kfp employees kfp is a
great place there's nothing wrong
there's no wheat
script basement everything is safe so
here it's fine thank you for protecting
kfb
keep it going keep it up is
there's nothing wrong with can't be it's
all all good here
well there's nothing suspicious no
no multi-cloud slick other than kashim
kinzidakis cloud
kelly's accent kelly's texas accent was
so good
i wish i knew how to do act english
accents like british accent
american accents and all that that would
be nice
[Music]
should i give you guys a link to the
8-bit remix
someone in the chat asked for it
let me i already mentioned it at the
beginning of the stream but let me let
me uh
let me pin it great that the house
doesn't have any
explanation on what it is but oh well
i'm too lazy to fix it now
[Music]
thank you for the membership
67 thank you i sneezed again so here's a
bunch of snooze strats again
vlog 67 packaging
star creators master dancer
looking for the
yeah it barely has any views so if you
want to check it out i think the creator
would be very happy
there's a bunch of remixes though i
wonder if i can i know i only got like
permission for that one i didn't ask the
other remixes but there's a
one remix from jackal diako
d-y-a-k-o that i also really like
i just don't wanna play it and then get
copyright strike i don't think they
would do it because it's my song in the
end
i thought it would probably be fun
probably would be fun
not me on pin that
i mean jackal asked for my permission to
make a remix
oh
let me play that remix
it's really cool did you guys listen to
it
listen to this
[Music]
me
which is coming now
[Music]
yes
and it's chill again
[Music]
oh
here we go again
[Music]
i that was that was my favorite remix of
cali song
so i was like so happy when diaco made a
remix for me
i was so hyped let's play it
again
i'll turn it down and continue reading
super chats
oh this is so good
[Music]
when it is
thank you
way to find songs out of japan's website
of course
do you have spotify do you have amazon
music do you have itunes anything like
that
yes open it up look for hinotoni
or look for
[Music]
ignore me don't look at the ceiling i'm
just taking notes for finding a way out
for myself later
oh casper you're so cute you write the
best super chats i swear
[Music]
thank
wow
[Music]
thank you
what will you name yours and what would
you prefer
dada i would prefer a daughter and
a name
name for my daughter
rafaeli obviously obviously what else
[Music]
oh it's difficult
oh you guys are giving me name name
suggestions
oh he's not exactly our daughter
[Music]
call it kfc bucket but that's a name
that's asking for be bullied in school
how about monica
monica clara that's a
cute name are you oh wait you're you're
combining
cali with kiana clara
i got such a cute name actually in
german is quite
um common clara i get the old name it
used to be
popular back in the days i think
clara that's cute though
[Music]
that's very cute i like it
which last name will you pick kiara
mori calliope
i think i would go for money i would
take her name because
her name doesn't sound so good with my
name but my name looks
sounds good with both names i'd probably
go for morty
[Music]
moss
oh
[Music]
and that's where the super chat for a
way out ended
so i'll read now the ones for
the minecraft collab that's
[Music]
the previous stream when you guys went
crazy
no tangent oh i did go on tangent one or
two i did i did i did
the collab was so cute which one
yeah we're getting a lot of really good
art that we can use for families i'm
really thankful because like
always using my own face kinda gets
boring at some point
i'm glad i can use
it
guys for drawing stuff for our
thumbnails thank you so much
yeah so here we go super chats for the
hall of fame lab let's go sweetheart
and also announcing everyone hinotone is
only 1.2 k views away from 1 million
you guys made it during the stream wow
that's all because you guys are so kind
to me
and always so supportive of me thank you
thank you thank you and everyone
thank you thanks for thanking canvas
nice packaging
canvas night again that vision wait
that's true has two red super chat
[Music]
for the glory of kfc church break the
one million line we'll live and die as
brothers
paint now rewarding the afterlife
thank you totally another coke by the
way we're just a family
i i'm not a slim either just like seeing
bright colors and stuff on the screen
but seriously brothers and sisters make
you stand here and now
one million do not falter remember the
cancer benefits package
yes remember everyone remember the ksp
benefits package
thank you
thank you for your support it's so kind
of you so generous
generous can't pronounce the words
thank you
i hope you guys are not sick of the song
yet
how
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat oh
wow thank you so much congrats on 1
million for hinotoni
very well deserved for such a banger and
for such a hard-working pigeon
kitchen
[Music]
i'm very confused but thank you very
much
thank you thank you sandy love you
always supporting me so
much you have no idea how grateful i am
thank you i love you
thank you always every every every
stream you're there
always there for me always supporting
thank you so much
[Music]
thank you but i'm not a pigeon
thank you
[Music]
thank you soon lovelock thank you soon
looking for the top also of the red
super chat thank you
congratulations channel 31 million views
you are now 1 million viewers majestic
youtuber phoenix
i'm sure that next year we'll grant you
many more million views
like yay
i hope i hope for the next year as well
you will all follow me and continue to
support me
it's crazy how it's almost 2021 huh
crazy
this version slaps doesn't it it's so
good
so good guess of course of course
of course of course hashtag
thank you yes we'll do thank you always
thank you of course thank you
thank you until the end of earth dental
thank you
thank you of course i will we will thank
you
was it even a question i don't know
sometimes i ask myself
i ask myself there several of me
[Music]
oh yeah here comes the chorus
thank you you're an inspiration so it's
a given i gotta stay with you till the
end thank you
remember when you retweeted the thing
[Music]
today
i i have to say
when i retweeted that i
did not realize and i thought that
mama luna just thought that that's the
way you draw
that i don't know
but then i got a bunch of replies which
were like oh my god
oh my god yeah bye oh my god what the
is that and i'm like
oh and then and then mama lonely tweeted
out that she was like super confused
about what we were talking about
and then i was like oh but i
already retweeted it
and i didn't want to untweet unretweeted
i thought that would be real
to do
sorry i i panicked but i
it's all good it's
[Music]
it was too late already
i didn't want to unretweet it because i
didn't want to hurt mamaloni's feelings
or make mamaloni think that you did
anything wrong
[Music]
by the way mama noni drew the
video artwork for him tony
which is so gorgeous
so gorgeous so
really appreciate her i mean i think all
of you know
because i always retweet her art that
she does for me
but it's so beautiful i just love it so
much tonight i definitely want to ask
mamaloni again for
assisting me in future projects
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
you know just gotta you know think it's
something else
i love the way she draws yeah i love how
she makes my hair like super fluffy
like i'm i'm from the 80s or something
i love the way she fluffs me up extra
fluffy
hey we're just using it on the nose no
no no
no okay
lovely so
i have sung a bunch of old songs already
but
apparently you guys are too basic to
recognize their own songs that i sing in
kanoke
because i go more into the female idol
directly i sang
[Music]
how is that not made into city pop yet
it's that is such a good song
someone made it into city pop come on
remix it remakes the out of it
when will we finally fully call plastic
love next
uh next unarchived kanoke stream maybe
but actually um
next external okay stream that is not
themed uh
christmas i think because i'm doing a
sunday american time monday japanese
time
monday europe as well
european time and i'm doing an archive
christmas
sunday for uh
american time zone and canada i guess
in all those areas
sunday night
[Music]
it will be on my on my following
schedule
but that would be already too late to
tell you so i'm telling you now
it is planned for um
monday um
i mean we could do it there oh yeah
should i do it one o'clock or two
o'clock it's one o'clock this time
monday yeah
yeah yeah
monday even one o'clock or two o'clock
japanese standard time
[Music]
for probably an hour or so so you better
come because it's not gonna be archived
[Music]
try to sing you some german christmas
songs as well and some
english and some japanese ones hmm
already thinking about what songs you're
saying at japanese standard time 1
o'clock for 2 p.m
2 p.m 1 p.m or 2 p.m
i generally don't like singing in german
but well anyway that was a weird
tangent thank you looking for the top
thank you
thank you so much you are
always there for me so i really
appreciate it really
really really i really do thank you
always
i hope you have them i hope you're gonna
have some nice holidays and nice
christmas
gift something to yourself please buy
something buy yourself a hamster or
something
[Music]
thank you soon sweetheart thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
i already bought myself a ps5 oh how is
it
eric the cafeteria
congressman one million views but he
knows he hope you have a merry christmas
that's quite early and happy new year
that's also very early thank you for all
that you have done so far this year i'm
looking forward to next year thank you
it is so weird it's so weird december is
like
it's so crazy that
stuff is happening right now also
tomorrow is my my brother's birthday
[Music]
gotta send him the nintendo switch for
my for my brother
he didn't want the playstation 5 he
wanted a nintendo switch can you believe
it
can you believe it good taste
i have to say because he wants to play
uh breath of the wild on the switch
which i deeply understand
happy only birthday i gotta figure out
how to send him
no i told him to make an amazon wishlist
so i can buy it off of it
let's see if i can handle that
[Music]
thank you guys he's probably not
watching this stream probably
not will we play
asap calamity so after a little bit of
thinking about age of calamity i've
watched um
i watched some play through
i've been ever let's player i watched
some episodes of the playthrough of it
and i realized
it's a fun game but it's not a good game
for streaming
because it's literally just just
sweeping enemies
24 7. i don't think it will be
entertaining if i stream it
it's just like continuously killing and
killing and killing and killing and
healing and yelling and killing
however the breath of the wild world
is really beautiful and i love the
graphics but if anything i would
play breath of the wild and not age of
calamity
she said you do a test stream now i'm
sad there might be
um a one time only like a me showing you
the game like the beginning of the game
stream eventually
that i still see as a possibility but a
whole play rule nah
nah definitely not
unexpectedly my birthday was today oh
then
you thought it was it still is happy
birthday
trevor g duncan thank you i love you as
you enter my theme song
the meaning behind it isn't lost on me
it helps me
it's helped keep me focused and
motivated when i need it the most oh
really
i can't thank you enough thank you
travertine
thank you jacob also thank you so much
for the red super chat i'll get to you
soon
cheers oh wait there's a bunch of those
oh my god
looking back to looking back you have
worked hard
struggling to find your path and yet
suddenly reach your goals
if for any reason you still might doubt
yourself in any way please remember
remember you've accomplished so much in
such a short time continuing
looking for it you still have so many
things that you want to do
so many goals to achieve so many
tangents to grow on
and words to mispronounce
i am burning with anticipation and
eagerly awaiting what your future holds
thank you travis
you're the best owl i could ever ask for
thank you because it really sweet thank
you for your kind words
thank you
thank you so much i will i will do my
best
i will do my best in the future as well
to to um
find the right path to reach my goals
and not not get pulled astray
as i've mentioned it in my in my songs
thank you i'll give you a kiss even
though that wasn't a red one
[Music]
congratulations on reaching one million
on the hino we're eagerly awaiting
casey's second season out of my opening
now
it should be more like an ending don't
you think
we have an opening now we need an ending
although people like to say the ending
is uh one of kelly's songs which i
really like
um i like the idea that was really cool
but i need my own ending
i need my own ending to my own time
your story isn't over yeah it's not over
but i already got to prepare the ending
what
what if my story ends and i don't have
the ending prepared well that would suck
[Music]
i hope i can give you guys some more
music
there is um this month
and at the end of the month i will
upload
something with kelly it's not as
original
it will be a song cover but we're
finally gonna upload it so
i'm just waiting for kelly's uh uh
vocals
just waiting for her to record the
vocals and then we are
ready to upload it hopefully i
ultimately at the end of the month
it will be uploaded in 2020 before 2020
ends i promise
and it will be dope
i picked a perfect song for us
i love it okay
you will probably also enjoy it since
you're you seem to be a fan of both me
and cali
so i hope you will enjoy that
[Music]
thank you you're the very first human to
say my name wrap the right way
wait did i say it right again or did i
mess it up this time i don't remember
how i said it last time
[Music]
thank you so much for your support thank
you
you guys are way too kind to me but i
appreciate it fodi
thank you so so so so much
i hope you're not sick of the song yet i
hope i hope you still like it
listen to it every now and then when you
when i'm not streaming or so
thank you welcome to the membership
kawaii pediatrics
lubricated
congratulations on one million views on
hirotoyo keep continuing being the
amazing majestic phoenix
[Music]
supplies
but i hope you also know that i love you
guys
can you share the link for this remix
it's in the pin comment
trevor t oh wait there's a there's a
super chat that makes all of your super
chats into a red one i think
in this stream
[Music]
[Applause]
wait a second
[Music]
bow
tell me
[Music]
but i know something amazing when i see
it and it's you
keep sending bright and burning hot and
being true to yourself and there's
nothing you can't achieve you're
my idol i love you oh come on i love you
too
it's so sweet you guys are such
good motivational speakers
i love you all thank you so much you're
a beautiful
owl you're looking really really fresh
in your
[Music]
picture as well in your profile picture
sexy owl i like owls
[Music]
congrats on one million on the hilltop
so proud of you all of your hard work
paid off and you're receiving all the
recognition you deserve
watching your growth was a journey with
such a journey don't stop being you
thank you i will try to do it i will try
to stay myself
and also always improve myself
which is difficult but i will try
manchester
united
[Music]
but this is a special occasion thank you
so much
[Music]
and i can't wait to celebrate with you
later you know you guys are
um you guys are all congratulating me
for 1 million on my music video
6 goals reaching 1 million subscribers
let's go
thank you for the rest of my job thank
you
thank you emilio
[Music]
bowie
[Applause]
tell me
it's not impossible the weird thing is
it's not impossible you know before i
joined home life
i looked at youtubers who had
100k subscribers and i was like wow
they're famous
wow 100k that's insane
i was looking up to them and was like
holy that's amazing and still
still it's still amazing but
seeing how i reached much more than that
now it's crazy
one 100k was already an insane number to
me
but i thought if i reach that i will be
so so so so
grateful so happy so surprised
but now we are over 600k and eventually
we might have 1 million
that's such a crazy thought to have
[Music]
that numbers don't even seem like
numbers anymore like it's so weird it's
so confusing
when i appreciate it it's crazy i would
have been
when i enjoyed her life i thought that
reaching 100k for me
was like already my goal
and something amazing and that i i
wouldn't i wouldn't expect any anything
more than that
i wouldn't expect more than 100k
but we reached that on the debut day so
[Music]
thank you you made such an amazing sound
that deserves all the recognition it has
received road to 2 million now
i don't want to keep on pushing you guys
to watch the video again and again and
again
but if you guys want to do it let's
let's do it
let's do it possibly one million before
six month anniversary
oh i gotta speed up a little bit to do
that that would be
that would be amazing to reach it before
half a month
a half a year hmm
[Music]
thank you
is
[Music]
my soul is satisfied yeah free free
collapse with
uh kelly in a bro the collab yesterday
on her channel
the way out collab and the one that we
did with all five members
[Music]
a lot of cali titty moments
damn ryan v duncan little debbie and
thank you for the win super dad
oh my god thank you so much thank you
for your support
thank you thank you thank you very
generous of you
thank you for supporting the song thank
you
[Music]
everyone's so kind you ain't good at
fighting on top of the tree was
hilarious as well
i don't know why i had put on my radar
please don't take it the wrong way
i just had fun with cuda today
i felt like fighting gooda but in a
friendly way just like how
how i don't know how kids fight with
each other but in the end they love each
other
me and good i had some fun there i
needed someone to let out my emotions
and my energy and my my energy i don't
know where that even came from i was
kind of sleeping
i i i probably will i probably will take
a nap after this thing
[Music]
summer tony was a fun comedy duo
i had to hold myself back so that so
that i wouldn't kill her
didn't want to go too far
[Music]
1 million
i'm so glad we reached 1 million i'm so
happy it makes me so proud i can't i can
tell my mom
mama i have 1 million views on my music
video
[Music]
is your dream come true
to have so many people listen to my
music over and over and over again i
mean you guys are partially
forced because otherwise you will be put
into the
usual room
[Music]
but
it's my top song on spotify thank you
[Music]
is there such a thing as free will kiara
yeah
yeah yeah you will have free will
but i think you all want to
support kiara i said woke hashtag yolk
i know i know you thought
[Music]
i wouldn't hurt you guys i would never
do that
i haven't been listening as much as i
could have oh that's no problem because
i don't want the song to drive you
insane yeah that is a good choice the
wife choice
thank you very much tai chi willie
thank you
[Music]
what you made your name longer i can't i
can't read all of it because it gets
caught up but what did you what did you
do
bronx 819 kfb shameful
time oh
oh because of fine
[Music]
are you ashamed of yourself now
i think it took me a moment to
understand what that means
sorry i'm yawning a lot again
don't worry about it i i like it when
you guys
um tease me as long as it doesn't get
too much
[Music]
you're the best bronx you're the best
not a shameful thought you can get rid
of that if you wanna
no no need to be ashamed i will also
visit
from my mate australian mate what's up
what's up
what's up congrats on one million views
on hina don't you think
thank you so much thank you for the
support
thank you sharon i appreciate it thank
you all my heart
with all my heart thank you so much for
your support
[Music]
thank you never been more proud of you
here's to another million
thank you vedo thank you
tickets monkey thank you for the red
super chat
oh wow congress and one million views on
hirokoni i guess the effect of being
happy when something good happens to
someone you care about greatly
but it's also given me so much joy to
see you successful and happy
love you kiara and i look forward to
your future successes
thank you
so sweet that you're happy for me
thank you i hope something happy
something great happens to you as well
so i can be happy for you as well
thank you so much thank you so much
that was on purpose i somehow mixed two
languages in one sentence
no way that was the real albedo it was i
think
i know it was a very nice super chat but
it must have been the real
he must have uh had his better face
did didn't do it he's going back to
tunsun very soon
he denies it he's just embarrassed
take it monkey thank you with all my
heart i love you
[Music]
comedian number one comedian thank you
my rep needs to stay but what
how does it help me to reread it
it says obito the jfp janitor it's the
same
it's the same currency
oh no i will not reread it
that was a wholesome message nothing
you would you you were nice for me nice
at me
for once in the i will leave it at that
there is no need to reread the message
no
[Laughter]
what a nice message he likes me again
finally
[Music]
i already read those quotes
you made a pledge to me your voice is so
beautiful and unique oh thank you
you're happy to hear that it's so weird
because after listening to my
voice after singing listening to my
singing voice a lot of times i got sick
of listening to it
i feel like it sounds stupid
because i'm just i just listen to it so
many times it sounds
awful to me now
[Music]
but as long as you guys like it
as long as someone likes it and i'm
happy
thank you cameron stricker thank you
thank you remember when i said i once
said
chat in a long time that was a lie
congratulations on one million repeat
i'm tony i have a lot of fun playing it
on my guitar
and singing it thank you
i'm glad you enjoyed the song so much
thank you so much
i'll keep cheering you on from my casa
casper in the ceiling
so cute oh my god
[Music]
so adorable thank you casper i love you
you are an angel thank you so much
congratulations on 1 million views for
hinotoniki
less than a month too really
[Music]
fast
i thought it was already over a month
yay oh you guys are amazing
came up thanksgiving yeah 26 times
oh that's that's
[Music]
let's
thank you jacqueline thank you i didn't
realize that
thank you so much jacqueline dr vibes
and bronx
[Music]
casper is this true if so why has he
escaped
[Applause]
[Music]
what wait my brain cannot um
understand what you're saying i told cat
i told bloop that if he would eat casper
i would let bloop free
but casper's still alive well in that
case bloop chose to freed himself
he just freed himself i don't know
gotta get comfy here it wasn't me
i guess bloop is just an independent
shark
anyway he is a shotgun he looks um
he looks like he doesn't look he doesn't
look very much like a
like a dangerous shack
he doesn't he's emergency food but he's
also
a shark isn't he
a tiny shark it doesn't look that
intimidating
[Music]
um where was i
take it monkey i read that lunch
dude
[Music]
who had struggled to go with the flow
she pulled out the song
that reached 1 million and now she knows
she's successful
congratulations you're doing great a
great job thank you
i won't read the rest that's insulting
thank you thank you so much
[Music]
is
even though i'm pretty sure i
contributed at least about a quarter of
them
thank you sapphire kitten thank you
and just want to give another big
congrats to you your song has helped me
warm up
in this chilly holiday season
yes i get it thank you
anyway so happy to be here celebrating
with you and everyone you rock my socks
dark purple
thank you i love you
fake cat sick burn huh
just kidding you're a real cat of course
you're a real cat you are you are a
little cat sorry
[Music]
you for someone else uh you are a real
cat of course
oh my gosh
[Music]
ally has no content thank you
are you patronizing me no because i
don't even understand what that word
means
i don't think i'm patronizing you when i
don't know what it means
[Music]
what
thank you
did you want to send that super chat to
amelia
smallwood thank you for the red super
chat
hey congratula thank you australian mate
how's it going are the australians all
listening to my song every day
if not why not
[Music]
well thank you for watching the
christmas collab although i i i
personally hope that we can do another
one on christmas yeah
franklin thank you and elsa
[Music]
but i kind of got locked out of my bank
account after the last super chat
don't worry about it don't worry about
it
don't worry about it please it's enough
you don't have to super cut anything
[Music]
i apologize for not hitting 100
recordings i had to make
do with 56 because hinata hit 1 million
views too quickly i still can't remember
the lyrics after all that
[Music]
me neighbor
me
[Music]
what
is
[Music]
gonna go on a trip with cali sometime
soon i'm really looking forward to it
we're not gonna say where we're going
until after we're going there
but it's the place i always wanted to go
to
so i'm really excited to finally finally
see
[Applause]
that that area yeah
thank you so much claymore thank you 29
thank you
guys general pickle in thanksgiving gary
carter thank you for the pinky
function i'm so happy for you and glad
you're here for us during this holiday
season of course i'll be here for you
24 7 anytime because i don't have a real
life
it's habit time living yeah
this is my real life this is my life now
i'll be
[Music]
now let me refresh and i i will also
disable the super chat now
because
[Music]
it's already gone it's already gone
i think everyone had their chance
[Music]
but it's only 90 minutes plus yeah but i
also didn't plan to stream today and
it's my first stream today
actually my fourth stream in 24 hours no
it's actually my fifth stream in 24
hours
what the it's my fifth stream in 24
because yesterday at this time i was
still playing rhizome
[Music]
right huh fake sleepover is two
a way out is free halloween collab is
fourth
and this super chat reading is 5.
[Music]
uh so i am i am quite exhausted some
monk
and i wanted to go to the supermarket to
get some bread
and some salami and
gherkins i still have at home
[Music]
so since this is my fifth stream
we have caught the super jets and we
will get to the end now together
together we will find the end
at the light of the tunnel no the light
at the end of the tunnel
[Music]
let's find the end of the tunnel where
did we stop
[Music]
here we are okay
thank you for playing it on superchat
everything i'm sure if fabulous reindeer
was here he'd be frill
it's dope it's so good i love the 8-bit
version it's really dope
thank you for commissioning me
[Music]
big super chat thank you so proud of
your amazing accomplishments and
milestones balls
i've been around since debut and seeing
your growth is so inspiring and you
definitely hold a special place in my
heart
all you do big love from your female
families female
[Music]
hello
look i have you on my radar
who's kidding thank you thank you very
soon i really appreciate it
i'm glad to have you in my fan base
[Music]
don't call the police please say
that same thing i'm sorry i apologize
i'm sorry
thank you soon i love you thank you for
your support
luna is referred to for chad thank you
so much
270 characters are not enough to express
my gratitude
if i am the one that needs to be
grateful
thanks for the much-needed boost to my
rick drive oh i've set
high goals in one step until i reach
them so thank you canada for everything
you've done and for everything to come
loonies i am the one who needs to thank
you thank you for the support
i'm glad i could help you with your work
motivation i suppose
that's great to hear i'm glad i could be
helpful
i hope you'll continue watching my
streams and getting some energy out of
[Music]
that
hello
[Music]
thank you my question is what advice
would you give to someone interested in
becoming a streamer
advice that's that question is very um
how do you say data in english
it's a very very um very
wise question uh
well uh
abrupt yes that's what i was looking for
it's a very broad question
because i'm not sure if you're asking
about the audition process generally or
the preparation process or i don't know
[Music]
but
it depends very much on if you want to
be an independent retrieval or
a victor but in a big company like cover
there's um there's a huge difference
you gotta you gotta think about
what do you actually wanna do and then
try to
figure out if you're actually gonna be
able to do that uh in
a company with restrictions
or if you want to be independent where
you can do whatever you want but you
don't really have the support of a
company
it's a big difference really so think
think deeply about it and one more
important thing
think about if you actually have time to
invest into this because if you want to
do it properly
then you should be able to invest a lot
of time into it
because if you don't then you won't be
very successful successful if you want
to be successful
then you have to be able to invest a lot
of your time into it
and you have to take the risk that if
especially if you're independent
even if you put all of your energy and
time into it you might not be successful
because right now it's kind of booming
and everyone is
uh everyone wants to be a beacher right
now there's so many independents out
there right now
so you have to figure out a good balance
of
having a base um a safe base
something you can fall back onto like a
different job or something
but still have enough time to actually
get this thing started because if you
don't
like hype up your w and then actually
like put out
constant content in the beginning from
the beginning continuously
and people will not pay attention to you
and quickly move on to someone else i
suppose
so the best is especially even if you're
in preparation
preparation time and you're still
debuting trying to prepare a lot of
things
try to think of projects right
and preparing everything as much as you
can
and then once it happens put all your
time and energy into it
as much as you can because the beginning
the debut
time is very important because many
people will pay attention to debuts
and then decide if they like you or not
the debut is possibly the most important
stream
for a feature
[Music]
i'm trying to be unique yeah
i know that's a weird it's hard like how
can you try to be unique
you just gotta find something about
yourself the important thing is also i
guess like if you're independent then
you probably have a lot of input in what
your design is gonna be you probably can
decide everything about it
[Music]
um
regarding that i understand how much
people want to
get become their dream dream persona
or whatever like the most beautiful
design they could ever think of
i think it's important to get some more
input than your own input because the
design
design decides a lot of things well the
design is
if it's something that only speaks to
you but no one else that's great for you
but if it doesn't speak to anyone else
but you
then you might not have an audience in
the end
[Music]
so it's good if you maybe get some input
from people into your
into your design yeah
okay that's that's all the advice i give
to you for free
thank you for coming to my ted talk
thanks for coming to kiara ketu
[Music]
so you recognize us by our pfps and then
who am i i know exactly who we are side
quests
where aren't you gonna hold back on the
super chats and you're sending another
one just to make a stupid joke
[Music]
welcome back i guess you cannot hold
back on those super chats everyone just
wants to tell their jokes
and be funny i thought you said you
wanted to
to not send so many super chats anymore
well here we are again
here i am once again i
turn into pieces can't deny it can't
pretend
i know you i sad quest
magazine
the fact that you're doing a fruit
stream today really shows your
dedication and hard work converting
thank you i was like
if i wouldn't have done this stream now
i would probably be napping
so it's probably good that i'm doing
this stream
otherwise i i would be i can't wrong
well it's the first today for me it's
the first day but it's the fifth and 24
hours
no problem you didn't count wrong at all
part time warrior full-time video break
hell yeah
nothing is very important that is always
good that is true but if i would nap
then i would not be able to sleep at
night and then i would mess up my sleep
schedule again and i just know if you
fix don't wanna
don't wanna mess it up again i just
don't sorry about it
thank you
that's also usually educational videos
what was not educational about my
streams
i think they're always educational who
is dead
how is that where is that what is that
explain to me explain
who said are you cheating on us um
excuse me looking for top you shouldn't
be the one talking
you're cheating on me with gloria okay
you are not the one to talk
that is true
don't break down
[Music]
why would that mean that you're perfect
what the hell thank you though
thank you i'm happy to hear that you
think that money
i'm glad people think i'm relatable i
know it's so relatable
i know it's so relatable to be a phoenix
who can never die that's so relatable
just kidding so relatable
just kidding i know what you mean thank
you so much
[Music]
isn't everyone in the phoenix now
can you speak spanish no don't you tell
me please where i need to go
[Applause]
[Music]
but the guitar solo gets me every time
every time
[Music]
anyone's favorite he doesn't remix this
there was um there was one one second
[Music]
there was um oh there's a rear beach
remix with hudson amigo what
oh this one there's a jazzy lo-fi
version i'm sure we can listen to that
i like this one jazzy low-fat did
i i do you guys know this one
let me share it with you it starts with
rain sounds
[Music]
in
[Applause]
[Music]
so
i have an idea
[Music]
let's cover this
wait i'll have my lyrics where my lips
are
where are my lyrics
here we go
[Music]
[Applause]
so
wait wait
[Music]
wait this is very improvised
oh my god
sexy jazz music
[Music]
[Applause]
tell me the music
[Music]
keep on
break i will never give up don't break
[Music]
is
but they keep pushing and pulling
could you tell me please
[Music]
tell me
basically
[Music]
no you give me the last line
i guess so
[Music]
i will i will try to make this perfect
at some point
i wanted to okay i i secretly wanted to
sing this in some kind of eventually and
surprise you all but now that it came up
i just felt like doing it now
[Music]
again
[Applause]
[Music]
tell me
oh
[Music]
fighting
number
[Music]
don't break i will never give up
nice and true
[Music]
to find my destiny
but they keep pushing and pulling me
astray
if i go wrong what awaits me please
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
ah they don't have the last line in that
instrumental interesting enough yay
isn't that a beautiful remix
instrumental
thingy jazz version i wanted to
uh i think i think the second time was
already much better than the first time
thankfully so if you want to clip it
clip the second one
so good
i love this jazzy vibe i love it
it's not funny
[Music]
the problem of this version is it's so
faffing good
i can't take it i just cannot take it
it's just too good
okay so let's finish the super chat
showing birch rafael duncaschen
thank you christian slayer dankeshen
thank you vessels
[Music]
what do you mean you want me to play
hirotoki at the beginning of my final
live streams i mean why not
why not i'll probably forget about it
but sure
i do want to upload uh since we reached
1 million i don't want to upload the
the one chorus only version so tv cut
version
on twitter just to say thank you
everyone
and to have it on twitter as well
but i'm too lazy to cut it does someone
want to cut it and then send it to me
just fade it out at the end
just fade it out after one one chorus if
someone want to do that and send it to
me
fade it out after one chorus please send
it to me
i am too lazy actually i got the new pc
so i don't have a video oh wait i
don't have a video editing software
how do i make my video for christmas
next week
i'll have to install it again i did buy
a license so
wait a second but yeah we'll find a
solution for that but if someone wants
to
help me and make a small it doesn't have
to be exchanges
fade out the after one chorus and make
it small
so that i can put it on twitter thank
you so much send it to me with a giga
file please
how do i super chat i turned off the
super chats because um i have too much
to read
next time but thank you
oh sure next next is probably
[Music]
i'm too tired from staying up till four
in the morning for three days in a row
due to a certain phoenix
streaming schedule so i can't think of
anything other than congrats on hirotodi
reaching 1 million
i'm sorry sean eonam
i'm sorry it's because i do such like i
i i thought
i thought it would be good because i
start i started it
i schedule it to start at times that are
decent for america
but then their streams are so long that
everyone's going to sleep at some point
during the stream
i have to start even earlier damn it
i knew that you would have to catch a
taxi last night yeah
i have a fiver for part of the fair oh
thank you that's that's so
very helpful thank you soon thank you
that's duncan i was seen on tv but 977
thousand something comments on the big
milly thank you
western telecom
oh if i might be selfish uh where some
telecom says if i may be selfish
please more good i'm a good place yes
yes yes yes it's difficult because
i try to um pull up with everyone but
it's like just
every weeks go by so fast and there's
always so much i want to do in one week
so it's hard to always schedule in all
those collabs
but i did too could i i did two collabs
with kuda recently
i did uh plan one with ina this week but
it didn't happen so i gotta
re-reschedule it soon
now i had a lot of collabs with uh cali
so i need to collab again with ame and
with ina that is my highest priority to
collab with
ahmed you know yeah
let's see let's see if we can make it
happen soon hopefully
[Music]
if it wasn't for you i would not be
fully hired by my company due to my
first two months of my work
evaluation discovering you made me
motivated to work three times as hard to
support you thank you canada thank you
i'm happy to hear that
spanking ham duncan darwin waits time
[Music]
no no you don't have to delete anything
i love your
i love your drawings i love them you're
so adorable
can you draw um can you draw
me standing in front of a door opening
it
opening it slightly and then there's a
bunch of chickens
spilling out like trying to get out of
the door and i look at them like really
angry like
you're not moving anywhere
you're not going anywhere
and behind my back i i have a knife
hiding it behind my back
i'll do it now
yay i love the way you draw the chicken
so
fat and fluffy and so round
mmm so squeezy so squishy
[Music]
eating excellent wait a minute if
nothing bad happens to us what happens
to kfp employees once they reach their
one year employment
[Music]
we don't talk about that just yet
uh friend france thank you
i wanted to say thank you to you and to
kelly for always cheering me up with
your lovable personalities i wrote a
more detailed message on the takamoni
sleepover stream if you want to read it
i don't really have access to it unless
i watch the whole stream all over again
and check all the superchat messages
they'll come up in the chat
but thank you thank you
[Music]
b
what the secret identity is
[Music]
the music stopped at the perfect time oh
i didn't even notice
[Music]
arctic foxtan
fox 17 totally don't have weapons of
mass destruction stash in our secret
sauce fault
recliner placed on kashin
difficult noah duncan
i haven't been feeling great mentally
lately but your streams have been
helping
thanks for all the positive energy you
bring keep up the great work and i can't
wait to see what you have in store in
the future
thank you keep on supporting me and then
you will see
thank you for the pinky thank you thank
you i appreciate it very much thank you
for your support
[Music]
i will only say that if my chat can
confirm that it is what it is
and what's the spanish greeting guys
that's telling you what's the spanish
greeting
what the is that sound casper
[Music]
not hola something with v
the was that santo no
no one's saying it maybe it's wrong let
me look it up
generally i would appreciate if you guys
would not send me super chats asking me
to say something because i have to make
sure
that it means something good
and not something weird and generally i
just don't like requests people asking
me to say something because eventually
people
everyone will send a super chat they
will say can you say i love you can you
say
uh kfb is amazing can you say
you look beautiful can you say this can
you say this and then
at some point it's just uh doesn't
doesn't
it's not that cool anymore
it's fine if it's on not too much
but the more i reply to these kind of
requests
the more they will come in and it's not
not so much fun anymore
and then then people will ask weird
things of me and then i don't understand
what it means they will ask me to say
things in different
different languages and then i might say
something inappropriate
[Music]
but yeah yeah
but i still don't understand what the
word means
what the hell some kind of
casino resort has that name
[Music]
it means old
there you go did you win your bet now
it's a spanish screening used by close
friends of mine and if you said i'll win
a bet
of 40 dollars
[Music]
well i am glad you made some money from
that then
beyond the stage live see i still have
i'm still not sure
um we can we have permission to do a
watch along with
our viewers but are you guys going to
watch it
are you guys going to watch it live
yeah i bought a ticket oh
yes yes
[Music]
there's no collab planned or so but
okay a bunch of you guys seemed to have
bought the ticket
how long does it go for i'm not sure
i i don't know how long the concert is
hmm i see i'm still thinking if i should
do watch along or not i have other
other um streams planned on that day
and the other day i want to take off so
i'm not sure i'll think about it though
when i make my schedule
i guess it would be fun to react
together with you guys
we'll see any big plans before flying
home
and hope your chance you have a chance
to meet all the whole lives of japan
girls in real life before flying home
yeah uh i don't think i'll meet all of
them
but i hope i can meet a bunch more of
them and become friends with them
but the big plans before i fly home was
very soon and
i originally came to japan this year um
i know i i lived here before but i came
this year because i wanted to also
like one of the reasons was i wanted to
finally travel more inside of japan
but then right after i came the thing
happened
and um that messed up everything so
before i leave i
quickly want to go to the very north and
to the very south
of japan because up until now
i mostly i only have been to
kansai and kanto kanto is the prefecture
where
um tokyo is in kansai is the prefecture
where osaka is in and kyoto so i've been
to those areas many many many times
and i've been to besides that i've been
to uh one more
city city in the in the very not in the
very south but very close to the south
but i want to go to the very very south
i want to go to okinawa and i want to go
to hokkaido
so i i don't want to i mean okinawa
would be better in the summer but
apparently it's even even right now
it's very warm there not sure if i can
go
swimming there but my ideal ideal idea
would be to go swimming in okinawa not
sure if i can
go there
[Music]
but i hope i can do some more quick
trips
the thing is i'm also busy with you know
streaming for you guys
oh i can't travel that much
[Music]
i will at least go on one more trip
maybe two more trips have you been to eh
no i haven't i really want to go there
hey that place is looks really beautiful
people have been recommending it to me a
lot
[Music]
have you been to disneysea yeah i have i
have a long time ago though
disney uh disney
land in disneysea and japan in tokyo is
currently open again but
it's a bit hard to get in there
apparently because the tickets are
limited
but i don't i don't like disneyland that
much anyway so
i like it but i'm not one of those
people who really really really have to
go there
did you see the new maori world no but
isn't it coming out
wait is it coming out in february or
march or something
is it opening and there's like a
nintendo world opening in
osaka i think february 2021 see i might
be able to
get a goodie check that out when it
opens
if i get a ticket if i get a ticket
[Music]
from what i've seen until now and i
really want to check it out
i've seen uh usj united not united once
again
what does usj say is universal
citizenship
universal studios japan i've checked
that one out
a long time ago that was also fun i
checked out the harry potter world
in usj everybody world was amazing
and now i'm excited for a nintendo world
yeah i kind of doubt that i will get a
ticket i doubt it highly
it would be very difficult probably
if they will be gone in one second and
they'll probably be very limited
why you have one million views what does
that mean at all what does that mean
i have to apply for the chicken normally
you think i can
get a ticket because i'm crying
because i'm a vip but i'm i would go
anonymously ask for sponsorship
that would be nice that would be cool
anymore let's go back um laszlo
alter dan thank you for the red super
chat
[Music]
converts on your original song hitting
one million views camera i've been
watching since your first debut
my first debut my first one
and it's been amazing to witness you
rats from your ashes again and again as
you found your stride and grew into the
talent you are now consider me a
lifetime employee thank you
i'm happy to have lifetime employees
don't have to worry about the future
that much anymore
thank you thank you
it's been alright the past few months
have been very crazy
um
[Music]
very very crazy
but the past few moms have been a
blessing to me
i think about it every day how how
blessed i am to
be in this position so thank you all so
much for making it possible thank you
leslie alter
thank you mwah jacobs toothbreaker danke
good night
the stream like points towards all
japanese version of the side
oh oh damn that sucks what the hell what
that's confusing it's a mystery
dankeshin
thank you too uh
swiss thank you i just took a sip but i
throw this earning boop snooting thank
you
for the double red super chat
thank you for supporting wait i need
more subs
i need more water sips
thank you i appreciate your support very
much very generous
though a little bit too generous please
don't please don't
send me too many donations
[Music]
don't worry about it
i think it's awesome how you sometimes
translate what you say during my stream
but i definitely i definitely don't do
it
as much as i used to anymore what time
i partially feel sorry to my japanese
viewers
[Music]
because i did it much more in the past
and now i focus much more on speaking
english casper what the
the
casper is trying really hard to make
another hole like
really hard it sounds so
loud like i always think like he's like
already through he already made a hole
and he's somewhere there
it's freaking me out
casper
stop making those noises
[Music]
anyway yeah um
but yeah because i haven't been speaking
so much japanese uh in my streams
recently
um i want to do a japanese only stream
next week
but i wonder if people will even come
maybe i already lost all
most of my japanese
[Music]
the is he
busy
[Music]
you know
what are
[Music]
soon
jacob's toot baker thank you for the red
subject sorry it took me so long to get
to your super chat
you have such a nice singing voice when
can we expect another original song
so i want to we're not working on
anything yet
just yet now i want to release another
song
before i leave japan
yeah hopefully that will happen
thank you for your support look forward
to the next song
i will try to get it to
have a have kind of a different vibe not
not as much like
anime super energetic anime opening as
uh this one hinotoni
a bit more i would like it to be a bit
more
hot not calm but
[Music]
it definitely will be different
i i don't want to give away too much of
what i'm planning
[Music]
but you will see
don't worry don't worry see you next
time congratulations on one million
views on hirotoni you've inspired me to
get back to
my japanese studies and this time i'm
gonna learn all those thing kanji oh
good luck with that
thank you good luck and thank you for
your support thank you shin
rikata thank you for the red super chat
i think something happened to my
previous super chat oh so to be safe i
wanted to say
congratulations on the 1 million views
on hirotoni
thank you yay one million
one of my favorite songs oh it's helped
me many days when things got tough
what and thank you for being here
that's so so amazing to me to hear that
that my song like helps people somehow
and entertains them and
and motivates them and inspires them
what
what's up so sweet
look glad to hear that thank you
gotta go thank you for streaming thank
you for coming
i'm done soon though
[Music]
toothbreaker dankeshen beef bloodstain
thank you for the red super chat wow
this is my first super chat too bad
youtube thailand can't send super chat
uh i need to use vpn to do that ah
oh it works when you use a vpn ah
congratulations on one million views in
autonomy yay
thank you one million subs in the soon
future i hope so
love your streams and thank very much
thank you for the good energy and
happiness you have given me
thank you
thank you i'm so glad to have your
support thank you for your generosity
thank you for your kindness
thank you let's go together to reach 1
million subs
let's do it together guys you and me and
you and you and you and you and you and
you and you and you
albedo white wings
expressing my thanks for you you were
one of my favorite eon members from
twitter interactions free w
nostalgic and still our moms later
oh looking forward to supporting you
down the line also
is watch only me the cults and film yes
it is
thank you i'm happy that there's people
from the pre-devil time even
that's very
[Music]
this majesty congratulates you on one
million oh you're
king oh i see i will not take my hat off
in front of you right now because i'm
too lazy
but please imagine me without my hat
which means imagine me naked oh yeah
i think you as the hentai king
will enjoy that my throat is dying i'm
sorry
i can probably say a country i
contributed free views to the goal well
thank you that's already
a big help thank you
thank you for your kind kind generous
support your majesty
[Music]
uh five streams in 24 hours is
taking a toll on my voice right now
[Music]
you have my favorite singing voice of
whole life oh
that's not possible that's not possible
there's so many more
better singers than me in her life but
i'm happy to hear that thank you that
means a lot to me
so he just made me so happy
i love you thank you
so even if you don't like your voice
just means i have to like it for both of
us my singing voice like
i liked it for a long time but just
recently
i started liking it not so much anymore
because i i listen to it too many times
it just
sounds weird it just sounds like
[Music]
i know i don't like it anymore but
really
as long as you guys like it i'm happy
reverb one one seven donkey shoot jeff
thank you we're gonna need a full-length
album sometime
that is a big dream of mine yeah i want
a full length album
but i wonder if i could do an album
maybe with some
like different like mixing up uh mixing
some
different uh producers together have
songs from
all kinds of musicians in there but
that is uh
i would like to do that but
that is uh to organize that it's gonna
be
annoying and financially it's gonna be
also annoying and um
[Music]
and expensive
i am so i might just stick with with one
producer
because it just makes things so much
easier
and i guess like sticking to one
producer gives me some kind of like you
know typical sound
like you know that you listen to a kiara
song and you're like oh yeah that's the
chiara sound
it at least will give me some kind of
like
how to say gimmick
could you say it like that familiarity
yeah yeah yeah
stability yeah consistency yeah
although every now and then i also feel
like oh i might want to try this style
and this style and this style
and my producer probably can't always
like get a trademark yeah
might not be always able to like
mimic every music style
[Music]
but i don't know i'm still thinking
about how i wanna how i wanna handle
that if i wanna keep on going with the
same producer which makes things easier
and i love his i love his style
or if i mix it up and uh put
like try different producers different
music styles
yeah oh well that but next song will be
again with gojo
that is for sure the next song will
again be made by him
the one who made hinototi
account name to account
arigato
[Music]
foreign
ice cream
[Music]
we are pretty much done with superchat i
just realized
[Music]
ah i know
uh do you guys remember the art that i
retweeted
yesterday i think it was yesterday from
toyomaru
who drew me and kelly in a japanese hot
spring
naked
she uh super chatted and i just have to
say
that art chiara
um
[Music]
foreign
i can't speak japanese or english or
anything anymore
my tongue is um turning into knots
i cannot talk anymore
[Music]
a
my flowers
[Music]
ah
toyo madison
[Music]
i want to get better at drawing but i
have to practice more
which is why i was thinking of um
tomorrow
my members only stream i wanted to do
a short stream where we just
talk like a one hour stream or something
but i might be uh drawing while i'll
be talking you will probably not see the
whole
thing like from
beginning to the end but i might just be
drawing while we're talking
we still have a lot of penis to talk but
i want to draw and
then the only time i have to the only
time when i have time to draw is when i
stream
if i stream when i draw if that makes
sense
i can't speak english anymore this is my
fifth stream in 24 hours thank you for
the membership
the last super chat is from um joshua
cries
craze thank you thank you
and now i have to end the stream because
my my my brain is going to explode my my
brain is leaking
[Music]
i think we all need to take a nap and
chill
i'm too lazy to go outside after all
uh and i need to reload my throat
yeah i love you all thank you for
celebrating hino31million with me
tomorrow i have a sponsor stream
so i would love if you guys would come
to support me there
go get those sponsorships babe go get
them go get them
go get em
has some amazing tracks in that game
some amazing touhou tracks
don't forget to tweet of course of
course of course
[Music]
mama will remember this why
won't miss it for anything thank you
no nap i know we're not meant to mention
other students but someone is about to
cook a freaking tarantula
what patama
is it hatama you're kidding me
is she cooking uh
oh that's she's not actually
what she's cooking what do you mean
she's cooking a spider where did she
get the spider
where did she get the spider
[Music]
it
look at her oh no look at her twitter
no
oh god i don't know if i want to see
that but um what
[Music]
what the
what the f
[Music]
what the
i'm about to throw the up just a
thought
of eating something like that
okay that's it
[Music]
you