[Music]
7 re
huh
me
want me
jr 2
me
[Music]
n ame
[Music] Matana-
kun 2
[Music] I'll
tell you secretly
Moody's
Hi 5 Series Ma1 Tama
Boy v Inuyama in the kitchen is a love story So today is love  Well, let's
go to the title call.
Phoenix attack cow No multi ring limit otaku is the soul character Dai Namba and Lou
Yoisho
Hello, I'm shaking violently,
but today's chopstick tag for distribution is at the sowing tag ring yard, so please feel free to tweet on Twitter.
Thank you very much. Well, it's today. I'll
also fix it in English in the comment section.  I received it, but
8 comments are welcome to translate it into English at the same time.If
anyone would like to do it, I would appreciate it.I
also added an English translation to the marshmallow that I will be talking about today, so I will also do that.
Please take a look if you'd like,
so let's go ahead and invite you. Let's
go. A
Certain Japanese Language 1-5 - I'll handle both Japanese and English. I'm a member of Ever Horo Live
English.  The
economy is good.
Good evening, good evening, bai mobawaaa.  It's
okay to be a character who usually boos, but it's nice to meet you. Yeah, it's okay, it's my first outside collaboration with Chara-chan.
Is it really a good role for Tama for the first time? I'm
really happy that Gyutamagi-san is the right person.  If you can do it,
that's a Lando laugh. It's a Lando laugh. You ca
n't laugh because you think it's really good.  I
was so sleepy, so blue skies. When that woman called me, she really told me to
eat and drink and get the effects. I
ate so much. I ate so much. I was so honored to hear Tamaki-san's voice.  I
'm a bit worried, but I don't think any of the viewers have expressed any concerns.What do you think
? Facer was only being streamed in Japanese a little while ago.  When I
talked about the price, I was a little more worried about the price. Oh,
did you say that's strange? Well then, everyone said
something like, ``There's no amplifier, it's dangerous, it's dangerous,''
oh, no, it's okay. How about
something like a window?  I won't take it down.
No,
please go to Big Hoop for slandering the leaks from the viewers about that North. They
didn't say that much, and neither did everyone. They didn't say anything bad about me that much either.
Thank you so much for letting me know. 4
Hey, what's that about Mr. Hatamaki's ball train? I saw the paulownia tree
, the distribution, the arm taking off in Thailand, etc., so I
guess he's not the right person.  I'm sure you understand that I'm serious, and
that I'm a beautiful woman, and that I'm a tuba.  I'm sure he
has something strange to hide.There's a lot of this in there.Something from the
past, especially that one.It
was interesting to cut out Lucia-senpai and non-
Non.Well, Lucia Sone is definitely my
girlfriend, so I
'll just hunt her down.Thank you.  Thank you.
What do you think about the relationship between Rothko-senpai and Honey-senpai?
Is it more than that? There's no more. Sure, I'll be happy if they say all sorts of stupid things later.  I
was on a date the other day, and I'm so happy that I met her, and I'm not happy at all.I've
been talking to Mari for a long time, right?I have a
character like this.On the other hand, I'm a strong queen of flowers and I want to leave it to someone else.  -
Well, that's the story.I'm a native of Japan as well, so I'm preparing for this.I
thought I'd probably be taken over by Marie, even in English.  I do
n't think the natural world will go that far even if someone says that they like me. Um, there's something about it that
grows like a spirit. I have to
fight for it. I can't
burn Arthur, but I'll
fight.  If you don't fight with me,
you're so annoying and so talkative. You'll be shoveling for the rest of your life. Even if I don't stop, you'll talk for the rest of your life, so I
feel like I'll be able to enjoy myself.
Thank you, but on the other hand, I'm doing a program called Kiyawa's Holotalk, so I'll be
doing interviews about how big the ocean is, so I'm
relieved that the business world is on the side of the interviewee.I'm happy and looking forward to it today.  I'm
going to ask you a lot of questions, so I'm going to ask Eunuch to answer.
Well, first of all, I'm sure everyone is curious about the background of the collaboration.  I'd
like to talk to you for a bit, and
we've been mutually following each other on Twitter for a while now,
so I thought it would be a good idea to dm you and let's do a big collaboration with the characters.  I
kind of invited him,
and my manager asked me about it, and I got permission, so I said let's do it together.
No, the real thing is that the manager was amazing and checked me out and was extremely polite.But the
manager was a bit surprised.Is everyone in my wife a god?Mikami Tsuchimura,
but please really check what the sound is.  I got a response right away to send it to you. I was
surprised that the festival was so fast and there were so many people coming, but Tabata Katara had
come too much. I was
slow to make a preliminary announcement, but I suddenly got a response from someone saying something to Koukiara-chan.
Please reply as quickly as possible by clicking @ and replying. I'll do my best. Please
give Pabu Gale. The child character mentioned below is
probably the one who is the easiest to contact and the one who can give you the answer the quickest among en these days.  Well, that
was originally the case, but I feel like the manager was just too quick to respond to Chankoro's return.
That's true. That's no good. Then it's really Jimbo.
Well, that's true, I got permission from the manager, but in the first place,
if I didn't say that 9 Ra-chan was good, this collaboration wouldn't have happened, so he
set this up.
Well, the song too.  Mr. Pi is interesting, so I
thought it would be an interesting experience to have a scene where we collaborated on those faces. It
's not like I'm a screwdriver or anything like that.  I had
seen Char's Great Luck Balloon several times before, so I wanted to participate in something at the end.Oh,
I see, it's already
Inspector Nagao.And this is
good.This is delicious.It's a lecture like that, and Yoshioki
Tayo.  There's a machine plastic cure room in here,
God, God,
God, I can't go anywhere. Well, that's right, that's right. This
means that my mother is in love with me.  I wonder if  I
can't help
it, haha.That's how it happened.At the
time, all the girls in Mahoro seemed to be falling in love with me.  I don't
want to worry about the possibility of this happening, but I've been trying my best
because it's about how much distance I can get over the past hour.I
also want a stupid girl ending in order to find a new owner.
Aonnyahahahahahahahahahahahahahaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaoh, it
's a ah, ah, I'm a new girl, ah, she's a new girlfriend. I don't like her new girlfriend. No matter how I say it, I still don't want to be that person. Oh yeah, I
want to be the best.  I
guess, but I'm not aiming for it in my month, and Tamaki rides spillo -san, what kind of child is it?
I'm good friends with Scan-senpai Oh, I'm a good friend, a good friend, a friend,
just a friend. Listen, my Morimae is good. Well, that's right.
Hello, how's the cooperation? Hey, that master and my pair.  Even if it seems like you're paying a lot of attention, let's
just leave it at that.It's like people who are bad people should listen to it the most.That's what I
like on Doru Island
[Music]
I like it.  It's good  I don't
really care about Driftwood at all, but now I'm finally
watching the characters as a follow live fan, but I
really like the 3rd generation, I really like the 3-unit setting, so there's a lot of variety, and I do
n't think it's too funny.  In English, the seniors and Ma-rin seniors, the department, and the prefecture are all very fond of each other, and of course
what's going on with the f later on is the hair.The
later people, this is the first thing that comes to mind, and it's really hard to make sense if you're a 3rd generation student.
Ah, I feel like that pair already likes all the 3rd generation members, but that's really annoying.
Hey, if you're a, then for example, the Beast Ramy. Starting
from Pillar 3 is good. Well, I think that's already decided, and the
same goes for Tatemori.  Shidomeshare 3rd generation is seriously difficult to understand, so I can't get enough of it, and there's
a lot of coupling.I have
n't listened to it, so I don't have much to say about it.
Because Stainless Steel Pon-chan is wearing it,
it's after a quick story.I learned it today, but when I say "da-sen", I mean "Yama" and "Kawa Ippo
".I'm going to do something like that.Why now, but I tend to go off the rails when reading Spacha.  I'm
sure you talked about something like that. I'd appreciate it if you could talk a lot more, so I'm going to ask you a few more questions. Is it
okay if I go? Well, I guess I'll go,
what to wear, okay?  Let's have it
As far as I'm concerned, I'd like you to tell me your first and current impressions of each other, so
first of all, I'd
like to talk about how we get along, but that Chara-chan got
to know about Tana Inuyama's stamps around 5.  Temasu Toko
ua
Saboom Look, I
may have seen a few things before going inside, but I didn't really pay attention to it. But
when I got familiar with it, I saw the boss, Tamaki Kumainoyama.  I
knew from the beginning that there were
a lot of people, but when I went to the show, it was like, ``Well, it's not like this live show.'' It's like, ``Ais, there's a really interesting guy at the city bar.'' Well, I guess he won the executive committee award.
Nokou is such an amazing person, I
thought to myself.Ah, is it okay to be together with Ari?The bad thing is, if I
don't join him, I
won't make any money.I'm thankful for this.
Yes, it's quite good.Isn't it great as a first jab?
Then, John Tokoro and Fujima, my impression of Kiara-chan.Ah, the
Minister's Award was the first one.His Japanese was so fluent that I really liked that character.  I
sometimes wonder if she was Japanese and thought she was good at English, but I thought it was
just luck or something like
that.
Although he is from Japan, his native language is Japanese and he is fluent in English,
so I thought he would be able to use it even after the same time.Oh, he
's so good at being able to speak such killer Japanese.  I'm so happy that you think that's what I'm saying Moe.
That's a different Asian thing, right?
Where are you originally from?
That green peach rally and the smoke,
Europe, Ah, the
story of summer. You looked at it earlier, right? You saw soccer.  here he is like him
Well,
that's right.Ah, that's what it is.When I press it, Ami is so angry.My husband, who
is not in the Australian column, is in a panic.The stick is his native language, and his cheeks are paved, and English is
different.But he studied Japanese at school, and before that he learned Japanese.  Well, I was
self-taught and brought some free gifts to Japan,
but now I'm back in my own country.Oh, I see. I'm sure that one.
That's right. You sounded like you were in Japan. Um, when I went to Book Live, I still
felt like I was in Japan. With an award like this, yeah, that happened to me before, but
yeah, I'm going back to my country again.  Well, I
came to Japan again last spring for a year, so I guess I'll wait and see if I can get back to you. I think there are about 3 people who
have lived in Japan.
Well, Japan is already completely familiar to me. When I woke up, I was already used to it. It was
in Tokyo. Hmm, I can
totally get used to it. But I wonder if Moon, Kosaka, etc. have already experienced such a thing. If the
earthquake happened, I would have felt like I had fallen from the seat.  Well,
there are times when he speaks in that Kansai dialect, right? Well, back
in the day, he spoke more Kansai dialect.
That uncertainty is good.
But I haven't lived in that easy way for a while, so I think I've lost quite a bit of it.Even
though I've said it over and over again, I
moved there when I lived in Osaka, and so did my Kansai dialect.  If
Nick appears in the photo, everyone will know why he speaks the Kansai dialect in Repair. Hey,
hey, I
wonder why the Kansai dialect appears here and there.
Yes, that's my impression right now, but when I first started watching that horror show, it was quite shocking to me.You know, there are a
lot of those chatty game collaborations on Eve, and they regularly show off their fashionable faces like
that program.  There are no people who do things like that, and
if he's sick, even that character from Choco Sensei would go out and play, but he
's watching the plaza dog as much as whether or not he's progressing and regressing.  That's
why when I started following on the 10th day, I thought I was going to do a stylish project, so I decided to make a girl
grade Indian me.
Oh no, we're having a difficult time as well. I wonder
if this was in another question. I'd rather go low.  Okay,
then 8. You
keep going off track by starting a dialogue and then asking for withdrawal.Let's go with
this then.Kyara-chan is doing a dialogue project called Horo Pork, but
Tamaki-kun's one.  There
is something similar to Iru Taiyama One. I'd like you to tell me why you decided to do a hood talk, if
there was a reason. Also, Tamaki-kun, I'd like you to tell me what made you decide to do a five-shot comparison.
Okay, I'm
going off track for a bit. Let's
go with this. Okay, now it's horror. Why did you decide to do this? I'm curious. Why did you choose it?
Um, um, uh,
this inside.
As you may have noticed even before the rain, the number
of viewers for the English-speaking world's live show has
increased tremendously since last year, and that's right.  It's
amazing how the number of winners has increased since then,
but those English-speaking viewers can
only
watch the clippings, and the only part that the Japanese members can see is the
top part.
I think the sea is only shallow, and I think I've won two awards, so when I
do a show like this talk, I do interviews with characters who translate on the spot and
talk about deep stories.
Congratulations on digging deeper and deeper for you. If you do something like that, you wo
n't just be focusing on the shallow areas, but the times you'll be
focusing on. Also, how did you grow from there, such as the difficult times in those early days?  I
wanted him to know all the details about what he's doing now and why he decided to perform live, so if that's the case, then I thought, ``Oh, only Kirara can do it.''
]
Hmm, I guess it's because the Japanese
company's Hoiwa
has 4 ski days, so since his debut he's been urging people to cut their hair in Japanese.
For some reason, there were quite a few people in English-speaking countries who were a little angry about the mayor, and there were a lot of people who were like, ``Oh, yeah,'' and some
people were like, ``I don't think so.'' He was speaking too much in Japanese, and
there were some people who were like, ``Hmm, I'm getting angry.''  Well, my
number 1: I do
n't know how to speak Japanese, but I'm
worried about how I can use it properly and if people will accept me, and this is it.
I thought that with this talk, I could use my favorite skills and my wife's skills to put out good content that would appeal to everyone.
Well, when it comes to chatting projects, for example, if you have a kid like me who can speak Japanese, I
think you can do as many chatty projects as you like with other people who can speak Japanese,
but people like Kirara-chan who can handle both Japanese and English really do.  That's because it's precious
As I said,
there is no project that only Kira-chan can do. I thought that follow talk
was about doing a project with Enduranma-chan that would make use of her strengths and special skills.  If
you're a good girl, I think you can rest assured that Reiner is fine.In
Japan, the time when we often do something is in the morning, right?The
most recent small talk is Charlie.  What about Oto and Aso?  I
wonder if it was Garmin Sui-chan's episode. I wonder if Mizu-chan's care has changed.
Well, I guess you're wrong. The time is right. From now on, it's already that night.
Just like 11 o'clock, it's 1 o'clock at the end of the day.  So, that Una
is a guest. All the guests are so sleepy that it looks like Sui-chan was pretty sleepy. Some
kids don't like mornings.  I do
n't know much about Aso Volcano, but the reason is that most of the English-speaking viewers are from
America, Canada, etc., so I wonder who has the hot springs there in Japan.
Yeah, that's right, I did
n't like it,
so I bought it. That's
right. That morning, I often have the day and night reversed, so that's what it says on
youtube. Who is this?  I was
still awake early in the morning and I was wondering if it was only the Chubu area that was having fun, and I went to Tokyo at the time and
thought Asui-chan would be great, so I watched it, and I was thinking about the drinking and automatic shops and the drawbacks,
and Sui-chan.  I don't think he looks sleepy at the store.I
think it's only a senior adobaya who says it's a slippery ride.I think it's good right now.Hmm,
no, it's really wonderful.It's still quite an interview project like that.
Um, I don't know why, it's hard to prepare, and even if you're playing two innings against your opponent, you have to study to some extent.So,
that's why it's so hard to do all kinds of things with three-yen fingers.Akiyama, wow, he's
fluent in all Japanese, English, and German.That's
right.  But I can really do Khyber Harbor, but this is the real thing.The person who
does the translation on the spot is a person who does it as a job.Wow, it's
amazing.I shouldn't say that he's so talented in the scene where he's studying.
Yes, I don't really have that kind of talent, so it's
quite difficult to convey all the details in
detail.Yes, it's a tomb's
messenger.Hmm, it's quite difficult to convey it correctly because there's a lot of pressure on it.  It's not just a matter of fact, but it's
also bad for the other person at the door,
so it's a technique of summarizing it, shortening it, and translating it, so it's probably a
good idea to shake it all at the same time and then say something really difficult.
That's why I'm taking those notes and protecting them as I write them down, but yeah, I think it's
really nice to see Lee changing the angle of Turnip, and the camera changing his clothes.It's like a close-up or a life story.I
think it's like a good program.  I thought, Well, now I want to give something to the fishing pond.It's
hard, but somehow the horse
is doing well.  I
thought it was Reiner, and I thought he was serious about his activities, and now I was happy for him.It's so
naughty, I deleted it a little, but I
was the one who started the discussion and project, and I was originally involved in that
game.  Well, you
might think that it's a normal game return, but I'm actually a little sick and
can't play games, so I'm
going to go to AFAN.
After watching the hour-long live video of my game, I thought, ``Oh, I'm probably a sick person who can't
play games.'' I can't do it at the same level, but you're a lot of crap, but you lie, too.
Ah, that's right, I wish I wasn't bad at it, but I can't do it,
but
since I can't do it, it's only a long way away,
so I thought it might be science, so I tried it here and there, but uh,
when I was sewing...  Every
time I open the armor, Komaeda tells me to leave the group for now since I have nothing to do but talk to him.An old
man who often comes in comes in and I've
been wondering if I should block the northern part of Class A Heart.
I wanted to increase the number of times I've had interviews with some people over the past four weeks,
but this one was a bit popular, and there were a lot of people who said they'd like to have a conversation with Tamagiku.  I
feel like it's still going on thanks to the advice of an old man who I thought was a troublesome old man,
right?
Everyone was immediately interested in that character because of the way he acted,
because it seems like he's so bad that he can't even look good anymore.  Yeah, that's true,
but that's what's interesting about
it. I'll probably get yelled at for the rest of my life. Hmm,
locusts, you know, they're really bad, aren't they?
Well, that's not true. I think the beautiful Evel is at that level of hilarious sloppy scum.
But I hear you're saying ``Yeah, yep.'' ``Yes, that
's probably going to cause an uproar,'' Hagi said.  The
reason for the uproar is that the comments section is full of people asking for death, so
thank
you very much. Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa way time you with a
cute
name?  It
's better if it's there,
but it's better
if it's not, but don't tell me. But, no, why did you choose to do it? They
say they're going to goug out the wound on the escort ship.
After all, you have
to look at the left navel. Hey,
yeah, but I believe it.  Teruyota Inorganic Acid is sure to
be Sandy Mecha, and I
think that the Nutreasure change of that change is interesting, so this has arrived Summer release tabunne is also a character  It's
so tiring that I want to write a rant about it, it's okay now Minoji Which one are you talking about today? Ah Booba I think it's easy to understand, so you can all eat udu but that's right baby It's too much Let's go with Kukan Ai Usuko version Myza derailment  That's right, we're all in a circle,
okay? Now then, this is a follow-up talk, and I think I've asked the full members and him as well,
but
q Ran-chan's v middle by  I asked him to tell me what made
him want to become a judo, and I was
wondering when he suddenly came up with that idea.I do
n't know, but now, Buchu is amazing, and every
time people say "Happu", I want to be, I want to be, I want to be.  I'm sure you're thinking, but
with the inclusion of Siege Network, the number has increased overseas as well, and it's seriously increasing the picture book's 8 minutes.It looks like it's becoming a military doctor.But
Killer came
to Japan last year with a guitar.This
is hi-ho.  Do you have free time with that and
that? That's right, hmm, now, uh, uh,
uh, I first found out about this live through Motion Senpai. There was a blizzard on the sidewalk. That's right, I
found out about it, but I'm not that into it yet.  Hey, hey, I went to Japan, and when
I had a lot of free time, I
watched Nean-senpai's stream, and I
got really hooked on it, and I thought it was called an archive of older people who live by their time every day.  I
looked over everything and couldn't help but wonder.It's Mako Someya's daddy's.It's so
deep,
aa.It's really in Jeans, no ne.Zap also
sings.I'll take it with me and spend the time with the marker.I
have a lot of things.no
It's Sagawa Handing Out Soup.And when I
watched it, I didn't really have any intention of becoming a member.I
didn't have any desire to become a member as much as I did.
There was no such conflict, it was just a conflict with the mainland.I
hadn't thought about it, but while I was paying the Honzon, I
think it was at the beginning of summer, when an
audition for Reiken 6 Hikkishu appeared.
When I found it, I was so
popular that I was so excited.If you think about Chiara's talent on the piano and her neck, I
think she's perfect, so I've got nothing to do right now.
In particular, it seems like it has a 9 finish.The
Asiana one is too big.My
mother heard that I had already seen it with a shovel.I had never
thought of it before, but somehow my way of
thinking changed at that moment.I
was like, ``Hmm, wait, I want to die in a bottle.''  That's when I got really motivated. So,
the good news
is, I thought this is definitely for me. Oh yeah, that's right. Eh, I was so
motivated with the edition that day, and
the moment I saw that one, I immediately went to that audition.
Well, Ohongo.  I
wrote it right away, and then I couldn't even finish it, and I couldn't help but feel like I was thinking about the quay,
wondering what I should say or write, and
my mother had already decided on that couch,
on the same day or the next day.  I sent the m in part.It
should have been done, but it wasn't too early.The real
labor staff didn't think about it this morning.Actually, there was a possibility that this would fail,
so I think they should have thought about it more.  Okay, here we have it.
Basin Gainer
Hmm, but I bought it. Wow,
even when he started out looking like a candidate, I thought he had a great offensive and defensive ability, but after all, even
before his debut, he was a person with great energy. I
guess that one time.  If you decide to do this, you may have to put in a lot of effort. Let's go there. We'll just
keep moving towards it. Don't
touch it. There are a lot of Ashikaga people, but it's still the same. Hebrew is also attracting attention, Holo.
live english  It was an audition for ``Tame,'' so I think the odds were really high.However, it's
amazing that he managed to get through all of that.I heard that the odds were really high, but that's right.Hmm, I
think it was a certain rate.  But now I'm being told things like 2000 times more,
but I
don't know what your hobbies are, but it's amazing. It
took me a long time to choose that one, so I guess that's true because I have to go back to it.  The
recent audition for Mr. Original Parts Guri's 2nd generation members was also over,
so I think there were a lot of them during the Roller 6 Lord's Go Hijirizawa as well.  I
think it's going to get really bad. Well, we're really in the middle of that boom, or rather, it's
like the top of the Boo Boo mountain, so if you think about it, I wonder how many copies have come in.
Staff, 3 curry?  Hey  I
think the tyranny of foreign countries is dangerous. I don't have a feeling, but it might be dangerous.
Hmm, that's good. I'm looking forward to the 2nd generation. I'm sorry, Kuro. Hey, this
is Keller.
Akira.  It's hard to get into the game, so I say things like Kise to the students, but in reality, from a player's point of
view, I'm 9th in terms of regulations.  I
have to make something clear here. If there is one, it's your bag. Just
because you're dividing it up, there doesn't seem to be a concept of separate 3rd generation members, please.
Isn't the sound good when you look at the value?
Thank you.  Speaking of Mr. Chiara, you
are famous for being able to speak English, Japanese, and German, but what made you want to learn a language that is not your native language?
Well, it seems like you haven't talked about it quite often.  I think so, but again
That's why I
'm No. 1
in English.
Even though I was forced to learn English at school, I was able to speak it so well. It's
hard to say, but I love English.  It was fun, so I loved that [ __ ],
and I felt like I got better at it because of that aura.That's
right, that character was generally the best at English in the class, so I was afraid that I could speak English.
Hmm, that's right, otherwise we wouldn't be hanging around for so long.Normally, we'd just
copy and paste our homework and show it to each other.It's a
mystery.In Soka,
carers are actually quite intelligent.  That's amazing. Well, I
get a headache when it comes to things like math. That's
amazing.
That Japanese language is so on. The
reason I decided to get Dawn was, well, that summer.  I
think it's a little hard to change this, but I'm
not trying to learn Japanese. I wonder
what it is.
People say I'm smart, but Kihara is already studying.
I'm not good at it, I hate it,
it's a hassle, ah, I'm pretty lazy, so I need a hot water editor dqn
But I hate reading books,
hahaha That's why I'm really into Japanese culture, and I post things like games and idols.  I hope that around
that time, my
desire to go to Japan will become stronger and stronger.I
want to learn Japanese now, but it's not too much of a hassle, so I was wondering how to go about it.Well, at first,
everyone was so stupid.
That was it. Horse: No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, it's\hokay, okay,
but it was quite a while ago, but I didn't use the jar pot fire and I didn't use the words\hsensei or anything like that. Oh, my
cheeks are already old enough that I'm only talking.
When I try to memorize one word, I end up memorizing it completely, so it's really hard.
So, while I was chatting with my Japanese friend, I realized that I had gotten better at
everyday conversation over the past six months.  Hmm, it
was a hot spring to say without borrowing o h It's green.
Please listen to rice fields only in 6 companies. That's
something while reading, or listen to Ago or Noky. For example, if you come across a kanji that you can't read, just
look it up straight a.
But I can't remember anything, so
Gywhite, who was born in Japan, only has Japanese.He tried to remember other things, such as how to help,
but later he realized that he couldn't do that anymore.He rides Shia's big pony.Japanese  I'm motivated
to learn the language. I
wanted to learn the tedious Giro, so you're right, sir. No
matter what, I want to experience Japan's hot anime and games, and I want to hang out with my Japanese friends.  It was a
joke about wanting to talk, so let's do our best.
When Munamu's motivation
was Japan, he probably wanted to have a friend who was pregnant.  Takara no Makai Code 1 Is
there something you admire? I'm happy, but even if I become addicted to it, it's
fine. I wonder if I'm not motivated after all. I
mean, it's really true. I don't think you can learn anything without motivation.  It's
okay to talk about the prefecture first in that community.
Well, that's the ultimate goal after all. I want to chat with that person, so it's
like memorizing it, so maybe it's a shortcut to put it into practice from the beginning,
yeah  I see, but I think I'd like to talk about one more thing related to language.a
What do multilingual people think in their heads when they think about something?  I'm
curious about what language you're thinking in, so I'd really like to know. Well,
when I think about what I should say, I
think I think about Kofu and Adam, but in the case of Aru Suzuki...  I
can speak three languages, so I cry and think in my head, but at that
time, I was speaking mostly Japanese.I'm Anand, and that's not my mother tongue.
Well, maybe it's because I lived in Japan that my boo looks so good.Hmm, I
can change what I think in my head, but it
doesn't change naturally.  Meat
from that mother.
All the staff members also speak a lot of English, so when that kind of spicy taste started to increase,
I started speaking English even though I wasn't like this in my head.
AsahiI'm a big English speaker right now, so it's a little hard to say because I'm not really aware of the timing, but I
think it's a bit difficult to say, but I think it's a bit of a bit of
a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit like I'm not aware of the timing, but I think it's a bit difficult to
say.  Well, for one thing, I'm in a German-speaking environment,
but I'm
pooping, so it makes sense, but anyway, I
don't have any friends who speak German, so I'm a bit of a German-speaking person.
Well, Takane Suru City Higashi has been broadcasting for a long time, so I have a lot of opportunities to come into contact with English.That's
right, I feel like it's always been the case, so even my wife has a dream of 10,000.It's
hard to say, but I do
n't remember much about that.  What I remember is that sometimes Japanese and English would come out in the gym. That's the kind of
anxiety I
feel. It's
funny because people like Meiwa can only speak their native language. You
know, I don't have that feeling, but that's what men are like.  I
'm a genius, so I'm really happy when people say that to me, like Wakiya Michi and Ria.I'm not going to fall in love with that anymore.Wow, I don't care if you
call me an idiot.What do you think?  That's amazing. Today, we're
going to have a low day. I wonder
if there's any air. I don't know if there's any agriculture. Hmm, I
guess. I know it's amazing. It's
quite old. It
's a bon bottom.  There was a lot of talk about the various functions of that house,
and there was a standard word for that, and that h was used to call it
idiot, and that's right, that's right, the House of
Councilors manta lost 3-  4 Are
you being slandered like that? Hahar, it's
okay, but aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa!
Hey, that's a word that was created from that graph.It's a long story, but if you
do that, and the
people at the soba restaurant really think well of that character,
yes, that number must be my brother's tinkering.2  I
thought for a long time that it was the mark on the bottom left of the screen, but that's what it was.That collaboration.Follow
life
with various functionsI made a graph when I was collaborating with iena.  I
guess they were using a graph to show whether all the members were smart or bad, neat or not neat.Hmm, it's the best, and if you
put it on the left, it's the stupidest and the best line, Panapanafest.It's
just 10 o'clock.  I guess it was just the end of the sound part. For
some reason, Naru was blessed there.
Ah, that's what it means. ua
Ah, haha, it's been a big hit ever since then. It
's just one patch.  I do
n't want to be in a temple without saying this. It's still good enough to have a radical view. Now that the topic has
come up, let's go here. The
nicknames [ __ ] and Leak have become so well-established that they're even included in Calliope-chan's song, but [ __ ].
What was the reason for people to call me good?
This is more than just a bad word, but what is this? The
day when Kaki-chan, who has never been said like this, released it at the 4th time.  I'll take you, but you'll die.
Please, I
think everyone knows about that, but of course Kagi-chan gives her a period of time before her debut.It's
Nan, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, but that movement character is just right in English, but that one, that
one, that one, that one.  Chiara's fast raps are a bit more difficult.I
want to hear those lyrics, so please give me the lyrics.I asked Tekari-chan, and she sent it to me,
but when I looked closely,  There's
something called a feces collector in there,
hahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaahahah that's a staff member of that album I heard you write about that house and it
hurts when I heard you say ``
Maybe you don't know anything.''  Oh, are
you making fun of me? That's
not a Bach disc. I
'm really good friends with Calliope, who's big now in house music, but back then I wasn't even close.  It
's not like I was still in the process of nurturing something like this, but I felt like I was preparing for a wedding when the marriage arrived and I felt like I was a shipwrecked person.Well,
at that time, we were both the same.Well,
since we were in that place, ah,
actually...  We were the
only members who joined the group, except for the stupid members, who
live in different places, so
we all live far apart, so we were only close enough to borrow characters and get along with each other.
Hmm, I guess we were already close and close. I guess that's
just a delusion, but we were spending time in the air. I took what I got from that, and I
wonder if it's Link and the leader.  I
guess there was a sense of distance between them, but the woman who was excited when Don's first debut song included something nice and unpleasant was
already quite happy.
Why can I do this? It's not like it's an important song. It's nice to have a shitty bird. I'm going to put some public character elements
into it. It's Yu-Ai. I'm
embarrassed before the finals. It's great. I mentioned
earlier about my favorite pairing of bones.  I put a pair of myself and Calliope inside.
Takahori is the best at Anu, but how do you really carry her?
She has a style where she pushes herself.  Thank you,
everyone, for your kind support, Mr. Takada.Next, let's talk about Japan.I
heard that Caro-chan lived in Japan.Do you
have a favorite place?Also, people of culture.  I was wondering if there was anything that surprised you outside.
Well, it seems like it's your favorite place in Japan. Well, I think Akihabara and Kusato are
also famous, but when you have five colors in your notebook,
that's the beginning.
Ah, this was a long time ago, but those
Japanese people were probably
all about the Kansai area when they first started. Considering the moving parts, I think the slopes of Osaka in the Kansai area were my favorite. Hmm,
Nousaku was the
best.  As I said earlier, I had a lot of fun with Osaka and Shinsaibashi,
and I
had a lot of fun there.  I
like that Arase Yamaa and that kind of thing, it's really good, I know, it's
beautiful, it's beautiful, I don't like it at
first,
but for some reason I liked that Omote sandwich, but now I have
4 likes and 3 likes  I wonder if it's the skin that hurts my stomach. I go to the streets where the trees are
open. Well, it
's that irritating, but it's irritating.  Oh, it
's impossible to play the guitar, that's what's so scary about it.People are hecklers, and if it's impossible, I think it's a lie.If you
go there for the first time, you'll suffocate.The first time you went there, after passing by the people playing, it
was still different.  If it wasn't for that, it would be like that bubble.If it wasn't for the generation correction, it would
be a cat.But compared to that time, there are a
lot more people now.  It's
different now, but I'm thankful that Naka-san's current situation is ah, that's right, ah,
there was something that surprised me about that difference.
This isn't a culture, but Amazu died because it was too hot.
Haha, but it's okay.
Then I heard there was an adhesion. Nyankura or Maria.  I don't know if
it's from the Tropics, but I wonder who's getting cheaper. It
's a concrete jungle, so it's really
vibrating. Oh, it's
hot in the country of that popular character who died,
but he doesn't eat Meiji food, so it's from that room. Hmm.
Japan is expensive,
so I'm not
sure if I want to be like that.Well, there's a lot of things going on in terms of culture, but Japan is so
expensive.  I was
very polite and polite when guessing the budget. I
was surprised, but Fuyuichi and I were like this all the time. I was
surprised to see everyone on the train.
Wow, that's a good book. She doesn't sleep.  I'm not saying that it's dangerous to close your eyes when you're at home on a bus or something like that train car,
but I
feel like it's going to reduce your aspirations, but no one closes the house next door.Even if you get second place, you can still hit well, you Japanese.  I
mean, let's knock down the lights.
Hmm,
even if I'm that sleepy, I'll try my best to open the book.a
So I don't know why it's so bad.I
think it's because my country is dangerous, but my character's country is different.  It's
not dangerous.
India is a picture of a sea without red.
However, in Japan, I thought it would be easy to get wet,
so I thought it would be easy. I
can do a little gold arirang, and I'm depressed. It's really
noisy inside those buses and trains.  It's
nice to talk when you're in front of the house, and there's not just one door in the city that plays music.People who don't turn on Nyan say it a lot.Hey,
Wash.It's
noisy because of the technique, but I'm used to it, and I wish I could do it in Japan.  I thought it was amazing how quiet everyone was, but
on the other hand, people were like, ``If you talk loudly on that train or bus, it's
so noisy,'' and then later on, it's like a barrel.
What's more, there are some people who join the club even though they are in Tanji.Ahaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaha Maybe that's just a nuisance.They're a bit sluggish and work too hard, so I don't think they'll find out.  I
think I'll talk about it.The reason I experienced culture shock was because I was guarded.No, I
guess that's what it was.That's why I didn't get any more time off at all.Um, well, I have to
take that day off.  It's
too much, but I don't even take a break like that.6 e I
wonder if there are people inside who can't get on the ride.It looks like a door sash if there's an empty space.I'm
playing a virtual tuba and doing it properly.  I'm
already able to take a day off, that's amazing, is you, who is this?  You're
trying too hard with your way of thinking, but diving is all about the English-speaking way of thinking,
so everyone takes a
break when they want to watch it.When things get tough, they just go and ignore it.It's not okay, but that's also a death sentence.The
child is also something.  They haven't told me to do it without taking any breaks.Eh, I've
selected 100 members of the Go-ya group and all of them, but that's
right.Hmm, Tamami-san, is it okay to take some time off?
Kita
Do you think that he is probably one of the people in this industry who doesn't take any time off?
Hmm, when I say "please take care of your body", you
work about 18 hours a day and do
n't sleep.  No, I do
n't have time.9 I don't have time to play. I work all the time. I work even in the bath. I
use my smartphone. Well,
there's a lot of things I want to say about that, but Sang-ho, who has no legs, is at another office in Aromar.
Hello!
Well then, I guess it's a bit of a commemoration of the hardworking people.I wonder if Japanese people look at it from other people's perspective, or
even if it's just my older sister.Hmm, it's amazing.Since then, I've been thinking about the hard-working people who work hard.10,000
yenThe good thing about Japanese people is that they're polite.  I think that's
what's great about Owada. woopie Village is no longer possible. When people say things like that to me, it's amazing
how good their manners are, thinking we're normal children. I'm grateful when people say that to me,
though. Hmm.
Navy Alright, let's move on. Come over here and talk about missions and
sex. Hey, what kind of viewership is on your channel?
Also, if you remember any differences from before, I'd like you to let me know. Well, that
guy...  I think there are many, many women, or there are many English-speaking people, or there are many Japanese people,
etc., but I don't mind being vague, so what do you think?
Hey
big  The one
about Sakuraan Merit is that the country is so big right now that it's probably the most popular.  It
seems like the number is increasing, so I wonder why it's popular in Korea.
Wow, I'm glad that character is fluent in Japanese, unlike the other members. It's newer than Law 2.
I wonder if there are more viewers in Japan.
I wish I could
say it quickly, but it's just the same. I don't know how to compare it. Even now, I often mix in Japanese when I speak, but compared to my earliest days, it's a
little more like, well, I still feel like I'm going to have a chance to speak Japanese, so I'm arranging it.  It's
stupid to think that the number of runners has decreased a bit because
it's a car, but today I took about 55 workers and it's a good day. Noon's
Soarer
Hey, you can speak Ion.
What's that?
It's been a while. Even if I haven't spoken Japanese, if there's a Japanese comment in that comment section, I'll always reply, so I'm not a picky girl.  The sound of the day Voight is also in Japanese, so that menu is
cute and has 4 heads.
Now that the ideal has been established, what was the consideration for that? My eyes and rectum are type 4. I still prefer that Japanese word, that Japanese prefectural assembly, instead of the type 4 that everyone says.  What is it? Yeah,
Sato. Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I don't think it's changed all that much from the beginning. Now, after all,
American Zinger is so sexy. There
's nothing wrong with that, but even when it opens, it's
still killer. Well, European mode.  turn mud  I
wonder if the number of 4-banner movements has increased because it has been discontinued during good times in Europe. I
haven't seen the part where the book goes to Incheon at all. I haven't confirmed it. I guess I'll see you later. I
guess it depends on the time of day it airs.  After all, there are people who can see and people who can't see,
so yeah, I guess it changes depending on that.What happens is what becomes.Okay
then, that
's 2 points.Let's go to the end.  I was
wondering if there was anything that was the best thing about joining Aehoro Live.When I joined Mahoro, I was able to collaborate with Pekko, who I admired, and I'm sure a lot of good things happened, but is there anything?  Good episodes:
Yeah
a,
aa There are a lot of them, but there are too many, but I would like to say that there
are many possibilities for agricultural policy,
and we were able to release some interesting songs.  It's
okay to be a provocateur, you know. I've made friends with all sorts of warty members, I've
been able to collaborate with various games I like, like Hearn, and there
are still a lot of other things I'd like to collaborate with, but members I'd like to see from A.  There are a lot of people out there,
but the
best part
is that I found a place where I can use my talents.
Even if you have a job that supports Japanese, English, and German, you can't be a translator, so
please be sure to work as a simultaneous translator or crane, so that's pretty limited.  I
like games, I like anime, I
like anime, etc., and it's a job where I can combine it all into a job, so it's
like turning my hobby into a job.
large  It's
rare to be able to show everyone that you're having fun playing defense and make everyone happy about it.Hmm, I
feel like I'm enjoying every single day of my life to the fullest.  Yes, it
feels like fulfillment and enjoyment, right? Well, there are no devices. Hmm,
yes, I
feel like I'm being fulfilled every day. There aren't many jobs out there,
so it must be a vocation. Then, for the character, v. The middle part is
like that.  g  It's written by Mapuko, and you'll hate it until you die.
Ah, you're dead and come back to life. You can live your whole life. It's a loss. Yes, it's been
4 days. That's right. The
couple got a letter job. It's great. It's really sad for Horo Live.  I'm so
jealous of that
move, I'm so happy, it's so delicious, I'm so happy, really, what's
wrong with me?
When I was able to live in Japan, I went to a school, ca-chan, and I met Ni-chan, too.  It seems like it's going to
be an easy turn again. It would
be nice if we all got better at language restraint. It would be nice if we could all go out together.
In 2017, we all lived in Japan together. It looks like it's going to be
really exciting. japan  I don't want to go
too far, I'm just a big guy. There's a lot of things I want to do with the five of us, but I
wish we could do some 3D shame. Ah,
but the five of us are going sightseeing in Japan and
wearing armor as a unit.
Yes, you probably want them to come in. Well, in the first place, it's fun just to say that the five of us are together to play. It's
finally time to fill up the rice, but I'm down and I ca
n't talk, but it's okay.
I wish all the male and female members of the Japanese free live show would be in the same group.As a
woman, I
would be able to do things like that, like buying a whole bag of Aota-bai or going out to see what's going
on.  Mr. Eagle can't do that kind of thing, so it's hard to get rid of him, and
everyone's been waiting so long that one day they'll get together.Even
if I trace it, my sister isn't there.Well, the viewers, too.  Talk  I'm
sure you'd like to see them working together, and that's exactly what those members want right now. I hope
things get better soon. I hope we can meet up or sleep over.
[Music] That's
great. Yeah,
yeah.  Yeah, yeah, there are a lot of things I want from Yamada, so let's continue to
work hard on the pad from now on. There
were a few derailments due to things like ah-ah-ah-hah, but the hour passed in the blink of an eye.
No, I want to talk more about the shadows. I think I'm too much of a person. I'm
going to ask for the En region. Jr. No, it's too much. If you want to talk this much, I'll
introduce you to Let's play a second or third time.
Collarless Aya  Sho:
Well, it was an hour today, but what did you think of the character
? Well,
this one broke, etc. I think it's 9 guitars.  I
used the phone at an amazing store, but I was happy to have a turn with Tamaki-san, and my older brother talked to me about the head and that
character group, so I was feeling amazing all the time while I was still alive.
But it was a lot of fun.
Thank you.
Thank you for giving me hope that I can speak Japanese. It's amazing
how much fun it is to speak Japanese, and I've met people who speak Japanese.  It's
fun to be here, and I'm the leader of everyone. It would be great if you could say hello to me. I'm
really happy, but
let's continue to get along.
So, hello, let's actually go to the stars together. Is that
okay?  Well,
everyone, please subscribe to the character and channel from the summary section.
Yes, I'd like Larimar today as well. Well then, let's go.
Mud Atsuta
Maaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
rar
[music]
[applause]
[clap]
[music]