​​​ ​Evil Overlord!​ ​​
​​ ​Summer has arrived!​ ​​
​​​ ​S-Summer brings with it the normies.​ ​​
​​​ ​​​ ​​
​​​ ​That's gonna suck...​ ​​
​​​ ​Ta-da!​ ​​
​​​ ​No! The Sun!​ ​​
​​​ ​And so the hero started her journey​ ​​
​​ ​to bring back the Sun.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yikes!​ ​​
​​​ ​Gimme your money.​ ​​
​​​ ​Already?​ ​​
​​ ​I haven't even left town!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm Municipality Suisei,​ ​​
​​​ ​the diva of violence.​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't have any money,​ ​​
​​​ ​but have this.​ ​​
​​​ ​Suisei joined the party.​ ​​
​​​ ​Shirakami Bar​ ​​
​​​ ​Gotta stock up for the road.​ ​​
​​​ ​True.​ ​​
​​​ ​Welco...​ ​​
​​​ ​Eek!​ ​​
​​​ ​Join us if you don't​ ​​
​​ ​want this place destroyed.​ ​​
​​​ ​Fubuki joined the party.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey, hey!​ ​​
​​​ ​You'll get nowhere​ ​​
​​ ​without equipment!​ ​​
​​​ ​The sound of my homeland!​ ​​
​​​ ​Iofi joined the party on her own.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey-up!​ ​​
​​​ ​This here is Atlantis!​ ​​
​​​ ​Gura probably joined the party...​ ​​
​​​ ​Maybe?​ ​​
​​​ ​I am a traveling NEET.​ ​​
​​​ ​My restaurant failed,​ ​​
​​ ​and I'm broke.​ ​​
​​​ ​Thank you.​ ​​
​​​ ​I can't be giving up now, can I?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll start another restaurant!​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara joined the party.​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait a second,​ ​​
​​ ​what about my restaurant?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll get it back up and running.​ ​​
​​​ ​Thanks for narrating so far!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh?​ ​​
​​​ ​A diva...​ ​​
​​​ ​Booze...​ ​​
​​​ ​And a harmonica?​ ​​
​​​ ​It's time to partay!​ ​​
​​​ ​Eek! Normies...​ ​​
​​​ ​Overlord Aqua!​ ​​
​​​ ​You will give us back our Sun!​ ​​
​​​ ​We're outnumbered here.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey, wait!​ ​​
​​​ ​Turn the sky back to normal.​ ​​
​​​ ​I... dunno how to...​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's dance!​ ​​
​​​ ​Campfire!​ ​​
​​​ ​Our very own​ ​​
​​​ ​summer...​ ​​
​​​ ​begins now!​ ​​