[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
good morning
yes morning how is it good breaking
morning it smells like a day for a race
I have one I have one uh cheerleading
Pom-Pom s
where is it oh there's like a pumpkin oh
yeah okay well everybody Welcome to oh
the year sports festival Hollow sports
festival yes yes yes is everyone excited
[Music]
[Applause]
we are I mean
uh we're gonna uh if a team leader would
like to uh start the introductions while
I also do an audio check
oh hell yeah let's do it hello I am the
leader of ytmc
um I am takanashi Kiara from her live
English and next up was that okay
[Music]
I am incredibly athletic and I'm ready
to open a can of whoop ass today on the
red team
you know what we should maybe say what
games we're participating in good a lot
games are you participating in
specifically
um I might get this wrong but I'm pretty
sure I'm doing the uh relay race and the
PVP
uh-huh uh-huh and and the uh Red Light
Green Light because those two relay and
red light green light I'll put everyone
yeah red light green light yeah PVP PVP
are you confidence today for PVP I
believe Pingus might have uh a different
a different say on how they turn out to
the event today is going to go but you
know what I'm here to do my best and I
and I and I I I I I I I I I I I I I I I
think that today is going to go well
thank you guys you have to you're gonna
have a great race just kidding no you
don't have to win but let's try to win
of our team and I also participate in
the uh ball tossing and the relay and
the red light green light so next up
Sana
a it's been a while
everybody has been training so hard I've
been sleeping I've been eating potatoes
and sleeping on the couch but I I'm
feeling pretty athletic to say
um
the relay and the red light green light
with everyone yeah
[Music]
our one and only Indonesian participant
today is
[Music]
[Applause]
although I'm the only one but I'm not
alone here because I'm with you guys and
also I will be participating in a red
light green light and yeah relay and
also baltas yay
[Music]
thank you thank you let's work hard
together
I
am nothing wow
hello
I'm uh what the hell are you doing here
and you know what you guys
um today I'll be participating
will you please
motivated
I'm motivated oh yes yeah yeah motivated
we gotta destroy the red team seek
destroy them easy peasy
next up
who's been practicing really hard in an
obstacle course
[Music]
number one detective I'm eating a piece
of pizza and
um they'll be participating in the
obstacle course which my world record is
34 seconds
let's go
[Music]
oh sorry did I miss someone besides Bay
no I think last one is bae
hello
that'll take us uh representing chaos
from Council on camera I am serving
humbly as the cameraman today I hope I
do my job correctly
um for those who are saying the game was
Frozen
um I was switching between tabs to fix
everyone's audio levels so I hope
um it's everyone sounds okay now
we sounded good I turned the game audio
on as well you sounding good
[Music]
I don't know do they say that in English
to get our chocolate sign chocolate sign
questions this is the good side of your
face or whatever oh I don't know but um
yeah we're gonna have lots of fun today
we're gonna kick lots of butt and I
would just like to uh shout out on
remember Elfie I hope you feel better
soon she will forever be a part of
Waikiki which is why her photo is up
there on this game forever
yeah unfortunately
[Music]
however for example for the Relay
instead of elfi meal senpa is running
for us just helping us out so looking
forward to that yeah in in spirit eofi
will be there probably like a ghost
she'll be like
I know okay
um
simple could you say something I think
you're a bit quiet but I don't know
is that better babies they're always
complaining about my audio so hold on
I'll put a boost on it motion
Amelia Boston
oh I better maybe it sounds louder on my
end
is better
yeah it's good guys we're good okay
we need okay slogan we need a team
slogan everybody
oh what was it why is everyone carrying
my w
apparently is our slogan the universe is
with us
W slap
yeah
I guess
no slapping teammates only arrivals
please slap them slap them good on their
butts
do do it do it do it but do it do you
want to
I want to
oh it's fixed don't don't destroy it why
is everyone holding Blue wool I heard
all oh no I heard a crash
um
[Music]
this thing is already making itself
known
[Music]
where's my goodness too do I get a good
luck too too
oh she's waiting but I don't oh it just
looks like you're chasing her now okay
oh
she's coming towards me
kiss me damn it come here
do what I didn't mean to
oh
it's fine you like uh I feel like a
certain onion Senpai is
trying to
get her attention
it's not even a love triangle almost
like a love
parallel
what oh
oh this ping oh
hello no how do you guys feel about
today's sports festival
how do you feel what are some nervous
nervous
okay follow me I'm jumping follow follow
me
I haven't called out team yet
goes
[Music]
okay okay no okay all right okay I think
they call us by team
um
[Music]
today was the first time when suguru
said stuff to us earlier and is it weird
that I felt really Starstruck I like
kind of hung up
yeah everybody is here
I know exactly how you feel
yeah
and then I sat on her trash can so
because she had no other chair and then
her attraction was destroyed by my butt
I am so sorry
[Music]
yeah
[Applause]
let's go
exactly let's go let's go let's go I'll
let you know
I just zoomed into your forehead I'm
sorry about the way
um when they're calling us over to the
big voice chat Channel we gotta stay
muted yes okay okay
let's go let's go let's go
oh my God
yes
everyone
[Music]
um
oh
I'm good okay
[Laughter]
got myself 20 pom-poms nice
[Music]
she's throwing me to have them follow
lots of red team it smells like a bunch
of them yeah berries over there
look at your berries
antioxidants but not a lot of W's over
there yeah
[Applause]
it might be poison it might be poisonous
oh okay okay
don't take their food don't take
[Music]
it's poison
trays oh I was trying out I was like
who's the pink hair with red eyes I feel
better
I love her
oh there they go
saving the best for last I see yeah the
women are going to enter
the winter the winners always okay we're
ready
I'm still waiting I've never been to a
sports guy hold your hands okay okay so
you don't get lost okay all right
no no okay wait wait wait
all right
excellent choice
oh my goodness okay
inside all of your hair okay okay we're
gonna see you guys
okay ah we have a ride we have arrived
good job girls okay
we're moving
[Music]
foreign
I love it
Elizabeth
[Music]
okay we're starting the opening ceremony
okay
[Music]
um
it is beginning
foreign
[Music]
suppose
um
[Music]
foreign
because of today
[Music]
all right
okay
[Music]
yeah
foreign
[Music]
the person bye hi
hi
what is happening
[Laughter]
already
foreign
[Music]
I know
the lines never worked lines never
worked in the first place
hi
hi guys
bloody mask yeah and that's the opening
Style
the festival is
[Music]
the first event is the obstacle
okay let's go back
welcome
are you guys ready for the obstacle
course
I'm very hyped at the moment I'm so
freaking hyped okay we are ready to go
okay
[Music]
yeah
I forgot everything that I practiced
we're doing obstacle of course first yes
aren't we
yeah
if you're not actually one of the
obstacle course participants you can
watch the whole thing from above uh in
the glass ceiling okay let's go
I don't remember
Amelia
[Music]
okay
literally I want to see them skills ah
obstacle race
good and Amelia only yes yes okay so um
yeah yeah yeah
thank you
we got our pom-poms ready we're cheering
you on oh I have a place no the first
place the first race is um red a versus
white a okay um we are our last so good
and I know you can wait you can chill oh
no no they mixed up they mix up the
groups no she is racing first
yeah oh no this is wrong in the in the
thingy oh okay um go to the near uh to
the latest announcement
I gotta go to the all when you're
participating to the all all channel
in the first round it should be okay
[Music]
because the others are also staying in
there please Gather in the old voice
chat
oh God she could do it she could do it
she's got it
should we call her from it Watson
um
come on they got nothing on you man
nothing
you see that 34 seconds nah bruh I was
watching her practicing and she was so
into it she was so passionate so
efficient gamer sense hell yeah
come come out somewhere
It's gotta gotta show results literally
let's freaking go
ah my tummy's in or not this is so weird
you'll be fine
[Music]
I believe let's go watch it
is so cute she gave me some something me
she picked up my pumpkin pie oh she's so
cute she is so good I remember and he's
interested in joining my cult
worshiper
yes
I remember
um when we were doing the PVP practice I
was like all alone because I didn't know
where to go and then she came and got me
yeah
good doggo
but no matter I'm gonna smash everyone
yes yes she's already intimidating
everyone like literally look at the Gap
look at the Gap look at the Gap you see
the intimidating Aura of owl she's
getting uh claimed her right corner
yeah
that's the lineup is like the gamers
versus gamer Army
yeah
all of those Japanese members aren't
Gamers yeah it's the gamer race oh my it
should be like gamer yeah
official Gamers let's close let's go
Gamers
oh wait no no they're the team okay got
it
because some people are like in the oh
no no I'm just stupid okay I should
probably go here
oh wait no I can't go I got that good
angle I need to get the good angle
um
let me find a good angle I think this
was a good angle for now hey oh are you
starting oh I have to go watch it
[Applause]
nice nice
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
he's down
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
it's so cool what
I can't see
oh
wow
okay and then she was doomed
early no jokes let's go let's freaking
go
you didn't even die once yo who else is
left no she's a great oh I see it
come on
[Applause]
[Music]
I'm success
up
[Music]
um
you did great I missed one okay
wonderful yes yes
cameras please I gotta get push push
through oh sorry
press pass
where is it
um
hell yeah
humble champ
very nice
yeah I struggled with the camera
give us a comment um
I'm gonna do amazing wait we can do it
which one is good yeah I'm nervous you
can do it again
somebody managed to be so freaking fast
yeah we didn't even fall down did you I
mean you didn't know I felt I fell at
the end I missed like one jump but it
was okay because I landed on the glass
to get to the finish line but uh yeah
you know just practice timing were you
nervous
uh afterwards my heart was beating but
like during I was just focused let's
okay guys
thank you
you can do it
yeah
thanks so much okay bye
wait where Did We join it doesn't say it
oh it's still just me calling me on
you can do it
I did fine and practice but now it's the
real deal this is what counts and this
is what I'm gonna do yeah just remember
to get those checkpoints you can hit
people I was too nervous fubuki was
right in front of me but I didn't want
to hit it
all right let's go are you allowed to
hit people no right yeah you can hit oh
you can hit me yeah
it's okay you got the same you got a
call a junior in here
[Music]
another
house
oh let's freaking go that's intense that
is very intense who is it foreign
maybe she's God of hell yeah
yes
oh
what did I say why
she wanted to uh what get a better time
or so
it's over Corona Senpai it's always too
late
[Music]
foreign
okay
you can do it
yes
[Music]
come on where is he respawning in the uh
oh what if she didn't actually look at
the bed oh no
it's okay
oh she's in hell
oh
father's still in there though and then
she is also still in there so
she's still struggling we can do it okay
[Music]
first we can do it
oh that's okay it's okay it's okay
one more one more good it's okay at the
end of the day
come on
I wonder
nice
[Music]
don't give up never give up
everything
water he would have won exactly come on
yeah
[Music]
it's okay she did great no problem
she probably was racing in Australia and
therefore last one was first place so
yeah yeah yeah she's first yeah oh it's
the pink it's the pink oh yeah it's the
pink not that pink
it's the Ping it's not her fault imagine
if she was like you know closer to
um you know the the pink was like what
like 10 ping yo she would have just
zoomed
exactly yeah
just zoomed
who's participating in the last one wait
what oh we don't have the uh oh no one
no one from our team I think
all right
look at her look at that white team go
go you're doing great you did great
she's just staring
is it great he's a great good app crowd
he looks like I
absorbed all the choke for everybody
everybody else is gonna do a break for
the game
cute it's all good
the most important thing did you have
fun
um yes
[Laughter]
oh my God I just realized
why haven't I put
it
okay
that will give us like boost yes yeah
thank you
Anya
yeah
are the ones that we got to support oh
man I saw onions
any any Insider info on how good the
others are
um I don't know
not sure but come on
magma is like customers like I believe
it's her territory
oh hell yeah hell is her territory
exactly we got this in the bag white
team let's go
I wonder if she can do like a Saturday
attack by just going hard to match them
on the voice chat
distraction it's gonna be so scary
though
distraction tactic is definitely a thing
exactly it's exactly that would
intimidate me and I'm the universe
it was you wasn't it
that hurt Bunda
oh after this one by the way is the ball
tossing so oh yeah yeah
we've got it
we're ready
[Music]
this is where it starts
[Applause]
[Music]
in the lead
[Applause]
because
[Music]
she could take it oh she just take the
bed oh
I think so I think oh
oh
this place what responsible Place let's
go let's go wow
that was pretty close
oh
let me go have a look hold on
this camera work is a little more
difficult
I'm sorry guys today
upstairs
okay
we're inside here restarting uh I think
she's in the last part okay
[Music]
oh she's in the pool she's in the pool
yeah swim swim
[Music]
[Applause]
did Anya make it oh she died
oh nice
nice
he jumps again
[Music]
she get the bed
[Applause]
[Music]
oh there she is okay
what's up
yeah that we did it we did it we did it
we did it come on look at that oh
no
[Applause]
no no there's there's always gonna be
someone that gets last it's uh
unfortunate but inevitable
[Music]
not bad the last part we're practicing a
lot perhaps yeah
I saw that skill I saw it with my eagle
eyes sorry thanks so much
well done well done
nice too very nice I think the megaphone
is a bit difficult to hear oh okay I'll
start from now on I'm sorry
oh guilt
I get the the feeling of wanting to use
it I get that
hahaha
love the megaphone I do got a lot of
megaphone
yeah I do really love my megaphone
anyway well done
Ian represents
[Music]
oh no oh no
oh no oh no sir dominance
laughs
I am proud
and then there's still goes into trying
to defuse the fine
[Laughter]
you're just hiding in the back
hello
all right okay
it's red a versus white a oh okay okay
this is
right here
um
right here what do I watch
um so we can see here
oh that is a great view okay
let's go
let's freaking go
do you know anywhere we can put our
stuff
your stuff which stuff do you have like
yes it's like I don't want to keep my
pom-poms
oh your pom-poms um
you can maybe store them or you can give
them to someone else yeah yeah I'll take
your pom-poms if you want I'll keep them
safe I'll keep them safe oh I'll give
I'll give my pom pom too okay okay
I don't know if you guys figured it out
but the
um the golden block to get the the
Snowballs it gives it much much quicker
if you just keep on stepping on it
rather than push pushing it with your
hands oh yeah just walk over it
okay
idle stuff I don't step let's go
and we should try to avoid being two
people at once at one button so oh yeah
oh probably like one person stepping
like five times and then just yeah go
around that yeah the other person's
stepping and while they're throwing the
other person's steps yeah stretch stress
guys we got them strapped yeah
we're gaming we're Gamers Gamers we're
Gamers here
yeah
I'm very excited you know my opinion I
feel like this is the hottest
like one eh I think I think it's easy to
practice but yeah it's quite a lot of
fun yesterday practicing oh no it's
really fun it's just really hard for me
to aim into the hopper
um
in my experience if I look up then it
lands on the other side if I look
straight then it lands on the hopper
yeah that's yeah I usually like look
probably because I'm kinda sure
that's a golden angle You Gotta Throw at
yeah
something
so the a teams are going first we can
look at their strategies but oh that's
something I'm gonna stay with mine in
any case even if they do something else
yeah
I think Lisa you you mentioned uh when
we were practicing you mentioned
something about you know someone
stepping on the pressure plate and the
other one uh yeah because back then it
used to be like lots of people at one so
there is there is somebody who uh
pressed the oh you know pushing that
button and then somebody that throws oh
that's also a strat
yeah but if we would have done that we
should have practiced that so I guess
we're not doing that yeah
oh
sorry if you heard that thump that was
my massive water bottle
okay it's the it's the size of my
forearm
oh sorry it's gonna replenish all that
water after sweating yeah
we're doing sports here right now we all
have some down time if you wanna take
some breakfast or dinner or whatever
yeah or take a break need some alone
time feel free to yeah
alone time sit in the corner
anytime I think we're going to stand
right next to you guys
but always make sure to be there in time
for your special mattress or whatever
by the way I I needed to discuss
something with you guys
um for the Birdman darts and you girls
will have to be shooting arrows at Muna
when she's flying and
um we are actually uh one person less
than their team
um so they have one more person to shoot
arrows but um they told me yesterday
that we will just get five more arrows
and we can either give only one person
five more errors but I think that's a
bit too much or we can spread them over
what is this everyone else
there is anyone who has like confidence
in shooting arrows you will get more oil
stands oh
sorry I missed it
[Music]
than shooting so what kind of oh my God
if you don't have so much confidence
we'll give it to someone else maybe
good at shooting
uh shooting flying thing is not too good
but I mean you can trust me with it I'll
do my best
too yeah yeah shooting yeah shooting
yeah
[Music]
what the heck
oh
my God
look at that because she's just focusing
yeah
you know
what's wrong
unless she's going to the other side oh
did they run out
no it's actually really good
attack oh look at that that's amazing
look at that nice
stretch
[Music]
Wow Let's freaking go
I wonder who has the most strong first
round
What's it gonna be
I can't do a drum roll does anyone know
how to do a drum roll
[Applause]
nice job
oh my fingers
all right is everybody here on the white
team because the names are not
um
yeah oh there's a right side oh wait
where are you I'm all right okay okay
okay
if you look at the Hoppers they have
white banners on our side and the red
banners on the other hand
what's happening
time to count Bono they exploded our
snowballs though Neil said bye
oh yeah she broke the chest
how do you count it though I don't know
sometimes a telescope thingy
[Music]
cute
oh yeah team wins oh
[Music]
it's okay
by four apparently
very close oh that's so close apparently
it's 92 to 96. oh my oh
is asking for how many balls it was
oh wow that's so close 96 that's a lot
we don't get that money in our practice
did we yeah
we're gonna like maybe 50 60 I don't
know oh
team is as good this one as we are I
believe in this one right this one right
here right here
oh my God it's okay you did your best
you did everyone did amazing
oh thank you
wait isn't it oh yeah okay
in so many balls
as long as you do your best I'm proud of
you guys yeah wow that's what counts as
long as you try your best that's all
anyone
um hit us for yes yeah
wow
oh at least we have someone with
experienced at least from last year oh
that's true yeah
I'll do it yes I can do it guys show
them show them both skills
okay so next it looks like fiance energy
and photographs and five yeah
[Music]
one yes
oh
very nice
are they are they being stretched or are
they going to
see all right sorry I thought you were
someone else I'm sorry
I don't know why I saw your hat and I
was like crony you're in my way but then
I was like wait no cronies
I'm sorry
okay
I'm ready I'm ready
hello oh
I got a funny assembly gave me a spy
glass to look at her oh yeah that's nice
you got good skin beautiful eyes wow
those plump lips
are weird
very interesting place to look at you
know well I had a big close-up okay
I thought you were I thought you were
protocol for a second
[Music]
are you ready is it starting oh my God
they're getting ready yeah countdown
coming soon I guess all right
after like when we're joining this or
not
okay don't wait actually
a team one second yeah
[Music]
all right
oh they're going in
let's go to him
let's go they're they're currently still
in their mixed voice chats I think I
think we're setting up maybe
oh yeah there's probably just setting up
stuff they might be replacing the
Snowballs and stuff
oh yeah yeah that's true
jokes
it's very cute how did you how do you
copy and paste stuff like from the
server to server I don't know and like
even the three two one stopping like
controllers
you select control C control V
yes control C control V this this only
this specific portion did they go like
by block
maybe maybe importance
oh goodness
coordinates
and then there's you know oh my God
everything
is okay
it's gonna be more intense though
because there's just gonna be like three
people in the voice chat oh that that's
true
but you can use Scare Tactics oh wait no
no you're in different sorry I thought
you were in the same voice
I'm not watching Miko Zoom around oh
yeah did you just show the the dragon in
the sky yeah I did oh yeah I was shocked
I thought it was like what what is an
actual mall yeah I built that yesterday
in the middle of the night that was the
last thing that they did
cute I was actually yeah talking with
them while they were doing that they
built that so quickly like literally it
took them five minutes or something I
mean
so from down here if it looks huge from
down here it means it must be huge if
you go up there yeah
[Music]
for the first time I saw it
oh meat
that we have to take 10 snowballs in the
beginning but I wonder if there's like a
limit or some specific food that they
want us to take our food limit is
unlimited uh for food for this round
yeah um
wait what's the best food this meat's
the best food cooked meat yes
meat is the best for like meat it heals
faster
yeah
falling down a lot you take damage with
every freaking phone
and
gotta be careful dying here would be the
most embarrassing thing ever yeah
well golden apples are not available
it was
his first name is k and the last name is
Kaku keikaku nice
yeah never heard of it
are they preparing now yeah oh they're
going in oh they're going on
the cameraman spot
I'm not going in going back uh-oh okay
hello
[Music]
this is a good team I believe in the
power of the line team hell yes
it's crazy on the other side power of
say so boys wins
it's uh looks like uh Marine Sam fine
I did see them practicing a little bit
last night but
um
I wonder
also I love how okay
okay you said if I was just staring up
oh There She Goes Again do you know that
the book Senpai is actually circling
around us oh really yeah
no no okay he's on the other team
they're staring off into space
I see you I see you
[Music]
again
it's like offering a cat like
probably asserting dominance
does pumpkin pie give you more Health
than a steak
oh look at that look at that goes
come on
oh my God
look at that white team Supernanny let's
go
him
first yeah
we got do we have any snowballs
look at that aim wow
oh my God
nice nice
look at that look at it oh
can we get an instant replay
it's absolute unload Madness dominating
that you spam the Q spam
the Q spam is fantastic with this team
of players here and it is Super Nintendo
currently reloading
is still oh getting that cue spam
oh my God it's also reloading yes
reloading super energy once again hop
with the dump
nice accuracy 100. look at that one was
throwing the ball
oh yeah yeah
[Music]
with the final reload in for this final
uh ball dropping challenge the balls are
dropping ladies and gentlemen
let's go
I'm gonna say something right now
let's go let's go
[Music]
take a little bit of pressure off of me
please
please my team please please white team
I can't cause no more
we can do it yeah let's
yell at home
[Music]
why are they hitting each other
it's okay they did great they did great
come on come on come on come on come on
come on what's the final score
Dallas
my heart is Doki Doki
I need to know
I need to know come on
come on at one snowball in the middle of
the field is annoying me yeah
you cannot touch me at all
oh
136 that's a big gap
s
yeah wait where are they posting the
results
oh God oh God it's okay
throwing
things
falling
the bowling game cause we balling
I think I think my team won that one
because it can't be a mistake that they
got 69.
bowling
balls deep yeah
oh I forgot to tuck your shirt in
what oh yeah that's how I messed up so
bad I tripped on my shirt on the
obstacle course and then like repeatedly
did tuck it in for me
all right
thank you
we're gonna take a screen not to give I
want to take one come here to me all
right I will show my fish
[Music]
right side
oh
uh I can't tell the difference between
left and right whoa Frozen
like they're here
[Music]
in the middle
then Sama will be across from me
I guys got this good luck please
go to the top left corner for snuggles
uh if you guys want to get snowballs I
can see for
um the bottom right or the left as well
you can join me or however you want to
do it
just throw me snowballs because I'm
pretty confident with my aim oh yeah
we got Gamers on this team on this final
round of the snowball to us I believe in
you guys are you guys moving to another
a different Channel
[Music]
now that the others did it
with like the bowling
I was just gonna have us all throw it
once uh and just take it whenever you
want it's good
it's all right once the like of summons
uh what you call it the switch I think
you can just like throw your throw your
inventory at me and then I'll go go
reload while I'm throwing or something I
think that would be fine it's like I'll
I'll like reload if like no one is there
but if someone said just throw it just
throw your stack at me
just like
um
well if if someone if both of us I think
like uh well it's rarely that both of us
are using the the buttons right
but if we are just like through your
second knee sir oh wait you can always
you can always control wait no no you
can control no no no no no no no not
into the ball uh into the hopper but you
can control Q at each other right yeah
yeah
yeah yeah just throw your stuck at me if
like if like if you happen to be there
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
I'll just like
press the button yeah yeah yeah yeah
throwing Stacks is not allowed no you're
not allowed into the hopper but if
you're throwing sacks at each other that
should be fine all right take 10 and get
right here
get ready all right let's try the
snipples at me and you know hmm shall we
go to the voice chat
oh my God
let's collaborate my team I'm not sure
we can have a comeback here to be quite
honest it's quite a
quite a heavy load they'll be carrying
this round can they make a color oh my
god oh no what is this looking very good
what's this possibly well over 150 at
this point really wait it was 6 59
versus 134 16 134 minus 69 that is the
totals though no no that was from last
round 134 minus 69. that should be 64.
before that 65 difference plus another
four difference where oh what was 69
points behind
oh all right well I gotta carry they
gotta carry who are they going up
against they gonna come back with a big
carry oh Cali okay we might have a
chance ladies and gentlemen
[Music]
yes yes yes
all right let's leave I'm not gonna take
it in you guys
I believe I believe
you have to you have to you have to
agree Sonic's aim is really good
actually
has past experience exactly we've got
experience and talent and Kiara
I'm sure we'll pull the uh I'm not gonna
say anything
outside
that's nice here
come on oh boy
enter the basketballs are in the baskets
Toby would be proud you're smiling down
upon this team today what about the
other side
yeah other teams got nothing idle step
very nice very nice very nice
to come back the white team has been
waiting for ladies and Gentlemen let's
see if they can pull through
okay
oh
oh come on Santa
come on Sana let's go reset Kiara what's
your name
no seriously I feel like they're all
like they're all doing great wow
wow
oh my God I don't think Cali knows how
the Slime works but she's doing her best
on the red team
doing your best oh
nothing nice it's all nice Kiara 30
seconds
say Let's go Team why let's turn this
around team wait another chance at him
something here trophy we got Universe on
our side we are bound to win there's no
way we're not winning this one 12
seconds the final big load let's go come
on
come on
let's go
[Music]
you did great
thanks a lot
so proud of him I'm so proud of everyone
you guys take away
so proud I'm so proud I could cry now we
wait the final score
white team's holding their breath or I
am I'm holding my breath come on come on
at least pull it closer you think yeah
yeah at least a little bit closer
69 point difference everyone's 69.
oh
okay
did it oh
is that a
it's a win is it a whizzy is it a win
I'm holding I'm on the edge of my seat
is it wind
s please feel in
come on give us the results yeah
no yeah
we thought we thought we're we're like
oh no we're doomed you know
I like swimming my entire I like put in
a lot of snowballs I think so I didn't I
didn't uh
the thing that lets you fly up there
yeah I missed it like two three times it
made me so good okay
okay all right
all right we are now
nice again we are now 40 points
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
okay she's gone they're gone the
interviewers are gone would you like to
translate what you said I am well just
the same thing as before that I thought
I up really bad with like the
pressure plates but yeah it was better
than I thought it was I guess
the pressure plate is really bad gacha
system now when I was practicing I I
mean I mean
all the circles on the floor so I didn't
have to gotcha very much
having always been feeling
now the Catapult didn't work so well for
me sometimes even though in practice I
was so solid I didn't have a single time
when I didn't hit the Catapult but um
when you oh my God so many times I told
you guys
I have no doubt that like we'll do okay
I have I have good confidence in my aim
we were singing I mean
so hello
height Advantage but I think Guru and I
were watching were like yo Sana look at
the balloons
it was enough to bring white team back
on them
nine points behind and then now there's
a difference
happy as long as as long as we made
Subaru Senpai proud then I'm happy yes
wait what's next I said it for you
a birdman died
on the left side yes yes
follow the dragon in the sky in here
now's our chance to bring it back yes
bring it back
you were born
and we probably got the best archer in
Ian I dare to say
um yes we do you know yeah but you know
they fly really quickly ah one one thing
that you guys definitely need to do
um you gotta raise your chunks otherwise
you won't see the birds in the sky race
okay all right okay we only take the
Five Arrows and then
a bow okay so yeah we get five extra
arrows don't just share them uh between
yourselves
but right now right now
it's not our turn yet anyway so wait
what how many challenges do we should we
go to
oh oh this is where we watch okay okay
since it's not our turn right now anyway
when you see them flying in the next
turn then just adjust your chunks
according to that I guess
when they fly because we still got time
anyway
is flying in the sky so maybe try to
figure I can see that you can see here
although she's still pretty close yeah
yeah
the Phoenix
okay so basically when we when the other
team is uh shooting we have to I don't
know when they're flying we gotta come
here right
Who besides Inna has confidence in
shooting
I'm not very confident
I have never I've never touched a bird
before every animal crossing when I'm
playing Minecraft I I don't know I don't
want to kill the animals
no but I might not
oh
let's go let's give the two extra arrows
to uh you know and two extra for gouda
and one extra for amen okay okay
oh wait wait so everyone gets five is
that wait wait what yeah basically
everyone gets five
some of us get more because we have one
less shooter than the red team
um
so there will be one more person more uh
shooting me when I'm in the sky in
exchange for that we get five more
arrows gotcha are you guys flying at the
same time no no no no okay
I can't fly though that's the problem
poop cake next to the big
you see the white Stadium next to the
next to the next to the black glass wall
yeah
do you see it yeah that's where we stand
too the red fire Subaru is yeah yeah
yeah yeah they're gonna shoot around
here yeah but right now pecora sample
from Red's team a will be flying so
white team a will be shooting her yes oh
I don't know how this works I just
realized okay let's take a look at what
they're gonna do now so is behind us if
you look behind us she's on that
platform that's why she
flies and then she has to go through the
Hoops but then as she's trying to go
through the Hoops the white team has to
try and shoot her down
I think it might be smart to aim um for
around the Hoops because they will
always go through the Hoops uh before
that will go or Muna in in our case Muna
will go through the red hoop on the very
left first then she will go through the
three middle Hoops you will not go
through the very right white hoop
because that one is only for the white
team players yeah yeah so try to maybe
aim at the middle I guess I don't know
what's the best way to aim to be honest
because I'm the flyer but you know
yeah it's all right we gotta lead your
shot it's not a it's not gonna hit
direct so you wouldn't want to aim above
wherever you're gonna shoot because the
Arrow's gonna fall
[Music]
I believe the amount of times Ina has
saved me from her arrows yo belief
s destroyed the dogs besides Sana has
anyone else never shot an arrow in
Minecraft
I have but I'm not really a bow user
yeah neither yeah I'm more like assorted
Shield yeah I'm more of an ass hack my
way through
I think yeah because they'll be flying
really really far away you always I
think you always need to load up your
shot
[Music]
rather than just quickly releasing it
yeah
um right clicking down yeah holding it
down longer and you will see it
um in your like Minecraft layout or
whatever you will see how it loads
itself up with I think a green bar you
will see that
all right let's go it's funny oh there
you go
it's kind of really cute
oh
is she gonna land on the golden block
actually the golden block and the white
block below is only five points
difference and I'm probably just gonna
land on the white one because I wow look
at her go I'm gonna how many chunks do
you have Kira I currently
15 but I don't see pickled all the time
either oh yeah I have it at 20 something
so I'm just that's good I'm munching to
put mine to 37. 37. you guys who are
just staying in one place shooting
that's okay oh that's cool oh
she's she probably gets 55 points I
think for that wow that was good
wow that's amazing wow should be 55.
oh God by the way uh the Flyers can fly
two times but it's not best out of two
it's um most recent attitude yeah so if
you get a good flight in the first try
then you or me
um yeah might want to just keep that
score
55. I can't tell is that high or low
that's high the maximum is 16. oh my wow
but generally I was also able to get 55
in practice so yeah let's go
but in in the practice there was a
practice stream where a lot of people
were trying to shoot me down and no one
was able to shoot me down whoa let's go
what if they shoot her down now
it's never good to be too
I wonder careful I would be careful I
wouldn't do it again if I have 55
perfectionist she's going for it yeah
that's quite a Gamble
all right okay I'll see you
okay shoot again
hi
I think if you want Sana you could
probably practice a tiny bit on the side
uh trying to oh at least how do I do it
there she goes uh
underneath the stage uh there's in the
Shocker boxes where the where the white
beds are there's there should be arrows
oh
whoa oh that was really close
I should be leaving where'd she go
I'm moving oh I see all the shoes
nice oh my gosh I got it
wow wow wow
where are you here I am
School 37.
oh my oh
yes wow
wow she got four
wow your first shot was lucky
oh my God okay I'm out
all right I'm picking up your arrows
wait wait where it was happening here
as she was I was helping her practice
all right at least now you have a
feeling for it you know how to load it
up right
up my man can try
maybe I can try shoot a higher Target
yeah maybe I'll try Apple player you can
try shoot the Blue Block here maybe
just don't but that one's not moving
yeah
okay move here here I'm moving
shoot me
just just don't hit please
you're not moving enough oh
thanks for taking the shot Lisa
wait let me eat let me eat first all
right all right I'm moving
wait okay how about this how about I
jump off the platform and you try and
hit me ready okay okay ready and cool
oh
did you did you get me
let's try again
okay are you ready
I'm out of hours oh okay all right
arrows
there's 10 uses to fly
oh wait put them down
yo no no words
nine
nice
big scores
she dominates the land now she's about
to dominate the skies let's go oh it
started oh my God
wow um
so close
um oh wait
that was so close
I didn't see well did she fly for the
middle one I don't think she did I don't
think so just didn't look like it I know
she can do it I've seen her do it before
55 no then she did
oh I was gonna try again is she gonna
try trying again nice okay he wants the
perfect 60. we can get that perfect
Steve
oh no wait 40 chat says 55 and 45 which
one is it 45 apparently it's not it
wasn't in the Minecraft chat yet so
but I'm pretty sure she missed the
middle one because I don't think I saw
her that's why it's 45 45 yeah
that's a good choice you must have been
nervous or something yeah
always you know you have a feel practice
and then you go for it yeah yeah yeah
that's pretty cool one
oh come on
man all that yeah nice
someone did here nice
okay
now she's gotta land come on God come on
come on come on nice and easy okay okay
no that's that's great
that's good though 55 55 it's okay
nice nice
[Music]
so close but it's okay
is B
nice who's flying for B
B is I think she once
yeah I think so oh and Canada for a red
team I think she wasn't bite oh
I'm pretty sure
I think are we all Gathering here what's
happening
oh we're still just chilling here oh
okay okay I thought we were like sending
sealants and by off or something wait so
those ones that are gonna shoot some
arrows should I I could go get a bow
yeah I feel like I should go get a boat
yeah I'm just gonna be like this oh same
oh yeah when are we shooting me not yet
not yet when Muna is flying yeah or
yeah
uh
all right so I guess gouda gets two
extras or seven and uh you know gets
seven and I may get six and the rest
gets five okay
unless anyone thinks stero the best at
shooting then nobody should I go get
extra if Ian is making six shots I'll
just pass mine over to her
well she means if I land six shots
I'm not very good at shooting flying
things why is there a Pom-Pom here
there's a Pom-Pom attached to the oh
excuse the character
he's flying kind of the Dead by flying
okay oh I need that bridge so I can
notice
all right they're growing up yeah
it's for our team
the flying witch
fighter
oh what's what's only doing here red
team Ollie's spying on us
huh what's their dominance
laughs
[Music]
somebody hit she's just like staring at
us like blank how dare you do this I can
hear her voice
oh Emilia both son oh you're right you
got that nickname Amelia
yeah have you heard about the Legends I
I expect greatness from you
else
oh
the legend of Boson
okay
you're not dancing but it's fine
oh you know we should be shooting at
shirtle hey
wait oh she better fly okay
yeah
shooting yes
get him down
oh there she goes okay shoulder down
shoot her down shoulder down oh I think
someone got it oh
oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh
okay okay okay okay
interesting
she's alive though she's alive
hey he landed on the white block okay
save
as long as you're alive it doesn't
matter getting hit
how many how many shots the Arrow does
it take to die though I think it's like
two because we're not wearing armor oh
when Santa hit me right in the face it
gave me like five Health points oh wow
okay okay she's flying again
yeah
okay
uh was that 55 points
everyone gets 55. when you practice that
should be manageable yeah experienced
Flyers
gotta go to infinity and beyond
it's so an endless kite
[Laughter]
German one oh
three two all right here she goes let's
go let's go oh
interesting okay
oh
she's fine very easy
oh oh wow
there's like one Arrow from Death yeah
literally she's one Arrow from Death
save it save her when she's about to
land because that's when she's gonna oh
that's not a bad idea save an arrow for
the for the end
[Music]
oh that's true oh I didn't see the glass
well I was like right above it and you
won't be able to shoot her anymore ah I
see yeah but you can Arch it
you calculate that trajectory yeah
okay 55 okay all right what next what
yeah
[Music]
garlic let's go
foreign
[Music]
book that you got oh it's from the uh
it's from Google
thank you Google thank you Google Uncle
Google
yes
how's everyone doing so far with like
tiredness sleepiness and food
I've been munching for the past like 20
minutes
I think most of us need
sleepers need sleep I'm actually a wide
awake some coffee but yeah I think I'm
on I'm on the oh she's fine oh she's
fine
oh
hey who's who's flying I don't see
anybody
yeah she's doing it she's doing a run-up
stories a few steps yeah she's doing the
prep you know look at those steps oh wow
I think she's getting interviewed all
right
I was like you should break dancing
what's happening
yeah are you ready
let's go
okay
oh god
let's go oh oh oh oh oh okay what was
that okay all right I see you see you
Sail
three two one
foreign
[Music]
she has to go again
sorry all right what happened
that was by accidentally yeah right at
the beginning and you only have a
maximum of free fireworks
if you use them too early then you know
you can't fly for all of them oh good
all right oh
just run
no problem yeah let's just run
hey I was like no wonder she went so
quickly she went Zoom
there's a big Zoom
okay
what are you talking about we're talking
about food yeah
um
I'm so hungry and then like there's all
this Minecraft food being close to me
what do you mean it's not making you
full
you can go get some food if you want
go see young
I
um oh
I'm ready for the takeoff
but no I've been munching on um
I got two two two two two two rows of
kimbap here that I'm just making my way
through
[Music]
yeah I like Kimbo sometimes I eat that
for lunch yeah tasty
I didn't have lunch and we're
approaching dinner so I just have one
row for each I'm just slowly making my
way through nice
okay okay let's go
[Music]
nice oh yes nice
[Applause]
[Music]
um
solids let's go looks like she threw 60
there at the end too nice
fell
are you okay
the cameraman our camera please cameras
getting excited
I'm sorry I got so excited okay
well done all right
before me so you gotta shoot her down
okay
is that our turn now yeah
can you do that can you can you be like
a close Empire there yeah like stacking
wool
[Laughter]
yeah no one died because of the
shootings it's hard to shoot like it
really is um wait whose turn is it oh me
and Laura but Moana flies first okay so
we have to go to the list
are we going over there now is it time
yes wow
[Music]
that is huge time to shoot
let's go get your arrow so it's a stand
here right okay I see I see okay fine
on the firing platform let's go I mean I
will not shoot but I will watch I have
to stand in the center of this white
thing I think so anywhere on the
platform
it's five blocks I'm guessing yeah wait
hold on
can you hold my extra arrows I picked up
okay
I have no idea okay anywhere here on the
platform I think is good shoot the moon
okay okay shoot the Moon foreign
oh my God brain explosion brain
explosion
it's our new catchphrase we just should
we shot like screaming shut down
look at the Moon
the Dark Side of the Moon
I like how awkward upon her
power
she wants good view she does want to get
here
she's so cute
I think Aqua Senpai streams for her from
her team so
okay that's not a big brain
I feel like if he does it she'll fall
full from the back hey that happened
foreign
that's true
okay
Bruno is taking off I'm ready to fly
you're ready to fly all right I can't
even see her from here though and I have
all my chunks up I I like barely see her
on the edge my boat is 64 trunks just
looking at me
let's go let's go
[Applause]
[Music]
I can't see it
when she comes back down
get your arrows ready
you can already get the same amount of
arrows again
probably yeah we get more arrows and
then we get another one again if she's
going again okay
probably I don't think she's satisfied
well she wants to get the perfect scene
oh that's kind of funny oh
God but someone hit her right
I think I think I hit her I couldn't do
it yeah the same spot yeah yeah
somebody's Like a Knife
we got a chance was she gonna fly
through this white circle first here
yeah the blue one no no no the red one
red for the red one first right above
her head yep she has to come this way
she has to come this way oh he is
calculating the good trajectory
calculating one step ahead okay I think
from this angle get ready
ready to fire
shoot the Moon
if you're happy about it but she can
just make a new one that's right now
let's go
she's coming
I can't hit her oh my God oh my God
two sure
oh oh is it amazing talk to you what the
hell
I'm about to die
what's it oh oh I don't think I got it
oh that should have got it oh
but she didn't land on where did she
land I didn't see it the white the white
the white white
ah so cool oh my God okay okay oh well
[Music]
guys
noise
look at that arrow in her arm
nice okay all right yeah it's your turn
to fly right yeah
[Applause]
yeah
you can do it
oh god
um can I can I ask you when I fly to um
be a little bit quiet because it makes
me yes everyone everyone
okay
yes now you can still be loud oh okay
[Music]
hell yeah that's my name
I like the Phoenix you're always meant
to be
hello
hey
yeah
but even though you're a phoenix please
touch the bed
[Music]
what it's like to fly as a natural
but I'm the one and only
um
[Music]
confidence we like the confidence
[Laughter]
okay
well I'm just gonna keep myself in there
because I can't help but be loud so I'm
just gonna scream for the stream okay
let's go
oh
nice nice nice nice oh so nice
okay
okay okay
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
she didn't get hit by any arrows
[Music]
she thinks they were scared of her
yeah
oh apparently she hit a phoenix it's the
same as hitting the Sun
so if the sun disappears
[Laughter]
[Music]
very nice
yeah
nice
all right
you guys can be loud again if you want
[Applause]
let's go
[Music]
I'm satisfied that was a great one right
mental support it was amazing no
actually that was one of my worst
flights because
um I didn't have enough height I almost
didn't get through uh the middle one
because I practiced in a way that um I
would go through the middle one from
above not from below and I almost didn't
make it that's when I was like oh
oh I messed up but it was okay
it always talks the real time around
thank you next is uh the Red Light Green
Light by the way oh yeah but we'll be
staying in this voice chat we have a
five minute break actually
is there
like what taste is it Sono ah
uh is this here wow
[Music]
that sounds so good that does sound good
do they have good Japanese food over
there
oh not really I just sort of know it I
order it from from space Amazon I missed
Amazon well they take quite some time
delivering
um
[Laughter]
so wait is this Obstacle of course the
red light green light or is it a flat
surface yeah it's uh rather clean out
here you'll see the text okay
it's flat but whenever the command comes
up green light you gotta stop otherwise
it will shoot you down oh yeah by the
way for everyone who gets shot down
um you will be unfortunately sent into a
spec spectation mode or whatever
we can bring this back you just have to
log out once and log back in
ah okay fixed it yeah all right
sent into limbo
I don't want to be ghosts
yeah uh 40 40 points huh you know wait
what are the points awarded for Red
Light Green Light
first is third
time number one
there's a chance there is a chance
excels at this game
right now is she a lighting
oh like like if if she's red team I'm
gonna like smack her or something
no that's not allowed you're not allowed
to hit others
no smacks no smack any smacks all right
only smack pump
yeah
okay smack functional hey if you punch
someone when they're red you're also
moving so yeah that's true oh yeah true
uh you are allowed to eat
um and eating doesn't count as moving so
it will not show them yeah that's nice
that's nice
yeah not even a little smack no not even
a little one
all right let's see
look at look at Subaru Senpai is
asserting her dog oh wait wait everyone
is wait are we on break
yeah I will break yeah five minutes all
right
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
oh okay did you guys like the video yeah
that video was really cool
I didn't watch it I need to watch the
Vlog yeah it was like a video we had all
of us they were showing all the
participants it was so cool
[Music]
okay hey ready for some red light green
light
is everyone going for the practice round
I think so
okay I guess maybe I'll be very crowded
maybe do we stand on the white blocks uh
behind the white behind of it yeah what
oh no no they say behind flashed in
front of it yeah I don't I don't know
it's not on top of it
she's going for it
it's going for it oh are there audio
cues at all no audio just huge letters
in the middle of the screen you will see
it yeah yeah okay okay so we just stop
when the thingies like yeah yeah I don't
know is there gonna be a countdown red
line three two one yeah and then yeah
you will see it's not difficult
aloud
all right are you sinking honey or do
you just kind of stay stuck on top slows
you down okay oh if you stop in the in
the middle of all those magma blocks and
you can't move I guess you can just
Crouch down yeah
oh really that's amazing wait have you
guys not been doing them
oh my God I was wondering why so many
people are dying during the pro yeah
like no one knows about
I don't know I just know about it like
today
yeah I didn't practice this one at all
you did I
he just landed
yeah
eyeing of the competition ready to kick
our butts yes
I see you I see you I'm alive gamer
she's so cute
she's so dangerous behind the cute cute
face Yes she'll eat too
oh no oh no
I think seeing how much you can jump in
the sticky you can't jump on honey yeah
you can jump but it's you basically
can't say it down little hops bunny hops
here we go wait you can jump you can
jump on the magma but it'll just hurt
random they're teammates what the hell
oh
[Laughter]
look at that right amazing
oh
[Music]
jump attack
Colony looks really good with the witch
hat it matches her it does it her
yeah oh I actually don't see her white
chat I only see it on myself why
are we all just creating each other
what's happening
oh no yeah
they they are really
what's going on I don't know
okay
[Music]
get out about section red team
you'll not want it here
this is for the white pure and say so
aggressively nice we aggressively safe
laughs
on this
what are you doing I'm punching people
Moana straight for me
oh
it's it's about to start okay okay okay
okay
all right
let's go I'm scared
Brown anyway
the Dragon Ball
she's she's getting this scary
administrator vibe
the president
class president here to kick their butts
only red a and white a are okay all
right all right I guess before
everyone's actual turn each group gets a
practice round all right where do we
look oh we look on that side okay gotcha
up here we got some seats all right yay
they prepared seeds for everyone yeah
nice nice
I'm gonna be here with my camera work
I'm gonna look at them
oh there's stairs on the left amazing
yeah and the red ones on the right
everything is so well built this is
amazing so
much love and work into this
[Music]
is the grouping order the same for the
obstacle course at the beginning than it
is for this so you Group B is always
Group B
yeah a b and then yeah
okay
yeah start moving once the it will be
displayed in English as well it's just
gonna be green I think I'm super simple
is asking like you know how the text
face leads like can you move when the
text is fading
you know you gotta find the opportune
moment to move uh-huh
right right
let's go all right okay we can go okay
I'm gonna use this opportunity to figure
out the timing of when to start running
when to stop
oh
I can't wait to see people explode
still running free
oh that's nice okay
three two three two one
oh
my God
leading right now let's freaking go
foreign
[Music]
I was talking to chat I fell off the
chair I'm sorry I was too excited all
right back to the beginning okay cool
all right that was really fun
yeah wow
end of practice
okay
my only gate they get a practice
do we get a practice too okay okay for
each turn oh I see I think I will save
my my food first food
food
it's okay this time I won't fall over
that was a practice match doesn't matter
okay no falling over in this match okay
so avoid the in the water avoid the
magma in the water yeah okay gotcha
gotcha
but it's my favorite thing it's okay
okay
that's really fun how did they engineer
this wow
but that's impressive that's impressive
there's so many commands I don't know
that it's a festival
I don't know that it's actually
you know possible but hey people made it
so cool
yes there's a enough command blocks
yeah it's really cool
I will wait a minute
oh they're starting
up I'm in the right voice call the other
one is just full of Valley girls I'm
scared
exactly girls let me join you guys it's
very nice yes
um
oh
smart
um
paper
[Music]
it's the pink pickle everyone becomes
better though that's great yeah wow
I think um it gives us points so
survival yes be safe
where is she where is she
[Music]
say bye oh she's on the other end wait
no she came back what so now we have a
practice
hey
Assad we can observe some more yeah
hi hello what's up please forgive me
from intruding yeah sorry but I can't
take it okay is it that can you imagine
is it that bad macaroni oh no oh wait
it's crony Iris Maury I need to listen
but it's getting into it oh no
we are to say so wide welcome yeah
exactly
by me
thank you
it's terrifying
on the other side nightmare for the for
the night I guess
I'm gonna go have a piece before we are
red and white team we are quite a live
Memphis and we are together yeah hell
yeah I'm gonna go have a peek at this
valley girl I'll be right back
oh no she's going all right yeah
sir
[Music]
oh my God
you like come here Robin
[Laughter]
yeah nope yeah I don't want to go back
yeah I'm here to take you home yeah
we'll we'll reduce the valley girl
accents to at least 50 percent okay
at least 50. now come on we got to go
home that is taking you home yeah all
right all right
[Music]
here he goes all right thank you ladies
for taking care of Ollie at this time
you're well
I'll be honest if that's came knocking
away yeah we are kind of scared too
I can't imagine how scary it is on the
other team I'm glad I'm here
I went into the other chat for like
three seconds
it's a good squirrel yeah oh my oh my oh
oh my oh oh my oh what what happened
nothing I think I would have an internal
conflict
can you move from the after it says red
and it counts down yeah maybe you can
move you think
I don't know I don't want to drive
somebody else background sure oh which
I'm trying to practice on okay yeah okay
okay
observe
right because it went three two one wait
why didn't do it no she moved after like
red light I'm pretty sure she like
inched forward so I don't know whether
that was ping or that was like her
moving hmm
uh during three two one I'm pretty sure
okay
good stuff
nice nice nice nice
baby
after our match there will be a final
match by the way with the top contestant
yep the top five contestants going to
the final battle
yeah
so let's try to make it to the top
up to the top
okay okay
we light
oh
safe side
we have to remember that we have higher
ping too so like it looks like one for
us it might already be zero that's true
oh oh no oh
exploded okay let's go
come on come on
well
all right
[Music]
[Applause]
very nice no more coming
very nice
the speed
okay ah but that was only practice Oh I
thought it was real huh
I felt so real so intense
you know ouch I fell again
third
yeah
I'm going to the other side
you guys should stay on the bottom one
and then run again there are people on
the other side I just couldn't see them
like this ouch
okay
you woke back with it oh okay that does
make sense
I mean
okay I'm gonna do that from now on
hey yeah do you have my pom-poms oh yeah
dude
hi
look at pom-poms
that's all I see let's go hello
let's go
we got the pom-poms no one can beat us
now we got the pom-poms
so that was the practice round and now
it says this is the Homeland this is the
real round
hey
I believe I
jump on the edge of my it's gone what do
you got your money on hey
easy Aqua senpai yeah yeah
oh I'll go in the knitting
I have I have High Hopes uh of sweet
season bye as well
come on yes I believe it all I believe
in all of them yes
are we starting
is this body
I guess no okay
I'm taking the stage okay
probably picking up the items and stuff
yeah yeah yeah
logical question okay
does the Red Sea team have higher
chances to win because they have one
more participant than we have
I guess I guess so
hmm But if they explode for the Relay
meal senpa is joining us maybe someone
joins us as well for this one oh
technically and I have more chances to
win hmm
I'll ask afterwards oh nice put on that
[Music]
we'll go go go
oh no
no no I saw that oh
okay
oh my God
come on come on
the same time
[Music]
oh my
uh by the way don't give up at the end
because dying even if you last is zero
points and I think if you at least
you still get points you get three
points so no don't give up never give up
never give up yes
um
nervous I'm nervous take this
opportunity to test out the timing
okay and even if you die and be turned
into spectator mode maybe try to quickly
restart and and go in there again
because it's it during practice I think
it's okay to give it another try
[Music]
okay International Teams let's go yes
let's go
worldwide power
we are the universe
okay
yes yes I am the universe but now you
guys are all in the universe
all right
yeah pom-poms
get rid of the pom-poms I'm ready
[Music]
place the pom-poms with meat
yeah I got meat
on both hands I will put meat on both
sides yeah yes caught on this Empire
ready what are you doing here
I think I think she's cheering on us or
something
Olly is turning into a white team member
look look she's like nodding her head
like yeah yeah yeah do well yes okay oh
they're still checking who actually came
first in the Finishing Line oh yeah it
was really close that was really close I
feel like they went like at the same
time it was money sent by an aqua right
yeah
hi
okay photo finish
we got the uh video video playback video
playback the replay frame by frame
um
story
nice
MVP
we'll go to the DaRuMa Miko
I know it's so cute
yeah
like that
it's the thing that the green light
never mind
oh yeah
because somebody's so scary
Cali's like on our side and it's oh
she's out for us so we're joining us
nice yeah let's go okay all right that's
how close she is he's here push her off
no hitting no hitting that's cheating
okay
nice hit
oh starting all right I'm ready
let's go we can go as soon as we see the
words all right all right
come on come on come on come on come on
come on let's go
I mean Soul concentration mode
[Music]
oh
I just hear people punching each other
to the side
oh you're letting out their aggressions
come on come on
ready
oh
oh okay gotcha oh
wow okay I didn't see the one but okay
I'm gonna practice again because that's
three okay let's tap on two no I didn't
see three okay it literally just went
one
yeah me too yeah the same
oh
my God
almost dark here oh my God come on come
on
I'm lying don't lie to me yeah the Ping
is the pig
it's the pig it's okay oh God where am I
I'm in the void oh God
foreign
's dying
okay
if I saw someone I think so
yeah but it's close
I'm trying to survive
nice I got everyone's eyes like what how
in the world have this Pom-Pom oh the
pom-poms
I got like six pom-poms
okay is someone still going okay
why is Irish just there
I Iris oh let's let's go back
menacing Iris
you good I think she's trying to get the
eyes
one more I'll go back one more practice
one more one more practice or yeah okay
okay
oh is it what what one more time
all right okay hi Scotty Moss
I'm sorry the Ping I got chicken I get I
get steak I get carrots and all that
kind of stuff I just have something okay
I
better stop early
don't make me hit you
okay
ready
[Music]
early
all right
I gotta eat well yeah
okay
I died I died okay I should have died
three times to be honest but okay
there
School let's go
all right
while the Ping next time I'll be more
careful at the Finish Line
okay oh okay I I I responded at the
wrong place yeah yeah even happened to
me too
okay
it's okay the pink it's the pink
don't even worry about it it is
manageable you're watching
or even yourself come on
who else is who's still in who's still
in
nice nice nice
I'm just practicing okay
I get it yeah yeah all right okay timing
yeah yeah
okay got it
red
[Music]
Focus
let's do this stuck at the end oh yeah
yeah
any food
give me food
okay I'm ready there are food yes I'm
ready I'm ready okay this is the real is
the real ones okay yeah that's the real
deal now
okay okay okay
let's go okay
we're focused
I mean it's been a how much time by now
it's been like what
voice plus it's been already almost four
hours yeah some of us were here I am
with my time yeah getting close to four
hours okay
while we're doing this other people
shouldn't run into the course oh yeah
yeah all right okay
we got leaked okay
I've never been this concentrated okay
hahaha
still
oh my God
come on teams
oh okay survive
yay yeah in any case just survive please
okay yeah survive
okay
please do not revive during the ah okay
I'll wait until the end yeah yeah okay
all right okay so just stay as good so
we should be ghosts yep gotcha I
okay okay I'm ready let me go close to
the line okay
yes the stairs make me nervous from the
left side yeah I know right
we are
going on the stairs you die so be
careful what of course of course yeah
there were a couple of stairs the
Finishing Line she means
[Music]
okay all right gotcha all right let's go
hmm
okay okay okay okay okay why am I so
nervous okay let's go
whoa
thing
fog
come on come on come on come on come on
do your best girls make me proud
why
oh dangerous in the water
oh a pig
oh nice nice stopping gouda nice call
all right oh she can make it good as me
come on come on come on come on come on
foreign
[Music]
Calliope Mori
nice
all right this is what we look like now
okay
okay let's go got it okay okay
oh my god oh I died
foreign
[Music]
but you got into the perfect camera mode
let's say you did it on purpose oh yeah
that's true
I just wanted to be the best cameraman
for you guys
a dedication yeah
good good stuff good stuff
I need food all right that means now is
the the uh MVP battle or MVP pad oh I'm
ready
I guess gouda will be part of it yeah
um
yeah yeah
foreign
exciting
I think overall white there were more
white team members and like the top
three
songs
in general like in the past battles can
uh calculate
let's put white team back in the game
back in the game
I'm putting uh one thousand dollars on
gura yeah yeah
come on we've got we've got a question
pie we've got we've got we've got
coronation
[Music]
white uh team members are in the top 15
and how many red team members in the top
15. um well we'll see that oh yeah oh I
think some of them are not 100 sure
either oh
gotta wait for the official
don't jinx things no
All Stars this is the All-Stars match
everyone
um
but but we are also stories by all of us
yes yes
Sana is more than just a stardo
you know stars in the universe
I'm gonna eat breakfast after this okay
our PVP team was uh Bales and and who
um
oh
I have high hopes for you girls
I hope I can I can I can kill
yes we'll stop at least
[Laughter]
I just hope I can kill
some damage
expects the rat yeah
[Music]
hi okay hi hey
hello
this is
sorry sorry
[Music]
you know
foreign
[Music]
Victory again I see
um
even if there's again gonna be some
quick runners in this round they say
this one is final for real yeah yeah is
that just uh like the instructions they
gave just for the beginning or also
throughout some sections of like uh red
lights do they show that daruma-san is
um says or whatever throughout the match
I wasn't paying attention yeah okay yeah
so they want us to walk only when it's
green light
when they say green light yeah yeah
it's okay we just get another win easy
let's go okay
I don't blame anyone though because if
it's possible to run then why the hell
not
it is a race after all
right
I'm ready
I'm ready let's go I'm ready
uh I'm I'm nervous now I'm so confused
now I don't want to do anything wrong
mostly right
um I think they're explaining things to
the other team because I don't say that
yeah yeah
they hear they're here all good
[Music]
which way do you think is the most
efficient by the sides or in the middle
um
I think in the middle is okay because uh
when I'm on the side I have to go to
like in the middle also so which way did
you go Buddha
uh I've been on the left side the entire
time oh okay
well a kind of like middle left side
though I think not on the very left
[Laughter]
ouch
why is only alone here
good morning baby
this movie says hello to everyone wow
nice in here
what's happening
what is it what is everybody
all right all right are we starting on
this side yep
I see okay let's try and use strats why
is every JP Senpai dying what's going on
I'm bored I think
we're ready
oh
that's too early I got rid of the
daughter not white confusion
oh no
oh should I respond to early no I I
think I'm fine okay I'll watch you girls
all right
could I still in the front
oh iris is really close too
oh my God oh my God oh my God stay calm
stay calm stay calm thank you
Iris got number one
oh
[Applause]
nice
um
right here
big schools
I can see another ghost I'm ahead
[Laughter]
okay okay at least I've at least at
least finished it okay still get points
yeah yeah hi okay
it's all right okay
nice although I died I'm sorry guys it's
okay
it's
really it's really difficult with that
delay yeah it really is
ping
ish ping
clap clap clap good job white teams
[Music]
all right I'm gonna say the results we
get two and three we got two and three
right
yeah nice a manifest I think
nice nice
three
oh thank you thank you for the me thank
you
oh I
was highlight over here wow where is
everybody what
over here
telling
you know I understand I'm over here
though where are you
doing no
get that tattoo going get that to take a
wing
please all right cool
hello
I'm so tired the tire that is tiredness
is kicking in you know what's inside
nice nice nice nice nice nice nice
okay now you guys going to the final
look
I'll be watching
good luck guys I'll be watching from
here
we gonna be sleeping from here oh yeah
[Music]
voice channels oh
um
yep oh you told just wait until Nicole
yeah
foreign
[Music]
do you have the other thing
the other thing the other thing the the
what you call it the one that looks like
a face raindrop guitar ah all right all
right
[Music]
all right
let's go 15 15 players 15 players yeah
yeah
definitely gonna do well again uh-huh
I'm excited I'm excited to see this I
think this is the only thing where like
only event where everyone is competing
from all enjp and ID together
this one is my favorite so far hmm
oh wait
oh yeah
[Music]
good luck
let's go
that's always everybody
I'm just so yes
kiami are motivated we can do this
yes
chugging
I wish I bought a beer for this
oh wait no it's a sports festival never
mind um okay you shouldn't be drunk on a
sports festival
[Music]
not until the end
celebrated at the end we can celebrate
yeah yeah yeah
why not with champagne though
hey
what's up
oh man
I'm definitely gonna take a long nap
after this whole thing and throw in my
sleep Circle again
I don't have any slips schedule so
oh I have one at the end of the day
with good and Amir and um
I gotta get some sleep before that
see all right got a lot of time get a
nice nap yeah
long nap
probably
six hour is too short
I think for a nap that's a good length
but for a real sleep six hours is not
enough oh really true my sleep is yeah I
need five hours at least but you sleep
five hours usually yeah yeah if on a
good day oh my God how do you function I
don't know
caffeine
no don't do caffeine It's gotta drinks
yeah
I could probably
coffee is Babe coffee is like practice
round nice all practice round very kind
who do you have your money on
uh Aqua Empire
come first oh I fell
I just hope they don't have too much of
a disadvantage to overseas participants
here no I think they're doing quite well
why does she have a wand where'd she get
that I don't know
oh
no oh we're doing quite well
nice nice nice nice nice oh please oh
Ina is yeah pretty fun yeah and he said
I'm there right next to Ina oh
cool
let's go
myself
[Applause]
let's see if she can do it again let's
freaking go oh it's practice
what wasn't she already done she fell
out of the world now oh
well
okay
all good okay
yo that was pretty cool that was pretty
cool we need to get some hype up in here
we need to get some behind
sorry
[Music]
[Applause]
and then
sorry
oh my God
so guys yeah don't do drugs
Roger
I give you me
[Music]
I am a straight edge Idol I don't know
what your assumptions here are oh this
is enough girl I don't know what I don't
understand what you just said
foreign
[Music]
what's up
oh my God
oh my God you're dying yeah
[Music]
I think that helps our points quite a
bit it does once he finished team great
team wow that's only money left on the
course I think come on there you go
is she
is
done
no I think she's just chilling all right
oh no no I think is she stuck
she's stuck I think she's stuck
are you okay
oh yeah I think she's stuck I think
they're stuck
yeah
oh look oh
that's a mistake I heard a game bug down
don't tell me there's gonna be another
uh reply I think I think so
um
easy
oh oh she's still playing I mean I guess
it doesn't change anything because she
still has points yeah yeah
okay no replay hopefully
nice nice nice
oh no need to stress now
hey
and
[Music]
party
nicely done
one and two
very nice soon very nice
okay okay I wonder what the point
difference is now
yeah I think we can still turn the big
moment
oh
I still think we can turn this around
let's freaking go
[Music]
okay
oh amazing stuff
[Laughter]
how did it feel girls party uh
participating in in the last match
that's fun
yeah
so I mean you know you did so well in
the practice round
as well yo yeah also I also realized
when I was in the practice round I might
have been going a little bit too early
when the red light faded out so I guess
that's what they meant like uh yeah yeah
yeah
I just yeah I had to ask to clarify
again
um
I do think that it's like a ping
Advantage thing too though because they
move first since they see it first and
then we can't even move like until we
have to stop it too I thought just in
case
so maybe if I do move when if I did move
when the red is fading out it doesn't
look like it because it would have
already been green light for them
I don't know what it was but um if you
timed your damage tick right you get
boosted of all you jumped yeah I noticed
that one no I was leaping
so yeah gamer you know
just happened to see and I was like oh
yeah that's big brain though that's a
big brain that's a trick
let's put the magma blocks
are you guys ready for PVP
no all right what's your strap team
is making me not feel so good
um I think what I'm thinking is
um
you guys can go and get the ores uh-huh
and you know how you set your two
diamonds and then the one gold yep um
I'll go for the gold but I'll also kind
of see if anything targeting you guys
Safeguard okay while getting the uh so
it's like capture the flag in a sense
yeah basically uh except kind of yeah
then we gotta go like like after
everything is mine I think that's when a
lot of the killing happens yeah yeah ah
so if we just have somebody if we have
one expediter right and then the rest of
us will be attacking them so they can't
mine so you guys can go you know
him on my name yeah and then after that
I can focus on uh getting so normally I
think at the start it's like the mindset
everyone wants to mine first
um once you finish mining like your
portion and then we can start going on a
killing Rampage
to keep an eye out so at least one
person kind of stay behind on defense we
can't steal
a great detail from the house
I think everyone's getting excited for
people PVP
make sure that you steal from the
opponent's Hopper that you stand close
to it so that it doesn't fall back in
they told me oh yeah yeah
it's not like right in front of it very
close yeah
it's not gonna be a lot of steals at
once but
um you just steal one item at a time but
still it's quite you know now you have
to like keep standing there and pushing
the button yeah so you have to time it
well
it's okay I believe
you didn't practice like uh at all do
you know how it works in general I don't
know how the or game works is there like
I'm reading the instructions and there's
no Specific Instructions about it about
the orange
the or or yeah the PVP or PVP yeah so
there's there's different amounts of
like uh blocks that you can mine
throughout the map on both on your side
and on the enemy side and so you wanna
the end goal is just to have as many you
know ores mind in the upper at the end
as possible on your side it's kind of
like Capture the Flag so you have to
defend like I think they can also take
from your side as well right yeah
everything goes fine and then um just
get mine yeah kill enemy Roger don't die
gotcha yeah
foreign don't mind the obsidian is what
we were told
you see some Diamond that's around
obsidian don't mind the obsidian
there will be a waste of time every time
you when you start out when you started
in the beginning and every time you get
killed you get spawned in your base and
you gotta click a button that
automatically equips you with a helmet
and a pickaxe
yeah and meat and then yeah you can run
out so every time you gotta touch uh
that button you will see bells and Ina
will show you yes
are we going I'm so confused no I guess
I mean I already ran ran forward but
yeah why not let's go is that a
different map
it's different Maps
um close to the relay yeah
it's the one that looks like a castle
wall
all right
because the audience
the viewers
last time a couple of times okay yeah
and don't steal directly from the hopper
that's it
oh yeah yeah don't take it just out of
the hopper inventory
[Music]
let's go my team what are the scores
I'm hungry you wanna go get some food a
little hungry I'm maybe maybe
calculating
come on come on come on come on white
team come on where is it where is it
where is it
she's interviewing a white B and C oh
okay
does that mean they won
I guess
perhaps mayhaps
does that mean they want
I'm confused what's happening I think so
well they're just doing interview random
interviews oh okay okay all right oh
sorry they'll probably
um
this scares me
oh
[Music]
how was it girls
um
[Music]
announcement afterwards in a moment
coming up right now yeah
I told you girls again to take take a
break if you need if you're not
participating in PvP that is I'm gonna
watch some gameplay some gameplay
footage
foreign
[Music]
oh that's a good point too let me go
find food they're back yeah you can
watch them as well how they do it break
down the footage yes
hungry
I'll be going AFK after the
announcements oh please
oh thank you all right
oh why is everyone dying
why is everyone dying
what is going on here all right
oh they're announcing it oh
what is it what are the results please
tell a link Nene
number one both on number two Nana
number three Iris number four pickled
number five Inna number six Uncle number
seven one number eight Watson number
nine cool the number ten spanner number
eleven money number twelve hello
five six
six eight
yo yo ten six wow
Tom
we're waiting for that come on
what's the overall score
[Music]
I think I'm announced the score
I think so okay
they did so every time after a game
didn't they the day on today today
ah only for each game huh probably want
to keep the surprise until the very
that's true that's true that's true okay
all right we come back it's okay we're
we're doing only the people who can do
the true math yeah they can figure it
out I can't do that so I'm out
what what is um
what what what number is one of the
numbers what did I mean Mason no idea
okay
what
what's everyone looking at
it
day
oh thank you
it's time to go ouch kill
all right
[Music]
kill
um I also want to be with you guys
during um the PVP matches
um because I'll be I'll be joining the
the people who are playing PVP
if I hear any stress I'll pass it I'll
come back and I'll tell you guys okay
[Music]
right right
all right we've got this Predators on
the white team
okay
um on the side here
right where's The Spectator place can I
see on the side on the side
other side all right oh okay oh there we
go oh that's red team all right
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay
I am going to go make coffee okay I'll
be right back
[Music]
okay all right
okey-dokey
um I might go off soon as well into the
chat all right okay okay
[Music]
have fun I shall
foreign
I think she's studying techniques
oh okay nice
but yeah so you see the um the diamonds
in the middle I think lost some sweet
season by and I went from either side
because there will always be someone on
the other team who's also trying to get
the diamonds in the middle and so we
sandwiched them
and kill oh smart
Strat so that was the strategy we had
but I don't know it's up to you guys if
you wanna
I don't know what Strat you want to use
okay okay okay
let me have a look
oh
okay we could we still good
I got pancakes
but like a Australian wink style
pancakes like it's more like a crepe but
it's like in between a crib and a
pancake it's called Palace
oh
you say it
what how do you say it
that's a really weird name yeah yeah it
sounds cute yeah
I think in uh in Australia they say
pikelets
what hi Glitz
Pike
Pilots
I'm pretty sure that's the thing
although I'm gonna google it just to be
sure it sounds funny
Pilots
pilot cyclists
what did you say hi you say it slower
like
p-i-k-e-l-e-t-s hi Cliff maybe I'm
saying it wrong Nicholas
okay I don't know is that is that the
Australian name for a pancake like the
real Ultra no the fake that land down
under huh maybe I said it wrong oh hi
clits
Pike yeah oh I've never just inhaled a
chili flame guys you're killing me
like what are you eating
I will put some sometimes I just eat
chili flakes with my fingers you just
like tap them
all done I do I do I do I do get that
oh we're at the PVP area
[Music]
oh my God
you can't lose now we can't lose now
okay
now we gotta win we got it the mash we
gotta kill we gotta annihilate we gotta
assassinate we got a Slaughter we got a
murder
you guys know who you're going against
is it uh there's anybody more prepared
crony Iris and Rain probably ah it might
be a little tough but we got it we can
do it
yeah
mark one of us
what
destruction yeah destruction is
destruction is good it's okay okay
they're focused on me just do your best
okay okay focus on everyone else too
just focus on critics do your job no
Spanish at the end of the day and jump
in okay
at the end of the day
it's okay I'm gonna go to the voice
channels now I'll see you guys later all
right
good luck
foreign foreign
[Music]
oh
it's me yeah
we can hear the wolf cries yeah yeah
I don't know
oh okay
okay
no more Health question mark
translate oh they're talking about like
um you know they want help or if they're
low on health or things like that
we're beginning first round here we go
hi
what's this beginning
[Music]
okay okay
oh what's going on oh my God
you're going to line some more
questions
diamond
[Music]
s
[Applause]
maybe I shouldn't have the megaphone
killings
oh
my God
she is Rampage
[Music]
okay I think they're drawing back for
once and before charging it
[Music]
come on
is still mining away
oh look at her dog
[Music]
go
go third go for the
killer go for the kill uncle's hole nice
nice nice nice nice
oh my God
apparently they can't get anything from
the buttons
[Music]
take the base
oh my oh my oh my oh my oh my God
oh my God
wow
I've heard that Taurus Empire is very
strong when it comes to this kind of
stuff but I didn't realize it was that
you know
no no
no everyone says
[Music]
I just realized am I not meant to do
this
I think I read the instructions wrong
I'm gonna go back
I'm gonna go back to my own team okay
welcome back I read the instructions
wrong
oh what do you mean yeah I wasn't
supposed to go into the voice chat
[Laughter]
and I realized at the end of the game
it's okay
well welcome back I'm back it's okay
nobody had to see that I just wish them
good luck it was just I was being
um
oh wow
I need to read
how was the match
thoughts
they are
sweet I think I think we have some
people you know getting coffee or
something but yeah it's pretty sweet did
you see the Rampage by what's going on
yeah she healed lots of people yeah
there's no spy glasses in the chest I
didn't realize oh really
before
they're over here I wanna try at the
beginning it might be a lot easier to
use in the zoom button
oh yeah oh I see oh it is easier
[Music]
oh that's so much easier
oh that's so much easier oh I wish I had
this since the beginning
[Music]
okay so second team five people
okay
second time we're using
um
oh wait no no it's still the first is
we're supposed to be okay I don't know
what I'm saying anymore
[Music]
well nothing much you meant to use this
yeah the spider glass do you miss toys
yeah it's like being an absolute
predator
[Music]
what is happening
I'm missing out on this TT oh yeah
[Music]
hi we're just I just I'm just letting
her hugging my tail before that's about
it
I wonder I wonder how many of them
why does she have two enemy Flags what's
going on
that smells so nice it smells like
peanuts awesome little sharks do you
like peanuts a little shorts
nice thing
yeah yeah yeah yeah friend
we can't ignore the gold
I think peanuts for squirrels are like
really fattening I've read that
somewhere so you should give them like
macadamia nuts oh Macadamia is not my
favorite nut I like everything so nuts
game cashew
that was a very close game
yeah those issues wow oh yeah do we get
to see the points the results yeah yeah
um
oh yeah
what's up hours 111. yeah we lost my
phone okay
bring it back
Champion Squad right here because isn't
wait isn't button in the next group
yeah oh I guess get ready to see some
Apex predating man it's so she was like
telling us how to fight
she already died already I see
there isn't it I think there's some
multiplayers from the previous round
still on
no more
are they yeah
because the other one was um
[Music]
so strong
yeah she got so many kills during the
practice round
oh my God
look they're practicing the crits no oh
my God
they're killing each other
already
I love the sound of zooming in on the
Spyglass oh I do too
is there a lag when you do normal Zoom
uh like when you're moving camera soon
yeah
yeah I think it's like an effect I don't
know actually that it was probably a
setting to change it a bit it's always
the setting for Shader stuff that's true
look at that
they're mumbling in each other's ear the
strats
yes this is like oh
I was like what what am I zooming in on
oh I'm his face
cute face what's happening
are we just getting restless I think
they're probably waiting because um I
think everything on the map is being
reset like the all the oars and
um
nice
noise noise noise
and pie
go go go go go go go go go go go go go
go go go nice nice pie let's go
this Spyglass is so so helpful
it's so much better than Zoom
there's no lag when I move and follow
why is
what did I just see
oh there's fauna
uh-huh
I am now watching this to hold his tail
[Music]
yes I saw
I just loved it from lovey
is here where
no no they're like in front of me all
right oh yeah
this boat on vampire in this one because
I thought she was in the uh
uh Birdman darts thing yeah yeah she's
not she's not oh yeah yeah yeah she was
just teaching them both no I don't think
so I don't know the PVP but she was
teaching us properly
[Applause]
they look scary it's so scary look at
them
foreign
[Music]
oh interesting interesting
oh my God don't forget about the red
team one by four points
with the gold nice nice nice nice nice
nice nice oh the diamonds nice ah
so don't forget about the gold the gold
like a lot of people forget about the
gold yeah so I think one person should
go for the gold and then two people go
for the diamond
oh yeah
defense
look at these strats you offense onesies
come on come on come on come on
guys
dump your um items before you go chase
to kill yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
First Blood
oh yeah
wait she still has time to time
oh
wait where is she where she stuck
India in the Slime oh
okay okay
I misread that I thought she had typed
Sugo couldn't I and I was like yeah but
what
sounds like what oh Google good night
right
obviously nothing's working up here
restart okay
there we go we gotta we gotta look into
the you know
okay all right
nice nice nice nice
strats
we're doing a rematch restarting do you
think their strategy is good would you
like to use the same strap
[Music]
the gold uh I guess I might as well
who should go for the gold though
I mean if you go for the gold you're
pretty always to the base so
yeah it's like
uh
should we do
I'm not much of a
baby fear so
I don't know do you want to stay back in
the base like around I think um I can go
for diamonds because that's what I did
for practice and then I come back with
diamonds and then go kill
okay I just need someone with me I mean
actually how about could I go through
the cold okay in the middle okay okay
okay oh let's go
yeah so two people
oh nice nice nice
so I think for the diamond one person
starts on the left side oh and that's
like
Smarties
if you're if you're a buff it's actually
easier to hit people yeah
go away
go go go go go go go go go go go go go
go go go nice nice
[Applause]
so strong
oh nice nice nice very nice nice nice
very nice
okay now it's cute that's a good Strat
like uh yeah you have one person digging
for the diamonds one person watching the
stairs and then one person getting the
gold okay okay and then the person
High ground and attacks from above yeah
yeah yeah yeah okay I'll get the
diamonds
um someone like someone someone guards
the stairs
are they coming in for this I think you
can actually just attack them when
they're getting gold when they're about
to go down because you could you could
she left some let's do some here there's
some gold here did I see that probably
not yeah there's some gold
oh look at this that's a waste
no
oh
look
look up back look up
where where where where
there's gold there's some gold stuck on
the on the ladder
I don't see that
yeah is that bug that might be I think
so because whenever
um items float like that it's always
been bugged for me nice I wasn't blind
nice
oh
[Music]
nice
um
all right nice
don't kill
me
[Music]
this is
so close today wow I wonder if the spawn
doors could be like on a timer yeah
[Music]
you can do it
nice
MVP team
now they're free to
defense nice
how long do they have left not much
right
should be reaching the 60 seconds sooner
yeah
look at this group
groups
that was the wrong one okay okay okay
okay okay okay okay
foreign
oh
oh no
[Music]
okay okay yes it's okay it's okay okay
nice nice nice nice nice nice
this is a great match wow why does it
also feel extremely long wow
took less than 10 seconds
[Applause]
so if you take from the Enemy at the
very end even if it's not in your Hopper
at least it's not in there
I was just emptying their bank at the
very end it's nice yes
we've got it in the bag on this one yeah
definitely
yo that's the stretch yo
100 why team one
I feel like we can do that too like when
it's like 10 seconds we just start
emptying if we're on the uh near the
enemy side
we could have one person like distract
them so they can't press the button and
then like
at least one person to press buttons but
I don't think multiple people can press
the button yeah yeah true true
very smart what a match what a match
that was a great match yeah that was an
amazing match
foreign
one gold was already
in there already from the get-go
apparently oh wait but red you had a lot
of Diamonds oh my goodness
I'm confused
what's happening
was it still from the previous round
because there was like a yeah apparently
just falling down she says but it's only
one so I guess I'll just not count that
one
but red one apparently what
100 years
welp
um
[Music]
foreign
okay
okay I see I see I see
okay they're still discussing about that
one piece of gold one piece of gold
basically red one so oh
right
we got good entertainment though oh yeah
the entertainment company yeah
yeah
okay we definitely need a goalie then
of some sort
mayhaps maybe after you guys get the
diamonds um Lincoln is good at like
protecting
[Music]
confidential confidence no confidence
it's all right yeah you have a powerful
presence
you'll scare them
that's me being they're all scared yeah
I hope so I think they're focused on me
that they forget about you know what's
happening that's my hope it's also
really weird because I remember did you
see Aqua Simba at the end like madly
pressing the button but nothing came out
um somewhat unless it's also gotcha like
that
oh you pressed it and it might have just
gone like straight to her oh maybe she's
standing right there maybe maybe maybe
maybe
probably
almost like discussing that right now
about how nothing came out
I don't know what's happening
how much is each Diamond worth um so
diamonds are worth five
um gold is worth two and iron is worth
one
oh oops okay
oh yeah she was pressing the buttons and
items weren't coming out they're
discussing that right now oh yeah
are they are we trying to press the
thing I think they're trying to press
the button but
um nothing comes out rematch
wow isn't that the third time yeah
I guess it was broken somehow yeah maybe
it's okay
we'll get more top-notch entertainment
then
refilled oh I would love some popcorn
I will get some snacks
you know what's missing here a kiss cam
troll
oh no she's she's my she's um related to
me no I can't kiss her
what's happening I'm so confused
[Music]
him sometimes
they'll figure it out
here's my tail
you have a life end the day and lay down
in bed and then you cuddle your tail
oh like the killer like a bunny pillow
yeah okay it seems almost working now
but okay Haley's big and fluffy are they
doing a rematch
I think they're thinking about it oh
it was meat in the hopper okay and then
the meat messed it up apparently oh I
see I see I see I mean if it would
happen sometimes yeah
oh yeah they just wrote in Japanese
please wait we're currently uh
trying to figure it out
all right all good round three ding ding
ding ding
practice crit right
um meets brexit uh completely really oh
wow wow is that early so wow it's two
thick to be inserted
isn't it is it a hopper it's a hopper it
depends if it's a dispenser Hopper
because like Whatever item is in there
might be like dispensed differently I
guess depending on what it is I've had
that before like uh with bone meal or
yes something weird oh Minecraft Sensei
Amelia Watson none
foreign
I was making a bone meal vending machine
and I couldn't use like a dispenser I
think
oh
um because it was trying to use it on
the dirt block in front of it and so I
guess depending on the type of item it
might be trying to use it somehow I see
I see I see oh
that's so strange
the seaweed of my on my kimbap has
turned chewy
no it's very um
add another layer
it's just been sitting out
it's now a chewy
maybe someone just died on top of the
hopper and then lost their items on the
hopper and the meat uh fellas
I think so oh yeah yeah I mean somebody
died there and then yeah like that's why
I've only pressed the phone the meat
came out yeah yeah yeah
that's really a dog it's like
oh no grinder
I don't mean oh no
I'm gonna make sausages out of it oh no
Idols sausage
if I became a sausage I want to be a
trouser you already became a sausage the
other day
sausage
[Music]
I wonder if next time they can make a
sort of item store so when the meat
Falls in it goes with like a different
box
Maybe
we practice I'm so confused because I'm
so pretty I'm pretty sure people died on
top of the hopper during practice as
well but we didn't have this issue
uh I think also yeah I think also like
after the red light green light like a
lot of people picked up items that they
didn't have maybe like they just didn't
know that rule like oh you have to empty
your inventory before you play and stuff
now they know yeah oh yeah because I
don't think me would have been the
problem like I would it would make sense
if it was other items that was the
problem
mm-hmm yeah yeah yeah
what's your items guys
noise
[Music]
you're looking very cute today shark
what does that mean postmortal post
mortal what's that achievement
use a totem of undying to cheat death
where did she get that get that from
where'd she get that from probably a
random chest oh because they they uh
copied the stuff right
achievement
foreign
[Music]
oh how your pancakes Kiara oh I'm done
with them oh that was quick
yeah I was super hungry
I ordered it yesterday at really smart I
ordered dinner and I ordered dessert
with it to eat for breakfast
yo big brain
yes that's pretty big bag
yeah it's pretty big brain what's
happening you guys wanna like do you
guys have your strategy now you're gonna
copy this this team's strategy
I'm so tired I'm a little nervous how
this is gonna go
um yeah what what was the why I'm going
to be the goal gold
I'll do it Aqua do
okay is that was that was that no I'm
just asking because I know I forgot what
aqua did
oh oh oh uh she was like she got the
gold she focused the gold and the iron
okay I kind of played in the defense
until the the wrong I thought the
diamonds were grabbed yeah yeah okay you
know that unless somebody else wanted to
do that but
I don't know I'm gay for whatever
oh
yeah rematch
[Music]
a rematch I'm gonna get my snack go get
the snack
BRB
I wonder what's happening in the other
chat right now
they look like they're messing around
over there
the red team see yeah yeah let's have a
look what are they doing
they look like they're up to something
up to no good
gotta listen into their strategies
if they even have one
do you think they'll notice if I pop
into the chat
hmm it's probably would be a a pretty
actually unfair for you to join if
they're really discussing something
because I'm gonna be participating
oh they're twerking apparently it's like
this
oh God
they're fighting about the time again
traveling
something like that
spawned it all right
oh no
the time traveling strikes again
you gotta play the game again I'm gonna
play right line green line
picking up some bows and arrows
it could be a new fence
good to be here I have three I have
three hours
yeah okay I am a queen welcome back
I'm on the match I'm on the playing
field I'm not meant to be here
okay oh
I just infiltrated the red area
uh I think we're waiting at the moment
still uh because
the second team has to go again or the
second match I see yeah
I need you to do some Recon for me yep
can you find out the position of uh oral
crony nope she's uh white face white
face
yes
he's here oh she's at the stairs of
white base over oh go get it it was an
arrow oh oh nice shot
thank you nice shot he doesn't he
doesn't know what hitter
and she's oh oh crony oh where is she
going where is she going where is she
going oh she's coming back to the red
base over
I'm gonna jump to your shot over nice
don't worry I got it
nice oh it's starting
let's go
I got my eyes let's get the W this time
all right let's go oh yeah they're fast
they're fast
go go
oh no
Clements did they get the diamond I
think they did
all the diamonds I think they got the
diamonds
take it back let's say beat up them
dispenser yeah while they're fighting
someone should go get that gold yeah
we're picking up that iron and peace and
harmony
for the
uh gold
did she steal some
did she steal some okay putting an iron
very nice very nice
it's going to need something good again
oh
there's still some left I heard some
splashing oh oh nice um
[Music]
can we get a triple kill can we get a
triple kill
let's go running away nice nice tactical
Retreat all right next time oh there's a
gold here God damn it what's the reason
I got it oh no she's not a finch
oh no
okay to be honest they have uh oh oh no
nice nice
all right very nice
they act so fast I know so now it's all
about protecting right I mean stealing
mm-hmm
protect and steal
nice nice come on
she's assessing my situation
oh no no no got a steal before uh before
they come back yeah
no
not nice
[Music]
MVP Aqua Senpai wow
so nice
oh no oh it doesn't come out again go
back go back go back all right oh my god
wow oh no oh no
they noticed she's dangerous
we've known it all along dangerous
there's no iron laying around are they
just ignoring it nicely they have a
pretty big lead so they're just like
I'll just leave me yeah yeah oh no the
Gold's looking good it's not looking
good boys
[Music]
the three protecting the base now oh
God
foreign
[Music]
nice oh no he's speedy speedy speedy
speedy
come on girls
what team would go
oh wow they're really good at his
defense
you say it's like I'm looking at you
until my friend is coming
[Music]
ooh
I wonder I wonder how I wonder how much
this why do them diamond blocks 10
seconds oh they really really defensive
yeah yeah I think they have a lot yeah
yeah
all right okay
well I don't know about this one yeah
look at their best yeah they did really
well in the first one but yeah they like
knew their Strat and the team knew the
Strat Yeah by that time by the third
time it's like oh we know what you're
going for yeah
um might have needed to change your
strategy but like in that short time
difficult no
I don't know I don't know
the last second really oh you got a good
eye chat oh
nothing came out of the Hoppers yeah it
didn't seem like things were still
coming out of the Hoppers it's very
strange again
yeah I don't know
maybe it just really goes straight to
the inventory when you just don't know
this maybe it's a yeah maybe it's a pink
thing also like it just doesn't show up
properly for you yeah maybe easily
mayhaps mayhaps
MVP Aqua Senpai how many kills did she
get wow
squizzy
one two three four one two three four
five one two three four five five
five kills I think they got four uh she
got more in the previous match oh really
got one two three four five wow five not
that I got five two months no no six
actually oh my soul is a big killer too
big killer big kills
[Music]
don't worry tail will stay why is Ollie
in the map I don't know
did you see Ollie underwater
oh yeah she's there
maybe she's hiding from the valley girls
again
how how scary are the valley girls you
don't want to know not scary at all your
worst nightmare they're done when their
nail breaks so oh my God that's that's
gonna be horrible I cannot imagine
they're all stats all of their stats are
on Charisma but not an attack and
defense and all that stuff
[Music]
okay
anyways yeah thank you foreign
[Music]
and make sure you put a steak in your uh
left hand yes eat on the go oh wait nice
see
can you do a wield yeah
eating is right click kidding is left
click yeah I like this oh
you want some diamonds
no I won't actually do that
wait where's the Hat do we get a hat do
I am I wearing are you wearing it you're
wearing it yeah
um yeah
just remember to uh also deposit your
things before you go after them yes so
are we not allowed to carry any food uh
let's get five steak that's it and then
you get a steal the other people's steak
if they die
okay but if it fall with five steak
58. should have come with the thing with
the the button once you press it you
automatically get five sticks
I had 15 for some reason
probably left over yeah
all right so I'm going for the Diamond
the gold and the iron go up to the um
the white player so we can discuss our
stretch oh yeah yes see you later girls
good luck bye bye
good luck guys
all right team for my team
all right what is the
plan
uh I guess what is what we're going with
okay so with diamonds and then I'm gonna
go for gold whoever you're gonna be what
you're gonna be our sneaky sneaky
mangara
so I'm going under for iron and gold and
then whoever is going to be protecting
the Diamond Player watch watch behind
you though because that's where Matsuri
was I think it was Matsui was sneaking
up anyway yeah okay I'll go for the girl
watch my back over the gold first nice
all right noise
you can probably get a diaper in the
middle
um yeah Q2 yeah just dump stuff here
right let's go team communication okay
okay
let's go
let's go post trash let's go
10 10 kills on the board right now just
let the red teams down
red player just got done oh no oh never
mind take me to your diamonds so I can
stick one day
we're gonna make white team win no
matter what it's today I really want to
show my pickaxe in here okay
[Music]
uh my energy drink we're wore off
remember no
yeah
let's get let's get this
nice let's go I'm rabbit I'm a rabbit I
wish we could chat with the other
players yeah
wait are they even there I can't even
see them
I think they are holding on they're not
there
it's possible
I see Ollie
oh yeah I have Max render distance it
might just be a server
scooch
okay
ready it's okay
we got this I want to stand at the edge
of the box
here we go
stay calm stay calm all right and get
ready to kill
and don't die in the hopper watch your
meat ladies watch your meat
if you must perish kindly do so away
from the hopper entrance as to not give
our team any please keep her hand and
feet out of the hopper finally keep your
hands feet me yeah
okay
why am I getting nervous
oh hey what's up
earpiece
Serenity Now
mine
I've been listening to smooth jazz the
entire time oh I've been listening to
feet of my heart
oh wait my hair okay
oh my God okay we'll do this hello
is that better
are you taking a
okay
nice
foreign
[Music]
thank you
okay
got food on the left right click
hit on the left click I'm ready let's go
ready as will ever be
ready are we meant to type yes I don't
know
yeah yes already
oh
oh whoops oh
Nick it's good
I think they're going for the diamonds
too watch my back
all three
oh ping oh dear oh oh is it good okay
I'm announcing it now so you're okay
team I've got ping
yeah I think it's kind of bad
I've got
okay
did you guys die diamonds collected
okay Diamond's collected
nice nice watch okay
okay where are they oh where are they
getting the gold they're a gold okay I
got okay
I am collecting the iron
oh sweet pinkies oh
[Music]
thank you
okay we got iron Oreo nice
okay
time to get our diamonds bag get your
diamonds back diamonds back diamonds
back
hello
none of my hits are landing okay I can't
land a single hit okay okay okay
I've got two gold from crony going in
owl nothing's coming out
there's nothing coming out nothing's
coming out
what
out
pink the Ping is so bad oh my God the
pink is so bad the Ping
oh the Ping okay
hey nothing's coming out I don't see
anyone
oh I see people now okay yeah nothing's
coming out
thing is should we say something yes
there's literally nothing coming out of
the hopper how long does it take for
stuff to come out
nice
does she have anything
no okay that's so weird
huh
yeah nothing's coming out love yeah I
don't should we say something before we
have to start a match over I'll type
something okay
are we all experiencing this I don't
know yeah I pressed something and
nothing came out yeah
oh no you don't
I got a diamond you got Diamond nice
okay I'm drawing attention
foreign
nice
wait wait oh I got something okay oh
sometimes nothing comes out that's why
okay
gotcha gotcha gotcha gotcha gotcha
gotcha
wait there we go okay okay
what's our plan team Kayla's with crony
kill crony I'm about to die
Michael
[Music]
I also want to stop okay oh
the thing
are we stopping yeah I think we're meant
to stop aren't we oh
or me I don't know pronounce nothing it
says stop in the yeah
[Laughter]
just bloodthirsty the blood thirstiness
like I would assume if you press it like
something is supposed to come out
yeah I don't know
is it pink I have no idea if there's
something in there and nothing comes out
then it must be pain though I mean I
don't know I have no idea
help
okay so it works we'll Miko Senpai for
some reason okay
okay I think she changed the bucket
Maybe
foreign
going into the ground or something I
have no idea
they're checking the dispenser oh okay
okay seems like it works now
sweet okay can you kill me real quick
I don't have a weapon yeah just just hit
me oh thanks so I have time to go do
something real quick uh Maybe
maybe not
sure
[Music]
okay well while they're fixing stuff do
anything different
but they all rushed mid
I still think we should rush for uh like
at least two people for the diamonds am
I good are you back
uh ah I can be okay I'm just waiting to
see how much time I only need like five
minutes do you think I have time to go
do something real quick uh I think
they're restarting yeah you might have
to tell them all right it's okay it can
wait it's good okay
okay
full team on diamonds hmm
maybe gouda do you want to try the
diamonds I can go for gold this time
diamonds thank you
we have to be careful also I guess
I was having some really bad pain issues
with the gold it was you know doing its
Minecraft things so I I don't know
but I mean if we're if all three of us
are dealing with that then I guess it's
whoever yeah I can I can do diamonds
okay you know you got my behind I'll try
not to die this time let's go
is there a way to block in Minecraft oh
no you can't we don't have a shield for
you
just gotta Dodge and hit somehow
I don't know
okay let's just have fun do our best
that's true that's what of course of
course let's go
yeah
I think they're still figuring out yeah
they don't think didn't you just say
that it worked like fine and the um
the practice does it change anything in
the design last minute I don't know I
don't think other Hobbies look a little
bit different I will say it used to be
on top of the stairs
um not below so
I'm not sure I finished it
[Music]
foreign
for the gold okay
how was your day Ina
oh that was okay what'd you do
uh uh went to go see a movie oh my
family nice yeah then I passed out as
soon as I got home outside is tired
oh wait no good at doing something
no I'm still here I didn't leave because
I don't wanna oh okay what to do today
oh I've just been awake for a very long
time
nothing I want to talk about I guess but
I've just been awake for a while so okay
yeah I want cake though I heard uh yeah
I want cake I want cake
I want fancy cake what's your favorite
cake
anything chocolate day
strawberries
okay
[Music]
we go for the center Diamond I'm not
doing it okay I'm good I got the gold oh
my God I think I was lagging for a
second okay oh I'm lagging too oh wow
foreign
delectable
oh nicely we have five diamonds
Brian you know I got 14 help me guard me
guard me okay okay okay okay well we
only have diamonds in our oh then
too sorry yeah that's me I just swung at
you in my bed okay all right now don't
oh they're coming
I got it I got it I got the base I got
the base
I got the base
dude this pain is impossible to go again
oh my God I thought I remember oh my God
I'm getting double tape help
no
okay nice nice nice nice nice
I'm coming I'm coming I'm coming
nice bro
okay I got I'm dumping the stuff first
we have our diamonds
okay I got one Diamond Back
oh I'm gonna die yeah
[Music]
oh I died Iris I saw that
is
sorry
whoa this okay the lag is oh nice
oh wow the light got really bad rain is
dead
as well
whoa what's happening hold on
you know what is happening what is
happening wow
iris is almost dead I need I need to get
irony
at least once come on
oh wow
nice
who's next
I just killed myself
oh yo
nice
iris is coming back okay protect the
base I'm mining some ore
no this is nice on the ground
nobody come nobody hit me
okay Reina is here okay
I got you um
I'm so sorry
oh wow
okay they're coming back
foreign
left side to distract
okay
wow team
come back here Steve
oh yeah I distracted arena for a bit
she might be going for a base
yes okay
I can't catch up to that anyway I have
one of their diamonds as well so now we
just want to beat the crap out of their
uh
yeah if we can do that if that's allowed
I don't know
try push push push push push if you can
push the crony is coming to our base
okay defending oh defending defend
defend defend
okay Smack That Thing bae
because they're all on this side yep
I'm smacking I'm smacking I'm smacking
tell me when if someone's heading my way
crony's coming back but she's dead nice
laughs
iris is almost dead I think okay I'm
coming back
you're gonna see it ow I got some warm
dumping I got a lot I'm dumping oh 10
seconds I have diamonds come on come on
come on come on
well ding
oh it's okay okay
[Music]
I have golden iron and my inventory I
should have jumped it's okay okay I got
some gold too oh my God I had like six
diamonds floating
that last loot was very satisfying I
will say
that's good thank you
[Music]
wait they have no time
that's good for us right yes it's very I
think the very start was very good where
I stole iris is like 13 diamonds
nice game changing
oh
Gary
parts are racing
oops
um
do you think you guys I don't know
I did empty quite a lot I will say but I
don't know well I don't know I don't
know I don't know I hope it was enough
I feel like most people that are like
when I killed them they either had
nothing or just gold yeah
um
I'm proud of us Steve I'm proud of teams
with that last we do very well
sneaky sneaky yes I was the sneaky
sneaky
whoa
let's go
oh yes
[Music]
166. oh
huge guys
Philippines
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
this is
thank you
[Music]
bye bye bye bye
hi okay let's move back to the other one
I suppose
yes okay
hello
MVP coming in clutch
can we get a comment from you
um really is a teamwork a team effort I
couldn't have gone sneaky sneaky if gura
and Hina wasn't you know drawing the
attention away so thank you team it was
nice that was really cool to watch
because you were stealing so much for
quite a while and then films and I think
Iris ran out of their bed
they didn't notice you at all unless you
bloodthirsty
camouflage camouflage
so nice
you're getting your cheese
save the freaking day we got it no
worries now it's time for replay
it feels like you balanced out all of
the of the previous matches it feels
like you balanced it out I mean I don't
know the like numbers wise who knows you
think by the way we gotta go up to the
tree house the tree platform
keep running
ah wow wow
for you
oh yeah
how do you go up there oh oh there yeah
there's a water elevator yeah
so wait uh what is the um
what is the oh that
that's so cute
oh
yeah
without what's the order of the relay
[Music]
um
an updated PNG meal goes first
uh it is
hold on guys I'm gonna I gotta I gotta
go to a meeting real quick I'll be right
back yeah okay
do we start up here do we just come down
here when it's like
when it's C team then we wait on the
ground okay I'm thinking we're on the
top
yeah
to make some space for the other teams
that are running
Donald from what just happened
how much points are the the really horse
I think
no no I didn't either there's so many
like so much information everywhere and
I can't I can't
[Music]
um
I may have messed with the water
elevator by accident
[Music]
I tried to put it on top of the water
everyone's stuff
not able to go up we need one more uh
one more water block at the top
[Laughter]
fish them out there or uh yeah
traffic jam
why are there so many people stuck sorry
how did you how did you break it I'm
back what's happening I tried to put a
honey block over it like uh shipped onto
the water but it just put it in the
water
oh yeah
one block right here and they can jump
out wait what happening I'm looking for
here it hey man I mean it might
have broken the Nevada elevator no
people are stuck and it's cute I just
broke a block here oh yeah yeah
come from
is it fixed
yeah
solution I'm looking for for what I'm
gonna go mining okay it's okay it's okay
it's fine now
how do you go down they almost a bit
dangerous oh there's a there's a you
just dropped off oh my gosh okay
so team a red and team a white
oh okay
okay we are just waiting at the top oh
do we have any strats for the Relay race
I heard something from uh I thought I'd
still be your best but I saw it I think
I'm a a big clip
and I was watching that on my clip this
morning
um you know the uh someone mentioned
that Ina was you know going through this
and then was like finding places where
it like accelerates you and then I mean
it was like that's cheating but then the
subscribers you're like she's on your
team you know no that's really smart I
don't I didn't think yeah
what what's accelerating
um oh and the relay relay yeah the
question mark over there question mark
yeah there's there's random blocks that
like slow you down right so I think some
of them are honey blocks some of them
are different blocks
you can walk over without being slow saw
them you will be slowed like if you uh I
would do stuff and yeah
in the in the red light green light I
think I realized that jumping over the
honey is kind of useless you just want
to control and walk over it yeah
control walk over don't jump on it
all right
um and then the other one oh I forgotten
you it I knew it
I didn't die
[Music]
I'm making a bucket right now guys I was
like oh someone's like the face is open
someone's gonna fall and die
oh my God
I'm in the red light green line oh
boy oh yeah
right right oh really the king
James
[Applause]
I did do that one but
dropped a lot of stuff she has a lot of
diamond blocks
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay what's the other parts of the relay
race you've got the I got the Looney pad
thing
yeah yeah yeah okay if you're behind
someone be careful that um the leaf had
three tracks yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
watch out if someone's in front of you I
don't wanna starting soon starting soon
oh hello
oh I just burped sorry
um okay so we gotta literally pass the
question mark
and the oh the honey blocks so do you
just walk through the honey blocks
control just and run through it don't
run through it don't jump okay gotcha
gotcha gotcha gotcha okay
and punch when when someone when you
pass through someone yes always touch
yes all right there's not much more to
this give your teammates a supportive
pat on the back on the ball hunt yes oh
yes that too
pat on the back you're gonna slap on the
butt Morris
yeah
it's kind of bad defenses
[Music]
oh yeah hug the inside corner yeah go go
inside Corners yes yes yes oh nice
Big Lean she's calling for them
very nice
question mark oh
oh
you have to run over there
yeah yeah oh
nice
nice oh nice nice
team leading nice nice nice put those
corners
it's beginning to
English quite quick okay on the outside
yeah
nice
[Music]
foreign
come on
easy win easy
wow sweet okay so where do they go in
the honey Bowl okay so jump okay nice to
jump on the outside yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
so hug me outer Corners yeah hug me out
of the corner pads oh yeah yeah nice
nice nice
[Music]
jump jump
it's okay
yeah
for all of you girls please run while
jumping nice
[Music]
so it is on the right side okay good
nice very nice sorry
[Applause]
[Music]
look at that speed
[Applause]
I think you can jump from the stone to
the other Stone you might just
fire yeah
the other side
stretch posture check everyone
my sister posture
got a stretch to warm up
and time
after that only super December left
let's freaking go no that looks like
easy win
nice
look at that
[Music]
oh I have I have this eyeglass
I forgot about it
nice okay
[Music]
speed please
yeah
nice
how about the very edge
for that one I don't know it looks just
around the right looks like a second
yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
nice nice
me
nice soon easy win nice Wow meow Simba
really set like a big big gap yeah and
guess what she's starting for us too hey
that's cool
yeah it's freaking gold
she runs like the wind yes
she's so fast
who unmasked you
have water
no I know who won last year
I don't remember no I don't know
um
let's see if Cat Knows chat chat chat
red team one oh red team won last year I
see I see balance out the scales
oh I see I see
a red team won last year well you're
seriously come back well it's time for
time for change it's time yeah change
you know
time to stop from a blank canvas what
oh wait oh I'm not going yet all right
next up baby
[Music]
oh that's strong lineup yeah
It's Crazy Ones Speedy boys
okay they're preparing let's go correct
time let's go
I'm not gonna lie my arm kind of hurts
my camera around too much
is there am I using poor technique to
play Minecraft
I just use C with OptiFine ah do you do
you have a spyglass
um no I'm using Zoom
oh here oh no no it's not my it's my
it's my um my wrist hurts like from
using the mouth uh arm pad maybe you
need one of those Mouse pets at the
movies yeah
well I've got many to choose from
anyway you have to make some merch
it's not even functional because the
planets are just like bumps in the
middle of the Mask
is it really a mouse cut at that point
who knows okay who's starting
okay that's a lot easier
three two one
go
sh
Zoom is easier
[Music]
nice
sweet
it looks like it's the oh I can't tell
because now it looks like she's sleeping
stepping on the really right one
question mark
let me stop in between them
[Laughter]
golden diamond for the wings nice
[Music]
maybe don't think too much about it yeah
just just go on
Twitter
[Music]
she can double jump on the blocks that's
good but if you get stuck just walk yeah
nice nice nice nice nice nicer
foreign
we're still good
it doesn't look like it's the right one
I'm so confused okay
Anyway come on let's go
surprise
nice nice nice nice nice oh nice oh nice
oh nice nice
touching up it's okay
thank you
wow let's begin
nice easy easy easy oh sweet I
think
everyone's wearing pom-poms now yeah
they're lifting while they're running
they got those lips in their hands they
wanna okay
[Music]
come on
whoa I'm getting dizzy with all these
turns yeah me too
all right
[Music]
okay
easy nice
[Music]
it's so cute
so cute
oh I fell down and got one heart left oh
be careful
nice nice nice nice nice nice
[Music]
yes
this looks really good beautiful
oh it's our turn
look it's our turning deep
oh I'm holding us
[Laughter]
keep an eye out on who runs before you
know so you don't miss your turn okie
dokie
um I want to get rid of my stuff though
is there a box
does everyone know when they're running
um
[Music]
I'll send it again okay
we on the inside of the outside block
outside
yeah yeah
okay pom-poms
I want a Pom-Pom I got Diamonds oh your
diamonds I want
thank you
um from I went because I went to go look
for a bucket but I have one extra
Diamond if you want an extra time it's
all food
it's all food here
Bay
whoa thank you
sometimes and stuff are over here in
these chests where that's another blue
one so we just went uh yeah there's no
one blue one is there any white ones um
okay
but why but okay what was it
next if if red team Red's team wins next
they're gonna give us the same amount of
points okay
um
I don't know how that works
let's not make them win yeah
yeah we got this
all right
thank you
nice for us I guess no meals new simple
first all right does she remember that
she's first
I think let's go let's go
okay all right
say bye
[Music]
there we go there we go there we go
foreign huh
[Applause]
[Music]
let's go
guys on our side guys
[Laughter]
I'm ready I got my I got my diamond and
my white Pom-Pom I'm ready
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
hi
no control confidence
[Music]
okay
huh
yes
[Applause]
[Music]
is
it yes next next
time
[Music]
yeah okay
it's okay
we got it we got it we got it we got it
we got it okay okay
yes come on
let's go Watson let's go Watson go um
[Music]
oh I gotta stand there then yeah
is nicer what's so nice
[Music]
I believe in you we can't do it okay
it's okay it's
all right
[Music]
now okay okay yeah yeah
all right I'll stand here
I'm done
we got it
[Music]
get in position MVP
go go
down marry me
[Music]
after this
girl
baby that you have eaten food Bay oh yes
let's go
[Music]
away
thank you
oh my God
why am I such a looking cool
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
come on
here
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm shaking I'm shaking yeah
I wish I ate before I went I'm so sorry
I'm following them so yeah it was
awesome
[Music]
good job
for everyone that was really well done
[Music]
I feel like I ran a real Marathon yeah
me too
suddenly like when I was on track I I
personally cannot hear anybody like oh
my God
oh seriously where's your tail
okay
thank you
my cat is stuck in a bag
[Laughter]
all right
wait but now what happens because it's a
China
I think so
um is it time now foreign
I wonder what's gonna happen yeah they
did already warn us about this outcome
[Music]
why why
are they cry I think they're so touched
that it's only a great successful
[Music]
yeah let's go with that I'm fine
oh they're crying that's so cute
[Music]
foreign
oh my God that was so intense
[Music]
candles
thank you
[Music]
hi
foreign
[Music]
oh my God you can't hear anyone
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
having lots of fun from now on
okay
[Music]
photo
yeah
hi you're taking a photo now
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you
yes
um
[Music]
beautiful party foreign
come on
[Music]
hi
um
I don't know
[Music]
thank you
you're gonna end the stream here thank
you
[Music]
guys
thank you
[Music]
hi
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
foreign