[Music]
hello
everyone
[Music]
[Laughing]
yeah no intro Legend
[
Music] [Music] [
Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [
Applause]
[Music]
about wih
try to
you
[Music  ]
there are so many companies that want to
and
okay
[Music]
I think I'm from of the please
and and let's
[Music]
hello
introduce
me My name is
from from  Academy
nickname
[Music]
[Laughs]
OK, the
nickname is
OK, so
yes, yes,
nice to meet you, this, this, this,
I, I'll just give you my CV,
OK, So this is my CV, I'll
drop it too in the inside.
You buy it? Yes, it's okay, it's okay, the
house looks really breathable. Ma'am, it's
written there, I'm calm, I'm calm,
everyone's really cool, so I
thought I thought it
would be bad, but instead it's really pretty,
so
oh, okay, okay, okay, okay, I saw this
from the email earlier.  Sis, he said he wanted to
go into design,
right? Oh, I can't see, this was in
2020 until now, he said he was in modeling, yes,
that's right. Is
there something in the card, oh, what's that,
his heart is suddenly interested? I want to
design like that,
I've made several
designs before, but  Unfortunately, the portfolio is
lost, but if I'm not mistaken,
it's there, wait a minute, if I'm not
mistaken, where is the portfolio that I made
? OK, let's try looking for it first,
Sis, I'll see
what else there is, Manager. Uh, there's this furna. This is
one of my portfolios.  what I
made eee where did I make the character design
eh maybe it could be eee
help eee preferences yes Yes OK so
I could be really interested in the
potatoes in that photo right
now huh Nowadays
today's kids Oh what is this potato what is a
potato  Is this what it describes? Is it
true that I just want to be a potato because I just want to do that? Yes, that's right,
so I can make money because being a model
isn't enough, so I have to have
another job, OK? So
what then? Why, because you guys aren't
enough? Is it?  there is hope if,
for example, it has been accepted by us,
for example, for example, how much do you want,
what is provided, what is provided? Just say that
you want
strong internet, yes,
strong internet, maybe at least
for money, food
or
transportation, at least hmm, at least 1
million.  That's how it goes, my expectations
are eee the salary is eee above the minimum wage,
oh okay OK,
okay, okay, maybe I'm
curious, why do we
really want to,
just want to or want to meet, I really
want to meet you, actually, yes, I see,
yes, but it's a shame, Sis.  I'm
on the
side of designing again, we are now
very, very good, yes, very good
and I also see that
maybe there might be another
position at another agency, Sis, it's a shame
[Music] I
've tried, if that's the case, I
'll take the CV and  but but sis,
I have this one, there is
another proposal, one more, it's
a shame you're not accepted at
our company, we, I was, I was one
more, do you want to design the
future with me,
OK, ready, sis, wait a minute, I'll look for
it. This is my pen.
There's a number.  call
[Music]
Thank you Ma'am
bye bye Ma'am yes bye bye
Thank you
[Music]
Oh my God
How is this I
think the account is lost
I think Wait a minute So it
looks like it
seems like this is over we have to
look for another one we have to try
the others are okay okay then
let's try another place
[Laughs]
how is he here let's go
[Applause]
Hi my name is other's
you
with Yes I want to be a police
s is a
bad ghost I want to be a  police This is my
rest to me
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
become Polri Softex
I can cake people
ofokay
[Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Laughter] [Music]
[  Music]
[Music]
let's go to the other let's let's go to
the other yes
okay
[Music]
maybe you guys
[Music] [
Laughs] [Music
]
[Music]
hello hello
[Laughs]  let
me introduce myself,
so I want to
register if there is a job vacancy.
Is there a job vacancy? I
haven't asked for the name. I was immediately given the
name. That's my real name
[Music]
my name is Munaroh.
I almost immediately rejected it because it's
Secret. If you want to register to be a Secret
Agent, right? Yes, you have to use a code name.  Yes,
my name is my name, my name is Munaroh, nice to
meet
me, I have a CV to
introduce myself, do you
need it or don't need it,
this is the actual name Munaroh, this is
the name Munaroh, no, no, not
munachinobi, yes, just this, just this, I changed my
name many times, right?  Become a
Secret Agent, OK?
Oh okay, okay,
okay, okay, I'm going to sell this,
right? I'm selling something
[Music]
or cardboard, two cardboard boxes. Yes,
where did the agent hear that we were going to
sell cardboard?
Who knows, because the agent
that information,
maybe that's not it, then this is the agent What's
not this, this is this, this is the agent, this is the
cool agent like on TV, you know, like
James Bond, like that,
I'm looking at
this CV, you know, for example, I
only need 5 criteria, if for example
registering to become an agent, yes,
first of all you need
communication skills like that, right? Well,
I can, I can, I can talk,
communication, okay, okay, I can talk
like that, like I can, I think there are
real resources, I think Yes, I
have Rich skills, research ee
like like
Build build a lot of Project by looking
remember Someone Like reasons right,
actually But
[Music]
we look at other people's work so we
use it as a reference Yes, right? That's right,
don't be happy, there's still more
OK, communication research, what is this, physical
endurance, Ouch, what is that?  physical
endurance Of course you have to be able to
walk a lot,
manage to do catwork with a cat,
that's one of my strengths,
I can beat a cat
[Music]
but it doesn't get tired easily,
right? Unless the cat runs, then it gets tired,
so the job depends on the conditions
the cat
OK OK then that's it OK OK
What's more, in the Season making skill you
can make it in the Season itself. What's this?
Always Looking for you skills
and then forget about reviews
[Music]
because I have it, I
easily forget it, my brain, it's just that
just like that. So, for example, it's
like RAM if you put one in and one comes out,
but once you put one in
straight away, wow, it doesn't work
together.
Okay, if that's the case, here's the
last question. He said he had
bought
groceries at a Japanese combini.
So, what is this?  What do I use to disguise myself? Ah
I disguise myself so
Japanese people get lost so I can Yes so
I disguise myself as a Japanese person
speaking in Japanese pretending to
speak Japanese in combination
[Music]
pretending
Oh good
it seems  It seems like there are a lot of
incidents where it
seems like you almost succeeded but failed.
Yes, that's right
[Music]
What do
you think? Yes, it
seems like maybe being an agent isn't
suitable. But if you sell meatballs, you can do it,
oh my, the one
with the meatballs. I ate it.
There's a job recommendation.  No,
I can't go, I'm tired, I'm just
looking at LinkedIn,
in my opinion, if I look at the CV,
I don't think it's necessary, just stay at home,
OK, that's it, if that's the case, I'll
try to find it myself, if it's
something like that, okay?  OK, thank you,
thank you, Munaroh. Yes,
thank you
[Music]
How come it's so hard
to find? It
seems like what should we do to find something
that suits Mona, I
think, but it seems like there's someone who
suits Mona.
According to Mosquito's CV, it looks like
Mona is suitable.  so what do you do Mona try
So go to college yeah
[Music]
but before that
how about that,
that's all, that's all
[Music]
okay
we are
[Music]
excuse me, it's
such a mess ah
[Music]
good evening
good evening, what's the matter,
so I want to  I want to ask for a
job. Is there a job that
I can do?
I've seen it well. I've seen it. There's Indonesian
Advanced. That's what it means. I
can speak Indonesian fluently. Oh I
see. Can
I speak English like a
junior high school student?
Oh I see. That's what elementary means, right?
OK,
then I want to hear an introduction
in English.
[Music]
What does all that mean?
Yes, I can't speak English. Yes, the
point is, the point is, I can do anything,
I can do anything, I can work, work,
work, don't be a typo.
Oh, I see, that means  More or less, I already
know the idea of ​​what I'm going to do there, right?
[Music]
I see, there's an experience in
becoming a comedian in the universe,
what does that mean?
This is just an experience of becoming a comedian in
the universe, so I happen to have a lot of
comedian friends, right?  So I
learned a lot so I I know
certain jokes like that.
Oh I see.
If that's how it has to do with working
in a factory, right? Working in a factory, yes,
that's what it means. Oh, what do you mean
if, for example, the machine wo
n't start because it's sad, like that?  You can
become a comedian so that the machine can
laugh again and work more
correctly. Yes, that's right, so
I
can be enthusiastic.
Yes,
actually,
what is this? Always looking for powder new skills
and then forgetting about the private skills.
What do you mean by that, I can't
speak English, for example, like this, I,
I eee want to learn how to make weapons,
right? Well, before that I was a
comedian. Well, so I am  I'm not a
comedian anymore but I became a
Webtoon maker, like that, because of my skills and then I
lost that, for example Oh I see.
So that means staying focused on what you're
doing now but forgetting what's in the
past, that's
good, that's good, I like that. So if
you do it later, for example, because you're already working
here
you mean you immediately forget everything
that happened here so you can't
tell it to anyone else that's good, that's good, I
like that, that's
what you mean, that's very suitable, that's
two points,
I want to look again, yes, the answer, I'll
look again,
here I am.  See where to get lapis
lazuli, what is lapis lazuli? Yes, this is the
first time I've heard that it's a coincidence
that you've run out of lazuli, that's a stone, right? Well,
if for example we become blacksmic,
make sure we need a lot of stones, like that,
rock, iron, gold, like that, right? Well, I,
I  I've found lapis before.
Oh, I see. So, for example, if you work
here, you can bring the lapis lazuli
here, yes. That's more or less
possible, yes, that's right, just bring it.
Oh, I see, then I like it,
so far, I like it, I like it,
I can try it
That's it, Tom, I'll explain it. So firstly, you
can make a machine laugh and make the mood
happy.
Second, you can't be a
spy. I don't like it if
someone can be a spy at
my place of work because then you
won't work anymore.  So
thirdly, you can bring new stones, which
I have been working for thousands of years,
I don't
know, it's really good,
so do you want to work here? I
wonder how much the salary is, right?
[Music] the
salary is paid here.
how many items are printed
a day So if you work, the
results are good, you get more
money, right? What are you saying, what are you,
hard worker? Yes, you are a hard worker,
aren't you? Excuse me, I think I
have a call, thank
you, thank you
[Music]
wait a minute  This interview is actually
not finished yet. Please, please come
back here first, sir. I'm not.
I'm not being paid. What are you doing? I'm working
here.
I'll be able to pay whatever you want
later. Actually,
how much do you ask? I can give you. Don't worry, don't be
afraid,
but I  I want to ask the last question.
I saw on Twitter that
Munaho Nova has a lot of followers.
I want to refuse because he has
a lot of followers
[Music]
because here it's only for people
who are No Life,
but I'm No Life, how come
I can't accept people who  there
are a lot of followers, thank you, please
exit over there,
thank you for trying
[Music]
this is the
working period, it's like that, it's really bad, it's
really bad,
okay then,
let's go back first How come
I'm lost,
oh, here it is
[Music]
Yes, never mind, it's
really hard to find  work, guys,
how about it
[Music]
so that's it, Muna, I want to
tell you something, let me know something, right?
Muna, I've been looking for
work for a while, but I can't find it, I
can't find it. What if Mona sells
first, Mona?  selling sales first
Yes, who knows, maybe it can be made for
today's meal like that Yes, never mind, let's sell
sales for a while, yes, sell first,
is this going to be on the street this time,
Muna is there Wow,
special item voice search anniversary
set complete anniversary,
get stickers from illustrations by
[Music  ]
[Laughs]
[Music]
There's a backpack, there's a kitchen.
What else is there,
wow, there's a lot of rubber matte,
there's also accompaniment, so the accompaniment will
be very similar to the one in this MV,
so you can buy it.  This match starts
from April 11 at 9 pm, the staff is at 9
pm and continues until July 24, then there
will also be a voice call. The age is
familiar
but don't laugh if you can
buy it, don't laugh at Muna,
okay, okay,
WIB WIB WIB
[Music]
more or less  That's it, friends,
this is crazy, I wonder if
this match can make Monas live
at least one day Wow, because Wow, it's
really hard to find that job. Fine,
fine
key, guys
[Music] [Music] [
Music]
[Music]
[  Music]
I hope I can I can I can see
I can get another [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music
] hello [Music] [Music]
Batman [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music]
[Music] [Applause] [Music
] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Laughter] [Music] [Music]
[Music]
[Music] [Music]
can I help
me through the speaker I'm sorry, what
can I help you with? Is looking for borax
for the bathroom borax for
weed or rice what is it for today I
want to apply
Alah's job is not a customer anyway Ah Tell
Mas Hendrina Sir if I pay it in
half first the debt is scary and the people are getting
different and every day they are surprised atuh
[Music]
I want to apply,
look at this, here, bring your CV
Wow, there's a TV, wait a minute, don't read it first  Don't
read first okay there is Oh experience present
there is candy okay There is education too Oh okay okay okay
okay okay indeed
you came to the borax shop Really
want to be a borax seller who knows maybe you
can make something toxic
Don't think that you
don't know much
but Yes  but I think borax is
interesting, isn't
it interesting?
I don't know
what part of it is interesting.
[Music] the
part that can make people die
[Music]
You might be a cereal killer, how do
you know?
Take off my disguise first, OK?
[Music]
Oh my God, you
can do that  So you're not the one
who uses borax to make slime
but to kill them,
maybe that's more or less
like that,
so you really like to fail
someone's kidneys with borax,
that's more or less
your own lungs with the
very strong smell of borax, maybe you
could say  That's it. Do your eyes
water when you see borax?
Maybe it's
a coincidence. Wait for me. I want to
ask because there is something strange
in this CV. Is it written
[Music]
Yes, I
can hold a lot of money, but I
lost a lot of money
and I'm not responsible. Coincidentally,
I'm there.  Special seats are for
employees like you,
so I'm accepted. It's
true that for every kidney
you lose you get as much as
the minimum wage, but times 8
[Music]
Is this how you will become
permanent employees?
[Applause]
Say it all together  first with me Come on
borax okay
thank you Wow thank you
I made a special song because I was
accepted at this borax place oh where
I want to hear it Wow so I
will Premiere the song
will Premiere the song for
everyone's ears
for borax toxicity it means
heavy I can't wait to hear it
When  you will sing it at 9 o'clock
wow Then let's listen I
want to move straight to
[Music]
thank you
So who is toxic is you
borax
[Laughs]
while watching you can
start work tomorrow okay
[Music]
what are you doing with the song
[Music  ]
[Laughs]
[Music]
we'll show it,
so here's
the song, it's
been there since yesterday, mona,
mona let the membership know how else to
prepare something like that, right? Well, this time the
lyrics were made by Arina
Epiphania and Arinadi with the song  which
was made by Mas Hari Renaldi
and this will be released tonight on
Spotify on Apple Music
Zero in your day and your place finger
place yes
[Music]
and also don't forget to buy the match,
guys, the match is already ready  There's a
mark, you can buy it now, you
can buy it anywhere, yeah
[Music]
yeah, yeah,
ready to do this, do you know what fun
fact it is, fanfect, that's all
the movements, isn't it?
like that,
Sis, Nauru is being cleaned, so
Wow, it's really, really true. So you're
dancing like that, you
keep on
[Laughing]
[Music]
[Laughing] [
Music] [
Music] [Music] [Music] [Music]
that's it  How many times have the lyrics been revised?
[Music]
because of borax, yes, because of borax,
then this, yes, for you, you don't
know, this song was written by Teteh
Arina, do you know Teteh Arina who
Teteh is
[Music]
singer in  Moka guys
for the song, thank you, thank you
[Music]
Thank you Thank you
later
[Music]
it's in the description,
actually
there's some of it, actually there's some of it too
[Music]
MLM is in the instrumental, guys, yes,
someone who's in it  the description
is the
background of the background voice, whoever it
is
[Music]
thank you so much
I'm surprised that usually you like to give
information if you want something else for fun Yes, I
don't want to  give me all the information because
this is in line with the job registration roleplay route.
Yes, it's already included in the script, guys. It's
already included in the script, guys,
so the concept is deliberately different, deliberately
surprising
[Music]
yes, yes, thank you so much everyone thank
you so much
description and
Please
the song  the song
intense Open music spotify
[Music]
don't forget to buy matc guys and
don't forget to play the song Thank
you Thank you Thank you my
[Music]