[Music]
by hello
made it hello hello
helloe wow wow all right thank you guys
for joining my the valve collab Marathon
thank you for play
[Music]
you a lot of you guys are new to the
game right oh yeah yeah I never played
before yeah we're going learn a
tutorial you don't need it
easy we skip the tutorial yeah we'll
skip a skip
[Music]
a all right I don't know if we need
introductions there's a lot of us here
so that might take like five or 10
minutes but just maybe for audio check
for the
Valentin all right fine all right we'll
go down the Discord list I'll go first
hello everybody I'm ailia Watson a
number one detective from Hall life
English Miss
[Applause]
[Music]
hello
everyone Harward and leader of Justice
I'm
[Applause]
[Music]
elizabe there's here
hello I'm I guess hello it's different
on my list
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
so
[Music]
[Applause]
good from H life English promise nice to
meet you all
[Music]
sorry I couldn't
tell it's
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay waa here I'm going to play Pyro
a fire good to know got a fire today
yeah oh yeah
true all right so we are going to split
up into different teams uh I I randomly
what oh what nothing so it just killed
me wait how am I dead why am I not why
am I looking at people I think someone's
cheating
what anyway you can cheat in this game
no no you can't you
can't are are we starting my phone yeah
yeah yeah okay if you're on Blue Team
we'll
go okay okay and then it's capture the
yeah any
questions somebody kill us where's the
flag should we all go
together let's the
bridge the bridge bridge no I want to be
a red team come on yes
I don't trust the robot I think he'll
kill us no fighting oh no it's okay no
fighting to die wait so blue team wait
so red team stays here or no no red team
and blue team everybody go to the bridge
just go inside the middle yeah outside
in the middle wait where's the bridge
okay it's yeah just find your way
outside I'm out
this all right maybe I can destroy my oh
that's GG oh
crap try
it I think we should just start start
just kill them just kill them okay let's
go
on I'll he you is this working thank you
I thought we
fire get out of here that's cool I like
that guys never fear ena's
here are you healed
yet I'm
okay I think
I'm I'll heal everybody else then you
healing oh my gosh
I'll you I'll kill
you we we're going to die we going die
kill kill keep running keep running I
killed you oh it's not easy to kill
somebody as medic
did oh there you are all right so we
have to try to sneak into their base and
in the basement of their base there's
like a a suitcase
SP I
stand who was
that I'm heing I think everybody's
healed no no they aren't nice I don't
think the other team has a medic do
they though
yeah
yeah you guys G I will heal you
yeah on Fire's on fire okay all right
I'm going into the base do this so we go
together let's go Fus
up the brid go the bridge go to the
bridge go to the bridge the bridge is
dangerous oh my God danger let's go
inside I'll show you guys get the Bas
yeah yeah I heal you get ready for gun
all right oh thank you for the he so the
we got to kill this guy we got to kill
this
guy I'm healing this is the
G's in our base there's SP in our
base all right CeCe come with me wait
wait wait going I'm going to grab the
I'm
going we won respawn 7 Seconds okay I'll
be back we won we got B A I thought we
won the one guy oh it's shorty shorty is
still here by the way have Tak their
intelligence I'll heal you is our is our
briefcase okay is that our briefcase in
their building right now no I I'm taking
their briefcase
[Music]
wait where
everyone together I dropped their
briefcase like in the top floor and it
has a cool down if you guys go up there
okay top Flor you could grab it what
button do you use to grab stuff uh it
should just pick up automatically yeah
you guys if you go St
heavy it looks like P nice try nice try
there everybody sit down I'll heal you
let's regroup cuz they're they're all
there waiting for I killed somebody good
job I saw
it
fire the fire just stay on normal jump
in the water jump in the water water
heal he it's down here yeah yeah yeah if
you're on fire the water will
help there's also a secret tunnel down
there to go into their base
found it okay let's go anyone's down
down in the tunnel I can hear you I
think went down there right oh yeah I'm
in that I'll go with you I'm with you so
sorry I I misund do we do we do we have
their flag or should we go get it uh I
had it but it went back to their base
yeah it's like in the basement in the
basement healing oh thank you I killed
him oh they got our intelligence okay
I'm going to go back
to
defend okay
oh it's the little square that's oh it's
the little blue
square yeah yeah yeah you can see it
through the map I'm going I'm going I'm
stay behind you just in Cas I have the I
have
the they're in the water underneath the
tunnel they're
going going the
tunnel see them in the tunnel kill them
kill them I'm so confused which way to
go
[Applause]
get a weapon I don't know where to put
it where do I put it got them so
slow make sure you get a weapon if you
see an enemy can't them get a weapon I
have the weapons yeah you have other
ones though you got
this wa wait where do we take the
intelligence is it back to the basement
do I take it back I oh we did it good
it intelligence was captured oh yeah
they got our let try to catch up go go
go go help one one one one yeah I'm try
to heal you shoot oh
sh all right where we going now I'm
going in the water again
goodbye okay I'm going to try going in
again somebody can I I'll stay behind
for defense I'm
are we doing the thing huh I doing it
uhoh uhoh uhoh uhoh behind me from
behind me behind grab out your gun grab
out your gun that's behind you
GG whoa you guys are
killing I'm in there but I don't know
what I'm doing I don't have I know what
I'm doing either where do I go why all
right let's get the briefcase go go go
go go or defend our there we
go anyone a sniper yeah there's like I
got the briefe
nice go let's go for okay I'm really SL
I'm heavy shoot
them I got him well moo if you guys use
your Uber he has kind of like an ability
let's go how
doble oh there's foko behind
you about let's go this
way I'll he you okay back to
base
good
Elizabeth Elizabeth where you there you
if you right click with Uber with your
charge down down down I don't know if it
was down there no it's up it's up yeah I
think it's up okay okay it's okay we
hand the suitcase to somebody else can I
drop
it there's a I think you have to take it
all the way down oh there we go I way uh
GG is coming downstairs they're here
they're here there Medics here I got
killed by the
medic
[Music]
get okay I have my gun okay uh are some
characters base speed faster than others
yeah like the Scout character
[Music]
I see okay I'm playing is real fast okay
sh that's the wrong yeah
dead nice all I'm going to watch cuz I
didn't realize it's a 6V five so I'm
going to
just are we bullying them a
little well doing pretty well
for shoot shoot
shoot yeah
I did it oh there's someone incoming
okay I have my gun go
two just watch yeah yeah yeah yeah
you're doing it you're doing it you're
doing it you're doing it go go go go go
go
[Music]
go I'm healing for I'm
healing thank you this way you got to
heal we're still danger we're danger I
can I heal myself the same as I heal
everyone else I don't know I feel like
we heal FAS if we heal others I think I
do
my yeah nice okay we got to
them I shoot I shoot I shoot no no no
[Music]
[Laughter]
I'm so good at
this I'm behind you I have the briefcase
let's go oh nice I don't know where to
go though uh we go up I watch behind I
wait about
behind he's a friend he's a friend he's
a friend oh is he taking my
stuff nice nice
nice oh yeah this way this way this way
I remember okay okay you thank you uh
this
way okay where could they be coming
they're too quiet let's go let's go
let's go wait the he wait here they
where
they're somebody needs to get him
[Music]
I I don't know out of the I don't
think basement
has
it
J the
backstab I see somebody I see somebody I
see
somebody thanks
what does battle I'm so confused with
the
map to learn yeah so I'm in the
intelligence but there's nothing here
so
no are you in their intelligence or you
in oh you'll see the you'll see the blue
uh kind of highlight of the intelligence
I think oh respawned okay I got it
every my job is to
heal all right okay we got we got a
guard STI together that's the best part
of our job is your guys
suit I'm not sure where they are oh do
they have
it has
aase dropped where is it um I'm just
wandering around their base I
am where's H is that elizabethy
they have oh no they're
going oh no G is going with the
intelligence grab it grab it okay you
got it you got it you got
it it did it okay together together pick
it up I don't know
I oh okay yeah there a timer okay okay
okay it'll go back automatically we got
this we got this okay we just protect it
we got it we got it
yeah okay heia do you need heal no thank
you
okay oh what's
what's of us up here yeah oh maybe
not okay they're guarding the suitcase o
oh oh
that's
okay I'm lost
again we just got to make sure we guard
this okay it's
been the wrong let's go with a little
blue marus on the map on the map and
let's try getting it I think it's up
here this
way they here they here they're coming
they're coming oh okay okay okay
ohas it's G here
I'm are they in their
base I'm behind
you
H suit
oh crony killed me oh crony's a freaking
SC
heels thank you okay okay good good good
let's go for the suitcase okay suitcase
I'll back you up this way okay I'm going
to go to our place and see if uh yeah
they're they're they're on a base ow
it's been picked up ah see see I knew it
they were too
quiet let ah okay I need help o stick
together stick together yeah stick
together for by nice
one nice nice nice nice let's go I'm
healing our intelligence now to bring
out the gun there's one guy here oh guys
oh guys oh guys okay we're good we're
good I'm out of ammo I'm out of ammo
healing I'm trying to kill you
thisa it's okay okay let's get out of
here
get AIT
guys I think she's running with it
there's
someone it's okay let's go
underground I don't have ammo I don't
have ammo why not why not it was it
wasn't oh the that is that ammo there is
this
ammo I can't him you picked up you
picked up nice nice let's go through the
hole here yeah okay hole healing thank
you did we get the with our suitcase I
think yeah you oh we're going the wrong
way we got to go that way which
way this way go this way yeah yeah keep
going keep going okay
okay o ready I don't know what that is
what is it do how do we use
it I don't know it's okay yeah
wait what is it what do you guys need to
help Uber what is that oh Uber yeah yeah
so you you click on somebody and then
you right click while healing them and
it gives them invincibility for a while
let's get close let's get close down to
to play the right way yes really good in
a big
fight we
won wow
all right um you guys want to play this
one again or do you want to play a new
map it I'm going to switch teams and
then I'm going to go to the other voice
chat and see how they're
doing okay okay we got this let's do it
we got this yeah found guys and then I
was surprised how do I get ammo there's
ammo sometimes on the floor yeah yeah
and when people die they drop ammo too
okay out that's
danger this is
danger okay all right I'm under I'm
under their
base distra them keep
theming
healing what the heck stop Scout in your
base here there's a scout in their base
too
oh the
shot it's too fast there's still Scout
at our base oh we're all doing well got
it oh we got to we got to
protect protect oh
what I'm going
under know going
take up a gun I see our suitcas take up
a
gun take up a gun
gun okay I'll go I'll go check our
suitcase I've
nearly to drop our
thing wait there's someone in the first
floor oh no I dropped their suitcase no
oh we going to go towards it
wait
tillit there's multiple of them there's
multiple angry
sounds to deal as much damage as
possible there's multiple car's almost
[Applause]
dead
one I think they're stealing all of our
stuff we might be in a bad place
the enemy
has got it around oh that's you
sorry it's me it's me you the
realia
everybody oh they're on the way they're
on the way okay I'll protect the Box the
enemy intell return to their base
that spawned everybody's help
okay
nice's oh they're coming they're coming
from the
bridge protect protect
protect I just keep like then just
anyway is there a map no oh there's the
case nice oh here someone pick it up
quick
I am going to shoot at anything that
move that's a good Strat I mean it's
okay cuz it Doesn't harm
us there's no team
[Laughter]
kill all right I'm going to try and get
the oh I should heal I can heal you way
I'm already I'm I'm way over I'm ready
to shoot okay I have my
gun
IO guard dogs guard dogs
yeah with G they are they are the
fire ni did you get
him Dr the fire Dr the fire they have
the B they have the B I'm trying to
shoot them y y y y
down
down the enemy has dropped our
intelligence is that Elizabeth that in
game
stressful the enemy has dropped our
intelligence I thought that
was a little
bit SC me sorry that's
me I just keep shooting everybody
okay I I'm using the fer
technique they're here they're all here
they're all here they're all
here we have sec the enemy
[Music]
intelligence above from above here here
here here nice thank you oh okay you're
good okay we did it one
more I'll shoot them
I'll heal
you he didn't make it in time I'm
feel that count something nice nice okay
uh can I get a
rest
go where's
H in
the Just Keep On Healing B stay behind
it's like I'm controlling her nice okay
like a
St okay
okay may it's okay I'm constantly
healing you so you'll never die let guys
what what everybody else
W you're
invisble no one else
matters
okay okay there we go ah they had a bot
there no okay back to Healing
just it's I think it's
not I'm heing F stop
what heing F again oh yeah I don't have
a plan I'm going in I will just heal you
he's going in it's okay you got the
power of fire
and oh behind us behind us maybe I'll
keep an eye on thought a song Oh I
tried ah who's on fire somebody's
screaming ow it's oh you're
bad it's me it's me it's
[Music]
me B they have a
Sentry yeah that's Amelia all right I
got
somebody oh that was crony
p uh
okay be on our base
still at finding place
okay I'll
you
okay oops
sorry I see them over there they're on
the bridge near the other
bridge fire fire maybe you sck sp don't
let it get behind you oh nice okay who
needs I need healing okay
[Music]
okay what our intelligence was up help
help uhoh it might be in the water I'm
going to go underground
I'm staying behind I see them I see them
they're running away where where where
at the basement at the
basement oh they're running away they're
too fast
uhoh uhoh okay one is
fire oh no they are R me it's a
scout H there's a blue one right there
get out water the a little bit up heels
please please
con next you where are
you here there you go thank you aw your
healer grab the gun grab the gun
grab go
Revenge let's go not listen to me I said
take out the gun what a moment to take
out the gun wait let's behind
you nice okay hold on can I heal the
enemy don't want to do that I don't
want I don't want
to be careful be careful wait let me
turn it off let me turn it
off
D no oh hey Cecilia has the briefcase oh
no she's take I'm take my gun here
go so you you can
[Music]
go oh no but you know can do let's go
wait did they have our
briefcase do well we can get those so
okay yeah alert the enemy has taken our
int
I don't know where they are though Focus
healing must be nearby
right must three of them in there I
guess that's
understandable run away run away run
away they
here I think the Scout with the brief
face is still in our base I don't know
if they're on the way okay I'll back you
up for now is this the only exit or is
there another exit who is
this cuz that must be another exit
healing with the hot dog is this
innocent place
yes
okay here cuz I'm trying to heal they're
going on the they're going on the ground
on the ground on the ground on the
ground ah the birds are
beautiful oh
no okay let's go let's go let's go be
careful they're all like all here oh
back it sounds like a big fire over here
there's someone in their basement there
so many up there they're all
waiting they're in the basement they're
in the
basement's in the basement oh wait I
think she's the only one that everyone
else yeah yeah she might be waiting in
uh in
case I hit from
behind man the blue one is the one
the blue one not the blue one I don't
trust all the spies the blue
one any healing the enemy on the floor
I've lost it why I was just here where
did it go no no no it's not no no
it's in the
basement in the basement what
line
nobody okay okay okay okay
two I did nothing that time did nothing
got
him uhoh there's no B down here please
don't left me another B on the bridge
with our case he's on the bridge with
our case I have that case there's
someone in face to no oh there's some
sounds going on
Wow I'll shoot them oh gosh oh why is
somebody
screams
damage yeah there is fall
damage goodby forever oh that's good
that's good no
I I think we want to shoot them I don't
know get him get him I'm running
[Laughter]
away it's the water we
go I need
healing oh no she's sto B you fa the
enemy in
[Music]
we tried
Tri that was fun
the we tied hey we're changing Maps Okay
we do random teams again this
time did you guys have
fun it's chaotic he hates me yeah yeah
up what why are you bullying us
[Laughter]
[Music]
H you walked into my buet yeah random
random you want us to hit random yes
yeah random let's go random move the
car
hi hi's this
tutorial yeah so this one uh one side
pushes the cart the other side tries to
stop she already H you die I had a heart
attack oh no how how do you know if
you're on the pushing team or the
defending team uh red is defending blue
is pushing okay I cannot okay okay do
you want us to move in a different
voice yeah yeah okay uh blue team or red
team go to the other Bush okay oh
[Music]
myby red red team this a red
team can double jump I didn't know that
what the now you know now I know we're
supposed to go even if you don't need
healing I can so this one is I
imagine way you push the oh I see the
card over there it's like highlighted in
a or highight and blue is that the oer
yeah that's the
O wow everybody's a
superhero I knew what you
meant oh I don't know where to go though
I'm so confused Mission begins I see it
I see I see what our
mission we have to guard the cart so
they don't push it Forward guard the
cart guys over this way where are you
guys I don't know I found
sh what is going on I have a
I
cool we got to stop it but I don't know
where to go making a sound and I don't
like it hello hello my red team party
[Music]
members St I'm going to S with
you bye they're about to kill me help me
that's good don't tell the cops tell
cops you got it we need to go to the
next car
is that a car oh the the found the car
is
moving
okay let's try and find it we need to
jum in
there oh well I hear death yeah I
that it's okay I look I look for
death got
you oh I need help get down this danger
hi behind up wow it takes up so much to
kill this one guy I will heal if you
fall back here he will heal you I tried
okay oh no it's okay I'm dead there's
herb
though oh yeah I think the teams were
balanced when it started hello welcome
welcome to the red team red for blood
absolutely no idea that
happened hi we're here oh
yep yep are
you imper I know where to go uh I see
the car the car's really wait am I going
no I'm going the wrong way it's this
way I'll follow you
ince okay it's coming it's coming it's
coming oh I'll
you I be here I should have be here okay
okay I need
healing I
you I'm healing I'm going to go
in oh C's behind you I'm going to use
U I used it but it's
useless I going get this orange
gun I'll heal if you need that is cilia
I think
we need heal too M so be careful
no there's a
dangerous
yeah this is
[Laughter]
hard it's fine oh they're doing well
they're going to next Point can
we shoot that we Sho it how does stop I
don't
know I shoot
the at least there's a attack over
time I need
healing we medic we're
medic
we're for you
what does she want to die all right herb
needs healing come over here by the
car okay I'm by
you okay over there come over here if
you want
healing wait what color am I
red uhoh uhoh uhoh uh uhoh
keeping oh dang it's okay and on fire
come over here if you want
healing cing
behind we probably need to move now no
I'm seeing right here we got probably
find us they're going to fight us we're
going to die yeah yeah yeah yeah we're
not going to make this we're not going
to make this we have to jump I'm going
to do
it okay my on
my I'm going do
was right strategy was good it's a good
strategy
yeah I don't want to hurt
her oh we need an engine that is not I
got sniped funny to become an engine
started to
[Music]
become
behind wait there 8 minutes it's so long
watch out it's a b it's a
b watch up we can't survive that we
can't survive
that flying going off that bullets are
stronger than oh I
[Music]
try oh it's coming in
defense is always so hard again again
let's go I'm going to try and do that
we're we're attacking
now okay we all stay together here I'll
he you our bullets aren't that strong we
should only use it we really need to so
let's focus on healing okay it's very
different from what you said just a
moment ago
take out the gun take out the gun I see
aggressive Target so we need to respond
aggressively yeah okay you're
healed let us let us I am F
Char we got 30 seconds Mission begins in
30 seconds let's just think about our
like our
family how do you look at what all the
the do hies do on each character
is there a button Uber is
ready do I have to press the Uber and
then attach to someone Mission begins in
10 seconds maybe 10 seconds what was
that oh you got to be attached to
someone and then Uber
yeah how do you I've changed character
how do you look at what the character
does uh period and then do
numbers backwards
I oh okay always tell me to good job
good job good job go for it go for it I
from here I think it's freaking okay I'm
just going to focus on pushing yeah oh
we're dying we're dying we're dying
we're going to
go over the characters it'll say what
they do can I
heal my I really like those gon guns we
should heal everybody getting we getting
getting up wrong way wrong way
oh I
shooting stick to the C the
C I'm going back to other voice wa you
guys have
questions thank
you all right they're in the tunnel
right
now oh it moves on its own oh that's it
I guess it moves faster if we're closer
to maybe it's time for the gun no he all
right
heal harder yeah good job good job good
[Music]
job
I'm they might come from behind us so we
got to be
careful I'll tell you if you're getting
shot
at from
above away from the B I'm trying to kill
Elizabeth going to be all
just like everyone's like
healer okay they're
up down here
too why
is good job herb we got revenge BB needs
healing almost there to the first stop
okay
uhoh
job Elizabeth is killing
you
[Music]
nice Oo we have an MVP so
far all I'm just going to sacrifice
myself
no stay safe she will we
mad watch out for the big
bullets watch for the big
bullet I'm
healing heal running
running
way oh I'm dead now hi dead shortcut
thank
you thank you just in time in time it's
a fight between you living and
dying oh my Gosher I
trying
elizabth I'm not there yet yeah can I
got a little Z too thank you
nice now we're talking okay watch's over
the big Bullets watch's Over the big
bullets let's keep
on out watch out watch out the bomb
let's see I keep
forgetting yeah to so used to Red oh
someone's flanking us from behind bombs
behind behind behind oh I'm from above
and above behind and above
[Music]
good jump good jump good jump good jump
good jump good jump he he he he good
[Music]
good
[Applause]
us blow up I don't know he someone
okay here I I'm on my way I'm on my way
on my
way okay careful they're above us
to I was on a kill
above who stopped pushing the C who
stopped pushing the
car I think we might have a live behind
us okay I'm going to shoot them with my
gun I'm on my way
[Music]
get you long way to run we're trying to
get together with everybody but we can
there all right all right run
[Music]
away heal you I'm try to heal
you it's a fight between healing and
dying indeed it is it always
is can I
come back a it come back a
it okay you're good you're good exploded
but you're okay thanks Lear following
you I'm just making sure that
[Music]
everything oh that was L that was Lot
another bomb another bomb another
bomb another bomb will go down watch out
for all the bombs there's a lot of bombs
get okay watch yeah I'll cover you
innocent fire I have you thank you thank
you get the car move keep an ey behind
yeah yeah they might flank us anytime oh
they're here in the front in the
front we're Ving behind
you fine make sure
everybody no it's
fine make sure we heal heal thees
okay we're good we're good stay behind
we go down watch out for bombs watch B
bomb in the front bombs in the front
Okay one's in the
front behind us behind us okay okay
shoot
themer we need a Healer we need healer
okay job okay I'll heal in the
front there's a spy okay I'm healing you
there's a spy I
[Music]
will okay keep an
eye survive and as long as you know how
to love I know you'll stay on the
behind us behind
us
[Music]
beautiful it's fun when you
win got
okay okay we're defending again let's
see how this go defending be
hard
is I'm going to change the game mode one
more time if you guys want to go into
the other chat for this round do
whatever oh sure okay
chaos hello hello friend
[Music]
Let's Have a Party
part come on good game good
[Music]
game how to defend
successfully I'm overcharged wait let me
just watch in one hour video real quick
I I I looked up like a guide and I was
like how to play this one it was a 2our
long video
guys I don't have time for that TR hard
team for no I didn't want
to that's a TR hard I cannot believe you
try
hard where is everyone of a different
game okay okay
yeah can you in this game Guess while
we're switching game
you each
[Music]
other let's go
oh take him
down come out guys come on blue team are
we playing
again team death
match I don't know where I am
death I'm a little bit lost
I might go the other way by the way did
I die
already hey I love these oh there is a
sniper
where I did it
now I died how could this happen
revenged by
shooting I don't have enough for this
actually can we shoot through
them you shoot through people like your
teammates
all my teammates eat my
missiles
[Music]
delous I'm sorry no no no it's not
yet okay
oops how do I get out of here
I thought you were my friends and they
killed me okay what you guys prefer to
stay all in voice chat or still
separating for teams
IP okay okay okay yeah otherwise it' be
too chaotic and we wouldn't
[Music]
be but every once in a while getting
together is fun too yeah
yeah you're going down whoever we're
going to be in a team again wait there's
no video oh my god well where's the
video raining I don't like
this oh we're free of the same uh
character
mine oh no wait how can oh let's go over
there we can go over there that oh
hi what's up losers hey we on the same
team we're on the same team now
stop what up this
yeah voice red team go into the second
voice chat red
team what's the objective of this game
mode Hell friend what is this game mode
there's three minutes on
each what are we doing is this Death
Match actually maybe I'll heal you we
need to know I'm going come back oh it's
raining what this Death Mode
death I we each other kill each other wa
wait you take damage from the rain I
think what you you took fall damage but
I'm still taking damage oh yeah we oh I
guess I'm not taking damage from R oh
I'm not taking
damage I'm dying everyone I'll help
you
but wi te red that's blue that's blue I
found the blue I found the blue
yeah yeah there sorry I forgot to tell
you guys it's um it's a king of the hill
objective so you want to get control
Point yeah yeah oh okay so we have to
stay there okay I think everybody hit
the the all right CeCe needs healing I
died to the Trap
everyone I guess you that
there I'm not going to make that that's
why you should say
it it's past t look how Mak
sense or or I should say I saw that
[Music]
coming oh
hi okay I
needing try to kill you
GG I'm trying to heal you I
you so what do we have to do uh stay in
the Blue Zone to get points I think
or I fell
okay okay we need to
heal King of the Hill everyone we're wi
we're
winning on
the I don't understand we just have to
stay in the Box area and not let them
kill us okay yeah they have one minute
over
us nice okay let's go to the B you see
the sauce
okay use the sauce coverage it helps
oh assuming you don't get hit by
it hear you if I can get there I'm don't
worry I'm distracting them I'm
distracting
them okay let's get
ready okay we're catching up for 20
seconds I'm
going there there's a scout in the bik
crony or at the at the thing at the at
the at the at the flag get him are we
doing pretty well though we're almost
half and half
yeah caping capturing the thingy this
good this good I
think back in the house
back it's the end it's the end of the
house that's red I think it's red oh
shoot they have a
medic scar medic good job CeCe know
where are see
them I don't know qu qu
they're capturing the point again they
captured it we have to go back to the
point okay let's go okay oh oh
here party where is it over here I
thought it should right here at the
Sawmill it's up this stair up this here
okay I'll just follow you we're Team now
okay here's the
house oh this
sounds go in the house go in the house
go in the house there there go in the
house
no oh good job
jump go in the house
no the house watch they'll be in the
house go in the house go they're in the
house go in the house oh that's on team
we got to run yes going attack them
let's go in the house in the
house the house oh there's one hidden I
think under the
stairs are
we you there medic on the way where the
medic where the medic someone saw that
coming I'm
[Laughter]
in why you fake
laugh hey what if that a genuine laugh I
lik
it sorry sorry my I get the Healer
they're outside
here oh behind you
[Music]
no help help they're all here it's okay
you got this one V5 maybe need more than
one Healer just to be safe cuz we
already how you doing way back yes no I
think I think you should stay as your
thing you're actually pretty good
CeCe I would prefer you to have skills
[Music]
h no they oh my God why did I die
Elizabeth is why you
[Laughter]
die oh not blue team yes that's why you
kept us go in the house go in the house
we're almost winning so confused we
almost I thought we
blue oh my God a good color that's why
is a good
color okay so we have it's okay we have
a second chance now yeah second chance
at Li I'll stay behind you okay I okay
so all right now we actually know the
objective yeah so what is the objective
I don't know right the center do you
guys see the number at the to 3 minutes
yeah yeah yeah so if you guys hold one
point that point we're dying we're dying
run away run away run away run away
trun away we're dying we're dying we're
try to get run away run away shared
point a shared
Point time down okay
okay all right we should coordinate
yeah okay
let's I don't understand oh right
click okay I set them on fire surely it
helps okay we we red we want to kill
blue I think this is working well just
stay
down know they don't know don't know I'm
here they don't know I'm here if you're
in the house come behind the the
wood I'll
you
okay can't it does no damage it's
actually I don't really like it oh go St
behind the wood here go away go
away yeah good job good dog going
away okay go here go here maybe maybe I
don't can't go here
there's to many
everybody yeah there's to many Heavies
right I'm going to I'm tapping in I'm
going to help you guys a little bit okay
okay mom's
coming Okay Okay who wants some Pockets
um you are damaged here you
go hide the hide
the I aming
okay never
mind I
[Music]
Trieda I'm trying to kill I hit him
once No Sa
save there so
am I on the wrong team no on the team
team
wow
nice so hi on it I
died oh the lag oh what yeah lagging oh
okay oh God nice I guess I'll uh I'll K
I actually can't move now
never
mind going to have to wait for us I
think our feet are a little bit stuck
right now oh yeah I I can't move at all
so
okay
yeah oh yeah guys come here also of
being clipped through
walls no it's okay the game's trying to
Nerf us because we're so good yeah they
going to win right
yeah I don't know so are we losing or
are we
wining
winning yeah they're feeling the lag too
it's
okay okay we can we can get the point
here just don't run into the saw
hopefully can we
move Miss ends in 10 seconds 10 seconds
No 5 4 3
2 no as long as we're on the point it's
going to be
delay okay
overtime anybody on the point I'm trying
I was not letting me
up ah wait timed
out it's okay we still have somebody on
the
pointa watch out I'm walking I'm walking
there it's
overtime the we got we got it we got it
we got it we can if we keep on it I'm
trying I I can't I can't move now go you
are the single letter oh where are you
guys I'm coming but I'm like rubber
bending oh my God oh God I can't even to
the
door it says server not resp what it
feels like to fast forward in
time should we wait until the server is
responding
D oh I think it's going it's fine it's
going good yeah it feels better now okay
for me it's like graub a banding still
so like I don't know if that's the right
term but like I'm a little
ball weird you weird that you're a
little
huh hey you
guys here we go here we go still some
time should no
oh I don't know okay te I think they
they're capturing it I'm frozen
again touch it touch it it's not too
late it's not too late how did I get
here what if what if I change teams
write this
instant all right we can go back into
Old chat and then um I think there's
like a sandbox mode we could do and then
we'll just uh yeah and then we'll stop
from there
thank you thank
you good good
game GG I still can't move that was
laggy wait a minute I can't move tting
GG oh I get it now okay
weird never too late never too
late never too late never too late is it
still isn't it still lagging should we
like
yeah it's lag lag has been really bad
can we restart somehow yeah for us it's
not lagging it just stopped yeah oh it
stopped the server stopped uh before it
kicked us out it disconnected and now
now it's just nothing's going yeah yeah
crony also got kicked out and for me and
Herbert's just like moving I can't right
now yeah
same I see okay yeah um I think I could
reset server or also I mean we pretty
much played for the amount of time we
were going to play oh yeah true that was
fun that was so
fast
fun
[Music]
guys if anything we learn how to
differentiate colors which
is we Lear was you guys got better about
it it was
fun funk you looking forward to Gary's
[Music]
Mod thank you so much
[Applause]
[Music]
by