[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
la
n
[Music]
la
n
[Music]
p
[Applause]
[Music]
la
n
[Music]
a
PA
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
a
la
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
no
la
oh okay
[Music]
can
mm m
yeah uh
mhm it's just
stressful I'm sorry once
[Music]
again for being
useless I'm looking forward to the
comments of free people saying why can't
you [\h__\h]
prepare yeah yeah yeah I'm looking
forward to bring it
on this [\h__\h] game capture card I hate
it so
much like it makes no sense I switched
the audio Source a million times and
then it it doesn't work whatever I do
and I restart it still doesn't work I
restart still doesn't work I restart
again and then suddenly it works this
capture card is so
inconsistent no I don't know I mean I
it's it's annoying to me stupid capture
card but in the end what is 10 minutes
out of a 8 Hour stream
that's an argument I would
say I did I did uh fix I I think I uh I
think I fixed the microphone I brought
got it back to the
usual
um the usual
state U I don't know if you can tell the
difference can you
tell it's how it usually sounded I
think the usual
state not the usual room it's the usual
state
mhm uh I didn't
tweet useless
unprepared I didn't tweet oh my
God and I'm sorry but I still care about
cyle sorry I am looking for
Cheetos
um I mean aren't we also wondering where
cycle is isn't that isn't that
legit isn't that a legit
[Music]
concern I I I knew I
knew when I wrote that I was
like yeah I was going to write something
like oh yeah
cycle have we we found we found a fake
cycle but where's the real one and then
I looked into my archive and I I checked
and I saw it was Cheeto the the that
fake so to Sayo was Chito said that I
was thinking of like buto said the
wrestler or whatever I'm like wait wait
wait wait what
what
so I'm getting everything
wrong it's been just a few days and I uh
don't remember anything anymore oops
Yeah
well
well who why who
is why do we need which is Cho Cho say
is the one who like got us drunk
right don't worry I got that I got it
it's back it's back that it's back it's
back right that's ch
right
oh
man yeah yeah okay she has my password
okay
okay off to a great start
today sorry the [\h__\h] capture card
annoyed me so much I hate it I want to
understand how the how my internal
capture card works I actually have one I
actually have an internal capture card
as you may remember uh that was built in
without my knowledge I don't know I
don't know how that
works how does that work I don't know
anyway we we are again doing a y
weekend they make internal ones now they
they're internal on existed for
ages yeah and we're going to hang with
some barracudas we're going to show them
we're going to show them who the biggest
predators in the waters of Hawaii are us
what are we sharks maybe Hawaii
sharks yeah
uh ooh we've played almost 10 hours
already how how is that possible
possible when my two streams combined
are longer than that no it's uh most
likely because I write super
chats okay so are you guys ready you're
hearing the bgm right the the game
bgm say yes say
yes say yes yes all right here we go
aren't we starting with a cut scene or
was that was last time I
guess is this where we're supposed to
start yeah yeah yeah
yeah ooh we we started and finished a
completely different
RPG in between the yaku are playthrough
so uh I will need to do my best to
remember how do I how do I run like this
okay uh what are we doing what are we in
the middle of doing let's just follow
the pink Mark oh and let's fight these
guys I guess we need exp anyway probably
yeah know streaming I I got to catch up
because I I came back in like the middle
uh the middle
of the T was the the front person
right I hope
uh yeah nice
oh nice
hit what was I saying what was I
saying
what was I saying what was I saying what
was I saying oh yeah I came back in the
middle of the
month
[Music]
and you know I feel like at the end of
the month my my streaming hours will
look like as if I was here the whole
month now that's good I want to flex
those
hours is this too quiet for me it's
pretty quiet I should probably turn it
up I don't know for you guys it doesn't
look so loud
so it's probably
fine they definitely will oh it is okay
no
problem how about
now
pink how do I I want to walk through
this building
please I don't want to go around can I
clim over over the
building slightly lower
okay
okay slightly I made slightly
lower wouldn't it be cool if you guys
had control over my OBS like everybody
on their own and you can do the sound
mixing however you prefer oh they should
make a tool like that oh pink is not
good that's not the pink I
want they should make a tool like that
for YouTube
streaming you can turn my voice up you
can turn the music down oh that would be
genius and if I do a Koka stream you can
just turn off the music completely and
just hear me a capella or you can turn
off my voice and just hear the
instrumentals hi dub
bye-bye the dudes in the car I can fight
the dudes in the car are they not going
to like if I don't fight them do they
ever drive away wait how do I do the uh
Hawaii thing
again I like that oh yeah oh oh my God
everybody wa me
hi
your oh hey I was saying I was being
friendly oh my God
no what the
[\h__\h]
ala oh he
missed too bad my friend all right Grand
liner yeah yeah
yeah the one in the back
right don't move don't move
I missed it but it's okay at least I did
it right I'll take the AL capella option
oh you want to hear my voice all on its
own isolated it gets the
car let's go let's go jabber
jobber normal
attack
[Music]
H Bo circle is block
right
yeah shoot I guess what's the
button always tryangle how what's going
on Focus Tommy Focus
I know I didn't play the game for a
while but you shouldn't be forgetting
anything double
[Music]
Miss oh baby a
triple triple
Miss what's going
on
F
magic work better against the of mhm
okay but was the thing that I used was
probably not considered
magic he get another
one oh
nice he moves is so so clumsy today
he so
clumsy what a weird weird
situation whoa waa I want to be friends
with
you hey hey
kid
who it actually has we just became
friends is that how you treat your
friends kid wait give me
that natural
herb bit fire in my face I'm going to
report you to the police honestly you I
can't just let that go they driving a
golden
car and they have sub roofers in the
car built in but they still choose to
use the [\h__\h] tiny baby radio that the
guy in Gray has you want to
fight what let
me there we
go you serious right now serious right
now oh they got Peppa spray pepper
spray Bo box all
right magic damage so this is is this
like our only real magic run try it I'll
try it
on I'll try it on you cuz you're close
is that good that's good right
not so much damage but
okay let's finish
[Music]
him how is he not
dead hey when you turned around did I
just block uh on on my own because that
sounded like the block what
are what was I going to say oh yeah can
you actually block even though you're
being attacked from behind you think
you're
tough
here oh
well ah no I didn't I didn't forgot I
forgot you have to press squ squ square
square square
[Music]
square as long as you press the button
hm
okay [\h__\h] you run they don't even use
their pepper
spray
ouch you're trying to
block uh okay let's try this
again and then
you yeah okay collateral damage where
the big guy come from I know did you not
see him he was the one who was carrying
the radio I wouldn't even call it a boom
box I feel like it looked too pathetic
to to be a boom
box how do I switch to him
again ah
okay I should have used a
skill you running away already [\h__\h] K
how can you let them do this to you
your whole
reputation is
on on the what do you say how do you say
this in German we say
Al oh okay on the
line on the line a very very thin
line
yeah why won't you just
die come on Tommy you can do this
right Thank
God learning random German I I want to
educate you isn't this nice I'm an
educational
streamer you have so many things to
learn from me
this is just another good reason to
watch W streams over
here nobody
[Laughter]
responds yeah you lost buddy you got
nothing left oh stop stop walking away
on the
street car is going to run you over why
did he
explode why did he
explode what what was there a a
mine it's so Random this weapon it
exploded on his foot though oh hello
friend
Danny D Danny what's wrong I can't take
it I'm on the job but I'm dead tired I
wish I had something to wake myself up
something
energizing
o
I'll give you the
Torina you're welcome now you like me I
see how is that is that never going to
come in handy for me
anyway why am fighting
again
ouch oh my God the
creepers
huh Dodge play again yeah this time I'm
going I'm going to use Magic on him uh
but first we have K
so this is AOE right come on so we can
get something good going here
no AOE only if they're in the circle was
it oh
well
mhm oh oh or he or because he used the
weapon oh that
oh
okay all right uh Tommy is about to
die not good I wonder if these are also
weak to
Magic are you scared are you scared he's
little dance what do you call that
dance o oh 60 and still so
[Music]
little you see where they are weak up
and just
[Music]
like I need bleach I need bleach I need
bleach for my
eyes Okay Kio help me out here
nice a [\h__\h] I was going to block but
even even with the block
maybe wouldn't have done the
trick oh man are you is he in the circle
too
no stop the
dance pissing me
off what a way to
die all right good I have no okay we
just got to go with our bear
massager with our Fair
massaging we have our D massage so what
the [\h__\h] are these K are these us we wor
using deals extra damage status element
uhhuh May lower their defense and
critically hits if the action
[Music]
prompt I don't
know
just relying on my fists
now this Kido still has like all his MP
and HP
you K will run from enemy to enemy it's
okay uhuh
uhuh okay I would like to be
healed you guys said hey hi you guys
said
hi uh before that I can get healed
[Music]
somewhere
but yeah
restaurant where is I'm running away
from my quest but where is the
next a here's
one please don't fight
me please ignore me garlic
shrimp that little hello
oh that looks so yummy I wish I was a
fan of garlic or of shrimps I mean I
love
garlic spicy garlic coconut garlic
shrimp coconut shrimp
wow lav in a creamy coconut milk
sauce I'll take the cocon not
garlic
yeah uh the comom I forgot how that
works
really just how do I know what to
choose hawaian macaroni is good really
why what's different elbow macaroni
carrots and onions dressed with
mayonnaise and vinegar classic side in
Hawai what's different or is is that
where they come from
anyway reading the description of
guessing ah yeah cuz I wonder what the
classics
are wait wait this is it says
classic and and okay so shouldn't that
be
it does it
not thank you
[Music]
Aloha I guess I still got to get free oh
I need a drink
too oh
[Music]
well but the dishes I got right I would
say I I wasted money man
yo
what about Judy though what about Judy
what are you looking
at how do I use my my roller thing
again no I want to DOD
down damn
it we're going to fight like a police
officer Mr Mina Wier St where the manor
Winer o
[Music]
come miss the wiener Wier this is what
you guys should call police officers try
it try it let's let's let's see their
reaction
maybe not a good
idea oh
[\h__\h] oh
well oh
oh you think I'm just [\h__\h] stun guns
me is that really necessary maybe maybe
Tommy can help
me Tommy he's right in front of you do
something I would like to to take your
stun gun home with
me
and study its
electric functionalities oo
that
for my
[Music]
streams it's not here who would use that
it says Hero's sword shouldn't that be
for
me a different class
[Music]
ah
nice okay we here aloha why not buy
something uh the [\h__\h] are these have
these always been so
expensive yeah right these these places
don't have the sandwiches and all that
stuff
I these are actually
cheap but it's just 50 HP and removing
an effect 50
HP healing expensive early on for real
yeah yes I want to get rid of the weapon
cuz everybody is like funny
weapon I want to get rid of it 500
that's like too
much I'll get like
U two of these do thank
you
at least I feel like the MP would be
helpful a
dog he didn't
recognize oh he wants ah he wants
something else he wants to like okay he
wants more than just a
greeting what have I got on
me I need my
food do you have dog food it doesn't
have to be dog food if I give them this
are they not going to be satisfied
anyway
Fe the dog oh oh okay you can buy do is
it
cheaper but not in this store I
think this Ain a show
dipit no no no no no no I'll sue you I
need to exp speed but at the same time I
don't want to always be on low HP and MP
holy [\h__\h]
werewolf get get all the oh my God look
at the claws get all the the Hol girls
that are into Twilight over here this is
Paradise for
them right do you think I can get the
other ones
too no wait how do I what how do
I tget again what the [\h__\h] I didn't
choose that how did that happen okay now
we saw how that
works oh nice wait now it's Auto
Battle it's Auto
Battle I was like what
what am I just accidentally pushing
these
things does this get stronger in the
range that would be
cool
we've done the same
before good I'm not the only
[Music]
one he l in his
knee
jawbreaker
okay at least now the path is clear you
there there's so much pink around oh my
God I I got to go there and there's so
many
enemies excuse
me
uh no no no no no no no if anything let
me fight the the red ones cuz they're
they they are where I need to go hi damn
you
you think I can deal with
them well let's get the red ones out of
the way first get that tip by any means
necessary never misses ignore ignores
guards and applies your weapons
attributes
okay let's try that do I get money from
that what no I don't think I did but
that did a lot of
[Music]
damage ni oh now I feel stronger
suddenly we should really save after
this fight okay I
will I guess we are going into
something like a
dungeon keep on missing the prompts to
dodge no saves run without even that
intention I often go without saving for
a long
time why do I have to make a new one all
the
time look at
Pi that
up do he also speak
fluent everybody speaks fluent Japanese
is that realistic in Hawaii I know
there's a lot the Japanese people
but and he doesn't even have an
[Music]
accent he talks like a
Japanese
I guess like scratching the reality a
little bit for the sake of having it in
Japanese excuse me American Americans
can only speak
American
that sounds
threatening do you have
family okay
20 20y old boy asks begs his dead for
sports car [\h__\h] up
mind it's not that [\h__\h] easy you
spoiled ass
kids get it
yourself
for oh
oh it's so nice of him to be so
passionate for his son's
gift he's selfless
not even about a gift for
himself
spee
fore
fore o
who
close well what are you waiting for well
now you can speak
English
the way he
moves these damn tourists think they can
walk all over us let's teach him how
wrong they
are get your ass
ready
tourist bring Hawaii all the
money
just wanted to use the furniture
but ah he's not going to do the AOE
either cuz of the furniture maybe what
if I what if I go from ah then he uses
that
one d d maybe let's do wait was it tone
F no this
one so he does this on everybody let's
see
oh that was that was good good good
good still got uh for the grand liner we
go for the front or the
back it's
confusing back their
back back
okay oh Roman is in the
back can we get a couple more let's
see
H we take took someone
down you want
a oh
Brian oh
[Music]
Brian what's wrong with me I can't read
the the timings I feel like I was better
that in
previous okay can you still will never
get shot from that
guy want to
[Music]
dance get cold
feet
I only got
him just try me come
[Music]
onad weak a
okay nice nice thre it like a
crispy
you're so close ran it's making me
nervous get out of my
face he
strong
uhoh
[\h__\h]
well you can't hurt me though I have a a
$10
bill under my Haw shirt that blocks
every gunot tag me
in how's Hawai Hawaii is
beautiful and so
peaceful everybody wants to be my
friend but also everybody wants to be my
enemy want to be my
enemy oh
oh ah no more
MP should I just try to do a whole fight
without and rely on the others on their
MP yes yes I
shall
uhoh blind
fire
what that's
AOE
[Music]
dude
B you dies you lose the battle
uh-oh
[Music]
uhoh
no oh how's it work again
[Music]
100 100 should be good
right
yeah yeah I know about the defense I was
thinking about using it because of that
but
[Music]
by the way because I was saying people
in America speak American you guys know
how many times I've heard after I say
I'm from
Austria like oh so you speak Austrian
I'm like
h
no
no but I feel like I've heard it mostly
from Japanese people
ooh nice back
[Music]
attack no not even technically no
there's an Austrian dialect but we don't
call it
a it's still German
just because the people who ask that
they don't realize they they probably
don't even know where Austria is they
wouldn't be able to locate it on the map
but I think a lot of people wouldn't be
able to locate
it small and you
know don't really know let's do the jaw
break up and hope for the
best
yeah I know where is on the map would
you guys be able to locate it on the map
you would at least know that it's in in
the in Europe
right we cored him he catches a
cold
a need to make him some soup I really
want to make soup because yesterday I
was watching cooking videos that's where
where basically that tweet came
from
and there was a channel which makes like
so much
soup and they chop chop chop they chop
chop chop and they chop a
little uh dude what the [\h__\h] is wrong
with
you
[\h__\h]
what where where did he [\h__\h] get a
rifle
from I don't care I don't care I'll try
I I'll go for it cuz I got MP
again yes yes if now we get Kio to
attack it should
be his cold killed him you didn't take
your cold medicine you didn't take your
vitamins you lost track of the real
important things in life
yeah
yeah but in case you didn't see on
Twitter I was saying I want to make a
stream or a video but maybe just still
just the stream is fine too but maybe at
first the video cuz like I'm I'm a bit
worried about Reflections and stuff uh
but I want to make content cooking
content where I don't even talk I just
chop chop chop chop and Sizzle Sizzle
Sizzle and Grill and wash and this and
that cuz you guys know and I'm so happy
I saw in the replies many many people
that think the same
way I don't really ASMR does nothing for
me but I like cooking sounds like chop
chop chop chop chop chop chop chop chop
chop chop chop stuff like that is nice
very nice and and yeah cooking videos in
general I like and when the sounds are
so nice makes it even better I wouldn't
even say that that's
like the same as ASMR to me but it's
just nice satisfying and pleasing
yeah
yeah no I don't want to talk I don't
want to talk at all I want people to
just enjoy the cooking sounds in the
background and maybe maybe enjoy what
I'm cooking as well and like the the
result as
well I have some stuff in my Amazon
uh
uh uh
shopping
bag I didn't buy it yet but I'm also
buying a complete green screen suit not
sure if I'll actually end up using it
but I'm just buying it for now and a
shotgun microphone from Road uh cuz I
just watched some YouTube videos with
their recommendations for like cooking
ASMR
basically and I bought some new knives
or I'm buying some new
knives what was
it some knce
Japanese
Ste yes Damascus knives
Chef h e
f ah we've done worse we've done more
crazy
[\h__\h]
[Music]
foree at look at that being cute
for K and ich now are also like besties
forever
for
Fore
fore
for
okay it's finally
listening now go home and let your your
your bombshell wife take care of your
cold
foreign fore
speee
won
man we can report a lot of dudes repu in
decency junky
wonky same animation from y oh I didn't
realize guess he can't take us right
away SOA it's late enough as it is let's
head back to chunky wonky to the hotel
for the night now there's an idea I'll
beat are all the enemies gone nice oh No
actually they're not looking at the
map
garden
water so this place now just you can
just have normal food in there and
drinks
nice oh Tommy kind of needs it should
I sorry I keep on pressing that because
of um because of the other game that we
were playing cuz that that was the dash
[Music]
button hello aloha aloha ooh
lamp chops pickles beef jerky smoked
cheese nachos oh the food as always
looks amazing let's see let's see if we
can get the combo going although I don't
really have so much money cuz like
medicine and everything cost so much but
okay is there tequila yeah okay
tequila vodka
up and smoke smoke smoke smoke
cheese that's got to be
it real
prices yeah but I have no money wait
what what
Whata huh got a good one I don't get
it you need all oh I
[Music]
not give
me hey
you no
you I don't I don't want to deal with
you guys I just want the treasure is
lying
around please I'm addicted to treasure
hunting oh we're drunk now right oh no
no okay I'll get the I'll take the uh
XP yeah okay I'll yeah I'll have so much
money let's use the calii
[Music]
sticks yeah oh we we killed one let's go
car help us be be
my be my
help let's get rid of these
[\h__\h]
together they can be part of my game
little
wor
bucks all right okay where are we
going
uh gosh really lot of enemies in that
area we got to go to Kos
Hotel okay how do I
use ah found
it found it does it go
[Music]
faster maybe
not ni taxi
no I want to use my super cool
Cruiser oh God I got to charge it huh I
do I have to bring it to an actual
charging
station why won't it just charge when
I'm not using it
display I'm probably never going to use
it again once it runs
out I don't even know where these
charging stations
are oh is that a charging station
it
my oh
[Music]
no oh well I
arrived so from now on we might never
use it again her was nuk is that also
for a different class now we have two
cool sounding
weapons that we can't use it that we
can't use yet
[Music]
probably
for if you're exhausted from a long day
you know what you should
do watch
[Music]
vtubers now that you have YouTuber
technology in the Yakuza
world just watch
YouTubers cuz not because I want to see
more of her not at
[Music]
all yeah but we're the cool people we're
better
so
[Music]
true yeah we saved
them
I love these
br
you're inspiring
me
[Music]
such a puppy oh my
God
[Music]
drink out of the bottle
no thought he was going to drink it
straight this means nothing to me I
don't understand was this supposed to be
cool
can't
[Music]
relate make itter
a just drink water then if you don't
want it if you want something water down
just drink
[Music]
water what an argument
wa or drink
juice
G what kind of
cancer huh that's how they kill off the
main protagonist they had for
years you can't do that to Mrs
K
what what what kind of
cancer
huh is are they actually n we're going
to he's going to be saved right he's
going to be able to get rid of it right
he's not going to die they can't kill a
k you
what what are they trying to do in the
ghetto huh you can't kill a
legend you see how much you
smokes no don't remember that he was
such a big
smer uh-oh uh oh oh
what stuff
inside isn't that isn't that that's yeah
that's
for that uh that's
uh that's uh
radioactive oh
that's
[Music]
y
oh [\h__\h] wait is that that's how he is
that wait
why what was he the one
driving
he tried to
[Music]
say wait why was he working there like
part-time
job
what
why
why side
[Music]
quest thank
you
literally
what
[Music]
they she was punishing
his
[Music]
become a
YouTuber stay at home forever never see
the light of day just like
me yeah I go outside a bit more buy
[Music]
groceries
n what the
[\h__\h]
fore
for
Fore
spee
fore
oh no what was K's
[Music]
reaction
foree
for how old is he supposed to be
[Music]
now
[Applause]
[Music]
55e
foree
huh
fore
yeah
m
for
[Music]
foree
for
okay hey obviously K was going to get
the
bed it's keeping
junken
imagine
the why would he do that maybe the
doctor is so
[Music]
corrupt I mean that would be an
interesting twist like ah you don't have
cancer don't worry you'll continue to be
part of this game series you're not
[Music]
dying
fore
[Music]
so
foree
fore foreign
foreign
fore
[Music]
hi where do you want to
buy what a
name here check is that what they want
me to buy here
oh oh oh
oh what are you free up to a little
secret club or something oh hey man
fancy seeing you here no nothing secret
just told M join us recently so we
thought he could give us a tour to
City how's
it anyway we're going to scope out the
anakonda shopping center to see what we
can
find well fun as that sounds it's still
a public shopping center not exactly the
type of place to go brandishing a bat
know what I mean no
no oh oh
sure oh yeah don't worry about that I
actually don't use this thing
anymore uh this thing was kind of my
trusty partner back home so I guess it's
force of habit so either way have you
whatever you do is done my business
still if you need to shape up I've got a
good shop I can recommend
it's a garage called Julie gear works up
on hoola Avenue you won't find a better
mechanic in the whole city you bring the
good s make it happen guaranteed shine
no man the job one visit and I'm sure
that batt of yours will Sparkle maybe
better
than no foing that sounds great one more
thing the place fronts and allo repair
shop they won't normally take any other
business but just say you truly sent you
and there shouldn't be an
issue thank
you k told me mind if we go check out
this garage first I want to cover all
our bases dogy let's do it let's go guys
you know what I
realized let's go in German is L skids
and it sounds so similar you basically
just have to switch out the O and the
E said let's go it's l
GES
sugy isn't that so
sugy this ain't a show dip [\h__\h]
[Music]
let's
go amazing isn't that so
fasinating you're welcome to use it from
now
on can we not do a grand liner cuz
they're all scattered Mama
M let's go no Lo
switch it switch it
around but how do I switch with him but
normally the switching buttons are
exactly the buttons
that don't get it how do I switch
enemies R to Lost Gates no l
Gates I'll sue you look at how oh ah
okay sorry I'm
stupid
did I use the wrong
one ah no cuz they're not in range wa
they're not in
range Okay Tire tumbler us the one in
the
back or not
[\h__\h] T Dum uses the one in the
front wow wow wow wow wow
wow wow wow
when do you
remember that could have gotten threee
enemies your face pisses me
[Music]
off this one I did right
though
[Music]
for
spee
spe
[Music]
was drunk
what are they still
drunk that one
time those get
emoji well then I have to get rid of a
different
one and
also that's kind of difficult if you
want me to have a
writing then it's probably just going to
be the
letters like 9 N
N this will be too easy no no
actual Wawa face or
so or we just make a honestly we have an
emote that really brings across to let's
go
bye but it's just not written on it you
guys can just uh say it yeah that
oneee
she has a mole in her
eye in both
eyes
some people have in their eyes something
like
that I think it was a bug cuz
now it's not visible and yeah it was
kind of weird not a bug but like
a thing going on with the
graphics well yeah I
guess
[Music]
for
H
okay crafting
tutorial certain weapons can be upgraded
into powerful forms imbued with special
attributes by using money and materials
most weapons that serve as a base for
these Transformations can be purchased
and storage any weapon without a special
damage type or attribute has the
potential to become stronger for
crafting if you've obtained one try
taking it over to Julie's gear Works
materials come in various forms such as
lav Stones El Stones rainbow stones and
I stones and
more
go okay uh
o
oh oh I like this
one okay okay so we're going to make uh
this I think they want us to make this
one this is me building
Furniture toing
me
yes who who the
spikes
perfect I'm not a carpenter I don't make
carp I hope so think God I don't have to
use Mass
anymore
let's
[Music]
go oh oh he could have
done only car repairs
here want to
fight
[Music]
for little
[\h__\h] oh I want to
spee Bring It
[Music]
On
L everyone has a
gun but I have a freaking
fat who brings it back to a
gunfight
nice
yes
finally
bastard yeah quick
business
K you can do
anything if anyone K you if anyone then
K can block it only kid
youee oh
what kind of relationship do you have
with the
bartender yeah you only do what he
says I'm still eating the peanut snacks
they're so
good
Don't Call Him old man he looks like
he's
20 maybe not
problem oh
okay yeah maybe 30 yeah spend money and
materials at jul gears uh to craft new
weapons and upgrade and customize old
ones make sure to stop by regularly to
keep your gear in good shape as you
patronize it the Shop's rank will
increase adding new weapons to the
selection
check what's available from your phone's
crafting app though you'll need to visit
the garage in person to actually
have oh what's you doing there been
watching maybe we can make something for
the other guys
too uh ah cabby we can make him a
cooling
wrench yeah sounds good it's plus six
like a
lot at this point at this
level I hope
so okay and
then a
oh there's nothing for
K there's nothing for K what does he use
wa what what just because he's punching
I want to give him a weapon
too you can spend medals and money to
upgrade any weapons to the max of plus
50 any weapon can be upgraded to to
match the power of a six-star
weapon upgrade vales Cara when a weapon
is used to craft a new one so don't be
afraid to upgrade the weapons you
currently have on hand additionally by
upgrading on certain levels you'll
unlock a brand slot allowing you to
customize weapons with special abilities
okay so what we can upgrade
this let's
try uh I feel like this also was a thing
in the previous
game so I think it's a bit familiar do I
just throw in
whatever
yeah should I just go straight up to
like level plus six or
so
wait now these give more
right
plus
seven can I do
that I can't
confirm
okay pretty powerful I would
say m I don't have much more materials
but we'll give him a little
upgrade
plus
one
okay didn't cost too much money but now
all my materials are
gone no I'm we're still going to the
shopping center
okay for clothes this time I
guess what are you staring at I'm not
looking at
anything I didn't even register you
there muscle
soda yeah I need more
materials as if I haven't been very very
carefully collecting stuff everywhere
what do I do with all these
herbs what you looking at what you what
you looking at what you looking at what
you looking
at I'm
[Music]
fearless be Yakuza pong bird
food okay no problem ah B rough start
rough start uhoh [\h__\h] he's going to
die stop stop stop stop stop you guys
said I would be fine I'm not
fine
[\h__\h] and I missed the
thing I'm going to
die let's run let's run let's
run
y one more time please let me go let me
go level 16 oh he's going to
attack Tomy Jaa
KO Tomy Jaa outo uhoh uhoh uhoh uhoh
okay okay oh thank God that was a
debuff Y no
no y y
y is this
impossible he can't run now cuz he's a
but but K can run come on K come
on oh my God oh God oh God oh God oh God
is there a restaurant
nearby
[Music]
says he's fine
still yeah then if you say so
ell she posed for
me uh
food oh there's the charging
station how's this
work
charge it costs [\h__\h]
money and not too
little there's H there's some food over
there
restaurant but there's
enemies it's not a
[\h__\h] I'm safe please give me food hello
I'm dying here
okay I'll just go for one thing I I
won't try to do a combo oh they look so
good I'm just going to choose the thing
that looks the best to
me
[Music]
hello is way too cheap
yeah in reality that would be probably a
bit more expensive thank you
bye-bye thank you for helping bring me
[Music]
out me I will C to
the wa I need to check how to get there
oh it's so far I think I'll take a
taxi
oops
yes I can buy bigger
batteries maybe sometime in the
future
free magazine it's
free let's sell it for 10
bucks lava
FR
[Music]
for o so much trash to pick up what the
[\h__\h] is
that that's a huge Treasure
Chest Yakuza kind of treasure CH free
keys oh but I got
eight courage pendant searches of power
dispelling fear and even the most dire
circumstances well if I don't have
anything else on me right now then I
think I'll wear it oh
yeah all right nullifies
fear you
e oh no I'm not going to eat that
cute Shaka Shak Shak Shak Shaka Shaka
Shak Shak liquid nitrogen spray let me
see if those if that's actually a
weapon Who would wear who would use that
you probably
not maybe K you no wouldn't that be cute
if we saw him attacking with
maras can you give the m to the dog I
will not do that even if I
could it's just a game
but I can't do that to a dog go even to
a virtual dog
go I was just reminded cuz I was
watching uh some video about
Nintendo's
history just reminded about that game
and virtual dogs being so precious and
like what the
[\h__\h] it actually really made you feel
connected to the
dog
so I'm also virtual guys and you
wouldn't give me a moldy Burger would
you just because because I'm virtual
just because
I'm in here in your
computer oh a wooden
board
I let's
go what is that what is
this
chicken what is this looks so
funny it looks like a toy why is it so
colorful virtual
Burger yeah as long as it's not moldy
h I will jump let go no
keep wait I got to go here what where am
I going where the [\h__\h] am I
going ah in
here I think I'm going to kill you why
why what did I do
UL ukulele boy saved me cute gorgeous
rubber gloves exclusive equipment for
housekeepers oh
I guess we also
can't
dead oh
[\h__\h] I'm scared y yo
yo he came running at me through all
that furniture and then he just goes
like yo yo yo you thought I was going to
punch you but in
reality I'll just throw some yoyo yo at
you cuz they're so threatening
justy he would probably like my Maracas
maybe he'll he'll be nicer to me if I
give those to
[Music]
him I don't need
him quick this
him uh uh well well he's gone now we can
this him
um yeah you you you're so wobbly so when
you
move so wobbly you should be in London
man you woby bastard uh I can't roast
people like that it wasn't much to
roast how do I enter this thing
where am I supposed to go in maybe from
the other
side oh no from here
may Tomy sawa's cake lesson Tomy Za's
cake
lesson tell me about it
Toma take a walk [\h__\h] oh oh no can't
measure up to my
[Music]
FL
what the [\h__\h] he's
like his hair makes me think that he's a
bird he looks like a
bird come
on
okay if it doesn't matter I'll just
break your
jump
easy maybe that's what he wants to be oh
there's two of them what the [\h__\h] they
multiplied
[Music]
I'm why are they all over the
place you got my popup parade figure
coming in threee days thank you what are
you going to do can you dress me up in
like Barbie clothes huh me
out h on
you yo I blocked three times let's
go [\h__\h] hell why do they attack so
[Music]
much
it's like a break dancer oh my God
Tommy's about to
die thanks for the
[Music]
help
[\h__\h] in the most important times
[Music]
yo I'm losing no I was going to use
maybe if I could but maybe I couldn't
anyway wow
beautiful
[Music]
I
okay oh my God that's so controversial
I'm going to record you post you on Tik
Tok and you're going to get
cancelled
what a
name G star in the Twilight movie
they're waiting for
[Music]
you look at the
bank okay uh I'm actually going to get a
drink
[Music]
here if I knew how to enter
[Applause]
I
no
h I'm not a coffee fan but uh you maybe
is oh wait this is uh not immediate
healing
[Music]
okay but the hot dogs are
cheap look at a couple
maybe even
maybe
Al oh nice
gift
okay oh so good coffee
alcohol I will never understand coffee I
understand like at least the smell is
nice to me
too
but I don't know maybe I should try
drinking it again cuz I haven't tried
for many many
years what the [\h__\h] was I going to eat
oh
yeah I will not eat the moldy Burger
I will not make anyone go through
that
smart same oh he knows where all the
past shops I let's go tell me bring us
there I want to eat all the
sweets oh are there no enemies inside
here that's nice is this
oh I can actually look
at oh my God he's walking up on each h
no not quite I thought he was actually
hitting each stair
separately ah this is a type that
doesn't just want to say hi wait I have
bir feed
actually I have the perfect thing for
you you're
welcome
Bes I'll
you better than most games yeah no
I would
agree over here he back up y'all already
so many people you don't need
backup this could be
good
he what's WR
[Music]
scared baby a
triple that's PE simulator W what
why you mean ah you mean that that one
enemy who was dressed up
the new F simulator came out right we
should play that sometime cuz I really
enjoyed the first
[Music]
one that was such an interesting choice
back then I just randomly chose beef
simulator and had so much fun with
it pretty please oh you really want it
huh what's wrong
get out of the
way do we get our HP and MP F back up
when we level
up is that what just happened
ATM yeah
okay
too oh another pawn
shop
okay here would be a clothing shop oh
shoes get some new kicks here is a
proper gear shop but apparently we're
not going there
no are you staring
at what the [\h__\h] were those
guys in the
blue you said this place was called
Anaconda shopping center it's
huge well it is the biggest shopping
mall in unol Lulu they've got pretty
much all you need we should load up on
supplies before we head into District
Drive okay cut
scene they saved me from those
guys Aloha after our last dog I realized
how I's been calling my name I've got
something fun to show you meet me by the
PC shop
no I don't want to have anything to do
with the with that guy what is it with
those
though those will probably be
interesting sujon but they don't want to
fight
oh that reminds me almost as if this
happened before they made the game have
you guys seen that uh like those news
from the the British the British piano
Guy recently I think it was pretty
recent I watched the whole
confrontation I
mean I feel
like the British guys also like
kind
[Music]
of but yeah what a weird
confront if anything I'm on team British
guy too yeah but like
still he was kind of teasing them like
he was obviously filming them them on
purpose at that point yeah he was not de
escalating
esap
[Music]
I think both sides were
weird
play the piano like a
[Music]
champ
no now they want me to become the
backup
[Music]
for they really love that color don't
they
[Music]
what oh
[\h__\h]
oh
uh
that's why I don't
need a
randomer I would say I'm
cityon is well known maybe not
yes but in other
places okay what do I have to
[Music]
do guys I'm the hero
of
seems like I don't have a
[Music]
chance
okay
I'm not really sure what what's
happening but
okay figure it
out
oh
[\h__\h] we have a
strong should be no problem my B is
totally
totally totally killed that pizza
delivery game on first try
[Music]
so let's do it how though how do I just
run what is is like an
OB finer details okay
[Music]
the 90 pizzas well I I collected them to
to uh solve the problem of world
hunger it's as easy as
that uh Anaconda Escape is what it
sounds like an escape room set within
the Anaconda shopping center your job is
to reach the goal before the enemies
reach you while completing missions
along the way M mhm you'll have exactly
6 minutes to reach your goal that's way
you first Super Chat oh happy
birthday I guess if I read that
right to your
uncle a happy birthday uh not going to
sing though back up set SEC uh one of
these missions you have planned so we've
placed laptops and containers all
throughout the mall laptops give you
quizzes to solve whereas containers need
keys or passwords to unlock that's all
these missions really are each time you
complete one your total is score
increase es which leads to a better priz
at the end oh and the C is all feature
trivia about this mall so you may want
to scope out the area before Oh no I
didn't also bear in mind that enemies
are luring all over the place so you'll
have to risk getting caught if you want
to
win maybe maybe I shouldn't play R away
then yeah you'll mainly be thrusted into
a non-lethal brawl that we not held
contractually liable for okay but wi you
incur a Time penalty a win the ducts 20
seconds from your remaining time while a
lost the ducts 40 seconds what why why
why does a wind deduct time so if you do
get caught don't give up you can still
fight your way uh to the goal as long as
there's time left in
the okay did somebody play this side
quest before it sounds rough difficult
your best bet is to play it smart and
avoid enemies at all costs as for the
enemies themselves there are two types
the runners are obviously quick on their
feet but easy to beat conversely the
wrests are slower but stronger oh it's
way easier than they make it sound
okay
okay I just ran to the end
okay okay you just went for the small
price
[Music]
okay should I study it
though I I should maybe thank you for
the
memberships hey I appreciate it okay
what kind of things uh do I have to look
at though what's going to be
important OMG trinkets ABC
Stores
aloha M
what yeah like what kind of shops there
are I
[Music]
guess I don't know man let's go to the
main
quest maybe I'll come back
later
may
maybe
good
decision yeah I don't know
man oh
oh it's
shirt must best especially made for
[Music]
him
no vacation the flowers are just you
know hell of a
[Music]
10 he looks so like Tommy what the
hell oh was that a
[Music]
secret we know the secret
code losing your starter oh my
God
uh Pokemon company look
away
oh what is this
Arena come
on looks nice oh my God these freaks
these [\h__\h]
freaks probably more legally distinct
than others
yeah
why does it got to be on the dark we
it's illegal yeah
[Music]
but go cater
go use a hardener or whatever it's
called pick no it's a me no it's it's a
catap not fire no fire is strong against
him
ah no he got his whole team wiped out
but it definitely looks weaker than the
other
[Music]
team
this is so
weird
am grass cutting
machine no I sound like the grass
cutting
machine what do you
call doesn't it sound like you're
sitting inside and it's the middle of
the day sunny day and you hear the sound
coming from outside
oh it's a lawnmower how nice somehow a
lawnmower noise is just nice to
hear sign up
no I like them I like the lawn
[Music]
sounds
what you signed us
up
why I don't know microwave sound I don't
really
know
course you
have we all have suim in our
hearts like a Japanese
comedi
God
[Music]
do I control
them here we
go okay in sujiman battles ichan will be
put to the test as a Simon trainer
pitting his team against Rivals and
commanding his sujon to attack and use
skills issue commands wisely while
keeping an eye on suon strengths and
weaknesses and you're bound to achieve
[Music]
Victory
oh
why I done
that yeah shut up let's quickly let's
get it over
with why not I'm a First Rate superon
after all I walk you through the
basics uh first step is to build up your
team strength attacking pointlessly only
exhausted suim stamina as a trainer
you've got to watch for the moment we're
ready to
go for suim can attack they must
accumulate suim power once say P gosh
reaches 10 you can give them a command
oh the rate at which your team gains SP
is determined by the active members
total speed more powerful attacks it
this main oh God more powerful attacks
require more whereas low spe attacks can
be used more frequently consider which
is best for the
[Music]
situation okay but we start with 10 okay
uh you should attack uh so that's a
[Music]
kick
no naturally great instructions on your
part kasan because I can't make my own
life decisions I need you to tell me
what to
do did you know that suim one have
different types it's a good idea to
direct us to attack suim one we've got a
type advantage over mhm
yeah
okay that takes care of the basis anyway
try commending us yourself
now
okay attacks aim Dead Ahead are stronger
while attacks on diagonal line are
weaker if you're too far away from
opponent you won't be able to attack at
all always take positioning into account
on the field and check targeting lines
to see how your attack type compares to
the enemies a red line means your attack
will be super effective a white line
indicates normal damage while a black
line wants have a type disadvantage
okay once per turn you can press square
to swap one suim place with no on the
field or in reserve suon can still
attack afterwards but swaps can't be
undone in the same turn consider the
enemy teams composition make every swap
count
okay oh we're back to 10 and that's
[Music]
nice I'll do another
one okay one
down did I just stay on the
field
okay oh n blast them with enus okay wa
come on Wawa blast them with your
enthusiasm suon naturally accumulate
moreal points as the battle progresses
and the team's enthusiasm grows
exploiting type advantages and attacking
multiple suon at once will acre more and
P the more you and your Simon care for
one another the faster the medum will
charge you pizza have Simon performs
special attacks special attacks can deal
major damage to enemies or heal sudon on
the brink of unconsciousness time them
well these powerful skills consume and
PE and your turn and empty your speed
glage
completely
okay
flaming what the
[\h__\h] when one of you Simon goes for
special attack cheer them on to give
them a boost your support efficiency is
determined by the roulette stopping on
red makes attacks hit all enemies and
greatly increases recovery for healing
skills green ures their attack strikes
forward and
[Music]
diagonally
I feel like red was the
jackpot
[Music]
M yeah it it's fun it's fine but I don't
have the energy for
this it's not a bad like side
thing but it's like that fighting arena
that we never used ever again didn't we
I think that was also that wasn't like a
dragon one
right some fighting arena that we only
once oh my
[Music]
God that wasn't I mean both probably had
something like this
right don't say his real
[Music]
name he's
addicted
craing batt
addicted he doesn't want to be
recognized
that dude though very
interesting he's worth coming back here
a few
times okay please leave me alone
[Music]
now
oh did you guys see on the community
board
yesterday I posted some Polo roids
everybody who chose number three
which I think was the
majority choose number
three did I
you wasn't
maybe alaro and unity
[Music]
chat you listen to the
guys I check
something
un CH I missed
indeed no problem I'll I'll uh get back
to you in the next but Alvaro I can't
see did you do it in the
other oh okay yeah okay it continues
here I actually I only looked at the
first
one I only look at the first stream I
look at the second stream
[Music]
too also I'm going to catch them
all
going
[Music]
okay okay don't worry guys I didn't get
there yet
so I'm going to get those polar words to
you guys no matter
what
[Music]
Justice
for
Fore fore
[Music]
speech
violer dominance okay all of these
buzzword I
understand
raid
for
Fore
spee
fore
I want to play yaku not
suim why I actually have to do
this
[Music]
what oh an
ana ana save me
hi Ana
waiters
[Music]
Anya anaon is real they
ready thank you oh yeah hey raid raid oh
oh oh raid in game raid in chat raids
are test of strength among the most
powerful of creeps sorry guys you're not
creeps if you're able to come out on top
you'll have a chance to recruit the
defeated suji
[Music]
okay bonus raids while participating in
a raid there's a chance of triggering a
bonus raid there are two types of bonus
rates reward rates
gr uh yeah I guess fight I don't
know you
reget Island
grapper just one of them okay easy oh
we're doing a normal fight though we're
not even doing a suon fight wait what's
we
electricity oh one
hit well if he's dead I can't can I
still recruit
him oh okay I
can now's your
chance you know why some suim might find
themselves impressed by kasuga strength
would hang around that after a f you can
use this opportunity to recruit them to
your sujon team to convince them to join
you'll need to make it worth the while
first put your heart into presenting
them with a sui gift then convey your
feelings with a show of sincerity the
quality of what you offer affects how
genuine your request appears so is that
coffee gift that I saw in the shop also
for
this
multier 10 out of 99 900 Oh No Maybe not
maybe it's got to be
this get shoe
box ah he'll take it he'll take
it hey what the [\h__\h] is
this oh my
God Smash and Flash level five
Douglas okay Douglas welcome to my suon
team I
[Music]
[Laughter]
guess suim recruit after Batts have
already built up substantial amount of
experience from the time in the wild
they can be of immediate help to your
party when suon seems willing to
negotiate after the fight there's little
to no reason to not recruit them
okay I skipped the famous
phrase 10 membership thank
you okay I said it
myself
get oh suim dossier is an automatically
updated list of
Munch this de is
creep great far
for Fore fore
spe
foree
[Music]
it says sub story that's why I was
thinking it's not main but you guys said
it's
main yeah skip lyrics
apparently yeah now you can ignore it
y I guess a forced forced sub story
mhm they forc me to do so many things I
want to be free in
Hawaii you really do got a thing for
trouble don't you hey it's not like a
good look looking out for it for real I
don't game forced me well at least it
seems like you had fun oh come on guys
anyway should we start heading over yeah
where were we
going now he wants to peek into stores
even
more how long are we going to be stuck
in this
mall no Sports Warehouse
okay once you enter District trap you'll
be able to unable to return to the city
or save your game for some time make
sure you'll be fully prepared on level
13 two stars plus uh we are not level 1
let's fight a little bit in here I
guess there we some
enemies right where are they now
vac where' they
[Music]
go yeah we'll buy
equipment I'm friends with
Kevin good having Kevin as your friend
always is a good
thing
okay guys don't confuse
[Music]
me
confuser nobody's
weak
okay
[Music]
uhoh guys she also have troubl blocking
so much is it just
[Music]
me all right looking hard right it's
intentionally difficult
okay
yeah yeah a lot of them have different
attack PS I feel like during a boss
fight you'll you'll have enough time to
learn it and then maybe not in the
beginning but eventually you'll probably
figure it
out but it's definitely
uhoh it's definitely
not look I used to be better at
this I don't all
day it does feel good when you block it
now for
real was deeper in the
playr but this is like basically the
same
game feel like we got to look for a
restaurant again and then do another
fight
maybe up level up level up let's go okay
but first I'll do like one or two more
fights I want to
eat
[Music]
what where am I I
here uh
uh
only this place maybe but I may have to
use my own
items
okay
okay nice look
music more oh we're actually going to
listen
in side quest again
huh I don't know that ukulele looks
really really small on
him embrace your Wild
Side
no
I don't feel like
it hey what's up
Tomo he got a pizza and a huge
soda yo yummy what a what a
shield and his pizza pants are
cute
yeah this is uh uh the back the back I
think the back
person
uhoh where the hell did Santa come from
was Santa always here crass cringle is
his
name not a y what the hell hey K got a
new new attack enemy area k impales a
line of enemies why is it always a line
with a short bladed do knife with a high
chance of making them
bleed but that takes so so
much will not use
this a
triple
I have a new AOE with itan too oh my god
let's go oh CR springle is weak to that
okay wasn't going to go for him but
[Music]
okay how the [\h__\h] is Tommy even alive
come on look a triple head shot the [\h__\h]
this game is so brutal randomly brutal
sometimes
oh up [\h__\h] I didn't press the right
thing all the damage okay what the [\h__\h]
happened yeah it's so
Random uh oh Mega swing okay
[Music]
well oh they're both weak to my weapon
cuz of the
electricity that's so
lame come
on Beast your
peers do he get from that no this is
attack and defense oh H defense lowered
okay Pizza fresh every day this will
teach you this is going to
hurt he what he got a Bend from me and
then he ate it but BOS are
[Music]
expensive you
bastard the cute lady from the store
made that Bento for me
oh my
God are you guys sure I can ever take
pink
battles doesn't look like it to
[Music]
me he went for the same guy oh cuz the
other died but he went for the same guy
three times come on get a load of this
[Music]
nah yeah I just need better gear yeah
but I still don't do so much damage and
I had my weapons upgraded just like a
little
bit you I always geted with K I always
manage to do that K
you I double
block yo it makes me so nervous when I
have to block that
[\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h]
guard
[Music]
my I have I have
no um
no peace mode
oh I didn't remember
that we do one more
[Music]
fight
we can do one more fight over
there I need
to I like them more
before ah is that I resisted because of
the
fear
easy
ah why you got to move like
that do your
wor all the enemies in them will be
around level 12 is I don't want to do
them come we can do we can do maybe
theele one I guess that's what you mean
right with sub
[Music]
story hm
escal
Chase come at
me oh yeah
pound all right I'll do the ukulele one
for now close reservation might be
soon this might be the best vacation
ever
well at least we're all now level
up so what do we got to do
here need some ukul lessons I know
someone who's good at
it for rain and shine I always be ever
at your
side
[Music]
woo
woohoo thanks for cheering thank you
thank you I know that was amazing woohoo
my next single please look forward to
it I ended up staying for the rest of
the show Life music sure is great man
I'm lucky not every day you can catch
Matt tropical performing in a place like
this oh my God yeah so true it's say
release party I hear he's going on t
course an ukulele tour maybe I'll buy
some tickets well what does a tour of
this guy look like just playing the
ukulele on a huge stage
alone so here's a big deal after all
that explain the huge
crowd is that Louis in the
back guess I got to go
to and that was an easy sub
story The End
what's happening why are they walking
like
crabs oh such crab wa
wao crab levels over
[Music]
9,000
calling me I'm so sorry for snacking so
much during
you I'm so sorry tell me if it bothers
you
guys
[Music]
thank that is so
true that is so
[Music]
true that's it didn't do
anything it so was my reward
you guys
[Music]
okay K you
Tommy what are you
doing this is not a running
machine it's
water why you got to do your workout now
here in the public this is embarrassing
come over over
here crazy boys oh you got your pants
all wet kid you look at
you now you're going to grab a cold you
already have cancer you don't want a
cold your immune system is [\h__\h] right
now trust
me I mean I don't really know a about
that stuff but still okay I'm going to
try this let me play your
game what are you staring at no I don't
want to fight them let me play the
game
oh I'll fail but let's do
it yeah I'm a
gamer Lo
SKS oh so I I I I tried to dodge
them
right uh
H just made him okay ready to make your
Anon Escape complete missions and slip
past enemies as you make a Mad Dash for
the
go that
sneeze
yeah that's e
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you for the
Super
[Music]
Chat sneezed all over the monitor no no
no it's some something
else missions can be found by accessing
the computers placed around the mall the
more you complete the better your
reward clear as many as you can in 6
minutes beiro if you get caught by the
enemy you'll have to fight them cosing
your precious time if you Hur the m and
run everywhere you're more likely to be
spotted by them walking can be a viable
strategy they're
like like how do I get past them they're
on both
sides
[Music]
um um
what
how they don't notice you if you stay
out of the vision and walk sneeze on
them I'm in a he's walking
away this is like hide and seek now no
no it's like a self
mission will they follow
me I think I'm good ah I think I'm
[Music]
good
[\h__\h] uh is the time still running right
now cuz I don't see a timer
does it just take off a set amount of
time this is fine this is
fine oh wait uh
okay oh
God
Mommy
where are these PCS
anyway oh
[\h__\h] there's so many of
them can
I
[\h__\h] so far I only had to runers
though maybe
it's you know a couple of days I have to
fight this seems impossible
otherwise
okay oh is that
it okay I
made was pretty
fun oh thank you oh this is soo oh thank
you wow thank you so much my life
changing experience one to thank you
thank you what a
blessing
see any
opportun oh
okay
we seems like we can do it more
often next time with
bikes check that shop
out hi
Roy um
uh
okay why do I got to use up all my items
here
[Music]
man let's go towards the goal we
probably have one more fight until that
point
people are so friendly if I ever why did
they switch SIDS if I ever go to
Hawaii I'll be acting like ich
B I'll wa but everybody be like hi I'll
be the most obnoxious tourist
ever no just kidding I don't have to
courage for that hi parrot he's not
saying H he's saying parot no
where's the store that I was supposed to
use down
here or is the pink leading me outside
of the
mall I feel like it's leading me outside
mall okay wait
here take a
break
aloa
[Music]
aloha the running clothes are looking
good I guess I'll buy it for everybody I
feel like we're going to find more
clothes and Equipment wherever we're
going
anyway cuz last time we also found so
much equipment in the
dungeon but okay thank you the rest is
[Music]
useless
a how to
sell thank you this place can I not sell
with her you might need to stay another
day I guess in the pawn
[Music]
shop
okay pawn shop
was hey what's up what's up H over to
you too
sir oh gift giving
upon purchasing the item you can
immediately hand it over and deepen your
relationship with the receiver no no no
I want to sell I don't want to give you
anything lady I don't even know
you or is it
for is it for
them it's only 10 bucks who would love
something like
this feel like kidu is not really about
you know getting presents
but a a watch would suit him a wrist
watch oh okay
nice let me
sell
uh reading this could impart job exp for
he y' those are the EXP Wait no that's
that's Grand blue fantasy that I'm
thinking of right now cuz we were
looking for exp books in Grand BL
fantasy I'm so
confused I'm so
[Music]
confused mixing up games in my
mind is this all pawn shop
material seems like it
okay the worms not the
worms
the key I should
keep
yeah thank you okay then
Aloha some old equipment perhaps the
hoodies oh they're only $120 now those
were no I guess those I got for
free but some of those I have to pay for
no that's PR barely any
[Music]
money okay the ones I got double I could
totally sell I would
think and the massage machine can go now
or do I still possibly can I still use
that for like upgrading it and getting
something better out of
it the keys 100 if you buy them oh my
God you can get rid of it yeah let's get
rid of it get out of here thank
youo take
[Music]
a which store
sells probably not that one maybe the
coffe again a coffee shop again want
some more food stock up on food and
stuff oh
wrong cookies Aloha you got cookies oh
they're just plain potato chips potato
chips black truffle Himalayan salt and
barbecue
wow oh they're
pretty cheap but also don't fill up much
HP but that's okay I'll get a couple of
these and a couple of
these yeah thank you for stopping by
nothing for
M should I do one more fight wait what
happened wasn't I just somewhere else I
I blinked for a
moment how did I get down in one second
I want to fight these guys play with
me rafian what happened to
you you got such long legs
today oh my God
Tall
[Music]
come
oh
you better FOC some stilts yeah crazy
have you guys ever tried walking on
stilts feel like during my school
time the kids a lot of a lot of the kids
were doing that in the in the
breaks I think during Elementary School
though it was like one of the toys you
could borrow in the a big
break I wasn't able to do that
[Music]
though another thing was that what do
you call it the
thing oh God he became small for a
moment he busts out his iron balls
okay and thing that's like a string
connected by two sticks and in the
middle you you're supposed to balance
and maybe sometimes like bounce off like
a interestingly shaped uh
thing any idea what I mean come at
what's with you I don't know how to
describe it what's wrong
scared cits yeah
why did I use the skill for this he was
almost
dead not a yo-yo no no you hold it with
both hands on one hand one stick the
other hand the other stick and it's
connected by a string and then
you yeah Diablo
Diablo yeah why the [\h__\h] is it called
Diablo
wait
yes that's what I
mean there are some kids that are really
good at that but I think I couldn't do
anything with it I don't even know I had
no chice that I was good
at is it also diao toy in English why do
they call it di because it makes here
one one slogan is
says satanistic good no a hell of a a
hell of a fun guaranteed maybe that's
what it's called
[Music]
diabo so
Random
devilish a man the good old
times you know when I was in elementary
school I loved
reading I Lov reading especially when
they made us read English
books I was really excited cuz I wanted
to flex my English
skills they made us read them during
classes together and sometimes on our
own
and we were like allowed to choose
from kind of a specific
library and I think one that I read
what's it
called what's it called Jane air is that
a is that a thing I think it's a
thing I think it's
really famous right I I like that and I
thought just by reading that book that
was so cool and so
sophisticated and all those English
books they had like a certain level on
them because they were meant to be read
by like students so they had like levels
showing their category of how difficult
the English in it was and mine the one I
chose was a bit more difficult than the
um basic ones that the most of the other
students
chose yeah oh and pride and prees was
also one that I read back then the
classics you know nothing special not a
biggy not a big please don't fight me
please don't fight
me no I really used to enjoy reading
this is not a lie
I mean it and then I also used to read a
lot of manga back in the
[Music]
day
huh there wasn't much choice in our uh
book shop book stores back
then
but yeah one of my favorite ones was
vampire night cuz I was back then I was
I was you know you know I was into those
kind of and made made my made don't want
K Sama or something like
that sometimes a person just falls out
of love with reading though yeah
yeah better than
Twilight B fornite I don't know I
mean if I were to read something like
that now I would cringe but
yeah okay let's oh wait I should
save uh wait for Roman wand around the
town
eh ah ah wait for Roman means let's go
okay will will it heal me if I go in or
do I have to heal myself
again I I I don't know maybe I did
cry you might need better gear e what I
just bought gear what else there was
nothing else I can give him some
accessories I have a toy bracelet that
boo this magic actually that's
great I have a auto heal oh
yeah eat at the
restaurant you're saying I'm still too
weak hey you what you looking at hey you
you
I no way no way think you need a last
Spight there you are you point fingers
at
[Music]
me
you want to
dance I keep on forgetting that he
automatically switches back to the the
middle fighting style even though I want
him to be in the rushing
one could just play
good RPG games often make sure you're
too strong
okay these level 10 were
easy where's the next
restaurant uh you guys said the yellow
ones it's kind of far I I guess the bar
is a
restaurant
H yeah let's fight let's fight one of
the pinkies hopefully this time I'll
survive but I should maybe heal up
first hey you there what are you looking
at not the crown
okay uh let's just have
something something that doesn't make us
drunk this looks good this
cheap
okay I'm a snacker even the game
recognizes me as a snacker it's so
true I'm a proud
snacker I I will try to be a proud
snacker I should be proud of
my I like to feed myself hey you there
okay these are only two maybe I can
handle and they're just caterpillars
what do they want to do huh what are you
going to do what you what are you going
to
do you chickening out on me I'm not
chickening out if anything I'm
phoenixing
out don't mistake me for
it
okay not so bad I'm not even giving them
a
chance [\h__\h] that was going to
block these
two One More Level would be
nice
okay monkey
man a you walked why would you walk give
me your
best no weak ah oh oh there's people
behind us too
okay okay they're
weak woo Sant I'm flying
that's poor now I thought it was only
two
[Music]
um okay this is not a
line only two people I don't know if
that's worth it especially cuz one is
almost
dead what's wrong scared try
me huh
I'll just do a normal
attack wa that killed him it was full
[Music]
health okay okay I feel I feel pretty
strong
now we're good
what do you think guys are we ready to
go inside I mean look at how how I'm
doing these these fights how I'm dealing
with
[Music]
them give me your
best
hey yeah I'm
good okay if you say so you should get
better hats and
shoes well where
where I'll check if anything's close on
the map
I'm ready okay probably pick up some
items in District 5 too
no what the [\h__\h] is this ra oh there a
ra
um I mean the mall but I didn't see I
didn't see anything in the mall I guess
ah the shoe store there was a shoe store
there indeed was a shoe
store I think on the first
floor
oh Soup Store no shoe
store
soup yumy
soup soup is
good for your
tummy what's
up looking cute today looking hella fine
today don't tell the others that I'm
flirting with
you uh no maybe was second
floor Reef
Riders iron gloves professional board
explosive sucking Psy
clone wait those are [\h__\h]
expensive 140,000 I can't afford
that value value pack
insoles golf
club and running CL oh we were in this
one though but the other things didn't
uh they weren't better than what I
had uh can I see the second floor from
here
what a hat shop upstairs what's up
going take a walk assle take a walk
[\h__\h] take a walk
[\h__\h] make a rap song out of
it blooming Maraca tribal a pearl ankle
oh [\h__\h] the
prices that's the shoe
store hello
ha oh we can only afford this it's just
plus two plus
six I don't know if I should get it for
everybody you think it's worth thank you
let's look at the the hats
first before I get more of
those what those start some
loers oh [\h__\h] some designer things
man here straw hat and ha mine hat and a
trick
hat probably can only afford the straw
hat maybe I'll buy them for everybody if
it's a good
Bo what what is the advantage again like
making friends with these
people oh he didn't like
me
Aloha I put on my straw head
too to match with the gang okay these
These are better upgrades
indeed these are
significant and I'm almost out of money
but now now we're going
in what besties
no she answer
[Music]
take a
bre we good
now oh there's stairs here
too what is this place no it's still the
same no where are we what the hell
time
look I just went through the
Matrix oh wait there's a lot of junk
here
H 25 cent I mean with the little amount
of money I have right now this is quite
a bit oh bronze plate nice wait a
treasure chest woo please be something I
didn't
F design
earrings okay who could want that kill
you plus 20
defense yo that's actually
amazing that's where she
is I feel like we probably couldn't do
any another uh upgrades
now yeah get a
quick
Aloha yum yum yum yum yum oh those are
to
go rainbow Bagel that looks like cotton
candy oh 200 that's that's quite a lot
maybe no thank you maybe when I have
more
H this
one why do I piss you off I just
I'm sorry why do you hate tourist so
much so
threatening oh Aloha oh why so
scary
yumy Boogie wogie Tomahawk
steak steak guys steak you love steak
don't you yo look at the prices though
I'm I I I I'm not so hungry today I'll
go for for a
salad I I'm fine with just the salad
things yeah we're sharing one salad yeah
yeah yeah the moment when you walk into
a restaurant and you sit down and and
you didn't realize it would be so
expensive until you your hand at the
menu and then you don't want to thanks
very
much embarrass yourself and you just you
just you say I'm not so hungry yeah I'm
only ordering so little cuz I'm I'm
really full I already ate I don't know
what I'm doing here to be
honest I still
really look a lot at like prices and
don't want to spend too much money on
food and
stuff I guess I'm still
pretty what's the word
what are you
staring
Fugal air gun wa what I wouldn't say
Frugal that's such a nice way to say
it she no
well like I don't know I invite um
people yeah and then then I see the bill
and I'm like damn it maybe I shouldn't
have invited
them
hey
now we go for real for real I want to
make some progress today
[Music]
please I wanted to save some money yeah
I I
really want
to be careful with
that feel like I spent a lot of
money
in the past
months and so I've been more
careful hey the guys are back the
caterpillars are
back how much until the next
level where's the
EXP did I not show it
here
oh we
still ah ah he's close he needs one more
fight n we'll get it
inside let's
go safe ah
[\h__\h] ah it's
okay it's okay
they opposite
right
h
you really got to be careful as a
tourist where are you
[Music]
wondering none of your
business don't say
it
well good
luad what's the hold up get this thing
open already who the [\h__\h] are they just
some Japanese tourists with more money
than sense said they want to see a
different side of
Hawaii come on on not like you've got
anything to hide in there right oh I'm
sure
the it's just a tourist uh
tour touring
[Music]
the
hello hi
hi
um Tommy Tommy's me look at how Tommy
walks that's me that's
me why I'm so
ter act
natural this is my my territory I belong
here on the left on the
left middle
left
now you guys weren't looking for the
pineapple
em
for such a
paradise pineapp and
pineapples
she a lady and I don't see a single
lady shouldn't be too hard to find one
lady she will stick out
we can probably smell her cuz she smells
better
probably hey she looks like did you see
a Japanese woman come through here goes
by
Japanese I actually might know something
about
that what you got few days ago some guys
got into a scuffle over in West block
apparently a woman showed up out of the
blue
not every day you see a little Asian
cutie like her in a dump like District 5
anyway she was all by herself with
nowhere to stay and didn't have a mind
to bring a tent as you can guess a fight
broke out real quick over who got dibs
in that one H who'd the gal end up
staying with don't know wasn't there to
see the
ma' best bet is to ask around West
block wow thank you for the Super Chat
both of
you let's
go why do I
get no where
superat are they silencing
you
what's going on are they silencing you
[Music]
too they have a gun to your
head I'll I'll save
you they have them hidden in the Fifth
District
probably I'll find both of
you if we hang right here we'll end up
in what they call West
block
I know I know I know it all it is known
ah motion also needs
help ah they all need help okay we got
to hurry oh my God there's pineapples
maybe the pineapples are a hint a clue
to where I can find my chickens from
what our friends had someone day I won
the fight for chck as to who that's for
you to figure out
N I thought you wer supposed to be our
guy
you think I'm bad people in West block
are even worse I try to avoid them
whenever I can besides what's a trip
without a few fun
surprises fine
whatever it's okay chickens it's okay
just stay calm I'm here for you can you
can you sense me just act normal just
don't don't suddenly make any rash
movements
just looking
around another another one they took
another one from us we can't forgive
them oh pound
Maids yeah wrong wrong
Cheetos we've learned
that
uh I know I see The Pink Spot but I'm
just having some
issues hey
move chicken not in
here is
it the spot the it's it's
uh
you
n hey there do you know a chicken named
unknown
unknown this this guy's trashed man I
know oh oh the girl I haven't seen a
babe like that in ages
oh I got knocked out real
quick yeah we heard about the brawl who
came out on top how should I know I
didn't give a rip once I lost so you
don't have any clue as to who it might
have been uhhuh you're a babe
yeah look bunny I ain't a fan of all
these questions you
dig look just W us a little K son can
you k can you spare some
change I pocket money from our daddy
here get yourself another cold one on
us try a d working out over
there oh
yeah damn look at the size of him good
chance he won the Battle
Royale let's see what he has to say
sorry about the money your son I'll I'll
make sure to it back it was necessary
I'll just put it on my tab with a DI
DOI
okay n chickens if this is who I have to
fight to save you guys I'm I'm not sure
if I can do it so I'll say my goodbyes
now goodbye
was nice knowing you um but uh I have to
choose my battles
wisely great great this one's a charmer
too was that oh I meant uh you we're
looking for a woman named Cho you know
where she might be who's asking listen
I'm sure we don't have to tell you that
surviving out here is about brains
what so what's your intuition telling
you is fighting us really the right
call what do you want to know like we
said we're trying to find a woman named
chos a fight broke out over here right
over her we need to know where she ended
up then you're going to want Jose
Jose so he's a big winner huh where is
his T hey watch it cocky had like that
will kill
you
K thanks K thought we were screwed for a
sec and I would have been on you for
real you really pushed the guy's buttons
but I'm glad we're all right wait to
keep things cool like usual cuy
son just be glad he was understanding
now let's go
find Jose Jose Jose Jose and the dot is
still here
is you
Jose oh deny and those sharp
eyes couldn't help but over here you're
looking for her tent right was got
everyone jealous these days he's been
counting that courting that little lady
you
know I'm saying those two are a thing
now he he he why is he laughing what's
so
funny oh he did do his brag about her
keeps saying he's going to marry her and
have kids the whole nine
yards T all the way at the end with the
deck chair
thanks he's got like a whole porch to
him with that chair nice if you plan to
speak with him i' suggest you watch your
back he's
quirky got what's the
about rad welcome welcome to the
membership nice to have
you
okay oh you weren't there before are you
Jose doesn't look quirky to me well the
belly is quirky
your
girl
for
Fore
no want to steal back the passport
please
[Music]
listen
not that easy here hey boys
oh hey
boys okay of thiss get rid of these CLS
okay
as
if
wow well yeah we
did
he's
fine he still got
it Tommy te a Tommy is so relatable
Jose
Henderson oh oh that was out of
nowhere
hey so we did immediately go for a boss
fight and I can't [\h__\h]
block two
people but what
30d I at least like to hit the boss with
that but I can't so I'll go for
something
else actually I'll go for the gr
liner
yeah
yeah I [\h__\h] did
it okay now the essence of dagger is
also an area what you on uh it's also
line
[Music]
okay why would you move so
much
[Music]
okay okay it that man is
beepy you're wasting your he got quite a
shield on his
tummy do your
worst not
oh
okay not as dangerous as I
F what what the [\h__\h] stamina ah no what
I say
[Music]
I
need he back get back you little [\h__\h]
not
fair sorry
Tommy you good he's
[Music]
good why can't I not BL what the [\h__\h]
why is my timing so
bad you give that back right
now
[Music]
yeah don't drink it don't drink it don't
drink
it that won't work right that won't do
AOE cuz now they're gone
this is this close
enough
[\h__\h] now he's a little bit gone
again I say it says proximity for
him sure that
work oh well that was good
[Music]
too easy fight
easy you don't deserve
her
keep the woman to me actually I don't
even want the woman I just want the
passport but at the same time we might
as well rescue her from the hands of you
[Music]
stinky two level UPS oo
nice now we are the recommended level
for this
[Music]
place
just give honest advice
[Music]
advice the [\h__\h] why would you say that
first
thank you for the
membership
welcome of course she did she is not a
woman you
should protect your quite well
she's fine
probably she's strong she knows what
she's
doing
[Music]
for Anthony do you want to buy it for
those 50 bucks I'll give it to
you sound like you would like
one
you guys know I once
received fan
present
dad was like a reference to my Yakuza
playr legit bad but like out of uh foam
so it's like soft but still soft as
softer than
wood but you
like and it had like wire around it and
some
sckers I didn't know where to put it I
put it in
my in my umbrella
stand and then I would forget about it
and just recently I realized when I had
like like basically basically like a
stranger you know like working workers
come over
realized at that moment I just saw it
randomly in the corner of my eye was
like
oh I wonder all these people who came
into my place until now are thinking
about the
bat no that's not what I found that's
not what I
meant that's a different
thing
about but yeah now I put it
away cuz I I don't want people wondering
I mean okay actually no you know what
maybe it's actually a good intim
intimidation
technique having a bat
there maybe will keep people from I
don't know that I I don't think that
would ever happen but you know like
imagine someone being like ah this girl
she lives on her own she lives alone
she's um you know easy to take advantage
off and maybe break into an apartment or
something like that but when I have a
bat right at the
entrance maybe they would instead say oh
don't don't break into her apartment
she's dangerous she she's like she has
trouble written on her forehead she got
a bat right at her entrance with some
wire around it they wouldn't know it's
made out of foam cuz they didn't lift it
so h
it's embarrassing we're going down party
of four the boss give you the okay don't
give me that [\h__\h] you want me to take
you out of here in
cuffs K who sleeps with one eye
open recently I've been sleeping really
bad
mostly because I've been having so many
weird nightmares that maybe don't seem
like a clear nightmare
immediately but it's really like
stressful
scenarios this night too and last night
too yeah so
weird although in one of those dreams
you guys showed up there was only like a
small part not necessarily a stressful
part but like I was like sitting down in
a restaurant and the whole table was
full of like fans like you guys nothing
just a bit of sightseeing but that was
the special part sightseers what else
okay hold on you even run this by the
boss do me a solid won't you I promise
we'll
behave yeah you're in my
dreams huh
behavior only gets you so
far don't get cocky don't get it
twisted it was kind of like a I
shouldn't be here moment you know oh
it's the
mall
what what's that what where this no more
what Shing
CER
what
you and in the way was kind
stress cuz it was like
yeah cuz you guys were aware and I was
aware it's like
[\h__\h] what's up his nose oh it's makeup
oh no it's
masks but again that still wasn't the
main part of
[Music]
the
for
they do this kind of
like show Bing in the middle of a
shopping
[Music]
center
oh it's not the same
sentence
underground copy okay but what are these
people they look like normal
people
for
foree
kind of a weird system I feel like you
wouldn't fashion show for
[Music]
that
makeal
their own special
way
so
well why had the stor created if they're
going to sell it
upstairs
right
is one of the
models yeah
weird
oh Roman hey who you got there with you
oh just a side job really nothing big
side job we're a side job we the main
quest what's going on why'd you shut
everything
down yeah didn't want to stain the
merchandise stain it how
exactly
a
Luna you really thought you could bring
in Outsiders to the core of our
operation Vendo
Vendo uhoh it's last Jun CL
time
oh Mama Mia I think it you're no
ordinary
tourists now start
talking would you rather spill your guts
for
for oh they know they
know holy
[\h__\h] holy [\h__\h] don't mess with me they
scar me for real like the way they kill
people is so brutal I don't think I've
seen something more brutal in the Yakuza
games
okay this is a line let's see is there
any good looking line here oh my God
stop what guys let's go here this this
this
um this looks
[Music]
gooded that was good that was
good kind of [\h__\h]
extreme I know I only played free but
isn't this
extreme feel like
stream U
Tire he's in the bad position
here maybe
him no I'm try might get free
people yeah now now you get closer yeah
okay Free
People good good good good
good
right
I'm on
[Music]
you oh he's even weak to it I'll do it
I'll do it only two
people
okay I
defeated okay I'm serious
here he's bleeding per well no
[Music]
surprise you probably don't know anymore
who's blooded at this point hry up
[Music]
Tommy [\h__\h] I need to block that
[\h__\h] assistance using R1 oh yeah right
uh let's go doesn't work sure taking
your time
is
it h up your timing oh know I'm
trying it's going to be e one oh yeah
yeah yeah
[Music]
okay let
taking oh
[\h__\h] to Hur on you I'm guess
come on I don't have the
money I'm gross taking your
time uh I don't know if I need to use a
skill to take him down it looks like he
doesn't have much HP
but stop
moving let's
go well I'll try
it okay may have been unnecessary but
you
know he has to heal
himself urgently maybe a tuna
sandwich yeah boss down didn't seem much
like a
boss I swear a pressed at a good time
though come on that one was bad though I
I admit
it I need to do it early I press it
always the moment it hits me [\h__\h] and
now too
[Music]
early yeah come here you [\h__\h] bastard
you guys are so
[\h__\h] crazy
[Music]
dudes the underground is so
scary nice damage over
100 good stuff good
stuff
don't hurt him he got
cancer have some mercy
man no respect for the elderly and no
respect for the
sick got respect to anybody at
all doesn't seem so I did it I did it
they seemed so
scared I have only three more three more
peanut FPS left
but I have another full B don't worry I
won't open
it that much if you think about
it second group okay Lo
K I'll bury you
I did not get
healed kind of
[Music]
rude
okay yo not
bad
wow do your
worst let's go if he's stunned how how
long will he be stunned
maybe I'll do this
instead Tomy is the only one nice that
has some mpu a good amount of MP still
St okay a that's pretty
op
Tomy Tommy sometimes is weak but now
he's really rocking it he's being really
useful whenever he has something that's
effective then he's the king
wasy they went easy on me though sending
me only four
people that were obviously
weaker rank up rank up scrap down
another new skill this time is
water
interesting
[Music]
say is in some big [\h__\h] I think
luxurious belt that sounds
[Music]
good let's
see ah Max MP increases by 10 I'll take
it ah he still only has one accessory
then you'll get the courage pendant
which which Tommy really needs and it's
not supposed to be a roast I feel like
you know I want I want to give him more
courage he's so relatable what there's
nothing wrong with not having courage
try
me like how how can you have courage in
this situation
man let's go scrub
Down Show what you got lowering their
resist electricity do
what better call
it okay I'll take
you
easy you
want easy
easy come on
a [\h__\h] nice Tommy thanks for making up
on me missing the
button
look
okay and you get the bat
congratulations so
lucky
rank
up easy so far the hell do you want I've
leveled enough to PA
off you look like you need to be
broken eyes on
oh ah actually right now they would have
been in the perfect position for like a
line
attack bad
oh
a actually they don't look like they
need to be
broken that chicken what what's wrong
with
chicken it's time we teach the world
that being a chicken is something to be
proud
of not something to be insulted
with
get him while he's still down no
mercy uh let me heal though a little
[Music]
bit some potato
and definitely
some it's more yeah yeah oh wait we
don't even have to go there oh no we
have to but
top light 300
HP you serious that's a good item you're
going to regret
this
[\h__\h]
why can't block that why it's been dying
again okay gr
liner
I go but I have to use the
background I think it's got all free
knock your lights
out look at this little piss
baby
yeah I was hoping that maybe it would
get the ones around me
but he Spa
nah okay maybe I
should oh yeah thank you for going to
Contin came
[Music]
over got to love those sandwiches my
life
[Music]
saers what an amazing healing oh yeah we
haven't used it yet
[Music]
M but that uses mp2
so I'm fine for
[Music]
now maybe some potato
chips
truffle how
sophisticated I don't even like
truffle
you guys like
truffle truffle on
[\h__\h] running
shoes never had it drle Mayo is
[Music]
nice uh oh actually shoes are perfect
cuz we only bought new shoes for
Tommy I appreciate that
see I knew we were going to get some
cool
stuff I read it correctly the
future
[Music]
okay these guys look tough nah they
don't look any tougher than the other
ones I'll help you
resue yeah same you're same
this time I got AOE out of
[Music]
it now we're going to do a
tumbler come
on good old
Tumblr you think I'm
stupid
oh yeah I like fighting in smaller uh
rooms oh come
on the
shotgun
no come at me oh my God
I'm
no in the smaller rounds I feel like
it's easier to get them like together in
a
line get some AOE from the brawling
fight style so that's pretty
convenient yeah I kind of saw that
coming that you couldn't take him down
that's okay Tommy don't feel
bad don't feel bad because I'm going to
I'm going to use this start with
you oh nice even better than I
thought
that's not what spray and prey
means
doesn't Tommy this time you get to
finish
it so happy level
up
oh no oh
no I I knew I was thinking he's going to
faint sometime soon for the dramatic
effect not saying that he's doing it for
the drama but the script is doing it for
the
drama it's time for us to add Cheeto to
our team and replace you again yes oh no
we got to
run
no
no are we playing the stealth game again
we should just hide under a box there's
so many boxes here just a box where'
they go they're gone theyve got to be in
here find
them
[\h__\h] just take it down
silently slice his fruit slice his
fruit that go down silently hey what are
you doing let's
move
right damn it missed your
chance
I can't believe it the hero that's
like been through
so there she
is
H
say you little
[\h__\h] we giving her Chan okay after all
that what a
[Music]
Savage Oh you guys like her
huh
[Music]
don't trust her don't fall for
it
[Music]
Tommy
for the mother right the mother the
mother don't worry don't worry I
got I got it I got
it I've connected the
dots sure I can tell you sorry they
didn't have enough budget to voice these
lines even though it's main story uh
let's take a break first you went for a
lot to get here are you going to heal me
please
do what are you
after what's your problem don't give me
that look I'm just trying to be
considerate yeah tell me she's probably
right let's call it for a bit I'm pretty
tired if you say so hey looks like
there's all sorts of useful stuff in
here let me know when you're ready to
move on all
right I didn't want to say um I find
it very fascinating and dope that I
don't know how to say it really but you
know how kidu has been the protagonist
for like so many Yakuza games and like
he built this whole Legacy as a as a
game
character and with Yakuza they're
building a huge story line that's all so
connected and
intertwined really really cool on its
own and then
they make him feel so vulnerable and so
real by
giving
him like an illness like
that and making you legit worried that
he'll die I don't know if they'll
actually go through that that would be
insane
but yeah I feel like it it makes this
character K you so much
deeper and like every character like all
our
connections man it's crazy how deep this
goes
yeah and also how they age so much like
in other games you even if there's a a
sequel you don't really recognize much
aging you don't witness it that much it
doesn't come up anyway mostly but it
plays a big role in also like the
conversations they have and in their
looks and in the experiences they gather
and now with stuff like this like you
get older and you get
ill and his hair gets
gray yeah
so that's so fascinating to me cuz
that's so rare to see something like
this in other
games
okay this was heing
okay okay okay I'm ready to
go most of us probably thought it was
awake yeah I just thought he dyed his
hair cuz I didn't even notice that
there's some white hair on his beard as
well I just thought he was being cool I
just I didn't even know it was him I
didn't even look
closely I didn't even close look closely
I didn't realize that K would be in the
game
[Music]
foree
for nice
time
pretty he would probably believe
this
H I guess
so
fore spee
fore okay
for
forei
yese
fore
foree
for
nice
for she not getting pocket
money
[Music]
speech
foreign
e
oh okay well I think I mean there's
certainly enough Rich families who spoil
their kids and give them a [\h__\h] ton of
pocket money even if they're adults so
doesn't know where
Supply and what the hell do the B do
want with you why did we uh take a break
in cut
scene yeah
H what chatty
well
fore
for who
Mommy
foree
spee
foreign
for
fore
[Music]
speee
for
Fore
[Music]
fore
fore for
foree
spee
fore
KAS
[Music]
for I ate like half of my sandwich the
rest I'll eat in another
long cut
scene yeah nice talk but get me my
passport back
Willam wait she's
not she's not going to fight with us
yet we need to go off oh
oopsie wait or is
she no she's legit not joining yet okay
she'll probably join like we'll get into
a fight and she'll be like oh I'll help
you because we're like losing
it wait what wait what where is she
what oh this
wayo Cheeto Cheeto I need to tell you CH
you have no idea I met another Cheeto I
thought it was you and it was so funny
because it was absolutely not you
and and she pounded me I mean she ground
pounded me
all right anyway never mind so John my
my such a
gentleman show us what you
got unfortunately I'm not really the
damsel and distress
type you going no fight too of course he
is I'm pretty quick on my feet you know
trust me I won't hold you
back ah she got like the same stance as
k she also going to just be a fist
fighter let's see what you got
then oh there's no
running she fights
too everybody in Yakuza taking your
time now her F now her hands are like
open so maybe she does like cut out
there oh what the hell palm tree post is
that yoga she goes limus up with a
modified
hastasana the [\h__\h] is that is that yoga
increasing her attack and Agility
Grant appla execution of one of ballet's
most challenging leaps oh damages an
enemy and applies your weapons
attributes she's a we fit
trainer Sip and share tody gossip as
chetos recovers her and her allies h
apore bringing years of te strict ballay
training to the battlefield damages an
enemy and applies your okay so her thing
is ballet maybe we'll get her ballet
shoes as her
weapon her her indelible interest in the
fashion industry cheo's runway walk has
a high chance of charmer
enemy all
right very ladylike
attacks one enemy one
enemy Ally area self only enemy
area harm not
all
beautiful wow the Elegance the
[Music]
charm what a
queen hurry up I I guess you could count
theay now as
a
fighting sport fight sport sport fight
spite sport spite
for
fight what fight sport fighting sport
fighting sport like karate is on the
same level
yeah a martial art that's what I
mean ballet is martial arts did you not
know did you not
know
sorry I screamed like a lady cuz I am a
lady
I need to get good let's see her normal
attack I definitely broke his guards and
maybe also his spine Maybe every single
bone in his
body and almost
dead okay come
on okay at least one thing I blocked one
thing
Mama everybody bully the [\h__\h] out of him
yeah damn Tommy I didn't think you could
do it
back probably helped
there
app does CH DOA have any gear now
probably not
huh what what what are you doing D no
don't press it don't press it don't push
the
button he didn't he just stared at it h
no maybe he did push it
maybe he
did he flipped the security system looks
like those lasers mean business we'll
keep pushing through just be careful not
to touch them all right pay close
attention to how they're moving we're
going to have to time this just right
yeah no problem let's go go let's go
let's go let's go little
kids we're four people
finally uh
oopsie no
uh now I would like to check ah she does
come with equipment oh chanto
so oh but I have no accessory for her
sad Sports
Cher okay but the rest is not
bad
okay
and do only I have to go through it
safely oh no they're
fine well that really was barely a
problem oh okay but this is more
interesting
I them
up I like this we're like a spy
now
a mhm
mhm what happens if I do touch it makes
me want to touch
it would be
proud
come okay let's get the
item
nice but I didn't want I wasn't going to
walk
over sorry but now we know what happens
and it's not too
bad puss he moves like a freaking
idiot
okay right
side I guess the right side would be
open oh now the middle was kind of
open okay I'm going oh it
worked I thought it would hurt me that's
a good defense accessory oh was that an
accessory that I could give to her
yes o okay
nice
what that one kind of
sucks no let me oh let me me
through I made it that didn't look like
it would let me go through but it it
worked it
worked not a
little
easy okay oh
hi the hell do you want let me uce you
guys to my lady my new party
member the Beautiful the wonderful the
fascinating
Cheo that's biry I'm put the hurt on
you you better call it
quick it
amazing ah she's going to get that like
care take a roll or whatever where she
can probably use those uh those gloves
that we got
right
teamwork not the buster
one equally strong wrong though better
call it essence of
the no I don't want to I don't want to
use it
yet
good one
team let's have some nice burgers after
this we deserve
it Burgers but Hawai burgers with a
slice of
pineapple because why not it's
amazing
wh
out what the [\h__\h]
preferably with out what oh my
God ooh ooh can only reach it from the
other side
huh oh there's some dudes there
can I
go a St King yo hi guys what you looking
at what you looking at what you what you
looking at I'll bury
you Yakuza scary Yakuza didn't make this
the Barracuda probably made this
right Whata just occupying it and it's
you know part of the thing they build
for you know the this like whole
structure hurry up let's
go you want some of
this
man that one inflicted
Co think he met the
game
[Applause]
woo yeah I saw the new
song I saw all of
[Music]
them my first impression of the main
track uh was like I don't like it you
know easy
because like it doesn't
really
doesn't really show off any of their
singing skills it's just like you know
hip-hop or whatever I don't know what
that's supposed to
be and it just feels like you know a
trendy thing that they wanted to do but
they're dancing
and Jon
especially
extremely amazing and the music video
and the outfits and the C phography
everything's like of course top
n now the first time I heard the song I
was like I don't like this but then of
course it stayed in my brain
so get I just want to see Chan dance you
know she's hot and I like smart more
[Music]
baby cuz that that one has a tropical
vibe
and again the dance is uh very
capturing and then the last one I forgot
the title uh but ah swan song swans song
has also been in my brain actually like
I like smart the most but swans song and
easy have been in my brain this whole
time yes SW song's pretty cool too
did you see twice this new song yeah I
saw also like a video of them performing
on a on a American News show the today
today
[Music]
show but the audio was [\h__\h] when they
sang
um I got
you I got
[Music]
you
that song is so
[Music]
nice
difficult music video makes me emotional
yeah cyber
choker
no they never miss I mean the new
song it's not a bad song but not as much
as a banger and previous songs I would
say okay
nice yeah kind of forgettable not going
to
lie I'm so glad somebody here relates to
my K-pop conversation thank
you you can just kind of like walk
through this in the wobbly line very
wobbly but this is a good wobbly line we
like it El squigle
yeah a couple K of Pop K of pop what K
of
Pops wobbly lasers dangerous sounds
dangerous oh my God there's even
more
uh you look like James Bond to you what
the
[\h__\h]
uh
there
n
okay a [\h__\h] I ran too fast through it I
bed into it
damn it almost had a perfect
run woo that one comes back fast hi guys
what's up how you doing I'll take you
down if you want to talk about
vicha vicha can I just say like I really
was unhappy with the
lineup like I just I just can't agree
with the lineup I think like some of the
girls I was happy that they were in but
they I thought they were missing some
girls there that should have been
in um and then also like I I like their
song the debut
song but I don't know like they're
supposed okay just to explain it's a
K-Pop group but they're
American and they're supposed to like
mostly do their job in America you know
promote in America they're like America
or like na based or like International
based but they produced by k-p agency a
very big famous
one yeah did you want Dina to get in
[\h__\h] yeah man I follow her socials too
now I love the song she dropped right
after but yeah so I wasn't happy with it
and I do like the
song year yeah um have it in my head the
whole time but I do think like for them
wanting to you know have an American
audience mostly rather than Asian one
like Western rather than
Asian I I think the lineup and the song
like the song is like kitty pop
basically and and I don't know if that's
like you know like I see them performing
it's super cute and all it's like really
great but like is this how you capture
Western audience I don't know you should
have gone for something like like Fifth
Harmony I I don't care about them but
you know and they look so young too they
have like literally like what
14-year-old Haley in there
so with the group overall being so young
and the song sounding like kids
pop it's just like I feel like this
would work well in
Asia uh or in in the western audience in
a more Niche audience but if you want
them to be like really
big in the western sphere then I feel
like currently what they're going for is
not a good
strategy it's not going to capture
anyone outside the the
current hop fan base that you have
automatically yeah
no idea what I'm talking about that's
fine yeah like I I I love the song you
know and I think the outfits are cute
The Styling is cute and you know I mean
I wasn't happy with the lineup but you
know
whatever um I get what they're doing but
I think it doesn't work for the Western
Market you
know he's managing too many girl groups
right now yeah cuz girl groups work
better for
him
like in other
agencies I don't know much about male
groups but from what I've
witnessed just that I think
jyp male groups don't sell so well but
in other of the the other big agencies
they have no
problem bigger male
groups
[Music]
that's the twice
song a nice really meaningful sweet song
that says I got you I'm here for
you my favorite member from
twice do I have a favorite member
actually that's so hard to
[Music]
say I think I don't have a favorite yeah
probably talked about this before I like
naon I like dasun I like Momo I like
[Music]
GI no I can't pick a favorite
though uh what was I doing are we ready
to go it seems like we're going into a
bus
fight that's half of them no not
quite oh now we're in the real one or
still in the in the fake one still the
fake one
huh
yeah some of these uh late night shows
have been featuring twice and some other
big groups black
pink
oh oh it's our Runway War Welcome to our
impro and we going to do a walk now
let's get this show on the
road first up we got an all access look
at our newest collection oh are they not
going to beat us up oh I think they're
going to beat us up uh they're walking
nicely though that it's not just hot
it's to Die For What the
[\h__\h] I'm getting mixed feelings mixed
Vibes what do you want from me do you
want me to walk or do you want me to
fight anyway let's fight cat we kind of
I kind of have to do it here we're on
the catwalk how can I not use this what
a it will barely get anyone n not worth
it I'll just I'll just show you my
B beautiful oh oh they fell into the
water and they all died you better call
it go why so
weak why so weak what the
hell oh he didn't die immediately
okay it's just a normal hit
though happy for
years
[Music]
y Bo baby a
triple pass
[Music]
BR up next a special yes for you our
prized auto win do I get to fight you at
the end though I want
to
[Music]
Edy leg move is that some kind of Tik
Tok dance do your Works teach me sure
taking your
time you think your
wor m
[Music]
yeah don't like it don't like it at
all nice hit didn't hit anyone around
you but still pretty clean I like it you
can't handle
this you think
they're all way to that
okay I would have been
dead
no normally I always get that one down
[Music]
clean
don't worry K is here to clean the floor
up nice oh don't fall down don't fall
[Music]
down oh he's guarding eyes will be
broken
and now the grand finale put your hands
together for our Top Model extraordin
there
okay you
too yes let's go k time's over boys and
girls say your prayers amen I was hoping
for fighting you I'm excited for
that H la
la thank you for coming
closer
ni they're already such a sweet
couple a come on could have could have
done one more
hit don't go away
[Music]
overall this dungeon this whole thing
wasn't too bad was pretty easy thank God
I
level now we got a full party member
we're
Invincible size is up this pray oh
no we still have a bit left to go yeah
are sure but I think I think we're good
nice
nice oh his name is
Malone Malon po
Malon
[Music]
9 bons
get will not be enough to lift you up
you probably need
9,000
especially on you
I that big
hammer
yeah just normal we'll
do depends on the size of the
balloons yeah I mean an air balloon is a
different
story oh he's weak to water let's break
his
jaw am so
excited oh why Tommy why you got to stay
so close to him danger danger Zone
Danger
[Music]
Zone maybe she can finish
it with style
W what a woman what a
woman think we've all fallen for
her wish we had that level of
Grace it's unachievable for us we are
just low
lives compared to
her fancy escalator
not
disco Poker
Room
oh different Vibes than expected
wow this one's
real
on the beach
side thank you for the
bra
Al looks nice does this place exist in
Hawai for
real
for maybe different
[Music]
name for
real could be in
there let's climb
outside on the walls in the
windows let's become
Godzilla here she is hey it's them the
guys who are stirring up [\h__\h]
underground um where's the stuff anyway
hello he yo hey yo man [\h__\h] that don't
let any of these [\h__\h] leave hey yo
hey yo man [\h__\h] that
I'm happy there's some English though at
least some of it to keep the the alive a
little
bit
aick
amazing why didn't they hire me if they
needed their English
voice I like to swear too it's like my
specialty what a chicken
what move like a little bit to the left
a little bit to the right
dude come
on otherwise I'll do this
way wait did I choose the
wrong oh right I should have chosen the
one behind right [\h__\h] messed it up again
but he did get some damage
anyway I was afraid to swear
once really when was I ever able to even
hold it
[Music]
back
maybe show me what you
[Music]
got
really yeah well wanted to leave a good
[Music]
impression but I never had a
chance I know there's some people who
legit don't want to listen to streamers
swear too
much but I guess that will never be my
audience I hope to make up for that
maybe there's some viewers who who
exclusively want to listen to people who
swear and can't listen to people who who
are too much holding
back we ENT the Next
Room didn't know that was
allowed
the more swearing the
better you and call are my OES yeah yeah
I
see I don't know if that's edgy
but I can't help it I'm a very emotional
person and I often feel like my English
vocabulary like I I understand a lot of
words but like spontaneously in the
middle of a
conversation I
can't give that much variety
ooh in language in
vocabulary so
yeah not saying that my my my swearing
is helping with that not at all that's
like all I can think
of oh hold up sorry won't
help sorry I just course we're staying
in the hotel why are you picking a fight
with
us just here for a good
time you too
right swear are German swears too
they're also
versatile can I go behind
[Music]
you it martial art you think I'm see I
know the word but in the moment I I I
forget so many words an unusual amount
of words I
forget
ahma swears no no I don't think I ever
heard her swear no she's a sophisticated
elegant lady you
know hurry up let's
go
yeah pretty professional
yeah I'm excited to go to my next Japan
trip I'll see so many so many like
everybody whole life
people
I'll see it I'll
[Music]
see Secret side
hallway uh-huh
oh
oh nice
okay yeah March March March March
March it's almost
March almost the
month for whole
life
now that you say
it but why would you say that
now yeah most likely
anyway
huh
it's just going to be empty
maybe yeah
jackpot was that
reaction huh
s
Pious now she's really confusing me
now here
here what I I think she's on my side
though no no no there's a secret secret
path for
sure but what was that with the elevator
there's another
elevator how could you forget
this how would you forget this
one like if this is the path you
wouldn't forget that and go with a
normal elevator
she's testing him she's testing
them testing us testing us for
what what do we need to
prove I that we would go even if she
like hints at you know why what are
those Mind Games you seriously P me
sorry won't
help
I
sorry I'm always using this attack this
kind of like a [\h__\h] I chose the one who
doesn't have a weakness of
it oh that was still good that was still
very
good I like
this your name is NY
as long as it works as it works it
works oh there was one right behind me
too that's the problem with these small
rooms you don't see like where is use a
track of
it
nice oh no
lucky
I'm out of MP
finally but she has electricity in her
fingertips as long as there's no like
saving spot
here then there's no boss but a cut
scene anyway I did feel like something
was off that door was not a normal
door
o oh [\h__\h] they're trying to guess
us guess they're not messing around
anymore with what this reminds me of the
chicken
game Kasa we can't stay in here for long
yeah especially you
don't
worry
[Music]
amazing
want some of
[Applause]
this
come how can this hotel let this happen
what about all the normal guests who
want to use the fitness
center what the [\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h] that's so messed
up so messed
up
I'm not going to stop making me eat The
Moldy
burger oh hello
wait we're kind of dying right
now
wait hi want an ass
[Music]
whoop want some of
this all
right ah hurry up let's go
the enemy name is
what oh it's one of your
names there an Evans but he's not Evans
L sure taking your
[Music]
time not the real
one EV before taking
it w I finally did
it got to protect
I think it's my subconscious trying to
protect
[Music]
K let's go want
some
nice apprentice and got some oh and he
died from
what
blood
boss Evans Evans what the
[\h__\h] you're crossing the line of
being
one more
[Music]
hit
oo that was a nice move
it again what do you mean
again value packing Soul let me look let
me look at I I picked up some stuff um
what was that before that I picked up
that was interesting was it an
accessory this is what I picked up no I
had the ankle we greatly increases XP
obtained from Battle great Lings w w w w
wow wow great L wait oh it reduces Max
HP she won
wi wa did she will we do another member
stream or was this a public one thank
you for the R I appreciate
it oh
um
hpmp yeah maybe I'll replace that one
but not necessarily for the ankle rat
greatly reduces I would maybe give that
to K because I give him a lot of uh I
make him use his normal basic attacks a
lot from power world stream
ah damn streaming early today
sh
J getting those European time
[Music]
zones
ah I don't know about these accessories
to be honest H maybe for her cuz she but
I this one at least not the MP one I
need the
MP early chill stream this is also a
somewhat chill somewhat early
stream
but oh wait we're going to get healed
right
yeah but uh not so chill like some
cutcenes have been really shocking so
far the barracudas are not
kill a running
cab
okay do you need
this
uh ah it's not better but it adds
evasion why
not yeah we saw guys getting their guts
filmed it's pretty pretty
brutal I like how the game when I go to
a save point it tells me that I should
save when that's obviously what I'm
about to do when I go up to you but it's
like warning me that what's coming next
is yit you should save if thank you
that's what I'm
doing let's go I am guessing my mom will
not be
there it's like a an endless
endless uh Chase until the end of the
game
probably that's plenty chill are you
sure it's probably going to be a long
cut scene
so I might m a little bit oh wow
i l places like
this that's insane I doubt this hotel
may be real but I doubt that this is
real in the
hotel if it's real then oh my
god
wow
she
Wow Ocean
volcano oh nice to meet
you
the white
[Music]
is
for
wait what this is
[Music]
DWI in English his voice is never no
way no
way all right just
thought you were saying the voice actor
is
[Music]
also
oh bring to bring them here
he was saying a
TR you can't take someone seriously who
sings something like
[Music]
that
for
spee
fore
foreign
[Music]
fore
I of want to hear this in
[Music]
English wa we safe we can switch and
rewatch The cut scene
[Music]
Eng
I'm going do it
now I just have to close the game once
right I did save
[Music]
so how do I close the
game how I
[Music]
close
say switching to English we may stay on
English for a while
[Music]
too
Sega speed
tree you got
Studio wow why did they drop the Yakuza
from from this title by the way and
Japanese is still kind of
there like the
equivalent doesn't say Yakuza ever in
Japanese
but ah cuz he isn't in the Yakuza
anymore oh well okay but he's still
dealing plenty with the Yakuza
everything around him is about
Yakuza
[Music]
to bring it in
line well yeah okay kind of late but
okay uh display
language display language or audio
language
[Music]
English I wonder if the voice will sound
familiar to me like who where where
would I where would I know that person's
voice from
Danny who is
[Music]
that what what the [\h__\h] is
ma machete I don't know that I don't
know that person Spy Kids no
idea he's an actor movie and
games the go goto bad as Mex oh does he
also look like that cuz usually uh they
also make them look like them
no a lot of the time this is the door to
the bosses Suite there's a good chance
he'll be inside and he calls the shots
huh must be a real scumbag let's make
sure we're good and ready before we head
in I like your
voices not
bad pretty nice huh a perfect view of
paradise oh good what's funny is until
last century this place was nothing a
taro field far as the I could
see agriculture was about the only
industry keeping this island afloat then
the white man came along and saw an
opportunity they crushed the fields
brought in Sand by the boatload from
sunny California and what was it all for
some fancy ass Resort built for some
fancy ass sons of [\h__\h] that paradise
you see it's all smoken
mirrors from SE to
Shin yeah what's your point it ain't
obvious H I'm saying a fate can hold
more value than even the genuine article
icha oh hi hi time you met the head of
the
barracudas names
Dwight
nice to know I've made a name for myself
out here I actually hold quite a bit of
respect for the Japanese people about a
100 years ago a number of your people
immigrated to my country they helped
plow our farmlands and our country
prer how about that nonetheless I'm
surprised you made it this far that
being said it's not you I'm surprised
with now now the real surprise is your
spunky little
friend you got guts betraying me like
that sorry Ichiban you know how I told
you I escaped after they found me
looking through the boss's study that
was a lie the truth is I actually got
caught and just in time Kuka it was
right as you barged in so I gave chos
here chos choice
she could die then and there or she
could do me a favor she told a favor
remember what I said about how I might
be leading you guys into danger or a
trap or something that I
am I meant it what she did and it seems
our deal fell through she led you away
from my trap well what's the Trap and as
a result you ended up here face to face
with yours
truie it does remind me a bit of that
elevator all right she said she made a
wrong turn yeah I mean the elevator yeah
but what part about it was the Trap like
would there have been people inside or
would it have
dropped not much more complicated than
that I mean have you seen how dumb this
guy is huh I've never met someone so
sincere and my entire life Ambush I had
no way of knowing whether you'd keep me
alive even if I did follow your orders
kasuga however is a different story I
don't think he's even smart enough to
cheat someone she how nice really tell
me this do you know what happens to
those who betray me who
gives the a [\h__\h] who would have thought
a Fuji nomia would be such a trouble
maker you must cause your parents a lot
of headaches how did you know did you
expect me not to the barracudas have
businesses with people all over the
world we would be remiss not to keep
tabs on those in
power besides it was obvious from the
start the moment I for saw you I knew
you were just you started dancing B I
figured I could use you I kept you
around that's also a good leg I kill and
the others anytime but I drew you in for
one simple reason their death would have
been on you and few things are so
obedient as a guilty conscience so it
goes I suppose don't worry I won't kill
you oh
no I'll make you my bargaining chip and
bed your family like
a fuk I'm person
bastard appreciate the kind words
chichan there you go again Ichiban you
sure you're not mad he's never mad what
for I made the choice to trust you
remember Dam you really are an idiot you
were wrong to trust her obviously enough
J two times already hey hang on I still
got unfinished business Dwight remember
the robbery that happened on October 7th
2012 betray us the target was Connie
Tanaka CEO of a well-known real estate
company on her way to visit a business
partner her car was attacked and a bag
of money was stolen and what's that to
you I'm the one they took in for it even
though they had next to no evidence oh
you were the Fall
Guy you saved me a lot of trouble so you
admit it you sick to Roman on me had him
pin your crimes on
me hey who could
say Dwight there's something I want to
ask too you were looking for a woman
named aane right AE oh God he's straight
with me you guys have already found him
haven't you
please only thing I'll do for you is
offer you a way
out all right let's go in fact it's the
quickest way I know cut to pieces and
stuffed in a body
bag you know what this baby is a machete
one of the most youthful tool that a
reference it makes short work of the J
you guys are saying maete not to mention
animals and here in Hawaii it's perfect
for gutting fish M Bring it on I think
it's time I showed you what this blade
of mine can
do ready to
bleed are you ready to
bleed oh
oh
wow
ouch TW mes Bara King
p
time to go all out all right let's
[\h__\h] go guys maybe now it's worth to
use something like
this uh should I try something wrong but
it will use up so much MP right in the
beginning try it I don't think we can
charm Dwight can we I feel like bosses
might have like a resistance to it keeps
on walking way too come on over here
come back come on come back will you
come back please come back come
back pal CL is really good try one of
his underlings yeah I could probably get
these
twoo don't BL bad oh wow girl let's go
yeah slay oh they're in so we can focus
on the other ones first cuz they're not
going to attack right oh my God what
happened
uh oh the boss is weak to water should I
work on the minions first I don't know
well I'm waiting are you weak to
something I got uh electricity bring
your I'll I'll start with got now armed
and ready here
a
good ready when you
are
and probably don't even
need any special
attack yeah okay okay I guessed it right
no oh with
K I thought it was K turn hey hey T play
fair think you can handle
[Music]
this
from guaranteeing a critical hit of the
action okay I think that's trest what
will the action from
f i going try to he guarding yeah
yeah triangle okay it's
over oh I'll
miss that was fast that was so
fast a
man can't FOC oh yes look at me look at
me I'm so
cute I can my fan
boys should we ignore them or should
I N I'll take him I'll take him
down at least as long as they're so
close to
me he
helped
a Dwight is enrange and only has I oh
but like in a in a romantic way
oh
scared here we go so that's why she
couldn't charm you you're to kill you I
see that's how it is to I'll try it
again
[\h__\h] I did it it's not even that much
damage it's just because he's a
boss he he's
helping he's
missing sure I'll play with you
okay here I
come
ooh Dwight is now weak to
us ready when you
are are you getting
scared I dropped the tiger what does
that mean well I'm
waiting
I don't have ice
but now brace
[Music]
yourself
100 I'll got your
ass do
it [\h__\h] I swear I pressed it the moment
he hit
me time to go need to press earlier but
this
time I'll take you
on oh come on bring
it sorry guys you got to help me though
follow me you got to do the bade too
guys with the finishing pose of course
my bad get
it the hold up guys you just don't get
it oh my God
ohow
me nobody ever taught them how to
B done with your tricks oh he's done
with my cringe is that what he said let
go oh come
on oh don't stand on his
butt like you own it it's not your
butt okay I'm so far I'm just going
to
something
wrong look at look
at oh tricks
oh CR is
better I'll take you
on got you now you're
210 I can do this [\h__\h] yeah Tommy is
killing
[Music]
it what
I'll actually help out a little bit and
give kinu some
food 150
[Music]
perhaps uh what what something wrong
here
thanks yo
yo but I block ball you got so much
damage and bleeds oh
man scared sure I'll play with
you is that nearby open one Safety
First much better
no wait what I thought he nearby animes
he was like pretty
nearby oh [\h__\h] I did it wrong oh
no all right oh no something
wrong don't get C damn it I can't have
Tommy die because like he's so useful
right
now anyway got to do some
damage yeah Tommy didn't want to be
helped okay okay
time to take out the crash all
right oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh input
[Music]
coming I got this i got
this
[Music]
nice feeling horny today aren't
you the fool is on my side I'll got your
ass [\h__\h] yeah
oh he's mad back he's so
mad what who streaking with
fear oh no my is stricken with
fear okay we need we need the jawbreaker
again come on here I
come I missed
no
[\h__\h] thanks 44 yeah thank
youy oh he broke
free oh
no his revenge is
coming [\h__\h] what's the hold
us now you can die on
Tommy I thought I could save you wait do
I have Revival
items [\h__\h] wait a second allow me I
don't have Revival items do
I you're in it now oh [\h__\h] I
didn't think about that do your work
I'll ah I do I do don't get C I do
oh okay time to get
real okay time to get
real come on oh damn I'm so sorry I'll
take
[Music]
you sure I'll play with you you get
scared
ah ah damn
yeah has his shield up okay we'll break
it we'll break it don't worry well I'm
[Music]
waiting second time I get the timing
wrong needed that but she's not scared
anymore I can do this oh uh what this
again increasing her attack and Agility
agility kind of late for that
maybe
oh damn strong though his buff here we
go sure I'll play with
you it's
over you think I'll let you win
this I'll stick you like a big okay
although I should have used him to break
his shield ah [\h__\h] that's the [\h__\h]
what do your work
cool
help I need somebody all
[Music]
right uh doesn't have anything that
breaks Shields
huh then he will H wait wait wait so
wait can I heal from here sure I'll play
with you yes okay so anyone who I choose
and then they're
nearby uh allies
I'll uh I'll do I'll do Tommy actually
cuz he's also close to K so maybe that
will do something no dyow and I Tommy
has the the stronger attacks for me
right now cuz of the element
up you
are here I come let's
go
you're
yes let's get this over with yeah we got
K heal too that that did
more sorry
girl her and her oh no so we could heal
her too with the skill
even I don't know if I
scared get rid of the
minion let me do that one of chance is
that he's going to attack her again
huh
Jinx I missed
[\h__\h]
see at least I lost one allow me m
well I'm waiting how about we
brawl then we can get two
hits like
this m [\h__\h] it we brawl I'll take you
off does he still have the the guard no
are you getting
scared
it okay now is looking very
good this the one that scares us is it
no what did he do something I'm out of
MP no but my weapon has the the same
[Music]
element oh he's guarding now
oh notop much longer but let me restore
some mp uh for
Tommy here hey
thanks so he can hit hard next round and
with K will break the
guard oh come
on oh he catches a cold
even the hold up kind of pathetic
looking right now
dud oh
[\h__\h] Tommy's hey the [\h__\h] what Tommy you
want to die what where was he where is
he where's his dead body does it just
disappear when he's
dead where you goong why was he what why
why I don't know if I want to uh revive
him
again I'll try without the
sure I'll play with
[Music]
you I'll take you
off
X yeah we just
now but I'll try to revive with someone
else maybe with
her open one
oh
oh you almost died let's get this over
there okay time to
revive our second and
last R
Resurrection oh wait now we have a
actually we had one that heals all of
the HP I didn't realize I'll I'll use
the one that revives with one
HP should be fine now right uh as long
as take why doesn't oh he does he's next
please please be nice he died on the
cult win right
oh well okay good that I used the one HP
Resurrection item he even got to level
up out of it
a a I guess that worked
nicely not a fancy finish though colds
are dangerous Conan here here or
not all right all right I'll be straight
with you we were looking for her but she
never showed up oh man if you don't
believe me feel free to search the whole
floor what do the barracudas want with
her honestly I don't know why don't you
know you're looking for her and don't
even know why it's not up to us we got a
request to look for
her we're just doing what we were asked
request you a small fish request from
who is that what you're saying I don't
know that either small they reached out
to us anonymously send it directly to my
address seriously info like that doesn't
leak easily and they sent a million
dollar down
payment if we succeed we would have
another 9 million coming our way that's
10 million just to find some
woman sure it was shady but who would
pass on on
that damnn it you don't know anything
else about aan son about Who the hell's
chasing after her if I knew anymore I
would have told you already got pretty
that's something that's the most real
thing you've said all
[Music]
day I assume that about does it for all
your aonan business Kasa no yeah I mean
yeah from here but I'm not done we're
finding her great then I guess it's my
turn
Tommy to
Tommy Tom me you give me a yes or a no
that crime I got locked up for was that
you both the setup and bringing in a
Fall Guy it was your
call answer me okay okay yes damn
it all right so it was you do you have
any idea how bad you [\h__\h] me over and
not just me wait wait stop stop wait
wait Roman might be gone but I can still
wipe your criminal record easy just say
the word and I got money a million no no
no $10 million okay okay hey that'll
give you a clean slate and then some
you'll be set for life like hell I
will you think money's ever going to
bring my kid back for these little fro
okay you think money's ever going to
bring you back Tommy [\h__\h] Tommy Tommy
Tommy it's F stop
it yeah he did right he stopped
him oh okay 3 one why wouldn't you stop
him though
hello you you can't let Tommy do [\h__\h]
like that you know CH to's name and
face you're going to get rid of all the
Intel you have on her she was never here
you got
it if you can promise me that you're
free to
go well it's your call he doing it okay
okay it's a deal I'll get rid of
everything and I won't tell anyone
either I swear I I
swear
what a
p all right now you are a [\h__\h] just now
if you ever go back on your word I'll
put this thing right between your
eyes it's nice to see people like him
become so pathetic oh and this lovely
little number here goes viral that's my
promise
[Music]
wo
[\h__\h] you're send it to the
vtuber well I don't know if she cares
but I think that about wraps things up
let's
roll you good now Tomy
zawa honestly I hope he's good I'd love
to see him
fry but that it means sinking to his
level plus it's not like taking him out
at spell the end of the
barracudas we don't know who might leak
info about chos
right better to leave him
alive keep everyone else in
line but why do this for me should have
taken the 10 million because believe it
or not you saved my life too
a I may not get why
but you still betrayed Dwight and let us
write to him on top of it we wouldn't be
here without you so
oh how about we call it
even between you and Ichiban I had
enough debt as it was I figured I'd
strike one off the list I love Tommy
when the hell do you get so cool
Tommy I've always been cool smart
ass yeah
sure he's really like
the he's like the the you know
the Mage from the previous game to
me like similar kind of
[Music]
character yeah alolan number yeah Al Lan
number you guys are geniuses sometimes
[Music]
man
yeah yeah I love his English
voice
wow chapter
five yeah we can switch back I don't
like how they pronounce names it
triggers me
huh pretty cool how we ended up here
after going through a dump like District
5 how can you be so chill we nearly got
chopped up by the Barracuda boss with
next to nothing to show for it only one
who got any business done was me
yeah but ain't that worth it a win for
you is a win for the team speaking of
then it was a win for Cheeto our team
just grew by one hey yo hello everyone
oh she's keen on stay you got a funny
definition of
teamwork oh is that how it's going to be
I helped you in the end didn't I yeah
and because of that we're still
breathing you did us a solid there my
pleasure it's nice to meet someone so
open-minded I'd say Tomy here has his
work cut out for
him Dam it you'll pal around with just
about anyone won't you she did risk her
life to save ours she will even if it
didn't start out that
way everybody's friend we want to find a
Kane son we'll need all the help we can
get sounds like you're in my corner then
sure you won't ditch me the moment you
find
her I should hope not personally I don't
mind to lose Canon as long as are on my
side I suppose I should take that as a
compliment ah
fine I guess if anyone SK Me of anything
it's me I English voice
actor see even backstabbers like us can
come
around yeah it's said it still doesn't
mean I have to trust you or like you a
why not I like you Tomy
yeah sure you got to be hiding
something and I'm going to find out what
I can smell the secret from a mile I
ship them oh come on the girls got to
have at least one good secret or
two here why don't we just start
over come on
Tomy okay but I'll be watching One slip
up and it's
over watch me all you want this looks
like mine I'm used to it ooh she got you
good how you like that burn
toy screw
you guess that settles it chichon you're
one of the gang good to have you good to
be
here don't tell me I'm supposed to make
a speech
now the name's
choia there you weren't I didn't ask for
that
Yoo now I want to play Super Mario
Sun
Danny Danny
D hey that reminds me you can have this
back sorry about
before Oh thanks how much was that what
oh the ah the actor oh I nearly forgot
about all that thanks
Chon nah it's nothing you got to thank
me for honestly you're way too
nicean okay we going achieve all we set
out to do be good to get a new plan
going sure then how about we go over
everything we
know all right but instead of standing
around here why don't we go somewhere we
can relax a bit like kio's hotel room as
always
let's wor for the best in that case how
about revolve oh oh oh oh they made me
go there because of her Koka
songs huh why
not it's a bar over in little Japan we
more or less use it as a hideout I'm
sure you love
to what's with you oh no I'm not
fighting you guys no no no no not right
now
took revolve
[Music]
here
T Japanese vo say okay okay you guys
really want it
[Music]
huh
uh okay
uh
save oh yeah suspicious
minds and return to title I just have to
return to title yeah I think
so yeah I mean the good thing about
English is you guys don't have to like
look at the subtitles the whole time and
I totally get that but this it's a split
opinion some people want Japanese some
people want English
so can't make everybody
happy I feel like generally for this
game since we're it it plays in this
location uh English would be fitting
it's a bit more
authentic but
yeah
I wish it was mix
VA yeah but then it would be probably
weird like
inconsistent
oh it is mixed yeah but not mixed enough
like I thought they cuz in the beginning
it started out with more English I
thought that's how it was going to
be and then surprisingly it was a big
streak of Japanese even for obviously
Western looking characters I was like
heo why why won't you speak
English more English why does and they
don't even speak um like uh Japanese
with an accent they speak legit like
they were born in
Japan they could have casted voice
actors that are not Japanese but maybe a
little bit capable of speaking Japanese
to make it sound a little bit more
authentic to many keys gut
booster
for
[Music]
charms yeah I know I could do that my
you mean my my
fortunes wait till you hear a certain
character's acent later on
uhhuh animal bone necklace exclusive
equipment for Pirro
dancers oh I have a feeling that might
be chito's job
later what the [\h__\h] is
that safe
Point
what a a sui
spot simply push him and you'll receive
free suon
items
ahuh sujon G ticket provides one pull at
the suim basic gcha or type
gcha
okay
hey stinky
towel no real use for this okay I'll
sell it
eventually and here we are it's cut
scene and then CA time probably
guys
[Music]
spee
for
yeah that's
it
for
Fore
fore
[Music]
spit it
out what's your
[Music]
job interesting job
choice
for easy
yeah that is a good
hint even if she's not there we're going
to probably find and people who know her
really
well it's getting late so let's try to
open it tomorrow still it's a bit early
to hit the hay so let's
in tomy's drinking all by himself we
haven't really had much time to chat
since we teamed up let's talk no you
should sing Koka
together let's try Cheeto song
only that
song all are new
[Music]
too is that
new is that new I think some of these
are
new and it's even got a judgment
version oh [\h__\h] I love this
already The
Vibes The Vibes please sing for me CH
[Music]
Ste
[Applause]
[Music]
he said long
long
she has such a good
[Music]
voice
what I love a [\h__\h] I [\h__\h] up because
of him he says I love
[Music]
swimsuit
I want to watch wi stream doing that
[Music]
with who fantasy is
that [\h__\h]
[Music]
almost golden
hour
beautiful ah hermit
crab I love
it what a bob yeah best hype
[Music]
man oh not bad I could have done
better
[Music]
bad
I love swimsuits so [\h__\h]
random she wasn't even in a swimsuit
yet oh the B I like
that I'll I'll try ah the other new
songs too if I can ever read the
microphone I want to watch the MV
properly so this
one we probably have different input
right
the ichan version is new
[Music]
[Applause]
right
[Music]
hi
yes their chairs are so
[Music]
Random they have no system no
rhythm bre
I can't sing along I'll mess up the
[Music]
Imp rocket
boys
romance
[Music]
yo he looks so good in those
clothes I love it so good
oh nice
rank thank you thank you thank you poy
poy
[Music]
poy it works with his hair
uh I think this one's new or am I
imagining
it I think that's new and he's like
let's go up to Hawaii it's a Hawaii P
[Music]
song it's difficult [\h__\h] why is it
difficult thanks for the pink Super Chat
I don't know who ched but thank
you suddenly so
[Music]
slow
don't
[Music]
for first try
guys who's
[Music]
crying let's
go ah he's do the T guys I Tau you
wait what are you doing
[Music]
here no you're messing with
me [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] oh god oh
[\h__\h] my fum is
dead
nice my fump and my eyes are dead no
it's not cuz I was distracted it's
legitimately
difficult oh my
God was there anything else new tell me
otherwise uh we're done for today with
the I Checker oh
gladly I'll prove
you Mama
Mia why is Tommy Za not sing maybe he's
too shy still he'll he'll get
[Music]
there he'll get
there
you
[Music]
voice
actors come
on you charged them too much
Char
song
for don't take the job if you're not
going to sing for
them
damn oh they you think they couldn't get
the r Maybe
his music
might they should have said okay for
game like
this
anyway personality
[Music]
chance
big lost opportunities for real like I
didn't even know that he's singer so if
he would have like done a cut
song especially for the Western audience
they all surely
and imagine if he sings in K and he
absolutely people get curious and they
like oh wait he's a real
sing big advertisement
dude why I mean even if it's not his why
the label not see
[Music]
that
and other Yak games and actually even
though I didn't play five I did just
recently see a video of that
Idol
performing so I think I know what you
mean
that's his
daughter but wait this like his adopted
daughter
right
[Music]
that song in the
background I
know
you I know it from a Japanese
musical from my ad
group B's coobo my
beloved
um
for
foree
Fore
fore
for Good
Times
[Music]
true you little [\h__\h] you were such a
little [\h__\h] back
[Music]
then
for that doesn't sound like a 100%
promise yeah drink Lings
mhm oh he can now use Tag Team I tag
teams yeah forgot about that cuz it
didn't come up
yet after forming a bond with your
friends you'll be able to tag team with
them tag team skills are powerful combo
attacks that can be performed without
spinning MP once a hype meter is filled
uh press R2 to initiate a tack team
skill mhm hype hype
hype okay he wants us to
sleep thank you wait can I only do one
drink Ling per
day seems like it okay one last song for
the night ah come on which one is the
new
[Music]
one must be this one
right it's like a an answer song
to
a
[Music]
for go 50y old old dude you can do it
yeah of style you're slaying
you still got
[Music]
it I feel
it s sips
wooo 50 years and still no hip
replacements oh
[Music]
oh his
fny I love it
to
[Music]
you can't do
this
you not eyes that's why he loves
ich
that's that was in the rhythm of him
scratching himself that's why he loves
ich because ichan has the doo eyes
number to both number and ichan no not
number and itan they all have Doo
eyes
a nice answer song nice follow-up
[Music]
song very pleasant to listen
to he's the leading of a rock band a
yo yeah did he start
before like voice acting for this
game or
after does have a dog like personality
100% ah I need to level up the bonds in
order to make the conversation okay well
I'll try my best I mean all
don't know how to do more than I'm
already doing all right let's head to
the
orphanage Lo
[Music]
KS there's so much stuff in here and
some
enemies they're only red so I wouldn't
mind trying that boss
too
muscle what are you looking
at muscle
soda what are you looking at Get
Wrecked brang it on island
brises unquiet RoR technomancer and
conscious which one is the strong one
give
up
H well I guess it wasn't
you
oh I'm too strong now I mean that was
pretty obvious level
15 but okay he's still he's still kind
of
chunky
[Music]
nice any
weaknesses oh guns okay he likes
guns he likes spe guns and he cannot
Li and
can
I didn't watch that new new what is
it TI love that Frey is so good what is
that even about I don't I don't know I
should watch
[Music]
it just saw the cute
thumbnail all over the place on
Twitter and on YouTube yeah I know it's
a Ian 3D repeat I know I know
damn he keeps on getting further and
further
[Music]
away just good at talking about her big
tail
okay okay KO oh ah I can catch him oh
he's a
suon yeah
all
right I don't care but okay here take
this gift show him I care I
I a [\h__\h] it shows that I don't
care anyway let please Anyway come on
I'm stronger than you let me train you
you'll become stronger
[Music]
too he accepted
it oh level 10 h
swing cycle swing hold on not that I'll
ever use you guys unless I'm being
forced or if it brings me money when I
really need money or something like
that but
yeah North Star soundtrack CD CD
featuring to receive you norstar from
the video game of Fist of the Northstar
lost par uh
okay am I supposed to sell
that
okay
um
ah taxi stand so far oh no wait there's
one here I'm blind right at the
orphanage okay
I can listen to it m restock on
Resurrection items yeah
yeah when I find the store
yeah
[Music]
for well I think that's
pretty I hope they will get
alone
Who ah but she's probably not in
[Music]
there
interesting good people finally some
good
people for a
oh
hello
oh [\h__\h] drops the
plates tomato
tomato No I guess we startled you cuz
you dropped the plates I'm
sorry
for
oh
no
fore
[Music]
damn
it oh but maybe the kids know Miss Dana
you won't believe it yeah the tomatoes
we planted turned out hug huge English
wow I see that why don't you share some
with our guests okay talk so nicely the
way she said that sounds like how Nissa
says that huh here you
go um who are
they they're a friend we're so scared
looking really does that mean Miss con
is coming back no sweetie that's still
going to take some time a how long I
really want to see her again I wish I
could give you an answer hey I know why
don't you go fetch a watermelon too find
the biggest one you
can
kids
wait is this the same voice act I can't
tell if that was the same
voice
damn they trying to
[Music]
me
e
[Music]
religion sounds like at least not bad
people
[Music]
for
the only I feel when I look at the
[Music]
volcano
pineapple and pizza yeah that's also
something that comes up in my
[Music]
mind party
time let's
party while it's blowing
[Music]
up
I was wondering what that animation was
[Music]
about
fore
[Music]
yeah the paj is
nice
[Music]
for
does have enemies but it's not really
her
[Music]
fault all right Dana we've grabbed all
we can so I'm going to haul this over to
the food
bank hey thanks Callen any chance we can
throw in some meat or fish to go with it
I wish but I don't see any fishermen or
butchers around here think we're good to
go with what we
got well I guess this will just have to
do some fishmen that
are and their
fish two birds of one
stone
my where you born in
[Music]
Japan
for
[Music]
Fore
foree
the Beats what of those
beats yeah he runs into the 5% influent
Japanese speakers in Hawaii and they all
play a role in the
blood
[Music]
just over complicating
things
how are we supposed to collect the food
this one food bank I saw in the news
they got a bunch of leftovers from the
local stores a no kidding but are any of
them going to be willing to donate a
bunch of
strangers well no worri is there my body
dad my buddy's dad runs a Fruit Stand a
Fruit Stand he must have all kinds of
tropical stuff then huh yeah he knows me
so I think he might even let us have
some of his unsold
merchandise
Park
okay
nice I wonder how much WR I should
[Music]
play got to read some
super what you looking at looking at
youing more bonds
yay oh no it's
side
hey you little
[\h__\h] that is not very Japanese
of
yeah I'm what [\h__\h] saw with my own
eyes so
rude oh is it a cleaning
robot it's
hug the robot is
huge no oh
the
[\h__\h] what should I know
him should I know
it I don't remember this at
all I remember the
[Music]
room
what I actually did
things I've played many many many hours
of these
games don't blame me for trying to save
some time here there so I don't have to
make
important oh it
[Music]
money how do you even transport
dude
from Japan to
[Music]
here now
points him long
[Music]
enough no I don't have that money you
little
[\h__\h] Mama
M you think I'm a
fool I'm not going to see I didn't give
you any money in the previous game and
you managed to build that thing anyway
so I don't think you need my help are
you what's that what's that again sujon
thing what is
that I can't click
it oh it's
gone a ra
spot oh nobody was raiding
it thanks for the membership we
all
right where do we got to go there's a
free
magazine more class
exp
right
[Music]
for local media the first thing I got to
know about
her I do but you want so many Doles I
can't help them in Grand blue fantasy
realing we only had cats and here
there's like so many
dogs all right I think we kind of a rock
what is this place
helloha fruit and other ingredients will
whip them up into dish
oh cool I have
banana but oh you can make tea with all
my
herbs
interesting this need ah the Supreme
let's make this one it heals 100 mp to
the entire party that's amazing I'll
make this one
too
y I
[Music]
understand these are so useful yeah I
got to remember this place give gift oh
sweets wait doesn't Tommy like sweets
but I kind of want to give it to Cheto
cuz I mean she's a
lady with healthy
movies Tommy
or yeah sure only Che
do maybe everybody would be happy about
it
H yeah cuz she's a dancer
yeah get the Cheetos on up okay okay I
got you I got you I got you hi there hey
there hi there hey there Mr
Yamada oh Ricky I haven't seen you in a
while
Ricky it's a nickname from the ran
era I say still Tommy is a better
nickname yeah
hard to say no
comment are you
friends oh oh well actually
where what the [\h__\h] do you guys want
here right
now yeah but has
business you're not going to like steal
the fruit
here listen y mother we all got a bit
too sippy last night my head's
pounding yeah what do you got for a
quick
fix oh some grapefruit ought to take
care of that I hate
grapefruit hey G what who would have
guessed not like you'd have much else oh
but wait actually you do I know
something you got that'll do us one
better money nothing for money you go to
the freaking vegetable stand Guy come on
you've got so much power in this city go
somewhere else go to a [\h__\h]
bank I don't know go to the store why to
a place like this to this guy like he
probably doesn't even have much money at
all like what the
[\h__\h] what register he doesn't even have
a register
dude yeah just let me just fight them
let me just fight
them I'll bury
you we solve all problems of
violence don't mess with us tourists
just because we're
tourists I'll teach you a
lesson
well I can use the tag team already I
think can I
R2 yeah oh it's a
line I think I luckily chose the right
person cuz I think it what about the
person to my left that was also in the
line was to
close damn it but that was strong oh he
can also talk him
what yo I saved those for later are they
that
rare or immediately a boss coming after
this yes my my my protection for KY was
holding up well oh
my I I have a I have a good heart yes
yes
KY
but they're already so
[Music]
low she
it makes you want to hurt
[Music]
somebody
wait that's not the
[Music]
lyrics I really to
hurt I really want to plant my fist in
your face I really want to let some
anger
out until you pee your pants tell you pe
your pants and
run nice nice nice nice song that was
Maron five for you they write good
lyrics they
do um starting to pick up the local
language I guess yeah
sure as long as they got the message you
can relax now they won't be coming back
really thank you so much oh they've been
frightening me for some time now taking
away my earnings every chance they get
all really well we won't bother you
anymore we can try somewhere else oh
wait is this for the food bank if so by
all means let me help you out my way of
saying
thanks I got the best produce in town
some of these I can't seem to sell but
they still taste great of course there's
these great
great sounds like one business done uh
thanks a
DA the
grapefruits okay yeah I don't want to
have them we can give them to the food
bank m
wow finally beat that's not in a
can shall we have some steak
tonight you're
welcome yeah
food's looking
good high quality
[Music]
man a month to live in
Paradise
not with your
cheap more expensive these
[Music]
days
no
nothing when did you do that we were
together all
along Dam do you guys know anything
about her me we need some advice some
knowledge except for
[Music]
spoilers bad
not very helpful are you
guys I doubt
that not buying
[Music]
that
so aloha Beach Before Sunset we still
have daylight to burn then maybe let's
unwind for a bit you haven't had a break
since you came here have you besides if
you're in Hawaii you might as well do
something Hawaiian for a change yeah
like what
surfing he did say something or take
hoola lessons hoola lesson be too fun
taking hoola
lessons I think Kido would be great at
hoola with his
[Music]
hips surfing sounds
difficult like for real you want us to
go hoola or or surfing for
real what
here in the sports Kingdom
okay maybe the last thing I do
today uh and we can buy some stuff there
too
[Music]
um uh that's a
restaurant Supermarket ah ABC
Store okay let
me check
[Music]
chicken Black Knight hi chicken never
mind I need more bird
feed I mean maybe the normal food would
work too
but Brown
Chicken oh I was looking for infrared
lamp but I couldn't decide yet which one
to
buy
cat let's
go I will buy
one and I'll try to use
it for my back and my shoulder GL Maria
bouquet it would probably make a great
gift you may think that I would give it
to the girl in our roomp but no I'll
give it to Tommy or to K you hey [\h__\h]
no I'm not going to follow the cliches
looking
at oh shaved ice hey no not side
quest
he's feeling hot he needs to be
refreshed he's doing the Ice Bucket
Challenge wet old
man
[Music]
uh if you want snow I don't know if you
if I can help you we're in
Hawaii in freaking Hawaii go somewhere
else go to a different country aloha
M MP and HP I'll buy a
couple 16 ah it's all the same
okay M thank you very much because it's
kind of
orange that's our
colormy mm M all right do you have they
got oh they got these
Foods I'm going to buy some of these
yeah and did I not have Revival stuff
heo no thank you do I have to go to a
pharmacy where's your
Pharmacy
where
a pharmacy no it's a
raid Pharmacy
only damn it Pharmacy is kind of
rare uh this this
one do they have the same sign as the
normal
supermarkets Healthy Smile that sounds
like a
pharmacy then I got to go somewhere
else that's probably one
right triangle yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah I don't need it
Don I have food for
you we're friends okay what do I get out
of
it what do I
get all I get is
Regret aloha
Aloha to you too do you have some
Revival
items those are absolutely
lifechanging oh the expenses Mama Mia
I'll just buy two that's enough
maybe thank
you now I will go back
here
I walk this time save some
money
beautiful why definitely has some
interesting
scenery nice nice
place I want to go but it's so far
America is so
[Music]
far you
Y no your name is
you yeah whatever don't care I don't
care if you're
popular I'm more
popular I don't want to be nice to
him
okay I'll fight
you
so making a live
[Music]
stream I'm so
excited yeah okay let's do it right here
in the middle of the
street
brought
one one okay okay I've become stronger
only level 12 ow weak you're such a
baby everybody get this on 4K okay 60
FPS
please [\h__\h] sorry I failed but it's okay
I'm not even using my full a
game cuz I don't need to oh that was
strong hey hey hey
hey this is why I'm I'm talking
about oh I got another
[Music]
one and another
one straight
left wait was I even full
HP when this
began did you get that in a closeup yo
it's got to be a
closeup hey stop stop stop stop d d d
d one more hit go
go
[Music]
beautiful oh of course you would be
tougher than last time
yeah you satisfied now satisfied my
assur when we first fought I noticed
something those other punks you were
with they were nowhere near your level
man
aw we're so nice we're trying to give
him back some
confidence unlike them you actually know
how to put up a fight yeah I guess what
I do if you know that already then why
keep wasting your time wasting my time
yeah going around picking fights for the
camera you've been flying across the
[\h__\h] Globe for that is that all you
want out of life or do you think hitting
random people makes you strong there's a
lot more to it than
that well yeah but damn
dude shut up LPA good good
argument maybe you haven't noticed but
it's what you protect that makes you
strong whether it's your dream or the
people around you as for you sure you
throw a mean punch but if the only thing
moving your fists is anger you'll stay
right where you
are nah it's not just anger it's the
cloud too for him so I'll ask you again
you satisfied where you at
asakura no not really actually I've been
feeling pretty stuck Star Struck last
time I even put effort into a fight was
I don't know and after getting beat by
you twice I got to say I'm pretty pissed
but at the same time I'm
pumped you are huh yeah all I want to do
now is get stronger focus on my training
then hit you up for a
remat you better stick with it then even
a bunk with dedication is going to have
a hard time taking me down I'm Number
One ichy
Bun I can see that it's why I'm going to
go back to the essentials no more
bullshitting around or wasting my time
like I said starting today the week
asakura you new is no more when you see
me again I'll be doing things legit that
way I can take pride
in not right give me another run and
I'll show show you how serious I am
maybe I've just been a punk this whole
time but I'll come back as the MMA
master I said I was and give you a match
where
fighting all right that's the deal I'm
sure we can both learn a thing or two
from that match until then don't let
upo
b as the MMA my asro huh I still got a
way to go but already he's a force to be
reckoned with hiding him could be good
for the both of us but I not
underestimate him though he seems dead
set on beating
me well this time was certainly not very
impressive I mean
yeah I I was uh pretty
damaged oh he need
help it's does that help involve
fighting actually actually we should
probably do it now before it's like baby
level like I said I should do the
quests I'll
s although this isn't the real Quest is
it oh level
eight
wow my new skill I'm not going to use my
new skill on these
punks they don't deserve to see it be
good even Tommy can hit him without the
type
advantage
you're
welcome thank you bye yeah that was not
even a place was just a friendship
thing sorry I saw this in the corner of
my eye orange fire that's my
color for for surf boards what you
looking at
perfect that's exactly the only
acceptable color for me you'll be
see there's something I need oh wow nice
outfit there's something I need to
find level 17 oh God they they've can
scale they have been
scaled for a SE oh it's with a SE oh
that's fine that's cool
[Music]
[Applause]
ni don't break the case over there I
need
[Music]
that HT oh they're not weak against
anything
then come
[Music]
gety and I think you'd like to eat some
tires this guy will keep on calling him
back up oh okay okay okay I'll I'll
focus on him then then him
[Music]
then Dam
strong come on
[\h__\h] nobody respond so much for
that maybe don't call them [\h__\h] tag
me
[Applause]
in these guys we should hire them to
become Cheetos say backup
dancers
his dance
team this going to
hurt oh yeah w
w
impressive they even so syned up must
have practiced a
[Music]
lot you know there's a super cool coral
ography out
there from
Tak her songs choreographies I like so
cool you should try recreating
[Music]
those try to do you
challenge
come on guys no no
no she's so far I know you'll keep on
calling new ones but as long as she over
here nice they're having a nice dance
battle dance off
come okay almost dead
almost they're better be something
really nice in that case
that's that that one over
there well at least we got good
exp you got a key from them too
oh never enough
key there we
go
come come at
me
me come
[Music]
on N don't call him
no okay okay
[Applause]
[Music]
okay play is safe of a
skill
he's gone
forever
nowo will never be challenged again to
be the number one dancer in
Honolulu get out of
here you have no
Grace and no
shame you're an
embarrassment to all the dancers out
here in
Honolulu ah eh was I supposed to go for
the back one Dam it I'll never
[Music]
learn what the [\h__\h] was he not in the
same she
not is she too
far I'll help him out over
here I did it right it was just too far
away the the the tire
one 2500
exp yes what's in here
kind look at my
Racers I did not need
those at all where was I going
anyway a okay okay
okay chicken I have bir feet
now this is for
you can you be this is one of
you you will not die from Hunger not
today not today not tomorrow hey hello
[\h__\h] it's
you don't you ignore me why are these
blue is it CU they're too low level for
me
now oh I've been training meet me at the
warehouse behind the dogs when you got
time
ahuh he's already ready ready I don't
think you really got much stronger maybe
take some more
time what you I don't think you're
ready don't stress it
man you'll regret
it you just got a a blue dark purple
eye 10 p up and feels
readying L2 on those
[Music]
blue
oh finally sone with an accent even
though it's a fake
one he's a he's a
tree he's a
tree nice I
guess nice shark is that a real
one and the
[Laughter]
smile
[Music]
yes
she's
crazy she's
crazy
[\h__\h]
insane wait I thought this was side but
isn't this actually what we're supposed
to
do going to tell me how to hola
dance oh it is was like [\h__\h] side quest
such
nonsense yes I am lucky Happy
People okay let's happy let's
[Music]
happy can I do the
dancing oh unlock new jobs oh
you mean new
classes feel free to change jobs you've
unlocked at any hello happy location oh
my God
okay oh oh like hello hello Al happy an
happy tours offers a variety of
activities that allow the party to
experience the magic of Hawaii H that's
okay so depending on the the job that I
want it would be a different like
experience Maybe
yeah okay oh
wow cute looks like there's currently a
free promotion for newcomers what are
you waiting
for diving
tour let's [\h__\h] L
it
[Music]
B wait I don't have to do anything I'm
just watching some cool cut scenes let's
[Music]
go it's your BN oh
doin be careful they're evil they're so
[\h__\h]
[Music]
evil what is it what would that
be
what I could not
what I mean
okay that's
red he was so
inspired I want to see more of these
cutcenes can I do them all right
away if I can afford them
no guys donate
donate yes yes Super Chat
please
okay I don't know if I can afford but I
want to do all
them what happens in the AL happy
room
than let's get Al
happy thank you L box
let's get Alo
happy dud how much is it how much is
it time for change other happy room is a
fitting room provided
byit where you can change jobs and
inherit skills
okay oh oh Indigo five Alpha let's get
aloh happy to tr let's get Al happy Lord
let's get Al
happy oh my God is that what what the
[\h__\h] is Tommy wearing I think he's
really Alo
happy Alo happy thank
you let's get Alo
[Music]
happy H you can set inherited skills
from any job you've had with the
exception of suji maner you'll unlock
skill inheritance slots let's get Al
happy as you improve your personality
and deepen your BNS the final rainbow
call slot will allow you to set a Ki
skill carry over different skills mhm
okay J let's get Al happy the gamer cre
let's get Al happy space wonderful let's
[Music]
get wait he is currently a hero right
yeah oh my God is that that even a good
class for
him let's get Alo happy myel my let's
get Alo happy oh my God stop guys tasim
let's get Alo
happy K let's get Alo
happy I happy oh happy [\h__\h] yeah
Trevor
Cruz okay I stop I stop stop stop stop
stop stop no more no more Alo happy Alo
sad Alo sad FR Alo happy we need to CH
happy Al sad very Al sad Al
happy
happy Galaxy
[Music]
ition wait what there we likeing Super
Smash Brothers oh I mean they have these
t for outfits in the previous game
too
dope okay Michael
H oh H is all sad you know I would be
really sad if
I oh they can all become aquan Nots wait
his hair gets gets
[Music]
ungr
yo he'll be so
happy was
[Music]
that oh
Tommy that looks kind of good oh she
can't have
it
it was amazing
so okay okay okay okay but but but but
but but
but I want
more maybe not but I can no no no we're
not leaving
yet I probably can't afford
anything you're happy to assist me I'm
also Al
happy
I can only I can afford
H and duty free
shopping the others are oh oh so I can
afford fire dancing and Paris
[Music]
sailing wa
yoga which one should I do maybe hoola I
want to see the hoola
video and then give hoola maybe I don't
know whoever maybe there's you got to
you guys got to tell me if there's
certain classes that work better for
certain people cuz that was a thing
before
too yeah
probably there was a stat locked I don't
know what that
means H let's get Al
happy worth my
money tomy's a good fight at oh I'm sure
he would
[Music]
be
wow let's join
in
yes although to do it
too yay
cute oh that's what the maracas are
for
I Geo
dancer
wow she's not a Geo guesser she's a GE
dancer let's go
wo oh
I like this color oh oh Phoenix colors
girl
fireing I think the red looks amazing on
her wow she loves it she's
happy wow
oh can watch this
forever it's
hypnotizing
the aloh happy guy loves it
too he's so happy that he can finally
make other people aloh
happy can itone take
this no but
maybe no so sad yeah only she really
realized cute what so what's the
inheritance thing what I do nothing okay
O Let's Go I want to
do let's do the fire danc can I afford
it I think
[Music]
I yeah I'll do it do it I'll freaking do
it Al
no
in front of the corrupt Hotel let's
go are you feeling it
Tommy is everybody can everybody here
except KY learn it cuz right now it's
ich the leopard Prince
yo he's rocking it
though
fire let's see if we can give that to
Tommy though I've unlocked the power job
let's [\h__\h]
go Tommy
please
yes oh it's all purple but there
different purples oh this one's green
purple purple purple purple
purple let's do this
[Music]
one
y grass cutter ah that class uses these
grass cutter things oh interesting look
at him look at him look at him
posing this is the best game ever
because they have nipples they're not
ashamed of showing their
nipples now I only need something for
K unless you guys say k is best in the
in the current class I don't know
but oh no for now this is
fine
thank
you happy photo R are
happy you're going to feel pretty
weak
okay you mean cuz the weapons in the
class is like
low
know she's
great how you going to how you going to
smoke
it
yeah
[\h__\h] makes me
happy we can pick up I happy F
girl to protect him to save him he's
important for the story
line
I
[Music]
know yes that's right
here just like
this
wow okay ah I get a surf flounder after
taking all these
pictures oh back to all happy okay but
this a sub story that I have to do or
what oh
wait you never did any of this well
probably won't
either
see you if we don't do it I'm happy if
we don't do it then he'll be Al
sad you got some good weapons from it
ooh maybe I'll do
it I Fe no man but that woman she scares
me are you Al happiest inside person
talking oh yeah so the sun is starting
set don't we have somewhere to be right
let's go clean up aloh
Beach uh I don't know about that it's
midnight dude it's midnight over
[Music]
here how the [\h__\h] is it already
midnight wait it's almost 8 hours wait
it is 8 hours of
streaming how the [\h__\h] did I a moment
ago I said we were at 7
hours
what the [\h__\h]
happened no not the new why do I keep on
making new
ones yeah we're playing tomorrow again
of course and um I think I'll do a super
chat reading stream on Monday or so or
[Music]
Tuesday to catch
up cuz I don't feel like reading now my
throat hurts a little bit and it's
late m
yeah and if I do that then we can play
tomorrow the whole time without reading
super chats too without worrying about
that and just go 8 hours again
yeah 16h hour Yakuza weekend VOD gang
good
luck let's be Alo happy V gang if there
are still any B gangs around
here show me a a sign of your life life
sign I want to know you're still around
show me in the comments in the comment
section I've been checking the comments
by the way I mean mostly like very
shortly after but maybe for the V gang
I'll check also a little bit a couple
days later too yeah I've been checking
though I've been
checking you can do it Vault gang I mean
you finished this whole Vault so I I
think you're going to be able to manage
the next one too you can do it God about
I know that was a very stream heavy week
and not even over
yet stream heavy as in Long
streams
yay yay yay yay I'm so glad I don't have
any work to do right now I think I I
cleared everything off of my to-do
yesterday yesterday I said I was going
to be lazy I woke woke up and I was like
I don't want to get up cuz smoothie woke
me
up and then and then I got up I had
breakfast and then when I cleaned up my
breakfast I was so motivated no actually
yo yo it was all I was already not lazy
anymore at the point when I went out to
buy nice strawberries and cream to whip
it whip it up make whipped cream I made
myself a wonderful breakfast yeah and
then I was like oh okay now I got to
clean so I cleaned my whole kitchen
again which was a mess again I cleaned
everything I threw out cardboard stuff I
threw out this I threw out that I
cleaned this I cleaned that I did my
laundry I I vacuumed everything yo I've
I wiped all the surfaces and this and
that I did so much stuff okay and then
and then you thought oh wow she did so
much for the day she won't do anything
else but then I did a recording that I
was asked to
do uh like some singing stuff and then
and then you would think then I would be
done doing things no at 2 a.m. in the
night I suddenly did the polar of wordss
cuz I was like I don't know if I'll have
have time tomorrow I don't know if if
I'll have time the next few days let's
do it now I want to be
productive
yeah wow I was very productive yesterday
on my day off
mm I feel like I have another
task cuz I was like I'll either do the
polar or I'll do this other thing that I
should be doing but now I forgot what it
was I guess I don't have anything to do
if I can't think of it I look
happy make sure to sleep yeah yeah I
think I get generally enough
sleep
yeah although I was a bit tired today
during the stream not because I I I I
get enough sleep but you know when when
I stream for
hours I get tired so
tired IO happy IO
sleepy sleeping on the beach of
Honolulu just got to be Al happy yeah
you almost at 8 hours
yo how
dare why wasn't it 10 hours will not vot
ah I'm so mad it's because of all the
times OBS cut out so even when OBS
showed me 10 hours it wasn't 10 hours on
YouTube
rude
tomorrow same time same place alola wait
I just realized yeah we have alola alola
Aloha same thing same
thing
hi okay guys have a nice uh night Day
evening morning whatever and I'll see
you
tomorrow w w w maybe next week I'll do
an sea friendly stream maybe feel like I
need to make an sa sea friendly stream
next
week and also still I don't know when
that trip is happening it's still
happening uh but it got delayed as I
told you again but it should be
happening like soon so maybe it's
happening next week so again as I told
you no no schedule but I think I will
still make a schedule for this week in
hindsight just for the record and you
know what I think I'll put today's
schedule as yester last time's schedule
I want to make the uh the schedule
thumbnail I want to make the thumbnails
more relevant to what happened in the
Stream and this one was definitely
definitely more relevant to last time
cuz there was no yumai
today uh and then for today I'll make a
I'll make a thumbnail that has uh the
Mendes
guy and and
Cho in it yeah
and for tomorrow I don't know I'll I'll
put like a I don't know I don't know
who'll be relevant
tomorrow so maybe I'll make it
afterwards
always I don't want to get spoiled
either of what will be relevant put Alo
happy or or because we just got new
classes for tomorrow I could uh put like
screenshots or whatever I can find of
those new classes of the hul out of the
hola dance outfit and the fire dancer
outfit and all that would be good too
and the the diver
outfit I'll think of something I kind of
probably should make the thumnail before
I go to sleep or I'll just put up like
the same one and then make it
tomorrow no no
okay so for now good night I'll go find
some food and cuddle the
Kito yeah hopefully tonight I dream
something normal or just nothing at all
take care guys and enj thank you so much
sorry for
the not so good start and but again
compared to the rest of the stream
that's a minimal minimal thing see you
tomorrow Al Alo s Alo happy
s bye bye
[Music]
bye
oh yeah mum's outfit I saw it
before it's so
good she didn't show it yet but I think
right but you guys are going to love it
oh my
[Music]
God
oh yeah right the re broadcast I forgot
about that thanks for reminding
me and that was going to be on a sea
friendly time this time thank you I'll
put it in my schedule on my Goog Google
schedule now that so that I
[Music]
remember ah I think yeah I'll try to let
you know if as early as I can
but I'll try to put it on the
[Music]
weekend thank
you
[Music]
is no one streaming I don't see anyone
streaming yeah no one's streaming right
not just me just me
Monopoly
wow wow
wow oh well all
right then go be productive chat go do
something