[Music]
oh wow
sparkly
[Music]
Sparks me remembering my song cuz Sparks
that's where it
ends
Sparks shine
bright don't stop don't stop just going
Your Own
Way ah light the way cuz Sparks light
the way e really no not like that light
the flame like
the cuz spars light the flame
uh
uh and then are you
sure turn the Dark of the night
into
oh need to sing Sparks more often I
guess yes I saw Yes yes every everybody
keeps on asking me did you see that did
you see this did you see that yes I saw
everything I have my eyes everywhere
have you not noticed until now that I
have my eyes freaking everywhere why are
we capitalized I thought today I you
know that's why I asked you guys to chat
a little bit I thought today I'll have
you guys looking a little bit uh
different to match the vibe of this game
a bit more but you a little bit too long
here there we
go oh why are we
killing you're not not no there's a
difference between even though it's all
caps there's still a difference between
caps and not
caps
look it it it kind of fits like Final
Fantasy is also being screamed Final
Fantasy see it's also caps but you're
not screaming it are you
normally
I just thought it looked
cool okay looks nice also I made you
guys are writing too many messages right
now but you're supposed to be fading out
of the
screen can you guys shut up for a moment
so that we can see ah there you go do
you see
[Laughter]
that see that when when you actually
don't spam then you guys are fading out
nicely uh I'm putting you above me
instead of like here like I usually put
you cuz I thought looks also nicer this
place is kind of empty and you guys are
when we're like deep in the game you
guys don't spam that much
[Music]
anyway Tom Tonight
Tonight uh the times times are
changing
tonight the time difference is changing
and my time zone will go back 1
hour
tonight
tonight let's go daylight having
time
[Music]
it's like in some way sometimes I feel
like it makes it easier to reach Japan
when I start later
but also like yeah if I start at my
usual time it's like worse but if I
start later than I usually start like
maybe at 10 p.m. then it's already like
6 a.m. for them rather than 5 a.m. so
for like sea and Asia it's
better and for you
guys like you guys na a it's like you
guys don't do daylight savings time
right do you I forgot but basically
we're getting closer right oh you do but
for now we're closer
right yeah you do it one so okay it's
just for one week uh we only have I
think with est a 5H hour difference
rather than 6
hours that's not even that bad
honestly that time difference isn't even
that
bad one week you'll be close to us yeah
just one week M enjoy enjoy we don't do
it in
Argentina why I was going to make a joke
but I'm not going to do it I'm not going
to do it I know not going to do
[Laughter]
it
uh think most of lam doesn't
oh no no no
no
[Laughter]
no um so I'm not necessary near the eat
well why is it is it like the time
actually like the the the the way the
sun goes up and down doesn't differ that
much is that
what or do you just not care cuz like it
differs a lot here but so many austrians
are so Shake of it they want it to go
away they don't want the tell also H uh
I would like to hereby
announce one of our
longtime
members in kfp M SAU is not the person
who we thought they
were as they are in their 20s and in in
North America and still their whole life
have not eaten eggs
[Laughter]
before um and I am challenging you to go
eat some eggs
ASAP
otherwise we will have to talk about it
in
private they're not vegan they have no
allergies against eggs or stuff like
that like there's nothing holding them
back they said in the pre- chat
it's just how it is
and you're not B of me dude like he also
hasn't had bacon
before what else have you not had before
yeah they live in New York like there's
eggs everywhere I thought like oh maybe
they live somewhere where eggs are
somehow not that big of a
[Laughter]
thing eggs are everywhere eggs eggs eggs
eggs so
oh please
please go eat them they're they're
good please it's good for you they're
actually healthy too like what the
hell yeah I I wouldn't recommend
drinking them uh
raw but cook them into something or go
somewhere where they use eggs maybe a
breakfast restaurant somebody kept on
mentioning this Greek place in New York
y who do a great job on eggs
apparently some New York
Insider what was it called take him to
IHOP oh yeah go to an IHOP I guess not
xlot but I guess you could go to xlot
too yeah dodging eggs for 20 plus years
it's
crazy crazy I mean I'm sure in some way
like maybe like some somewhere hidden in
a food you had it before but like just
you know something that is mainly eggs
they say they haven't had before so that
is a crime that is a
crime yeah you had cake yeah I don't
really see that as an egg dish so that's
different but you need to have an egg
dish please yeah and you were also an
egg before M and you not vegan you eat
chicken so go eat
egg my God otherwise I cannot rest
assured that you are fulfilling the
purpose of your life also you are not
allowed to use egg
puns until you eat an
egg eat your
eggs and the bacon while you're at it
eat some bacon what else have you not
eaten before
that's crazy that everybody
eats what else are you going to shock me
for life about this is like the shock
most shocking things thing I a lot of
things like what I did you like grow up
in like a bunker or what like sorry but
this reminds me of the Kimmy Kimmy uh uh
Kimmy Netflix show uh
unbreakable Kim me like growing up in
like a cult bunker
for yeah kimy Schmid your whole life and
not like getting all these
things how is this possible it's like
fascinating I feel like I want to study
you like science this like a pickup line
I want to study you like
science this is natural pickup line I
didn't mean it like that I really want
to study you like
science I'll make a document about
you I'm sorry I can't I can't not let
this I can't let this go I can't let
this
go see I'm even translating your story
to
Japanese
what's going
on the eggs are ready for you and
they're like you can order something
right now isn't it you're in New York
isn't it like a good time for a good
brunch go out or order some brunch now
with
eggs I forgot I need to bring my my
phone over from my tangents otherwise
I'm absolutely lost when I'm back you
will have eaten eggs
okay I'm expecting
it
I totally didn't check out my cats for a
moment totally
didn't
okay
yeah I thought I F I found a chunky
wonky cuz it was her favorite spot in my
class closet but it was actually
smoothie
surprising very surprising but you guys
don't give a I guess so let's
go it's okay it's okay you don't you
probably don't care that much about my
cats it's
okay it's it's special to me like seeing
my cats in unusual places is very
special to
me oh
where have we ended last time it's
like a furnace in here we're inside the
volcano you get used to the heat I don't
remember it being quite this
hot we're in a
volcano why are we in a volcano
ah I guess I
remember getting closer to this place
oh I I can't see so well in the Dark
Places cuz like the sun is shining on my
screen a little
bit we're breaking the ah Crystal
breaking the music's
nice that one cause for concern it
was okay how do I fight
again let's test it at least this time
our test object will be um
oh
uh these these small guys and not a boss
monster like last
time get him get him get
him so have you guys seen the
ID uh I I I mean I understand if you
wouldn't want to collab because I I they
didn't speak in the single word to Eng I
think the only word they spoke in
English was swimsuit when they said
swimsuit in the middle of Indonesian
talk so I understand like not like
saying uh not watching if you but they
performed some songs and that was cute
so that might be worth it you know
um they were cute like and Kyla like
like constantly moves like a freaking
dork Kyla's so funny she's just like so
long she's so
long she's the longest person ever
besides besides Ellie of
course to kill tole kill wow okay chill
the
out her L like even with the swimsuit
model which is I don't know if you guys
know but they don't for the swimsuits
they don't even use our actual models
bodies have you guys
noticed it's just like a
like a base model and they put our heads
on it have you guys
seen yeah
efficiency for for most members it's not
like a big issue but then there's some
members where because of the art style
of their mommy of their artist like KY
for
example for sake I had flying
enemies uh that then it loses like a lot
of its like charm I
guess
yeah crony as well crony kyella those
kind of
peeps anyone who has like not like super
typical anime stick
bodies I mean those are stick bodies too
like in a different way you know like
like some artists they have a very
special way of drawing
bodies and if you have an artist like
that who doesn't have like super basic
proportions that's what I mean
then no it looks different from usual
stands
out my
body my I don't know what do you guys
think does it look better in the
swimsuit actually cuz like my butt looks
nicer I think in the swimsuit
of can we talk about that for a moment
like yeah game audio low okay one
second go is it really guys is really
low the shorts maybe it's the shorts but
like at the same time I don't know I
think it's more than just the shorts am
I going in the right
direction little low
okay just raised it a tiny bit probably
not even noticeable salamanda I I I
wasn't there a song like that salamanda
How does it
go help me sing it for
me oh my God can you stop Spitting Fire
have you like do you have anything else
in your repertoire oh my God
boring boring little
and he's one of the strong boys too
oh
dear you you
y here
uh uh uh uh I don't know I don't
know here take this take this I guess
take take this and this and this and
whatever yeah pretty good pretty
good oh he still stays in the same place
nice
nice use of the lightning or yeah it was
totally on purpose yeah yeah that's why
I went to go get that yeah mhm let's
try uh take down what do you oh yeah
well just throw in some more hits yeah
yeah spam spam spam the hits perfect
setup mhm mhm yeah I know I know I know
that's just me that's just my my play
style oh there's some weird door and but
you can also go right side so hard to
see for me maybe it's a dead
end you can barely see
it let me close
curtains okay oh that's much better
that's much better I'm in a Cinema
now yeah sun shining on my
screen what what do you call no uh
what's olad like the switch if you have
an olad screen does that exist for like
normal monitors
too the GMA is genuinely low though
yeah super bright OLED monitor yeah but
I guess I most of the time I don't have
the situation where the sun is shining
on my screen with a dark game I could
also just change the position of my
table against the window I guess and
even less I would have this problem
um
wrong
button screen
brightness maybe a little bit less
actually just a tiny
[Music]
bit got
a so what about
this I don't know where to go first man
I hate this don't give me so many
options no there's
[Music]
okay is there a map no is there no
other way across oh oh you actually are
asking for another way okay then okay so
this is the dead end
and
okay
they first wanted me to see that and
then go here as if I as if this path was
so hard to
find oh wow I'm a genius for finding
this path wow
[Music]
so illusion of choice increase the
brightness and no it's too dark for
you huh I
mean are you sure
I I think it's best to just show the
game the way it is but it's just a
little bit dark in general I would
say I mean maybe your screens are dark
cuz yeah I think it's fine I'm not going
to not no no no
no no but one second I want to check
something
no
okay yeah we're in a volcano okay
everywhere where
there's lava is where it's going to be
bright and everywhere else is just
dark I
suppose outside it will be bright
again doesn't look that dark to me
though wait did I go the wrong
way he did
I huh cuz that door didn't
open R free what's
what's what what did you have right is
that is that what you needed to Super
Chat
me where the am I going
I I'm
lost
animal how do you do that again he's so
angry cuz I keep on running around like
an
idiot okay okay okay so for a while I
was going
back
go but we already fought this oh my god
when did I turn around hey but this
boxes oh
okay did I go in a
circle
got is it a circle oh no he but didn't
they say is there any other way or
maybe there was another way like
actually through the gate and
then are you sure
too cuz like they were like is there any
other
way oh I guess St we're like we wish
there was another way but we have to
take this
way ow come on misunderstanding
corner I took it literally cuz there was
another way at least I thought
so what what
what what are you going to do with your
ice freeze
it did I say
what did I write in my twin we did I did
I not forget about her I wrote we had
wind thunder and fire and I actually
forgot about her I just
realized this is going to be close we I
forgot to much nice but she's really
cool though right
now well we don't have her true we don't
have her power in our body yeah that's
true okay I totally knew that and and
and
yeah that's why I wrote it like that
let's not do that again game volume's
still low that's
not well it was fine don't you think it
was fine what we just
did wasn't a big
deal oh I stopped
moving okay I don't look too tough
perhaps not alone but in numbers like
these you know the way she
talks reminds me like her voice and her
accent obviously probably mostly that
reminds me a little bit of uh
Pandora
Pandora or there's another
girl um I think her name was
uh never mind never
mind
what this
one there's only so many British
YouTubers like
two this one a what the is it doing
though am I is he going to good I
didn't know how to leave because like I
was focused on that little why wow
chill my
God you can think of 10 wow why are they
not joining H life please uh I need
someone with a British accent and Stream
in my time
zone Drake's breath Drake's breath the
or Tre this this this
stuff wow
real
brid remember to spam the skills what
the hell is that I have absolutely no
idea well whatever it is I don't think
it's
friendly
ow
hello what the
come
on
oh
oh what wait what is what what is going
on
uh okay okay okay okay
okay sometimes I'm like not sure in what
state I actually am or like the
mob
over here what's that
ow what the is this monster red
moose come
on
die over
here no
good iconic punishment let's go oh My
Ghost was so smaller small
ghost
okay I'm dying let's
go oh
chest give me a Potion No my
w wish wilets
wilets
that's exactly how you say it right
weets wait I already have them
huh huh I got another
pair what no no wait it was on them and
I was just looking at the new ones I'm
so confused I'm so sorry well those are
much
better
okay
should I look at my build
[Music]
2,000 what do we want to get with 2,000
I was like saving for some
stuff maybe a g upgrade with do uh what
does it do increases follow-up strike
speed
okay
this sa for judement Bol this one okay
we're pretty close all right all
right no it's G trust me I know English
better than all of
you what
the LA to be like what the
if I Didn't Know Better
I think this volcano was about to
erupt let's go
eruption sexy peaceful creatures
cute wait it reminds me of the big fat
uh thing of uh
the uh Dungeons and Dragons
movie didn't we fight this thing again
before
it's cute it's
cute
cute wa let me do my
thing there we go let's go
too
hey
uh okay uh what's going on how do I
fight again I
forgot
woo
W sick uh oh I don't have oh no
it's already I can't I'm stupid I'm
stupid let's go oh let's go let's go
let's go let's
go
get all
yours what's it doing I don't know
nothing good it's annoying because I
literally just activated my super
cool fire Prime
sub
[Music]
n
nice nice get him you can't get me your
range is
[Music]
W this
one cycling through all my Powers at
least once
completely
me
almost let's go let's go you didn't get
me you didn't get
[Music]
me let's
go is it using the thing probably not
now oh
no
niceo nice he's like throwing me around
kind of of fun it's kind of fun nice
try how many times you going to become
ball huh round boy he wants to be a a a
hedgehog he's pretty close to being
one
oh nice a nice timing okay
okay spiky
boy spiky ancient
Sonic he's ancient Sonic
yeah gar scale all right that's uh fine
that was fine
cute ah
oh that's sad are you hurt I'm
hurt in my C it's hot
[Music]
the way he just fell down man it's like
they're roasting
him let's hope the guards didn't hear
it the gate to the inner Chambers is
just up there I'm so connected to Jill
cuz I also for the sanctuary drank I
need to finish
this before the heat finishes me you
mean the drink or dis
Quest it would make sense if she was
talking about the drink is in context
we'll enter the com by the hand living
quarters it was always a hive of
activity sounds like we'll have a hard
time staying out of sight we won't have
to there's someone there I should very
much like to
see I will not mention handmaid tale
just because I heard handmaidens I will
not mention it I will not mention it cuz
my brain it doesn't work that simple
okay you can't just say one word and
make me feel think about you know
something that I watched where that word
is being used I'm more complex and more
of a complicated uh far thinking
Universe brain kind of
person I'm not that
simple it's hard to understand me not
like the other girls you
[Laughter]
know she's not even wearing red why
would I think of the handmaid tail
they're not wearing red
so there's no connection
at
all wow we're so sneaky right out in the
open so
sneaky Oh Lady
M it's me trying to be
sneaky chill it can't be no it is it is
it is my lady
we cannot talk here come with
me
[Music]
what why are they in a
volcano I'm so glad you're
safe and I use
you why ever would you risk coming back
are you a fool girl or have you g tired
of your freedom
already forgive me my lady but I had to
come
back there are things I left
undone tell me where is the
patriarch
at this hour he'll be in the
comre giving
thanks you
mean oh fiend n
Clive we have to get to the sanctuary
now lady Marley you must flee this place
gather your things and
go now listen here Jill in we have
company oh
guards the mods of the
volcano this
way follow this passage it leads
straight to the com what that come on
stop Doling yeah for real like why
people always Dole so
much you were always so kind to
me my light in the
darkness that's sweet take care my lady
please you deserve better than this a
long and happy life promise
me
are they going to kill
her I'll live if you promise to do the
same you
better talking is a free
[Music]
action come on
Clive we're nearly at the comre all
right all
right yeah anyway on the topic of
idea today was the collab and yesterday
was
the wow the cobal fre deut showcase
whatever here's our welcoming party you
surely watched it right
everybody so
and K said it's okay to say like I'm
obviously that wherever I was part of
was
pre-recorded I flew to Japan for KOB
Frey
showcase she asked me if I would come
this is why I said she owes me
dinner oh made to be
broken um but you know it was my
pleasure
I'm really happy to have been involved
in this it was fun I was really
excited kle chose a really fun song for
us which is kind of
about some
girls wanting to become president and
making arguments about why they should
be the president but the lyrics are
really funny
cuz I think one one part of my lyrics
was
like I'm going to for everybody who says
something uh about blah blah blah I'm
going to
stick uh uh a dyon or something up your
ass um something like that yeah so the
lyrics are
fun just up my alley which way is it by
the way which alley is
it
um
oh
Secret
is this the path I don't want to if
there's two paths I want to go to the
dead end path
first
[Music]
understand chicken stuff with donon
could be good oh yeah doggo says that
way okay okay I should ask dog more
often
[Music]
um eh can I open this one too no and so
so yeah and when I flew to Japan we had
a dance lesson with a teacher ah okay I
then list with teacher and then um
because brain H we had one more dance
lesson without a teacher just with us
that was like kind of like the coach
like getting her to kind of controlling
like let's do it one more time let's do
it one more time let's do it one more
time let's I wasn't stoping cuz also I
really felt like I needed how many of
them are too many ow I needed more
practice too so I kept on ow for
sake getting Co
to uh get up and dance more but we had a
lot of fun practicing together we were
like laughing so much and I feel like
it's like maybe the most fun I had uh
ever with another po member at a dance
lesson cuz like she's she's just ah
she's so she's always such a fun cutie
patootie to be around and always brings
a lot of
energy and fun to everywhere she
goes
those were the times
when I don't want to focus on that
little
[Applause]
ass yeah uh what was I saying what was I
saying
what that
ah all
your oh that was the time thank you that
was the time where I where we took the
the whole the messages that's why we
were together cuz we were
practicing could you imagine oh my God
surprise yeah on on uh the dance on the
day where we were doing it with a
teacher
um I also met the a couple you know a
couple the
other her gen mates were also there for
a moment cuz they were just like ending
their dance
lesson oh this
way I didn't think they would be there
and I didn't wear makeup so I was really
embarrassed but it was so nice to see
them they're so cute
attack oh and we had this like really
tiny um Studio to dance in but uh it was
it was quite comfy and jenma and K's
manager were also like chilling while we
were dancing in there doing work on
their
laptops but
get I I kept on cuz like when you dance
it obviously gets hot right so I kept on
turning on uh turning the the AC colder
and colder and colder and kobal kept on
like freaking out about it like what the
was that it's so cold how you're
hot what why you hot I'm like yeah we're
dancing you know and I'm used to
different weather please let me make it
colder was that the wrong way oh ah this
way oh my
God and sometimes I think either her or
jenma there something I need you to know
someone would like sneakily turn the
freaking uh AC back warmer again and and
I I'm like what the I would notice
immediately like something's wrong
something's wrong here it's it's changed
even though it was just like maybe
2 and I would figure it out and then
turn turn it cooler
again has to be like when we're dancing
you know it's hot it's nice to have a
cold
climate too hot for for
me who dares yeah who dares and then I
when she was like too cold I was like
kobble I came to Japan for you okay we
will have my
temperature I feel a disturbance in the
forest exactly
remember when Ollie was freezing in the
summer that's like literally
impossible I can't imagine how how that
even is possible summon from the heavens
a mighty 11 B
wow
[Music]
wow which
one this
one I guess we have a new one saw the
patriarch do things no one should have
to see oh and so I swore that he would
die by my hand I
understand I face my demons and you must
face yours wait
which
okay are we byy any chance having more
similarities with the handmaid's tail
than I
[Music]
thought
M you know in the Coro there were like
several moves where um we would kind of
do a very similar movement but the
timings where we would do it were just
very slightly one beat off like one of
us would do it earlier the other one
would do it one beat later for
example
and I was actually like sometimes
struggling a little bit with that and
with uh automatic Ally adjusted to
kobo's timing maybe my brain just likes
to have things like matching and on the
same beat and
K after a while she like kept on like
roasting me and like looking angrily
like jokingly angrily at me whenever I
did that but whenever I actually got it
right she was like like she did the
happiest cutest face ever and got really
excited it's so weird her expressions
are so cute I can't get over
it yeah actually I think in the end uh
our last
pose I think she actually messed up even
though I was usually the one who would
mess up um but she we were supposed like
we were beat off like with our moves
that was on purpose um there was like a
difference there but the moment where we
look at each other should have been the
same and she didn't we didn't look at
each other at the same time so we
up
there
but besides that uh we're pretty well I
would say we're nearly there just one
last
push and yeah I would I would love to
dance with K again because freaking so
much fun so much
dorkiness and I love how she also just
like messes around so much and obviously
really
enjoys dancing a lot like I can
tell
just really shows
it I not dance moreel football but
well I don't know if we get many
opportunities
because oh oh oh okay
chill cuz she's normally in Indonesia
and I'm normally in Austria so I feel
like you know for
like if I want her to be in my like
birthday frd for example that I get only
once in a year then she has to be able
in Japan otherwise it's not going to
work out right
so
chance is probably
generally kind of
low oh too
late
ow to me
FL for sake for
sake
and we just don't have many op like
opportunities to actually dance in Ford
at least usan
girls besides like the concert obviously
but in the concert it's
like not really my
choice to say I want to dance with this
person I want our unit to be
uh consistent of this consisting of
these people and so
on so I really really hope that there
will be
another opportunity in the future to
dance with babo she's my baby on babo
like I really liked her 3D stream like
overall like
storyline the beginning was so cute when
she was like singing in the
classroom about her boyfriend oh as
smart
that one oh my
God the way they were using the
camera tell a story and all
that it was so freaking cute my heart
went doy
doie I guess there's a sacrifice going
on
here and then you know she she the
boyfriend gets stolen by Zetta then
she's sad about it
so then she talks to cie her dad Uncle
dad about it Uncle dad wants to again
Revenge they sing a song about being
heartbroken which I will I was uh
watching by the
way on the side was so funny this is not
so funny on the other
hand they looked so dorky they were like
purpose I don't it actually came less
across less dorky maybe in the final
product but they were pretty dorky IRL
so funny they're just messing around
man okay let's let's focus on this for
now Sha's dominance that's
me that's you come to beg forgiveness
for your
failure my failure for years I followed
your orders
fought your
Wars all to protect the children you
took just as you took
me and what did you do in return yeah
tell him tell him
to you put them in Chains and you
slipped their
throats fet probably pretty proud of it
their souls were sullied with a stain of
ether I merely cleanse them of their
corruption a Penance pay or just do them
a favor just as the holy mother wills it
villain logic repent Abomination you
mean Abomination EXC for a monster like
you to set foot in the Holy C is in
itself a crime deserving of death you're
right I am a monster
and my soul is stained
black though not by
Ether but by the evil of men like you
who made me close my heart and drown in
darkness when I should have raged
against
it this is my Penance I will correct his
English yeah I will be your monster no
more nor will I suffer you to create
another
[Laughter]
does the Beast bear its teeth at its
Master to go up the stairs rage as you
have ever been a monster and what are
you
Imran I was forced to kill you do it by
choice but never again I bowed to you
once now it is you who shall bow to
me kill
them oo
yeah now
right Jill is in
control
oh
what's up with that mysterious
boy what who turns out to not be
Joshua where is he like that's not
Joshua right he he was also alone and we
already saw Joshua so the game has no
reason to hide him still from
me I don't think it's
Joshua they're just trying to fool us
into thinking Joshua does evil
things I don't
know but I think that's what they're
doing is that like another fire dominum
thing what's going
on
wow
yes full Prime baby
Flawless
skin
no
chill
that fire
Ultima come on remember how it
felt
sorry but
like he's not able to
perform when he wants to must be
tough why why can't I do
it I don't know I don't really I really
don't know why you can't do it I
wish you could do
it
Ice
Arena iconic
dysfunction please just
once yeah yeah let out the ultra
growl that's how it works do we get
another big fight like the whoosh whoosh
whoosh no no she won't be able to hold
that love
forever make this
quick those
steps funny
oh did I just
carry
W oh my
God yeah you got to show me more than
that over
here oh ah that almost switched away
from it I almost panick at
that wait let me put that here
way oh yeah I should have waited a
little bit for wasting all my attacks
like
this but at least we got go
go oh that's it that's all I
have yeah oh this
one low low damage sorry cuz I wasted
everything a
ow all
your oh I I swear I dodged but okay
okay Dodge Coin stons are
low
oh damn it damn it that's better
go ah wait wait yes sky gy gy
gy
tole kill tole
kill what is he doing
oh Jill protect
me oh that that
love look like so
Blobby now it's looking better for
sure where was the texture on
that Molten chees
she's so
pretty I love her
right I won't take
long oh he became an
animal what the hell what the
hell
okay what the hell like give me some
chance to do something
too oh my
god let's
try why is he a shape shifter suddenly
huh let's
try
[Music]
okay come
on oh he pisses me
off that's weak though nice
try
waken close
get
him okay okay nice
Dodge wa this attack why is that so
funny to me that reminds me of some Acro
acrobatics or something
maybe get
him I needed that a Sumo
Slam come on stagger the out of him
now too
slow get
him does this use up a lot of time when
I do
this all yours to now
to y okay this should be good damage
yeah
35k
oh 11th Hour what the
what NY what is this good
oh my
what
are you done oh
what that that covered the whole
area how was I supposed to steal
that not good okay I might die I might
die
get
him hoping to get some heal but don't I
have to attack in order to get heals
too I'm so close
no no
no
no I so close man so
close some parts of that fight were
really like what the is going
[Music]
on black rent curl
hey I
dodged too
slow okay why is the camera so weird
too I hate this I hate this
thing
flag R wion okay seems like you can be
anything but this should be
inspiring
go kind of annoying you
are oh
sometimes it feels a bit more lenient
than that the timing of deadly
Embrace get
him over
here
oops come on help me boy oh wait help me
boy who's trying to look
for the potions can you let me attack
you for once
please I swear to God you pissed me
off all yours
to
knil in front of the
Wawa Jill's just chilling in the
background cool good for
her
[Music]
too
slow all yours
to this
one
attack oh just stop already my
God
why you got to be like
that maybe most annoying boss in this
game for
me okay okay oh and staggered no half
staggered make
mistake
okay anti climatic
ending Paris paries do feel good when it
happens yeah that's for
sure unnecessary death but super
annoying
enemy
[Laughter]
I reminded me of the meme you know long
time
ago when I did that video I was like
blowing at my tea and then was it
pudding who made the edit where um after
blowing like he put like a really really
really it was hot CH really loud
disgusting cough on top of
it
like that was so funny Moy sent that to
me a while ago that's why I have it in
my brain recently but she thought it was
real
I'm like no money it's not real to
Ed
it so
funny can I had another idea I'm so
sorry about
the I'm I I I I'll try to take it more
serious but while we're here do we have
some new active time
ler wa I'll look
later I'm going to finish this clim look
how you pretty close to finishing
it she's not okay my
God oh my
God does
she aftermath of Corona
much what the
here use
this now she gives me her
power wait is she adding it like temp
like just now temporarily or
permanently her lung is turning to
Stone oh my god
what temporary buff
okay pretty
Crystal break
[Music]
it
hey are you watching
Sid any SIDS in the chat one step closer
to Freedom
the
crystal what did you do to
it let's kill him stab him oh we
destroyed it what
but poke him to death monster do iter no
mercy do you have any idea what you have
done no mercy Jo
father I have killed yeah the
monster thank you for an outlaw not
being
lame May the blessing of the crystals go
with
you
yeah it's
over it
is and shiver exacted up
prise she
did again the burden F to
you and I bore it
willingly this was a sin for which I had
to atone now I can continue at your side
with my head held high
yay
and she bore his child
willingly
uhuh Clive
look it's just like the want at Phoenix
gate
oh damn it we need to leave agreed
everything always falls apart when you
destroy the
core oh oh that's creepy that's
so creepy holy
but it's not Joshua cuz like you
don't see you don't even see the
hair
ooh that looks so
awesome
whoa yeah oh look look look
up it's
beautiful maybe also poisonous oh CH cuz
of the fumes I kept my promise now you
keep
yours that's
beautiful
yeah
yeah we did
it thank you thank you PlayStation thank
you Joshy
boy oh no he's C is
BR this way your grace is this like a
case of pandemic it really do be p
pmic pandemic of becoming
Stone you're
bleeding I have a tonic which will I
thank you for your kindness truly but I
assure you I Will Survive please save
your medicines for those who need them
most oh oh well if you're
sure that's sweet for a moment there I
felt my brother's
presence you
did I fear he is in ultima's thoughts
again oh but why now after five years of
Silence
I cannot keep him sealed away much
longer Your
Grace no do not dirty your
[Music]
hands there's an ultim side of all of
us yeah look at them all
deep like a river flowing to the Sea
philosophical Phoenix or must to a flame
perhaps the crystalline Dominion their
light in the
darkness more and more loose their homes
to the blight and set out in search of
sanctuary While others lose their
fortunes to the dmean levies and leave
to find new
livelihoods are a cookies still good
what is it that you seek in the Dominion
your grace
oh Dion lash you mean the Crown Prince
of
s he has many titles Dion the Bold
Prince of
drons Odin's Nemesis or simply Bahamut
Bahamut I met him once when we were
children he was a chivalrous Soul even
then and has served his empire
indefatigably ever since
and you are confident that he will
listen to what you have to
say our world lurches ever closer to the
abyss and a Hidden Hand ushers us onward
Ultimus influence extends to Every
Nation SRE
included If His Highness is the man I
believe him to be and I pray that he is
this truth will not have escaped his
notice
as the mother crystals fall the Eternal
Flame wavers and the Azure Sky begins to
bruise how lucky we were to be blessed
by the
crystals and yet how
spoiled
like canaries in a g builded cage
growing fat on seed just like you
guys but now the bars are closing in and
we must take
flight painful though it be to leave our
home behind it is what we must do to be
[Music]
free which is it that men cannot live
without a blessing that leads to
damnation or a freedom that leads to
deprivation uh uh what I do not yet know
the answer to that question I also do
not know the meaning of the
question your grace let us find a place
to rest a while we can return by the
Delian Trail once you have recovered
your strength I realize your duty is
pressing but if your health should
fail I know thank you y
y not J not hot
Y what a good wing
woman
the Army's attempt to breach the
Empire's defenses and gain the Isles of
Ark has failed yet again only because
your fleet has proved as impotent as a
unic on laying night you we back to the
capital enough both of you all here agre
think I know what a un is allowed to
maintain it on the Dominion however our
casualties just make a eggs
joke have no peee
right there is a literal sea Twix you
and your prize the armies of Sam bre
need but sit back and watch as you
harmlessly lap against their
walls they are dug in like ticks and
seek to draw out this Siege knowing the
capital stores are n
bottomless and what of our wise
rulers goed into war without any thought
as to what chaos it might
reap oh he's
cool Republican soldiers starve while
waiting for orders from
randar if you would but take the field
their bellies would be full by Nightfall
if I take the field soou will baham it
and our duel will shake the island to
its
foundations instead of liberating the
Dominion you would Doom it to
destruction
unless that is what you desire that's
reasonable right of him to say um no if
our learned advisor has a solution to
propose we should be glad to consider
it so he's a reasonable
villain oh
Mommy they made a new channel is that
the
empress that chat looks
traumatized what is the meaning of this
Lord kopka we have prepared a child what
it
means is that I am disinclined to advise
you any
longer
okay ah the looks on their faces is when
you walked through those doors a perfect
picture of
stupefaction they could not believe
their eyes though I confess I had my own
doubts whether or not you would accept
my
invitation she's uh not as Happ happy as
I thought you would such shocking
news Sid isn't a son of a
he's the son of an empress H your
own dear Clive what absurd okay s who
fed you these lies they didn't mean the
old Sid I have never spent a moment
among criminals save at The Gallows I
came here with my son not to entertain
your baseless accusations but to put an
end to the senseless hostilities between
our Nations very well you need only
agree to the terms I set
out Sid took the life of someone dear to
me a Woman by the name of benedicta
confusing that even he call I swore to
take his inter
turn this would not be disagreeable to
you I take it
you would finally be rid of the stain on
your Noble
name in return I will leave sandre in
your capable
hands your
Imperial
Majesty just feels a little bit
unnecessary to me to make that whole
thing a thing that
clist and all for the love of a common
called Sid from that moment on
dominant or no one cannot hide one's
breeding and Beast will ever belong with
beasts
this this is there are greater things in
store for you my darling Olivia
soon enough you shall be the Crown
Prince of
SRE and when your father goes to meet
great
Grier you shall be emperor of all you
survey the old order shall come tumbling
down and you will rebuild the world in
your glorious image feel like she's
drugging her her son in some
way
soon
like some weird is going on
there so that you know she doesn't fail
like she did with Joshua she's been in
there for
hours something must be
wrong this time she'll do it right
she create a new version of herself
basically for her
child hey we are back in our
headquarters ad
Turtle it's a turtle hi small
turtle not this door it's never that
door okay I'm drinking Coca-Cola so
is it true what I'm hearing I don't like
what's happening to me when I drink
Coca-Cola did you didn't hear it did you
you don't say you just say you didn't
hear small small t
[Music]
house
no so what it
be E I don't know what what will be this
this thing maybe should I is it
worth it's better it needs the liquid
flame which is ah the thing that I just
got from the boss monster so not
bad
myself yeah I'm really like
against you
know these kind of bodily human
functions uh in my
body should last you a good while like I
don't want
to show
[Music]
them anything else wait did the things I
just make were were they worse
huh H
partially and the demon T massage gives
me Health
too I don't know oh what's
better what for
de that's at least
reinforcers yeah that should do you and
this okay and then this one gets some
health too
[Music]
okay okay thanks black
porn you're such a nice dude where am I
going
[Music]
let us know if you find any rotting
planks maybe
here in one way or another we will reach
the goal cuz this is all connected like
a
circle the plus Quest that's just the
the hunt
board I I don't really I don't know
isn't that like basically just telling
me to go
hunt one stupid
monster
wait I'm following the plus now I'm so
you confused me but there's another
plus but I want to go to the main quest
actually I don't know ah it's so
confusing oh fake
doors hate
them I've done what I can but the rest
is up to you you need to start taking
better care of yourself
potion upgrades I do want potion
upgrades
understood and thank
you CSE spread make sure she
rests make sure she wears clothes before
you walk
in if it
hurts you can tell me in you know I'll
understand I can bear
it oh maybe you shouldn't have
to not
anymore this isn't just your struggle
Clive it's
ours and when we see how hard you fight
it inspires us to do the same
or would you rather we left you to save
the world all on your
own
no that's
not ignore
me
oh and someone will interrupt now life
where are
you in
here
you gape or whatever it was what's wrong
hell Rose are is under attack
give what okay he's a cool dude but you
ruined the
moment God damn it this isn't the dmean
Army which talking about it's the men of
the Rock from Drake's Fang Hugo cop's
private
God there is in hell in roosth trying to
batter down the castle gats gats looking
for
me seems that way reckon old Hugo has
finally worked out who Sid really
is then this is just another trap ah
it's a trap all right the dad of all
traps okay I'm going to
roosth you're not serious that's exactly
what he wants you to do Clive
look I don't know why kahab is such a
grudge against Sid but as long as it's
left to
faster our world will never know
peace he has dragged the rest of storm
into this pointless War just to find
me beside which I'm not about to stand
and watch while my home gets ground into
the dirt such a
[Music]
hero Hugo CA Must Die must
die I have lost enough friends to that
man
already I don't want to lose
anymore so let's go and kill the bastard
he wants to join let him join for once
I'm coming too will he actually join
after we're in this together are we
bringing him all
right are we bringing
him no way I should probably speak to
Otto before leaving his dream is coming
true we need to know what we're getting
ourselves
into he's going to be so
[Music]
happy uh what's this about I didn't
finish black porn's Quest
[Music]
either wait that's just a
board what where is the other wasn't
there another plus Quest I'm so
confused this is just a hunt board we
must be ready to leave for roosth at a
moment's notice don't worry everyone's
prepared yeah the monster the
monster where where is it
then I want to look at the board not a
you
okay which thing this
thing SRE can I go there now car North
went who the remembers what's
written
[Music]
here can't even read
it
uh
[Music]
what was I there
before ah this place no
almost unless maybe it's connected to
the
this maybe I'll go there for
now item oo free
potion uh what what
uh it was
no no
nor Rivergate
no can I even get there
now this
area oh it is at the River Gate for real
for
real okay can I make a
mark okay
[Music]
uh choo
Cho oh uh how do I ride you again uh X
let's go okay let me lower the jam a bit
and think think
think
about uh book 3D again what else was
there to say yeah yeah I was like
watching
Callie and uh babo do their thing they
were so
funny like B just you know she'll just
bring out these random Tik Tok meme
dances out of
nowhere but also like they were moving
so dorky but still Kobo sings so
beautifully and like Callie's rap is
just like really you know cool as always
but then they move like freaking dorks
it's
fascinating get
off yeah so good girl then The Story
Goes On from like cie being the like
protective
dad
to them
uh can't pass here can I
them uh you know like being very
dramatic Bo like shoot me shoot me dead
so
cute and then I show
up
to be like what the is
happening your parenting sucks why leave
my child to me
basically and does I'm look at the map
up and
left and thus uh I take
over and oh yeah she she dead right so I
cry and I didn't even think of it in the
mo
moment
but I just thought it was like you know
one of those typical moments where you
know you cry and The Tear magically
revives or heals the
person but I didn't even think of it as
like a phoenix tier like that it was
just healing her spe specifically
because of me being a phoenix maybe that
was the
case but wasn't it really great acting I
was I was like crying so
dramatically and and like uh I was like
told um stay stay stay stay cuz they
because of the tier right and they
wanted to get it on camera
properly and whenever they would turn on
their microphone for my earpiece in the
production area I heard them laughing so
hard all the time like generally I feel
like the the staff had a blast with this
whole
production oh yeah yeah that was one
funny thing so we had to like plan out a
little bit you know um because of the
tear and everything like where exactly
kble would die here oh okay
and
so here what is this
[Music]
oh they were just going to like Mark it
in a really simple way on on the on the
floor but then I was like once they put
like one small marker on I was like hey
this looks like one of those like crime
scenes is the with like the dead
body uh drawn on the ground of chalk
chalk
and I told them to like put the marker
around her whole body so on the floor we
had like taped out her whole body just
for fun like it wasn't necessary but we
just did it cuz it was
funny for Coble well this way she knew
exactly where to
die
perfect M and yeah so that happened I
revived her and then we
sang uh
Our Song which was so difficult for me
by the way to sing cuz the the the part
where we go like
s that was so difficult for me to
learn but it was so much fun like we
were messing around and um then that
ended but that wasn't the end of me so
if you guys like were watching the
reveal of herd and then you watch that
part and then you thought okay W part is
over I'm turning off back to the
archives with you because it wasn't over
there I came back at the end for a
little uh you know ending song ending
fun with everybody
yeah the ID Girls and and kowi and me we
came
back for some more celebration cuz kobal
announced
something H about her you know releasing
a song with a joint label I honestly I
was like what the what is
this I don't know what it is joint
label all right I literally don't know
but congratulations she deserves it like
she's she's so talented and she's doing
so well so I'm happy for her to get such
a
chance so where is this thing will I see
it and so for celebrating that we came
back at the end PR and babo was there
too not Yago was there
too small small
Yago seems like the Griffin should be
here he said something about it the way
you picked him up yeah her Lighthouse is
so cool
too she's got like so many areas to use
like the beach then the room then the
stage she even has like an
elevator there it is
[Music]
that was damn another work we have to
wait tole look sharp and just generally
I really like how they put so
much detail and ideas into
her into her whole
like coo
area but also
nice try I'm just going to guess that
all of these ideas of how the stream was
going to go are mostly from kble and I
must say she's such an entertainment
genius like for real for
real really love all the ideas she had
for this and also I love the part that
you know she would take a moment to play
her acoustic
[Music]
guitar oh what the
there's a good
boy oh oh sorry I don't know what I'm
[Music]
doing she was even able to take off her
jacket for that which looked really cool
like she looked so casual I can't do
that I don't really have anything to
take off
really
all
let's
try now
go attack but she sang so beautiful
right think so
well all yours
tole now tole
I love his showcase I think that's like
definitely one of the best
showcases cuz it had so many so much
personality so much charm it's not like
too perfect either you know there's like
so much fooling around and you really
just see what kind of a person she
is it's so much
creativity and honestly her mom is just
so cute too my God nice try her
hair is so
fluffy everything is just
perfect I don't want to heal myself you
heal me
too not good okay I guess I'll heal
myself kill
good
a oh it's not too late F I feel like
when you're in that skill it gives you
more leeway actually it let's it it
waits for
[Music]
you
a
all yours
to what the what
wow
wasted just zooming
off that's better oh my
God oh my
[Music]
God doing my best
yeah come
on almost dead uh
no give him some go SC MO
this
one okay
you well that's like I always think
I have to uh bounce when he lands but
no a Jill messed that one up for
sure
this
one that attack is so funny all right
nice finishing move notorious Mark
Slaine let's
go it's just a griffin model from 14
with better textures what no
way no effing
way any marks in the chat if yes I'm
sorry I didn't mean to hurt you I love
you now I cracked my
my oh
hello could that be a
man it was an obnoxious Mark that's for
sure are you all
righta dare say I'll survive YouTube
didn't caught me before I could get an
arrow off notify you must have lost
sight of me in the grass though I'd be
dead if it hadn't more likely they're
not SS a
girl their name's
Camille I'm a lonely leather worker if
you couldn't tell by a smell of me I'm
so lonely from what I hear Do You
Remember selling to a merchant by the
name of
Karen she's not an easy woman to forget
bought a carass from me after I lost my
buyer parents are usually very difficult
to forget didn't stop her bartering me
down to a pittance though she sent you
for a refund it's not her who sent
me my stream started 28 hours
ago well that's a bit of a
stretch well consider me flattered you
should be I read flattened he's a master
of his art and not an easy man to
impress
blacksmiths are proud
folk it's a rare thing indeed for one to
praise a glorified Tanner and I don't
imagine an impressive swordsman like
yourself would be getting your steal
from any but the best I'd dearly love to
help a fellow Craftsman but consider me
flattened
actually I suppose you could give him
this what is
it treated leather same stuff I used to
make that Cor
if your man's as skilled as he sounds
he'll know what he's looking at you
sure well you did save my life and
thanks to you I'll be going home with
all the Griffin hide I can
carry I'd say it's the least I can do
hell yeah short of in that Cas no you
could stop talking that's the least you
could do you will
do I don't think anybody cares about
this hopefully this will swe chit
chap
right oh man look at the poor
bird man what did we
do I feel bad it's not quite a bird but
it's like partially a
bird I I I feel like yeah I hope it's
not like completely dead why couldn't we
have just knocked it out and like placed
it somewhere else where it doesn't
bother
us this was my favorite character why
did you skip it this was really
important to
me
yeah I
bet okay let's go back
here give back the quest I
guess
M wait let's not go all the way around
again I can literally just go up
here it didn't look skinned when I
looked at it that's unrealistic must be
ready to leave for Ros at a moment's
notice do I talk to
you it do
I not get anything extra now I'm not
supposed to
report my
actions oh
oh talk to blacksmith
okay all
right
cute day I want to okay it's so
cute how charal is always like somewhere
else like chilling with the others while
I'm doing my business
that's so cute such a sweet detail
too let's go to
my cute dog a community
dog hi how'd it go Clive did you find
him or does the hunt continue I found
him and he asked me to give you
this take it
do something nice for me with
that I'm trying to save time
okay he said he wouldn't teach you how
to work it but that if you were as
skilled as you
sounded so that good few times too and
that's no ordinary oil he's used to get
half this is f must have been the
expensive oil that I bought
yeah the olive oil charity oil just
looks like Leon here
Clive camil I believe I thought as much
let me turn on the light there ain't
many level workers in the realm Dar
enough to do their own hunting see and
his name kept cropping up when I was
asking around turns out he's from tabber
and again most level workers are but our
friend Camille guards a long held Family
secret the details of which are the
subject of some debate in the Lev
working community
then we better keep this close to our
chests listen sorry for putting the both
of you to all out trouble should have
kept my moaning to myself still I'm glad
you found him this is Che me right up
that was the idea I'm here Clive's idea
anyway he did most of the work it's good
to have you back black I
leave just don't expect me to go turning
out word like this there's a reason he
does his own hunting he knows exactly
what Ides to look for and that's how he
gets them to lay up so I wanted to
switch to get me started how much oiling
this leather would need but I reckon
make something about as good the curse
breaker will have no trouble caring for
anyway enough now in I read one one of
comment the same time I was talking
about my pajam I just wanted to get more
comy pajama pants man and look like
blacksmith yeah something as if there
was a better one out there and socks I
wouldn't have been the same anyway no
one's like old black for in his
cups right now that's sorted I've got
duties to attend to Quest thanks Clive
you've given me my mate
back pajama
Quest
cute I have so many
pajamas d B Slayer gear design draft
what craft a belt that V braces Fit For
A
Hero uh
okay do I give that to
him can I craft it you have obtained
design draft for the Drake Slayer gear
design drafts unlock new crafting
options at the black hammer visit black
front in the Hideway for details on
material requirements oh what' you
need oh I guess use the force what you
want
what anything
else back are
[Music]
you it's a belt oh what you want
a this one I'm missing
electrum what is that where do I get
that and how am I meant to do that then
what what bring me the materials and
I'll think about it why where do I get
that maybe
next belt and bracelets oh bracelets
too gelatinous Mass H it f the the same
hunts from the hunt
board like I mean like well different
ones but the same hunt board
quests okay h i maybe I'll do them off
screen
then okay okay ah sounds good sounds
good
okay
um then we shall continue with the main
quest I
think
offscreen
[Music]
grind go gave you the news then we have
time to do maybe maybe but not before I
know exactly what's going on what have
we heard all SS nobody was expecting the
delx to open up a new front against the
empire least of all our friends in the
provinces reports have been rolling in
from all over the place with no two
saying the same thing I've been passing
them on to Vivian in the hope she can
make sense of
them thanks if going membership Pool Egg
understood I can change chills CH chill
I just read it the change with a J and
Jill Jill with
ch jange
[Music]
chill what I can change her costume what
in our room do I do I change her clothes
personally like do I do
it oh what I found the treasure
chest
[Music]
ohu yeah I
mean pretty got pretty pretty close now
so is this my
room no
sorry for the
intrusion still trying to understand
this
[Music]
place here is where my room is right
wait is it
up
are the bunks my room wait I'm not
sure
what no here C's hell
what now maybe here is so
faster it's about time I wish I could
teleport within this base
camp I
wish
did what so I didn't read the whole
thing I thought my my brain auto
corrected that I can change her clothes
in my
room is it
wrong
the training Stone not the room wait
that one's here too
no this
thing all right all right all right all
right that's where I was going all this
time
anyway oh okay parents is matter do I
have something for me
too oh I don't like it though let's stay
with this one
huh ooh that's cool I love that wish I
could turn
her and there's a bluish Taro let's
go
oh rosarian
gold I'll keep it without the armor less
heavy
too oh this will be the the looks uh
like the skin of my sword basically like
even if I had wear a different sword it
would look like this the onion
sword oh this one looks kind of
awesome this one too
[Music]
though I'll go for this one cuz I think
it suits
[Music]
me
yeah onion sword oh yeah it does have a
little bit of like waa candy core
uh sword Vibes
H wait there's another close
Quest
n who
whom whom needs my
help please tell me I'm going the right
way I think I am or is it the is it
the no it's not it wait that's no no
that way is it the the the the
board no a huh this is the potion
upgrade
okay Sid
I I know that when we came to the
Hideway we chose to let go of our past
in order that we might focus on our
future we
did noteless I was wondering if well I
know you are from roseria and I'm in
need of someone with intimate knowledge
of those lands intimate apparently the
duchy is home to all manner of Curative
herbs found nowhere else in the
realm among them is a flower called a
Morgan beard that increases the potency
of lesser medicines I can't say that
I've had much practice healing a shame
and when those shipments are late if we
could find this flower and Le however
now I'm not asking the busiest Man in
The Hiway to drop everything and make
the journey for me but if you happen to
be in the
Dutch hell yeah of course tell tell me
of these Morgan beards then make my
potions
stronger if my old Toms are to be
believed the flowers are bright yellow
and as large as Goblin eyes oh GR in the
mares
of if I am to propagate them here in the
backyard I will require several samples
preferably of blooms which have already
gone to seed and before I
forget I do seem to recall learning in
the course of my research that their
odor has the tendency to attract
unsavory creatures what does that mean
nothing you cannot handle though I'm
sure I'm sure of that
too okay this this this this is good
Quest this is important
Quest this is the good
stuff should I do it now maybe I should
I probably should wait so where is this
monster
Rosario
[Music]
where is
Rosaria I don't remember these
names Ah that's ah where the plus let's
go
okay I wish I would have noticed that on
my
own I wouldn't have embarrassed
myself does it show
uh
[Music]
okay
thank you for sticking with us those of
us who are still here have to look after
each is from rosarion yeah
yeah I know I
know it's just the location of the map
is you
know
[Music]
unclear cuz it doesn't even say R area
it says Mara's
[Music]
wrist good
girl yeah here we
go and while I'm at it let me pick up
everything that's
sparkling and okay the turn on this Cho
Bo is
[Music]
see now it's too loud
again can
I every time I play this game I have to
adjust to sound cuz I'm always unhappy
with
it let's turn the music
down
okay high speed low handling
yeah that is exactly what this chle boy
is are old CH like this the marshes near
the Abby are certainly damp let's see if
they're oh
Goins now the reference makes more
sense hello size of a Goblin's eye wait
they don't even force me off
my you certainly wasn't wrong about them
being attracted to the flowers
too slow wow wait that was a Precision
counter even though the one who was
attacking was the other enemy but I like
didn't I didn't counter the enemy who
actually attacked I countered whatever I
was focusing on that's
interesting all yours
to ow okay I dodged right into
that
nice try wooo nice
timing nice
[Music]
timing
okay by the way let's talk more about
everything
uh let's talk about the crotch
story which I'm so sorry it's not about
ka's crotch it's about my crotch but Kaa
was definitely
involved um
basically when we were like changing at
the beginning of the day what am I
doing everybody of course as it is usual
noticed when there's uh overseas
members you oh come on stop it
already uh everybody wants to change
know separately even though the room is
really big so we we take
turns
but
um
I I just wait what happened actually why
did I not change change
separately nice try for some reason I
decided this time it's fine and I was I
guess I was changing while Kyla was in
the
room
and I was I was putting on this thing
that
um that has
buttons on my on on like you know kind
of
sake on the
crotch wait what the
um now on the crotch like you know
between the legs there's buttons and and
you know it's kind of like difficult to
close them
um you could you could also close the
buttons before before putting it on but
uh I chose to like first wear the thing
and then you know bend over
weirdly and try to close the
buttons and there's like several buttons
so it's
it's difficult okay it takes some
skill no it didn't rip no no but then
while I was doing that um I was trying
to cuz that's obviously an awkward
position and I was trying to
like position myself in the other
direction from Kyla so that she maybe
doesn't pay too much attention to my
awkward pose but I was grunting cuz I
couldn't close the buttons I was like
and then
she looks over to me and she just like
so innocently so like without I I don't
think she really was grasping the the
situation but she was offering help she
was like do you need
help and I started laughing so hard
because no Kyla I do not want you to um
close my crotch buttons thank you I I I
I
think I think I'm okay but like also
when she was asking that she was also
kind of like bending over and like
looking looking at
that yeah
so bit
embarrassing you
know and then I was so amused by that
bright
yellow Morgan beards all right I think
well what I did is I'm I already barely
remember it but I think I
um I was like pretty much wearing the
whole thing
but one of the zippers maybe wasn't
completely close of like my top like you
didn't see like anything you shouldn't
be seeing but it was a little bit
dangerously wide open uh but I was so
amused and I wanted to share the story
so I ran out of the changing room
where um don't worry they were only
ladies
but I was like listen listen what kind
just said and I just like loudly start
sharing this story and then they're like
k k
kop you're Z I'm I just like I barely
hear him cuz like I'm so excited to to
tell the story and then I'm like oh
oh that's
embarrassing so two two
embarrassing moments in a
row
yeah never leave the changing room
without being completely
finished
yeah oh at one time at one time um
before we were
changing like everybody I don't know why
but you know the staff kept on telling
us like please everybody start changing
now cuz like you know we're on a on a on
a tight there's something familiar about
this and shut up Clive it reminds me of
home shut
up on a tight timeline enough schedule
I've had my fa of goblins shut up now
and they kept on telling us you know and
then I I I I I also was like kind of
wasting time but I was telling my my Koh
eyes cuz I'm Senai I was telling them to
go change first you know but nobody
would
change I think it was the first change
but then after that everybody was just
sitting and staring at their phones
while the staff kept on coming in like
please change uh please and I'm I was
always like Su yeah um we'll we'll get
someone to change now we'll get someone
to change us sorry sorry sorry
sum I felt so bad for the staff I could
have gone changing too you know but it
wasn't only a me problem it was like you
know the other girls didn't want to
change either so I started um fighting
Kyla and Zetta and be like you go change
you go go change and they're like no you
and I'm like no go kohai i s by you go
change and then I was chasing Zetta
around the room like I was running after
her trying to grab
her and I eventually won and I put Zetta
in the changing room and made her change
I
succeeded it's quite funny we were we
were laughing obviously like everything
was just a JK
JK that was funny like there was so much
laughter the whole day actual anime
moment
yeah I don't know why nobody wanted to
change but everybody was just
chilling taking their time as if there
was so much
time
a that was fun we had a great
atmosphere then once we were all changed
like we would like be messing
around like I would make everybody hold
hands and with coobo in the standing in
the middle and we would form a circle
and I made them do like a ritual like
where oh no first she wasn't there yeah
yeah we were summoning her we I I made
us do a summoning ritual for
kobal oh I I stopped moving
yeah we were standing in a circle and
then like I don't
know raising our hands and lowering them
and chanting
something cuz we were bored I don't know
we were just bored and and I was trying
to you
know be funny and everybody was so in on
it everybody was just so we let's go go
go I don't know what we were chanting
but just imagine us chanting like we
some uh crazy cult people in a
circle and then running really fast with
our hands connected in the
circle random noises yes yes it did
eventually work out yeah we were
huddling rain
dance oh you know one plan that really
failed uh at the end of the
whole um last
song before that happened I I told uh
cuz like me and cie were waiting on one
side to enter and uh Thea were waiting
on the other side to enter and we were
looking at each other you know like I
told them that when we walk in we should
be like waving at kobul and like acting
as if as if we're going to hug K but
then just ran run past her and then you
know hug each other instead you know
Kelly and me would go hug Z and Kyla and
just say hi to them just pass by Kobo
you
know and oh coobo was in on it too but
then when it actually
happened uh like she kind of like didn't
really react to
us she didn't look at us not really at
least and and we were like passing by
awkwardly and it didn't quite come
across the way I wanted it to come
across and fury in my head it was so
funny but it was still overall
everything was funny we had
fun everybody was just goofy very very
goofy skip ad skip
ad oh is YouTube bullying
you yeah anyway that was the crotch
starring and the Z chasing
story I have I have one more
story it is rare that we see you if you
want to hear
it I found your
FL yes yes
wonderful these are almost identical to
the plates in my tone yes you missed the
crotch did you just enter I told it like
two minutes ago well that's on you
buddy I don't remember these flower
if the petals are meant to improve the
effectiveness it's possible that the
core physic has grew them for the
tinctures and treatments they made my
brother oo if the Dual healers were
convinced of their properties that is
all the more reason to begin growing our
own Supply let's do it to use some of
the flowers you brought me to make
something that might Aid you on only
moment to extract the
okay A bit of lore possible lore he said
maybe it wasn't
sure
potion making
ASMR and here we are a file of pure more
permanently making my potions better a
single drop added to any one of your
restoratives will increase its potency
at least I hope it
will okay and it's like passive I don't
have to actually add drops
right the root of the problem y nice
okay no Alchemy mini game a no I'm glad
there is
none yeah I wonder how much better they
are
now uh hereby increasing the both
potions High potion while last longer o
wow okay
awesome nice now we can continue the
main
quest
what's time to know okay I'll tell you
now so that I don't have interruptions
and
uh did I write anything down I don't
think I did I just have to tell this
from
my um from my memory so on this day when
we were recording um the parts that I
was part of let us know if you find shut
up
and I it was around around a time when I
was like
rushing completing the song for EUR
Vision right and on the day before I
think I recorded the vocals but then it
became clear that I missed recording a
few vocals and however I was going to be
like you know at the studio all day
doing stuff but I asked if I could
squeeze in um uh a little bit of
recording time maybe an hour or so uh in
the recording booth and uh they made it
possible so I could slip away somewhere
in the middle and go record a little bit
while everybody else was just still
hanging out uh and so I was gone and the
record they they're like in the same
area basically but there's some distance
so sometimes uh even maybe coobo
mentioned this I think I heard her
mentioning this uh cuz she talked about
not meeting pekora even though she was
actually there uh sometimes you know you
just don't really know you're not that
aware of who is actually there on that
day and you could be missing out on
meeting certain members cuz they're like
in a closed studio room doing their
thing and then they quickly silently
disappear cuz they want to go home
fast however I was like I was doing my
thing and I I I I looked around to find
some more Hall members to see if there's
anybody
there that's also when I met
Ida and and I saw also fubuki sandai and
they were they gave me the the the udon
stuff from their
collab and then also I think maybe it
was the same day maybe I'm not sure but
I saw canata
standby and
then hidden
away in the very furest back room
ever I heard from a
manager that mikoi is there and I'm like
okay I got to say hi to her too so I go
over to mikoi and she was like really
excited to see me she was like
a and and I was like telling her why I'm
here and this and that
and she was really sweet she was really
happy and she had some snacks that I
think staff gave her and she was like oh
do you want some so I took one and uh I
told her like hey if you want did you
ever meet the the ID Girls before the F
gen like you can meet them over there
they're actually here and she's like oh
really oh that's great yeah that sounds
great
so otherwise they wouldn't have met but
I I dragged mikoi over and then first we
um I introduced her to Buu cuz we found
her first and it was really cute they
were like immediately talking about oh
babies yeah hello
babies and then then mikoi gave some
snacks to kobal and she didn't know that
they were actually just snacks that she
got from her staff um so she was like
still very very like honored like oh my
god really can I really have one can I
really really have one for mikoi was
just like yeah yeah of course it's just
actually not even really for me I
actually got them from someone else yeah
yeah take one take
one and they were just being really
adorable then I uh dragged them over to
the others so Miki had a meeting with
everybody and that was sweet that was
really really sweet Holo baby's bonding
yeah
[Music]
mik meeting and I was really happy
actually cuz like um mik while we were
walking she said something like she
asked me how how long I'll be in
Japan and I'm like that question seems
like the way she asked it seemed like
she she no way no no way does she want
to see me
again so I was
like like why are you asking this
question I'm I'm here until this date
but why why yeah she she did have like
you know kind of the intention of maybe
seeing me again when I said okay maybe
not this time cuz no time but I'll tell
you next timei Senpai when I'm
here I didn't think you would want to
you would be interested in seeing me you
know I don't know if it's for an off
collab or just hanging out but you know
she was really
cute yeah I'll remember I remind her
once I have the dates for my next
[Music]
trip but yeah that's like I met so many
members all the time you just got to
sniff them
out ask all the managers that you can
see who's here who's here today and then
you can make beautiful meetings happen
meetings that would have
otherwise not happened and you would
have missed out on
it it's about time yeah Miki very very
friendly very
energetic she laughes so much
too Vivian's got all the
information
um that's where I'm going
okay I saw the article yeah I talked
about it in my member stream and it made
me feel um a little bit uncomfortable a
little bit weird that especially after I
saw like how many people are reading the
article and like talking about it in the
comments
everybody's like discussing it most
people are nice about it there's like
one dude who seemingly replies to
everybody who doesn't seem so fond of
the idea but a lot of people are like
yeah this could be great because like
well you know let's try something new we
would be doing something
unique
who
knife yeah but then I was happy to see
um there there must have been some of
you guys uh who can speak German who are
like going in there to explain to people
who seem really like like confused about
it um explain to them a bit more about
me and how it would work and all that
thank you thank you for trying to get
some information out there
dun
yeah thank you I
appreciate ah if it is my favorite pupil
let's see now where did we leave
well this is a surprise my lectures are
rarely so well
attended you know what they say a little
knowledge uh can't
hurt we going to roosth to deal with CA
that's what they say what's the
situation
there wo there Lord rossfield I'm sure
you're champing at the bit to return to
your Roost but to fully understand the
present situation one must first
understand understand how it came to be
am I
Roost here we go Lord
dump
concentrate let us begin with the story
of Hugo kopka or the permanent economic
advisor to the dmean government to give
him his formal title in a Republic
founded on Commerce there could hardly
be a more influential position it has
granted him both extraordinary wealth
and extraordinary power mhm mhm not that
he ever wanted for being Titans dominant
he's also Dalia's last line of defense a
fact he has used to his considerable
advantage while he was even able to
Pride Drake's Fang one of the pillars of
the Republic from parliament's grip what
and he was quick to buy the Loyalty of
the Fang's protectors today they are his
faithful creatures a private Army in all
but name the selfsame army that marches
upon rosarian soil as we
speak by which I mean Imperial soil not
that you need reminding of the fact do
suffice it to say the Empire's
attentions are elsewhere at present
deadlocked as it is with Dalia over its
occupation of the crystalline Dominion
where its Legions are now
gathered scarcely a handful of garrisons
remained to secure its Western provinces
and half of them left after the fall of
Drake's breath what I stopped with the
threat of the iron blood thus diminished
they had little cause to fear a maritime
Invasion and so today only a token Force
guards the former DUI shores as kukka
was quick to descri what she saying he
landed his troops on the rosarian coast
without encountering so much as a single
ship All For You Clive uh he wants your
head and so he and his men Advance upon
rosali not to capture the province but
to draw you out okay so basically she's
saying they're
coming you said C's forces sailed up the
coast what of Port is aler then is the
city safe quite according to the
Guardians of the flame the dmean fleet
floated by without incident but not
without remark when they learned kupka's
forces were making for rosali
our friends were quick to begin
arranging The Exodus of her
citizens and so the stage will soon be
set for your heroic homecoming alas it
will be a more trying task to enter the
capital than it was to leave it Hugo's
men hold buitt Bridge despite the
imperial's repeated attempts to rest it
back from their grasp and they were
careful not to repeat the Empire's
mistake in neglecting their Coastal
defenses the seas around rosali are
firmly under dmean control my brain
doesn't register
anything let's read this SRA left for
his area undefended since they busy
fighting in the
East uh and with the iron troops
diminished since you destroyed their
mother
Crystal
okay
cool ever tell no you no
no bad guy to keep being a live person
okay
kopka swooped in to draw you
out with Rosaria
[Music]
undefended um
okay okay there
yeah I I was supposed to be defending
it what no who's who's going towards ARA
now cuz cop Gua is coming to me right
and then who's going to
Rosaria oh no he's going there and how
did he draw me out of
roseria okay okay he's attacking R to
draw me out uh to to go there so that uh
instead elsewhere they can find
something else to to so because I can't
split my bodies or something like that
maybe I don't know yeah whatever tell me
people mine what do you believe to be
the best route to
rosali the north yes the north yes we
cross the northern border near Phoenix
gate then take the road through
stillwind down to the
capital hardly the quickest route but at
least it won't be spotted a little local
knowledge goes a long way and so must
you we'd best get a move on then oh will
you be going too I I've been waiting a
long time to give that a taste of
his own medicine I would have missed
this for the world all right we should
be on our way lead
on
nice all
right here we go no Koopa wants to kill
you but you are hiding he attacks your
hood so that you go there to defend it
okay thank you Unity Chad you're the
best I understood
that that was in simple Wawa
[Music]
language wow the clouds look really
nice
the tips of all their swords are cut off
that's interesting fortify the castle
gates at
once is this where the the pleasure
house
was Hugo and his men have been busy
they've already breached the castles out
of wall
the Imperials are holding the ground for
now but it's only a matter of time
before the keep
Falls those really went to town
on this
place almost like they want to wipe it
off the
map just a means to an
end what the Fitz this the one man
they didn't have to go so
far if you keep your wits about you I
reckon you can make it up to the castle
without raising the
alarm I'll sniff out any Town's folk who
haven't escaped yet and send them on the
way be
careful likewise don't do anything I
wouldn't do so in the end we still
separate
man
he called me a sexy
dwarf so
confused in
German
okay he'll never be part of us with were
click I thought I was ready for this but
compared to Ellie I'm a dwarf it's like
a nightmare this was our
home come on
Clive we have to keep going yeah just go
for
it no time to
waste talkie
walkie
capital punishment they really like to
use cool words in know cool
way this isn't an
invasion it's a massacre he'll stop at
nothing
Clive
nothing okay doy
Walky oh he's so cute why he looks also
like so cool now with his new skin
no why why do
this to make you angry we can get
through here the angrier you get the
easier you
will turn into
iFit just for you protect o ooh protect
spell
murderous there's only one bitting
punishment get
him go
tole now
tole w
wow this one me likey fancy
effect get
him taking them to
town my
town just giving them a
tour as they seem very interested in
my
oh in my
town flow
Town
CH
oh who whoa do I fall down
uhhuh oh yeah oh yeah yeah we have to
stop
this not
quite just a catapult I
guess what's the difference between a
cult okay
power size what we have
here
gentlemen
okay H you think you can stop me you
won't
Escape kill you can never stop
me
what did they say always in
um in Elden ring what what am I supposed
to do with my
ambitions foolish what was
it cut them down with me not not the
rolling for
the out of our way is that what they
said put your foolish Ambitions to rest
oh that's the protection stop it all
yours to I do not
allow oh my God what where where's
the a what
here this one well he's very protective
of his
doggles
understandable did you hear this the
doggy sounds over here
attack go to all yours tole let me go
for
him okay collateral judgment I see I see
you this one
[Music]
Overkill yeah got to use it every once
in a while why do I stop moving so much
today it's a little bit
annoying wait which way this
way no ah above or in
between
[Music]
he's just dancing
around I'm not paying attention to
him over
here I just Eed him
away oo I like their designs so that's
pretty
[Music]
interesting wait when the what was I
what can I do with the normal enemies
when they're half staggered cuz it just
gave me
a command for
them wait this isn't up this is uh a
strong enemy I just
realized relatively
strong I was like why am I taking so
much damage from this one do I actually
have to pay attention to this fight huh
I won't all right all
right
oh okay so this does work that's why
okay cuz I heard the sound and I was
like wait but aren't these like pretty
normal
enemies I was like wait if it's this
small Bob low Bob enemy what can I even
do why is it telling
me about the
the half triggered
timing
n it was big enemy looking small but
don't judge Enemy by its
[Music]
cover yeah like I find it kind of weird
like for some enemies they put the their
health bar at the top right and for some
they don't first I thought like all the
big important enemies have one at the uh
top
but there's
like some that don't some that
do this this is small still small but I
would also say at the same time big I
feel like every enemy that has a stagger
bar should you know
be
wait well the other one
to could be highlighted as
such get a bit more you know a bit
more uh in a way that's too
slow that they all mat I
know but you know I'm sure they
have uh reasons for why they chose this
way of
design just dagger no cuz like it's
obviously still too small for me when
it's a small
enemy I didn't
notice she looked just like the other
weak
Bobs the wheel of lightning pile Drive
oh does that make the the strong Thunder
attack that I got
stronger pile
Drive yeah just make the HP bar stand
out more remember get wow this this is
why we
started get
him wee
all yours
tole stay down stay down oh the
aggression in
that oh no he's
protected where's the protection
dude wait which
one this
one
protect
this TR what he he lives was that him no
wait this is different dude gosh they're
so
confusing
here who the is still protecting
him ah
all yours
tole okay o I got to level up from that
28 Let's
Go
YouTube oh YouTube was pretty lame today
during the ID collab stream too set her
loose
NY set H
loose oh a
cur
meow oh
pretty
attack ready all you
think let's go
curl wait
these this reminds me of something these
like things that this thing has
attached this
one over
here ow ow ow ow w wow w w
kill free get
him over
here
okay that sound is like I wish I could
make it even more apparent to
me get him I'm always so close to
missing
it
get him wa oh that's
[Music]
no let's go right in
the Thunder Crystal
thingy and I wasn't even
done
that is perfectly executed we need to
stop it Whatever It
Takes how go get him oh yeah I'm
supposed to do damage oh yeah yeah yeah
okay
okay not good
oh yours
to wait I
can't you guys do some more stuff over
here
come
on we live it's down oh thank God then
let's make this
count
[Music]
no oh ah ah it was still enough okay
kitty kitty that so kitty
[Applause]
kitty
don't you hurt my
crystal this a pretty good fight I would
say um uh
uh thought that was ready it
wasn't SM baby Smo
Smo wait I'm not done with
you
too slow nice
try oh W who W what was that I needed
that why is it just waiting
here nice
try oh wait what what is this shut
up this
one
go k I'm ready I'm ready for
that last couple of hits let's go get
him
don't run away it's over accept
it enough a no I feel kind of bad I was
just trying to
survive it was put in a situation where
it had no choice
anyway this girl is also just a slave to
these evil
people thank
you every sneeze brings a new
member too bad that I don't have
[Music]
allergies
Jill we meet at last a come
on or should I say Lord
rosfield I've been looking for you for a
very long time let her go
CA I'm so glad you accepted my
invitation
I went to some trouble with the
decorations do you like what I've done
with the place
bastard Such a Pity your predecessor
couldn't join us but I am sure you will
prove compelling
company
be still Little
Snowflake I would not have you melt
before your staring
moment let her
go do you think those can take care of
me no no not again
[Music]
no
guess this one's even
worse
don't we you you say that's going
to make him snap he immediately gave up
he didn't snap he should have snapped no
not on him too hell he got
us we were aware that this was kind of a
trap oh into the festivities and we
still
couldn't avoid this
outcome maybe Joshua shows up randomly
and helps us oh G right cuz gav is
like yeah that was that was good that we
separated oh to also toy walkie be
careful get
g go get
CF they all underestimate the power of
the
tole that's just great that is I suppose
it's up to me then
mhm thanks for the
[Music]
memberships more of a struggle
yeah considering how powerful these
people are supposed to be but I guess
kopka is also
powerful trying are you planning on
beheading
us oh they got
a y that that's a bit over kill you
me that's Overkill come on you bring the
prisoner he got pretty eyes
though yes no more than she deserves for
getting into bed with an outlaw
we should get into mine excuse me who
are you talking
about
Jill Lord coper commands your presence
you're to Bear witness to the girl's
execution such a
[Music]
waste
gav
shh
Crystal f is a bastard to open just so
you know we are going there but we're
going on our own way and blink where's
Jill in the
courtyard
ah he wants to be his lover too
that's how he to retreat and cleared out
of the castle but the place is still
swarming with ca's
men listen to me I'll make my way up top
and circle around the back quick as you
like
eh nearly
forgot
[Music]
mhm hold on Jill I'm
coming I have to get to the
Courtyard but first let me collect
item is this the actual
path did he say he's going a different
direction
G you know I always want to check out
every paath where did he go didn't he go
that
way didn't I see Gaff running that
direction he just
disappears
teleport
I guess I'll be fighting the the
beheading
guy chunky boy don't you let her
Die thanks for all the
potions how about high
potions just checking out the area what
is this
stuff nice
weapons man nostalgic at least this
place hasn't been destroyed yet
always look at the bright side of
life oh what an axe
like what an
A so Overkill hope you've got a plan
Clive cuz we are if you don't the
plan is to
Prime
talkie
poie
go sweet
boy at again we're like so last second
what it's a bloody
wolf not bloody yet but he will be
bloody after this oh okay wo wo
he's Ming
what he he didn't explode himself right
he still lives right wow wow did he
Prime togy wagi is special
doggo every doggo is special doggo of
course can you stand did I know that he
evolved more like a diyon though a
Digimon come come Lord rosfield
don't tell me you Tire of my
entertainment
enough yes Perhaps it is time we served
the main repast bring it on you are
hungry much
obliged stay close we're getting out of
here oh poor gentan thank you was about
to die and now it has to get
straight into the battle care to explain
what the your dog just did man
later I wish I knew with me that
includes you
tole his tail is
glowing oh his aim is
terrible H wait what ah ah ah I
missed what I was when I'm already
in the green one when I have to like do
the thing I switch all I circles cycle
through all of them once wo wo
wo silly
Wily silly
W am I doing damage to him and not the
yeah oh wait what oh I kind
of I didn't realize got staggered I can
try
W oh wait oh h on I heard another funny
sound
wow wow how easy is this
boy I don't even I'm like I can't even
keep up with all the time I'm like
staggering
him what's going on over here are we
done yeah
sh still breathing are you not these
then Lord kupka's reward shall
be ours
Flex can we do it separately but's
always came in threes
let them
come too
slow or
kill let's
try oh wait ah I missed
it thank you camera great camera
work second time
I purposefully went first to the thuner
as I'm supposed to
do
nice
I'm good at uh countering that
one I got
it I finally got it the
go yeah yeah and staggered right into
the staggy nation
uh what do I have
nothing didn't expect it to happen so
fast okay that charged up
quickly all right all right all right
all
right first
potion this
one let's
try it up have to learn something new
you my
friend is that all you
got and
[Music]
sagging I did get the potion upgrades
yeah
yeah I didn't look at how much they heal
now
though that was smooth I only took one
potion could have maybe even done
without the
potion just played the Safe
Way anime
finish it's
over for now but I bet that wasn't the
last of them T they won't stop hunting
us until cop is dead what's so you get
in there and finish the job eh me alone
on if they come again we'll hold them
back all right but be
careful you're not making me do this
alone okay well fine I can handle him
alone I they want one of these like
big Prime Subs no
prime prime fight again he'll die by my
hand
nice wait let me check if something's
here no
ah I I guess I got the prime Sub in my
brain right now because of uh
twitch being involved
yesterday CA
Copa you're
late trouble on the
way just enjoying your he's so big he
does can't even sit on his own Throne
how
gratifying have you come to defend your
father's Throne Lord rosfield cuz it's
not his
throne the grand duche of
Rosaria a realm without a ruler an
army even a
people
a veritable Kingdom thank you guys of
dust thank
you
m let's
go truly I see no Throne to
defend oh no you
didn't
you big
doesn't sound as good enough of your
games
CER just tell me what you want sit's
head in a
box but I'm s imagine my disappointment
when I learned that he met his end at
the hand of
another and my relief to learn that you
had taken up his thric damned
name you're
welcome yeah that was
your master slew benedicta Harmon and
defiled her body no so we actually
didn't
apparently maybe it was the you choose
to bear that murderer name then you
shall answer for his CRI the mysterious
hooded person might have done
it the only crimes I shall answer for
are my own Sid yeah I mean we her to
save that woman though she was long past
saving MH mhm that is true and so I did
what he
couldn't it was me all along
Hugo it
was
you I had no choice man you tried to
kill me it was self-defense
you you killed it was
self-defense I
did
oh he going to morb stand
back then I am fortunate indeed yes you
are are you realizing it now oh he's
happy now I had thought the most I could
wish for was to take the life of one he
loved just as he did to
me but it
seems I was wrong
and I shall have my
revenge yeah we shared a dream a I would
be the king of the
world she would be my queen and together
we would rule like the gods we
are but you crushed that grounded into
dust
okay h r for got to get me someone who
loves me like that you w pay for what
you've done I'll tear you apart with
my and what have
you how many people have you killed how
many dreams have you crushed
you're not the only one who seen their
world fall apart around
them you'll get no pity from me ker no
pity and no
mercy can I prime though now
die they sinked
like oh
it is time you
learned What Becomes of those who dare
to cross me okay he's fast CR I'll
kill
you you know what I should kill him with
the powers of his
beloved we'll get
there I got to be really fast to this
guy man especially cuz I'm still trying
to learn all his
moves you for too
slow oh uh okay oh that was close close
close here you go the love of your non
wise
yeah this time I I dodged both and got a
counter but no double counter no double
counter too
slow ouch OU oh oh okay okay chill chill
chill we lost
it we got the fair and we staged
him all right I didn't place the Thunder
but it's okay
oh I'm wasting
time
[Music]
nice try no why was you having a
I hate this thunder thing I swear see
no oh my God what a
oh my
okay oh
hello
um it's so K why it's so cooky cookie y
die by my
hand my hatred for you is
unending smoo transition yeah let this
Palace Be Your
Grave oh
angry um Clive it's time to maybe prime
a little bit you
know uh R1
so so I already got him like what
down4
maybe is it doesn't look like 13 which
something more like 1
[Music]
14 oh yeah but he might have another
face which is probably just like the
like big versions of us fighting
[Music]
again maybe I don't
know
what world contagious has
chosen what damn he's like Iron Man I am
in my El but gold man there's no esake
he's a gold digger oh he's for real
and he's gold will be let me move I
can't
move let
TR too slow
nice
try
oh you oh damn Titanic counter what do
like really work like a counter he can
only do it as a
counter oh okay oh oh this is like rope
jumping
[Music]
let me do something come on
please why did I bring this oh wait ah
ah I missed it I missed the
timing where am
I too
slow swear to God the stupid fun there
nice
[Music]
try a
not
now
[Music]
what ah I canceled it why did I do that
I don't know how I did
it oh he countered
me
nice
try Okay this way it's actually
easier
oh
okay
insert
[Music]
rods was that fun for
you I'll rip out your heart my
heart I don't have
wood no I have but you can't it's
currently in position for possession of
kfp can't have
it they're keeping it safe oh my God
the what the he do what just like
your
forefathers what am I doing your journey
and what is that what is that what the
Dam why is he
resting is he
okay I'm so sweet I even worry about
him is she
okay what the what the is
that
this is
my what is that how do you even guess
you got to Dodge in that moment but like
if you see it the first time like you
know yeah you with your stupid counter
you I want to
go too slow I'll tear you
apart
ah he he combined
[Music]
it it no okay thank God I thought he
would shoot it at
uh the Thunder that would be that would
really piss me
off oh come
on okay okay okay let's
go do we have to do it until the very
end or is there like some cinematic
stuff at the end come
on my scream
you
will I come on who who
what a come
on no I'm on the potion no
please
[Music]
please not
good
too
slow oh no
no
damn I would say that was pretty much
first
[Music]
try you
will
this is my uh okay I think I dodged it
but it's like what the is this
timing too
slow I'll TR
you oh 50%
coming
[Music]
okay okay the first one is always a bit
rough but
difficult you will die here did
I
suddenly I am so
powerful come on bring me this thing
thank
you that's all I got
this
oh his guard was
broken Ah that's that
okay okay it's kind of fun when you
actually get it oh come on
no now he got
me
you I don't care anymore just
die
oh I was in the air he couldn't get me I
tried to stay in the air as long as I
could I didn't realize though that he
only needed one more hit
there air
finish
yeah I wish I could have done it in the
first try I was so close
man looked cool right thank
you damn I think I did well yeah even
though I failed
once nice finish oh thank you guys wow
do you think I'm
cool thank you now let's
see face two
does usually does face two ever happen
when you get this screen
already so golden not
anymore no more Golden
Boy sorry you're not a match for
me
[Applause]
and now suddenly I'm like a warm who
can't do
oh what what did I just cut his
hands
[Music]
ho
um
holy this
game Square
enx oh he's not stopping
there oh I'm getting the power
already oh
what
guess that was the power I'll kill you
I'll kill you I'll kill
[Music]
you
sh don't chill maybe we can still soon
them back
on Ice put them in ice
we we Jill can help you
maybe I'll kill you selfdefense
it was all self-defense okay when
anybody asks just say was
self-defense
oh there there wait you mustn't get
yourself worked out wait was
that wait
another time
muthos wait first I thought it was Josie
then I thought it was gav then I was
like wait is it the son but then he's
already so grown the son the new son I'm
like going through all the blondes that
I know cuz they're all
blonde wasn't G is that all of them
I think so maybe it's the cloaked one
without his cloak who the invited
them not that that's the biggest
surprise we've had today doggy Wy how
you learn to do that
tole not telling you suit yourself well
he can't G we have to find
Clive right
sorryy walk
it's not an icon though
right you little
Clive's back you missed
one we were
worried so was
I what the actual cutting off the
hands but he lives still right no wait
he was taken away if it hadn't been for
my gift I would have finished him but he
lives I'm just glad you got out of there
alive well what can he do with maybe
he'll right after you went inside
replace them with weapons we thought we
were shot of Titan lot in pile Orin not
enough of them to worry your huge
hammers on your hands or something like
that you didn't see the one who took
sounds like something he would do
yeah so what you think they came here to
save
him well I'll be of I know what's
going on but every minute we spend
rocking our brains that bastard's
getting further a
away so what do we
do with Ben we also first had this go
back to the Hideway one big fight and
then again later on I'm too tired to
think how are you by the looks of it why
do I have to kill everybody twice and
after what Jill's been
through let's worry about CA later shall
we I all right you'll give us a chance
to Solve the Riddle of your magic mud
too magic mud he a do wle hey how you
feeling ready to go
home Babble
bble he fell into The Magic Pot when he
was a
[Music]
small
yes got a
trophy
yooo all right to The Hideout we go the
Hideway imagine they just like give no
explanation about togi
wagi NE never throughout the whole game
everybody's just like hey do you want to
explain like more of a wreck than this
place you just stay silent this what you
call taking better care of yourself no
more excuses your ladyship I order you
to rest they do yeah but imagine if they
wouldn't I'll rest would be funny just
don't talk about it just don't
purposefully don't explain it at
all don't worry G she's in good hands
but we should have never let her fall
into hugos don't feel some like the
question is where is he now and what the
hell were those royalists doing
there I was wondering about that all the
way home Oto may have heard something
I'll talk to him and I'll talk to Toms
the Lawman about what about your
faithful Hound for a start if any
four-legged friends ever done that
before I'm betting Toms will have read
about it but what I want to know is what
happens afterwards it's all well in good
tole saving our arms es but if it costs
him what it cost Jill
a let me know if you learn anything
we'll do and you do the same
eh
chill listen to T I
will thank
you and do I have to do it even when I'm
wearing when when I turn on the thing
that makes Tori do his things on his
own the power of damn that
picture my God CLI has claimed the
portion of the icon Titan's Essence ATT
tuning with Titan not only changes the
elemental aspect of cl's magic spells
but also allows access to several new
iconic abilities such as wind up or wind
up a singular strike that increases the
potency when
charged is but I can only have three at
a time right so is this one better than
a different one should I be switching
out
something oh he has a
block most incoming attacks using Square
immedately after perfectly timed
position
square a devastating
interesting
I use a lot
myself that one seems like it would be
kill a close range
yeah this element relies heavily on
timing as everything really does I would
say but not all of the Nobles made it
out alive C is made fun with more than a
few okay but then I'll I'll get my
points back I'll I'll take my points
back from the 3,100 one
especially
yeah you know what the Thunder can suck
my I don't know whatever because uh I
don't like this wherever this thing is
the the yeah I keep on like accidentally
attacking it which is so stupid so give
me back my points please
uh at once oops
I want my points back thank
you wait can I get anything back no okay
all
right
o ah this is yeah when I was standing
behind him that's pretty cool drive both
hands into the ground into the ground
causing the land to sech
upwards upheaval
it's just like a punch on the ground
okay welcome to the slam what wel come
and jam what let's slam what come on and
what slam well well welcome to what I
can't come
on what what come on and what
slam come on and slam welcome to the jam
thank
you than punch forward hold button to
wind up
attack oh H which one should I
use oh oh that looks fun it's
another like quick
muchos
ponchos yeah this is like goou basically
basically what do
upgrade increases attack potency
okay
uh then I guess I'll go with these two
Earth and fury and the Raging
fists
Titan H where should I put which
one yeah I think like this
no
what huh how do I change upheaval to be
Earth and
fury I guess I have to go like this okay
confusing okay so
the whoosh it's even the form of a tri
angle kind of so maybe I can remember
that and then SW is on the same Button
as the fast one from the wind and the
fast one from the IGN from the fire of
the empress very good
good well sorted
out oh Clive welcome to the Patron's
whisper the Patron's
whisper does that mean someone else is
taking care of our friend's donations oh
no that's still me it's just Karen has a
toll Black Thorn has his hammer I
thought a new name might Len things up I
still catalog every item that arrives in
addition to setting aside those tokens
of appreciation the sender is specified
as to be presented to you personally
would you like to see if we have
any yes come to claim your Just
Desserts yeah uhhuh
what getting
gifts the blood W thank you oh you earn
this oh ability points 400 let's go here
you
are
o best of luck out there Sid best ring
in the game no way
[Music]
really temporarily increases attack
proficiency with each
Precision
oh should I switch it
out I do Dodge a lot so just don't know
how how effective the increase really
is
oh you
okay all right I do hit those
Dodges okay OT from the grto
OT is now a good
time it's not a bad one how's J doing
she's been better thank you Evan is
making sure she gets the rest she needs
good any word on koopa's movements viv's
do what she can to try and track him but
she's feeding on scraps should have cut
off his Fe out to The Curse Breakers and
our other friends in the west asking
them to keep their eyes peeled for
anything unusual no don't peel your eyes
but it's only a matter of time all
right let me know when you find
something there he is oh all right
Clive still busy saving the world who
she's got cute eyes she looks like a
Senai
when did you get
back just
now what about your studies A
J since Hugo cupka invaded Ros areia all
the canvas in uproar about it he's gone
mad he's turned Rogue it'll be us next
you try concentrating with all of that
all right all right you win how long
will he be staying this time she's kind
of M A While most likely no
she's m I was opening you could do us a
favor you can't just expect me to please
oblige
her what a cutie pouti while we are busy
tracking down kopka you should have a
little time to
spare Professor now there's a face I
haven't seen in a while shouldn't you
have it buried in a Dusty old
to I did till a familiar Trill pricked
my
ears as ever your your exuberance is a
breath of fresh air Kelly hat
successfully scattered the painstakingly
assembled fragments of my
thoughts I'll take that as a
compliment well Clive you heard the
professor so I'll meet you in the store
room when you're done wait hold
on breath of fresh
air bloody Tempest more like
boy Otto you got my guilt
complicated huh what you all about my
fee for bringing mid across she said you
were paying that little
wait I have to read midad doll is a
full name midad doll what a weird name
ton midad doll
ton
what student of engineering at
University of canvas she is as well
versed in the secret of modern and
Fallen technology as any scholar in the
twins it means to put that knowledge to
use in the service of the
highway okay know it all look how cute
she
is OS an old friend of Autos from his
Merchant Sean days now serving as a
fairy man between the shores of bener
and claps Hideway knowing him to be a
trustworthy and tight lipped fellow Al
invited him to join the cause after
Sid's death that he and his trusty ski
might help them build and operate their
new Hideway Hideway in the lake mhm
mhm the stor room was
it I wonder what mid
plotting
okay
H
following the
red thing
marker and speak with
meat why people say she's said daughter
do I even am I even supposed to know
that what the
hell you took your time I'm a busy man
mid I'll get to the point then I want to
turn the room down there into a workshop
like the one I had at Dad's
place you've only just come back and
I've been thinking about it for a
while Dad said I had a knack for
engineering taught me everything he knew
about it then sent me off to canva to
learn everything he didn't that was his
dream for me that one day I'd put my
studies to use for the good of the cause
but Sid was just sit sit and if she's
the daughter why does it not say so in
her description that's important for
hore the School I've studied enough
it's time to put me that to work I know
that I can help the people here and I
want to do it well well
well if sick could see you now m i can
thank you I'll tell ot to you'll be
staying I knew you'd say yes which is
why I wrote up a list of jobs for you
for
me who else more side quests or
what what do you want me to do not main
quest right first things first I need
equipment and materials to start making
me own there's the design stuff I need
and the stuff it needs smithing from the
other materials I can wh myself just
need a generous benefactor to lay them
on for me eyes are so apart from the
wood I'll need a carpenter for that but
I can just borrow yours Carpenter are
you sure you need a carpenter for the
wood I'll let you know if I need else
man this girl is
confused
don't don't even say anything chat
where's it start materials and tools
that means car and
Blackthorn all
right I will do the thing Blackthorn may
be the manliest of men but it does lack
a certain
tenderness he lacks a certain tenderness
but is the man of
men is that so the Litt have been up to
their old tricks again
on Jill looked white as a sheet when
they brought her
[Music]
back was wondering where you'd got to M
back from canver Have You Seen Her mhm
just now gladly she's planning to set up
a workshop in the stores and ask me to
to buy here some materials here's the
list uh yeah
[Music]
yeah think you can find everything on
there that NPC who just talked about Sid
about trader if I could the blacksmith
excellent talk about payment it's paid
Romancing every over by what that girl's
done for us if it weren't for her
filters we'd have not to drink but
blight water and that would have drained
the life out of us long ago indeed it
would I'll send the stuff on to Med when
it comes in thank you
Karen
dad's
interesting she's always up to date on
who I'm talking to stalker lady
Blackthorn you busy what do it look like
I have a commission for you for Mid she
requires certain tools don't be so
grumpy black
for you think you can make them happy
birthday K she planning the Bild with
her stuff and
Airship I'll see what I can do till I
bring them up my thanks I'll properly
congratulate you that just leaves the
carpenter let's see if Bard off's
available when I read the super chats
the it's all
right okay where is
this down
here how do I get
there
[Music]
elevator are you me next year I'm I'm on
top of my super
jets
could do with a good oil in this could
I'm only like one stream behind should
be enough to keep or two now maybe
Master Sid B off mid's looking to build
a workshop in the store
room I'm afraid I got my hands full just
keep sorry my fingers slipped when I
sneezed there's olds need patching and
if I don't patch him will all of us sink
into the mirror
I
it don't have to be me though does it
what about that other you know the one
over at Martha's
rest Bernard oh I remember him that's
right and he he started this whole
discussion I'll ask Martha if she
can our
fight our discussion thanks for the
[Music]
membership and mar mar show
[Laughter]
no no I am on top of my sneezes as I am
on top of my Super Chat Empire have
drons wait where
is circle Marthur like a sister you do
inside what
oh
okay
here oh
YouTube find out oh okay don't worry you
you only missed that I ran around this
house two
times ah Clive what brings you to the
rest our home finds itself in need of an
extra Carpenter I wondered if I might be
able to borrow burnard for a short while
I don't mind if he don't thank you
Martha he went up to cresa on business
cres no idea far as I know I'll look
from
that cres
cres
Al maybe I go
here yeah this is just
filler can use my Cho here
huh talky
Walky all
right now it's chocoo
time oh he's like hitting on the choco
ball I mean if you the wind if you
whistle like that that is
obviously a flirt dir
whistle cat calling
[Music]
chobu nice feathery
butt that you obviously trying to show
off to
me flap FL flap flap flappity flap
PL
PL wait let me look around here
too I said flap flap
flap you know
it you deserve a
rest me you
right
fly
Ambrosia did he just say fly
Ambrosia I know he's not much of a flyer
I
[Music]
think I have end the lad who saved my
life what brings you to a place like
this you do burn it Martha said I might
find you here I'm I have a proposition
for you oh do you know a
proposition oh
[Music]
o you could make us some carpets
building a workshop you say well that
beats sacking boards to Bridges sure
enough and if Martha didn't mind me
being gone a while then neither do I
okay
let's
go oh yeah it's not like you need it
here there is cres at all I grew up and
much left of it now though except my
parents CU obviously they don't need
carpets no one's living I came up here
hoping to visit I even patched up the
bridge to get across damn find the place
crawling with fiends oh do you want me
to clean that up you're a daband when it
comes to dealing with
beat yes leave it to me
[Music]
I already knew what you wanted from me
after the first letter that you
uttered bring it on this shouldn't take
long let's
see oh wow it's so
cinematic whoa what was that
is that my new
Dodge it's
over the ring is going to do that every
time I
dodge how do this work by the way just
holding
it try didn't
work did not work I want a
refund sh up tole he no attack
me okay that's time it worked even
though I wasn't even looking at you come
down
here come
[Music]
down get get
him
attack
go stay
down stay down is there something left
oh yeah here
[Music]
hi
go
okay
I was trying to dodge
[Music]
it oh no I'm going to burn these these
grasses these
kusas itms R2 plus Square just as an
ed wait R2 and square
what oh wait that was the wrong
thing was that different from wait what
just as an enemy ah Ju Just okay okay
okay let's try oh this is a strong
enemy
wo
W oh my attack actually gets uh like
fiery to show me that I have the buff I
guess oh oh God
uh
get oh okay okay let's calm
down
can't even see what I'm doing yours
to
and this
one
hey he my my lower arm
kind
you little
who you thought I would block but no no
I
decided
hey I was going to do it differently
after
all
I've only been doing it for 4 hours
today man
what I need to massage my right
hand
go
okay only only 4
hours yeah okay bro
rotation
stretch
sensation
multiplication
damnation
[Music]
Suffocation okay hi I'm I did
it that should do
it you made short work of that
lot suffocation no breing don't
what arm bleeding how long is it since
the village was
abandoned oh people started packing
their things after the deut she fell
just like between the BL and the
Imperials you just make End
meat must be n on a decade since the
last wagon left bleeding
though it may as well have been a
century looking at the
place this isn't the cador I
remember I'm
sorry ah don't be can't live in the past
no matter how nice it might have been
soon as I'm done saying a prayer for
those that raised me it's on to your
Hideway a nice I'll meet
you nice dude he's so positive how can
can you even be so positive when
everything around you take care of mid's
little list is destroy before
she thinks of anything
else everyone's
[Music]
dead can I enter this house no right no
but there might be a chance
[Music]
somewhere no what the
hell there it
is the chests really blend in of the
environment so
[Music]
much we' been here before I've explored
here before I think but still the chests
are
untouched maybe
refresh isn't this why I was like
fighting in the very beginning like some
goblins or
[Music]
something Ambrosia won't help me here oh
okay
well was it okay some part of it looks
similar to me it wasn't though no I
guess
[Music]
not okay now I'll
go
back to where I came
from y y yep it's okay thank you I know
I
[Music]
see y
yep I don't know it looks familiar to
me no I don't want to talk to you
whatever I two those girls what do you
want and we most certain you
wouldn't oh I see she happy to let them
freeze to death are you ever will Young
jail think shut up
don't you dare tricks again you
know I'm busy with bigger
I'm saving all of
humanity so don't make try to make me
feel bad even the tiniest
[Music]
bit the comments man shouldn't you be
getting some rest here she should be
more like oh okay maybe you'll do it
later then thank you for
now now like okay then I guess we'll die
guess I'll die
[Laughter]
guess I'll die I'm not trying to make it
feel bad but guess I'll
die I've placed your various orders and
a carpenter by the name of Bernard is on
his way from Martha's rest that's
brilliant thanks Clyde is
there anything else you need nope Black
Thorn and Lady Karen have already sent
over everything asked for and I've got
all my plans drawn up so as soon as
Bernard gets here we can get to
work I can't wait
hey why did he say it like that you mean
CLI just now I was also thinking he was
a little bit like anything else huh
anything
else no hold
on that's my good deed for the day done
let's see how Jill's fairing yeah that's
more important and get our kiss going
frying
[Music]
pan been doing mids bidding have you
everyone wh it's fine it was just a
little bit wasn't that much of a
bother where is
[Music]
she oh in
Dare
[Music]
buds mid bids what bid mids
bidding bids
[Music]
Ming ah Clive T how's Jill recovering
but she still needs her
rest of
course take her care of her won't you
I'll do my best oh gav was looking for
you you he said he had something to show
you in the shelves the shelves mhm oh
that's right he went to ask he must have
found something toy walkie
lore all
right I'm curious
maybe either he's also like
something like me
or like an Obelix thing where he just
like accidentally
by being around me or
so got some of my power
or someone
else's let see bow bow
lore Clive where have you been I've been
wanting to ask you something about tole
I have no answers where did you get him
like in the first place uh my father
father brought him back from one of his
Expeditions into the Northern
Territories they were crossing a
snowfield when they heard his cries and
seeing no sign of his pack they took him
in what you reckon Toms it certainly
adds weight to the theory cive I believe
that tole may be no mere Hound but a
rare frostwolf an animal native to the
far Northern reaches of valisia in one
of our oldest myu is I found reference
to a frost wolf who served as guardian
to an ancient Queen of the North Queen
of the such was his Mastery over ether
he could cast Magics on command cool his
name was fenri that sounds familiar
fenri the
frostwolf now the animals do not state
it
explicitly but I have reason to believe
this Queen was a dominant of Shiva a
girl from the Northern Territories and
her faithful Hound one awakens as the
dominant of Shiva and the other you're
saying that Jill granted tole his P
that's why they kind of match visually
just like
Fen people called him my Hound but togle
and Jill were
inseparable H he grew up as a faithful
companion to the dominant of Shiva and
years later his powers awakened so late
just when his master needed him the most
a you're right if it weren't for tole
blasting those bastards to Kingdom Come
he I thought it was my
Dole though toal's power is his own I'm
sad his latent Birthright as a frostwolf
it had only to be
unlocked oh get you
tole you're an even fin than we
thought got a mared Jill and regarding
your original concern you need not fear
for Tal's Health why the Beast has the
appetite of a behemoth just this very M
I found him with his nose buried in my
nuts
oh
okay there you
are I've been looking everywhere for you
burn I need you to introduce her so we
can get to
work oh I'll be a moment no way they
didn't put this there on purpose but in
Japanese wonder if it
works as funny in
[Music]
Japanese
nuts
nuts what's nuts did just say
nut is it
brilliant It
is Well I couldn't have done it without
you you and everyone else but promise
I'll pay you back yeah but it's got to
be I'm going to the fingers to the Bone
for you l starting right now just you
wait not for I'll make wonders like this
world's never seen then I look forward
to seeing
them
nice table now that that's settled I
wonder if Vivian's made any progress
tracking down
[Music]
Copco my chat there we go okay my chat
was like
lagging yeah maybe it's just a little K
ation who was having some fun
[Music]
there oh now we have to talk to Vivian
again you know what that means brain
hord I think I'll wait till mids away
take
a mids dungeon he wants a tour of mids
dungeon
where are all these
comments how goes the hunt for CA at
Japan got the localization a we have
Myriad sightings of strange soldiers in
unexpected places that always the case
but nothing definitive as yet with Final
Fantasy only we knew for certain by what
route he left
roosth well keep at it that was the
first if anyone can piece this puzzle
together it's you hey and I'm willing to
wait as long as long as it
takes
well okay got to
listen she going to say
something say something I'm ready I'm
ready to
listen
what here yeah would that be a problem
do you know Clive I believe it a mercy
that you didn't inherit your father's
Throne your poor people would surely
live in fear of you you have nothing to
worry about on that front I won't be
claiming his
crown that is a
relief uh Clive have you got a
minute we um have a
guest a
guest yeah the lips do seem very
accurate to the English language what
they're saying
true I
guess
yellow oh for your trouble it was a
pleasure wait you know I Uncle dad Uncle
Byron Uncle dad Clive my boy Tas can
stoke the ovens for your favorite uncle
is here he can really be uncle dad cuz I
got no more dad so he is uncle and now
Dad we need new
dad
awesome
meanwhile Twin Side holy Empire of
Sri damn seat of Imperial Court wow the
dmean government SU for
peace how shall we
respond if they're willing to accept
their fault in the
matter to refuse them oh my God she's so
drugging him must insist on substantial
reparations twins side stores are not as
bottomless as reported I and we have
many more mouths to feed we shall just
have to have the Dalek empty their
treasuries for
us yeah I was thinking of the boy from
the veil in Game of Thrones 2o they must
have inspiration from
that of course we see no sucking yet
this would have been possible without
your timely intervention Prince
Olivier indeed I doubt any of us would
have had the courage to trade words with
the mighty Titan nor less the wit to win
him over the Empire owes you a great
debt is he may the blessing of the
crystals go with you your highness May
the blessing of the Crystal manipulated
in some way very
good now let us come to the question of
precisely when the Dalek will withdraw
their troops be's fire could rid us of
them
in that look was Susy it was so
suspicious does the
boy come from this
guy she I mean this
guy is he the father or they just have
an affair who
knows who won his throne at least
partially by virtue of his son Dion
having awakened as a oh he's the Bahamut
oh first one stand a loyal subject of
the emperor
sylvestra blonde hair mattress right
right right and that look that look you
can't tell me that was not the look like
they're
they're getting it on
XXX rul as well as leader of the
Empire's most elite fighting force the
drons oh Dion is also the dominant of
baham Ven of light and has of been call
of
German been called upon to summon his
icon in defense of his countrymen most
recently in the year of the realm 873
when Odin took to the field against them
in battle of
theor she's his step yeah so
what so
what you remember where they took
inspiration from
right read this the crystalline
impass
a conflict fought between the holy
Empire of SRE and the Republic of dalmia
in the year 878 878 largely concerning
control of the crystalline Dominion the
Dominion had previously been the subject
of a non-aggression pact between the
valan Nations but in 873 the Empire
claimed twin okay I
can't understand that anyway the
Cardinals senior Statesman at make up
the highest office of
government is comprised of the high
Cardinal and the four Cardinals who
administer and administer the outer
provinces five smaller States is located
in the southern half of the continent of
storm has Capital at randel also home at
the mother Crystal known as dr's Fang
which the next one will be taken down
maybe inside which stand Castle dasb
home of Hugo kopka dominant of Titan
kopka obssessed with finding Sid and
exacting his revenge for the murder of
benedicta Harman co-opted the soldiers
of the realm and had them commit a
series of
atrocities and an attempt to flush him
out of hiding yep yep yep that
happened the former capital of
crystaline dominion after a unilateral
maneuver by the holy Empire became auh
okay the men of the Fist will not
withdraw until a peace treaty is
concluded so let us keep the
negotiations open give them time to
gather what gold and trinkets they can
and once they deliver that which we
demand what worth is a piece of
parchment your Radiance were Prince Dion
to take the field the enemy would surely
send their own dominant to meet him and
while his hin this would of course
Prevail of course there would be heavy
losses on both you need not fear Hugo
Koper he is engaged on the Western Front
even where the D descend for him he
would not arrive in
time as much as I would enjoy witnessing
a clash between Bahamut and Titan no me
too it is not to be
man and what of your subjects your
radiance
if the fighting spread to the city
proper the people would bear the brunt
of
it there will be losses it is
true yet for every citizen Who falls
another can be
bred for every home that burns another
can be
built this guy seems
nice
is he a good guy
Dion yes sir is this like a thing where
like there's the Cersei but the
the the what was his name he's actually
pretty good if he's away from
Cersei yeah
Jamie
mhm
okay I thought he was going to slap him
prepare for battle
something like
that do not make me repeat
myself return to your camp and await my
orders
flower if that is your wish your
Radiance I shall depart at
once
maybe it wasn't the look
like but more like a she was giving him
like that smirk was more of a evil smirk
cuz right now his face was more like I
don't care much for you but who knows
could be both could be
both I was more like I'm in control
forgive you you can't stop me
from her I
mean oh yeah what do the astrologers
or the stars are in agreement your
Radiance the shadow of treachery hangs
over Prince
Dion so annabella's Tales were true oh
you disappoint me
Dion Oh My Oh My but he's got the
eyes of not his mommy I guess from the
the Sun is from the guy that was just
sitting next to her right the I forgot
his name already is that there bab here
only one way to find out okay that's why
he's got brown eyes okay yeah good good
good n you know could have been from
Dion too but I guess not would have been
spicier
though if he thought it was his child
but it was his son's
child that's that's
spicy cuz that's going to make him mad
have been up to their old tricks
again that makes no sense you make no
sense we will we can make it make
sense if they were willing to but no
that was too spicy for them cutting off
hands it's fine but this too
spicy cuz I'm too spicy for your
[Music]
heart too
spicy too
spicy Esa Uncle dad ah my dear nephew
how I've missed
you how did you find this place Uncle
hug through the good offices of young s
Wade he really is the most helpful
fellow as are you I hear the Guardians
and those they freed tell the most
outlandish Tales of your heroics in
rosali which is why I came to learn the
full truth of the matter sought the fact
from the fiction so to speak you were
working with the Guardians of the flame
to Evacuate the people of rosala ptis
Alda I was I no then I have questions
for you please come inside Uncle gladly
interrogation uh you there friendly
interrogation there are 2,000 gold
talents in those chests see that they're
added to my nephew's coffers would
you
2,000 free money thank
you and I'm afraid that is all I
know a fleet sailing South past Port
isala most
intriguing forgive me for not being able
to tell you more I hadn't the faintest
idea Copco withdrew wounded from roosth
still less that my own nephew dealt the
decisive
blow what do you think
Vivian I think with this news of the
Delan Fleet and recent reports of the
royalists movements that the final piece
of the puzzle has fallen into
place come here and I'll show
you closed
window show me
okay it is known that kupka's forces
entered Rosaria via its unguarded Coast
mhm mhm okay so can the same be said of
your visitors from
wud certainly her royal Navy is famed
for the efficiency with which it Bears
her knights from one Battlefield to the
next and in the IR Haya or black gallion
she boasts a vessel nigh as Swift and
every bit as feared as the Kingdom's
legendary
Cavalry A fitting Flagship for a she
already lost me her Naval presence being
crucial to her Ambitions Beyond
Ash yes it seems safe to assume that the
royalist did indeed enter Rosaria from
the sea uhhuh so then I'm back I'm back
had you a vested interest in Titan
survival with would you take him what
kind of sentence was that to Drake's f a
place Rich enough in ether to conjure
the Magics needed to mend his
HTS but would that not entail an arduous
Voyage around the southern
Cape let us say going on about did put
aore with a mind to Spirit kopka Away
from under your very nose could that
truly have been their plan for him why
do I to load him aboard one of the ships
flying Republic is it weird is is it is
it just me who has such Troubles of
understanding this woman I'm sure that
if English is your first language you
have no troubles but anybody whose
language first language is not
English okay you guys partially struggle
to okay thank you thank
you thank
okay good very
good to load him aboard one of the
ship's flying Republican caller SED of
the
coast colors sighted off the coast near
Port isala to spend weeks at Sea being
tossed hither and ywn by unforgiving
waves his life hanging in the
balance no no the journey would mean
Titan's death and kupka's faithful
creatures would not allow it are we
discussing so what then was the plan of
our Wuda friends how they got Cort
suggest they made not for the coast but
for the
Desert and by cutting through the velcro
a party traveling light would have
tightened back in his bed days before a
galley could Lurch into
port to ITT it was the royalists not the
Republicans who affected Hugo a safe
Retreat uh-huh I would stake your life
on it I believe you yeah yeah sounds
[Music]
legit so it was the wers who spirited
the wretch
away now I think about it there was
something a little strange about the
ships I saw the men seemed almost
crestfallen as if in mourning as if they
believed
Jun
so actually I did um use my dualingo
yesterday mm I did a little bit of study
yeah quite quite surprising I know maybe
maybe I'll do a bit more
today or well may
to believe that their master was
dead you have a keen mind Lord
rosfield and you have your answer to
find kupka you have merely to follow the
royalist trail across the velcro all
right it may well have gone cold by now
but as they say in the Republic all
roads lead to dr's Fang to Rome you mean
allow me to accompany you part of the
way as luck would have it I had intended
to Journey canver word on business after
visiting you here the Fang would be but
a short it was Rome right I'd be glad of
the company give me a moment to make
ready I need to tell my friends what
we've learned and where we're going very
well but be quick about it my boy time
waits for no man
okay
[Music]
byebye mid's finished outfitting little
work your by here
from of
course love his name copas at Drake's
Fang I'll be leaving Before Sunset
you're not going in there alone are you
don't
worry I'm not going there to destroy the
mother Crystal all I'm after is koa's
head yeah from malol in the middle I
promise the L are on the
Fang's personal Thom you have any
trouble on the way you ask for Rosena
delill some call her the desert hair who
is
she an old associate of Sids and only
SIDS all I know is the name and that
they used to meet at the delill Inn
we've heard nothing from her since he
died but I'm thinking maybe the new Sid
might be able to bring it back into the
F thanks I'll keep that in mind so uh
what about your uncle thank you disy I
mean he's welcome to stay but don't look
so worried he'll be coming with me thank
for that gav Otto I'm leaving you
two in charge you can count on
us at least you're not roasting me on my
taste okay like come on I don't
understand why you guys were roasting me
yesterday because okay maybe there's
some weird shows that I watch but at the
same time not those shows you guys are
like
based what's wrong with Home Improvement
man like there's nothing wrong with that
and the office and scrubs and all that
like get it like what you
[Music]
problem you talk as if like every single
show that I watch is garbage well also
in the end it's personal preference okay
there's so many people who watch these
shows
too okay thank you the Litt have been up
to their old tricks
again you're not the problem we just
don't get it sometimes uhuh
uhhuh Home Improvement is
fine but I can't accept liking family
but that's F it's not about like okay no
I I will say I don't like SpongeBob
really but I'm also not like constantly
watching Family
[Music]
Guy spongeb is
[Laughter]
[Music]
just it's just so childish
Patrick make
booger
also the the Plankton small smaller
Plankton he scared me when I was a child
okay okay didn't like him especially the
episode where he was like I don't know
taking over the ocean being evil
that was traumatizing for me as a child
[Music]
okay don't make fun of my
feelings as every episode no there's one
that especially step stay in my brain
okay but I don't want to remember it I
don't want to remember it it hurts
okay you guys suck you're for making fun
of me oh thank you tiet
[Music]
monkey all right Uncle I'm ready to
depart shall we we shall come let us a
away to
Adventure he's so
cute so
motivated that's cool
oh why thank you for loving me
anyway also the squirrel is stupid like
my God underwater squirrel she's
[Music]
stupid
yeah I don't like Sandy don't like her
much she's cartoon C
why how yeah she's annoying thank
you her ACC no I was watching in German
I don't I never heard a text young man
when last I walked this part accent cuz
she was speaking
German doch uh SpongeBob scham Club
SpongeBob scham Club Spong Trading Post
not far from here Road toang leads
through
it the trading posted is he does live in
a pineapple
though
wait before we
continue you must forgive
me in my apparently so bad
tastes if I sing for you in
German the uh
song
okay
Alice I I
Captain Lou I captain Oh
[Music]
SpongBob
SpongeBob SpongeBob spam cob
SpongeBob spam cob
it's a bit of a tongue
twister okay I have been forgiven right
you forgive me
right good
good great I have redeemed
myself no not rip F no no no
no it's
passible not until you hate Big Bang
Fury I will never hate Big Bang Fury I
don't like it as much as other shows
it's definitely obnoxious here and there
and I hate how they don't eat the food
in the cafeteria ever my biggest
Pat beef is when they just dab dab dab
dab da dab B the food and don't eat it
um it's the worst thing I hated that I
can't watch it anymore because of that
makes me so aggressive
man but the spin-off is so cute like
genuinely uh uh I forgot my my
brain um
the that little Sheldon is you can't
like if you
say just because you hate Big Bang Fury
that little Sheldon sucks to It's So
Different it's so different young
Sheldon not little
Sheldon it's so different and and it's
such a sweet show no it's like something
completely different it's not
comparable I love young
Sheldon do they eat the food in that
more than in Big Bang
fairy give it a chance
please please
please all right I love this music
already is our uncle dad fighting with
us that would be great can my Cho come
here
too oh
hello they can but I'm going to walk for
now our destination Lies over that Dune
Beyond The Ruins okay Mark them well
Clive it's all too easy to lose one's
bearings in the
Sands really
quietly now man I already feel the sand
in between my
toes
sick go
tole tole
kill all yours to let's go for a ride
scorpion years ago when you were just a
boy M you and I rode this way together
do you need help being your father on a
scouting expedition to D he's so far he
let me come with you he's not even
attacking I'm not surprised you don't
remember it's nothing was just before
Joshua was born why do I so eager to be
there when your brother arrived why do I
even have teammates your chobo too hard
on the journey home and fell from the
saddle no I didn't don't say that that
never happened you'll never forget how
elwin fussed over you as you sat in the
sand balling like a babe hell diver cute
cute wait when you were sitting you
looked really cute sit down
again
attack stay
down aggressive I think I think
C might have some issues
go let's help
him too far too far too far there we go
this
one
[Music]
attack I really don't like flying
enemies in this game at least the
smaller ones I don't like cuz
they're hard to
reach even like normally in other
games when you like shoot them or hit
them once they fall down and then they
stay down but these ones often they just
stay
flying I know I have ch but I said I
want to
walk feel like walking cuz then I can
open any chests right away and you know
I feel like fighting a little bit
anyway I don't mind fighting a little
bit oh oh okay I thought I couldn't get
up somewhere there
okay look at us zooming for the sand wow
he's faster than
me Uncle
Dad
she must be doing some
cardio I want to
explore what if I walk into this
whirlwind
oh it's
gone there's something over
there okay maybe we'll get there later
no chests though what the hell no chests
at
all oh wait we have to go there oh never
mind I thought we have to go
here
ch also it must be freaking hot here so
I'm just trying to not OV exhaust my
choco B there she is the good old doll
in do you know this heat has given me
quite a thirst oh that water before we
press on that water
though
amazing Dam they may not have much water
but the water they have is
[Music]
beautiful a bit
wobbly that look so
wobbly mhm n
n darker tall look there what those are
Ashen steeds
no doubt about it and such a long ride
from Stone here our Wuda friends must be
soothing their saddle SS in the Inn
shall We join
sadd run along and play now togle it's
not allowed inside
what
sad
s
too no Siam
too
[Music]
sad did he just look at her
ass
n
just peeking right at the people there
totally yeah
yeah good day to you
eating sorry about my pal he only talks
when his mouth's full what do you
recommend CL just trying and snap if you
after something light we do a fine
Chocobo soup with lentils and honey M
two bowls of that then an ale right you
are hey girl
[Music]
coming your pal would you rather be my
Squire what's
this nice cheese and salami
platter oh where is she bringing that
to special room
oh
oh oh so
close and they don't
know josy
wasi he's got the
cof oh that's wor wor than the C Your
Grace it is plain you are not yet well
enough to travel if you would only let
me take you to someone who can better
attend to your ills no we must press on
Prince Dion has returned to his camp and
will soon depart for the
front I must speak with him at all costs
miss this chance and I may never get
another you do understand
that yes Your Grace but you must at
least agree to take your
medicine I'll fetch you some
water maybe she'll see
me yeah show yourself to your
uncle
cam
ah keep watch they tell us but all I see
is sand I hear they got our guest back
to the Fang without any trouble we'll be
leaving soon enough why the Lord
Commander dragged us all this way just
to save that Blockhead skin we never
know dominant or not he's a bloody
idiot that'll be cook bloody he
is
Uncle let's get this down us we have a
long way to go hey
you
[Laughter]
yeah yeah just ignore it yeah yeah it
will go
away
sorry she didn't see him she didn't see
him of course she didn't see him but she
saw the
soldiers I got seven DMS can you walk
your grace what's wrong I fear trouble
may be Brewing downstairs just
this all from one
person you two are Travelers are you
not me and my companions are strangers
here perhaps you'd be good enough to
accompany us while on help us find our
way sorry lad but we've got business in
camera that can't
wait ah I'm sure you could spare us an
hour or two everybody's leaving
friend
get it's it's another one of those
battles
[Music]
I'm afraid a moment to lose
friend CLI stay back uncle
gladly oh they're funny
D yeah he's not much of a help anyway so
that's okay try
it I went to the side to get more of
them my boy just like
that yeah you're seeing it right these
are the powers of the very Titan that
you supposed to protect
nice kick slow
motion if you go into photo mode you can
go into photo mode during a fight like
this you can see him
hiding game of FRS the Hound
a I I I can yeah I can see that you mean
the Hound with
ARA yeah yeah there were moments like
this
this I need to rewatch Game of Thrones
it's time it's been a while it's
time it's that time of the
year feel
trouble uh word of advice miss that soup
could do with a touch small salt
Uncle
dad was she
watching yeah all right so she must be
aware
now cuz she saw my
Powers she she knows
right oh a beautiful holy
now's our
chance what do you mean you never had
soup before
M get out of here I'm fine did you ever
have water
before get out of
here you're kidding
right never had soup have ever eat
anything no bacon no eggs no
[Laughter]
soup I'm losing
[Music]
it is that a
joke
Clive OS answer me I need your answer
but I need to look at Clive too he
missed
him what did you eat soup
before he got he got to remember that
Joshua doesn't like carrots what is it
now
never
no what
you're oh my
God I am in
disbelief soup is
amazing creamy tomato soup or pumpkin
soup taste the season of pumpkin soup
please go and get some pumpkin soup
although I don't know if you can get
really good pumpkin soup in uh New York
but it's a season so some places might
have pumpkin
soup I like I like also potato soup of
Fick potato soup is really nice even
onion soup is can be really nice that's
all the FI all the Fick soups now
remember from my from my plane ride when
I showed you guys I ate this like um
green
ORS what's it the green
balls pea soup yeah that was
surprisingly good like wow one of the
best soups I've ever had probably my
whole life I died in an
airplane that was
great
H damn M sauce it's like you've been
living under a rock and only
eating
ants cuz that's all you have under the
rock my
God okay okay Cal
down everybody calm
down calm
[Laughter]
down
it it's nothing it's everything let's
go somebody who's in New York take him
out to eat
please
you never had
peace I'm not even going
to cuz peas are okay you can I can see
how you could miss peas but soup in
general eggs bacon we didn't know where
to find cupka before we do now the ress
said it themselves their guest is in the
Fang you should press on before any more
of their friends turn
up all right let's check out this new
city oh this is
cool got a haggle
though candles candle
store
ooh I will make you a full course meal
ah they've closed the road and it's the
only only way from here to the
Fang it would seem Lord Koper is not
accepting visitors at present maybe it's
like a guy thing I was just thinking
like cuz you just said for some meals I
just have you know a slice of bread
maybe it's like you know a see some in
some like room
reviews where uh room is just empty all
it has is like a a TV and a PlayStation
on the ground and maybe a bean bag chair
that's all the things in the whole room
so maybe it's
like for you it's like a that's all I
need kind of thing and you don't even
make an effort to eat anything else cuz
like it's
easier you're you're you're just
wow it's
amazing
judgmental it's an M thing not a guy
thing he still puts an effort to make
soup nice soup is great it's
great and
SAU I I can't help it but you're taking
it really
well oh man we have to get through that
gate uh not by force I trust we've
attracted quite enough unwanted
attention already by gu then perhaps the
desert hair can offer us her Aid Rosina
Dal woman of mystery G but how will we
find her we know not of her but her name
and that she was working with Sid s
other collaborators have all been people
of means the wealthiest and most
successful members of of their
communities I'll wager this Rosen damel
is the same that would certainly help to
narrow the search we need only inquire
as to who is in charge of the town and
that's exactly what I mean to do I'll go
find this Rosen and ask her for a
collaboration on my
channel speak with for Gil sake you're a
bear anything I can allow me my good man
we represent seeking to expand our
business in the region and would very
much like to make the acquaintance of
Dam's leading
entrepreneurs if only we knew where to
find
them well we're best known for our baths
our markets and our
smiies I suppose you could do worse than
start your search at one of
those thank you oh um you wouldn't
happen to know a lady by the name of
Rosina Damu would you no no I can't say
I do
well roasted Bell Pur M okay all
right someone knows what's up looks like
we won't be getting back to Drake's Fang
wait I want to look at this beautiful
water wow
fish saw a fish in the
water oh hi oh my
God this
is
as yeah pretty much as transparent as
the water in the MS was like you could
really just see the fishes so
clearly a lot of them had really bright
colors though like light like at the
shore they had a lot of like silverish
fishies so they were hard to perceive a
little bit but you could see them easily
through the water
H we're at the
moldes I'm so excited oh my God it's
like uh I'm stressed out about like time
passing really fast but on the other
hand I'm super excited about it because
the faster it passes the faster I'll be
at the moldes and it's honestly not that
much time anymore
actually not that much more time
left wait oh this is
pretty oh what are you doing lady
Daydreamer just like me are you also
dreaming about the males this river runs
all the way to the southern
Seas they used to load the crystal onto
barges and sail it to the Villages
Downstream before the Canyons were lost
to beasts and bandits mhm when I was a
girl I would wave to The Boatman as they
set off on their long journey and they
would throw me sweet meats in return
such Happy Times sweet
meats what sweet
meats sweet
meats a
candy what the called sweet candy
sweet
meats a Candi bacon really
sweet meats are great and then explain
what that
is caramelized
pork
[Music]
what what' you want can't you see I'm
busy she's your eyes well I'm looking
for someone a Woman by the name of Rosen
damil do you know her never heard of her
is that all one more question is it you
if I wanted to find the richest traitor
in town where would you recommend that I
look well that's easy the Briar's kiss
don't find a finder Smithy this side of
the streeta is only a young spri but
he's got all the right ideas the Bri's
kiss you
[Music]
say no thank you for you is the person
we're looking for you said Sid's contact
was likely to be an influential sord we
just wait influence comes with age and
experience believe you
me you'll just
wait Mommy I want to play with the
crystal how many times do I have to tell
you it's not a
toy it press
destination
nearby
H is it this
child
no
what someone hiding
here
[Laughter]
oh can I help you
yes I'm looking for a woman by the name
of Rosina delam surprising pillar of
your community I believe from old
trading stock then you should ask
further he's been here for years knows
the place and its people like the back
of his hand and he's in with all the old
Merchant families try the baths that's
where you'll usually find him the thank
you
kindly okay
well it sounds like we have our man from
one place to another they're sending me
let's go and find out exactly what this
fur
knows do I have to censor the baths
h
no excuse me are you fer don't I am can
I help you Trav I like him I hope so
scary you've lived here for some time is
that correct do you know Rosina Dam
we believe she may be a Trader of some
Renown and what business do you have
with the desert hair she was a close
friend of mine I was hoping she might be
able to help me very
well go to the bardello I'll arrange an
introduction
okay uh just look at the details do you
think we can trust him only as far as I
think
so you're the ones who've been sniffing
around oh they're going to beat me up I
beg you
pardon don't play the fool stick your
nose in our business and you're likely
to lose
it you don't know who you're messing
with but can't you Ste like look at my
armor I'm not normal
[Music]
okay no no no no no no
no new enemies
approach this
one all yours
to we have plot
armor want some more how about this
power or
this or
this you can Cho
with what power do you want to be
killed guess it was too late they
couldn't make a choice after
[Music]
all YouTu being weird again
o who are you working for him or
her him the boss him he wanted us to
test you uhuh though one could hardly
call that so that dude is probably
the secret his code name dragged in
maybe your scale with a blade is rare
indeed my Lord A fitting talent for an
outlaw you know who I am so what now
call in the men of the Rock and collect
the bounty
that isn't my decision to make our work
is
done take him to meet his precious Rosen
oh she will be interested to make
acquaintance thank you for 28 months to
the lock of leisure then thank you
that's a long time to the lock of
leisure next stop lock of
lger
you know reminded me of one book Al
[Music]
song and then there's the bridge and
then I forgot that part but then it goes
uh uh at some point it goes
like it's
fun I think it it was a I think it's
called dancing
Samurai my carpet listen to it it's
fun the dance for it is fun
too is this the
place luo's Forge the Bri's
kiss right you know
it ah ah so it was the young sprig after
all so much for Rosina damil being a
woman of
experience how wrong I was it was an
easy mistake to make Uncle after all it
must have been years since Sid last saw
her sorry
him whoever this lubo truly is he's
clearly a man of
means I'd say he deserves our
respect see that he gets it
oh sorry it's a handle of my chair I was
trying to
stretch luor Lord furda told me to bring
them to
you my boys tell me you're in need of
assistance oh Sid the second
confidence I won't waste your time time
I need Passage through the south gate
passage
what tell me what do you think is a
Merchant's most important
commodity why trust everyone knows that
without it you have
nothing but I'm Sid and nothing is
exactly what you have I have the title
and so for you I do have
nothing okay I'm not in the business of
helping every lost puppy that wanders in
off the street I'm a busy man as you can
see busy let's leave this mama don't
look busy by all
means find someone else to help you on
your
way just be sure to tell them you're not
the two travelers from the Inn the
guards are looking for don't want them
jumping to conclusions do we why
you so funny what do we need to do to
earn your
[Music]
trust I like this one willing to do
whatever it takes to get what he
wants not
whatever than you like Tyson's ass
special place in my
heart why you
ask because they get me what I want
always
fine so what do you want get to the
point don't tell me you're going to
listen to this we might as well hear him
out assuming he is an ally of course and
yet even then I had more good sense but
enough of the pleasantries okay I want
you to put an end to the trouble in Dam
oh return to me when you have done so
and you shall have my aid until then I
bid you good day oh what trouble if
you're going to give us all maners gra
beard one catches more damsel flies with
honey than with vinegar sorry foring you
call me my apologies a word of advice in
recompense it's kind of funny to follow
the crystals Uncle dad oh but that was
three
oh I'm making this too easy teasing
him it will be easy solving his little
riddle should be like dealing with him
Child's Play Let Us divide our forces
cleive I'd rather not drag this parlor
game on any longer than we need
to all right good luck Uncle he's like
he's become a character a little bit um
unexpected we were the only ones causing
trouble in from what I thought he was
going to
be he's more like surprisingly
childish clumsy L what the I I like I
like it it's just uh un un
unexpected do you have why do I keep on
stopping depends what for well where is
Stones Throw from Drake's F the soldiers
guarding the mother Crystal and the
shipment need a place to spend their
hard earned guilt the men of the rock
throw their money about like there's no
tomorrow is that
so okay let's talk to everybody
everybody has really interesting things
to say after
all right give me some childlike humor
yeah yeah he's he's great he's a great
character wait what the
hell nearby
you rest
go ah here okay I okay that's why I
didn't see it at the dock before either
cuz it only pops up when you get like
close to it excuse
me you've heard then I've heard rumors
damn pilfering the crystals that were
meant to fill our cups and light our
stoves ping us common folk have hardly
had a Shard to share between us these
last few and it isn't as if we can buy
them on the black market either
whoever's taking them they aren't
sharing n that's not
good leave it to
me Kiana said excitedly
deposit for what you mean when I was
talking like this yeah
totally and port or bread so much bread
but most of it is flat and Port oh
nice nice bread nice bread I like the
detail believe how much he gave me well
I what can I do for you Soldier very Smo
need that sword polishing I'm not a
soldier then be off with you I serve the
men of the Rock and the you have an
agreement with them don't be stupid I
just know which side my bread is
buttered speaking of bread I want to be
stuck under some paa when they come
knocking with Pockets deeper than zamas
and an urge to empty them no just leave
will you before you scare them
off I think you've said enough I think
I'm starting to get an idea of what's
been going on I wonder if Uncle Byron's
learned anything of
use he'll probably be back at the End by
now feeling in tummy again the most
fragrants and unle
B all that crashing and banging
about it's you the one who broke all our
furniture what do you want haven't you
caused enough trouble already I guess
that was me I'm looking for my pal have
you seen him the gentleman who was with
you yes he's upstairs
but
but thank you I'll go and fetch him what
did he fall asleep cuz he got drunk in
the short amount of time
or
uhoh
upstairs
here let me treat
you oh ah there he is NY why is he so
secret is he making a secret
deal will this suffice as a deposit he's
getting scammed by the
Sands that's a black not really one of
the many Treasures in my collection
wasting his money only tooo happy to
part with should you give me reasons he
scamming
him all right I'm sure that we can come
to an agreement but not
here no Uncle dad what are you doing
uncle uncle dad stop we have plenty of
information
now such a boomer
you feel the Boomer
energy care to explain why you're giving
gifts to Koopas men bait my boy one
cannot catch one's prey without him
trying to be cool and I do believe I've
snagged us quite the Quarry oh really I
started by asking around the markets as
to where I might purchase crystals I had
no luck of course it's forbidden to
trade in such things but my
uncharacteristic
indiscretion just happened to attract
the attention of those uniformed
Ruffians they took me aside and said
they could procure the crystal I sort if
I proved I could pay for it so the Pearl
was your
proof I thought they'd asked for more a
second raade specimen like that would
wait so you were actually
useful price to pay for admittance to
the
underworld but enough about my little
Act of fuge what did you discover that
the supply of crystals has dried up of
late and some people seem to think
they're being stolen meanwhile members
of koopa's private guard have been
spending money all over town I'll wager
those soldiers who've been talking to
have been siphoning off crystals meant
for elsewhere mhm and pocketing the
profits I'll all
right we'll meet with them then and put
an end to the
trouble okay it just goes to show one
should never underestimate a rosfield
we'll soon wipe that smirk off his
face Dam I arranged to meet with the
soldiers in a secluded corner of the
velcro far from prying eyes the perfect
place for a spot of double dealing the
Boomer energy I trust I can count on
your support if things turn
sour of course let me treat you you got
out there I need to drink oh she lights
her
cigarette with the stone man of
the wrong W okay don't swear so
much well out of here I guess not
through here where can I leave this
city from here perhaps light it for
Gilbert's will they not let me
out can I please oh
no Gate Keeper the gate is closed the
gate is
closed by the orders of Lord kopka
no by the or by the or wait can I listen
to it again the second part the gate is
closed the gate is closed by order of
Lord kopka by order of Lord to's
Fang by order of Lord CS that doesn't
even sound so
British
Sil how do I leave this
place back I need a new dress the gate
is closed here
maybe oh my God look at all these shitty
chatties on the left
side let's go
choco B choco B speaking of choco B did
you see the finished drawing I uploaded
it I completely forgot about uploading
it yesterday
man I wonder if KOB saw it did she reply
to my tweet while I'm
streaming did you guys see
it he was just looking at it I'm
actually you know not even that unhappy
with it
even when I slept over it and looked at
it again so that's a good
sign she didn't answer maybe I'll send
her the link so that she doesn't miss
it can I
no Al is this even
connected wait
I wait wait what I have to go through
here but isn't this the one that was
closed oh no it was a South Gate ah
hell got to turn
around no no no no no no
no just wanted the
item forking bloody
helmate oh by the way my sister sent me
uh a
screenshot of something about my stream
with
Ellie like a part of the conversation
that was like posted on
Reddit cuz my my sister you know she
browses Reddit and like she sees the
front page I guess it made the front
page again cuz otherwise I don't think
she would see it she only sees things
when they make the front page and then
she's like oh look at this it's about
you
the might have been I can walk from here
might have
been
here what the how did I not see
this my talking tweet reached also the
main
what I was legit like watching quite a
bit yesterday um of the twitch bot cuz I
wanted to see what like normal
AOE um fans like I can I assume that her
viewers are
all quite good at AOE I wanted to see
what they would be
saying and just also out of Interest
like how was like reacting cuz sometimes
sometimes she went kind of quiet and I I
couldn't
make uh out of it like what what kind of
reaction she was having but then I saw
her move in the camera afterwards in the
VOD and explains
[Music]
everything they were happy to see you
improving I definitely improved
proed I definitely did I'll take it from
here I felt
it you'll take it
okay can you walk any
slower
ooh I was beginning to think you weren't
coming my
Lord you've brought your contribution
all the silver and Stones I could scrape
together at such short notice you
brought the whole 500 Talons that was
the price we agreed upon yes if you've
no objections I'd like to see the
crystal well can't you see it from here
right this way my lord they're out in
the
open wow
shiny are they
real not bad at all you weren't lying
about the
clarity but what of security if I were
to be stopped on the road what guarantee
have I that it wouldn't be seized as
property of the Republic none because
these crystals are no longer the
property of the Republic you're not
buying from us you're buying from them
H LA and we have no more jurisdiction
here than you my Lord but we have ships
and will gladly deliver to a port of
your choosing now that our price has
been
met royalists eh what brings you here
why to collect their share of Dr fing of
course our nations are allies and so
they are entitled to a portion of the
mother Crystal's Bounty and being such
good friends we elected to increase that
portion
and share the
benefits and now that these crystals are
officially property of the kingdom of
wude we are Duty bound not to interfere
no matter where they might happen to end
up
next did you get all that they're in
cahoots so it would seem my
Lord what is the meaning of this double
crossing dogs did you get all that h do
business kill them they're working
together kill them
both get wrecked oh that kill all of
them oh except for you just getting
warmed up
V
oh K's private guard let me bring you
closer to where the party is over
here
stay this
one this one
wow she was he
bastard yo come
here is that the wait aren't they both
the healers
kill now
No more healing on this battlefield
please I'm not healing either okay we
want a fair and sare
battle it's over damn it's like
interesting how we're like able to like
get up on all these rocks even mid
battle not the
chocobos
[Music]
no not the Choo
I don't want to hurt
[Music]
them
sick get
him hey come
here let me fry you
alive
who
left oh it's a heavy animal
okay sorry that sounded insulting I
didn't mean you were
fat you beautiful just the way you
are as a chicken in armor can I ride a
CH ball go for it do what makes you
happy I support
[Music]
it well that wasn't too bad howd you
like my performance huh I've often
played the villain on the stage I think
I did the role Justice don't you yeah
yeah great bid you were magnificent oh
the battle scene was particularly
thrilling I saw it great such a shame
you didn't have more of an audience but
perhaps that's for the best how long
have you been watching long enough to
witness your uncle's sworded transaction
it was acting I hardly expected one so
venerable to degrade himself so
thoroughly shut up buing one's way into
the confidence of
degenerates ingenious is that a
compliment now this was the trouble you
spoke of the men of the rock taking
crystals men for the common folk and
conspiring with the
royalists well now it's
over is
better be the people of dam had scarcely
any means of address against ca's men
let alone a foreign
army until you two came along that is
[Music]
M
nice
nice well we' better get these crystals
back to town you won't mind waiting with
them while I fetch a
wagon
[Music]
sure sometime
later it occurs to me that I still don't
know your
name Clive maybe should have asked
earlier so Sid II is a
Clive I suppose it could have been worse
well Clive you held up your end of the
bargain so I must do the same Passage
through the south gate was it not to
tell the truth you've helped a little
there too many of the gods have already
been redeployed to deal with the issue
of their missing comrades and those Left
Behind have been encouraged to look the
other way should you attempt to pass
through thank you and please allow me to
cover your your costs uh you still have
the purse I gave been having a lot of
fetching quests right now one of the
bodies running around quests as I really
so obvious kind of a weird point of
myard it is Lord Byron rosfield thank
you very much no thank you very
much Gray beard cuz until that it was
like pretty much
like at a nice Pace it went like where
this
from big thing to another big thing
continuously and now it's like any
friend of mine sees you with it shall be
a friend of yours thank you lub and
please feel free to send one of my
stoles back to your people tell them
that Rosen damil is back in bed with
Sid oh oh uh uh okay uh I don't want
that to spread to to jildo
turtle byebye turtle
fly see
you I'm trusting you Sid or should I say
Clive yeah please I prefer that so be
sure not to let me down I have a
reputation to uphold shut up I hate you
this guy I don't like
much mid is
fine and it's not just because she's
cute well then I wish you a safe journey
South he's just got an attitude not at
all I don't appreciate that pleasure an
attitude and an
ego come on Uncle let's
go oh Quest
complete y
uh what now go
home no make for Drake's Fang all right
all right which
exit
oh
ah now down here okay now we can take
the other exit
okay ah so the guards are gone now like
you said is it true what I'm hearing I
can go there now okay it would a fine
gift for your
beloved she'll look at you in quite a
Different Light I'm sure like
jewelry oh
yeah and I I really like this detail
like warm from the oven ooh the food
looks really
good damn and they're working in the
back he's like turning the sausages
around or whatever that
is they're baking the
bread light ands bows and basins bit and
pots bowls and
basins just look at the detail yeah I
amip you're
looking the from your door keep the
darkness from your door the gate L was
true to his word hell yeah let's
go we should get going soon seen the
food andine what is that uh 15 ah I'm
not too late what is it
lubo a question that I neglected to ask
earlier where is it that you're bound to
dr's F good game by the quality of his
bread just as I good criteria then allow
me to share a secret Drake's Fang is
currently riddled with royalists so
makan wot our allies and as you have
seen their soldiers work hand in glove
but no nation has ever before allowed a
foreign army to make a Barracks of its
holiest of holies not by choice at least
and there's more my man on the inside of
the Fang has failed to report for
several days oh I fear there may be more
trouble lying in weight for you on the
road
ahead isn't there always yeah if you're
determined to beard the Lion's Den then
promise me one thing that you will enter
via the mines where the guard is
lightest okay thanks bye-bye I've lost
one Sid already if I lose another people
will start to think me careless I don't
plan on
dying not before Koopa does anyway well
so long as you have a
plan
[Music]
no yeah I forgot about it we
underestimated it is it better to
connect it to the PS5 or to the power
outlet
I
wonder charging
now good point to stop ah I guess that's
kind of
true Drake's Fang should be just beyond
these
Springs shall we press
on
but
well I guess we're playing tomorrow
again I just feel like I didn't make
that much progress but maybe I
did tomorrow is starting 1 hour early
anyway right
so come on girl open now we can press on
made a lot of progress you think so
I guess I destroy the crystal
yeah
okay well it do be true it's already 10
p.m. if I read super chats and probably
end at 11:00
p.m. and then I can cook or like eat
whatever
okay
but but I want to talk a little bit
about
[Music]
yesterday I was trying to start this
conversation while running over to the
next destination but then I guess I'll
just talk about it without anything
going
on
um if I don't stop now I keep on going
oh really one of the most exciting Parts
in the game damn okay well that's coming
tomorrow then the most exciting part in
the game let's go to Maru let's go to
the office I guess cuz I look like
[Music]
this
with
feeling
[Music]
emotional
mature
vibing me covering go Chate by the way
what I can tell you now probably cuz
like it's almost happening uh and um I
would say the list of people is pretty
final cuz nobody said oh Sor I can't uh
participate after all really um I can
tell you who participates in family if
you I
think oh I was supposed to do
this let's see if I remember this
afterwards remind me I have to retake
something I recorded before at the end
of the stream okay
[Music]
um so family feeld
members uh uh I'm I I I think it's a 1
two 3 4 5 6 7 8 n Plus me is
10 no wait no no mineus one uh we're
nine people so I'll be just hosting I'll
be focusing on
hosting and we have two teams of
four okay uh participants will
be H fua Moco I'll put them in separate
teams and then koseki
beu Nissa
ravencraft yes yes yes then Nashi
M yes mmy Oro
cron uh ailia
Watson there's somehow more emotion when
I say her
name
a and
go you know she actually immediately
reacted with uh I want to participate
when I asked for family Fe participants
and I was like that makes so much sense
family food seems like a game gooy wants
to
play stacked lineup right yes we
got all of these people Kelly was going
to participate but then she realized uh
something was clashing in her schedule
sadly but this way now we're uh an
uneven number which I think I appreciate
uh I think I'm fine just doing um you
know uh first interaction with Advent
yeah I guess so maybe no no uh we they
interacted a little bit during the myth
Third Year Anniversary
right it's a second
interaction
[Music]
yeah we don't have an empty spot no no
no no this is fine the way it
is and I also felt like oh I'm am and
goba they both seem like people who like
Family Feud kind of streams
so it makes sense to me that they wanted
to participate I'm excited yay yay
yay so hopefully it will go well I'll
have to wake up really early but this is
the good thing I only have to control
the typing oh you know when I was
watching uh like V me and F play this
game on their streams um typing in for
their
participants it's a bit stressful you
know and I I I hope I I hope I can keep
up typing fast enough so that nobody
hates me for not inputting their answer
[Music]
correctly difficult I wish I could type
in with a
keyboard but but yeah there is AutoFill
got to keep an eye open for the autofill
I'm usually type of person who keeps
their eyes open on autoi do you ever
have this moment where you look over
someone's shoulder like they're typing
something in that maybe you told them to
type in or so you're just watching them
type in something and then they're like
so slowly typing it in but like it's in
the autofill like right away and they
just don't notice it and keep on typing
like painfully like trying to type
something that they don't really know
I'm like just just just there's it's
there it's there it's there and they
keep on typing and I'm like it's there
it's right there just choose
the I keep on typing keep on typing a I
got
it oh man he was there oh it was here oh
I didn't see it was right
there yeah yeah ah so I wanted to talk
wait I'll put on some BDM I wanted to
talk a little bit about yesterday so
want to say um I had so much fun
yesterday I I I I think I improved a lot
and I was so surprised that um me and
Ellie were like absolutely vibing like
what the
hell
how I think we got along really well I
was really worried because like
beforehand we only exchanged a few
messages and she seemed like a really
serious type to me because um she asked
me a few questions like what's okay to
say what's not okay to say she asked me
a few things about my audience like what
kind of
um like people you guys are like in ter
terms of age and uh gender and all that
just to like get a Vibe and she was like
oh it's just like
AOE CU like mostly male and a certain
age um she said it's just like AOE
actually has an
overlapping uh what's the
word overlapping um you guys help
me demographic yeah yeah yeah that the
word yeah so she seemed like really
serious to me um we we didn't
really like blond at all before that and
I was honestly really worried if she
would find me weird or finds the whole V
tubing thing weird and like you know
wasn't sure and then um we started our
Discord call for the first time 10
minutes before the
stream
uh yeah 10 minutes before the stream and
couldn't even really like talk like do
small talk cuz we were like busy setting
things up and then things weren't
working cuz like I was getting uh we
were both hearing each other in a
robotic way whenever I was screen
sharing so we were trying to figure out
those things you know um and and I felt
really nervous um and she was still
pretty chill cuz she was also focusing
on setting things up on her side so I
still couldn't quite get you know a
feeling for her but then once it started
you know I was really freaking out
inside because uh things weren't working
right away and I was hoping that she
wouldn't get like super
annoyed like oh man like so unprepared
why is it not working this is
frustrating no she was like really calm
and and we figured it out
thankfully and then from there on you
know we had small talk and stuff and and
got to know each other and she's just
she bounces off so well of me I was I
wasn't sure you know like you know
there's a lot of streamers out there but
m a a lot of people might not you
know have the same kind of style when it
comes to uh talking on the stream and we
actually talked a little bit about this
after the stream and she said something
that
just felt so much like oh just like me
for real for real she said that she
hates uh awkward silences and dead dead
dead uh air you know she hates dead air
and she always wants to fill
it and I'm like oh my God I yeah yeah I
can see that get
it just like
me yeah
and yeah we talked a bunch afterwards
too like for an hour it was actually
like I didn't know that after I ended my
stream cuz I asked her like are you
going to do anything after the stream or
just take your dog out and she said yeah
take my dog out but
I thought she was really ending it at
the same time as me but she was like
talking a little bit more with you guys
right so uh when I ended my stream I was
like all right I muted so yeah that was
nice right and then I noticed she she
left the Discord for she's
gone so then I waited for her um a while
uh and then eventually she came back but
I I had to like go and make food and all
that anyway cuz I was really hungry so
she she was like oh sorry did you want
to talk afterwards I'm like I it's fine
I I have to do stuff anyway and then I
don't know why she misunderstood it or
so but she immediately called me I'm
like I just said I'm I'm kind of
like not I don't really have time to
talk anyway but then she called me and I
didn't want to be like oh all right I'm
sorry I actually don't have time so I
just stayed and we talked for like an
hour and we just couldn't stop talking
like she was also really curious ious
she asked a lot of questions about um
you know me my job like V tubing whole
life Etc um and she was so happy about
how you guys were so nice to her how you
left so many
comments yeah so I think you guys left a
great impression I saw you guys in the v
afterwards like that a lot of you guys
were in her chat at the same time as in
my
chat
hello that's fine uh I think that also
left a good impression like you know my
my fan base uh asserting dominance a
little bit and showing her support as
well and then that way you know she sees
oh streaming with the Wawa is actually
also good for my CV maybe it's nice it's
nice when I can you know help
someone I I like that I want to bring
someone more new
viewers I heard she raided someone and
then they were like what the how do
you have so many viewers what the
yeah so hey I don't think it's the
first time must have been like similar
when I collabed with
like um the Indie girls before or was
that on my my
[Music]
channel was That was it on my Channel or
like one of
the was it on office Channel or
Pandora's
channel on office channel
right so I would think that I I brought
my my my my chickens over there too
obviously since especially one of you
guys
is deep in love with
her yeah um yeah
so I had a good time and like in the
beginning you know we still had if you
remember many many problems like I still
even with her coaching I quite couldn't
get a win in the beginning so I was
feeling kind of like overwhelmed and and
stressed uh but
like somehow in other games when I feel
this I don't want to play the game
anymore I don't really feel good about
the game but the thing is for
AOE and this is most likely the reason
why I keep on playing
it um even on my own especially on my
own is that the stress and the
frustration and the overwhelmingness of
AOE in aoe's case it really motivates me
and it really makes me want to get uh
over it and and it's like it keeps
me it keeps me a drive but a positive
one like it doesn't affect me negatively
it just want makes me want to get better
in other games I'll just be like uh I
hate this I don't want to play it
anymore but AOE gets me in a different
way yeah it's really difficult but
really makes me want to get
good so then later on it did get better
obviously it was still with a lot of her
help but if you notice like I paused way
less that was
important um I was able to keep up with
like Idol villagers and the production
of new villagers and uh military and all
that kind of stuff and and and uh I
guess I would say the beginning also got
better with like getting the order right
I I honestly in my solo stream I think I
already had the order right but then I
forgot because I didn't play for a while
and then I got really nervous cuz I was
being coached so my whole brain went
like I don't remember
anything yeah but I think I think it got
much better and that was fun to to feel
that I am actually improving and getting
over a big hurdle and then and at the
same time I'm like me getting along way
more than I thought with
Ellie actually feeling like a strong
connection and having fun with her and
and noticing how she's having fun with
me
actively that also just added so much to
it so I had a great time yesterday and I
hope we can do more like I'm serious
like this should be a regular thing me
playing AOE with her she seems to be
very open for it also for the uh German
Channel yeah so thank you guys for being
so sweet and welcoming to her and I know
that I I was concerned about you guys
cuz like uh I wanted to do well and I
wanted to not annoy ell so I was
focusing very hard on the game
especially later on uh so that I could
barely speak uh trying to like multitask
and look at everything that's going on
when there's like action everywhere on
the map so I couldn't talk much with you
guys and I noticed the chat was getting
slow too so I was like oh oh
oh the chat is so slow oh my God
what is going on I can't talk though so
I hope I hope you guys didn't uh think
it was super boring you
know yeah she kept on wanting to go on
that surprised
me and really surprised me because uh
you know after the beginning where was
like really frustrating still and then
we finally got the first win I thought
she would have been
exhausted of handling
me and would maybe not want to do this
again for now but then she she's like oh
yeah so let's do another one yeah and
I'm
[Music]
like okay and then we did another one
and then she wanted to do another one
and like oh another
one
wow that went surprisingly long like for
me
uh after like at the end it got better
but the beginning and the middle I was
feeling so overwhelmed that it was like
so stressful that I I would have been
okay with ending it
there although still wish we could have
done more but I would have been okay
with it just to calm my brain down it's
like so
much
stress but yeah we got a pretty long
stream out of that so that's
great yeah she's so sweet and she's
funny and she's interesting like she has
like this whole history and now she
lives close to me she even told me that
about her upcoming plans of coming to
Austria
and I think we can
meet I think we might just do a little
meet up H
possibly I got a
friend I got a
friend yay oh my God she's going to be
towering over me can you imagine I'll be
looking up like crazy like there no joke
she's no 170 no she's over 180
184 what that's so
tall my God walking next to uh her would
be
[Music]
fun neck pain
yeah for her too looking down too
much
damn
Tower over
me she's six I don't know how much it is
in feet but she's 184 cm she
said
yeah
big bigger than a bunch of you guys
too she she
she can intimidate you
guys taller than you damn just over six
feet wow
wow well you know some people some
people are
extraordinarily tall she's one of those
people yeah so I'm really happy happy
that we made this acquaintance like it
was planned since a long time ago like
last year December this came to my mind
I don't know why I didn't immediately
get to
it uh but I guess I didn't also feel a
rush cuz MOA was planning uh a
tournament since then all around that
time I think and I it it was just not
happening it took this long for it to
happen
but yeah because it wasn't happening I
also and and me being annoyed by
scheduling
AOE I also didn't really feel rush for
it I guess yeah so I'm going to get good
I want to get decent um I might just
become the best AOE vtuber I heard
there's maybe one more YouTuber who's
currently a bit better than me or so but
uh I will surpass whoever that is and
become the strongest AOE
vtuber oh and somebody even said I might
just um be not like the strongest uh
only but also the biggest
AOE YouTuber or
streamer definitely on YouTube the
biggest AOE
streamer road to 2000 L that sounds like
a
lot t hate the
throne decent is being is beating the
air on medum yeah like hard like you
guys need to understand I don't know how
easy it looks uh when you're just
watching and never played AOE but hard
AI is actually really difficult to you
saw me struggling on my own and even
with the coach so even with the coach
that you you must understand it's
difficult
[Music]
yeah
so again I'm not going to be
participating in uh any tournaments uh
from like whole life side at the moment
because I just don't uh want to
really make
myself
experience that
like toxicity again of the um you know
certain comments and I don't need to
experience that I want to just have fun
with the game so and oneon-one with some
whole life girls is fine like oneon-one
I think may not result in that cuz like
that's just more chill you know I would
say just a chill one-onone I don't mind
that if they want to um but gen
generally I just want to you know do my
thing mhm cuz I'm really having fun with
it
surprisingly yeah and I also like seeing
um you know view like RTS enjoyers in
the chat who normally aren't there um
just appreciating like somebody playing
AOE at
all seeing the words coll the Worlds
Collide and all
that happy to see that so
um maybe maybe I can make them regular
customers
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah especially if I collab
with Ellie more often and I can reach
also some people on
[Music]
[Laughter]
Twitch two birds with one stone even if
it's just a few you know have you
considered do stream like honestly if I
do stream AOE on
Twitch it might be the top AOE stream at
all times yo I checked it out and
there's quite a few a like it's a it's a
it's definitely not a dead
category there's many AOE streams people
seem to be there interested there's a
there's a community for
it but I would be the
biggest get the
twitchers
yeah you can sble cast with no problem
apparently I wonder what the what what
the reason is why twitch suddenly is
okay with
that have Coach you and elen elen ring
what why she doesn't play Elden ring
does
[Music]
she they got a new
CEO losing stream
yeah
what a
surprise people actually ended up I
actually know I legit mean like wow I'm
surprised they actually left cuz people
I thought people would just endlessly
complain but still not leave cuz there's
not a better
option I mean look at the absolute
disaster that kick is every time I hear
something about kick it's just
about stupid doing stupid
so don't don't don't know if that's
a good streaming
[Music]
Place
yeah kick kick yeah that's the only Ki
kick that we need to know about the only
kick yeah they have too many problematic
people there
mhm like today today even today I saw on
my Twitter timeline something I didn't
care about but it was was about
kick some kick stream that was making
negative
headlines the punch with The Bodyguard I
don't even know who all these people
were no idea don't care but somebody got
punched real hard and somehow made me
feel
like maybe they deserved
it I don't know what the backstory
is
yeah they did they did oh okay
okay H yeah there was no context
really no no no not the Japan guy no no
see that's the thing there there's many
of these stories from kick it seems like
it h yeah The Bodyguard one yeah yeah
that one Sor
today h
H you know I wish Twitter would still
show when like stuff shows up on your
timeline because someone liked it or
someone even retweets don't show up like
that anymore do they I wish it would
still show like that cuz then I would
know who the hell is the cause of this
showing up on my timeline so that I can
unfollow
them retweet still do okay but most of
the time I see like random stuff on my
timeline that I don't know why it's
there only if I click
[Music]
it I have to tell you which one's paid
to get
there I still see that though like it's
very it's very obvious which which
tweets are the paid
ones the
ads I don't know anyway so basically
just wanted to share my happiness about
the stream
yesterday I ended up like watching uh
the stream of the dude that she raided
much later um cuz I I just quickly it
was in the in the AOE stream
recommendations and then I saw and like
oh my God the game play of the pros holy
he was good right
that was insane like the match that I
saw he was like absolutely dominating
the whole map like he didn't just stay
in one area no like he went everywhere
and this is a cool thing that I already
saw before um from AOE players um maybe
eventually I'll pick up this strategy
too but like when people are um like
trying to get to you and you uh have no
real borders but you need to border
something up really quickly what you can
do is if you have a villager close by
doesn't even have to be close by I think
you just make them build a house or any
kind of building there and already when
the foundation is set when they haven't
even started building yeah quick Walling
it already counts as a wall and the
enemy will not be able to pass
through yeah just leave it unfinished I
mean you can finish it eventually if you
want it but The Unfinished buildings
just the ones that you just quickly
place count as walls all you need is the
resources and a a villager to you know
quickly wall it uh where you want
somebody has to be
ready
that's
yeah I like that but
um I I think I I I need to be way more
like aware wear and and also like yeah
able to
handle
everything easier before I can get to
that that's like next next next
level oh and I learned about a thing
that I didn't even didn't know about if
you have like a big big amount of gold
you can get spies and then you can see
the whole
map I don't know if that's really that
worth it cuz he was already seeing most
of the
map yeah these people play these games
for years and years yeah but then I
think about Ellie and it gives me hope
because uh she said she only started
with the pandemic and then even then
she's been mostly casting for a while
now so it's not that much time that she
put into the game after actually maybe
one or 2 years that she played
actively so maybe maybe it's not that
far away from me getting
[Music]
decent yeah she was most
casting these
days she played when she was younger I
don't think she said that's a long long
long long long time ago and who knows
how serious she really was back
then she said that it was
basically uh just no no knowledge when
she started again she said she didn't
play for on her own for a year yeah but
then she still remembers how to do
everything cuz she played you know
basically her own game with me like I
was just like chilling on the same map
but she still had it all in her the
quick micromanage and all that like
everything was going up like magic the
buildings were suddenly appearing I was
like whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa W all the
villagers are working what she's going
for war oh there's a castle oh there's
another Castle oh my
God yeah
so if she hasn't properly played for a
year but she started with
Corona
time she probably didn't actually have
that many years on her back so that's
impressive that's I thought you would
need like 10 years
now it all looks so natural and fast no
no I don't think it looks natural looks
like magic and and crazy like w
especially with the pro pro players
they're like whoos whoo whoo whoo whoo
you hear the Town Center
sound so many times
refreshing
refreshing there's so many here so much
going
on you can be cracked in a month or two
if you pick up things and understand
what you're doing you can definitely do
it let's go let's get cracked and let's
get
[Music]
ranked won't be funny if I can get
pretty decent I want to impress people I
want like people to come into my stream
and be like what the is she doing
like how's W this looks like she's
really good at this game wow okay kiaha
is actually like good at one game
wow are you're going to you're planning
to go rankon yeah I guess so yeah I know
I'll fail a lot uh in the beginning but
you have to fail to get ranked properly
in where you
belong there's a new AOE coming out next
year
e
[Music]
you didn't expect it would be AOE well
as I said like AOE motivates me in a
different way than other
[Music]
games so I want to I want to get
better I already felt like this when I
was playing
campaigns in my first AOE
streams
but
yeah I couldn't get across that hurdle
either I wonder if I would play a
campaigns
now if I can get over those difficulties
that I had
[Music]
before
the OG
[Music]
version why the definitive version is
fine is it
not I want to try the campaigns again
then so I'll try to uh get another AOE
stream in next week but I'm not sure I
like I have like next week is the
Minecraft
tournament um uh and some other things
going on like sponsored streams I have
two sponsored streams next week let's
go oh GTA too I think like we're all
kind of sick of GTA uh being played by
me right now aren't we like we could
live without it I
[Music]
think team meet up next week ah that
reminds me thank you for reminding me I
have to put this in
my in my schedule I think there
was uh
one
[Music]
thing uh first oh
okay do I have this in my
calendar
uh
first
[Music]
November ah okay I didn't okay 10 so
that's 2 2: p.m. I
think damn
okay wait no day
off what
it
uh
[Music]
well uh the currently it's looking like
two streams on Monday one in the early
morning and I want to do one in the
evening cuz I got to squeeze in some
horror games right and then
Tuesday I I got to get up early again to
do something some business but then
during the day waya collap Fatal
Frame then on Wednesday the first is the
Minecraft thing that I should be
joining uh Thursday I have a sponsorship
early in the morning and I know I was
going to sleep after that again so I
kept the rest of the day empty it's just
a short stream probably they they just
want one hour probably
but since it's that kind of game I'll
probably make it maybe like one and a
half or two hours at least it's short
but still no day off then Friday I was
going to continue Final Fantasy cuz like
maybe we can finish it
maybe uh
Saturday many many hours I will be busy
with the sports day and the Minecraft
sports
day and
then um Sunday I was going to do members
and another sponsorship members in
during the early day and sponsorship in
at 10
p.m. should I take Friday but then
there's like so much time before the
next Final Fantasy
stream I don't know I
guess like this there would be no day
off but in F first day I just have one
short stream and then the rest to the
day
off but I probably should yeah give
myself a bit more
[Music]
time just take it off just think
it okay I guess I'll keep it open for
now but no AOE
either
[Music]
damn what about
AOE
wow what if I add one more stream to
thur day in the
evening so it's not just the one stream
in the morning
[Music]
there will be double streams a
lot just want to play a little bit AOE
[Music]
maybe just one AE
stream I'll think about it you you can't
decide for
me and then I didn't book any flights
yet but
uh I'm probably going to go to Japan the
week after
that so getting difficult to finish
Final Fantasy you know that's my problem
I want to finish it
before but I'll I'll put one stream
[Music]
here I know maybe
here
[Music]
we'll see how far we get tomorrow I'll
try to get go really long
then ah yeah Tails DLC what's the
date again when it comes
out what's the
date I might just want to wait until I'm
back so that I can play it uninterrupted
you know don't worry I don't have like a
sponsorship to play it somehow they only
sponsor me always to like not play the
game even though it's a great game don't
know what they have to
hide they always only do these like
non-gaming sponsorships so I don't have
any obligations to play it right away
mhm they know I'll play it for
free well if it's about that then they
wouldn't have to sponsor me at all cuz
me playing the game game is
already advertisement
enough it's nice enough that they still
sponsor me so much even though it's
obvious that I'm going to play their
game they want a hype man yeah I'm their
hype
man oh yeah maybe they did sponsor me
for the first one
hour of gaming did
they maybe they
did but I obviously went
[Music]
longer oh yeah I need to ask for a
code
oh they're now in the game uh-huh
uhhuh
[Music]
interesting
m h talk I want to do whole talk but
there
just so much going
on so we'll see anyway that was enough
chitchat and use about whole life Island
calendar it's in the works
now it's uh in the
works did you hear back from the is no
so I have to give up on
that uh and actually
like like I've been trying to ask other
Hollow members to like do something with
me in for that for the stream uh instead
of basically that one song I was hoping
to do with the idol
but every like everybody I've been
asking so far is like schedule clashing
schedule clashing but each one takes
like one or two days to get the info so
I'm losing more and more time it's like
stressing me out cuz we still can't
finalize who's going to be in it and and
and we need like to decide also eat the
song and we need to make a Cho maybe
depending on the
song and yeah I need to sort everything
out and it's just not really possible
when I'm we're not finalizing this
stuff are there any non holos you can
ask um yeah look well I
tried um but it's it's difficult it's
easier within Holo for a lot of reasons
but now the more time passes the more
their schedules are already filling up
and
uh so they're turning me down so I go to
the next one but then they they're
also clashing schedule so it's just
getting more and more difficult the more
time
passes yeah yeah I've been bombarded
with
questions and I was trying to start
Super Chat
reading okay stop asking now stop asking
me
questions there are certain things I
would like to not talk about
because I shouldn't give too many
details don't make
me all
right H so super chat Super Chat the
reading time Super Chat the reading time
Super Chat reading Super Chat reading
Super Chat reading time Super Chat
reading Super Chat reading super reading
time ads Hyer what's up with
that the ads are like hard
to get like see where I can really close
them okay um
M where are we Final Fantasy I read I
guess fzero I probably read or did I but
maybe
not where did I
still I do have ad blocker I
[Music]
think are you sure it's only
the ah the one ah the one I have in my
head is the the other member stream
where I was like okay I read the the
previous one now I don't want to read
the current one okay that is just the
AOE okay okay oh
nice well
done that's not
much oh and today I
guess
okay here we go oh oh it's looking
colorful my my oh
my
can we get a
f there it
is
ell this is her with long hair but we
saw her with short hair looks good with
both I like her with short hair she the
impression changes a lot
though you like my thumbnail nice glad
you do glad you
do take7 soon soon
oh oh man I feel like I hear this a lot
recently
okay see you hopefully
[Music]
again makes me sad people
leave come back come back you sussy
Bas py danas and Trav G thanks for the
[Music]
pinkies hey wa who is it going had a
random idea crowding my brain I know the
game types I know the game typ is not
your usual cup of tea but if it were
possible to get lorder Rings Return to
Mario perms for members streams maybe
that could be a fun way to play for a
survival game with members Windows
version supports up to eight players at
a time could be interesting waddling
back in time M slow slow turtle still
thinking about if you could should watch
One Piece Film red I wasn't a conclusion
that it was too early for me cuz I
wouldn't understand what's going on the
music and animation made the movie for
me story was okay you may not know all
of Who's Who but honestly when when are
you going to be able to catch up
never I'd say feel free to watch it but
defer uh to Cal's opinion if you haven't
as she's your buddy and I'm just an owl
hope don't don't say just an
owl take
pride owls are
amazing wait how far behind are
you that's all that that topic was like
old old old
old are you watching like super old
vods catching up like from ages
ago or is it like you you didn't miss
all the streams since two year months
ago you just missed that one or so just
stuck in my head oh a Slowpoke Trev G
are you the the the secret Slowpoke is
it you slow Oak
slow
slow slow
slow oh I don't know I mean I don't
really have a a current urge to watch it
um I only had the urge I think maybe
when I was watching the Netflix show but
currently I don't have the urge so
there's no no hurry in watching that
movie I can watch I can wait for another
at least another Netflix season of One
Piece
maybe hopefully they're fast can do you
think they can make it within
please what do you think is it realistic
did they talk about
[Music]
it cuz like stuff like um House of the
Dragon they needed like two
years when they when their first season
was done they said in two years you get
the second season so that's really
sad but one
piece
a
[Music]
no what do we even get in
2024 ring of power I think should come
out in 2024 but nobody's happy about
that rings of power anything else in
2024 everything's coming out in
2025 cuz how of the dra uh ring
ring oh yeah how of the Dragon also
still needs time
right or or is it already time for
[Music]
it is expected around 2024 what House of
dragon or raise of
power it's going to be at the end of
which one house of dragon end of 2024
okay I'll take it I'll take it Wednesday
oh yeah maybe they'll make a new season
in uh in
2024 that could work they probably don't
need as much editing time as these
fantasy
shows and they definitely had the demand
for
it yeah bring it on please bring it
on mea movie I don't really care about
the mea
movie I enjoyed first season of that and
I don't remember maybe I also watched
second
season but didn't they eventually
replace all the girls with new girls
some stuff like that like
well let's see I don't really need
[Music]
that nice a
spinoff there's a second season oh what
was there all already an a movie
though I feel like I consumed quite a
bit of me
[Music]
maybe I watched season 1 and the
movie I might that might have
happened yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah I might want to watch it
frein yes I might want to watch
that I'm
interested but I I I was thinking about
watching it when I'm in Japan because I
noticed when I was in Japan
uh my Disney plus had fre
episodes now that I'm here it doesn't so
I'll just go back to Japan so that way I
can watch it
legally don't have to bother myself with
how how do I get
it I'm going soon so I'll be binge
watching F
hopefully the season will be complete
while I'm
there m
that's not
piracy my when my PE changes my my
Disney plus Netflix they have different
shows it won't okay well that's fine
whatever anyway thank you try here's a
kiss for you cuz that was a pretty big
one together a big sandwich thank you so
much I hope one piece Netflix season
comes sooner rather than later but for
now I'm I'm fine and uh Lord of the
Rings we'll see about that I think I
requested perms ages ago but back then
it was just declined cuz the release
date was too far off or something like
that GD thank you for the red super chat
and the pinky good day Ki it's my
birthday today is that why you were
impatient about the Super Chat
reading
sorry you wanted me to read this
[Music]
probably happy
birthday I don't see you where are you
did you go to sleep no you're still
there you got a headache I'm sorry
that's also cuz of me
probably Jokes Aside it's been a
wonderful nearly 3 years of you and kfp
been spoiling us with great content on
and off YouTube love your humor singing
and dancing and most of all your
kindness and
empathy you're the best my
CI I still am yeah you're trying to stay
awake because of me I'm I'm a fault for
everything all your sufferings jokes I
wait I read hope you can grant my reest
of a birthday song Kia of course of
course my Australian mate um don't
expect too
[Music]
much you have to stop suffering for me I
feel
[Music]
bad what do we sing about how do I how
what what what can I sing about
Australia kangaroos
koalas
veite
oh okay okay I'll I'll actually I'll put
a little bit of effort into
this
m e
[Music]
uh
um
[Music]
e H
genius it's actually Genius of me while
scho and one more verse there's two
verses or three
verses hopefully just
two
I'm lacking critical
information cooking scorpion no I would
never I would never do you have
[Music]
some GD who g g
g
g what's what's your what's your
preferred
pronouns Alie even asked me that
yesterday I was like nobody ever asked
me this ever
before I'm I'm I'm keeping I'm keeping
you up all night I'm sorry she's okay
[Music]
okay
well
[Music]
how many verses is it really let me
check
[Music]
free honestly from now on we should cut
it there cuz it's always such an awkward
ending isn't
it I just cut it after after the that
course is there cuz otherwise it's like
what the
[Music]
hell okay okay listen listen listen to
this
happy
birthday happy
birthday to
you happy birthday to you happy birthday
in your
shoe happy birthday in your skirt too
happy birthday to
you to my sweet mate
G I wish you a happy birthday
maybe get a
cakey with veg and my tea happy birthday
to you happy birthday happy birthday in
your
shoe and this night you're staying up
late too happy birthday now go to bed
Sho
shoo since almost 3 years
ago you are stuck on my big toe
spending time with the waa show oh I
love you so well happy birthday to you I
nailed it happy birthday in your shoe
happy birthday in your skirts too happy
birthday to
you that was amazing wasn't that amazing
oh my God that was amazing I rhymed
everything oh I wish I could do that
naturally I forced the words to rhyme GD
biry cakey veite
te did you like it did you like it TD
you can go to sleep now I'm just sorry
matey
t l o e
T just like a rapper did g say something
I don't see G maybe maybe you're crying
from
happiness I didn't a you're writing a
Super
Chat yay yay please go go Sho to bed
Sho thank you so much also one more
K you're you're always there even though
it must be so painful I'm so sorry sorry
thank you for suffering for me
always you're the
best hope the headache goes away thank
you for all the support stay the way you
are cuz you're beautiful and amazing the
way you are I wouldn't want you to be
any
different
[Music]
oopsie
congratulations okay okay okay
awesome than for Pinky hope your
coaching goes well T sad I'll have to
miss most of it due to work no looking
forward to the VOD maybe I'll see you on
the ladder soon enough oh well sounds
like you you play the game too I didn't
even know about this word like being on
the ladder until
yesterday do you play this
game
Nathan are you
here tell me is chat dead Chat is dead
are just looking for Nathan everybody's
staying quiet so that I can see Nathan
if he's here seems like he's
not no he's not
here he's just chilling you're alive I
see you I see you you're chilling I'm at
work that's okay I was looking for
Nathan anybody here called by the name
Nathan no no okay then tell me next time
are you playing the game what's your
rank what's your
ELO I am
curious uh but yeah maybe you'll see me
on the ladder soon maybe you will be
careful watch out for me I'll be
climbing up those ladders
not that it
matters also my
bladders falling apart um I meeting soon
rhyming
wow
bars forcing the
Rhymes no not at all take for7 now
thanks for the pinky I got my freee
badge on my main today
oh oh
[Music]
wait wait Jacob 47
alt for me you've always been Jacob 47
alt I don't even remember your name
without the alt but I guess the alt is
for alternative and you have a main
account there's a
main but you members on both what
it's B what
it's weird sometimes people report to me
like I'm bad and then I can't find it
though like in my let me see if I can
find something that's called Jacob is it
Jacob 47 without the alt is that
it where do you find this
again you see their main on R's channel
oh okay wait uh where is it maybe here
ah might be here no no that's maybe
here since Skyward
Sword okay
uh I
normally don't go here maybe it's been
like banned by accident at some point
but took you long enough to tell
me
no no
[Music]
no no no wait there's so many I have
like a lot of like spam Bots and
banned cuz there were were times when
there's a lot of spam going
on um
jacob jacob jacob jaob jacob jaob jaob
jaob jacob jacob
Jacob adult dating s jacob jacob jacob
Jacob Tinder
hot jacob jacob jacob
[Music]
jaob jaob jacob Jacob naked
HD jacob jacob jacob Jacob
jacob jacob
Jacob sexy
chat jacob jacob jacob Jacob best camps
hot girls and boys
J jle jigle
jle Tinder again Tinder Tinder Jacob
Jacob jaob jaob
jaob jaob jaob
[Music]
ja naked HD yeah yeah I saw you before
Oh my God they made so many accounts
with the same
name jacob jaob
jaob jacob jacob jacob
[Music]
Jacob funny sight
everywhere they all have the same names
ah here's a new one
xxx18 jacob jacob jacob Jacob
ja tinder's life no you weren't in there
you weren't in the list
that's unfortunate I'm sorry I don't
have you in this weird list
of hidden users is there never list for
band I don't see anything else
here I just see another list for like
band words
[Music]
but a search function
oh
no I don't know if it's like let me try
to search okay no no no Jacob no
Jacob it finds other words that I'm
seeing but it doesn't find
[Music]
Jacob but yeah I've had this before
so
this i' I've heard about this issue
before but I mean I know you I know you
was Jacob 47 Old so
if you would change now I would be like
who is
this but you know you can always cancel
your membership on the other one but but
you seem to be fine with having two
memberships so thank you for the
support sorry I couldn't find you you're
welcome you're welcome damn YouTube is
so weird about this kind of
stuff
oh yeah can you try
now can you try again like now maybe you
haven't tried for a while and suddenly
it's
working
but yeah Skyward Sword is a long time
[Music]
ago D no Dan to you thank you thank you
if you want to try you can try again but
I'm guessing you already tried every
once in a
[Music]
while you have to issue sometimes too
with the commenting in chat I even
honestly even with whole life members
sometimes I go into chats from All Live
members and I don't I just don't see my
comments showing up in their chat oh I
even I get that so weird I type normal
things like not even with like like
messages or like words that should be
banned really normal things I thought
like it shouldn't happen to
me it's
weird but one way I always know if a
message went through or not is if
everybody's spamming oh
kah blah blah 1 million
people
saying
[Music]
you has e my M Super Chat like four
months in a row
what they should like be like I think
like with a like with a super chat when
you type something in that you're not
supposed to be typing it just won't let
you send to Super Chat they should do
the same with membership messages
[Music]
then
weird oh
anyway thank you for three years of
support on two accounts basically almost
3, era Dan Edward V Dan J SW thank you
for the red this is so fun ell is really
reassuring that's great no Panic Jo only
tactician CH today go go go thank you
yeah she was great great coach um you
know there's there's not much Choice
when it comes to female AOE streamers
who good good enough to coach but the
one I found was possibly the best one I
could ever ask for no I Love Her I Love
Her She's Mine she belongs to me now I
adopt
her and she adopt
me we we are a pair now we come in pairs
okay no apples just
[Music]
pears blamed her yoink mine mine mine M
mine m m mine mine m
m yes more I agree I'm glad you guys
also want to see more even though I know
a lot of you guys don't even understand
the game really but see you're on a
journey with me pay attention and then
you will understand the game just as
much as I will you know just have to pay
attention cuz I'm also so learning we
are still in a phase where it's still
pretty easy to perceive what's going on
on the screen cuz I'm not that
fast I don't think it's
that difficult to understand what's
going
on but I hope you guys are enjoying it
even if it's a bit like what the
you re it let's
go yay it's fun to get into it again if
you having problems with hard AI then
watch my streams I guess or get a coach
yourself but not Ellie She's mine so
thank you J
MBG thank you sh definitely there was
Panic though Panic show was very much
there no matter what I am a
te m I don't want to do the beep cuz you
guys said it's really
loud beep than I saw you also in in her
chat your name your name was uh written
interestingly should I pick a new name
no but this is your identity maybe I
should just read it but
um you can't just change your name to
something that doesn't sound
like these words put together
who can't do
that didn't you already say you introd
no I said if they want to be coached you
know I can introduce
them why not I
did g
din wait what was it before I'm so used
to gir now gir didn't
I love the name
g g g g so
[Music]
funny it's fun it bounces it's
bouncing
G
exactly
exactly was it like basically the same
but just written
differently it's Welsh
[Music]
wow
fancy ah I think I saw you too in the
chat my name was my real for a long time
oh
dangerous you had a different name
during my debut Chang when I open
monetization oh so if I would watch the
Debbie stream I wouldn't recognize your
name
huh yeah you live dangerously especially
Nathan cotton cuz like definitely cotton
is his real last name right is it maybe
it
[Music]
is
wait I already read that right so I am a
t d 3,000 ER D 3,000 ER D dun a castle
destroyed over % completion is known as
a do
Castle what a castle destroyed at over
90% completion so not completely
complete this Don as a do Castle okay
okay okay but adding to my P super chat
if you lose a castle with over 95%
construction you get an achievement
called castle of
[Music]
Doubt
okay wait doubt and doubt d a u
t versus d o u
BT is a play as often Den his castle
what they made like a like a
Easter egg for a
player
funny but then why did they add another
achievement at 95% with actually written
as the d o u
BT oh you know
him why do you guys know
him for optimistic Castle drops I get
tonight hey that's funny I want to look
that up is there like video of
dad doubt Castle
compilation
oh funny I will watch this later it's a
thing it's a thing it's an AOE meme it's
an AOE Community meme wow I'm getting
deeper and deeper into this I love
it more more
knowledge thank you for this knowledge I
like it skyim Tracy D and looking for
the to Dan thank
you hell yeah hell
yeah let's read today's super
[Music]
chatsy
Coy you know I was really trying to hold
back yesterday to use all my like
weird Japanese words that I say like
naturally now like y
and and and you know words like
that I was trying to control myself cuz
I know she she really doesn't speak any
Japanese she wouldn't understand
it I did still use yab sometimes cuz I
just could
not it was a really yab
situation yeah but at least she watches
Anway I was really happy to hear that
because uh I thought she had absolutely
no interest in that kind of part of our
culture um but it's it's reassuring that
there is interest on her side because
then she could be understanding all
these memes and and you know V tubing in
general
easier she's very open-minded yeah our I
don't watch anime excuse
me excuse me I I say our because cuz
like I literally am anime right
now
so you
know and take 47 now D endless D for the
red super chat new zand let's go love
the aoe2 stream it was great watching
you move from choosing to play defensive
at the start to being more and more
aggressive as you became confident I'm
impressed that you found such a
compatible coach Sho thank you I thought
defensive would be easier but yeah it
turns out that you you as long as you
don't back down and you show confidence
then playing aggressive is easier
against the hard AI at
least probably probably could be quite
the
general
tip
[Music]
no Bots get aggress bots aggressive is
way easier against B B yeah yeah yeah
yeah that's what I mean yeah
and so I guess I got to become more
aggressive but it's good practice I
guess for you know the future and ranked
matches got to be
aggressive that's that's one thing that
like scares me a a bit still I feel like
I really need confidence for this
game
and yeah
[Music]
it's hard to know like when's the right
timing to really start
striking
and
yeah I feel a bit intimidated by playing
against real people a bit I mean a
[Music]
lot only a tiny fraction of oh yeah I
saw I saw in the video of I keep on
forgetting the channel name something
with
s Spirit of the law was it
that in his video uh about
online
matches uh he showed like how many
people play AOE in general and then
versus how many people play in rank
matches it's not many actually it's
really small
portion
[Music]
yeah that's time to
grind most of us just like chill against
AI it's true it's just it just I also
just don't I'm like concerned about
like embarrassing myself like to like in
my first matches they'll they'll
probably be like what the she's so
weak what's with this PE
person but yeah I have to get over
that shy shy wahah but yeah I found a
great coach I agree thank you
endless I'm glad that you're like really
enjoying this AOE chapter of My Life RV
last than SP time D for the red chat you
know what tastes great with Spam
pineapple where did that spam come from
wait what
what first of all I don't know about
spam it just doesn't look very
appetizing why why did you mention spam
well where did that come from are you
just advertising
pineapple it's just r a
[Music]
sausage it tastes better than it
looks most of the
time I like to eat things that don't
that
don't uh get preserved in
tin
hands
no but I know spam is quite beloved so
it must
be
tolerable must be decent
enough I guess what about your tuna
pizza that's different caned tuna is
different that's that's one of the
exceptions how many times have you tried
it
never I I don't know spam is not really
a thing people commonly eat here it's
like not common I can probably find it
but I don't think any of my friends eat
Spam either like nobody says Okay I want
to eat Spam nobody thinks about spam
nobody wants to
spam it's just not not a popular food
item in
Austria we have better food than we
haveb we have okay visually
similar but better by
far
yeah so is do yeah yeah that's a fact
mhm yeah we have good sausages too
that's true yeah we got we got our own
good meat stuff going on we don't need
spam yeah
yeah nearly similar yeah like visually
yeah but it's not out of a freaking Tin
Can anyway
D anony web oh wait spank did I give you
a kiss M Anthony thanks for the pinky K
have you ever seen kindergarten crop
there's a scene where he's telling the
kids to shut up that you reminded me of
AR know shga is also from a I know thank
you he's acting in that show haven't
seen it
before
no VI sausage is coming can though uh no
like maybe you can get some but normally
here you buy them uh from the like
fridge section and they're like in
plastic wrapping excuse me like we don't
sell wiener sausages and cans ew do you
hear the disgust m in my
voice um oh my
God in the US they come in cans but you
guys in the US have things in the
weirdest containers like
ew
it's not very
appetizing so
unfresh everything that's in cans is
like made to be stored for 500 years I
don't want to eat something like
that toan cake in a candle yo I'm going
try that right and she told me it wasn't
particularly good or was that was that
in a candle or in a glass maybe no it
wasn't a glass that one wasn't a glass
she said it
[Music]
was
not so
[Music]
fetch you guys know I'm roasting you
right like I can imagine the canned
sausages will be fine but we don't
that's not how we go about selling our
sausages in Germany and
Austria
no this actually surprising these
differences
I like this kind of cultural differences
will there be care followers next week
yes I must do it I don't know when but I
must do it because I already have the
finished
menu of uh nine
new uh chickens in
costumes and free frames even though I
only asked for
one
Duma made
[Music]
free when will you find the time for
that maybe I'll just like uh open the
thing but then I'll sign them later I'll
I'll open it for like Monday or Tuesday
stream and then I'll sign them another
time when I find
time anyway that's that uh interesting
interesting interesting Revelations that
we are having morally
imoral
[Music]
uh a rice of
free okay rice of free f with the pinky
switch on PS5 close curtain start
streaming kiaa stay at home gamer mode
activated
yes it's so comfy stay at home is comfy
why would I want to be anywhere else
right thank you R over thank you thank
you thank you so much for the uh
beautiful pink Super Chat thank
[Music]
sh
gim
Tracy
M
mother thank you m
d oh a letter to be only to be told it's
from s's daughter oh really well that
did not have a Plus on it so I didn't do
that one Cy thanks for the pinky hey Kaa
it was my birthday yesterday a and I
decided to use some of my birthday money
to give you this long overdue Super Chat
no
no but treat yourself coted my
art um thank you for helping me through
bad times and inspiring me to do my best
every day love you forever as a
fan I love you too as a Entertainer or
something like
that thank you and happy birthday to
you thank you for being part of kfb I'm
happy that I can help you for all kinds
of times I I wish I could help more I
feel like
um I I don't know I need to do better
but I'm glad I can be of help some
way thank for your lovely support I hope
you keep on staying in kfp no pressure
on super chats but thank you for your
first one or is it your first one says
long over would
you is
it if yes thank you I am honored first
one woo than
soon now I hope you made yesterday to be
the most enjoyable day for
you and hope to see you on your next
birthday as well next year maybe
hopefully thank you sh for your
sweetness I'll give you a a free kiss
M okay let me finish
thison I was not referencing anything
there but apparently you felt like I was
[Music]
Dusty
P than soon
black boo
7 black I am a CH thanks that's just
your new name now I am a
chib I am a
chiib I am a I am a
chap CH
beep D soon golden soon you never needed
Redemption just keep being yourself I'm
glad you share your case of us whether
we agree or not don't be discouraged oh
thank you that's nice I I I would like
to think that you guys are only like
roasting me but sometimes it really
feels like you know maybe
really respect me a little bit less for
my some of my
interests not true right not
true
right right not
true okay
good thank
God what about cats
though I'm also like I told you again
and
again that it's not like I love cats the
movie I just thought it was
fine but okay let's not get into that
let's not
[Music]
that Alex
D
avatar
SC no not
really Wiki tun D I don't know if I
really
perceived that but that's cool M at dun
but the classic is the OG I love the OG
you know space
[Music]
wild thank you g d naan C down oh pinky
oh there you are Nathan what was my
question to
you what was I asking
you
I don't even remember the AOE yeah do
you play
AOE you here
[Music]
now cuz you were talking as if you you
do you
do are
you how much better than me are you are
you a
legend could you beat
Ellie
in
[Music]
Fury he's working and
peeking well I just caught
him oh 1.2 okay I still can't really
judge how good that actually
is that sounds good do you start from
zero I guess and how much like
how how it's above average
wa definitely not in a fist by she's
R
oh Ellie around 1,900
really oh damn damn ell cracked
[Music]
them W that sounds like wow you could
coach me too
Nathan well then I'll I'll be keeping an
eye out in future AOE streams to see if
you're commenting something that seems
to be the way to go you seem to know
what you're talking
about she can carry you figuratively and
literally
yeah she's really like oh 1,900 1 ver 1
2,600 oh is that like different ratings
depending
on
that what not a
hotel interesting interesting
interesting
interesting yeah yeah yeah Olympic coach
almost thank
you Tassimo thank you for the pinky
thank you for the awesome stream today K
thanks to the weekend I can finally
watch the entire stream live and I have
some holidays in next week so looking
forward to the upcoming streams thank
you that sounds sweet you
[Music]
you
you don't normally show up in my super
chat so thank you where did you come
from huh
you I was always
get interested when I see people who are
normally not in
[Music]
here but I guess it's because you can't
catch my streams live normally oh and
you're kind of new oh you yeah you're a
little chick you're a little chicklet
cute still growing becoming bigger and
bigger thank you for the support happy
to see more new people and also European
um fans that's great to see
than and refreshing for a moment I'm
after at the pinky thank you seems like
you're starting to feel that slow part
of the game yeah but tomorrow will be a
uh exciting as for guests in your life
if your trip overlaps of ena's M can
finally get e and and go to the meeting
already meeting oh idle meeting so if
Ena I talked with her about it it seems
like our trips don't
overlap she leaves too early
sadly yeah I don't think I will be there
that
early I don't need to be there that
early and I'll just be you know I don't
want to be there that early like
unnecessarily early it's unfortunate
yeah also me and Ena like I I hit her up
a while ago uh asking if she wants to do
the kind of stream that I did with that
we did with uh Council before designing
their uh casual clothes if she wants to
do the same thing for Advent and she's
like up for it but you know she's it's
been really hard to find time
time so it it's been delayed until we
both have time
again which will
be at the end of all of these Japan
trips afterwards
yeah yeah but I do want to do it again
and she's up for
it definitely want to do it before
Advent gets like their own casual
outfits but I feel like there there's
plenty of time until that
happens so yeah it will happen hopefully
within this year I'll try to get it
happen within this
[Music]
year so
uh that's
that okay
then hoping to see that happened me
[Music]
too
mhm so yeah see you tomorrow for more
Final Fantasy and J in oh one year
membership congratulations thank
you yeah reminded ah ret thank oh thank
you thank you
thank
okay it's just a small small thing
uh where was
it here okay thank you I literally
forgot I really forgot
[Music]
Tas okay byebye does in
byebye
[Music]
yeah
there she
is one second after I typed
that oh
did you hear it probably not oh man I
wish it was picked
[Music]
up that's just
me he's a
baby she watches the
dream
cute