[Music]
hello I can't believe it's day 15
already technically uh we were supposed
to have another session but there was
enough peeps I can't believe we already
had a day second the the the second wave
what anyway I'll be spawning
soon okay sorry I I just got
out let let me hit the spawn and then we
will begin
shortly with day 15 apparently I have
also failed a quest apparently oh I'm
guess see someone tried it I have no
idea oh oops okay hold up oh that's what
I had to do okay now I can do it yeah
woo and
now hello oh people coming in
you are the farmer you if you have some
time today can you try to plant our
super corn yeah yeah I would love to
plant some super crops super super corns
okay um if you uh the the super corn
seeds are in the new house next to the
fireplace in the food and Medicine Chest
um there is free uh ears of super corn
don't take don't just take the Super
corn seeds there's five of them and if
we need more with more grown ears of
super corn I can produce more seeds
because I have some but for now it's
just five seeds the question is will the
farm be at the new place now nothing
cool in here um anywhere is fine I got I
got some magazines though okay cuz uh o
nice oh blade crafting I need that knif
gun I have heard that the second wave
has already been finished yeah we did it
I I
see we're
so we survived the second
wave uh are we still going to be using
this house for another wave or are we
doing a different house now well we
might use this house because it's it's
well reinforced right yeah it's very
well reinforced okay so the new house
alling what what's good still all right
make the most of it let me just check on
the other crops for now are those lions
or Tigers what are those big cats
mountain lions big cats big cat I a big
cat means big
trouble oh big cat hurts oh that was a
bad idea
[Music]
MH are you guys questing right now or
are you doing stuff at a new location
uh um bble has like a treasure chest and
we want to go there yeah I have a
treasure map that I'm looking
for um where did you guys go I left but
I'm waiting for you somewhere close by
okay well I'm going to go to the other
home so I'll stick in a a different VC
I'll see you guys
later I'm right next to
you all right I I'm going to vc2 cuz I
have no idea what happening so I guess
we got to figure out things now the farm
oh oh they have the DU collector in the
old uh old place though it's so
laggy all right uh now the question is
so from my my
gathering we are now going to work on
the new house to take care
of yeah I assume we're going to have to
prep the new house I I am actually a
little surprised that the spikes held up
and I also find it a little hilarious
that we weren't even around for this
yeah I guess we got to do that all right
I'm going to leave the crops behind the
reason being that they're not even done
they're not even grown yet actually
which is a little
surprising yeah I'm going to go fill it
with spikes and dig more Moes I
guess I'm just going to help them
prepare for the third wave I'll be busy
with things tomorrow since you have
the uh I almost had the intervention we
have the convention is tomorrow so I'll
be busy with
that I told you I told you guys you were
carrying not in terms of combat in fact
I'm pretty sure there's uh why am I
weak uh durability okay can I
repair I am unable to what what do I
need for it didn't exactly tell me what
I need to to get I mean I could just
make new one
really I assume I just eat
grass yeah I'm just going to help them
with the third wave I think the third
wave is at the rate we're going uh I
suppose tomorrow I made a good base I
know I'm a home builder not a home
wrecker it's it's interesting because I
don't think the spikes are always that
powerful I'm pretty sure they used to be
a lot weaker so I I don't know I don't
know what happened
uh am I like anywhere close fauna's
nearby I was looking at the builds that
uh I could potentially do I'm not
entirely sure how many more days I'll
play with this uh at least this is my
confirmed one but next week I'm going to
be going back to Resident
Evil I got the
buff yeah I think they did get buffed
they were a lot weaker before um the
death penalty I think that's always been
there not that I I don't I don't really
remember too
much with the Faun okay but I didn't do
anything she placed her bed next to
mine oh
man yeah yeah I I plan on doing Paper
Mario but I'll have to wait I also got a
Silent Hill Silent Hill game so what I'm
going to try to do is I'll try to finish
up
re4 uh next week like Monday and Tuesday
and the world of horror I'm thinking I
think it'll be
Wednesday uh I was initially planning on
going somewhere this month but uh I've
canceled it so I'll just be
staying little unfortunate but but I'll
try to do it some other year I
suppose yeah I wanted to see like a
bunch of
places yeah uh I am uh getting some help
with unity chat GPT could not well it
had the base form for something that was
to makes shift and I needed it
immediately it's pretty good but uh I
need uh someone to code something for me
so I'm working on that and in the future
it'll probably be like an enhanced
script so here's hoping I I have to
admit I'm a little overwhelm what the
amount of stuff there is to to
do yeah maybe next year and hello
everyone hope you're
well oh yeah yeah I need to collect
something from her it was really sweet
of her but uh there is a gacha for like
Fire Emblem rings and actually I wanted
to buy with one so she she basically
tried to clear it out so in her purse
that is what is meant to be given she's
about to give me a ring
guys whenever we meet up
again the gacha gift yeah I I hope that
she remembers to bring it though
otherwise there is a place that I wanted
to go to I think it's in akih
Haba it's a little funny but like uh one
of the the staff actually staff is
pretty aware of how thirsty I am guys
they they're aware cuz I think they're
like gossiping like why does why does
she always talk about like the Mei who
who is the Mei and then like uh the
director was like oh that's just uh her
hwando it's like oh okay and they just
accepted it pretty well you know it's
like oh okay
it's like I
see uh this is not the place I wanted to
go to but it is on the way I wonder if
it's worth looting they probably have
been here before but then again there's
also the risk of death so we should
probably not uh tempt fate but anyway
one of the staff aware of my my
obsession honestly obsessions kind of
make life a lot more interesting
assuming assuming it is not at the the
injury and the harm of
another so it's fictional so it's okay
but they're like hey look at this in
akih Haba and I was like oh [\h__\h] I need
to go there and then I was like I where
is it I I need it and they're like oh
you know if you want like I can I can
just like get it in the next ship it's
like oh [\h__\h] yeah well should I get you
like oh [\h__\h] I need to get some a steam
gift too I was like ah I'll I'll pay you
back don't know when the [\h__\h] I'll pick
it up honestly see or when it'll get
delivered but like I I'll pay you back
and then do you want like a steam gift
like nah I want [\h__\h] Legend s it's
like I got you fam so whenever the
exchange the transaction the business
deal whenever that has been made I will
work on
that speaking of I have some uh friend's
birthday so I better gift them
something funny enough I could probably
do it now since it's just us it's just
you it's just see me and Novi oh by the
way and teeker herself yeah the new the
new Legend of
Zelda I will make the transaction
assuming assuming they don't buy it I'm
freaking hungry bull
crap you guys don't even have wood for
this so you have a broken
door do I even have food a tuna I'll eat
it I do a recipe with it no we can't
cook I have any cooking skills
I don't think there's any cooking skills
I think I actually have to learn it at
least there's no chances for
denter by way it's like it's really
silent in here I think we should have
some bgm in my head in my
opinion hold up let me let me get some
bgm in my head what you guys in a mood
for a Zelda one I don't know when I plan
on playing it I'm not really a big Zelda
fan to be honest I do want to play s
Hill but right now we got some games uh
Wukong I'll consider that when I feel
like it uh Paper Mario I definitely want
to though something funky Jazz okay oh
well I hear music now I'll stick with it
for now but but maybe when it's really
silent I will uh we'll just straight up
play jazz you like
jazz yeah I know some you guys are going
to be like ooh maybe you have a thing
for James Sunderland huh Shori he's
blonde okay but guys guys he's uh he's
already a complicated man and kind of
married sort of
so oh also no I don't really I'll be
honest I'm not really into the pillow
talk with James
Thunder oh is that my
stomach you guys will Pro some of you
will probably not understand that
reference but for those who do let's
just say I'm not into that pillow talk
I can still convince you guys come
on hold up I think she's
here well well hello there farmer maybe
maybe when we do quests we'll get a lot
of food hi look at you my little farmer
fa hi everyone Welcome to our home our
very
comfy you've got bacon and eggs
oh thank
God oh you guys ever searched a
toilet oh
reseta oh they respawn I see okay yeah
all these cars are um unsearched again
all right uh this is a new base for
protecting right so we should put spikes
here I think we're still going to
protect the old one keep the old one as
the base for the next raid until it's
compl run
over okay the farm is still at the old
base as well um it has not grown despite
it being a week later in the
server oh actually well sh while you're
here maybe maybe you could throw the
super cor next to this house yeah I need
to get um I need to get Rotting Flesh
nitrate powder and clay soil so running
flash is also in there and maybe stuff
yeah maybe okay I I'll work on it then
awesome thank you so much no
problem oh you got a spear stuff I'll
take
that take what you want it's
[Music]
fine but I think we really got to go
questing soon to get like to find food
and stuff oh it's night time so we can
wait for the night accept
a quest while I was out there there is a
quest it might be mine yes is my name TI
your one clear I feel like we could we
could do that oh can you guys invite me
to the party so I may much the
XP thank you I'll work on the farm in
the
meantime okay thank
you oh you are in the party I think I am
I don't think so I think I'm the party
oh thank you
you confus okay all right I'll set up
the farm here since like I'm already
here okay nice thank you no problem
hopefully this grows within the next
week apparently it needs
water oh watering it uh I have not been
watering it I don't have a watering
can oh that's also something you need oh
oh no yeah I thought I was hoping the
rain would be enough you know Mother
Nature at its finest seven days to
grow how can the rain why why doesn't
the rain water our plants cuz it's
Arizona the rain is
over
Twilight if only this was the Pacific
Northwest if only there was
vampires who could protect us I
know I was talking about this with Nissa
yesterday um about Twilight in Arizona
do you think that Bella's first time
seeing grass is when she went when she
moved to
Forks do they not have any grass in
Arizona they got weed don't they I don't
believe it there's some grass right if
they do I don't believe it
maybe fake
grass oh like artificial ones she took a
little Cactus with
her so
Random it's
plan for one stone Arizona plant I have
stone I will come and give the stone
after I hit the street
[Music]
Timber all right here's hoping that the
grow uh the corn grows but super speed
pray for the super corn and put it in
the chest put it to the side of the
house I heard that super corn is not a
food but rather a fuel no no no no most
of the high-end food is made with super
corn oh is it like super corn meal uh no
like several Foods also just grilled
super corn is fine too I guess but yeah
I don't know they they listed me a
couple things in chat before that you
can make hold up I accidentally grab
regular corn your cooking might not be
good enough yet but yeah it it will be
good enough at some point no no your
cooking's great though I appreciate your
cooking these bacon and eggs are
delicious yeah better than
charred thank you I've been working
[Music]
hard all right you guys want to
prioritize super corn right what about
like Yuka and hop whatever that is yes
Yuka I heard is good too I forgot for
what but okay I'll take like two yucas
then
mhm all right seven days to grow let's
go s days to grow Corin yep yeah once I
can make armor I'm going to make you an
a farmer outfit there's a oh thank you
for Farmer buff
ohaw I like how the farm plots kind of
it's hovering
well it
works pip pip p pipe piper pepper
pickles oh we got one more
slot pip I bet we can do the quest even
though it's night time it's going to be
a little dangerous though I think we're
strong no we will do it strong enough
good luck you guys I'mma stay here and
farm like a houseway just spawned right
in front of me I wasn't ready ready for
it oh yeah get him you're so good at
fting it's like the shown in anime
fastest way to grow these so much
stronger how much did I experimental
method I've been is like you actually
have to water these perhaps I'm just
talking to you guys right now I'm going
where you girls are uh let's see I can
probably get more nitr okay I don't
think I'm anywhere near the quest you
look okay thank you you shouldn't have
to water anymore okay what if I die on
the thing
oops is there more are cook let me turn
this off it's a waste of fuel I would
like a little bite to
eat oh I should eat too
actually uh let me get hungry and
thirsty but what don't worry I can eat
this egg in this
economy I'm fing these raw eggs do we
have any
water uh there is the DU colle there
you're right as long as you R Us we can
just drink from the the sea that's
wonderful oh can you actually drink from
the
river yeah with her hat if you put it on
oh oh can you make more hats like that
then no I found a special part that lets
me do it I see I
see because of that hat is actual the
real reason why I'm sticking with you
what what about wife just kidding oh it
was only for the Hat yeah sorry it's all
about you know materialism and then
using people for you
know my
advantage it's not true it's not true
it's not true fun I can't believe this
after
everything what a
zombie die potato seeds oh
nice all right the farm shall
expand okay should we yeah go to the
quest Point yeah yeah
yeah maybe we'll find food on the way
hopefully zombies zombies
yipp
exp
yummy I made it to level 10
oh
nice oh you're so powerful okay okay I'm
going to Club it in the head
die wait I think you're lower level than
me now aren't you don't worry I can
still protect you
[Music]
die all right I'm going help I'll hop to
a different VC since I'll be focusing on
this stuff I'll see you guys in a bit
[Music]
okay all right I it is now silent in my
head uh how do I Al have safely
there you
go I can't think
sometimes uh let's just do more gloves I
don't really want to make the crafting
kit right
now there you go we'll just wear
it
wear um my primitive shoes my
caveman primitive
items the voices are getting loud
uh is there I could scrap it it's
probably for the
best I wonder if it's worth like
learning how to scrap better something
there you go there's
probably a way to get better armor I
assume I have to learn it
though how about more Farm plots what do
I need Place soil okay so I should have
a lot of clay soil at the base
perhaps it's kind of
oops they should get the living of the
land you can get more yield uh do I even
have points right now I don't think
so you can't re what do you call it resp
right I can't do the workstation I think
someone else has to do that I have very
limited points I'm going with spear
expert or spear Master just to stay
safe I might go for archery it's just
like what I find fun honestly and then I
guess like living off the land would
probably be good along with any mining
related
things yeah I think waa or Kiwa and R
are probably working towards it okay so
let's see what else can we grow pumpkin
I assume could be useful and we can have
regular corn seed I think uh Golden Rod
you can make tea with that but the issue
is really the water part so maybe Golden
Rod I shouldn't bother it is there clay
here
clay clay clay clay clay here I don't
think
so I might have taken all the clay at
this point they're also very poorly
organized
honestly H my issue is really getting
water we got the
flesh let's put this back I think right
now I think uh food sustainability is
the more important
and I suppose that's
it and then regarding XP do I have to be
in vidity just to to mooch off
curiosity okay so we got whatever
pumpkins oh you got to be close oh man
darn it this what happens when you focus
on the home
front all right uh we have of I think
just two more or is just three more I I
think three more man darn it that ain't
like the MMO
way uh let's see this
way all right we'll have to do the MMO
wait I will return to them then did I
well what do hops do isn't hops for like
alcohol Alo
cream we might be able to do blueberries
and what else coffee beans I don't know
about that one
personally uh we have super corn we have
more Super corn let's do that super
Corin for super
[Music]
crap okay this
one I was just thinking how fun it is
being here actually I I'm having a lot
of fun with s Days to Die
it is fun I I'm also having fun um
getting to talk to everyone so that's
neat I am
content why is there like creepy
music I know it's not necessary to fix
this but I think it would be nice
to uh I'm already out of
stuff yeah I'm I'm aware that I am
usually the the slowest burn in terms of
anything
shotgun
shell why is the music so ominous right
now oh we should probably call this like
ingredients how about we organize things
in the
meantime actually there's an organized
button uh first click this one sword
container why is the music so
creepy oh sudden
farming yeah I'll take it I'll use is
not that one um I don't know about that
one just yet cooking
grill is this music normal what is going
on let's just put the food away at the
very least I think anything uh Farm
related even crops I'll put here
actually let's take the oak
seed we'll leave half
here the night is a spoopy okay
guess I should stay put P primitive
gloves uh let's make another storage
thing and we'll do a
closet maybe maybe
here oh people be done uh we'll put like
armor armor weapons here
perhaps or May and maybe ammo actually
ammo it's spray General so primitive
stuff I will use this though sorry I got
to use it oh is this just for
fighting I will repair it for
you there you go is this just for for
punching cuz in this case I think this
could be useful for fauna for punching
okay I don't usually punch so I'll leave
this here um I'll put ammo here I will
take I'll keep the 9 mm because I think
I use that for my pistol which I
apparently have put away so I will
actually put it away then you got iron
we'll keep that I'm keeping the
Primitive stuff so the others can keep
the more important items a vitamin so
put in the food and
medicine this one too CL fragment I'll
put an armor yeah I've been using a
spear cuz uh I'm not going to be here
for most of the days essentially so I'm
trying to give them the more important
items and I'm just more of a
support okay Stone
shovel what about bullet tips we'll keep
this we'll keep
that because that's ammo related
items um nitrate I'm going to put in the
farming plot same with
that there you
go oh those are for rifles
not uh what else
chrysanthemum um this should be here I
see that they have not oh they have
placed it okay
good oh they put it in both okay good in
that case I'll just leave this over here
cuz it is related to
that and then for
here I know I know it's not the most
riveting game play
I am here to Aid in what I can I will
keep the arrows though arrows are kind
of my default at the moment Stone Arrow
iron Arrow at this point I might as
well and then I'll do my remaining Stone
ones you like the chill grind oh
good o this one definitely needs to be
replaced uh what do you call it building
block
I mean it's not necessarily
important is there a way to just like
make this into something
else I didn't I didn't make this so I
guess not I just don't think this is
worth having a
window all right uh once it's daytime
I'm going to go back to the old base
because they still plan on protecting
that uh let's put this where is
it oh this is the que right now
uh I guess it's
fine and then what else could I do for
them that could help
out I think we should probably destroy
things that are not
necessary cuz they just take up space
like what about the toaster does it do
anything it gives us like metal pieces I
think it's not like it's going to toast
anything oh good so we got
[Music]
potatoes uh we got
break what's
that I'm going to keep
moving let blure it
out
hello there you
[Music]
go how about you come to me there's a
little bit of a pause when they're right
in front of
you honestly I wonder if there's like a
better way to kite them oh like for
example if I were to make a block they
would have to destroy the block
[Music]
right oh oh they died a lot
faster oh it's the
lag there's lag right now I mean I did
send some
okay uh in the meantime I think
we Let's Go destroy
this put it here I don't want them to be
able to see us from the first floor a
lot of people died
oh wow it's a good thing I'm just a home
builder
huh you got B the Builder now you got
Sharin the
Builder uh let's see I think if I press
was it R
all right I guess uh I guess it doesn't
really matter just stick with
this oh they got holy crap they got
other shapes I didn't
realize destruction
construction I didn't know they had
other shapes well we're going to we're
going to make it basic
though you do an inside corner or 3 four
why would you want to do a 3
four because it feels nicer does it
matter I really don't think it matters
though yeah I didn't expect that let's
go
basic and then we could probably change
this into something else honestly let's
just destroy
this yeah I'm pretty sure you can shoot
through the hole
H I think the host would be good for uh
the second
area I mean like higher up just a little
bit
Oh weird oh is this like why is it not
perfect uh let's change it to a
different shape it bugs me how about
reforce
y okay how about how about
what other shape you got what about a
corner ah let's just let's just keep at
it but it bugs
me is it the window in the top that
makes it
weird well we just keep that
window hopefully hopefully they don't
notice how weird it
is we'll keep that
window I think we should only focus on
like the first layer I hope they can't
see through that
okay that's good we're trying to give us
complete privacy or privacy however you
want to call
it um I'm not too worried about this
one here you could probably do it more
building
blocks there you
go I can't fix that well it's not too
bad so I think uh we're good here I'm
going to go back to the old base
then all
right uh let's go over
here uh it's so this
way where is everyone like how far away
are they they're all the way over
there I guess I guess the best method
for me is assuming I am even there for
the third
battle I'm I'm so surprised it's been a
week
um I will just try to get XP based on
the people who are the most violent so I
should try to party with them and I
should stay behind and just do the Bob
the Builder
lifestyle they're all dying oh I heard
that uh with each death you get the
XP the debuff the
Mordor uh will miss thank for the
support by the
way yeah yeah be bees is definitely one
of the more violent ones and you guys
thought I was a red flag
huh I'm a householder
uh I wonder if it's worth
Scavenging okay uh if I am going to
scavenge well we can spawn near our
thing the issue is that we just have to
not
die let me gather some wood on the way
I'm the interior
designer it's like whenever I played
Minecraft I literally just built stuff I
didn't really do the combat
route oh for example I think there's
these enemies called the Wither and all
that uh
oh the do
hickey oh it's kind of
spooky have they been here surely they
have well maybe they're like a let's
player here
oh I'm pretty sure they have considering
that everything here is emptied out okay
yeah I'm I'm assuming they
have yeah I'm not familiar and then
there's like the warden in Minecraft I'm
not familiar with that
either so all those things I have never
encountered
them oh you can break the curtain
okay do that
then I do like the oy house it is a
pretty good idea I also can't believe
that uh ra has technically stayed here
for that long I find it
hilarious oh it's pretty
nice oh oh they're spawning okay I don't
like the fact that they're actually
spawning just now so I I'm actually
going to leave I don't think it's a good
idea because they're probably going to
spawn more is my
assumption we have a goal and our goal
is just to make a nice little base it's
a good thing now just C like home home
making stuff gets XP honestly it's not
too
bad very slow XP but is XP I'm thirsty
fudge I can't believe he can't drink
water
here why not
are you sure I can't drink
water I also can't believe that you
actually can't look up and just drink
the
rain I believe them all I believe them
but they were a
liar I got to empty my
hand uh let
me I think I have to be at the The Edge
right the shore let's let's do that oh
you can't drink let's try it I know it's
dirty but we'll we'll get health I don't
know where the water came from look as
long as it's not from downhill let's
assume this is
uphill you'll get bow movements okay but
that is the price to pay for your
thirst okay how do I how do I drink
eat I did
it okay dentary do I have
dentary we could we could just drink
from the land
why do I have so many
shovels guys guys holy crap this was the
method all along so our characters are
not completely stupid they're somewhat
stupid they'll eat the the glass the
glass
jars wow so we can
live I assume there's a percentage
chance though of getting
denter no no no guys I have no denter
we're good we're
Gucci we he found the the
method the secret to
life I got to have the Magic Hat okay
but but I think the magic hat is hard to
find if it's a magic hat don't you think
it's going to be a little bit more
magical uh let's just get rid of this I
have enough
axes it's not so magical if everyone had
a magic
hat I passed a gacha for it heck yeah I
did
oh man okay so I wanted to leave a a
tweet like a comment to the artist who
did the the Demitri art right but but I
thought like maybe maybe this is a bit
too much I I was going to okay first off
they
Japanese so so they'll see like a random
English comment there and I was going to
say like I will worship the ground he he
he he walks
on I I don't know if you guys were an
arti this and someone said that to you
about your art wouldn't you be happy
though no I'm I'm not really a defeat or
anything but but that feet I will
worship you'd appreciate it there you go
there you go also I I prepared my
thumbnails for next week for the
Resident Evil uh stuff I prepared two
versions of the thumbnails by the
way I prepared two versions one of them
one of them is like the self-insert kind
okay I have have a self-insert thumbnail
and then I have the cooler the cooler
thumbnail which is going to be censored
anyway cuz it's a r18 stream but I did
it anyway because those screenshots had
to get used okay I looked at my
screenshots it's not enough Leon
honestly I did not do enough Leon
screenshots how freaking dare
I pathetic of me so so they're getting
some use okay I assume be done in like
what two streams maybe three depending
on the difficulty
Spike I was reading a comments so
apparently um essentially I am actually
decently good at the game which is why
they give me nonstop freaking pettas so
the pettas I was like pettas now it's
like oh
pettas probably three streams yeah I was
looking at the amount of hours I did
take a little longer in one of the
sections I think they gaug it to be like
1 hour and 30 minutes it took uh maybe
like an extra 30 minutes I guess we'll
see we'll see how it
works oh I would still go for the former
uh only reason is that I don't really
trust Leon around a although I think
they did the dynamic differently which
is good I actually hate the the pining
archetype oh my
base I got to go fix my babies no one
else is gonna F my uh fix my
babies you work so
hard from what I heard uh cuz I was
looking at you guys during
rehearsal cuz I have to you know OBS
right
there um RAR is actually on top of oh I
can make barb wire
fences I have the iron for
it oh that's good you make a KingSize
bad
I'll think about that in a bit uh let's
actually do a favorite here and then
let's do the wooden spikes are wooden
spikes still useful though for
later I don't know why I'm tracking that
I don't need to track
that all right I'm probably going to be
the only one to focus on this at the
moment so I will do that to help them
out you can upgrade them sorry what was
the context again upgrade what
oh I can upgrade my existing one I
assume especially in pits okay so they
are still
useful I thought that maybe by the third
wave they'd be very useless is my fear I
wish that there was an automatic uh
craft in or a
automatic Harvester that's probably what
I
mean guess we'll slowly get there
yeah
automation that would be
neat no I'm not the MVP I'm just I'm
just helping I'm just
support the [\h__\h] last a while that's
pretty good I assume the difficulty also
adapts based on how many uh people are
here but yeah from I don't know I feel
like one potential that could
happen is that we have a sacrificial
lamb and from what it sounds like that
was RAR on top of a car and she just
doesn't she get like um XP loss though
each time she
dies oh I don't have enough I think
that's the issue gosh it takes a while
no I should have enough what do you mean
oh these are these are good okay I need
to look for damaged
ones surprised they didn't go
here they definitely try to go here so
this is the weak point what it looks
like uh let's do the barb wire
inside meantime I can equip
it let's just look at my
favorites that's not my
favorite okay it knows it's not my
favorite oh we don't get XP lost so we
can actually wait she only died once how
did she live
how do she live all
AFK oh she was stuck at the respawn
screen so that is maybe that's the key
actually oh that was my stomach okay I
was
scared I'll just eat this and I'm
thirsty I might as well why not I'm
actually taking care of myself look at
that what does that uh mean I'm actually
full I am
good all right now I need to find a way
how to um Harvest water without a du
collector the time is still going I
wonder if that's the method
actually pleas don't
respond there you
go uh let's
see oh my babies my babies were good to
go wow they really they really freaking
carried holy
crap it looks like the right side is
probably
weak okay so the back of the house is
what is considered the weak area based
on the things that I'm
fcing Yep this side too probably which
it was is fair I have to admit it's a
little dizzying uh being near these many
[Music]
spikes ooh this one looks a little
broken
okay there you
go uh
there oh by the way I rehearsal you guys
got called novel lights
again I I did not correct the person of
course I I just whenever I hear it I I
raise an eyebrow
like I do
like I just did that little reaction
like
mhm like it's okay I forgive you I
forgive you to the the Tex support
you're
forgiven but you will not be
forgotten just cuz you're forgiven
doesn't mean you're going to get
forgotten same thing with Ollie saying
it and practically probably at least
everyone
[Laughter]
once man maybe I should just call your
Novelties huh but no the novelty should
be the
Japanese it's like they're the ones with
he inner Zen that's what they got the
tea it's
like the tier four membership I don't
think I can even do anything for tier
four I'm already busy with through tears
guys I try to keep you guys satisfied oh
by the way uh what's uh in two days okay
your bingo card is coming soon I've
already I've already uh scheduled
it my schedules are so in advance your
comic is already scheduled too and
you're getting the community post
tomorrow for the
members uh so don't forget to write your
prompt if you want a chance to get
chosen for a comment
yeah that's okay I guess I should
promote while I'm talking about it offer
no unfamiliar for membership what is
this uh we do like a writing prompt so
if you want to practice writing or you
just want to write for fun you know uh
so you'll get like three three
stories and at the fourth one um it's
actually up to you to continue it so
it's like supposed to be
open-ended and depending on the
durability of your writing
basically if it works for a comic format
um you might get a chance of getting
Chosen and this goes for all
members and if you're into more of like
the the novel light novel light the
novel The Novel night okay the novel
Night videos that's a tier three thing
every into that so yeah there's my my
promo here you
go oh K thank for the gift and no no
thank you thank you you happy 12
months all right that was my my promo um
I'm good I'm done
now oh look at the so many
trees I'm trying to think of what I want
to do oh my idea for November I've
already thought about it I'm just
thinking about the timing wise so for
November I'm thinking of asking for
recipes that don't involve a lot of
complicated cooking because I'll be
doing everything from my office and my
office gets unbearably hot it's really
warm right now
actually so my idea was maybe that could
be cooking month or a combination of
camping Muth I'm not sure I'm not too
sure how to involve the camping Motif at
the moment though oh I'm hungry oh
Ingram thank you for the gifts again you
spoil you spoil thank you thank
you uh here you go have some
fireworks happy 4th of
July I remember seeing a beautiful moon
on that
day but but sometimes your girlfriend
just turns into the
moon and then uh yeah that's that's what
happens it does happen yeah and B thank
for the gift thank you thank you you
guys
spoil oh I'm trying to think of when to
fit in a movie thing the Seven Days to
Die took some days and I try not do
anything the weekend that's prepping
day I know uh next week I think we're
doing phasmophobia for Advent
though oh Ry thank you for the gift than
you thank
you yeah the weekends are my days to to
figure out um new things like topics or
behind the scenes
stuff I I'm probably going to try to
watch The Joker by the way
I'm going to try giving it a go because
I heard that it was uh I don't know I
heard it was like a butt
[\h__\h] uh hello green
one oh hello oh hi hi hello green one
stuff what are you what you doing oh
what stuff what are you oh I'm I'm
helping with the base apparently we're
still going to use this
for our uh distraction
oh thank you for doing it do you want to
come with us on Quest or do you want to
keep doing base stuff um I could use XP
and I could remain useless and just
smooch off XP if you're
willing oh oh should we just invite you
and then you get the XP that's a great
IDE go okay okay well apparently it had
to be in proximity to you guys cuz I
have tried it with another group
Unfortunately they have wandered off and
I am not in proximity ready to
mooch yeah you can us if you want to
come with us it would be fun yeah yeah
I'll do it let me leave some spikes
really quick apparently um one side is
weak drop all my stuff one all right
good good I'm I'm surprised that is
already day 16 time flies when you're
not here oh TR flies when you're having
fun it was not totally because someone
yeah yeah definitely not like a random
cat don't worry about no don't worry
V
yeah oh my God instead of putting it
into the thingy I accidentally dropped
it all on the floor it's over drop it
all on the floor something give me some
more this now a
rave dance
dance wow what am I you're you're a
monkey or something
dance monkey dance
wow I see how it
is would you would you dance if I ask
you like that I I'll wiggle I'll wiggle
only if you dance too hey I'll take it
okay I'll dance I'll I'll wiggle with
you okay I'm going to um let's go to the
other reer well what's wrong with your
what's wrong with your legs your legs
look flat holy
crap what kind in my screen your legs
I'm sorry sorry so you can't just I have
about my flat legs okay were you hurt or
something did like uh Bon actually oh
okay I thought a bulldozer like ran over
you or
something it was a bunch of zombies in
the shape of a bua they were like oh I
I'm so sorry about the horrifying memory
it is quite traumatizing you bring that
up is a little bit insensitive to be
honest um oh yeah but that's like that's
what I'm best at you see it's when my
charm points yeah
yeah I am I happen to be blunt but also
polite but the thing is I have to feel
like being
polite oh so your natural state of being
is being BL yes it's called um not
giving a [\h__\h] I believe oh not giving a
[\h__\h] syndrome or yeah yeah I was I was
born this way that that is why the world
is a little cruel
wait this one's good it's
unused use that
one uh tool I'm going to be honest I
haven't really leveled anything yet like
except for medicine I I guess you're
also doing medicine oh no you can do
medicine I'm probably not going to play
like all day no no it's okay go ahead
I'm just uh defend no you go first no no
oh no no I'm not going to play all the
days it's the
thing than you yeah yeah I'm just being
the the home builder while you guys are
the home recers for the
zombies no I also want to be home build
I think okay you want to replace Bob huh
mm just me okay uh I I don't even know
what weapon type I would want to go with
to be honest uh I'm just doing spear I'm
going OAB boonga I kind of want to do
Club oh yeah you could we can go
clubbing I tried doing I tried doing
bow and arrow but the the Ser is a bit
you know oh yeah sometimes it misses I I
Tred going for Club but I don't like the
you have to be near their faces but I
don't know I want to be tank I want to
be tank I think said that she's really
ahead on like she soon if she gets
enough workstations she can start
crafting really good armor and then
maybe I can be tank o also my club has
blood on it which is very metal and I
appreciate lick it lick it
good tastes like lollipop huh bloody
ons iron deficiency is going
away okay okay should we jump into the
other VC yeah yeah which one yeah let me
leave this party really quick uh how do
I how do I leave party I don't know see
all right uh let me let me tell them
just so I can be polite uh okay I'm
going to switch
parties uh thanks
for that's it thanks for
nothing I didn't get XP from
them I'll leave it like that okay you
can invite me now okay okay I'll I'll
drop it over to me see okay me
too
hello gu hello oh holy crap hello
everyone the hello yes I would like to
moch your XP if you will have me yes of
course we'll have you wellcome well
thank you don't tell the other party why
I left
them huh oh no uh I was going to try
mooching off of them but they were too
far away to mooch off of so it was not
helpful
a how but is audio
okay oh my thank you I appreciate
that sorry sorry sorry Sor sorry sorry
couldn't see
soroc excuse
me thank
you all right I am here to benefit we're
ready okay where are we heading we're
going to do class pretty soon we're just
at the at the house at the old house
stor and stuff and making food okay I
will head to the trader in the meantime
okay wait we wait we we all going to go
to the Traer in a second I think to go
together yeah well I'm planting trees on
the
way okay okay I have I put more farming
magazines into the old house chest by
the way oh thank
you har us yes Harvest Moon yeah can't
wait to marry a zombie died more often
from ra killing me than from
hey at least you haven't died for my
spikes but to SP too La has six player
kills she is the second most player
killer besides me wow up you guys are
messed
up okay du tape
here I guess I got closer to Door unless
that's you guys damaging the spikes near
it oh maybe
okay would they attack it randomly if
there's no humans there though I wonder
I don't know so I think they would oh I
got guns but maybe maybe they did
okay we have that okay I'm ready the
breakfast will take a while to cook so
like while we while we Quest at out
breakfast we'll be ready when we get
back all
right
[Music]
okay uh I need a
new I'm going to check on the farm near
here okay they have not grown from what
I have uh last
Saw
why cuz it takes 7 days to
grow it takes seven days to die it takes
seven days to
grow I I don't know but it feels like it
it's technically been like 2
weeks okay I got do you have the meat
for by any chance um I I'm using the
meat to cook bacon and eggs but it will
take
like it'll take
about 10 minutes cuz cooking okay no
problem wait wait the farm plot has to
be like loaded in to actually grow so if
it's too far away from us it just
doesn't grow oh that sucks oh really I
don't
know it's kind of lame unless unless we
just have to harvest
it hold on maybe I harest
for no it's grown yay yay
okay yeah so we actually have to
harvest I'm so
done so done with what with the spikes
in the entrance I'm breaking
them she uh keeps dying oh wait wait we
need them when the raid starts you just
have to go straight just here they one
just no I cannot go straight iume the
issue is that I don't always get the
seeds the drunk
test the
glasses okay I had
enough she's done with it okay I'm going
to go
all right well we got some some stuff oh
actually okay I okay there is this one
area that I really want to go to and
it's east of where we are right now we
can go to it mind Mark lots of stuff and
it's it had like a like a store with a
bunch of magazines I already took a
bunch of them but is this big like area
with the L is the F sh I have an outfit
for you a farm outfit it's
am chest in our house okay I I will go
equip uh your new fashion thing then
thank you so much beloved thank you okay
bye how kind I'm coming to the store if
you look at the square uh you know this
farm that looks like a flag and then the
road keeps going and then there's a
little like an h and then at the bottom
body of the
H is like a big area H well I don't know
how big your map in that area if you've
been there
so can I mark
it uh maybe we should go to the trader
first since Call's waiting for us there
oh okay I didn't know that okay I got
head there
now right
yeah okay okay okay can't wait to eat my
rot
egg yummy I love Ro egg now oh you
do yeah I like I like raw egg over rice
yes I love raw egg over rice but I have
I have to like uh filter the whites out
cuz I don't like egg white oh it's too
it's too goopy oh what I like to do is I
just break the I break the yolk and I
keep the egg whites
you you break the yolk and yeah wait wa
don't you fry your egg when you go put
it on Rice oh I think they mean raw yeah
they you just raw but I feel like that's
um that's only common in Japan isn't it
it's not really common it's not it's not
really I don't know if it's safe to do
in the US it's not it's definitely not I
don't think it's safe to
do safe in some countries but most most
countries it's not so yeah America hates
us though they want us to choke in our
own
eggs but I tried it I tried it in Japan
like egg like oh yeah it's good it's so
good so
tasty
yeah I want to go to Japan eat all the
food yeah I want to go back too actually
I I went to a Denis in America and then
I remember the Denny's in Japan and it
was like
if it was was it Denny's do you know
that one place where I got hamburger
like onion soup french onion soup with
hamburger good in Japan Denny's in Japan
that was really good it was not like it
wasn't it wasn't french onion soup but
it was really good I really liked it I
never been to the Wi in America but
everyone keep telling me that the the
one is better yeah yeah definitely well
it's totally different because Denny's
in Japan is like a breakfast place
primarily and Denny's in in Japan is
like a family restaurant yeah it's also
like it's a quick stop for truckers
essentially stop there to grab the rice
with the burger and the D gloves or the
the Hamburg Hamburg steak thingy oh it's
so good you guys are making me hungry to
be fair it is my
fault sori and I would just go to those
Family Restaurant friends all the time
like Denny's and Jonathan we were just
like let's go get food and ice
cream yeah oh yeah the perfect it make
there is crazy good too they make
amazing
perfit the other day I was like okay you
know this was I've been having a lot of
fun I want but I want I want to um
what's it called uh treat myself and I
was like okay theoretically what if I
you know for because ra has thank you ra
does have like uh um space because uh I
I and since we're in different we stream
different times right I was thinking if
I visit her I can just steal her PC I
was like okay what if I go just just to
sit out and
food thinking about it I'll be there
I'll be there in a few months and then
you can have you
can can have your food too you
can off you guys a
faster yay make faster for everyone
actually I I make amazing meatballs my
meatballs are crazy good because my
grandma taught me how to make them do
you do you use bread crumbs and your
meatballs yeah
a we should all do a food party yes I
would love that
yeah I'll probably head back there at
some point next year we should do we
should do a f a food party but themed so
like for example you can only bring like
a dish that is the first letter of your
name so I would bring a be dish that's
cute yeah I'll bring is is my name okay
yeah yeah
whatever Pizza Pizza I'm here I'm here
I'm almost I'm here
too dang looks like re but pink yeah
[Music]
I
Flo no that's me what this guy want
havein D yeah no I told her I told her
that she can take them but I don't know
if she listen up jackass you want work
can't say I'm not surprised
maybe I'll me
too some Rand tell her I'll be right
back no I'm at the I'm at the trader I'm
going to accept the quest and then we
can all do our Quest together okay I
just took whatever is the closest Quest
it's okay we can take double of the
prices with but wait are all quests like
shared
automatically yeah yeah okay okay
because if you die and you've done a
bunch of quests you lose all those
quests okay Quest Mor yeah that's okay
that's fine guess we'll figure it out I
I got a special job I I actually have
Moria at 200% I can't go any more Beyond
this trade theth she is the maxed out
guys Jen oh we can get Trader
Jen oh I hope she's
nicer but by the way Mor you're a little
quiet for me I already have you at two
200% as well hold on just a sec let me
get oh you're better now slowly do I
like talk what do we do I take any Quest
or yeah take any Quest and we will we
will all share it which one should we go
to
first um oh wait do you guys do you guys
see if you zoom out of the map opening
trade routes B Boo at the I I see a
fetch quest for you to fetch it's
southeast of the trader it should say
opening trade route B do you guys um I
will I will just follow you South where
southeast of the map if you zoom like
out as far as you
can I I will follow you uh Alpha if you
if you don't see it that's okay we can
do other people's Quest first and then
I'll grab that I see I see like tier two
fetch people yeah okay one I see and
then that's probably just a my special
Quest then so we can do a bunch of
quests we got to do more quests yeah um
I want to meet the cute
girl speci Quest is not shared okay I
see oh okay that's why we got to that's
why we got to go do these quests okay
let's do let's do you guys' quest first
dang look atana Reeves in her her pink
hair
H I'm coming can you try something can
you take out your bicycle uh hi you to
be bleeding okay so sorry I miss I miss
the um okay I'm standing on it now try
dang it it doesn't
work apparently you can get a seat for
your bicycle though that you can carry
to people oh that's so cute I hope we
can get a car like a a clown car oh yeah
yeah I want a motorcycle that's what I
want car and then I want to drive into
the into people which class are we going
to are we going to the highlighted one
in Orange I was going to go to your your
uh your fetch one cuz it's the closest
one okay tier two fetch B boo okay I'll
go to that tier two fetch
beo it's next to the new home
no yeah it's pretty close by we're all
kind of close hi
hello am I going the wrong hold on a
second you're going you're going right
you're going right yeah cuz I too am
near you oh nice okay wow you and your
bicycle compared to me and my feet her
bicc you you all get bik you just got to
do a few more quests you know oh I guess
so how many quests is it look based 10 I
want to do 10 oh I don't think I've even
come close to that I I Haven
in so all
the a new
home okay I am at the residence is that
what you wanted just come to B Bo's icon
I am at the exclamation point okay
heading there oh there's a swing oh it's
really big I see it
too
nice just take these cards
by the way can we can we go to the new
house because I don't know where it is
is this one yeah yeah don't don't forget
to leave like a a checkpoint there so
you can go back
anytime okay are we all here yep I I'm
near your fetch Quest oh wait I'm at the
wrong one I'm at near Mor a different
different F Quest it's oops okay thank
you let me just pass the
Washington it's very close ow
ow might my hold on my character's tired
H every time you say CL you have you
after you have to
go okay I am now at the
McMillan
[Music]
the
good I'm
ready let's do it all right I can't wait
to
mooch up oh
I don't want to hit
anyone so I will just stay
put wow good job we good many hands make
quick
work what if we what if we bait all wait
wait wait wait guys guys guys guys guys
ba bait all the zombies and then put
them in here and then we turn on the
vial and then they burn to the
crisp that was a good idea yum okay I'm
going to wait here at
I think they've already gone
in oh they're
here oh they were doing
something something in
there y good
job got I got you I'll be the lighter I
will light oh thank you fire fire light
the fire you are the light of our Liv
spreading out like wild
[Music]
wild how did that Miss it's Cally right
there
what what it's
lagging what okay that's it spear
time I don't know how oh I'm also low on
stamina
oh can you climb this rope to get up
here you can
[Music]
oh hey let
me I hear it I hear something it's the
pades do you'll get
there it's okay my spear takes it at
least 10 hits you'll have time to
help I want
this
nice can't tell if it's
lagging
yeah never mind chill here I
guess climb the roope what why are your
things still on fire but you just climb
the roope
yeah you oh sorry I thought you were
Z I have a on me
in what if she can't read wa this is
cool why do I still hear zombies but I
can't see
them oh no you
died
I I'm so sorry
what do you got there I think we can go
down here uh you can come down but I am
surrounded by yes I I will not go down
then I will shoot from
afar well he's wearing a
helmet bar come on good job
y nice
job I'm back welcome back good job
te I found steroids that picture o you
going to take it I have the cat oh cute
cat I wish the cat picture yeah I want
the cat place are so bad but you did it
just get destroyed we can't keep it I
guess no you didn't destroy
it all right we can destroy things to uh
harvest the materials at
least okay I finished the class how
about
you you have to you have to check I to
find a supply the distance the distance
away from you you have to check the
distance I found a wi everybody has
their own their own uh Supply they got
to find yeah oh crap I found the White
River but I didn't pick it
up oh what am I looking for did the
quest um if you the top said it'll say
return
TR I don't see anything is it the
bathroom
I don't have the quest anymore oh I
think that might have been the
case oh so I need to find something it's
called a sack
okay here Cy I'll give you a present I
sorry I killed youy water in the toilet
did something wrong uh 3.3 2.2 it's
probably upstairs for me it's a mod that
reduces uh durability I'm go in the
kitchen and try to climb up cool thank
you yeah I think it might be up
here wow you guys could not
climb hey I found
it
[Music]
y oh good job good
job found here behind the
Y got it all right we're good who else
uh I'm still looking for mine I am
unfortunately a little blind is it up
here here maybe it's behind this thing
this is I don't know but I think I think
it's below here or near me right now cuz
I'm 7 up here in the Attic oh s it's got
to be below you unless oh okay oh it
might be in the Attic like yeah I'm in
the attic but I don't see anything to Lo
it's a it's like a brown bag a brown bag
okay it is below me okay let me look uh
underneath
then not the corer Satchel oh it is the
I found a cookie but there's something
in
here oh that then that's somebody else's
corer Satchel maybe down here okay the
second
floor wait is that mine
no good gosh I will never find a a
little bit confused about how to like do
the quest so what it says on the top on
the top right what it says the wiing
residence I think if you died then it
probably like stopped all already oh
yeah you feel the quest if you yeah oh
okay okay okay no problem basement for
me okay we still have plenty of quests
to do that yeah it's fine it's fine no
worries just might want to make sure
that I'm not accidentally like not doing
the stuff
properly I'm a little
slow and it it looks like a satchel
right yeah it look like it's not going
to be
okay all
right let me know if you guys find a
satchel in the basement
perhaps I know what is a satchel I mean
I don't know if it's the same for
us um it's going to be her own Satchel
oh cuz it spawns it spawns satchels for
all of us I believe
you okay wow I am not really good at ice
spy all I know is at least like near the
attic or below the attic that's the only
issue
beyond that I don't
know okay how about how about what I do
is I'll go to the attic and I'll destroy
my way down okay okay okay that's going
to be my thing now force it go for it
yeah no
problem it's a great idea oh oh there's
a compass bar too
okay most dissatisfying thing is when
you find a secret item kind of oh why
did you oh sorry sorry sorry those are
mine it has to be in the and then it's
like MTR has very little in it yeah it's
my favorite I see oh I see a s on the
attic oh it is in the Attic hiding it
was hiding behind something was over
here oh you're so smart thank you my my
beibs yeah let me just press e oh it's
empty actually never mind it's not mine
however it was very cute of you to have
almost found it you don't think it's
going to be at the like the freaking
roof right locked door right here wait
can it's it's not up here is it we can
we can see each other's satchels yes
I'll Che the
roof it's in the ground floor it tells
me if it's up or
down it's at the first floor okay I'm
just going to destroy my way
down need to go on the roof it has to be
at the garage okay
yum there was a St at the garage I
think okay it has to be it has to be
like here come on okay I see it I see it
right below okay it's a I have to
destroy something that's a 5,000 I
haven't gotten it though I I haven't
gotten it don't don't don't say yeah
yeah wait is it in the freaking vent is
that I couldn't find it oh my freaking
God
messed up it was an event okay I'm
done nice okay shall we go North to do
the one up north
yeah just be careful cuz it's almost
nighttime
and yeah it should be an easy one just a
clear
let's should we wait until this morning
because it's almost a little bit more no
we're overpowered this is only if you
have guns SL I'm going to stay behind
my character eats nothing but
eggs this one right
wait that's still burning how I think
it's the one over here actually
yeah SP the one over
there wait my quest already activated
here for some reason you have two
different
ones oh no no no no Maybe not
maybe mind I think I think we do this
one twice because there's Callie's Quest
and Ra's Quest
okay
okay okay now I see it it says like
clear areas and stay
within I hear them don't leave the area
oh they're behind they're behind oh
they're behind the door oh behind us
behind us good job
what uh I'll keep the door and locked so
we don't get
cornered we should probably
close I'm getting
shreded uh does eat more eggs because
I'm dying I have eight eggs he can have
some
eggs ni you dead okay thank you no
that's I hear them ah there's a there's
a basement there's a basement oh it's so
dark ow I think you stabbed
me uh I'm going to stay behind I am
bleeding uh it's okay I have one I'm
using it oh my God the ey the light
flickering all right uh try not to stab
me spooky down here guys do you have the
key herei here you have two there's a
key here do you see it as well or is it
uh a key I just have clear areas I don't
see a key know right like hanging behind
you oh hanging key no I found if you
come to the basement I found like a
little secret passage okay oh I'll lose
my health if find something that's
locked like a door or something that
says requires let me know because I okay
I need to eat all my eggs I am dying eat
your eggs sure eat them I I am I have
eaten all eggs I need one more medical
to have a first bandage
oh it's so
dark I oh we can climb up there's an
attic oh the
garage I got a farming book for you sori
oh thank you I can live out my days and
semi piece what doesn't mean me I'm like
near death so I'm just going to
chill uh who is using arrows were you
using arrows me uh me too okay I have a
book for you for that where did they go
did you guys go from the basement we
went from the basement we found some
loot but no enemies so oh I hear enemies
and I do not want to die wait where are
you I'll save you I'm going back to the
garage oh no I'm not dead
yet it's just that you you stabbed me
pretty hard my girl oh I'm so sorry I
have it's okay it's okay no I already
fixed it I I was going to die from blood
uh blood loss though I'm pretty we
finished oh hey we finished now we got
to do it twice
okay we got to do it again do it again
yeah yeah out of curiosity if you die
before turning in a quest do they reset
like what happens yeah you don't get
that Quest have be careful not to die at
all I
will try not to die okay everybody
repair yourselves if you you bandage
maybe I can make you you can make that
yourself take this
thank you here's a bandage sry take this
will that heal me I already sto my
bleeding killers and a blood bag thank
can I drink the
[Music]
blood oh here okay thank you wait that's
vehicle Adventures why am I why do I
have vehicle Adventures wait that was
supposed to be Southern farming where
the farming go yeah no you you want me
to ride a bike or something I'll get the
blood
bag and the painkillers go I dropped it
back
again oh I can craft first I can't craft
yet I will take the
painkiller nice oh if you have one
vehicle Adventure I'll give you the
second one people because then we can
stack it because I'm almost over it's
here does anybody has a first eight
Band-Aid oh I no I can't craft it yet
either
May will help hey go I dropped it oh
thank you I'm dehydrated am I going to
die oh B use it yourself yeah yeah yeah
yeah oh I have a first
AK
dehydrated that's fine oh no what is
that
sound that was theor
[Music]
I'm going to go get
some too bad we can't eat the snow
although there is a river I can drink
from eat cat
food yum yum yum yum yum yum this is
where the Yumm cat food yeah this way
is I can't see my cursor that is the
river behind that house I'm back
W my bow now makes 20% more damage nice
why are you naked
yeah I was going to make one of my I'm
having an armor issue but problem is uh
I don't have any cloth to make new armor
so oh I have uh some cloth I think have
cloth yeah I have six yeah thank you
yeah thank you I need as much cloth as I
can get thank you so much all right let
me drop you some here you
go cloth can someone come to the river
with me I'm
thirsty okay I come
I have no I don't have juice I mean I
have murky water but I'll I'll like lose
five Health if I drink murky water right
now let's go let's go I come with I
think it's this way yeah just behind the
house is it
here yeah it's down
here okay I am dying of dehydration holy
crap I am so glad that there is a river
near by how do you zip from the river
stand um you have to have empty hands
with
empty but you might get diarrhea that's
okay I'll take it over
death am I I now not too bad I
guess oh also yeah I need a little
water let's see I found a cooking W how
do you make painkillers they're really
good
I don't know so oh someone needs to like
take medicine or
magazine I am still good to go actually
I have not been uh hurt by the water yet
that's crazy to me I
know I need to heal I'm so thirsty how
much do I need to drink you need a z zip
go go okay how do I heal oh I'm I'm
taking damage though I am taking damage
you should be able to just equip the
bandage and then left click it no I did
it but I'm still
like uhoh oh don't leave me I hear
zombies and I don't want to
die that's wor maybe you took damage
from drinking or something oh yeah I'm
pretty sure I did oh they're
chasing one's coming okay we can do the
the mission
again
okay minut almost oh they dropped
something
hey there's another oh that's you
okay need
food uh I have one egg you can have if
you
want yeah food will be nice here here
here I have one
egg I'm sure if we do the class they
might like respawn the boxes and maybe
we can find some food in there yeah okay
okay I
have here you go ra have one egg fresh
from the pockets wait oh no the
sandwiches made me
sick uh-oh okay we've begun the
quest just you're just going to have to
fight with
dentry oh no I'm hungry
now darn it it's okay it's okay I'm
going to break in didn't to do that all
right I'm going to stay behind so I
don't die yeah you stay behind we'll
we'll take it for you hello
I don't want to hit
[Music]
anyone
do I'm staying behind actually
especially as an Archer yeah yeah no
worries you guys stay behind we'll take
care of it thank you
papa lose my quest uhoh oh wait hey
there's people here I thought they were
zombies look look it's a whole gang yeah
there's Chi FAA and then uh
yeah what's
up oh I think they they have to wait for
us to finish the quest for they just
start you got you got to wait
[Applause]
unfortunately oh thank God for shared XP
you guys are doing
great thank you I'm oh shoot I don't
want to get
hit
no don't
die okay we we good we good okay I'll
just light up the way for you guys there
you go thank you no problems I think
there's one more zombie down here maybe
in the basement uh we're in the basement
right now I hear it I hear him yeah oh
there he is found
it you go okay we good
job wow you really shank oh nice art
this is nice can I steal it a
Shanker noce uh should we go to the
Traer and deliver those quests yeah yeah
I don't want to die with this many Quest
any
further yeah that's not we got a bunch
of quests to turn in
okay oh wait I have a quest oh that's
got some food whoever was hungry oh I'm
hung I am hungry as
well uh also we don't should we should
we tell them that we're done with the
quest if they wanted to do this yeah
I'll tell them we're done with the quest
here
okay
yeah did someone have pistol something
oh yes I use pistol I found I don't know
if this is pistol I
found a magnum
enforcer oh I am going to use Magnums
whenever I
find okay I'm going
to here it is uper head
back thank
you okay so we heading to the Traer yes
yep okay I'll just follow sh okay we'll
go together cuz I am blind to the map
it's okay I'm hungry and dying oh
actually do you have your
food uh I only have the food that
damaged so I don't think oh okay I I'm
not ready to get damaged that way is not
good for you
okayand I'm sure you did like a great
job making it though you your bike I
found it on the floor I I see okay maybe
that's the issue probably second rule
doesn't work in this game hello infected
to oh wait wait wait wait say say still
beefs I saw like a pop weekly a it's
locked I honk your horn
instead that for me I'd be
happy oh we can have like a little bike
gang yeah biker gang yeah I'll be fine
I'm want that bike too I hope they're
going to give it to me there was a bike
at the base I think it's one of yours
though oh it's it's just mine I see I
see you messed up I don't think anybody
else has a bike yeah unless they did the
class I think you make it but it's
probably hard should be able to make one
because she has a lot of vehicles thingy
I think she's like 10 or something but
she needs I think she needs the four the
workshop thing I have four vehicles on
here I can give to her as well nice nice
maybe we can feed them to her and then
she can make us
[Music]
bases yeah cars or
motorcycles oh this is this is is the
new house we can store stuff in here I'm
going to store stuff
okay okay oh yeah I should uh put the
farm plots here then oh what is what is
new house let me check on the oh yeah
yeah make sure to leave a mark
here ooh how do you name
crates um hold e uh hold e in front of
it okay our Farm's going well it's
actually here
all right WR uh let's see oops I have
any seeds I do not think so I got an
outfit ooh fancy right the farming
outfit I didn't end up seeing it short
oh wait that's the I need to get the
outfit
actually oh painkillers uh shotgun
weekly should probably keep one pain
killer okay okay I'll just I'll just
keep yeah
where was the outfit again I forgot
where Faun left
[Music]
it oh the a new house to deposit stuff
because I is that the base this one
right in the inventory ammos and
weapons uh this
one yo when does he open open up oh yeah
I guess so he's open
nice all right put shotgun we oh I'm
stupid okay say 17 so in 4 days we're
going to
have yeah
yeah actually I can't repair it
my I'm going to leave this here for now
and I'll only equip it when I'm
harvesting I
think um sh for farming do you need like
rotten fles or something yeah so yeah
you can leave it in the food and
medicine box it's good for PL okay yeah
you're
one that a silly question how do you
name your box hold e hold e and then the
one of the a yeah
yeah nice I got a B
bicycle
yay bik game
nice nice
[Music]
nice okay I'm coming to the Traer
now okay some
food oh
[Music]
finally much
better much
better oh where did the farming outfit
go I just put it back in here
oh never mind I have it okay going to
leave it behind so it doesn't get
damage and then I'll get a Repair Kit
Repair have a room just for
me
so armor
part wow we're hungry
people sewing k
we're hungry for zombie murder and
knowledge honestly if you're think about
it like how badly we
want to read I just want to read I just
want to know the world I just want to
learn okay okay I'm heading to Trader
now okay me too I'm going to the
trader oh oh yeah I need the coins I
[\h__\h] there you go tokens wait is it
is this a different trade out is this is
this the guy I have to talk to oh you
guys need to turn us off oh
yeah take some
water my
money your money skill magazine I love
my money on your not your
money okay okay I gave back my trink I
did it I finally did a quest good
job good job that's my first one okay
say I'm going to go sleep now guys
okay thanks for playing with us have a
good sweep actually first uh so I don't
spawn outside next
time could be a good
idea
[Music]
byebye wish they sold water in here dang
it you can drink it from the river but
you know at the cost of
Health I'm good that's that dang not
into the the camping huh nah not really
my style I still don't know how you
collect water like you just loose the
jar you I'm just going to take it and
then if anybody needs to buy anything
I'll buy it for them uh I don't need
anything at the moment I think I don't
know what to
want thirsty again for
had what is
a you can purchas purchase drinks from
vending machines
oh yeah but how do you how do you
collect murky
water is the thing I guess you just find
it nowadays you can't just uh use a jar
collect it from the river and all that
stuff that sucks goodbye
you can cook yellow and red flowers to
make a for I
see I got a everything's for
sale and now you can also take special
everybody with a bike could take the
special
Mission oh yeah I guess crafting
skill this
one I'm so
happy ooh
and then if you get the special Mission
we can go do it
together even though we got it it's
technically separate but we do it
together uh do you guys need a refle
sorry refle world as a magazine rifle
world I think Kiara needs those uh rifle
okay what about
I'm yeah everybody needs those I think
in
general oh oh they are more yeah I'm
going to use those oh pip bombs okay I
need figure out what I want to do now uh
I'm still going with spear but we're
already good that we should probably put
medicine honestly I'm taking the P
cannnot I guess I need to find a
medicine book is the issue oh special
job so uh let's see what was another
thing I was want to
do got it like I'm I'm not going to be
fighting too much so I'm not going to
get the like more advanced stuff I'm
only sticking with like OAB
boa healing Factor oh yes please okay
I'll Dr here thank you so I guess I'm
going to drop farming e and Har
tools oh thank you I guess I should do
tools
digest o i can get
coffee
coffee I'm going to put those in the
chest I don't think I need did you take
a tier two clearing Quest B I did oh
crap uh who wanted to focus on clubs
again I think CeCe did right I'll leave
it for her
then I'm I want to try oh okay I'll give
it to you here you go take your club and
go
clubbing time to go clubing
yeah you pisky kids and your clubbing oh
I should take more quests actually I
forgot
oo oh my God
who's doing uh how about I take a look
at the [\h__\h] I got don't expect me to
cook it for you okay here this is for
for you I'm
jobless oh is that for me or for thank
you I'm coming doing sharp sticks I
think oh yeah
yeah I've lost my big
cat I am outside trying the bike
okay take your time oh I have a quest
here actually actually it's near yours
beeps so I'm going to go home and then
uh go meet one of
you I got a rogue Hood wow how do you
get out of the
bike oh
just and then if you want to put it back
in your inventory hold e and then hover
over it and click
take thank you so much oh K can make a
workstation
yay okay
here awesome oh right over here this is
your sharp stick magazine oh thank you
so much you're going to make the
sharpest stick oh yeah sure did you get
a bicycle
nope a man oh I haven't been doing a lot
it's okay it's okay I'll be
farming I'm a stationary woman
getting strong
together all right let me see if I can
Harvest her stuff growing growing nope
not
yet okay would you guys like to go meet
the new Trader together okay yeah we can
let's see what
they y
how do you know well you took the
special job didn't you oh opening trade
rout
right is in
here okay then my character is so
cool look at how cool my character is
yeah I love it I love your hairstyle
then you look good so good is everyone
did you did you fall in a hole yeah yeah
we can go I'm just putting some stuff
away before uh going back to
[Laughter]
Yonder you need some
help how that happen where's the where's
the new Trader actually what was that
where's the new
Trader uh if you it if you leave your
house or the it's just keep going South
Road on that road and you should be able
to meet up with us okay I mean I'll just
follow you anyway okay I'll see you guys
there
okay
no
probably it's okay I got out no I don't
need
help are you sure M I'm following you
okay follow me we're
biking oh let may be thirsty what a
lovely bike what a lovely Trail a biking
trail even a lovely Dey morning biking
time
yeah I love the I'm so happy oh this
isri oh no this this doesn't look very
good but not very told not
go oh is it a burnt area yeah it's a
burnt area
ooh those are well I don't know how it
is
actually really scary everything's kind
of
hard just like my cooking fire fire like
fire them
Vibes awesome VI maybe I like
it yeah for
sure I wonder we can Rush all the quests
by this next Trader and then get to
another
Trader I
wonder okay I'll head towards you guys I
hope they have better stuff me too
I bet she will and I bet she's nicer
well she's equally mean I know about
that you think she might be mean I think
she's I don't see why not maybe that's
even better oh oh that's what you're
into oh you like the mean lady yeah
could you like Mean Girls oh she likes
Mean Girls I oh just like the movie huh
no that's not true just like you know
maybe when I don't know you see like
there special the cisal residence get it
cuz is crispy their house burn
[Music]
to so
silly man it's ominous here I'm behind
you like what happened to Canada
mountains yeah oh that's a that's why
you go around the
mountain around okay we can do
that oh oh no no no it's kind of scary
to Sounds here it's like a little windy
road a windy Mountain Road what're for
those Pokmon don't you think yeah you
people okay yeah follow the windy road I
think it kind me biking I used to use my
bike all the time oh yeah you a biker I
love I used to love biking now I don't
bik anymore
I like baking but but my my parents
would wake me up in the morning at like
700 a.m. be like oh yeah we're going to
go out to the park and go biking and I'd
be
like and then but it was nice biking is
fun but not at 7 in the
morning yeah that's totally something
that Mama Mory would do too dang for a
walk on the trail it's like 5 a.m. oh my
God my dad is the kind of guy who goes
on my dad doesn't use the bike it is
like
the uh like the electric one oh the
scooter or something yeah a scooter guy
and he goes around okay man my parents
just woke me up for
church no my par oh my God speak to
church you like Church's
Chicken are you okay I saw that
oh there's a big city here or something
a
factory Dan's Clinic oh it's a clinic
there's a lady there's a lady I hope
she's nice I want to talk hope I haven't
left my back my my my my bike no your
bike is still there this place looks
dangerous uh it's fire bath uh I'm in
the factory
actually o
wow she lives in a
church oh no not the
memories when you talk to her you just
look straight at her stuff at her stuff
does she have good stuff like good wees
go around um no well yes she has some
good stuff yeah see she's nice I told
you she'd be nice that's good oh did
they go through here she's got blueberry
pie o I need to go
down oh
oh stim packs but but brother adus loves
stim
packs thanks
lady she's got tier two fetch queste is
back how do you oh I can
repare started a quest oh that's where
she is that's a really nice place
actually yeah oh you before
cleaning nice it just looks nice yeah
fortified cream we can finally make too
bad she'll kick us out
no would be nice if she lets us stand
like the other traitor
[Music]
Hy woman
I've got Goods yeah that's my oh she's
got Goods I want your goods yeah she's
got a lot okay um
goodies we can clear zombies do that if
you do this for me I will never forget
you waa this is a danger never forget me
oh she wants to get
radiated hey no
fair did she tell you that
yeah I think she's just flirting kiss
you should I should I get the first a
kid or the
magazines um I think magazines is more
useful yeah we'll just have to tank
dying and technically you don't really
lose that much when you die cuz you
still
Level like not really of
consequence yeah notic
that well I'm probably okay
here oh
money make a ton of bandages
now how do you make bandages you have to
unlock medicine don't
you yeah but I have a decent amount of
medicine
nice trying to think of what to put my
stuff
in first
penetrator oh she SS um I'm thinking I'm
going for Lucky looter
honestly yeah I I do prefer to spear but
I can't like afford any other levels
from what it looks
like uh let's
see better odds I can make wooden Club
quality like the better b y you need to
put more into
perception oh like in
general oh I guess I
see well I do like head shot damage yeah
okay I see no I use M Spear
and okay let's just put in perception
then I'm not using anything else oh yeah
I will take that here you go damage nice
okay thank youcome
oh and now I can unlock if I were to
have more okay that's good I found an in
the future I will probably do do Lucky
looter but the thing is I don't go out
often wanted to make motorcycle or
something I don't go out a
lot I'm a home bu is anybody here doing
the
wiring magazines nope not me not me you
can use it if you want looks like a lot
of our quests are near each other except
for a moris at least one of yours okay
let's go to the ones near each other
first yeah
okay I zombies around here yeah the
zombies are trying to get in the door is
literally
open do you guys have any leather BS
no there's some at the house at the
house
then I need to wait for me because
she is the man I should probably put
stuff in
cooking going to be mean she I'm feeling
Rowdy I I got a I drank beer
oh can't believe I'm feeling Rowdy
where' you get the brusis I don't know
how you sp oh my vision is so
blurry oh
no what a what an idol I should we head
now while it's still daytime by the way
I'd say so yeah done did anybody have a
drink the beer did not quench my thirst
I am thirsty was I supposed to bring
money to her there is a there is a
vending machine inside look what the cat
drag jet stim packs and now radex no you
got the wrong
store really I too am thirsty who has
money
have money what do you want I just want
water or any oh sugar butts they don't
really have a lot of that they have like
coffee and beer and uh anything that
gives food I guess is
fine anything that gives food you say
yeah wait was I supposed to bring those
tokens that look like arcade little
things oh man I never bring those those
are those are money I see all right I I
could appreciate some oh really into
coffee but I'll accept it ooh tea I'll
take tea drink
it let's see um I got finally oh it
cures Senter too y
juice Yuka
juice yeah something like
that oo thank
you Yuka
Yuka yum y I hope that satisfies me
something very quickly I'll wait until
it satisfies me okay let's uh head out I
guess you ready to head out yeah I'm
need to wait minut because my leg is bro
broken but until me
I oh
okay she's
great yeah I think how do you dye your
stuff I have a crash question o I can
use this
I finally unlock
medicine you got make and she's smart
because she
DRS uhoh my bike is pink
now
oh oh good job
yeah all right I'm ready where are we
going hold On's leg is broken let's okay
sorry no you're fine you're fine we're
just killing things they look like from
uh Legend of Zelda
actually the burn dud
yeah Yik that's rough buddy that's rough
Budd let's see the next Quest we want to
do uh we can do the Mory tier two fch
which is very close me away okay we can
do yeah let's do this one hold on I'm
cucumber I I think I can slowly
come yeah we're going to need to go up
the path again I
think we might need to
CL the fet clear
Mor I don't know if we can Skyrim horse
it up this this we actually
can uh beeps did uh there's a call going
on if you wanted to attend
first a call uh for the Encore thing
with the the dogs oh yes um
yeah here how about we stay in here
really quick uh we can try doing a two
call if you want to do two birds and one
stone yeah let's let's go yeah we we'll
be we'll be right back after wait wait
we'll get kicked out here huh we're
going to we'll at the quest spot but uh
we got to do something really quickly
going leave the voice chat but we're
going to head to the quest spot yeah
we'll be right back after these
messages Okie
[Music]
doie the SP
yeah uh wait what
uh you and me you and me let's go let's
go are you I I I don't know what server
they're going to be in so I'm just going
to stay
here I'm hungry
I'm hungry and
starving hi you come here off
wow I just waiting for yeah I I guess
so yeah
some
um I wonder if we should just like run
there while we're waiting actually yeah
no well I'm going to head to the quest
yeah me too okay yeah wow it's so
private
it's just just us it seems like but by
the way are you heading like the right
direction I'm going to the the Mory fet
class that's but I'm going by the road
so I can take my bike since I have oh
okay you are not a natural climber
unlike uh us
hi sorry huh no you're fine we just
started I mean we're still waiting too
we're just chilling are you streaming
yes yes
so so don't say anything like your
credit card number unless you want to
share that with us my credit card number
is 55 five five five oh how do you even
get her out here we we need one more
number dang also the the three numbers
in the back of your card too as well as
your exp very helpful yeah this could to
be 011 uh yeah yeah H it's so hard
without a bike in this world yeah get
you that bike soon I know I I think I
went the wrong way too I got to go
through the freaking Mountain
Trail how are you
Rea enjoying your Final Fantasy
games yeah just chilling I was actually
watching a musical but you know musical
yeah Elizabeth dos musical oh is
that yeah the one that only I like the
only one only like
yeah no one else likes it only me oh
yeah I I bet I like it if I watch
it make want maybe we still need to do
Phantom of the Opera too oh yeah phant
of the Opera yeah you got to make it
work okay I'll stay quiet you guys uh
have fun oh no you can you can talk yeah
we can talk we not doing anything right
now I'm yeah we're literally just like
freaking climbing a mountain at least
for for my case oh my God a mountain I
know it's so hard I hate
it well I'm glad you're having
[Music]
fun here baby oh yeah yeah every time I
see a bird I just think like I wish that
was
her and then we everything makes me
think of and we eat the well I don't
well only in self-defense but I just eat
the eggs and I think of
you I see well I guess I'll have to cook
you eggs
yeah
thanks good gosh it's almost night time
in here and I'm still not there where
are you oh you're close you're I know
I'm I'm like Skyrim mountain climbing I
kind of missed that game let me let me
check
on
um okay they said
soon okay so
all right I am I am near Mor's
location okay I'm with I'm with myy
right now so you should oh shoot it's
the Crips two and a half uh the area
we're
in can I throw away money I don't really
need it
right you can do whatever you
want are you guys ready for for
Halloween yeah oh yeah what what are you
guys going to
be dead
uh I meant like costume like what what's
your
costume
um guess I'll figure it out I I actually
have it prepared sort of wait wait are
you just for real yeah yeah oh okay in
that case I can't tell
you oh well you have to text well I I
think we're going to be busy on
Halloween aren't we or maybe not I don't
remember that doesn't mean we can't
dress up yeah you can dress up still mhm
I guess I should dress up as a
goth that's well that's not really dress
you just you're that every day yeah yeah
bum
bum did you you did finish that right
yeah yeah I did
night did you do that the
true of course not you think I'm that
gamer yes you are you are I don't feel
like it though if you if you went for
the beef you would get it first try
short oh no no the thing is I'm too lazy
bebs you actually like pain I just don't
care for pain let's that's the
difference between
us also it's funny but your gamer stance
is like you lean in I just like I I do
cross-legged
stands oh I'm kind of well my legs are
up on my tail right now I have like one
leg in here M mine is legs up and then
and then like against my chest and then
lean in legs
up yeah that's my gamer stance I have
one leg kind of like tucked in and then
the other one's probably just like
dangling or it's uh it's like kneed up
or something what about you Rea do you
have a gamer stance yeah what's there's
a game or sit how you usually sit when
you game yeah I don't know I'm like too
zonked out whenever I'm so you're the
you're the peaceful
gamer yeah I apparently I have like a
bit of a gamer pose I'm always like
looking down as if I'm like slouching
but as you know I can't slouch so oh got
the good part
yeah I got that
posture yeah apparently I look like I'm
slouched over oh my favorite oh there's
a c
here I like how you went for the cactus
and ignored the
zombie oh good job
you know that sound when they like flesh
gets sliced off their body it's so
sad uhhuh it's very ASMR for me should
we do like a Gore ASMR actually you're
doing ASMR aren't
youa I did I did do ASMR in my members
yeah how did it go what did you do How
it
Go hi
[Music]
congratulations
yeah we all we all
represented they just said your name so
fast you didn't even realize yeah how do
you feel do you feel good yeah you feel
[Music]
good MK you good job good
job yeah
work really hard all
together
[Music]
looking some more cool things coming up
in
fure yeah I been strong great job
Doos thank
you let's keep do thank you for calling
[Music]
oh I have a
question yeah what's your
question what do you all want to aim for
next now we had all our girls and
everything or maybe there's
something I I think you should take a a
nice rest at some point yeah oh
uh I really want uh separate you know
you know back in the day when anime
would make Character Songs characters I
really want one character song for both
of you each
separately song yeah yeah yeah yeah
that's just like very individually about
both of you cuz obviously as Moko you're
amazing and even separately you're
amazing too and I I want to be able to
see that individuality too sh not it's
just me obviously cuz I to death that's
the saying oh
soong
individually
individually character songa character
song actually I'd like to see you guys
have like some separate streams too I
like seeing more of the
perspectives I still haven't done a Solo
solo yet still hasn't no
get on it stop being lazy no they're not
lazy
joking Bing your
body it always ends up you know it's fun
together so then
right but I was glad that you were able
to do like a Ian
recollection as like separate point of
views and all that stuff yeah we still
we still right by each other though so
it doesn't really change that much what
I think it's still changes though if you
want you can come over to my house and
I'll let you stream from my room
wow no
what no I see I thought you just I
thought you DM her just a little while
ago saying something different no I know
I'm so surprised suddenly
to I don't know you really I from my I
said
yes love
you now
it's I want to see you guys play
challenging games oh that would be
interesting
challing actually you guys are able to
play some some spooky stuff yeah do you
think we should play on my car yeah play
on my yeah oh my God that'll be hard at
least from what I
heard there's a lot of games that seem
interesting but yeah I want you guys to
go out of your comfort zone and play
game that you
necessarily like feel like oh this might
be a little difficult or o this is not a
kind of game I want you to try out new
game a soul game yeah specifically a new
game yeah doesn't doesn't have to be
Souls game but like a game that you
might think like oh this isn't like our
type of game but let's try it out anyway
that's my challenge to
you Souls game yeah monster hunter is
Monster Hunter not a type of game we
want play it's not that hard I mean it's
like grindy is Monster Hunter that I
mean the new monster hunter game is
coming out I think that's true that's
true I think we should all play it
together please please
please
CL yeah that's fine please I beg of you
I won't ask for anything else just let
me have this pleas she's lying she will
ask for other
things we should do monster hunter Club
Monster Hunter when wild comes out we
should do like we're going to go wild
weekly out but it's just Monster Hunter
yeah double challenge oh well I'll be PR
by the end of
it has to play on on my own too my own
Monster Hunter I become my
own is that a possible thing is four is
that one demon do to many unless CH
[Music]
Li M Ison and then FL is eony or the gon
what oh I talk about their armor no as
in what monster narissa is Monster I
don't even remember the monsters in
there
honestly my
favorite as long as they're cute yeah
yeah they're cute yeah cute and
deadly recently we've been more
interested in figures and Twitter was
promoted to us a monster hunter
figure a monster and I was saying to
M how could you have that next to your
cute down the wood what do you mean the
monsters are cute
[Music]
too it was like a tube with a
legs youever seen a nyante and been like
oh I want to rub his belly oh what you
what no you don't you guys cuz you
haven't played Monster Hunter yet I
can't remember there's so many monsters
in there all I know is you killed
them I'll send you my favorite monster
yeah is also my favorite M is adorable I
love no but you can take their skin and
make armor out of it o deadly only s
your favorite one through oh okay M I'll
send it to
you there you
go like a sunet mhm
yeah a little water are you calling me
pretty it looks like B is what I I
thought it look like I don't know she
called
me you are I guess you put lemonade
welcome to Trader
[Music]
lemon sign at
lemony oh I should start selling that as
you
doing
tasty
CFE oh
ready yeah no this is squiding
pasta blueberry we cute not pretty what
I'm B excuse me I absolutely disagree
with that you know I know said I'm both
but I heard it I'm bald
Noe that I heard both you you can be
cute and pretty thank you you both at
the same time yeah same
time yes you can be all at once okay
yeah yeah is also cute and pretty and
[Music]
sexy congratulations everything thank
you con we're so proud of you yeah
congrats
[Music]
okay
byebye
bye oh I guess uh we're going
back yeah I guess
so oh oh
[\h__\h] wrong one wrong one well what's
going on
Gamers
hello yeah hello hello hi
yeah it has been completed but oh good
you should let me craft things because I
have the highest skill ah yeah you're
the one that can do it but every piece
of armor needs two armor crafting kits
and then 10 claw [\h__\h] fragments I have a
couple of these things but barely enough
right now I see especially like armor
crafting kits and I can make armor
crafting kits but then I would need uh
like more duct tape for example I need a
lot more duct tape okay oh I see so if
you guys have either duct tape or I
think I had some duct tape in my uh I
have need a duct tape though to make a
baseball bat
or buy it uh could you put it in the
Discord server so we know what to give
you and we'll just put in your box if
you could label it okay you were doing
vehicle too right I have four vehicle
magazines o nice
see that um there are some legendary
Parts in here you actually need those to
craft the strongest version of whatever
weapon you have so the strongest version
of the club level six you need one
legendary part and then the basic Club
just so you guys know what that's for
I'm going to make a baseball bat so I
don't necessarily need a legendary Club
but I'm just letting you know that's
what the parts are for
[Music]
okay yeah shotgun weekly let's go where
are you I got a B you're there ah yeah
take magazines if you B you want to go
together to base again to drop our crap
or do you want to go I want to go to I
want to go back to the quest Quest or
not the quest Quest the new house I want
go to the new house I have oh am i m now
you're here now you're here yeah I have
uh something for you I think want oh you
do oh well I give it to you now that you
here before I leave oh I am not I am not
at the house yet you can put it in a
chest though and then I'll grab it if
you you go it does says that you right
there next to oh no wait no no sorry
that's wor never mind yeah I'm pretty
far but you can put in a chest or
something okay okay what is
it h no it's nothing it's just like a
Knife Guy the magazine oh yes she's
going to shank even harder people where
are you
right now I have a oh we're at like the
the desert or something we're coming
back to we're coming to the the the new
house though we're coming to I got stuff
for you too Kiara hold on hi you in the
house oh good gosh why is it so hard to
control a
bike by the way how does the bike take
damage is it like if you fall or
something no I it's it um it rally redu
it its durability as you use it doix the
main thing I wanted to give you I think
I don't know yet thank oh no I've never
I've never taken care of a bike
before how do you do that I'll press
X yeah Scream It's kind of romantic
here small
raid maybe looks like a small is coming
[Music]
already are a lot of
them I will help
you I'm punch let's
go hi BS
hello look at us having a nice romantic
bike ride
together yeah in the
forest Canada yeah
yeah these dreamers these ones
oh yeah it's a peaceful peaceful
existence in Canada and uh she just
killed
someone so
peaceful yeah the most peaceful
loot I wonder if these guys drop a ton
of loot I got one they're not really
dropping much at all except exp which is
good drop something you
fools leaving my bike behind here yeah
hit him yeah I got him with the they
I'll park my bike next to yours here we
go oh
okay I'll leave it here hello need a
farm who that lady
look all right
right there extremely strong now
lock okay I locked
mine I think I need to go now everyone
thank so okay thanks for playing with us
for playing thanks for playing bye bye
bye bye
byebye see you next
[Music]
time okay you made everything respawn so
was awesome
excuse all our
loot
yeah byebye everyone see
byee KY you got a bicycle too yeah I got
a bike and we met the new Trader there's
a new trador yeah she's nicer too as she
kisses
you she could kiss you if you if you um
what is it if you get
a bike and tier 2 quest uh you can talk
to the guy and he'll give you a special
dialogue to see like special Quest and
then he'll give you a quest to visit the
new TR
o excuse me you're blocking the uh the
entrance or maybe I should just widen
the entrance Quest F yes thank you okay
I'm at the start Point okay we go I
failed the quest oh it took too long
guess I'm just looking do we not have
any lever at
home lever maybe I can make
it you're so smart but
no ST for you okay here's vehicle
leather we do have leather um here's
rifle thank
you I have 100
leather 100 yes
I'll give it to you in just a moment I
have to run through the old house really
quick to get duct tape I'll bring my
duct tap soon do you have a storage uh
in here Kiara yes mine's over here uh in
the living room ceing okay I'll just TR
find it as long as it's named over here
okay okay it's not named all right I
I'll name it for you it's okay I got it
oh thank you
no wow the archiv are doing archiving
things
by the way we did um plant the super
corn yeah yeah yeah it's planted it
should be growing or done growing
hopefully I think I might have messed it
up cuz I punched it and I only no no no
it should Harvest it um seeds are 50% on
whether you get it or
not but you should punch it right I can
you can punch it yeah farmer
yeah I mean you don't SE turn guaranteed
it's like 50% depending on your level
probably so punch away as long as it
says it's not
growing for now should we all get into
the same party do you think okay
yeah H you're leader right now so I
think you can do
that yeah I can make a
lantern do we have a C the table down
yet or no yes yes it's in the kitchen in
the
kitchen but you want to make armor then
you should probably leave it to me I
think I can make weapons with it to is
this scary outside probably it's a
little it's night time it seems
scary ah she's
running
oh oh yes our spiky house spiky house
it's very
powerful very hard to get into for
zombies and
R
hair no she is already wearing the
farmer out the farmer I know are you
yeah I'm wearing
it it's scary I don't have a random door
here I have candles here I'll put in the
mood
lighting I can H I can make ammo wait
are you girls doing the Pet Quest right
now I I can make supp Quest I'm coming
over
okay the clear the area what do I put
on the supplies Quest
oh well I'll just go where you are okay
I can make I can make all types of ammo
now really I how to put the stone uh I I
have the still for it I guess
[Music]
oh ammo for
everybody oh
zombies owie guess you can only put on
surfaces but you didn't start the quest
yet did you no just killing them in here
okay
okay almost
[Music]
there so easy when I have such a strong
fist on my side that's o
oops pumpkins there's some good stuff in
these
cabinets I can make pumpkin bread nice
pumpkin bread looks so good in the game
that I went out and bought ingredients
to make pumpkin bread in real life and
pum oh this is the guy it made you so
hungry it did I had to have it in real
life
can we come over and have some that
sounds so good
yay pumpin bread yeah about to head to
some of you guys I see you're doing a
quest he's fast oh you're doing a class
I can join you yeah yeah I see um most
of them there too by the way uh myy
don't you have to add everyone into the
same party I'm trying to I sent the
request okay or we can just span and
join theirs whichever work
oh in the quest right now so you have to
wait yeah okay I'll just join that then
yeah let's merch and Quest together
since I think there's five of us oh crap
I I failed a quest oh it's cuz we
dropped the party I guess yeah oh that's
fine that's fine that'll happen let find
our supplies I found I forgot my bike
that's not mine so there's a biker gang
in here I forgot my bike I'm already
running they all
upstairs oh I'm
hungry so anyway I started
blasting oh can you guys add me to the
party me too please I think
mid what you mean our are we waiting
yeah yeah cuz you guys are in the same
location as I am you're sker
Place yeah yeah yeah darn
skery zombie I he
I think since you guys already
started you a pretty lady around the
corner there's a courier satel here one
of yours it might be
mine oh I just got an invite okay uh I
don't think so upstairs I forgot we were
on a quest again iing and punching I
think there must be an attic cuz I think
mine's
down all right I'll wait for you beibs
okay I'm coming yeah you still got to
get the the invite
anyway in here look at you and your bike
I had a walk here just like the olden
daysie I thought you had a bike that a
oh I I left it oh I left it near Yours
by accident
what they they already
started oh let me flat in there oh yeah
oh uh
sorry should be crate o murky water nice
a kitty there's a cat picture in here a
different one the same as before
different
one A orange cat's
Behavior new stone spear
oh okay found
[Music]
mine oh nice oh my God what a cute cat I
know is there attic I'm so upset we
can't take the cat pictures and decorate
our house yeah I was going to steal some
lovecraftian
thing I'm not sure if yours is up here
too but in the Attic that where we were
make a new
party there's a
um
careful oh basement yeah sure
like upstairs
again on a really high
shell oh weren we
mering I think they already started so
we have to do our own thing W for them
to finish their Quest okay it there's
like a respawn time when we were tring
your quest it made us wait like 2 hours
hours in game yeah should we do
something else then besides this
one
um you see I don't have I don't have oh
I see one yours okay yeah I see yours I
don't think maybe I have to break it
what we going just do this one I have to
break the kitchen to get my stue oh
found it yeah found it yeah we can we
can do this one for you after they
finish and then we can move yeah okay
how about we do yours yours is like
right there and near
myy oh true we are pretty close yeah I'm
heading
there you have the F we're dring yes oh
yeah uh the animated short is about to
start we can also join if you would like
to check out the official challenge for
Thea it is there yeah turned the quest
of the Trad yet not yet you need do that
or
else so please be sure to check out the
thing and take a view on it have the
quest in the meantime I will just head
over hither and chill and
relax
yeah okay we can wait okay I'm at the
Harrison residence if you want to do
your thing otherwise I'll just
uh um I have a bike at home it's my bike
it's my pink bite what a cute bite thank
you ah empty hand
[Laughter]
forgot don't look okay now you can look
I'm watching I'm
watching I'm watching I'm
watching pretty good pretty good pretty
good driving skill yes watch watch me
drift dri I'm drifting look I'm already
see it I hope you
enjoy oh my go she's crazy I'm so crazy
with that she's driving on the inside
yeah all maybe I'll just
uh R tracing
R Tracy so long she's not disgracing
us I'm intim I'm try to look into the
thing for it I can't even oh here it is
okay swag it's like it's like 2 minutes
or something I don't know if it's really
worth doing it but check out that link
yeah woo green
one I hope I hope you enjoy it wait know
you do have I do have my hair out
oopsies should be yeah I know I was just
I don't know I thought you were behind G
or so let's see all right I hope you
like it I think they did a great job on
it and then we can
combine we
back well we'll wait to start any quests
until we combine so that way we can all
do our Quest together
yeah I'll head
to by the way Kelly did you like
actually I can slow redirect even though
it ended probably okay let's just do
that I'm going to go ahead and end it
here so I'll see you guys like next time
yeah
byebye
bye okay uh go go enjoy it yeah I have
um and don't forget I have my thing
tomorrow so if you're meeting and
greeting I will meet and greet with you
and we have the panel
with so I'll go ahead and send you guys
off since and U make sure to leave a
nice comment okay they worked very hard
on that and they're working hard on
other things most likely that I assume
coming up soon so in the meantime sh
thank you thank you for watching me
today I'll see you next week woo
[Music]