​​​ ​You don't want to see an idol​ ​​
​​ ​putting on this many calories...​ ​​
​​​ ​Today we'll be revealing​ ​​
​​ ​everyone's top-secret food habits!​ ​​
​​​ ​​​ ​​
​​​ ​695 kcal! Nice, nice!​ ​​
​​​ ​I didn't know it had that many...​ ​​
​​​ ​Guess the calorie count​ ​​
​​ ​of foods you've eaten!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ignorance is no excuse!​ ​​
​​ ​This is the Calorie Count Game Show!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hold on.​ ​​
​​​ ​This was way more than I expected.​ ​​
​​​ ​Extra oil, extra firm noodles,​ ​​
​​ ​extra thick broth...​ ​​
​​​ ​Witness this menu of gluttony!​ ​​
​​​ ​Food choices revealed!​ ​​
​​​ ​Will they be okay eating all of this?!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm feeling famished,​ ​​
​​​ ​so yes, I'll have everything.​ ​​
​​​ ​Real pics, real food!​ ​​
​​ ​Let's guess their exact calorie count!​ ​​
​​​ ​Nail Your Calorie Choices!​ ​​
​​​ ​hololive English -Myth-​ ​​
​​ ​Takanashi Kiara​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm hungry....​ ​​
​​​ ​I want some ramen!​ ​​
​​​ ​2nd Gen​ ​​
​​ ​Yuzuki Choco​ ​​
​​​ ​I wanna slurp a nice, big bowl.​ ​​
​​​ ​1st Gen​ ​​
​​ ​Aki Rosenthal​ ​​
​​​ ​Same here!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hello! Hello!​ ​​
​​​ ​You girls, over there!​ ​​
​​​ ​Thinking about food all day​ ​​
​​​ ​I want ramen.​ ​​
​​​ ​won't make you into a​ ​​
​​ ​top-class image-conscious talent!​ ​​
​​​ ​Why?​ ​​
​​​ ​What?​ ​​
​​​ ​I never really thought of​ ​​
​​ ​becoming one, though.​ ​​
​​​ ​That's beside the point!​ ​​
​​​ ​If you're even a bit​ ​​
​​ ​conscious about your image,​ ​​
​​​ ​then naturally, you'd be thinking​ ​​
​​ ​about the calories you eat, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​To be quite honest, I haven't really​ ​​
​​​ ​thought about calories until today.​ ​​
​​​ ​Until today?​ ​​
​​​ ​For this episode, the girls will​ ​​
​​ ​guess how many calories are there​ ​​
​​​ ​in the food that they eat,​ ​​
​​ ​while aiming for a total of 2,023 kcal!​ ​​
​​​ ​This looks high-calorie!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's pick healthy!​ ​​
​​​ ​All-you-can-eat time!​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara's onigiri​ ​​
​​​ ​They can choose any number​ ​​
​​ ​of everyone's dishes!​ ​​
​​​ ​Choco's pasta​ ​​
​​​ ​Aki's salad​ ​​
​​​ ​But if they go over 2,023 kcal,​ ​​
​​ ​it's all over!​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't trip up at the finish line!​ ​​
​​​ ​Stop!​ ​​
​​​ ​First off,​ ​​
​​​ ​let's look at everyone's picks!​ ​​
​​​ ​Most of Choco-sensei's​ ​​
​​​ ​are all foreign-sounding foods...​ ​​
​​​ ​They all sound chic!​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara-chan's menu​ ​​
​​​ ​has quite a lot of fish.​ ​​
​​ ​I thought she most ate chicken...​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, you're right!​ ​​
​​​ ​Look at the fourth one!​ ​​
​​​ ​It says "fried chicken pasta"!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, it is there.​ ​​
​​​ ​Come on now.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's start with Aki-san's choices.​ ​​
​​​ ​Round 1​ ​​
​​ ​Aki Rosenthal's Calorie Choices​ ​​
​​​ ​Time to start with what I know!​ ​​
​​​ ​Picking high calories​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll start with the tonkotsu ramen!​ ​​
​​​ ​Tonkotsu ramen with English members​ ​​
​​​ ​She went for Kiara's tonkotsu ramen!​ ​​
​​​ ​So I took this picture with​ ​​
​​ ​the English -Myth- girls here in Japan.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ate with English -Myth- while in Japan​ ​​
​​​ ​This was taken at a certain​ ​​
​​ ​Ichir*n ramen shop!​ ​​
​​​ ​Gura-chan never had​ ​​
​​ ​real ramen up till then,​ ​​
​​​ ​First ramen experience​ ​​
​​​ ​For real?!​ ​​
​​​ ​so she was pretty nervous​ ​​
​​ ​about the whole experience.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm nervous...​ ​​
​​​ ​Understandable.​ ​​
​​​ ​You'll be fine!​ ​​
​​​ ​She was like that​ ​​
​​ ​even at the convenience stores.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yep.​ ​​
​​​ ​That's cute...​ ​​
​​​ ​I really love tonkotsu ramen,​ ​​
​​​ ​LOVES TONKOTSU​ ​​
​​​ ​but iekei ramen is where it's at.​ ​​
​​​ ​Extra oil, extra firm noodles,​ ​​
​​ ​extra thick broth...​ ​​
​​​ ​That sounds nice.​ ​​
​​​ ​I treat tonkotsu ramen​ ​​
​​ ​as a fancy beverage.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm guessing it's at 555 kcal!​ ​​
​​​ ​555? Okay...​ ​​
​​​ ​Hmm?​ ​​
​​​ ​The calorie count for​ ​​
​​ ​tonkotsu ramen is...​ ​​
​​​ ​Calorie count data does not​ ​​
​​ ​constitute professional research.​ ​​
​​​ ​630 kcal!​ ​​
​​​ ​You're in that ballpark!​ ​​
​​​ ​I guess so!​ ​​
​​​ ​I thought it was at 900 kcal.​ ​​
​​​ ​900 kcal?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's move on to Choco-sensei!​ ​​
​​​ ​Round 1​ ​​
​​ ​Yuzuki Choco's Calorie Choices​ ​​
​​​ ​I pick Kiara-sama's​ ​​
​​ ​tuna margherita pizza.​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara's Tuna Margherita Pizza​ ​​
​​​ ​Alright!​ ​​
​​​ ​What is this thing?!​ ​​
​​ ​Alright!​ ​​
​​​ ​Now that's an image.​ ​​
​​​ ​That's one way to use corn.​ ​​
​​​ ​My idea was​ ​​
​​​ ​High-calorie pick​ ​​
​​​ ​that pizza had a lot of calories.​ ​​
​​​ ​Th-This one's homemade...​ ​​
​​​ ​You made it?​ ​​
​​​ ​Wow!​ ​​
​​​ ​I made this one during a stream.​ ​​
​​​ ​Looks delicious.​ ​​
​​​ ​I thought putting corn on​ ​​
​​ ​the crust would be a good flavor.​ ​​
​​​ ​I see.​ ​​
​​​ ​Nice!​ ​​
​​​ ​* Depiction​ ​​
​​​ ​I bought a pizza oven for this too.​ ​​
​​​ ​That's pretty cool!​ ​​
​​​ ​And it turned out really great.​ ​​
​​​ ​I guess it's around... 680 kcal?​ ​​
​​​ ​Mm-hmm, I see.​ ​​
​​​ ​The correct answer is...​ ​​
​​​ ​669 kcal! Amazing!​ ​​
​​​ ​Your guess was very close.​ ​​
​​​ ​Next up is Kiara-san!​ ​​
​​​ ​Round 1​ ​​
​​ ​Takanashi Kiara's Calorie Choices​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm gonna pick the beef stroganoff.​ ​​
​​​ ​Beef stroganoff!​ ​​
​​​ ​Beef Stroganoff of Bliss​ ​​
​​​ ​So tempting...​ ​​
​​​ ​I made this with Lui-sama.​ ​​
​​​ ​Made during a Rich Chocolat collab stream​ ​​
​​​ ​There's a ton of butter in this.​ ​​
​​​ ​Has lots of butter​ ​​
​​​ ​I think we added a bunch of spices too...​ ​​
​​​ ​I see...​ ​​
​​​ ​No roux went into making this.​ ​​
​​​ ​Is that so?​ ​​
​​​ ​We only used fresh ingredients.​ ​​
​​​ ​Made fresh with real herbs and spices​ ​​
​​​ ​Whoa, impressive.​ ​​
​​​ ​I wanna dig in...​ ​​
​​​ ​Have you ever made beef stroganoff?​ ​​
​​​ ​Whenever I think about doing it,​ ​​
​​ ​it becomes hayashi rice instead.​ ​​
​​​ ​I can totally see how that happens.​ ​​
​​​ ​I really don't have a clue,​ ​​
​​​ ​but I'm guessing 650 kcal.​ ​​
​​​ ​650 kcal. Okay!​ ​​
​​​ ​The beef stroganoff clocks in at...​ ​​
​​​ ​699 kcal! Spot on!​ ​​
​​​ ​Not that big of a difference.​ ​​
​​​ ​Nice one!​ ​​
​​​ ​Thanks.​ ​​
​​​ ​Time to dig in.​ ​​
​​​ ​For the first round, everyone went high-calorie,​ ​​
​​ ​with an average of around 600 kcal!​ ​​
​​​ ​For the second round, they will each pick​ ​​
​​ ​two dishes to get closer to 2,023 kcal!​ ​​
​​​ ​Aki-san, please pick two dishes!​ ​​
​​​ ​Round 2​ ​​
​​ ​Aki Rosenthal's Calorie Choices​ ​​
​​​ ​Making me pick two​ ​​
​​ ​might make me go over...​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's go with Choco-sensei's​ ​​
​​​ ​Hamburg steak, and my own...​ ​​
​​​ ​glass noodle salad!​ ​​
​​​ ​Mmm, alright!​ ​​
​​​ ​You're going for a main dish​ ​​
​​ ​and healthy side combo.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, that's my goal.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay then.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's take a look at the Hamburg steak!​ ​​
​​​ ​Special Hamburg steak​ ​​
​​​ ​Looks quite delish!​ ​​
​​ ​It even has veggies!​ ​​
​​​ ​Is this all homemade, Choco-san?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes, it is.​ ​​
​​​ ​That makes it even better.​ ​​
​​​ ​Nice, nice! Very nice!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yuzuki Choco's homemade Hamburg steak​ ​​
​​​ ​Is that a ketchup I see?​ ​​
​​​ ​It's a demiglace sauce.​ ​​
​​​ ​Demiglace? It is!​ ​​
​​​ ​This is the glass noodle salad.​ ​​
​​​ ​AkiRose-style glass noodle salad​ ​​
​​​ ​This is one of​ ​​
​​​ ​my specialties, actually.​ ​​
​​​ ​That's nice to hear.​ ​​
​​​ ​The other day,​ ​​
​​​ ​I made one bowl of the salad,​ ​​
​​ ​which was way too much.​ ​​
​​​ ​I ended up taking a pic of it in the bowl.​ ​​
​​​ ​And you posted it.​ ​​
​​​ ​Guess how many calories are in each.​ ​​
​​​ ​How many kilocalories are​ ​​
​​ ​in the Hamburg steak?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll put it at around 450 kcal.​ ​​
​​​ ​Alright. As for the glass noodle...​ ​​
​​​ ​The glass noodle salad​ ​​
​​ ​would be around 180 kcal.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's check the Hamburg steak first.​ ​​
​​​ ​It clocks in at 350 kcal!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's healthier than I thought!​ ​​
​​​ ​As for the glass noodle salad...​ ​​
​​​ ​it's at 99 kcal! It's not a lot!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's low!​ ​​
​​​ ​AkiRose's guess​ ​​
​​​ ​Actual answer​ ​​
​​​ ​That's a huge gap...​ ​​
​​​ ​It kinda is.​ ​​
​​​ ​Aki-san has racked up 1,079 kcal!​ ​​
​​​ ​I feel like​ ​​
​​​ ​I can push a bit harder for this one.​ ​​
​​​ ​I pick Aki-sama's​ ​​
​​ ​beef and veggie chop suey rice​ ​​
​​​ ​and my own eggplant bolognese.​ ​​
​​​ ​Sounds good.​ ​​
​​​ ​A real garden of carbs and meat.​ ​​
​​​ ​\{Restaurant Eggplant Bolognese​ ​​
​​ ​Much Yum Beef Chop Suey Rice!​ ​​
​​​ ​Rice​ ​​
​​​ ​Pasta​ ​​
​​​ ​Meat​ ​​
​​​ ​This is the beef and veggie chop suey rice.​ ​​
​​​ ​Much Yum Beef Chop Suey Rice!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh dear, this looks like a calorie bomb!​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait, hold on.​ ​​
​​​ ​This was way more than I expected.​ ​​
​​​ ​It certainly is a lot.​ ​​
​​​ ​For real?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Is this one also homemade?​ ​​
​​​ ​Aki-san?​ ​​
​​​ ​So actually,​ ​​
​​​ ​I bought this at a Chinese-style restaurant.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ooh, makes sense.​ ​​
​​​ ​I see.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm gonna guess this is​ ​​
​​ ​around 580-600 kcal...​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's take a look at the next one.​ ​​
​​​ ​Restaurant Eggplant Bolognese​ ​​
​​​ ​Looks really good!​ ​​
​​​ ​Was this at a restaurant?​ ​​
​​​ ​This was at a Western-style restaurant.​ ​​
​​​ ​At a restaurant too, I see.​ ​​
​​​ ​It was quite a big serving,​ ​​
​​ ​so maybe 470 kcal.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, okay.​ ​​
​​​ ​The calorie count on​ ​​
​​ ​the beef chop suey rice is at...​ ​​
​​​ ​695 kcal! Good guess!​ ​​
​​​ ​I didn't know it had that many...​ ​​
​​​ ​As for the eggplant bolognese,​ ​​
​​ ​it clocks in at...​ ​​
​​​ ​642 kcal! That's on the heavy side!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh wow! That's a lot!​ ​​
​​ ​Aren't you close to going over?​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh?​ ​​
​​​ ​Speaking of which...​ ​​
​​​ ​Current Total Count​ ​​
​​​ ​Her total count is​ ​​
​​​ ​2,006 kcal!​ ​​
​​​ ​Way too close!​ ​​
​​​ ​Seriously? No way!​ ​​
​​​ ​I would like to stop myself right here!​ ​​
​​​ ​Understood.​ ​​
​​ ​You won't need to play anymore.​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara-san, please pick two dishes!​ ​​
​​​ ​Round 2​ ​​
​​ ​Takanashi Kiara's Calorie Choices​ ​​
​​​ ​I wanna pick something high-calorie,​ ​​
​​​ ​so I'll go with Aki-senpai's olive oil chicken​ ​​
​​​ ​Olive oil chicken and...?​ ​​
​​​ ​and my own galette.​ ​​
​​​ ​The galette!​ ​​
​​​ ​Show Aki-san's chicken thighs​ ​​
​​ ​in olive oil, please!​ ​​
​​​ ​Addictive chicken thighs in olive oil​ ​​
​​​ ​That's what it looks like.​ ​​
​​​ ​This looks pretty healthy!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oddly healthy​ ​​
​​​ ​Take your chicken and fry it​ ​​
​​​ ​1) Fry skin-on chicken thighs​ ​​
​​ ​in olive oil.​ ​​
​​​ ​in olive oil, skin and all.​ ​​
​​​ ​With the skin on?​ ​​
​​​ ​2) Add salt to taste.​ ​​
​​​ ​Then season with salt after. Simple food.​ ​​
​​​ ​DONE​ ​​
​​​ ​I can see this tasting very good.​ ​​
​​​ ​Simply delicious.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll put it at 250 kcal.​ ​​
​​​ ​Here is the galette.​ ​​
​​​ ​Deliciously yummy galette​ ​​
​​​ ​That looks nice.​ ​​
​​​ ​Is this for breakfast or for lunch?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah this for break― Erm, err―​ ​​
​​​ ​I woke up past noon but​ ​​
​​ ​I felt like having a breakfast.​ ​​
​​​ ​Something like a brunch.​ ​​
​​​ ​Was this homemade?​ ​​
​​​ ​I had this at a place in Shinjuku.​ ​​
​​​ ​I see, I see.​ ​​
​​​ ​It was surprisingly filling,​ ​​
​​​ ​so... 400 kcal, maybe?​ ​​
​​​ ​400 kcal, got it.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's show the correct answers.​ ​​
​​​ ​The (salted) olive oil chicken has...​ ​​
​​​ ​287 kcal! Quite close!​ ​​
​​​ ​You're almost at the bullseye.​ ​​
​​​ ​As for the galette, its calorie count is...​ ​​
​​​ ​Bring it! Bring it on!​ ​​
​​​ ​437 kcal!​ ​​
​​​ ​This brings us a total of​ ​​
​​ ​1423 kcal! Not bad!​ ​​
​​​ ​Current Total Count​ ​​
​​​ ​Still a bit far...​ ​​
​​​ ​Why don't you both pick​ ​​
​​ ​one at the same time?​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yep.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ready, set...​ ​​
​​​ ​Fried chicken pasta!​ ​​
​​​ ​Cotton candy!​ ​​
​​​ ​Aki-san picked the fried chicken pasta.​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara-san went for the cotton candy.​ ​​
​​​ ​It really is fried chicken over pasta!​ ​​
​​​ ​This one was homemade.​ ​​
​​​ ​Compared to the average fried chicken,​ ​​
​​​ ​Average​ ​​
​​ ​fried chicken​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara​ ​​
​​ ​Fried Chicken​ ​​
​​​ ​It does look healthier for you.​ ​​
​​​ ​this one's cooked to be a bit healthier.​ ​​
​​​ ​Does this use chicken breast?​ ​​
​​​ ​I think it was breast, yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​Chicken breast, huh?​ ​​
​​​ ​Breast + no skin = healthy food​ ​​
​​​ ​There's no skin on it either.​ ​​
​​​ ​So it is healthier!​ ​​
​​​ ​Since it's a pasta, I'd put it at 650 kcal!​ ​​
​​​ ​650 kcal!​ ​​
​​​ ​Is it, really?​ ​​
​​​ ​Next up is the cotton candy!​ ​​
​​​ ​Cotton Candy​ ​​
​​​ ​Ah, it's this one!​ ​​
​​​ ​WataMerino!​ ​​
​​​ ​At the bottom...​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey, there's something...​ ​​
​​ ​At the bottom...​ ​​
​​​ ​I can see some meat down there!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yep!​ ​​
​​​ ​This came with a lamb hotpot.​ ​​
​​​ ​Lamb!​ ​​
​​​ ​That makes sense.​ ​​
​​​ ​It was a collab, after all.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm guessing 300 kcal?​ ​​
​​​ ​Meat + Cotton Candy combined​ ​​
​​​ ​A total of 300 kcal for everything, okay.​ ​​
​​​ ​Aki-san's fried chicken over​ ​​
​​ ​basil and spring onion pasta is...​ ​​
​​​ ​647 kcal! Pretty much on point!​ ​​
​​​ ​As for Kiara-san's pick...​ ​​
​​​ ​it's at 277 kcal! A good prediction.​ ​​
​​​ ​Calorie count data does not​ ​​
​​ ​constitute professional research.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's look at the current total counts.​ ​​
​​​ ​1,726 and 1,700 kcal!​ ​​
​​ ​We're in for a close match!​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait, wait!​ ​​
​​​ ​We're so close!​ ​​
​​​ ​Almost the same.​ ​​
​​​ ​If Aki-san goes over 300 kcal...​ ​​
​​​ ​Current total: 1726 kcal​ ​​
​​​ ​I'd... be out...​ ​​
​​​ ​she'd be eliminated.​ ​​
​​​ ​I would suggest for​ ​​
​​​ ​Current total​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara-sama to go for​ ​​
​​ ​the low-calorie options.​ ​​
​​​ ​That would make sense.​ ​​
​​​ ​Please don't remind me...​ ​​
​​​ ​Aki-san can probably go for two more.​ ​​
​​​ ​Current total​ ​​
​​​ ​She does have the room for extra.​ ​​
​​​ ​I might as well pig out!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll go for the strawberry milk​ ​​
​​ ​and Aki-senpai's mapo tofu.​ ​​
​​​ ​Mapo tofu and strawberry milk, got it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Are you sure?​ ​​
​​​ ​That's quite the combo.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ah, umm...​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara-sama? Earth to Kiara-sama?​ ​​
​​​ ​Is this over 300 kcal?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll be taking the apple pie​ ​​
​​ ​and oven-baked fish!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's like she's in a restaurant.​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't you want to​ ​​
​​ ​think this through, Kiara-sama?​ ​​
​​​ ​Should I? I'll take off​ ​​
​​ ​the strawberry milk then.​ ​​
​​​ ​Just the strawberry milk?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll stick with the mapo tofu.​ ​​
​​ ​No more milk.​ ​​
​​​ ​No strawberry milk? Okay!​ ​​
​​​ ​I had to chicken out.​ ​​
​​​ ​So do we have any​ ​​
​​ ​strawberry milk available?​ ​​
​​ ​I had to chicken out.​ ​​
​​​ ​So do we have any​ ​​
​​ ​strawberry milk available?​ ​​
​​​ ​A full meal with a drink?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes, with a drink please.​ ​​
​​​ ​Umm...​ ​​
​​​ ​Are you sure you're ordering all of that?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm feeling famished,​ ​​
​​​ ​so yes, I'll have everything.​ ​​
​​​ ​I guess she's going for it!​ ​​
​​​ ​No way! All of it?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's look at Aki-san's picks.​ ​​
​​​ ​Aki Rosenthal's Calorie Choices​ ​​
​​​ ​This one is the apple pie.​ ​​
​​​ ​Apple Pie​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh...​ ​​
​​​ ​It's two apple pies on top of each other,​ ​​
​​​ ​A stack?​ ​​
​​​ ​topped with vanilla ice cream​ ​​
​​ ​and whipped cream.​ ​​
​​​ ​A honey sauce is then​ ​​
​​ ​drizzled on top.​ ​​
​​​ ​Why isn't the ice cream in the name?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's next look at the strawberry milk.​ ​​
​​​ ​Strawberry Milk​ ​​
​​ ​Recently Addicted to​ ​​
​​​ ​Strawberry milk.​ ​​
​​​ ​This has more than it looks.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's the typical convenience store​ ​​
​​ ​strawberry milk.​ ​​
​​​ ​Finally, the next dish.​ ​​
​​​ ​You'll regret this.​ ​​
​​​ ​That's a lot on the plate!​ ​​
​​​ ​Whoa, that looks good!​ ​​
​​​ ​I want to eat it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Once again,​ ​​
​​​ ​I cooked this one myself.​ ​​
​​​ ​The fish sits on top of a bed​ ​​
​​ ​of mashed potatoes,​ ​​
​​​ ​and the stuff around it is zucchini.​ ​​
​​​ ​All of them combined should be...​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll let you guess.​ ​​
​​​ ​The shapes of the lemon and zucchini​ ​​
​​ ​look like zeroes.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm calling it.​ ​​
​​ ​Those ones are zero calories!​ ​​
​​​ ​Effectively 0 kcal​ ​​
​​​ ​Zero calorie, you say?​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's look at your final total calorie count.​ ​​
​​​ ​Final Calorie Count Reveal​ ​​
​​​ ​Will it be under 2,023 kcal? Let's find out.​ ​​
​​​ ​Would it?​ ​​
​​​ ​Would it? Here's the answer.​ ​​
​​​ ​3,058 kcal.​ ​​
​​​ ​Calorie Overcount!​ ​​
​​​ ​No way!​ ​​
​​​ ​Is this amount​ ​​
​​​ ​Total​ ​​
​​​ ​not safe for idol work?​ ​​
​​​ ​These are enough calories​ ​​
​​ ​for Swolenthal!​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara-san's pick of mapo tofu​ ​​
​​ ​sits at 451 kcal!​ ​​
​​​ ​This brings her to a​ ​​
​​ ​final count of 2,151 kcal!​ ​​
​​​ ​Calorie Overcount!​ ​​
​​​ ​Which means our winner is Choco-sensei!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hooray!​ ​​
​​​ ​Congrats!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm number one! Smell y'all later!​ ​​
​​​ ​Subscribe to the hololive official​ ​​
​​ ​& our guests' channels!​ ​​
​​​ ​My muscles itch for a beating.​ ​​
​​​ ​Can we add 1,000 kcal to that?​ ​​
​​​ ​Another 1,000 kcal?!​ ​​
​​​ ​She's calling for it.​ ​​
​​​ ​She is.​ ​​
​​​ ​No? Fine.​ ​​