[Music]
so
sorry
i'm almost there
just putting on some gloves
[Music]
hey
okay
um
close your eyes
[Music]
okay
open your eyes
hello kitty
oh i forgot to put down the screen
where's my screen
uh there it is um
wait
oh
i can let you see the cat here
this is a pillow cover on top of a tiny
tiny tiny side table
um because
i um
because because i i i the table that i
used last time
um
i put it back to where it belongs
uh they want to bring that back in there
because it's pretty big now this is just
a tiny tiny tiny table
uh
not streaming from bed i wish i could do
that
uh yeah it's a pillow cover from
from guess where oops
from guess where i think this one was
from ikea
yes
[\h__\h] the cat hairs don't go away from my
gloves okay there we go i think i got
rid of it
okay
[Music]
so i'm a bit nervous about this setup
because it's my first time
uh trying it this way
it's just
sorry in
in
[Laughter]
in swedish right for
lord
for lord for lord sorry
sorry sorry sorry for lord
okay uh oh oh i forgot the music
uh
and this one this one today is on me um
me being late today is on me
because i
was
taking a last-minute
nap with my cats
but
that's because
i
just made um i just put on fresh bed
sheets and all that and and
and it was really nice and comfy i
wanted to test out the new bed sheets
so the cats were testing them out too
you know gotta test them out as soon as
possible
um
what kind of btm how about this one
the book the cooking bgm
hi is this
is this too loud is this too loud is
this too loud
yeah my cooking museum
they were chat in swedish
i would prefer if
if generally you try to
do it in english
because i don't understand what you're
saying if you're going to type in
swedish
yeah how to appreciate that
well uh everybody
will today be another
failure
or
or or or
or will today be better than last time
i mean
the last time wasn't really a failure
right it was just
let's just wait why am i recovering why
is no one saying anything about my
lightsticks
why did you don't say anything
are you dead i didn't see it you should
have said it louder
louder
god damn it
amateurs amateurs
still happy from the festival
let's do another watch along
hey kill your pen lights too late
i thought it was intentional why would i
have pen lights now
in my hands makes no sense
okay so today we are doing a
swedish sweden
snack box review
and the picture on it i think is already
supposed to kind of
depict what sweden is like this is
totally 100 sweden man
i mean
this is
maybe maybe
how it looks on the countryside
um in winter time uh probably about
300 years ago
200 years ago me
[Music]
i don't know how do you know it's not
that's exactly a good
good argument okay i don't know
but the the the little ship
i
you know what no the little ship is 100
accurate what i'm saying is that the
elks
the elks are the hint
because elks only existed until 300
years ago and then after that there were
no more elks yes
yeah did you not know that
amateurs amateurs
vikings
on the other side still exist and that
is the main transportation method method
in sweden using
uh viking boats i'm just kidding okay
okay
so we started like last time we're gonna
use this little booklet to tell us a
little bit about sweden first okay and
then we snack
and then we
[Music]
and then after that we're gonna have a
little little test a little quiz
maybe we know more things about sweden
than we did about guatemala
it's true though is it oh my god
[Music]
um
so did you know that wait no let's say
the other way what is the capital of
sweden
[Music]
stockholm
correct everybody
the
language they speak there is
[Music]
swedish correct
apparently there's about 10.2 million
people living in all of sweden
and they actually
are also one of those super special
countries in europe which said no [\h__\h]
you to the euro because they use swedish
crowns because they need to be special
yeah
so if you want to go as a european to
sweden
don't shoot dare think that they're
gonna use your dirty dirty dirty ugly
euros no
they don't give a [\h__\h] about our euros
no they will take only an only
swedish crowds
oh
interesting what is
uh
typically swedish it says here for three
or four things
uh
cinnamon buns not buns but like the this
i guess i guess there are also buns the
swirly it says tim schneider so swirly's
um
cinnamon buns in the form of a
of a snail
basically i don't think
[Music]
i didn't notice
i didn't know this but i like cinnamon
buns
[Music]
um
and apparently
wait what's the word for this
in english
[Music]
i'm typing with one hand for some reason
uh
[Music]
stupid chihuahua
crime
novel books
are
for some reason
typically swedish according to this
pamphlet swedish people where are you
what is that about
crime novels that's a thing really
was are you swedish
i know you were swedish
[Music]
very true really
really
i don't know what to believe it's a
thing really
really
[Music]
what
okay i mean it must be true everything
that this company writes in their
pamphlet is true
and another thing
uh
is alex
which was on the on the front of the
uh pamphlet and another thing i'm
looking up right now because i don't
know what it i don't think i know what
it
is ah
fika
is used as both a noun and a verb and is
derived from swedish word for coffee
it's national obsession for the
obsession for the world's third largest
coffee drinking nation
what
unlike the american style caffeine jolt
the swedish coffee break is a moment to
literally leave work behind
uh-huh
so uh fika is uh yeah coffee break
uh and the switch people are really into
it free coffee coffee
someone said fika i said fika you say
fika we say fika
what is the greatest switch invention
is it like uh
like uh
what's the word
like the
fiesta is like fiesta just with coffee
everybody
all the shops are closed except for the
coffee shops
because everybody's just drinking coffee
i don't drink coffee what am i gonna do
more chill fiesta
okay
[Music]
so
next page
uh
or sure you should let me
fold this
i will read this to you
uh no i will not read this to you i will
only read some fun facts to you
um
[Music]
18 62
sweden was the first country in the
whole wide world
to give women the
a right of voting
[Music]
of swedish people
swedes
[Music]
drink
daily coffee 82
that is really pretty high damn 82
damn
er
[Music]
[Laughter]
they are pop there are um some signs
with elks uh on it uh like maybe you can
see
these ones
um that are uh uh popular souvenirs and
are often being stolen
because i guess there's a lot of elks
there
yeah yeah that reminds me of um
in austria we don't have kangaroos
and we have signs that are basically a
sign like that
uh but with kangaroos and then
an x on top of it like no kangaroos
and that's one of our souvenirs
because people come here and it's our
joke to say haha we're not australia so
we don't have kangaroos yes
um oh
sweden has won the eurovision song
contest six times that's i think pretty
good
pretty good
[Music]
um what is this
happening
without it don't talk to stores
does that only
no that also applies to english
they're saying that the names of the
weekdays
um
the derived come from
northern mythology for example
torstag
is a first day which comes from the day
of four
[Music]
t-h-o-r ho ho
ho-ho-ho
oh
wait do all of our weekdays sound
similar in german and english montag
monday
tuesday
dean stock that one not really
wednesday midfield also not really
i wonder if this only applies to
[Music]
does this apply to
only swedish weekdays
like the names of swedish
or finnish or whatever all the northern
countries weekdays
friday it's friday okay i can hear that
wednesday weldon odin
oh
[Music]
thursday odin's day four's day freya's
day and sun's day
[Music]
applies to germanic
languages
okay and the last one is swedish vikings
did actually not have horns on their
helmet so there's a little puke drawing
there
[Music]
here they're missing them
they didn't have horns on their head
good to know
the next page is
um telling you where to go if you ever
happen to go to
sweden
number one tip is obviously the capital
stockholm uh wait that's how i say it in
german uh
you know what
[\h__\h] how you say it in english how do
you say it in swedish probably also
stockholm no
[Music]
stockholm oh no you say stockholm okay
stockholm
okay everything's written here in german
so it's a bit hard to um translate
quickly the whole uh paragraph but
[Music]
there's like a place
a
place where
abba fans can go because there's like
like a like a abba museum kind of museum
kind of
um
blah blah i don't know it's too much
text and every city uh
that they tell you to go to is umea
uh
oh because it has a lot of
trees
a lot of trees
[Music]
but specific trees burp
bee bee can
burp burp trees
[Music]
odd recommendation but umeo is nice
birch
okay
another one is
uh
[Music]
it is on the south fern beach
uh shore of sweden
uh there's a little
cute um
um um
what do you call it [\h__\h]
the tower that's shiny that shows the
boats where to go
um
and there's um yeah it's so cute it's a
cute place apparently it has a historic
charm
with an urban essence they say
lighthouse yes thank you
shiny house shiny tower
and then the fourth stop they want you
to go is guterbolg
sweden's second biggest city
is
a cultural center
uh
is in good book and
oh they have the biggest uh
[\h__\h]
english doko
wait
i will not ask you guys i'll ask my
translator
they have the biggest hardboard
in the country okay
and um
yeah
blah blah blah
cool stuff
oh there's some people saying it's
better than sweden
oh get the book represent oh
okay next page is that already the snack
page or am i too stupid to open the page
in between no this seems to be the next
page okay
um
now
we have one two three four
five six seven eight nine snacks
okay
um
let's just get into it
and i want my swedish friends to tell me
whether or not this is something popular
and common in sweden uh and if this is
specifically from sweden but for me to
be honest in order to make this snack
box a success in my opinion it doesn't
have to be
a snack specifically created
uh originated from sweden
i would just be happy if it's actually
something the swedish people like to eat
there or drink or whatever
um
but yeah um
we got you covered okay okay okay
[Music]
um
well first of all let's start with a
drink they always put a drink in there
and this one is a
strawberry drink
soccer fruit sugar-free that i'm 100
sure that means sugar-free single york
called yard good you're good probably
means strawberry because it's strawberry
drinks what do you say about this one
they know jingle
don't say it's from mexico
though
zingo is a classic wonderful okay
okay
oh yeah so we have a permanent sparkling
sprinkling
um but sugar free
strawberry juice
[Music]
it's not mexico come on
i don't know
is it originally from sweden
it's a classic but i don't like it okay
well that's your problem sounds like a
you problem
uh sugar one is better
okay well
let me open it i'm having problems
opening it with my gloves let me use my
scissors
okay why the [\h__\h]
oh
good smell
what's your
okay
let's uh
come by
kanpai
[Music]
very good very good
very good um
10 out of 10
[Music]
easy
easy rating ah
uh light
cheers how do you pronounce it school
school school ah so when there's a
little circle on top of the a it's kind
of like an o pronounced okay school
school
okay 10 yeah this is a 10 out of 10.
that's good because we have to refresh
our mouth sometimes
all right then honestly we'll start with
already with a snack
the drink is like a side
should i leave it on the table i don't
have that much space today on the table
uh
damn it i wanted to have things on the
table oh i'll um we'll put some snacks
on the table
um
[Music]
[\h__\h] this is um
expiration date
is
i think
over depending on how sweet if swedish
swedish people you put the day first and
the month second right
just like we do
in austria right i mean it's fine it's
probably fine i'm gonna eat it
anyway daymond yeah okay then some
um expiration date was
seven for february
but i'm gonna eat it anyway it's
probably fine
yeah the thing is that this this snack
box uh
um
should have apparently arrived way
sooner i don't know why they sent me
this one
uh because it's weird like i didn't get
the one that came after this
i ca i got the one the first one i got
from this company
was a snack box that was supposed to be
two months after the swedish snack box
that's the first one i got um and then a
couple ones later
they sent me the swedish snack box which
i checked on their website was
a little stack box from i
think in
october
[Laughter]
so back then it wouldn't have been ex
expired so let's uh
forgive them i guess but i really don't
understand why i got this one
because like the thing is after that one
should have been a korean snack box and
i never got the korean snack box that's
why i got my own korean snack books
right
yeah i i got my own i ordered those
really old korean snacks
um traditional korean snacks
and everyone was like haha boomer snacks
because i didn't get that one and then
this december snack box i'm pretty sure
it was an international snack box and
that's the first one we did on my
channel
yeah this is weird maybe the the other
thing is i think i'm missing a different
snack box that was supposed to come at
some point
so maybe they ran out of those and gave
me a leftover swedish snack box
here uh you guys can use my my crunch
cons conspiracy uh yeah perfect bakajin
you're doing it already use my
conspiracy emote here we have a usage
for it make use of it
stocks it's free real estate
[Music]
anyway what do you guys think um it's
potato chips
uh
with
um it's said it here actually um
diddle uh what's dill and schnitlow in
english
uh
you like those those stuff yeah i think
those are probably fine right i can
still eat them
oh chives and dill
chives and dill flavor is this some
some kind of like
popular flavoring
specifically popular flavor in sweden
[Music]
they're really good
is is or yeah
oh and is olw
a swedish
brand or
is it uh just a like
some neighboring countries brand
it is okay wow so far
so far
i'm impressed
so far i'm impressed okay
do you like dill um i think i do yes i
really like um
there's i don't know if you guys ever do
it in your country but there's this
salad with um
cucumbers and like a white dressing with
with dill
and that's one of my favorite salads
ever
cucumber salad with uh
dill
you know what i mean i'm trying to open
this way let me use my scissors
yeah so i think i like uh dill pretty
sure i do
that sticky also has dill okay then i
really don't have a problem with it and
i also like chives so this could be
pretty good
let's just hope that the expiration date
didn't
didn't change their flavor too much
[Music]
okay um the uh the the scent is okay i
think
also there by the way they're riffled
which i like too
okay
i have so many cat hairs on my gloves oh
man
um
i think i'm gonna take off my gloves for
a second
and secretly eat okay
okay
i'm digging in
[Music]
oh my god i love potato chips i love
salty snacks like that
[Music]
i usually always go just for basic
salt flavor like no extra flavor
i'm boring i know um
but this is really good
[Music]
oh oh god
i can't taste the
chives and the dill that strongly
um
but
it is there i think there's some taste
it's like not super super super super
strong
um
yeah but it is it is there mm-hmm
[Music]
hmm
someone stopped me
okay i'm putting them away
[Music]
the problem with my snack reviews is
that i open
up so many packages
[Music]
up until now the good thing was that a
lot of the snacks that i opened up i
didn't like so
i didn't have to eat them afterwards
but we have a problem i'm liking these
snacks so i have to eat them quickly
after
afterwards
[Music]
okay ah this is getting them a 10 out of
10 from me besides being expired
okay
next snack is also expired
[Laughter]
this one is expired for one month but
should be fine too
[\h__\h] inspired snack box
oh my god
okay
now
take a look at this
cheese doodles oh also from the same
brand so it's again from the swedish
brand
cheese doodles the cheesier snack
original
oh you guys are excited about them oh
wow this this snack box is doing great
so far
those are great those are popular i
think they have a better
um i think they're just doing better for
european countries because the snack box
company is in europe
and
they have an easier time getting snacks
from there
than getting it from
a country
somewhere
far far far away like guatemala
is maybe one of my
conspiracy theories
that makes sense yeah
[Music]
yeah best before
uh 28th
yeah it's okay it's okay i'll eat it
there's it should be fine um i'm not
like a huge fan of cheesy snacks
but
let's see
this might bring down the rating because
i don't like cheese like that much i i i
can eat cheesy
things but
yeah
um
so these are like puffy
puffy flips
apparently
opening up
[Music]
yeah cheese balls but in a in a
different shape yes exactly i'm taking
off my glove again
okay it smells bad really
i mean not bad but
yeah it's fine it's fine
okay i'm eating one they're shaped like
a like a worm
ah
[Music]
not my thing
not my thing doesn't even taste that
strong like cheese but
[Music]
that's what they look like you guys want
some
they're fine though i guess could be
saltier could be a bit saltier
um i'll put them here
i hope the swedish people recognize it i
can't have ever i need to get a
different table again i'll do the big
table again i guess next time
[Music]
if they expire no thanks come on they're
fine
so i keep them oh raining um
i'll give them
[Music]
five point now
that's just because i don't know should
i be very um
personal like this because
should i put my own preference too much
into this
i think for someone who likes
cheese they would probably be younger
but they're not even that strong
strongly cheesy tasting
[Music]
my personal tongue
taste
says
5 out of 10. i i wouldn't buy it
i would not buy it
yeah
okay
that was two salty snacks let's get some
chocolate going here
and tatara
pops
and luffy
lady
pups
uh as you can see they have like they're
like uh airy they have those
bubbly holes in them
never had them before
um that's not even swedish okay here we
go that's norwegian
norwegian peeps what's up
what's up
that's not written in swedish what
[Music]
what
but the cl uh cloetta is a swedish brand
i looked that up and did look that up
uh-huh okay
swedish brand but the snack is made for
no way
hmm
maybe
they had something left over for the
from the north
north
norway uh snack box oh it's okay close
close enough close enough
close enough
nice shot okay
oh are there any no no way no regions in
the chat
[Music]
what's what's up norwegian peeps
what's up are you guys good with sweden
are you bffs are your friends from
sweden
you get this one no way
[Music]
but not the next one
what's up what's up now we hate them oh
come on don't love only
hey what is that super chat
you hate each other it's complicated
oh come on
damn norway killed our king oh how many
hundred years ago is that
no uh you had some problems back in the
day in the medieval times understandable
i also am still
mad at henry for killing ambulance
[\h__\h]
okay i'm gonna dig in
[Music]
okay so it's like little little balls
like that i have cat hairs on my hands
ignored
[Music]
hmm
is it just me or does it have a slight
coffee flavor
in the chocolate
did someone ever ever eat those before
it's next spot i didn't look but nah
chocolate is okay
ah this one is
not expired
[Music]
i don't really
like that much also it was a short
experience like because they're so small
the first bite is
interesting
but then it quickly it quickly just
disappears in my mouth
looks like maltese is uh mmm a little
bit i guess
but the inside is not
cookie like my taser is this is just a
airy chocolate i think
um
yeah no not a big fan no i'm not a big
fan
i think i won't even leave it on the
table because apparently it's not even
swedish
apparently you guys don't even know it
and i need more space on my table anyway
i'll give this a
5 out of 10.
okay next one
[Music]
okay
we have some jelly snacks
what do you say about this swedish
people
cool hellon
scala
gelatin free skoom
uh from dubs
do you notice oh
those are swedish
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] there's actually a lot of
swedish rings in here unlike the
guatemalan snack box which was more like
a
lot of snack box
what
wow okay raspberry is it raspberry
did it say raspberry what's the word for
raspberry here
i don't see anything that looks like
raspberry to me
hello oh
okay expiration date is fine 2023 they
gave me a fresh one for this one
okay
opening up i love raspberry i actually
have
um on my on my balcony um
i have raspberry plants
i'm waiting for them
to
er
become vegan bigger they're gonna be
pretty big my mom said so
um
but currently they're still very small
but but today i checked on my balcony
again um because you saw the picture on
twitter uh probably where i i showed you
guys some
some green stuff happening on my balcony
um but i had more uh than that um the
other ones were different plants because
that was that was not raspberry is the
one that i showed you
uh
that was the other berry what was that
again uh
in english i forgot it was not it's not
very common
um but raspberries i was looking at them
um
a red currant yes that was red currant
but i was still waiting for the
raspberry to start sprouting
and it took it it took them a while but
today i checked again and it started
sprouting but in a different way i'll
maybe show you a picture
on twitter again um but i'm happy i saw
some green fresh green sprouting
so i have high hopes of of eating lots
of raspberries this one this this year
one of my raspberry plants will be
having fruit uh in summer apparently and
the other one will be having fruit
apparently in
in the in autumn
they seem to grow fast they must be
because they're like currently like
there's almost nothing there
but i'm excited oh my god i'm gonna make
pancakes with fresh uh raspberries all
the time
okay so inside we have uh
here we have some
yeah
whatever what shape is that like what is
that supposed to be
like little heads or what
where's that what is that
it's like little heads i think
oh and they have quite some sugar on it
okay digging in
[Music]
skulls
oh
they're sour
[Music]
and they're soft mm-hmm
little raspberry dead deadbeats yeah
[Music]
all right now i recognize it
now it took me a while to recognize it
probably because of the eyes not really
typical for a skull but that is a skull
you guys see it it didn't look like a
skull to me before now it does
[Music]
okay these are good
now we go
i'll give them
an eight out of ten
i'd probably
have bought this if i was younger
um i used to be really into these kind
of snacks
is it just me or does do people just
grow out of eating
snacks like these
[Music]
like uh jelly
jelly kind of snacks
like haribo
[Music]
i i grew
owl ouch i grew out of the work
no
i still eat them
no okay
not me
of people still eat them
okay okay well good for you
but they're good i give them an eight
out of 10. i just don't buy that kind of
stuff anymore
okay next snack oh
interesting
[Music]
oh
i like the packaging
is smarty
smarties buttons
we i think we know smarties is not a
like sweet originally swedish thing at
least i would think so
um
correct me if i'm wrong
smarties are not from sweden right
but maybe maybe the button
thingy
maybe that's uh
like something that is particularly
popular in sweden
maybe
maybe we have them but i don't think
they're swedish hmm
it is common in sweden okay well that's
that's okay that's okay i'll count that
i'll let that slide
never seen them before oh first time
seeing oh
uk product
[Music]
there is indeed
only english language on here
what
and it's expired let's go
huh
there's only english language on the
packaging
we don't sell products of english
language in
austria everything's german
even if it's a snack from overseas
oh weird
but they did they at least definitely
and did not just throw that in randomly
because it is in the pamphlet there are
quick sneak peek there are like
explanations of what's in the box
that's a uk snack
what the [\h__\h]
you know what
i disqualified this
i i don't even want to open it i want to
eat it later um
another time because i'm sure this will
taste good i like white chocolate and i
like sparties i guess
i'll just eat it another time i don't
want to open it up yet i mean ah but
it's already expired
[Music]
but it's gonna be fine
um
okay
okay then skippy skippy scoop don't
worry guys
don't worry don't worry about it we'll
have enough snacks don't worry about it
we have another snack another uh sour
candy i think
fizzy pop malaccal
small gold is made public
sterling smack
oh you like them ah i like i'm so happy
when the chat goes oh cause then it
shows that they know what it is
those are popular oh
those are in the candy jar often yes oh
favorites my favorites are showing up oh
is the company swedish too or is that
from somewhere else malacca
go google go google
staple swedish classic candy
finally
hit one on the mark
danish in swedish is malaco
[Music]
[Applause]
uh this one is not expired hallelujah
hallelujah
okay i like the the cute packaging
um the colors the pink and the blue
all right all right oh [\h__\h] it said open
on one side and i opened it somewhere
else with my scissors anyway i'm so
stupid
okay
give me one
[Music]
so they're probably sour and fizzy
yummy
once again sour candy and jelly type of
candy is not something i would normally
buy but this is really good i want to
eat more of that
[Music]
i knew that european candies generally
would taste well to me
hi cool come here i have lots of snacks
come here come here
[Laughter]
uh what was i saying yeah i knew that
european snacks would
generally taste good to me because it's
just
um we have
our snacks are just just um adjusted to
similar taste buds
so it's it's rarely a miss
the cheese was just these ones were just
a mess because i don't really
like this type of cheesy snack
but generally i think other people would
enjoy it
oh wow there's oh
because there's a lot of jelly snacks
man do switch people really like jelly
snacks
uh next snack is from malacco as well
snure cola flavor
er
nice smack smug
with an elephant and it's all slit all
the way to the top so you don't really
see it but it's like a
um
string string shaped
there's a danish oh okay
that's okay classic even in finland oh
okay i guess it's just like popular
in uh
those countries
northern countries in europe probably
they are sweet yeah i mean the company
is swedish right so
but you guys eat them in in all kinds of
northern countries apparently okay
that's good scandinavia that's the word
sorry yes
scandinavia
okay i'm digging in i like i generally
really like coca-cola flavored
jellies
i really like those
the the scent is weird though
so it's like i opened it weirdly but uh
it's like that it's kind of sticking
together let me um
finland is not part of scandinavia okay
let's say nordic countries okay
let me give it a try without my gloves
because i gotta
[Music]
rip it off here
oh that's really weak
[Music]
that's a really weak flavor
that is that tastes like
that tastes like you had a
coca-cola standing around outside of the
fridge for about four days
in summertime
um
there's
it's it's really really weak
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's really weak and
um the strings are a little bit
stiff like um not stiff but a little bit
hard
[Music]
oddly specific
i don't mind coca-cola that's lost its
fizz i don't mind that
um
but if you're gonna make a coca-cola
jelly like dad that's obviously
tailored uh for children
look at the elephant i mean come on then
it should be way stronger than that oh
my god okay i'll give this one
oh expired oh good question didn't look
oh
no not yet
um i'll give this one
[Music]
four out of three honestly a three out
of ten
it's not really
no not convincing
but at least it was a snack that you
guys have up there
okay
next snack is finally finally finally
some chocolate i don't know we already
had chocolate but
i wonder what you say about this it has
swedish flag on it
plop
made in sweden
with
nuts
almonds is it almonds
my favorite oh really
good stuff
those are good that's guatemala no it's
not this is sweden on it is that our new
running gag
is it made in sweden it says made it
sweden
it's putting sleep in here
i believe it
okay
uh
holy [\h__\h] this is
this is uh
this even if i would have received this
chocolate in time
in in somewhat earlier time
then it would still
probably be
expired
what's wrong with these people
end of november
oh okay well it's chocolate so it's
probably okay
it's probably okay i'm just saying i'm
just saying you're not supposed to sell
things anymore that are uh expired right
i mean okay
but there is this mystery about why i
received this snack box in the first
place it came out of nowhere it it
i was not supposed to receive this i
think but okay
uh let's start opening it up
[Music]
it smells good good milk chocolate
uh
i shall i see the nuts a little bit
[Music]
it's a nice chocolate bar
basic
basic chocolate bar
okay digging in
[Music]
i swear
it's not the chocolate that is spicy
sweden mm-hmm
[Music]
it tastes
like yummy milk chocolate
just like the milk chocolate we have in
australia to be honest like our milk
chocolate is just
amazing in europe i would say
um
the nuts in it are not like super big
they're really really really crumbly and
small
get the inside of this
it's the wrong side though you don't
really see much
[Music]
it's really good though
yeah i would tell you just buy this
if i was in a supermarket i would i
actually would
um
i'll give it um
10 out of 10. i'll give you a channel
10.
yeah
now
the thing
is normally
um there's two things that are not here
on the table right now no three things
the drink and the two snacks the others
two snacks um normally this
would be the end of the snack box
but
before the stream
um
some people on on twitter
swedish people supposedly
told me
um if there is no if if there is
humuhumu and fumuhama
in there then
uh
then you're set
um but i looked at this stuff here and
it had that nowhere and i was really
scared that this would be a failure
again
um
and then that i would disappoint the
swedish people who came to the stream
so
what did i do
today before the stream
i went to
dki
[Applause]
[Music]
because
they did have at least some things that
are missing in this stack box
yes
saving my [\h__\h] lives man
i bought some things where i'm not sure
if this would be
something uh but other things i'm sure
that this was supposed to be in the
snack box
so
let's go
i have additional one two three four
five snacks
additional five snacks you know
up until now i was not the type of
person who would go to the kale and buy
snacks besides uh kurt bula
um
i love kurt bola but that's food but i
would never buy snacks there
but today was my first time buying
snacks at ikea
ikea
ah of course okay i had to make some
kind of appearance today i came in in
the clutch yeah
so i bought some things i i
i didn't want to spoil the fact that i'm
going to ikea so i couldn't ask you guys
what's in the lineup of ikea
i should buy but i bought several things
um
uh one of the things i bought
is potato chips
fast leaked potato crisps with pepper
and leek flavor
now i don't know like this is probably
not really specifically swedish
but
i don't know
those are legit good
it's it's just potato chips
but i found the flavor to be interesting
there was a different flavor with
mushrooms
uh pickled mushrooms i think i didn't
buy it because i don't like uh i don't
like mushrooms so i bought this one
um
but you know what um i'll actually not
open up this one because i'm looking
forward to eating it another day and i
already opened up different potato chips
um so
just so you know i did buy that
um okay
um let's go
with
i wonder what you guys say about this
one it's also from cloeta
i think this is fairly well known in
sweden
polly
uh
[Music]
is chocolate thingies with arak what's
aura and butter toffee and vanilla yeah
you know polly
see
i found one good thing there in ikea not
not only one thing not only one thing
really common in sweden wonderful
wonderful it's quite a big package
so i hope
after opening this i can enjoy it for a
long time i don't eat that much
chocolate anymore
no idea what arik is but it is common
what is it what is uh alcohol
okay hopefully not too strong tasting
so everything
now is not from the snack box anymore
it's just what i personally additionally
bought at ikea today
polly is my go-to when going to the
movies what
common in finland as well cool
titty
nordic countries be like tea tea
vanilla e flavor oh okay okay okay
simple classic taste
snack books dlc yeah
yeah i really was scared that this would
be like
only snacks from other countries besides
sweden
so
i
um
quickly
made my way to ikea before the stream
um was actually fun
and i bought of course some other things
besides
snacks
i only went through the voice tags but
then i was there and i was like oh might
as well buy some extra things so i
bought a summer blanket because i was
feeling pretty hot these days when i was
trying to sleep because it's getting
really warm outside so i was like damn i
actually don't have a summer blanket so
i bought a big ass summer blanket plus
covers for it so that's why i had to
take a nap that's that's that's the
reason why i had to take a nap guys
because i had to test it out it was so
fresh
fresh out of the plastic
yeah
yeah yeah yeah how do hot people sleep
in the summer
you need hot people like me it gets
really [\h__\h] hot on there the blanket
yeah it's a hot hot blanket as a hot
person it is quite troublesome
yeah i am
wash it first oh i didn't wash it
i just put it on my
on my on my bed um
yeah it would be tough being hot so
anyway let me try the chocolate um
going to ikea was fun i want to go more
often again
[Music]
uh
okay scissor i need a scissor i'm
incapable of opening things when i have
my gloves on
oh sure okay
[Music]
before
oh
interesting smell i think that is the
rock that i can
smell even though i don't know what it
is i think that's what it is
[Music]
interesting okay
i want to like this because this seems
very popular
but it is a little bit specific which is
to be honest good because like stuff
like this
that like the plop i could easily buy
something really really really similar
in austria i like having like snacks
that are really specific to the country
and i think this is this is the case for
paulie at least
okay i'm gonna try there's like a lot of
uh uh where are we where are we where
are we here a lot of small ones
in there you see them
you see them
[Music]
it's a sharing mix but i don't have
anyone to share it with
and then oh
[Music]
they look like this
they don't have a completely um smooth
surface they're also like the pops
they're a little bit
uh they look like
and they look like a other snack but i
don't recall which one it was okay let
me try
without cat hairs please damn it
damn it
[Music]
okay oh
oh yeah
[Music]
oh interesting
they are very chewy i did not expect
that i thought they would be more
like um liquidy
[Music]
you guys know i don't like alcohol
and it does have like i think it is that
arak taste
that gives it this
slightly really slightly
for someone like me who doesn't drink
alcohol
it is pretty strong
for you guys which would probably be
totally fine
does taste a little bit like alcohol i
know there's no alcohol in there
probably but this there's like an
alcoholic taste or something like that
the red packets are more tastier
oh they didn't have a rat package just
the blue ones
[Music]
oh is is this a special flavor ah
there's a classic flavor and this is a
special one
[Music]
the red package is milk chocolate oh
okay okay
milk chocolate and what wha what would
the inside be
still arak and butter toffee and vanilla
or
[Music]
was there white ones in there oh
no
no only these ones
inside is the same huh
um well i'm gonna be honest um
i don't really like them but now i have
a big ass package of it
[Laughter]
um but i'm happy i got them nonetheless
because it's a good addition to my stack
box
um
[Music]
it has an interesting uh texture to it
so i'll give it five out of ten
the other ones are all great so we can
have some bad ones that's okay
sorry swedish people
next one from ikea is this one
a
vulcan
a sour foam candy with apple flavor
you guys really like your sour snacks
don't you
um okay jelly again
let me take off my gloves
to each their own spring feeling it
means spring feeling
today
[Music]
oh the smell is apple but also very um
industrial
uh-huh
what what is that shape it looks like a
snowman
is it is it because
i eat it and then the snowman will go
away therefore spring feelings
is that on purpose
chemical yeah
okay i will i will eat now
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
honestly the apple flavor could be
stronger in this one
um
[Music]
the texture is really interesting ah i
meant artificially yes the texture is
like
not like other jelly
uh
foamy thingies i've eaten before
[Music]
the sourness is also
not very strong it could be more sour
and more apple and i would probably like
it
but i don't like it very much
[Laughter]
you're disappointing me
[Music]
so this one i will give um
five out of ten
it's okay i can't like everything
i'm very picky
now
i have
uh two two more stacks
one
two didn't i say five
i had to put a potato chip so i put
those away okay
now the next two
are the reason
why i went to ikea in the first place
because
people told me this needs to be in the
snack box and it wasn't
let's
shall we start with
um
the one that's probably gonna taste good
okay let's go with that one
um yeah a lot of people told me about
madame bull marabou
um
but
there were two choices
um there was normal mara ball and then
there was daim maga bowl flavor
um and i went with the dime one because
it combines two swedish things i think
yeah
i thought kill two birds with one stone
smart
smart tension
[Music]
i think it's like a combination
of two popular things i think time i've
seen a lot on on the shelves in the
supermarket it's a
pretty common chocolate snack
uh i don't i don't think i've eaten it
before but i know it's very well known
and marabou is a swedish chocolate
company i think is it expired no no this
is from ikea this is not expired this is
fresh
diamond is extremely common all over
scandinavia
here as well though i think i've
definitely seen it uh in the supermarket
very often
uh together they're extra delicious oh
i'm excited okay okay okay okay okay
it looks like there's a
caramel
and nuts
inside maybe
i'm not sure but it looks yummy
so let's go
uh they had this in
all kinds of sizes and shapes and all
that
i went with this one so the inside there
is like uh
two
rolls
separately packaged i can't get it out
damn it
[Music]
yeah inside there's like these rolls
nice
and beautiful
[Music]
i'm excited about this one
you guys really seem to like this one
aha
cute interesting i like the packaging
it's very clean so they're like stacked
up there
okay i'll eat the one at the very top
[Music]
mm-hmm
hmm
10 out of 10.
yeah
i really like the milk chocolate flavor
um and i like the there's some nuts
nutsy texture in there
it's a little bit sticky probably
because of some caramel
i added another one um
[Music]
wow
i'm actually impressed um
like we have a lot of good chocolate
in austria but
nothing really is
almost almost nothing
is actually from an austrian company
we just eat a lot of german chocolate
and switzerland chocolate and wherever
chocolate
but we don't have many companies that
are like from austria and
makes popular stuff
so
i'm pretty
impressed that there's where there were
actually
so many snacks that are not only from a
company in
that are not only eaten in sweden but
from a different
uh company but so many of these are
actually from a swedish company
like 90 percent
[Music]
yeah really really impressive so that
was definitely a good one
and
now
the last thing
um
i know i i'm pretty sure i will not like
it but i also haven't eaten something
like this in
many many many many years
[Music]
licorice
love
dark
sweet liquor is
yeah there was no licorice in the snack
box which i was like that's okay i don't
like licorice anyway that's sweet
licorice will be fine yeah i've heard of
some
i've heard of some really really bad
licorice that like somebody on twitter
also wrote this to me there's like this
this one licorice snack that people that
swedish people make tourists buy
um as a souvenir or whatever but
they're basically trolling them because
they know they will not like it
uh
yeah red licorice is yucky
salmiakki is better i think this was the
only licorice snack that i found in ikea
um
yeah i mean close enough at least it's
licorice so we just had to cover that i
felt like even though i don't like it i
have to cover it so
so
uh i i cannot remember what licorice
tastes like it's been too too long
[Music]
in nordic countries in general
licorice
because here
it's not that popular no not i mean
there's some people who like it but
really not many i would say yes yes yes
yes yes
wow okay
you guys have different taste buds after
all
damn
okay i'm opening it up
[Music]
i'll probably throw the rest of this
away
oh oh oh okay the smell is
smells like coffee
no actually it smells like i don't know
like something you shouldn't be eating
um okay so there's these little blocks
just just gonna
just gonna um get it over with
uh
oh oh here
three
two one
[Music]
oh that tastes like
that tastes like like um toothpaste
[Music]
why would i eat this
why am i eating this
[Music]
it gets worse
it's not like it's not the toothpaste
it's the
[Music]
it gets
worse oh let me drink
oh
[Music]
ew
sorry i spit it out
[Music]
zero out of ten not my thing
i'm sure there's people out there who
really really love licorice
but i'm not one of them
i'm not one of them no no no no
understandable thank you thank you thank
you thank you
i mean even in austria there's people
who like licorice but it's not very not
very common
thank you for your sacrifice i wouldn't
want to eat licorice
i just felt like you know as a youtuber
this has to be done
i have to do it
i have to at least try it
i have to at least buy it so that was
licorice from ikea
yeah
i actually also bought frozen cut bolas
and
mashed potatoes and the sauce for the
cut bolas and
uh bling and berry jam just the whole
thing just a whole meal
[Laughter]
i might eat that for
dinner tonight i haven't eaten that in
such a long time my mom used to make
that quite often yeah the ikea meatballs
my mom used to make that for us pretty
often
yeah yeah yeah i mean she would actually
not
uh
not that often make it herself she would
just buy from ikea
it's really yummy i really like uh
that but i haven't eaten it in a long
while so
you should pronounce it or ikea
uh in in german we say ikea but i guess
in english you guys say ikea so i'm not
sure which one to say the whole time
it's pronounced shirt bulla what
funny even though it's a k
what wait so is it ishiel and not ikea
why is it just because the k is at the
beginning
of the word
[Music]
i would say that the yeah that the
swedish way of saying ikea is more like
the german one than the english way of
saying it
[Music]
um yeah yeah yeah ikea
at least one thing i get right
[Laughter]
so i would say
by the way this was also there in the
beginning i would say overall the snack
box was really really good i made some
additions thanks to ikea
um
like the
marabou i don't if my level is so
popular like so many of you guys
mentioned it before
um beforehand
then i really wonder like how did it not
end up in the snack box
but besides that it was pretty good
there was like one snack
of
these ones these ones were really
questionable so i disqualified them
because it's not it's a uk snack it
doesn't even have any
any swedish on it
so
that's questionable that could have been
replaced with licorice or with marble
but i feel like they didn't put licorice
in it because they try to
stray away from things that uh the
customers probably wouldn't like
that's my impression
because in the
in the other boxes for example they also
didn't have anything like super spicy or
whatever just something that
most people probably can eat
yeah
um
so storming is a trap even this week
i've heard a lot about that now is that
the licorice that's really really really
bad
[Music]
surplus stock islands what does that
mean
yeah
for i know it's the fish
yeah some people warned me about getting
swedish fish
fermented fish
don't worry they never had that in the
kia nor did they have it in the snack
box so it was out of my reach
but it's the smelliest thing ever it's a
smellier than a durian though
is it worse to the durian i think the
durian is worse
so delicacy pickled
pickled heroin
yes
yeah you sure because then
holy [\h__\h] you could use that
to kill someone probably
you open that fish under the water
outside
[Music]
rotting
ones rods and the other ones
you it's illegal to bring in an effort
are you [\h__\h] kidding me
imagine someone
[\h__\h] control
opening that [\h__\h] up in the in an
airplane although in an airplane
the air is like
[Music]
maybe it's worse in inside of
a train or so
it's classified as a weapon
[Music]
well but the thing is for durians
they're i know a lot of people who
really like durians
[Music]
what about
search drumming
is there anyone in sweden
who likes that
if there is no one who likes it then why
would it be a thing
i'm eating it in front of you or
like 10 people me
yes
i like it wow
interesting
i can only imagine it smelling it really
disgusting like rotten fish
and i don't understand
why someone would like that but okay
read super chat about exploding search
driving cans oh my god okay looking
forward to that
there's four 14 ways
of spelling the ch sound oh
okay interesting
it's a thousand times worse than you
imagine
[Music]
okay
is that something you can order in a
restaurant because that would be really
rude for
the other
uh
customers a poll for the next box oh
that's not really in my control
no no no
okay
good
um
actually yeah that's not in my control
because the next snack box is from spain
yeah
the next snack box will be from spain
and
uh
after that i don't know but actually i
think after that will be australian
snack box because uh just today i talked
to the bales
bales was like yo yo yo do you still
want to do that snack box snack snack
exchange
on that exchange she was just asking if
she if i still want her to send me
australian snacks and i was like yeah
you know what yes how about we make it
an exchange i sent you snacks from from
germany and austria and so on
and then we make a collab out of it so
the next snack box review after spain
will be a collab actually
yes
yes australian snacks i told her to not
send me vegemite because i could just
get vegemite here probably if i wanted
to
but i don't want to um but anyway i
might try it anyway um we still have the
quiz guys let's see we have a lot of
swedish people here today actually so
you guys can help us win the quiz
i mean there's nothing to win but
um
quiz time
[Music]
question
uh
where is it here
oh wait here's a crash crash uh
quiz
crash lesson in german we like to say
crash quiz
um for a quick lesson uh
oh dear i don't know how to pronounce
these things um
how are you is who
more do
uh and chorigong is ursekta
thank you uh and please both of them
you're welcome is tak
uh that's right or exactly is lagom
my name is kiwawa is jack hetel
uh
post
uh uh cheers is uh school
uh goodbye is hey doll
uh snacks is goodies
like goodies
that was yummy
is
that smackadegot and that sounds a lot
like german
because i could say
that's
doesn't that sound similar to that's
macadam got
got is like good smackade is like
schmidt
germanic languages let's go
[Music]
okay
now let's do the let's do the quiz this
time we have less delay in the chat so
this should be
uh easier okay i'll use the poll
function all right
help me out guys
let's see let's see how much the swedish
people also know about sweden and the
non-swedish people
uh question number one
how many
[Music]
how many elks live in sweden
three hundred don't look it up guys
three hundred thousand
seven hundred fifty thousand
or
nine hundred thousand
[Music]
elks
hmm
i don't know i'm gonna guess
750 thousand maybe
the answer is
wait i'll give you a bit more time
one two three four five six seven eight
nine ten
the answer is a
300 000 well that's actually not that
much i mean the other numbers sounded so
much that i was expecting like insane
numbers but okay for the thousand i
guess is still a lot though three
hundred thousand damn
a lot of people guessed uh
not a free wait wait
yeah a lot of people get 750 000.
okay question number two
ah
[Music]
okay
what are
don't look it up
what are the
typical
small
vacation homes
called
in sweden
now one of the answers we can already
say no because we already learned what
that means before i know what it's not
fica it's a finka then i think it's
finka
i heard that before
or
what
wait then what is finca
basically like the german
no don't tell them the answer swedish
people keep it to yourself now everybody
knows it
keep it to yourself man
finka is jail
what in swedish it's jail i heard that
word somewhere else before in some other
context
let's go to finka
okay well it's stuga
as all of the swedish people in here
already told us okay
uh
yeah okay next question
[Music]
ah
scania
also known as native name of skanda is
the southernmost of historical provinces
in sweden
okay
um
okay uh the question is
[Music]
you mean do you mean mountains
what is
the highest
what
do they mean mountain true sense
in german
elevation
what is the highest elevation
in
uh
[Music]
scania
which is like
a provence in
[Music]
sweden uh holland thousand okay i can't
write the the same letters unfortunately
[Music]
how would i know
maybe the swedish people know
yeah it's like i guess the highest
mountain but if they don't call it
mountain then it's probably not as big
that you would call it a mountain yeah
maybe there just are no mountains
is sweden a pretty flat country do you
guys have no mountains
[Music]
or maybe that provence is specifically
flat
uh and
uh therefore this one place stands out
because it's pretty high in a flat area
or so
i am confused but
okay scanner is flat schoolness but not
a hotel so the answer is
uh
a
holland
so
which is probably winning because all
the swedish people are voting for it
thank you guys
[Laughter]
okay
ah
i know that name i wonder if you guys
know her
very well known
um
where was
the very
well-known
uh
children's book offer
[Music]
[Applause]
is that really what she was
[Music]
singing i i love that song
yes red hair and twin tails
pippy lungs
[Music]
okay apparently you guys say it's vimer
bean the answer is uh yes
vimer b did you did you look it up on
google
you cannot cheat don't cheat no cheating
two more questions
ah we know the answer to this
because we talked about it so i will not
type this in but another question is
what do people do in sweden when when
they meet up for fika
go for a walk and then go to sauna
or
drink coffee and eat snacks
or get drunk and dance
yeah we know it's getting coffee
because they like to drink a lot of
coffee over there
[Music]
okay last question
wait what you guys still have a king
what i i guess you did
doesn't have
your king is not as famous as the queen
huh
what
is the name
of the current king
of sweden
[Music]
olaf
e
we
scarce
oh gord or
carl
gustaf
or
[Music]
anderson
okay
there you go
pewdiepie
who could it be i actually
don't know
i don't i don't recall having heard of
the name
doesn't seem very
famous oh but apparently it's carl
according to you guys
wow
you knew this one nice good for you
is it really is it really karl
is it really carl though is it really
let's see the answer is
b
carl
the
sixth sixteenth
wait 16 for 14 uh no 16th yeah that's 16
right
card the 16th gustaf
smort smart kiwawa
[Music]
okay
that was the quiz thank you oh by the
way here's another another thingy about
sweden apparently there's a mint somal
a middle of summer festival
um between the 19th and the 25th june
the swedes like to celebrate things
about the summer sun and vender what's
that in english again
something about the summer summer and
the sun and all that
they
they decorate trees
with lots of flowers
they dance and sing and eat traditional
foods
such as
that
rotten fish hopefully not a summer salt
thai salty solstice salt on salty salt
ties whatever
[Music]
yes that's it
and that sounds nice
maybe i can visit sweden during this
time that would be nice
that sounds like fun i want to see those
trees decorated
is it nice in sweden during that time
is it really pink that does everybody
celebrate that
is it like oktoberfest
we get usually drunk and eat so so i
mean no way really you are
big celebration
oh
cool i want to go and then there's
actually a recipe
as well for
[Music]
ah swedish um
oatmeal cookies
for some reason
[Music]
oatmeal cookies why i don't know
do you guys like oatmeal cookies that
much
[Music]
hmm want to bake those no no
no because i don't care about oatmeal
[Music]
oh
anyway
yay
that was my swedish snack box
[Music]
that was a good one
that was actually a good snack box that
also
was not only pretty pretty accurate even
though i had to add some extra things um
but it was also yummy most most of it
was really good i just bought the
licorice knowing that i would not like
it
but besides that you missed your screen
okay okay
[Music]
wait
my gloves are still dirty from the
painting
there you go
okay
i hope you got that one hope you got a
good shot
[Music]
helvetic wait i know that word helvete
what does that mean again i heard it
before
helvete
[Music]
nobody means hell
go to hell
are you telling me go to hell
why didn't you say that because you were
late someone was like oh i was late just
notice you were streaming helvetica
oh it's like a [\h__\h] word oh come on
i thought it was a nice word
[Music]
whoever said that is now oh it's like
damage ah okay that makes sense yeah
[Music]
okay i think i'm pretty satisfied with
this one um i have to read super chats
now
uh
yeah
so that's okay for you guys
uh
tomorrow is
tomorrow is another yakuza stream
i think
yeah yeah and then on friday uh we have
basically two
april fools streams
one is my solo one and the other one is
after midnight for me so that's why it's
on saturday on the schedule
um
yeah yeah but now we'll read uh super
chat so thank you guys for coming today
if you don't want to stay you can go if
you want but you're also welcome to stay
uh it won't take too long i think yeah
so if you don't wanna if you have
nowhere to go you're welcome to stay
[Music]
yeah okay
let's do this
thank you sweden for that really yummy
snack box
even though a lot of the things were
expired
but it was really good let's go to my
normal office then or should we stay
here
i guess i can stay here so you guys see
that i did for the people who come in
later they can see what i did eat oh by
the way let me show you
[Music]
i talked about it yesterday and i didn't
show it on twitter yet but i'll show you
here is that magazine
meet her
[Music]
it's pretty pretty damn fake
most of it as you can see is a manga
and then
there we go there's a lot of whole life
there
i'm gonna show you
um
on twitter
the pages where i was on
okay
but let me quickly show you now
let me quickly show you
see
me
[Music]
something fell down this table is way
too small yeah but there you go
yeah
big big page
and then there is one page with whole
live english or whole myth
either either just myth or all of this i
forgot
[Music]
and there you it's myth
like this
[Music]
and then on this side there's like some
streams that we recommend i think i
think we chose them ourselves did we
i think they they gave us a choice oh
and we could change it if we wanted to
if we didn't agree
i think that's what it was
and it came with this super nice
clear file
kind of yellowish from sugar's butt
butt
[Music]
this one's cute
full body on the back
yeah
cute
[Music]
yeah oh oh oh oh and this was sent to me
too
nina new album i really like the
packaging
this is so cool because this is like
this is like a hole
there's like a paper cover on top
actually i mean on top of that is
another plastic layer but this is like a
like a layer of uh
thick paper and then there's
a cd underneath yeah
yeah nice does it include vampires yes
there's vampire and animal and parasite
like basically all of the recent works
from deku nina they were releasing so
many songs recently
um
i need to drink i'm like out of breath
oh my god
[Music]
okay
okay that's just something i wanted to
show you now let's go to superchat
let's go let's go let's go
let's go
super chat house
actually
let me tell you something today was the
first time
in
whoo
i wonder how long i don't even remember
the last time
first time
in
[Music]
maybe a full year
since i
have
taken public
transport
[Music]
means of public transport
yeah i've really only been using uber
but today i felt like
i've been wasting so much money on uber
i guess i'll use
public transport i did not use the bus
card no no no no it's not even a bus
card it's a general general public
transport uh card but i didn't use it i
bought a ticket because i don't have the
card and i don't want to be like yeah in
theory i have it when someone um comes
up to me and checks it and i don't have
anything with me
[Music]
but but but it was still cheaper than
get way cheaper than getting on an uber
so
no i didn't cancel the card
but but but but i only bought a ticket
for
the first ride not for the second ride
for the second one i went in and and i
was like you know what
[Music]
i'll risk it
because in theory i have a card that
i've been paying for
for years and haven't been using it
um
there is a story there yeah from before
i went to japan
before whole life i had a job where i
used public transport to get there
so
um yeah but it was only supposed to
be for like one year um
but they continued charging me
afterwards and i thought it was still
charges from
you know the one year
uh because i i was paying it off in in
rates
and small steps
but
then
yeah i went to japan and one year later
after i came back and i noticed i was
still paying for it on my bank account
and i was like well that
that doesn't make sense
i
i must have
paid it off by now
yeah installments
but apparently they renewed it
but i never received the new card
because it did say there was an
expiration date on the card so after one
year i just got rid of the card i never
got the new card though because i think
they sent it to my old apartment if
anything
and um
yeah so i never got it
yeah well anyway
anyway
i i was able to ride the
um ride back home with somewhat good
consciousness
uh
without a ticket but with with the
thought that i do
pay for
a yearly card i just don't have it
so
worst case
they're gonna kick me out and then check
and then later find out that
in the in their system
there is my name
so
yes
anyway
and you don't know i didn't confine
that's okay
you're out of your mind you know this
right what why
[Music]
why
i don't want mine i know my mind
[Music]
foreign
well anyway it's okay don't worry about
it cancel it right now i don't know how
to cancel it i have i can't just cancel
it online i would have to go to like one
of their offices
in order to cancel it
anyway
a fairy tale gone bad yeah
let's read super chatters
[Music]
oh is that swedish
is that swedish
pepsi duncan
and the game of crete duncan
swedish neighbors oh you're from north
no way maybe one day we can have a
norway snack box
dunk joker thank you for the two pinkies
mwah
i watched the first episode of upload oh
my god
you followed my recommendation i'm
excited and i agree the way they move
their hands to cover up the bloopers
pretty funny right
right
thank you for saying that
thank you i'm i was saying that
[Music]
please don't be lazy tencho
please don't say you are lazy
[Music]
crazy
did
[Music]
why can't i not be lazy huh
wow
so wait
go back to the super chat go back and i
agreed a little bit my dad and i
finished season one of the gilded age
all the expensive ballroom dresses
reminded me of our elegant empress oh
the gilded age
which where can you watch that
here's one more super chat to support
the snack box review thank you
i know you're eager to set up the 3dw
but you come up with a lot of original
fun content that isn't free like
snapchat's review yeah
well be patient boss your content is
great thank you so much
hbo max your rmt would enjoy it would i
not enjoy it
[Music]
would i not enjoy it
ballroom dresses tells me i will enjoy
it let me look it up
[Music]
but it's only on hbo can i watch it like
i don't know on amazon prime or
something
[Music]
uh
ah
it looks like um
[Music]
just looking at the screenshot it looks
like a non
spanish
um
uh
oh yeah
it's like it looks like downton abbey
from the crate of downton abbey let's go
i mean the style um but i i meant like
the the garage hotel
the grown hotel
has like
i think it's from just a similar period
of time
because they wear similar fashion
although
not quite
somewhat similar i guess
[Music]
but that that one is uh spanish
uh
so yeah i am yeah
but i want to watch this
i like downton abbey too
i remember binge watching the [\h__\h] out
of that when i was really really really
really sick
at one time
hey i want to watch that can they bring
it to amazon prime or netflix or
something what the hell oh it's pretty
new
january 24 2022 oh that's
yeah
probably not gonna
put it on
anything watchable for me anytime soon
[Music]
i already have so many subscriptions i
have amazon prime i have netflix i have
disney plus i think i got something else
too something within amazon another
subscription
[Music]
and i still can't access every show that
i want to watch
[Music]
it is so tough to be
legal
it's so tough
[Music]
also the bus card it's not a fuss card
yeah
why are there so many
less subscriptions please
please um
yeah then there's some subscriptions
that i can't even get because
they won't let me pay for it in austria
uh that was hulu i cannot get hulu i
really try getting hulu cause hulu has
some good shows as well
like two maybe two good shows
what you know what [\h__\h] you yo
you're you're
your problem
you won't get my money then
no i tried i think i tried a vpn and i
still couldn't get it yeah so
why why why why why why why why
ah
[Music]
are they not on disney plus stars what i
have both of those
[Music]
ah i mean yeah the shows that i mean no
they're not on there
anyway
and thank you dr joseph
please um if you're interested feel free
to continue watching upload because i'm
really addicted to it right now they
just put out a second season recently i
think
i'm still on the first season though
it's uh it's getting interesting there's
like a conspiracy going on
they did oh you didn't know there you go
yeah it's pretty recent i think so you
might have not seen it yet
um that's why i was um being
advertised a lot i think on my streaming
service
because
uh they just put out a new season
conspiracy oh my god
[Music]
yeah mr casper
thank you stratosphere in the game of
korean
um
[Music]
mind your own business thank you oh
from sweden hey i've been watching your
stream since your debut but i've never
sent a super chat and i thought it's
about time to change that a big tax so
make it for all your streams from a
swedish fan thank you
i thought you know i thought i didn't
have like barely any maybe two swedish
fans but today there were many many more
also looking at the super chat there's
also a lot here thank you guys
you guys are usually a bit more quiet
but i'm glad i got you out of your
hattie holes today
this is really nice because the the
snack boxes
smack snack box reviews make people come
out of their hattie hills yeah
like they're like oh she's doing
something about my country oh oh oh okay
okay i'm gonna i'm gonna be active in
the chat today
yeah
that's really nice you guys are welcome
to stay out of your hiding holes
afterwards as well
yeah
i totally get it though like if someone
would make a stream about austria i
would really like to be active in the
chat for that one too
you asked us we crawled out of our house
[Music]
don't go back okay
we swedish people very shy
yeah
[Music]
quiet people oh wow i like that i like
that
that's chill you guys are just chill i
would say
[Music]
i want to go to sweden
i'll go to sweden this year
oh thank you
thank you
[Music]
board up the holes yes do it
don't piss them off
they tend to bear circle what
[Music]
i don't believe that don't steal or
moose our moose signs don't worry i'm
not planning on it
i'm not planning on it
do you guys eat
uh elk
meat in sweden though cause you have so
many
is that a popular choice of meat over
there i mean in general i think in
austria as well we do sometimes eat it
so
oh it happens
we do
i do it's super good
[Music]
i can imagine that must taste really
good yeah i'm not really a fan of eating
horse
uh
but
what's here chicken
here she's not elk but
oh right here
[Music]
dear
i like deer so
sometimes
it's a fancy meat here
i don't i don't think we it's that
common to eat at all time
[Music]
but yeah venison is great for grateful
like um i would say
um dinner in the winter like especially
like around christmas it's a very
popular choice on the menu
of course
don't worry i won't eat of course no no
no no no
no no
kobo is gonna be okay i won't eat her
horse she doesn't have one yet anyway
ah
what does deer taste like
[Music]
i mean it kind of depends what kind of
sauce and all that insides you eat it
with
i don't know it's tough to say
it tastes good though
[Music]
gear is good very good
uh
silverian dancing thank you
what
tai chi thank you for the rest of chad
hello oh
[Music]
wait
do you guys say that in swedish too
because i see tai chi wrote it in a
swedish way but it is definitely a
german hello
as well maybe you guys also say hello
with the
oh you do
ah
i mean it's written differently but it's
pronounced the same
nice i feel very connected to you guys
thank you tiny hello to you too
[Music]
oh wait
that reminds me because i'm giving
kisses
and
and a lot of these people are swedish
not tai chi though but that reminds me
swedish kisses um we have a snack here
uh it's called uh
uh no wait not kisses sweet swedish
kisses no schwedenbomb
uh swedish
bombs
now i'm just gonna assume
that this is not actually from sweden
let me look it up now
[Music]
wait it's from austria
what
[Music]
uh
it's it's made by by an austrian who had
a
swedish friend
[Music]
it was made in austria what
what
it's a popular
snack here actually i used to really
like it
um as a child as a teenager or so i'm
totally still a teenager
i still like it
um
this is what it looks like
uh
inside is like a fluffy
fluffy um
cream like like kind of like whipped
cream
and it's protected by a layer a thin
layer of chocolate either normal
chocolate or with a coconut
on top of it
yeah i think in germany you call them
something else uh
mom moms in sweden
oh i wonder if they're like exactly the
same or just a little bit different
mum moms mommas
cute that's a cute nail
[Music]
okay but the austrian version of it is
called swedish
bombs
for some reason because the austrian
person had a swedish friend
just like me you guys are my swedish
friends swedish people hello
[Music]
see this this snack is the the proof of
our love
between austria and sweden yeah
eternal titty
yeah you are all swedish now
[Applause]
it's not a marshmallow inside but it's
kind of like a marshmallow e cream
a fluffy marshmallowy
mmm cream
not really marshmallows though no no no
no
the bad gamer duncan
[Music]
not quite swedish
but close
[Music]
thank you for the pinkies tank box
review is turning into country review
and i dig it now i think it's great like
this is the one good thing about these
snack boxes is that they have this
pamphlet with like information about the
country some words a recipe a quiz and
all that so i really gotta uh um praise
them for that and it's also making the
stream more interesting giving me more
things to talk about so yeah it's pretty
cool
we all learned something about the
country a little bit
no it's not nougat no no no no no no no
no it's a white cream
white white but it's not really a cream
it's just some fluffy whatever
yeah so thank you tanaka i think it's a
great format that we have established
here
yeah like whipped egg white kind of
[Music]
a six
hot or six shot savior duncan zebra
duncan
oh caramel dancing it's a swedish song
you're right
[Music]
swedish
caramel
dancing
lyrics
[Music]
dance
[Laughter]
[Music]
cute song
but it was [\h__\h] everywhere back then
man
[Laughter]
uh
camera dancing intensifies
[Music]
that was a very fake german accent i
tried
damn it i tried what's wrong
well what does uh
mrs
google say
[Music]
dan samios
um
hello
was that better
it has a stockholm accent really yeah
an tap was made perfect thank you
it was my collaboration uh song with uh
google the google lady
[Music]
and where was i where was i here come
samnita thank you
careful food poison oh don't worry don't
worry don't worry looking for the top
junction tony and duncan
uh oh dear don't don't pick a fight with
them be nice rise so freedom kitchen
[Music]
that is a good way of judging pack
duncan frosty paws duncan
okay thank you
thank you for saying i'm your favorite
you're my favorite too now okay
messed up brain spike dancing i am a tea
duncan
[Music]
oh yeah you know what i'll give the
snack box an overall rating of
[Music]
8 out of 10
for accuracy and yumminess it was still
missing some important things but that's
okay
[Music]
yeah
good one
mundo thank you
bamboo blankets
[Music]
what that be like really stiff
eh
mundo what are you talking about
zork787 dakota i hope one day you can do
a uk snack box we got some great
traditional brands over here like
barrett's maynard swizzles walkers and
cadburys to name a few yeah you guys
have a lot of original brands too
definitely definitely want to do a uk
uh snack box review um
i
i do have some people that i know in the
uk
so
i could definitely get someone to send
me one um
[Music]
if not this uh company makes one first
though
the last snare box i didn't give it a an
overall rating but due to the lack of
accuracy and even the snacks not being
that good
and not a single snack being from the
country that the snack box was from
um
a one out of ten
[Music]
bamboo can be tuned into fibers and
weave like a cotton i guess i guess yeah
that makes sense now
i guess so i've never seen a bamboo
blanket before though
yeah i'm sorry but like
i mean there were some some decent
snacks there but even then it was
nothing from
guatemala so
half swedish oh
which half
la talata 10
bamboo tail is very comfy here
[Music]
fanatos x for the free dancing duck
joseph duncan
[Music]
yes yes
i went shopping to get even more snacks
just before the stream because i thought
you know what i'll make the stream even
better
brandon dancing
loyal lakshmi thank you for the pinky
hello your live 3d performances was
three day performance was incredible i
loved seeing all the other ladies
perform but your stage presence was and
performance was just truly incredible oh
i look forward to what is yet to come
your hard work is admirable thank you
people still sending me
messages about the
about the concert thank you very much
you should try some swedish search
timing you would love it [\h__\h] you
get out of here i know what you're
trying to do
you can't fool me
i will not i refuse
[Music]
where can we see your concert um um it's
not live anymore but you can still watch
the archive
uh
if you buy a ticket on spawn
spwn
uh is the website where you can buy the
ticket uh but yeah look up link your
wish
hololive link your wish whole live and
then you'll get to the concert
it's worth it it was a great concert two
day concert i was on day two with kelly
but both of us only had one song but i
think still um it was worth it there was
also the indonesian
uh girls did i say saturday i was there
on sunday did i say saturday
i mean sunday if i said saturday
[Music]
any idea when on blu-ray no but they did
announce that there will be a blu-ray i
just don't know when but i think it will
be worth it
you're thinking of talking what no
shut up you're thinking i'm talking me
why do you think so much about dokomi
guys
dear lord stop thinking so much about
dokomi
[Music]
[Laughter]
creeping me out man
anyway
[Music]
it's illegal to bring on an airplane the
pressure might actually cause the can to
explode uh-huh you can imagine the
consequences
i don't know
i mean but that's generally for all
kinds of like
liquid foods in a can right
anything they say could explode
but in this case it would be a really
stinky explosion so
look it up on youtube
did someone do it
oh hell no let me look it up strumming
[Music]
gordon ramsay
what
gordon tries fermented fish
[Music]
i need to watch this
quickly
wait can we watch it together it's four
minutes long
can we watch it together
let's watch it together
i'll count down
[Music]
okay the link is in the
uh in the chat
let's go let's go let's go let's go
let's go phone gang i'm sorry you gotta
wait four minutes
he's british i already know he ain't
gonna like it british people eat some
weird stuff too though
okay uh on zero on zero three two one
zero
oh that looks so nice
oh winter in sweden is beautiful
hmm
who is this who's this guy
oh is this
is this one of those houses
rock fisk
black fisk he sounded like an austrian
to me
backfish
[Laughter]
okay this is when they're not rotten yet
i like their hats
oh really
popular are they trolling him
is this gonna be swimming
because they said different name they
didn't say sewer streaming
you suck gordon ramsay
that's not but similar oh okay wait why
did it stop for me continue sorry it was
just for one second
is it still stinky though
[Laughter]
what a [\h__\h] amateur
don't you love
those times when other people
make fun of gordon ramsay for being a
[\h__\h] cook at what they're doing
and but this is
not rotten yet is it
oh christmas match
stinky bloody hell mate
oh yeah
[Laughter]
well i mean people like really stinky
cheese too
so
but how was the flavor you have to eat
it out of respect gordon
oh [\h__\h] yeah
what is his reaction
we'll never know his reaction
i'll never know his reaction
[\h__\h] cliffhanger
oh come on
he probably didn't like it
okay but what about swish swimming in an
airplane what airplane
what what did you mean with look it up
on youtube i don't see any videos of
search dreaming in an airplane eating
sour streaming with pewdiepie
oh dear
i don't say anything about an airplane
i want to see someone open a can of
search timing in
oh my god wait someone uh trying do you
mean this one in the car
and the thumbnail it looks like they're
like it's exploding
it says i've ruined my car trying switch
streamings
yeah
i wanna i'm kindling yes
that one's fake nah really
all right
okay let's quickly quickly watch this
one
cats reacting to so slamming oh oh no
those poor cats you're like poisoning
them
poisoning their noses
poor kitty cats okay on zero
five
four
three
[Music]
two
one
zero
no
this is a famous youtuber that i don't
know
funny
youtube editing be like
[Laughter]
open the door
you stupid [\h__\h] open the car door
you're poisoning yourself you're not
drinking
ewe
[Laughter]
oh
yeah but you still should open the car
door
okay stop i've had i've seen enough just
i've had enough okay
not a huddle at least at least it
happened right in the beginning
that's all i needed to see
all right all right all right okay good
enough
man this is like uh
this is youtube huh
youtubers be like that
that felt so much like youtube
like the the oh dear
oh dear
that is that's youtube for ya
the editing was so utelish man
and the jokes like oh man
okay
okay i've had enough of youtube for
today
[Music]
youtube in a nutshell
all right let's continue where was i um
yeah messed up brain spike
wow
thank you
many sweets don't like licorice either
but also many do like it which is okay i
mean to each your own i'm i'm surprised
like
but it's really just a
thing of what your taste buds are used
to
[Music]
nice gordon ramsay
you don't remember eating that huh
yeah
uh 24 rare rough duncan thank you
[Music]
thank you my grandma and her friends ate
so swimming when i got home i honestly
thought the sewers were blocked or
something
[Music]
interesting
wait today when you came home
davashi thank you
[Music]
someone telling a story about opening up
a can of swiss swimming in the in the
water of a bathtub like under the water
and it still was so strong that they
threw up
because of it just because of the smell
oh my god lino's omega dangerous
for the pinky thank you i love your
streams you're amazing in hall of face
more dancing feelings please thank you
any chance you and reina can do a
karaoke stream when you're together i
know you both like michi m i do love
midgm perhaps a cover of my favorite
news three nine uh only guy
uh
well me and dana are definitely planning
on doing a song cover um
but currently we're not planning on we
were not planning on doing michy m i
love for example id
but uh elena already did that with
neneji
um but that would have been a perfect uh
two people
in collab song um but yeah um i'll
probably
most likely cover a michy m song
sometime in the future
even if it is so low
yeah and uh
because you're asking for more dancing
phoenix uh i'm gonna tell you one thing
now
that
is a bit unfortunate
i
was planning i made a whole list
of songs that are
okay in karaoke streams generally so
that i could sing them
in an archived stream
like japanese songs like vocaloid and
idol songs and all that that have a
choreo that i can also dance
now i had this whole list
um but then
[Music]
i was
i was too
good
because i asked on a different topic
how it is with you know choreographies
copyright of choreography
do we need to get permission from
whoever makes the choreographies of each
song as well i asked that because of
something else
for like future concerts if i want to
cover some songs and dance along with
them
and i was like
yeah you know what yeah actually yeah
we have to ask
so
[Music]
that is not true
how would you know like someone made the
choreographies just like so just like
how someone made the song i mean
i think
i mean that one goes a little bit too
far but um i i somehow get it like
someone made it so i guess
i mean i don't see why
the person who made the choreo for any
dance would care whether or not i'm
dancing there's the choreo
but in theory
they made it
so
i mean i wouldn't say it's cop i don't i
don't think they copyrighted it like
but but
but
[Laughter]
yeah so now because i asked
i have to
for every vocaloid song or idol song or
whatever
if there's a choreography that i want to
dance
then i have to contact
[Music]
the choreographer and ask for permission
but the thing is like most of these like
idol music videos they don't credit the
choreographer so i don't even know who
the choreographer is so i would have to
ask
the the music
the people in charge of the music video
or like the mu the label or the
management or whoever is behind it that
is
uh contactable reachable
yeah
yeah so
it's it's
gonna be
not that easy i was gonna do it like
sometime soon but in this case i have
a full choreography is copyrighted but
individual moves yeah yeah yeah yeah
they're not yeah yeah that makes sense
but yeah um
so
i will try to get um permissions for as
many
songs as possible
maximum tie hen yes
[Music]
why is everything so complicated oh
being so complicated i see a layer
[Music]
acting like somebody else gets me
frustrated lives like this you
yeah
but it's gonna take a while probably
to get actually answers from all these
places and sometimes
probably for a lot of the vocaloid songs
like the older ones
that have choreographies probably a lot
of them are not even reachable but
yeah i'm gonna try
i'm gonna try
i know
okay
[Music]
um
they don't do dance streams and in
concerts i've seen like even when they
perform songs
that have like
choreographies that i know they usually
don't dance those they they
have like original
different mostly different ones i've
seen them dance
something before
i don't remember what it was but i've
seen them dance something before that i
i know is like
not their original choreography but
really from the song
um like someone else's choreography but
not that often but i don't know if they
asked permission for that one
but in any case i i will have to
ask for permission so
in order to get a whole stream together
where i can dance
um
i
i'll have to ask quite a lot of people
yeah
so i don't know if if it's gonna happen
so soon i wanna dance more
i wanna dance with somebody
um
yeah
i thought yo let's go
i'm really motivated to dance and i got
my vr bottle and all that let's go but
no no let's go let's walk very very
slowly
one day we'll reach it one day
it is what it is guys it is what it is
jim tracy
now my mom won't let me watch your
stream anymore thanks kiara eh why
because i didn't like the licorice
messed up brain spike thank you and i'll
call this duncan fat cat duncan
if there's a time i should be super
chatting as a swedish now hell
yeah by swedish peeps
i'm kelly from sweden hello man to you
[Music]
oh because i said hell with it
unity chad dankeson
yeah yeah yeah
i love it too
spain comes first though um thank you
for renewing your membership angry ghost
the gamer creed duncan thank you
yes different cultural snacks yeah yeah
yeah
i think it's a great
great concept that we're doing here
[Music]
mr khan 56 duncan judy duncan eric
newstern
glad you liked the snacks also i cannot
let the earlier super chat stand
unchallenged
friendly rivalry ah
thank you for the pinky
it's both of those countries are great
sweden and norway so
come on hold each other's hands shake
them and then give each other a hug okay
be nice to each other all right all
right all right
and blazing blade 147 duncan
moment of the bra vacation
yeah the pony one
i would have probably liked the
[Music]
oh i would have probably liked the the
other one wait what
the polybag has two different flavors
the bright milk chocolate ones with arak
that you didn't like and the dark
chocolate ones with vanilla flavor oh
wait there are two flavors in there
they all look this ah wait no um
actually
wait there is indeed
darker ones and brighter ones i don't
know which one i ate
i think i ate the brighter one
[Music]
which one am i supposed to eat
the dark chocolate ones are supposedly
with vanilla flavor okay let me try
that one i should like
[Music]
that just tastes
fine
[Music]
i guess yeah it was the rx i knew that
though because that gave it like a weird
alcohol flavor
[Music]
this one is better yeah yeah
for me at least
five of the tent yeah but i don't
i don't like this marshmallow texture
that much the chewy
marshmallowy texture
inside
[Music]
i don't like that
so much but
it's all right though
thanks for telling me i didn't know this
because inside the bag it was so dark
i thought it was all the same
[Music]
i don't really like the texture chewy
texture too
same tbh
you guys are so much alike hashtag
relatable
and eddie duncan
so swedish and norwegian crown so i
thought i should join
where did you see them hi from random
japanese living in denmark oh
hello
dark master dankeshun uza dankeshan in
sweden
so
so many swedish people what's up
palestine
oh you're drowning in swedish people
dark 111 dancing it's not syndra
uh no way
danish crones no norwegian crones
swedish crones so many crones crowns
crones crowns
let me koopa 13 function
insert name here zero zero one dankeson
[Music]
i mean we're we're good with hungary
are you are you making a joke because of
history doctor no shame thank you nice
gordon ramsay thank you so much
hell no
that sounds like a [\h__\h] out of work
but i wonder
if they would let it slide if i do it
unarchived
i might ask that maybe they'll let it
slide
if i do the dancing stream unarchived
even though it's songs that could be
archived
[Music]
maybe they'll let the slide
ah
and the game recreate duncan
ah sweet that's titty good to hear that
i think i'm done reading super chats
only took me one hour and i had chit
chat in between
yeah you surprise kfp
i can be fast too
like sonic
yeah thank you
thank you soon everybody
thank you
i only have one glove so i'm just going
to do a one-hand heart here there you go
korean heart
[Music]
please try being slow and excited i'm
always so slow no i want to end it at a
decent time today
that was fun i like these snack box
review streams thank you guys for
joining me today on this tomorrow we
have
a long long long yakuza stream again
gonna continue with majima's storyline
yeah yeah
so if you're curious what happens next
in yakuza
and if you didn't
catch up yet with the previous episode
do it now because tomorrow we're playing
yakuza
and i would love to have you guys there
also my swedish friends and everybody
else
[Music]
and thank you for all the people who
came today
and for the swedish people who told me
if these snacks are accurate or not
[Music]
very helpful thank you
oh yeah if you want some of these there
are like for example this one you can
get in ikea
uh this one
this one too some of the other ones as
well or similar ones yeah the the poly
one you can also get an ikea
and you can get many other things in
ikea that are not edible though mm-hmm
oh but
if you guys never had kurt polla before
wait it's not purple it's shut bula
you should eat it
[Music]
yeah
i might eat it tonight
[Music]
all right and thank you everybody i'll
see you tomorrow good night i'll i'll
sleep tonight in my fresh
new ikea summer blanket with my fresh
new ikea
uh
[Music]
sheets
yeah
it's gonna be comfy my cats are enjoying
them too
[Music]
hello from sweden a goodbye to sweden
it's over now but feel free to watch the
archive
i like your snacks yo the good snacks
you got there
awesome
[Applause]
[Music]
blue
do
[Music]
you