[Music]
this is
thank you
[Music]
this is
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
ah five minutes is normal waiting time
why you guys like quinoa
it's normal
[Music]
it's been five minutes
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
that's so hot and I feel
weird
I feel like um I know look I'm just
drunk in 20 liters of water
but I didn't
oh my God
wow
[Music]
God damn it
my cats
[Music]
they went to the balcony
I have to wait for them to come back
but
don't talk about idle meaning
[Music]
uh
here here have some music do you hear
this
maybe not
sure
oh
you don't hear it
okay now
hello
we're gonna finish playing the entropy
Center today
uh can I play full screen last time
[Music]
I think so I miss that video it's so
nostalgic right
classic
yeah yeah yeah
I did
okay okay okay and then I guess I'll do
that again like you go here for now
let's play
the entropy Center for like 10 hours
today shall we
I don't think there's really 10 hours
left
oh but
maybe the game will surprise me with
some difficulties Spike
and
who knows okay we can turn the museum
off now
[Music]
mail mail
maybe my cattle should come back now
let me get my cat's back
foreign
[Music]
towards chonkers and she's like
and runs the opposite direction away
from me I ran after her and she hides
under
the
balcony
Furniture chair
to escape but
of course
I'll catch you snow Escape
[Music]
I might have to
um
open the window several times today
because it's I feel like oh I'm feeling
weird
[Applause]
[Music]
I feel like there's no air coming from
my lungs that's one of those days we're
having one of those days
loud
sorry
yes
one cup of tea
some water
and
I have only one fruit candy left you for
real oh my God I need to buy more fruit
candies [\h__\h]
ah the tea you sent to bite now I'm
drinking a fruit tea
in the distance yeah man I I was eating
so many of the fruit candies yesterday
huh
sword is now
um
I'll probably feel normal again in like
an hour or so
yeah
uh okay
uh so
are you guys ready for this
portal free just kidding
for the entropy Central
[Music]
is meowing in the distance
it's been a week or so
chocolates
but oh yeah November 4th
that like 10 p.m I got really into it
last time I think it was
um
really really like I don't know catchy
grabs you the puzzles are I don't know
if you guys all saw the last stream but
the puzzles are very manageable still
too loud okay
[Music]
very manageable and uh yeah
I'll just make it quieter here
thank you
wow
how about now it will probably not be so
loud when we're in the game because
there's normally no bgm I think
and uh yeah yeah yeah yeah what was I
saying oh yeah I like the story so far
game gives us lots of little itsy bitsy
bits of story and then it's really nice
um oh yeah full screen I guess
yeah I guess I can do full screen
[Music]
this is
where we left off lasting
what oh
is this where I came from last time okay
last time the last puzzle was it was not
necessarily difficult
because I did figure it out by myself
and I'm so proud of myself the last two
puzzles actually were tough
Oh see now it's too quiet at least for
me
thank you
let's hurry I can't let that reactor
become too unstable that's decent
yeah yeah yeah oh Lord oh we're already
starting back with some lore
tell me tell me what's this about
uh how to play this game again their
puzzle operatives I think that's me we
would like it to remind we would like to
remind you of the following side effects
of repetitive rewinding as you are all
aware you endure a personal
self-isolated
wait I've read this before
[Music]
have we
been here before
there's no save like it was supposed to
be automatic safe after every time you
enter over a door
wait is this new
I think
[Music]
I read the Lord okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay I just read the Lord I
was like I probably was like oh my god
well let's at least write the Lord
before we go and then okay bye-bye okay
okay I feel like I remember now
oh thank God thank God I was gonna start
to morph in five seconds
oh hi
so let's see if I remember this game uh
actually I
don't I think he was like placing things
and then uh ah our R is resetting
and then
what's rewind
wow what which what
ah it's just left click Mouse click
right click we're still left click
it is okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
so that's I think that was most of that
oh
something about that laser we have to do
something with
the laser is another Cube
uh-huh
that
okay that moves the platform and this
helps me get to the door okay and I
probably need another Cube up there
because the door is locked
[Music]
I made a game because they were big fans
of portal and they're not like really
even trying to hide the fact that it's
like portal so you're seeing that
correctly Cali however it comes with a
time rewinding function which portal did
not have but yeah it's really cute I
agree the story is cute and like they
they make some things different and the
puzzles are kind of easier
you know oh my God Cali was part of my
dream I just remember last night
Ina Ina and Cali
um they took a it took a private jet
from Tokyo to Osaka
[Laughter]
and Cali was like telling me to not talk
on stream about the fact that they took
a private jet
because it would be like
kind of like showing off that you know
it's so expensive and
and the people shouldn't know that we
take private jets now
but yeah it's bad for the image yet
yeah yeah
but uh I was not part of the private jet
team I think it's kind of sad I want to
ride the private jet too
you're living it big wow
her street cred
oh that was just one part of my dream
I've been having so many weird ads
unnecessary and and just weird [\h__\h]
dreams recently every night every night
it just
it's so [\h__\h] weird I wake up and I'm
like what the [\h__\h] just happened
but but a private jet that's just gonna
say this right now I'm pretty sure
taking a private jet is like
way way way way way
out of our
budgets I think
right Kelly I mean
I mean I I I I I I I I don't think Kelly
um I mean I don't know how much does it
cost
they have enough
to private jet from Tokyo to
um I took you to Osaka the most we could
do is probably shinkansen first class
Maybe
not not first class they call it green
green shop greensha
the green the green the green
yeah yeah it's too much too much private
jet crazy
okay let's let's start uh using our
brains so I'm guessing that I have to
reach this thing like
here wait what did this door ever no it
didn't it did never
open it's that thing up there
oh god oh
ah two thousand to eleven thousand per
billable flight hour
that's actually a bit cheaper than I
thought it was gonna be
when you say flight hour
does it really not matter how much
distance you travel in that hour
maybe that's where the 2 000 to 11 000
uh comes from the variation
okay
one hour five minutes jet slide in Japan
next time I'm there yeah Daddy will have
to split it
I mean a 2000 if it's really 2 000 for
one hour I mean I doubt it it's probably
more like six thousand Japan also seems
like it would be more expensive six six
thousand okay let's split it let's split
it after all
oh my god well that's that's surprising
but maybe that's like American Standards
or so
yeah is Yen is cheap is that a good
thing uh in terms of private jet
um
let's look into it yeah only not only
the outlet can do it because it's cheap
all right all righty
so I feel like eventually I do need this
here
but wait I am already confused why why
what do we how does this work again
the laser oh wait
isn't the laser actually already
activating that thing oh it does not
have um it's not meant to be activated
when it's not activated then it's
activated
I'm turning everybody's brains inside
out
a little
[Music]
okay so I need to turn it off
um so for that
I would like to bring a cube up there
when I jump
I don't remember how to play this game
how to think how do you launch the box
but I need oh wait I can stand on it
you're right oh God
ah oh sometimes you have to think
outside of the box AKA beat a box
yourself oh and then
um we rewind the time
and make it stop
when it's intercept
how do I go back
was there a a go back rewind stop rewind
stop rewind just makes it drop right
there right
oh [\h__\h] ah oh never mind stop rewind
makes it oh go back what what's the way
to just drop it there was a way to just
drop it there we go
yeah okay
then we have made it we are here with
the cube if it doesn't fall down
okay
so
aha maybe again we do this thing where
no no this time the cube is not gonna go
up there because the cube is not picking
up the other Cube I am the one picking
okay
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
uh-huh uh-huh I almost fell down did you
see that because I thought I thought
maybe you guys didn't notice oh [\h__\h]
huh
uh how do you drop it again
there we go oh yeah oh okay I guess it
didn't work like that when it was in the
air because it was like still like
flying oh oh
oh but the laser killed
oh
it's all laser Cube
uh what are we gonna do with the lady
how am I gonna get up
a jack
would I land there
[Music]
is this portable Portal 2 already exists
this is Portal free okay
but I do need
ah I see oh [\h__\h] no uh no wait it's okay
I think I need to throw both the cube
and myself
but first the cube
yeah and then probably the thing to open
the door over there is one that needs a
laser
hold on oh we can just wait we can just
fly together
wait this wasn't so difficult hey wait
I did okay
um so it wasn't so easy
[Music]
I forgot one detail
um
I have an idea
oh [\h__\h] I have an idea that
um we will have this cube move over
there
and then back here
and then basically like where you rewind
so it will be there to you know whatever
explain
is difficult
but I need this Cube up there so I can't
have it be this Cube I need it to be
this Cube and I think that could work I
just need to
be smart about it total weight
let me get you
um
I think
and then
yeah okay I get it I get it I get it uh
but hey let me let me put you here and
reset
and then with you
I fly over to the other side
place you here
and then I bring you back one more time
holy [\h__\h] big brain waves are coming out
of my brain so now I think that does the
trick into my mouth
wait no
but wait
how
what
How Will I
okay
um
yeah maybe
no no no no no no no no no no so
I I need the skill to be there so I can
jump but I also need to skip to be there
so I can land
um
oh [\h__\h] I just set the plan in motion
yeah yeah but I feel like there's
something missing
it hurts your brain too early in the
morning yeah for me too man
let's see can I drink my tea
laser Cube rewind
um but to what point you mean so that it
stands on there but then if even if I
land up there then have to like get the
cube up there
you mean like catch it in the air
I guess we can try catching it in the
air
let me um erase that down
so
okay I mean yeah it's got pretty much
the edge of that should be possible to
catch it in the air
Canada
what what
of the international YouTubers scene
becoming as big as it is being an
Insider what do you think is its impact
on Japan's Japan's
soft power
does that mean on the international
stage do you think Hawaii and will start
getting deals with the Japanese
government
no
he's ranking in a much bigger picture
[Laughter]
oh I'm not sure a hundred percent
understand the question but I think the
answer is no
sorry I think the answer is no
did I get it right is that is that a
puzzle too
are we gonna be politicians
you didn't think
thank you
if I rewind it to catch it then the
platform is gonna fall down
I see okay don't don't even say anything
guys I get it so before we rewind this
one we rewind the other one I can't even
say rewind anymore
thank you
okay oh that added all to the time she
so smart
so now we bring this one back because we
don't need to jump anymore
hi hi hi hi hi uh is that properly on
there because that's important I'll just
drop it just in case
and then
bring this one up here
oh yeah
let's go
16. no I was I was tangenting I was
talking to Callie 16 minutes that's not
accurate like time puzzle solving time
solvling
solving I puzzled the solving so bling
I finished chapter eight it seems oh
wait I was so close to finishing a
chapter oh
no no no no no no
she forgot how to resume
the laser
um
run uh I don't have a running
dashing button but sure sure okay let's
run oh [\h__\h]
up
so cool isn't it oh God
goodbye goodbye
good morning you are surrounded
[\h__\h] what about this one can I can I
dust that platform
thank you for telling me Oh my God
[Laughter]
uh crunch Crouch oh
I I like that they implement this into
like Escape missions though I think it's
really cool no no no no no no
time to waste Arya
recommendation they're mad as hell let's
go
[Music]
next is right side right side
don't get too close buddy
uh now uh this thing is gonna drop it
faster faster drop it drop it faster
oh God
the platform heated me into the fangs of
the robot
just touching once is apparently enough
to die
[Music]
recommendation oh
okay this time I'll try to not stand too
close to the platform
for Japanese culture and then we're
getting where the government are care
about cultural experts so do you foresee
any deals no no no no no so that part I
think I understood no I don't think
we're gonna get any deals with the
government I don't know what what
exactly you would like imaginary though
hahaha
uh I would like some deals with Burger
King though oh [\h__\h] Which Way ah this
way maybe they just
wanted oh Burger King or or or
uh any other cool fast food restaurant
those guys
oh oh that did not hurt so much
interesting
yeah yeah yeah we can take that one hit
apparently
I think
oh it's not over
here
lock down lock down oh [\h__\h] never lock
that I thought wait we're done with that
[\h__\h]
[Music]
oh
jumpy pants jumpy pad jumpy pad uh where
where we're going out here here
[Music]
attack rewind it oh my God
interact okay uh that uh was one of four
okay this is so stressful
where should I go next uh over there
over there looks like there could be
something over there I'm just I'm just
stalling
that one I think I can reach without
jumping uh with a jumping pad
never mind I need the jumping bag
I thought maybe if I was lucky it would
shoot the uh the other robots
[\h__\h] stressful okay that was the left
two I need one more on the right side
yeah
foreign
over there okay okay okay no problem
can I like do this oh
a little protection from the absolutely
batshit insane robots
Okay
it is
you you oh they're not following me
suddenly
[Music]
sheesh that moved
been a while
that cube is huge oh wait it's a it's a
statue
oh
doesn't work so well on a cube does it
it's not that like impressive
[Music]
pray to the cube
okay I suppose we have to jump over that
how how
convenient that it exploded
lore looking for some lore
oh really no more
what about this one what about this one
oh that's the one that's the one
it's time for some more
Sam ball says to Leanne
hi Anne I just wanted to get in touch
regarding the latest entropy rewind
events of Earth I know you're analyzing
the subject as well with the
humanitarian study team well the latest
data is I'll let it speak for itself are
you seeing this pattern too we're seeing
a 60 drop in random natural disaster
events
oh that sounds good and the 76 rise in
cataclysmic events caused by Humanity
oh
we used to be about saving endangered
species and Wildlife now we seem to be
to mostly be caught up in humanity-based
Affairs how much longer before this gets
out of hand I'm going to be hosting a
lecture during this Friday's meeting
going into more detail about this let's
catch up soon interesting
have you known this already that this
cataclysmic event was most likely caused
by humans I felt that we heard this for
the first time
oh there's extra lore if I go up oh I
will try thank you
okay please note that this Friday staff
meeting is now mandatory Dr Sam ball is
hosting a lecture regarding some
important findings regarding the
frequency of the type of cataclysmic
events that we are encountering oh
they're actually like supporting it
so what should I stand on can I stand on
for sure okay
okay
what the [\h__\h]
you then troll me right to kill me
okay so that area okay okay
did I just stand on the wrong spot
oh there is a really really okay I'll
stand on the box maybe that's the same
ooh
we didn't die this time
very sick
it's like strong moment
I would respect you for that
oh
[Music]
exactly what I needed
welcome to your daily dose of entropy
cat facts did you know that cats have
whiskers on the backs of their front
legs as well oh yeah I think I kind of
did they have like longer hairs there a
few that stand out and also the cats
have 230 bones whereas humans have two
and a six
that small thing has way more bones that
we have in comparison yeah I kind of
knew that too I think because they can
like twist and turn in all kinds of ways
stay tuned for more entropy cat facts
unsubscribe please Ben what the [\h__\h] why
would you unsubscribe Ben sucks
thanks for subscribing to Enterprise as
you're already a subscribe member we
will continue sending cat facts no
unsubscribe to e-pails
you cannot escape the cat facts Ben
unsubscribe is just seen as subscribe
but that's not how that works Ben like
when you want to unsubscribe from
something like that you have to scroll
down in the email and click on the
really really small letter link to
unsubscribe
that's how it normally works let me just
check out this area I guess there's
nothing here oh
no number nine nope nope nothing nothing
okay
[Music]
yeah Ben doesn't know how to interweb
break that down
I think we can just let it fall before I
fall oh all this one's still here
um I I know I guess it belongs to that
okay okay next door next door
I think
it was worth going back for that
oh it's so steamy in here huh
very steamy
oh the windows even have um
that's kind of like
cracked not cracked like the once when
it's [\h__\h] cold outside
uh effect I like that no no nice detail
a frost oh Frost yeah
so we have
our beloved Bridge again oh how I missed
you the watercolor is so beautiful
is that a dead robot what is that
something in the water looks like a
something
interesting
but anyway I'll just bring this with me
for now
how do we make this move ah
Ita
oh
so this goes on the bridge
uh
you know what I don't I don't have the
I was gonna say
else to just place it on the bridge so I
was just gonna rewind it to that state
um
can I can I get you back
and just refresh
the site
[Music]
um
okay there you go I did that and now I
kind of rewind it
should have waited a little bit longer
why don't you guys tell me to wait
longer I'm so impatient
and you know what just in case we need
it
I will rewind it so that you know I have
it here in case I need to catch it I
don't think so though I will see
don't put this on us
do what I want
and I'm staying this is on you
hey
oh
I need the bridge
here
I have to okay
[Music]
I understand though I need to
um hold the bridge down here
yeah
so that it can go for the water and then
I can catch it in the water and now
damn it
let's do it again hi
go back
pretty much quite though repeating
patterns so it's easy to figure out
so now I want to
um can I audit
you can like do stuff with the laser one
from here but not with the bridge one
did I do it wrong
no no I guess I'll just do it from here
that way I should probably reach it yeah
okay okay
oh everything's falling down
please don't tell me I have to
eventually bring them
back again
into the original position but what I
will do is bring this one with me that
was probably necessary
oh no
how how how
what how how
oh
I called it I need to start by once
placing the bridge so it goes through
here
it's [\h__\h] bastards
make you like redo everything
okay
oh wait oh
no that was the original state of the
cube anyway
if we didn't like move too much with it
we may have been able to
get to that state
anyway I don't know
but it only has like what 45 seconds or
so that you can record on it so
um
we needed in three different locations
[Music]
I don't know man
I don't know if this is really
possible well I guess we have to try and
try to save as much time as we can
oh wait
um
let me reset that uh
one more time because we have to start
by holding it out and then placing it
then
and
this one goes back dude am I doing it
right
I I think wait
no I forgot the cubes ah
no no no I didn't forget them no this
was right oh God damn it
um hi
uh
I'm not sure but let's just dance wrong
yeah but now
no it's okay
it's okay it's okay guys
okay this one's this one's safe
I just hope it doesn't waste too much
time floating in the water
and then you little [\h__\h]
uh
okay
15 seconds
that's all right
that seems all right
okay
I thought it would be more by now
uh yeah okay okay that's it I think
that's the most we can do with that Cube
don't tell me I need it over there
that's like impossible
so now
go to the very back
how I am today well thank you for uh
asking
thank you for asking
I am okay I guess
I know I feel like breathing is a little
bit hard today but besides that
oh my God it looks gorgeous I wanna go
um
are we going down there I want to go
down there I want to go to like uh one
of those indoor tropical water parks
oh that's just in case you do fall down
I think
maybe the secret lore down there though
check
oh please don't reset me to the very
beginning okay there's nothing here
and they could have placed like a
maybe they did and I didn't find it
because I feel like they could have
easily placed like a computer somewhere
you know like we had one very hidden one
in between the Rocks before
yeah I think I think that's tropical
indoor park is in Germany I I don't know
which country which one was it do you
guys remember
did anyone have the info
actually sounds like a fun trip
depending on which country which city
and drink some more Tea near Berlin
because you know it deemed
near Berlin
[Music]
near Berlin that sounds kind of
difficult like it wouldn't be very easy
to reach unless you have a car
I'll talk to you rewind talk you can
restore its tall State no time Gates do
not remove rewind from tall cubes
how many more of these puzzle elements
do you have oh many many
hot club
so I suppose it's like you stand on top
of it
then you rewind it and you're able to
reach like it's like basically like a
jumping platform but you just don't jump
I don't know I don't like tall Cube tall
Cube sucks
but okay oh
when you pick it up it falls
okay
[Music]
why why are we uh
making it tall wait
ah
I think I understand though more or less
well then what is the bridge for
if I reach the top with that
let me just bring the bridge with me
uh
I don't know if I can
oh I can't
but hey this is not even high enough
never mind
ah it's for here it's for here
and then the bridge to reach the other
side okay I'll go easy easy easy
all people propaganda
okay did I like miss any lore
I don't think so
smart yeah see this is when they
introduced a new
um element they're gonna give you an
easy oh wait ah I okay I think it's okay
oh wait
[Music]
that had to stand on it but the bridge
killed
okay okay okay
uh
there we go that should do the trick
talking this is a silly idea it is
foreign
[Music]
I thought we were like
I know 25
seconds
[Music]
I can't pick it up
redo
25 seconds is too much you haven't
already get to 25 seconds what the [\h__\h]
that's when the Companion Cube is better
I I would not necessarily agree with
that
[Laughter]
maybe the looks uh and the charm is
better
but
I feel like
this Cube has more uses
I made it a little bit unnecessarily
long but oh yeah oh yeah yeah
now you move back
[Music]
companionship would never threaten to
stab me what did this one important to
stop me
I don't remember that
foreign
you could only put it on bridge on the
walls so if you place it here then it
goes like straight from there
so sometimes it was quite difficult to
place it how you wanted it to be but
then the cube can be wherever wherever
whenever we need to be together I'll be
there and you'll be here
oh okay we're dealing with one normal
Cube
a Tolkien Cube
ah
[Music]
no no no
reset
um I understand this
the percent this is uh easy
okay and now
[Music]
and then if I rewind it I can
you know
move over there but I guess I'll be
taking this one with me
I hope that's the one that I need
because it looks like it can make me
reach the top over there on the end
oh wait
it's the other one first ah you know you
have to think backwards
backwards so
starting here free fresh
it's always backwards always think
backwards when you're rewinding the time
hi okay
taking this with me
okay now you can all go up there
very finicky here
because if we go too far
on it
there we go
too far we [\h__\h] up we don't want that
let's see I already solved it but today
yeah
excuse me
[Applause]
lower time baby
why does it keep happening we want to
cut the cosmic event
hmm
because the humans did not learn
why is Earth on fire fire in the Earth
make a better tomorrow
how does the world end
um to rui the world ends with you that's
how it ends
that's how with you why why fire in the
water what no
fire inside Earth wait there is no lore
here I guess the lower is only the
these white panels I thought there's two
PCS I thought there would be some lore
okay
oh 904
what do we have here by the way I do
have tangents
I'm just like
I don't know I'm I'm enjoying the
thinking time right now
I'll talk about things
uh a little bit later
who I think
opens the door okay
so that's where it has to end up last
um
oh yeah
where is ah I didn't see that those look
like decoration
let me try and see what's up there
another place where the laser must be
placed and here
here
too but
oh there's nothing
no more what
freaking bamboozle
why do they decline me the lore I need
to know
ah but I think
don't get it
we'll figure it out as we go
I will I will
reset you here although I probably have
to redo everything again
uh
most likely
[\h__\h] what happens
it doesn't have enough space it's stupid
call Cube needs to be not only tall but
also a bit thicker
foreign
okay why did they open that up for us
because I was already able to get there
why why why why why not
[Music]
bring tall Cube
because I can't bring him up like that
but I can walk around
go up the stairs go through here
yeah okay so I was thinking as well
to try to reach the laser
like this but
if I understand correctly
then
I can only really send the laser through
this not for the windows
wait wait what what is this for then
what is why did I bring it here then
why did I bring it here
or does the laser
that um
no not the lens does that door up there
open as well no wait
ah
I just saw it
up here
there's an opening a nice opening there
but I feel like I already have
too much time on this Cube
which
um I think maybe is not
even a problem
let me just reset this again
because I can walk around but that adds
a lot of time to
ah wait the door
oh
why are you calling me a cheater
wait actually like I [\h__\h] up though
because like I can't I can't get anymore
I thought the door stayed open or
something like that for some reason
[Music]
ah
I have to redo now
yeah bug report I'm a game tester I test
this game and I say the result is
I have found a bug
yeah you're welcome I need to be paid
for my hard work
a fun bug though very fun if only it
would have landed exactly so that the
laser would Point towards the
the panel
nah of course it's not that simple no no
no no no
I would have appreciated the bug then
now I do not appreciate it
wait
oh
um let me think
I place it here to open the door then I
walk around bring the tall Cube here
okay okay
why did I do it right there
try to not get too much time on the
small cube
because otherwise we have to do it all
over again
finding all the bugs I'm an exterminator
bug exterminator
all the austrians
Arnold Schwarzenegger and me we both are
exterminated no wait he's the Terminator
I'm the extraordinator ah okay what's
the difference there
ah goodbye
don't shoot dare fall down
seven
I got it I got it yeah why did this door
open
ah
none
the wine
wait a second
oh I did it
[Music]
okay
well my problem is that if I move that
one
back then
the stairs won't be there
but
it was disabled to activate buttons on
the ground just by being flat
him yes how can you eat
it's not gonna work
what do you mean to eat
um
wait can I can I if I go all the way
down can I get all the way back up again
no no I can't because that door is
closed
um
ah
wait but does that really work on flat
platforms like on on these flat things
there
does this really work because
even if I redo everything in reverse
do I have to
reset cue while it is on the top
go for the door like you did oh
it but it's closed
I mean go for the door which door
Oh you mean like the cute products
don't worry again
well I wonder if I can
ah [\h__\h] I don't want to do this all over
again
you tell them onto the bridge and Falls
you stand on top
and reverse it's to lift it back up
you think that it will be enough to lift
me high enough to get up there I don't
think so if that's what you're trying to
do yeah
take the tall one to the bridge when it
falls you stand on top and then reverse
it to lift it back up
I mean like stand here
huh
no no no no no no no no no like how do I
undo this then while I'm here
yeah and the reverse of the tall Cube
only makes it taller it will never go
back to its original position either
uh yeah I feel like
[\h__\h] up
I [\h__\h] up again
[\h__\h] eh no no there must be because this
is already I can't do the whole path
twice this is already at 33 seconds
I can't I can't think
end up here
no it can't um
I don't want to reset it no
no it's okay it's it's okay it's it's is
it okay it might be okay it's okay I
think it's okay
I have an idea
um
oh [\h__\h]
wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait
okay that's not even necessary but
wait let me let me let me
test yet don't test it now Chihuahua you
won't be able to come back
but um
[Music]
actually that might be pretty smart
thing to do
because then I can skip this door can I
not
no I can't
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
but
I'm thinking take this one down
here the that Cube bring it here stop
run down bring it there
oh but wait
but wait
um
problem is I need the door no
I don't need to be open
I just need the big one in the end I
only need it down there maybe
so that after I drop off the cube there
I lift myself up with the tall Cube I
come back here
and then I walk up here
and reverse the small cube all the way
to okay I think that should work
are you following my train of font hmm
thought of train
ah bye bye Mario
yeah of course I can't have it in two
places once but I think I figured it out
I think I got it
so you're gonna stand there
so okay okay my my goal is just to bring
it down there I guess right
right wait wait wait wait wait wait
no wait wait
wait
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah yeah okay okay in that case
[Music]
um
in that case
I will just
but now I really have to redo everything
dad left me with no choice but now we
can test this at least
okay it works
hi hi but then yeah I I I I I I I I am
confused because in order to get up
there here in the first place
uh upset oh
yeah
and activate these things I have to
bring it there and then if I want to
bring it back
and
all right time to explain
[Music]
ah
like now even now I need the cube
huh
no okay well let's do this this one I
understand okay okay okay but but but
but but the butt
a bottle
I I can't rewind it to go there so like
um
I feel like I get it okay testing
wait oh yeah that doesn't work
um
come with me
[Music]
one two three four five oh it doesn't
matter
bring it back
to here so
does that make sense
does that make sense does that make
sense does that make sense does that
make sense does that make sense
doesn't make sense oh my God am I making
sense
because now I have the door open for me
yeah
and then
we reverse it oh that's actually I I
guess I added one unnecessary stuff
oh thank you so much
oh I did it
hey it was so simple and yet it took me
so much brain power to solve that one
but I solved it alone that's all that
matters
I got to that Solution on my own
maybe some of you guys were trying to
tell me that but I definitely did not
understand what you were trying to tell
me
why are you playing music I detected
decreased levels of motivation and
puzzle
Optical music can make sunflowers
produce more pollen and it can make
Chihuahua go crazy I will change
no no go back to classical music maybe
now isn't the right time disabling music
or a plane do you that would be nice
hearing my own music
maybe also not helping me in in
concentrate but it's a [\h__\h] Bop
and well
what's going on here
what are we dealing with here
[Music]
um
oh my God wait no way
oh well that's an interesting mechanic
that I did not see with the trampoline
wow
wow um like useless after all
you guys thought yeah
what is this area for
what is that everything
ah
but that's not quite explain me what
that area is for
yeah unexpected usage right I was like
looking at that and I was thinking oh
this Cube holds that door from shutting
completely so
I guess maybe we could lift it ha ha
all right so
I'm not sure
oh wait we need ah
don't I need the lifting Cube over there
once I arrive oh wait look there's also
wait a second
it's not connected are those two areas
connected
let me see
I need I need to talk Cube
to elevate myself
the thing is I was like wondering if
that's not connected if I could stop in
the middle to pick up that Cube
um but stopping like releasing the cube
from this platform will only make the
platform go back completely but maybe I
have to be fast and pick up the cube
fast I don't know
Tokyo Tokyo instead of tall Cube
Tokyo I think Tokyo no that sounds very
different
I'll just do it a few times
oh wait ideas already
Lifting me up now
oh wait oh oh
um okay
no that's fine just wait dude on the way
back
oh that stays there no no oh
we need both cubes here in the end
oh my awesome what's that I I think I
know how to do it though but first time
we bring this Cube there then
I think
huh
okay okay okay okay okay okay I got
one extra Cube also let me check this
out is that where I came from
Coney Island
we'll just we don't want to think about
anything else we
um
um yeah we're just gonna
bring small cube I hope I don't regret
this do I end up needing both cubes like
to play around here
uh
[Music]
okay and now
this is when it gets interesting
because
well
yeah hmm
[\h__\h] I I knew it would trigger me again
um
think kiwama think
let's drink
well well well
yeah yeah usually when it's something
like this then the new Cube you acquire
you will not you don't you're not
supposed to bring it immediately
immediately to the point where it needs
to go this this has been a pattern as
well
but instead you bring it like to the
other Cube
like this happened before so I had a
feeling that this would happen
so uh yeah okay I get it yeah yeah yeah
yeah so I bring it I reset this one
right here
and now I bring it over there
so that it can transport me my my old
Cube over here and then I rewind it to
this position okay okay see I understand
it like we've had this before I remember
rotation yeah
okay
I will just
um
I just don't want to make a mistake you
know um so I think it's okay to just
take it
oh this is still standing on here
so we bring this bad boy
back wait
I will already place this old Cube on
here
just kind of now be um
careful
okay this is all I needed to do s'mores
quinoa
yeah
okay okay okay okay
very smart
yeah
yeah oh big brain
Breeze now we bring it back up here
this one was easier than the previous
one for me for some reason
I'm happy with how I solved that puzzle
who is this oh we have a PowerPoint
presentation again from December 2035
okay
puzzle operative
let me move that
my shot
Sam Josh oh so many names
performance review where which one is me
yo I was foreign
[Music]
puzzle efficiency oh wow wow
overtime
not so bad for me
oh there's people who worked longer than
me definitely uh-huh
polite reminder
personal rewind event complete puzzle
generate entropy energy complete all
puzzles you get the money then we rewind
then we do puzzles then we generate then
we complete all of them then we get
money and so on and so on
um
do we forget about the money that we
received though when we do a personal
rewind event because then they could
just
like kind of like
Gaslight us couldn't they
I know
team meaning okay okay okay
I was thinking exactly that
oh
because like wait that implies that Arya
like Arya starting from where we started
in the game it felt like she didn't
really understand that she was doing
this before so she must have also
forgotten that she has ever like
received money or solved puzzles before
she did not know about this
so that means
that even if I was given money I forgot
it already
so they're probably not really paying
any of us
because I can't remember this
whole scheme any oh my God
who rewinded Arya well I mean the
management
oh
anyway like this is a whole whole
another level of brain [\h__\h] this game
it will we're getting there it will get
more and more
me criticizing someone for not paying
their employees
but is there anything weird about that
maybe I should start rewinding your
guys's memory hmm
[Music]
what do you think Hmm
hey Darren I know the entry percent is
going for some real tough times at the
moment but I think you might want to
hear this are you experiencing any
difficulties or strangeness with the
entropy Market Bots currently the
entropy Center automated messaging
system was freaking out a bit earlier
and then the nearby entropy Bots started
to look agitated towards me I found they
went incorrectly entering their hostile
state which I know is only reserved for
extreme circumstances of direct attack
on the center
anyway we should double and triple check
that their systems will maintain
correctness and don't suddenly start
attacking staff members something
strange is going on with them maybe it's
to do with the damage that the entry
Center is receiving
like it's like destroying their
their signal on their nature or whatever
I don't know
oh yeah this is the one that like just
starts automatically when I step on it
thanks for the super chats guys
thank you
we can't remember much except for you
as long as you remember me everything is
cool that's all you need to remember oh
it's like
it's like the powers out in here that's
weird okay
so
weird
in here
why does it feel so weird
is it just me
I mean
maybe some sound effects and so on are
bugging out
I knew
I know it
I knew it
foreign
maybe maybe I can drop it when I'm
higher so they all fall down last no I
can't oh
[\h__\h] I already feel like I wasted too
much time looking back don't look back
guys goodbye
okay I think now I saved some time maybe
quick reaction oh oh
they can't do that
they look so angry even though they're
so cute come on
oh my God oh my God oh my God
[Applause]
I thought I was safe
now
turn around and it's like
Booyah bamboozle surprise
you have not successfully escaped yet oh
[\h__\h] The Landing not so nice
see this time I
mean that's very early
and now it's coming from the right side
so I go left yeah yeah
I know I know
um now we're just fall down but turn
around
run around
run run run run run run
hey oh God okay
it was stumbling there
okay okay okay okay oh oh okay be
careful here
um because
it's gonna come for me
this time okay whatever whatever don't
need it
foreign
I'm guessing left
yep that was correct
female intuition
oh yeah
oh that one's coming for me
nice skip
nice does it no okay it knows it does
again
[Music]
um
okay stay cool
oh [\h__\h]
wait wait what what what where are
they're switching
oh God
uh ah there's one up there
this is so intense
I got one I got one let's look for the
cables I guess
please don't look at me please don't
look at me oh oh don't look at me don't
look at me oh don't look at me don't
look at me don't look at me oh there's
something there there's something there
come on
wait no no no no no no no
no
why did I touch it holy [\h__\h] yeah no I
know the launch pad like I don't know is
this a moment where I have to like
quickly
bring back the launch pad to I don't
know oh my god let's just do the first
button first um
holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
um
it's too close
oh they're all looking at me yeah
[Music]
okay just get them out of the way for
now they are going to respawn but oh
[\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh God no
shoot me
okay okay okay okay okay okay
oh [\h__\h]
um so okay I think I do have to bring it
back and then
[Applause]
this is what I was thinking
because I have to activate that
that's what I was thinking okay but
that's like really hard to do in this
situation holy [\h__\h] okay don't fail Now
where's the last one over somewhere over
there ah
I think up there okay
huh
I think they all don't know where I am
right now that's good
[Music]
to me
get up there
uh I didn't I finally could get up there
like this is
I'm not sure if that works no probably
didn't oh
[Music]
it was a springboard oh I should have
taken the one I used before with me
let's do this one first
oh no
directive entropy transport system can
be activated via three power switches
let's do this one first
oh that was tough yeah they do keep on
respawning but I think sometimes it's
good to kill them to just get them out
of the way
okay
um
[Music]
thank you
okay I guess I'm going to bring
now this little stalker piece of it I
can't even destroy this one because it
just will not show up
want to pick it up
okay I got it oh something's hitting me
okay okay
um
please please
look here I forgot wait no it was not
really here
Oh wrong area
oh the stalker John
let me just activate this one now then
yeah bye
-bye
oh god
oh it's going up all right
oh wait I think the ones that are
that are shooting are okay to touch
maybe but I could be wrong
no no no
no
[Music]
okay
I thought I had to bring my own jump pad
okay that's what you mentioned with
there is a jump pad oh God
wow
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
we did it oh
analysis conclude that you survived
what if I go down now they will not
attack me
[Music]
so intense
love it
wow
wow they did a good job of this one
so stressful chapter
thank you I can confirm that we are
close to the reactor we should be there
soon okay
[Music]
lore time
this desk is so like hidden they really
wanted their privacy
what for
I'm not kidding this entry budget spoke
to me Spock he was looking at me with
his weird little smiley face straight
into my eyes and I swear he just said
beans I know I know it sounds ridiculous
he must have been a British one
but it was just like that he said beans
I can't get him to talk again he just
wheeled off I think they're becoming
sentient Brooke I'm getting a little
worried please check in with me soon the
entry Bots don't talk they just have
beeps and trips how about a coffee if
you've been working so hard recently no
um it spoke to me I can't believe you're
not believing me I'll go tell Mary she
will believe me who's Mary
Jason message me again you absolute
maniac
[Music]
yes user has now blocked you okay Mary
does not seem to believe you that's
really sad No One Believes him
well I think
I think everybody who didn't believe
them
uh paid a very
expensive price for not believing
as they are dead
how
I just did a pun in the hongo
[Music]
congratulations
my device has increased 174 percent wow
and
any of the month badge wasn't even
playing for four hours
[Music]
yeah I don't think Employee of the Month
holds much weight right now
thanks and I think you're welcome
it's not
never mind there was something there
wait Maury one time wait did you just
say that
I can rewind things
longer
but this one's uh unlimited infinite
why
oh
I can make it stop moving
oh oh
okay I don't know what I'm doing
anyways we have to get up there to
activate something and we have to go up
there to activate something
okay
am I supposed to make that jump no wait
I'm supposed to make this jump
wait oh yeah okay that's where I need to
end up that
if I go here
it needs a few seconds to reach Max
Speed during your rewind is what she
means
jumping platform thingy jumping Cube oh
hey Cole thanks for sending it through
your research I've just spoken with the
entropy reversal team they've said that
it's just happened again so that's what
four times now we've witnessed the same
cataclysmic event I don't understand I'm
considering arranging a call with the
entropy ambassy on Earth for an
immediate check-in
that's good let me know the outcome
what was the outcome cliffhanger
[Music]
am I supposed to take you with me
perhaps oh
wait a second
oh
hi hi hi
no oh [\h__\h]
uh
okay easy easy
there we go I saved myself
um the jump platform I wonder why I have
to bring that to
where
ideas Mayo
where was the first cable going to there
and I feel like this is
um
but what actually would help there is
probably a bridge Cube maybe there's
also one somewhere
let me just
bring it with oh my God
two uh
I don't know where to go with this
I guess it's pretty fresh in here for
now
um
I need to get an idea over this layout a
little bit more
um other
one one is there
oh is it not just like bringing this
thing down here and then Fiona up there
[\h__\h] should have taken it with me
this is the thing like I have problems
with big structures like that I can't
see what is where
holy shock
hopefully that jump is manageable though
what no
where are the fences
gaps aren't very dangerous
God damn it
have a night there
thank you
and we have to get the platform again
I'm sorry
yeah I'm gonna grab the lore as well
just in case I I'm guessing we already
missed some so completing them is not
really gonna be an option but
oh wow
uh
hi
there we go 37 out of 76. hmm
oh that refreshes it
[Music]
that is not one of those buttons that we
really want
careful now careful
no no
at least there they Place some ah but
wait
my platform
[Music]
it will go away
oh no
no
wait maybe maybe maybe maybe I can save
it come back where so I don't even know
where it is
maybe I can still say that
can I can I where is it
which way did it go
it's gone
[Music]
my jumpy pen
it's because I'm just not confident with
my jumps this is when I get for that
huh new one
is taking me an unnecessary amount of
time but hey right now at least this
one's already stopped so let me just uh
and just drop it okay
okay okay nice job
okay here I need a a bridge Cube maybe
I'll get that here please
foreign
no but I did activate one of the doors
do you think I need a bridge Cube or
maybe I really also need the jumpy Cube
again
really
but it it's it's taller so I can't do it
from there I doubt that but if I place
the jumping one here
yes
but then how do I get up here in the
first place
and a little bit down
you think I guess
I guess that's true it does give you
back the amount of jump you put into it
the relationship you want with anyone
get as much back as you're putting into
it
what a perfect
boyfriend girlfriend
this trampoline
I'm gonna [\h__\h] this up though I'm so
gonna [\h__\h] it up
I know
oh wait give me one more
I'm not confident
and now I just
what I can go through this right this
was safe for me as far as I remember
stop
stop stop stop
moving or do I wanted to move where am I
going with this
hey why did this open for me like
there's nothing here
go back
oh wait what's that I didn't see it oh
there's a room here ah
[Music]
and I'm getting my
my uh running
uh exercise going here
who needs to buy a treadmill when you
can just run around here all day
okay
do I need to jump back now
I mean
ah keep opening so close
of course
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah it's not
that easy
[Music]
uh
Cubs
wait wait oh
how do I get to those
huh
that jump I don't trust myself to make
this jump
hmm
oh
that was on that side nice
oh oh
thank you
oh
[Applause]
my God see I feel like stuff like this
was impossible in Portal
and yet they make it happen here very
interesting
yeah transport Goods in a linear
Direction note rewind conveyor to
reverse direction of travel I feel like
I'm already done with the tutorial and
now you tell me about it a bit late lady
okay
well we're still still in the tutorial
it seems
for the tattoo
uh-huh
[Music]
I need to
no this is not too difficult probably
oh yeah
wait I really have unlimited rewinds
see it says unlimited seconds
what
oh really
we've got upgraded so much
wow
oh that was fast
5001 I did over a thousand puzzles guys
oh how many percent oh you they tell you
that too 51 percent
do a lot more puzzles let me turn on the
lights
so dark
okay
gets dark so early in the winter man
a thousand more to go
yeah we totally did a thousand puzzles
and did we no the videos can be used to
increase your speed if you walk on them
in the same direction of travel hmm
muscle just now
I understand
ah oh
does that speed translate into the jump
if I can make it oh my God
no I'm always very wobbling with my
jumps do you really expect me to oof
okay
oh
first try thank you Astra thank you
you're welcome wow
I deserve that Applause from first try
net jump
oh well it just happened so naturally I
just let it happen
belated birthday Glenn thank you for
watching my streams I'm glad I'm your
favorite
thank you I think it's the other way
around
but who knows
what is over there that looks like lore
to me
yeah
yeah happy birth to you happy birth in
your shoe happy birthday in your pants
too happy birth to you
cold oh it's cold again
that was one of the most frustrating
calls I've had in a while let's start
off with them saying Oh this is
the Cliffhanger sign off of them saying
that they're aware of the issue they've
seen the data we've sent them but they
keep saying it's not that
straightforward it's not an isolated
disaster like all the other previous
events this is a major deep rooted issue
that is suddenly surfacing
and they don't know how to fix it then
they just blamed our data saying it was
incorrect granted our systems
consistently get scrambled whenever we
try to analyze this event because it's
just a large in scale but still I wasn't
in shock why aren't they listening to us
overall I don't think I got anywhere I'm
starting to get a bit worried Beth I'm
sorry that happened this sounds urgent
let's set up an urgent meeting today
invite all managers and leads from all
departments urgently do it urgently it's
urgent
urgently urgent
I urge you to do this
ASAP oh is it telling me to put the
trampoline here
what what does that do
oh does that
close the bridge
no because that looks like it would go
up
oh no wait there's another button
where does that go oh
go up there ah
open your eyes okay Wawa
smell
but now we have unlimited time man this
is really helpful that I don't have to
like be so fast in transporting my cubes
I appreciate that
uh okay I do think
I need to go up there to make the jump
um close eyes take nap
wouldn't that be nice
[Music]
don't you think I oh oh oh oh don't you
think I had enough
is that not possible
do I have to place the trampoline on the
cube
gentle right
hey
I don't think it gets much higher but I
mean I can oh [\h__\h]
try to make it a little a blue Mark oh
well I guess
I thought that was for the other side
oh oh well okay
never mind
it's nice how they're like babysitting
me by placing those marks on the ground
though you can't really call it puzzle
solving then
oh how smooth you like get onto the
trampoline I like it no I'm supposed to
put something there
yeah of course
never forget your Cube
just like you should never forget your
wallet in this game
always bring your favorite beloved Cube
[Applause]
okay so that won't just open up the path
for me
jump
over to that side but the hmm
how is it unrelated I think it's very
related
by the way is my German or was my German
worst than usual yes and my English
worse than usual yesterday
by any chance
I feel like it was
wait ah
we go from the other way around at this
time I think maybe maybe
I think it was and I think I know why
what
let me tell you why I've been watching
um a lot of YouTube videos from a German
uh YouTuber
who's English who speaks English in her
videos
and also doesn't speak it so well like
she has a pretty oh wait it's not
Unlimited
she has a pretty strong uh English uh
German accent that's what I'm saying
yeah and she yeah
okay okay but let's see how far do we
get back with the kill
can we make it we can make it oh but
wait no
I have to bring it back
no
[Music]
okay but now I know how to do it
does she say that instead of that not
that strong but like she just like me
but even worse she forgets a lot of uh
words all the time
and um that is pretty cute though
like I like it it's funny to me because
it's relatable
it's so relatable
yes
and then I don't know every now and then
she would definitely purposefully
pronounce things in a very German Way
which I do enjoy
very much
actually
go go go go faster
yeah she's quite
um famous though quite well known Naomi
John is her name if you want to look her
up she's a YouTuber that focuses on like
fashion and food reviews and she does
like makeup really crazy makeup looks
it's
I think the fashion videos and stuff
like that make her
um
mostly entertaining for like
uh girls watching her
she also does music though
anyway I don't know she's been really
funny I've been I've known her uh like
existence since a long time ago
but like for the past two days I just
somehow felt like binge watching her
videos
a little bit
[Music]
not fair
no
come on
no conveyors can be used to increase
your speed if you walk on them in the
same direction we'll have to do this
part too
what
another
why
[Music]
I'm down
oh oh maybe that's not enough
[Music]
I didn't expect me to die in that
section
I can't guess
in the same direction
little English that little accent is
explaining thank you for saying my
English is good
sometimes I obviously also purposefully
add a German accent to my my words
because I think it sounds funny
every now and then as long as I
actually am able to
speak proper English I think
[\h__\h] around with it every once in a
while is fine don't you think
I I think so
accents are cute yeah yeah like when I
was watching her I guess I got like a
little bit more confidence about
speaking in an accent in the first place
because when she does it it's pretty
cute
I mean from a Mexican accent onto words
for fun what does that sound like
it's a Mexican accent sound like
no I don't think my accent is very
strong definitely not as strong as hers
but then I feel like it did influence me
into speaking a little bit worse English
than usual yesterday
well if it's not for
uh if the unlimited is only for the
conveyor belts and why doesn't it there
you go now it shows the time it wasn't
showing the time
that's confusing
oh well okay nah
the cube is placed
rightfully and now I will refresh I
think and then put this one
here
I think that would work
[Music]
and then rewind everything
oh wait
[Music]
oh
what the [\h__\h]
go one more time do the four times the
charm
when you try so hard but you don't do
what the [\h__\h]
succeed please
no no that that won't work I didn't have
enough momentum I feel like one more
huh I guess I get stuck there
and I feel like that messes up my
momentum
there we go
that's what I'm talking about what
foreign
[Music]
it's like one centimeter
I I like land on the edge and then I
can't get up I'll try again
I will try oh that's nice of you red
no what
is this normal
I I did just jump on the path as well I
did it didn't really make a difference I
think
yeah I am holding forward and I jumped
on the pad but
I'll move it like a tiny bit just a tiny
bit even though I think it plays
perfectly
oh this will work
should have worked before though because
it was perfectly placed in the Square
okay
Oh yay hey
hey the square is placed incorrectly
hey
bad very bad
now you
oh
meet the Goran
foreign
the cube was not part of its system
either
working mysterious ways yeah think how
fast [\h__\h] again huh
[Music]
urgent you've been saying that like
forever
it can't be much more urgent than this
Carla
um I just wanted to ask about a possible
relocation of my office it's really
quite unstable at the moment and I
figured a puzzle area we'll just
straight up collapse at any moment
thanks Tim
hey Tim I do apologize for your current
situation unfortunately we are
experiencing this across the board the
ongoing issue with the current
cataclysmic event on Earth is creating
such a huge shock waves such huge shock
waves and slowly destroying the center
if you could maybe get one of the puzzle
operatives to rewind your office space
in between plus and exercises
that sounds like a boom
I think in the end his head was crushed
and then landed on the keyboard I
think that the email was still sent wow
how does that work
okay so that's already activated ah
well we wanted to deactivate
um
hold on
this one has to be like
moved outwards
there we go
oh oh oh
can I have this Stone
[Music]
well let me try first
no no
so how do I get the cube up there when I
need it in order to jump
there's obviously an easy solution to
all this
ah
huh
I think I understand
can you guys write off Super Tires as a
business expense no are you are you
serious about this question why can I
not land on that anymore
foreign
edge of it then it works
okay so my plan is
to
do this
Drop It Up
why is it not fly oh yeah because I
wanted to stand on it
um
I want to stand on it to make it fly
but then
then I have nothing
yeah we have to
um stop this thing
yeah okay I think this will work
so that it doesn't go over there yet
what the hell do I get up there again
on it
and I'm I'm getting there I'm getting
closer and closer
um
yeah well I guess I'll have to do it
twice
if I reverse it like
I think it can go back
no no ah
and this time I think I have to re
outrun this because if I reverse this
doesn't it reset what does it no it
doesn't it doesn't reset the Cube's path
right
that jump
I don't wait wait I'm just looping this
I'm just repeating it again the same
thing
I feel like I'm missing one element but
whatever
[Music]
um
foreign
oh
[Music]
well
I mean that's okay because I can
probably grab it
how much time is on this Cube now show
me show me
now
hey
uh
yeah I know I can grab it but if I run
through that with the cube it will
disappear
no
I'm pretty sure where is that just the
kind of laser that
um just kills my rewinds but does not
kill the cube I think it does
and in the end I still need the cube
over there took them
ah
wait I'm scared
thank you
it went so far
sometimes I wish it would go a little
bit slower
[\h__\h]
um
oh God
ah no okay well whatever that's probably
fine
oh man how much time is on the cube I
didn't reset it
but will it fall if I stop this now
[Music]
wait
um my brain
still a few reasons
this is so easy
[Music]
brain horn
what
doesn't even it doesn't even
know I'm just more confused
oh yeah okay I'll count that that's the
order that's the order we let it jump
and then I go up yeah yeah yeah
now uh
wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait
I'll do it
oh I could jump I can jump I can jump
I can jump but like I don't know how to
do this
[Music]
okay I hate this puzzle with a passion
because I know I'm making it a more
complicated and difficult than it is
oh I want to reset it kind of oh wait oh
wait okay let me test if it does
disappear
okay it does
wait it landed
I forgot an important step here before
doing that
uh
[\h__\h]
yeah yeah
but I I should have placed it I forgot
to place it on here before didn't I
button to drop the
belt
bye
[Music]
we'll just do it again right
it would be really nice if
it's me on there again
wait this
what's going it was going in the wrong
direction right I was unsure it for a
moment uh
foreign
[Music]
come on one more time
one more one more one more
I believe in you but but but
why do I even try to do that
uh yeah right I have to
sorry my brain I can't comprehend the
simplicity
um
what do you mean stand on here I can't
just stand on here
I hate myself
too much for me to do at once I'm not a
multitasker
there's so much too much thought
do it one more time
no
do you really think I need to catch it
though
yes I
ah what
why can't I not just
I I feel like I went back with my
thinking backwards I don't uh I forgot
all the logic that I had acquired
beforehand
yeah yeah yeah I need to be down again
to activate the jump
I don't know
huh
um
okay can we just yeah
um yeah think out what I need to do step
by step
we
um launched it
foreign
bring it back
to here
then I launched myself then I rewind it
to be launched
and I guess I pick it up
and then I bring it over there
stop the laser
but then how do I
I still don't know how to how to bring
it there at that point though
I don't need to begin oh
if the launch is correct it will land on
the treadmill well then just in case
let's place it in the front and see how
that jump goes
[Music]
okay that was a perfect jump that was
perfect now don't mess that up now oh
wait I did mess it up
I didn't mess it up because I can't
catch it now okay
I should have just made me um
um
like just
gotten rid of the
uh
sorry guys I'm kind of weirdly stuck on
this one
I don't know why I'm so stuck here
okay what if we
get rid of this
I know I think hopefully this is not
just RNG but if I place it here then
it would hopefully land
in theory on the conveyor belt
so there we go
and now I bring it
here
and we bring back the conveyor belt
your goodness
that jump is not enough keep on making
that mistake too oh
[Music]
and then
foreign
okay
went too far because it's so finicky
oh we still made it it's still made it
wait my cube is not gonna disappear if I
go through there right because it's
already there
it must be fine it has to be
[Music]
can we just forget about everything that
happened in that room I don't want to
think about it
what's going on here
it's like some kind of
cool disco outside Disco
palm trees
no my tea is gone I have no more tea I'm
just living on water now
anyway let's do this okay that is
obviously an opening for a cube
to be conveyed through the conveyor belt
oh
interesting though because
so that's supposed to block the lasers
um
let me make it go through first
I don't know if that was smart no
probably it wasn't
oh
interesting and very oh no oh
but no that works because if I just
rewind the cube
then I don't need to conveyor belt to be
up
oh
wow I think it was good that I did it
like
go first all the way over there smart
I'll just get the finicky timing right
there we go
I was gonna tell me oh but you need the
pube at the very top but how how would
that be possible that's literally not
possible it can't tell me that Captain
Cannon
ah there's a jump fan hey yo why oh I'm
supposed to like
get over there oh wait but there's
um
nah that's just decoration right
what do I do with this I guess that's
just decoration that's just decoration
surely that is just decoration
I'm curious but
I I wouldn't be able to make that jump
I don't know
oh
foreign
ERS have to
run over now
the jump pad has to be there and the
cube has to be
I think on that
pressure plate I think
oh
foreign
[Music]
will be stopped by
this wall
I can't just go straight from from the
conveyor belt over there
and
yeah
well how do I even get on
on the conveyor belt though
wait oh
what I'm thinking is
um
nothing brain empty head Fork
what
oh
I broke it
this is fine
this works does it
I can't
drop
ped
stuck
it's stuck
ah there we go
oh yeah yeah it fits just right
it's rare perfectly now how do I get up
there
maybe I'm not actually supposed to go up
I don't know
so that works and that's cool but
damn it
I feel like
I feel like I got a room huh
use box rewind yeah
oh
yeah I noticed the blue
mark
and that was that's why I first wanted
to place the trampoline on it but I just
don't didn't think the drum could work
then
maybe it would maybe I need to undo this
I feel like my solution was more
interesting
Yeah so
basically this will help me get up there
um
foreign
am I not like
sing something though
I feel like I'm missing something
does this hurt me I don't remember if it
hurts me
can I not get on the conveyor belt
of course I can
there we go it's just weird
does it hurt me it doesn't
okay okay okay well let's try it I'm
just gonna jump
um what the [\h__\h]
moving automatically I'm just gonna jump
uh right when the conveyor belt ends
hopefully
uh
go
oh it does work easy
[Music]
oh hello there Bridge Cube haven't seen
you in a while fancy seeing you here oh
what's this
oh
it's just a going back area okay but I
said bird bread hey that sounds like an
insult
are you trying to praise me that's not
how it works
it's cute bridge Cube does come here
often I've seen you around yeah
yeah does this side work through the
window no it doesn't okay
oh but ah are we supposed to send it
through
that's what the window is for right
and now we check out what's going on
down here otherwise we will never
understand
there's this one there how do I get June
so far
I don't understand this
this riddle
puzzle
you chased to this level how can you
cheese it
cheese
there's a cheese swing tell me the
cheese way
also I wonder if you can like go over
there
hmm
this one's tricky unless you cheese it I
guess
let me I don't know about the bridge man
even reach it from there ah
well
it doesn't make me a bridge though at
least not right now
do I want to drop it
you know
facing the wrong way no like in this
state it will not make a bridge I think
I think it has to be on Solid Ground
I mean now it's also in solid ground but
it's not making a bridge because of
reasons
um I don't know like I think
like here if there were a bridge to be
created here I could jump on it and go
get the trampoline
no no bridge at all maybe if I just stop
that Trump at that platform
can you please obnoxious
no
huh and something's happening there
something's off about the cube
maybe now
oh
no wait what are you doing
huh
the direction is wrong but it's not
making a bridge in any direction no I I
saw it
hold on let's refresh it though
thank you
I wonder how you can cheese it I want to
figure it out
how do you cheese this
where is the cheese stretch
that doesn't that doesn't help
finding out how to change it I think
requires you to have a couple of brain
cells
so I think
the fact that you were able to cheese it
makes you very smart and gets you on the
same level as being able to do it
normally
so I don't think there is any shame in
doing that
um
but I don't know how to cheat
so
if it falls down there
we want it to fall like this I think
maybe I should have reset it [\h__\h]
[Music]
crumbles boom let's see
um
[Music]
uh it's already in an unstable position
but
if I stop it it just does that it goes
back there
foreign
[Music]
how do I
I guess I'm not really oh oh wait I got
it I got it
I was gonna say I guess I'm not really
understanding this but nah
worry
awkward but
uh
let's go
so is this where the cheesing begins
Maybe
so I'm supposed to jump probably and
then place it like I don't know
somewhere here
but I that's just the normal way of
doing things probably
I do assume that I need the cube with me
so I'm just gonna place it here for now
oh
but I feel like it's not that simple
I will regret everything I just did
in a moment
because I'll be missing oh
critical information
huh
where are we going yeah
[Music]
where are we going like I came here but
what far
this is not where we're going
one below me
I need to drop
down here but wasn't this place always
accessible anyway what
foreign
lit part
this this is brightly lit
below where you thought the accent would
be where did I think ah
ah yeah
how how how how how how how
do I get there oh no
so I'm assuming the bridge is
useless
for me here
I mean
I want to cheese and I felt like I
choose it when I did this on YouTube
how do you guys Chase all of this
let me pour some water
add another 10 cheese scraps
ah
oh it has to be there
okay well it could can't we just like
bring a jump light from there and then
put the cube there and then isn't that
just it
well that's all is that cheesing or is
that not just normal
I don't think it has a limited range
I don't think so oh maybe you cheesed it
by like I don't know stopping it in
flight
see it's endless oh but anyway I won't
be able to get through maybe it was a
jump pad though
maybe on the other side
okay so is this where you started
cheesing it
I can't pass through
and about it
why is there a button there too
open the door like
well maybe I can make the jump let's see
but even if I can
I can't
walk a very useful and needed button
she's by glitching the cube near the
treadmill hey
that's just that sounds like RNG to me
and I don't even know how that would
help me
okay
um
well it probably has to do something
with rewinding [\h__\h]
oh where to my brain I don't know my
capacity my brain capacity is just not
maybe strong today
that is glass
that over there is glass yeah
pretty sure
yeah it stopped there
there's a lot of steps to this
that makes me not happy not happy at all
um
Maybe
I I have to jump onto it
from the other side so I have to
um bring the jumping one
back there
job seems very risky and difficult
oh
what
take the bridge
jump to the right of the stair is that a
cheese strap
oh
that sounds like a cheese one because
you mean one of those rocks over there
to start take the bridge
jump to the right
do I want to see I kind of want to
change them
sounds interesting I don't understand it
though it went they were in it again
from the start take the bridge jump to
the right of of the stair on top of a
rocket I think I know which rock you
mean to play support you and walk on it
done
I want to try that but uh
do I really risk resetting everything
now
you mean one of those
these ones
and then if I stand there
does that work
uh I think I'm floating
okay
I had to jump back to make the jump okay
uh
wait now I have to get the jump pad
again oh that's okay that's okay
that ain't so bad can I choose that too
[\h__\h] that's the one thing I can't choose
Maybe
don't need you say no need
[Music]
really
I was trying to jump again
but with the cube right from where do I
jump from here
or do I try to jump on this ledge
from top of the railing
oh am I on there no
stop
talking sounds they make me nervous oh
[Music]
I'm gonna get like a million devs from
doing this
that's quite the leap yeah what the [\h__\h]
foreign
hardcore
hardcore you can do it you think so
with a railing jump what
go the railing jump and then press
forward jump parallel to the ledge
parallel to the ledge
[Music]
it's okay that makes it easier
and then we're trying to jump like
from a little bit lower or higher
yes I know what parallel means bottom
Fragger you deserve a timeout for that
question
I don't think I can make it
she in fact could not make it
oh if I was back for a moment
blocked in the void forever
to never be saved
and brought back to life
lost for eternity
you're the confidence I I
answer that the cube was in the way
there's a lot more to do right okay
[Music]
don't fall
okay now only this now it's about the
placement of the cube which I don't feel
much confidence in either
you know it doesn't even want to make a
bridge
drop the cube
what
why
can I always only grab it from that side
hmm
why does everyone just try to oh that's
interesting I want to go there
does everyone just try to choose this
level huh
just do it properly
the developers are watching this stream
and crying
and what I'm trying to do
it's gonna be banned to play this
forever for life
so why why yeah
oh wait this
is interesting
I did not think it would just stay there
oh
[Music]
that could be it
I do wonder if I can make that little
jump over there though
and if I can make this jump
so efficiently
[Music]
I wonder what the real solution was
I still took about as much time as I
probably would have taken if I would
have tried to do it properly but
this way I did not break my [\h__\h]
brain cells for the sake of this
zinc seems like a chapter is that oh
yeah
chat is over oh
oh yeah oh yeah
thank you for helping me Jesus
I thank you
we're doing so properly we're allowed to
cheese every once in a while
this music it sounds like they're gonna
start the wow
the Illuminati kind of alien music
you know it's doing this thing again
though where it's very like
oh yeah X-Files
it's very much
about to do something something's about
to go down left all right left or right
I'm
not
check this door first oh it's closed
okay
nervous yeah the suspense
Ryder
there's gonna be some robots chasing me
again right
entering staff quarters oh we need to
find a way to the top floor
no
oh it's like Apartments there isn't it
what is that
oh oh oh oh yeah yeah there's one is it
a friendly one
are any of them friendly
[Music]
choose to be accent
maybe I will not be cheesing it this
time
uh I guess once it sees me and we'll try
to
where is where is the exit to the top
where are we going
what happens if you excuse me
[Music]
oh hi
hi oh can I just let's see what happens
[Music]
I'll have the same face
I think you can help oh I'm relieved
Oh Oh I thought it was gonna kill me
thank you
reach top floor so sweet
fun I had to dodge and then find my way
up secretly
[Music]
it was indeed kind of a cheese Strat oh
oh oh oh oh
thank you how convenient
everything is so convenient I guess I'm
going this way
something fell down again no I'm not
going this way oh
[Music]
you've done a lot this is how the import
apartment form like
[Music]
no static charge emitted to handle grip
tiredness detected and puzzle operative
hey turn that off static charge
all allocated puzzle exercises during
the Working Day
actually it looks kind of cozy
surprisingly cozy
it's like the size of a Japanese
one-room apartment
I guess the showers are shared though I
don't appreciate that
um okay I saw something breaking down
here so am I laying
supposed to leave you there
don't think so
or maybe
you have something to lift no
and I I don't think this is the way
must be like
we're going down again
and then we're going up again or so I
don't know
maybe from here
and then
oh
but something broke down here and that
must have been for a reason right
however
ah maybe I'm supposed to go up here
oh elevator no but we are on level
that's interesting why is it the other
way around that's so trippy we go from
ground floor downwards but in reality
we're going upwards okay level two to
level six
that's how I got up there in the first
place what what
are you saying this is wrong
no no
okay it's reverse like everything else
in this game true that yeah
that's the bridge the robot broke for me
oh
ah I guess it just fell down because I
did something else somewhere else or
yeah okay okay I was like uh is this
happening because it's trying to tell me
something
uh check out
who want to go
okay
so we've been on that level but then I
must feel so get from that level
where else
well wow wow
how about
all right yeah we can get up with the
jump pad what am I doing
okay we are on level two with the jump
pad
no we were on level two jump pad before
[Music]
what am I doing
what am I doing I want to go maybe
perhaps to the different side of
level two
foreign
it was no more
space to go left
I don't know
you need to leave it below and Rewind it
back up
why isn't the result the same
what isn't that the same
your father's part was pretty
straightforward it probably is oh
[Music]
wait that's that part
oh wait this is
uh
no
that's like what
did I not see that opening there before
how did I not see it
how
but even now that I'm here I am
[Music]
confused how do I get this I was here
before
foreign
and then I rewind it to be here
ah never mind I got it guys I'm okay I
know I seem exceptionally stupid today
uh I probably should have like
rewind it not rewinded but refreshed
wait how do I get no
no aha
refresh it here
now oh
jump myself up
not there
yep
I'll bring it back
oh wait what
and no I think we're probably good
[Music]
here okay
now let me refresh it again
we'll figure this out don't you worry
oh okay
it was just one more level higher
now fully I placed it yeah
it was too close and I fell down but I
wanted to replace it anyway because that
was too close more like maybe here
[Music]
probably
the jump almost seems manageable
that's probably fine
okay
up up we go
and uh yeah place the properly ones
that's too close
oh there it is okay that's better than
before a little bit
no it's taking so much time
I have learned I've Been Told
that
um in games like these and FPS games
um the little
Circle in the middle
will tell you how to
um
land where to land
[Music]
[\h__\h] and I fell back to the house it was
so close no but yeah I understand now
that you're supposed to like you know oh
that really feels like I could do it can
you just cheese it here too
because I literally saw the mesh there
oh wow
hi one more time no no
no about last time after you guys gave
me feedback
but
I would say my my crunches
already understood that
was
before you guys told me I just did not
really realize it
you guys actually have advice for me and
that's good
I appreciate that last time I did it all
on my own and this time I just don't I'm
not smart enough for it today so thank
you for being here and helping me
hey
yeah
I don't see any way in bringing the pad
with me so I hope this is okay going
without it
[Music]
what's next though
no
[Music]
don't tell me
that that was one step
as always
I'm supposed to like
bring it here
and then I don't know look around first
yeah please please tell me I'm wrong oh
I'm wrong okay I was hoping for a bridge
Cube
oh Lord
oh there we go
they're a puzzle operatives that's me
and you maybe remind you that taking
puzzle elements out of the puzzle areas
is strictly prohibited we are currently
missing one down Cube and one Bridge
Cube
from puzzle areas 11 to 12. puzzle
elements are not for recreational use
please return these immediately ah so
these are stolen
[Music]
oh
I guess I'm leaving the bridge cubes
behind
yes I have to
okay
I still always love an open room there
so scary
oh more
hi Beth I just spent the day with the
entropy reversal team I don't think
they've ever seen anything like this I
too am getting a bit worried after
rewinding earlier and being sure that
this was the one they witnessed the same
cataclysmic event occur on Earth just
about an hour ago what's even worse is
the blast from this event is so strong
that maintenance that they're detecting
damage to the main entropy device and
our exterior protective Dome and that
there's a risk of permanent damage to
the center I just can't believe that I
don't get what's going on down there
that means they can fix it when faced
with damning evidence of their own
demise and show the exact cause of it oh
you don't know anything about it let's
see set up an urgent wait they do know
the cause
they figured out the cause and told them
oh I mean besides just telling them it's
you
it's not me it's you
because that's not very helpful
you made me yawn who else did I make
yawn oh
scary that felt like death was passing
by
and that wasn't written there a moment
ago
quiet it's turned into a horror game I'm
scared
scared here before I don't think they're
before a moment ago why
element introduction nah a new word take
an entropy Cube through a Transformer to
change it into another type of entropy
queue this can be rewound through a
Transformer to restore it to its initial
State got it
thinking of walking through a
Transformer will not turn you into an
interest for extra safety please don't
stand near the transformer for extended
periods of time what happens tell you if
I start feeling boxy
nothing's happening
it's pretty dough it's very pretty I
like the the purple violet
beautiful
ah oh
interesting
[Music]
because if I just rewind it from here
ah it will go back to being a laser
that is cool
okay so
um
oh no
huh I thought you were supposed to be
something else
ah
did not go through prop I guess I went
through double
so
huh
foreign
just reset that [\h__\h] for me
Okay so
we place it here we go through or is
there no returning after you change it
once except for rewinding can you not
like go endlessly for these Transformers
and change it again and again and again
and again and again
oh did I just miss the moment
[\h__\h]
oh there we go okay we're good
just for rewinding huh
okay okay so it's not like GoPro change
it go through change it back go through
change it go through change it back
again
that's what I thought that was okay oh
there's two now different colors
oh so the purple one always makes it
into the bridge Cube
and then the blue one
into a jumpy one wow
no
no it's just gonna get more complicated
oh
[Music]
I feel like we have to like drop the
cube the jumpy platform here eventually
to jump from one side to another but I
don't even know what's up there we will
see
huh okay and that opens the door
[Music]
oh wait this thing I didn't see that
oh well
oh
so
that is interesting
um I need
uh
that's interesting it has to be a jam
platform and a cube and a bridge
platform
um
so
but how well
I think I get it I think I get it I
think again let me see let me see let me
see let me see let me see so
while it is what is this
um I will put it here uh here
and then I go through the purple
and go up with it together I make myself
the bridge okay this is still simple
because that's still tutorial stage oh
[\h__\h] this is gonna get tough
complicated puzzle yeah we're gonna get
avocado okay I guess
wait a second dude I'm not ready I'm not
done with this puzzle yet
oh I was so sure I was gonna [\h__\h] up
that uh
[Music]
that's a jump
oh thank God I did not forget to do this
smart
man the shock wave some Earth erupting
yeah but can they just wait a [\h__\h]
minute
give me a break man puzzle areas 11
continuation and staff launch
oh cute what about you guys are you
having an angry day or a happy day
Oh Happy Day
wait it's the bees that are behind all
of this
if we die we're taking you with us
don't let the bees die is what we take
from this because apparently
the bees are the source of the
cataclysmic event wait is it really in
this game
is this the hint
masaka
poisoning
um
don't have any arms yet oh wait I would
like to play some ping pong deeply
Squirtle the bats there's only the balls
here
but I think we've played enough
stressful ping-pong in my members only
stream the other day and moon pong was
fun but very stressful
[Music]
yeah so take care of Amity cherish her
hold her tightly don't let go of her
you know what will happen otherwise
dear South America Center ping pong
competition are now open
I want to partake in it
I've been through moonpong I think this
will be just a walk in the park for me
is that open
no
I guess we're not playing ping pong ping
pong games sad
1am good night bye bye
if I'm going down
foreign
that's where Moon pong came from maybe
yeah because they're on the moon
[Music]
what are we dealing with here oh there's
like a transformation thingy
there that turns it into jump flat for
my bank oh and there's a red one wait
what does the red one do
I'll do you oh [\h__\h] I left it there is
this perhaps
um
can I like
bring it through there with like by
bringing it below me
oh maybe not I don't know why I'm I was
even thinking I would need to do that it
sounded interesting oh
foreign
[Music]
but that is probably not really
the end game I want to see
what's there that we can check out right
now I think if you're having a great day
thank you I'm just puzzling on a
beautiful Sunday
refresh
[Music]
what what do we have
nothing
aha
why
I need Bridge or jump pad
ah
perhaps
we send it through here we drop it at
the state of where it is a jump pad
put it here jump over but we probably
also need it after that as whatever it
turns into after being
um sent through the Red Gate
is a cube oh okay that's probably
necessary over there in the parts that
we can't even see
Okay so
oh
send fruit make into jump pad
but then this is probably the end so we
would first jump
wait
we still need to
like
this is called hated
what if we
um send it through all the way to the
end
then
reverse the conveyor belt so it goes
through the red one
and goes for the blue one again so then
it's trampoline
then we can use it to jump up there then
we reverse the trampoline it will go
back it will turn into the red one
and land here and that's probably what
we need right
correct
sounds correct to me
how do you plan ahead so long I have to
look
but this bottom this one do you just you
just um
your job is later
uh oh no wait wait but you also
let me up there we'll figure that out so
that means
wait we're doing all this with one Cube
your last point is here
but your second to last point is here
yeah let me refresh again your last
point is here
second to last point is here
now can we really do this in 38 seconds
we jump up together
wait a second uh okay
um
I think I'll go first and turn
oh oh I can't
ah I have to
I have to stand on there I suppose
to make it go up
to raise the conveyor belt but then when
I drop Where can I
[Music]
um to drop it though
I guess I'll just drop it now
[Music]
it's already at 34 seconds though
I feel like that will add more than four
seconds to it
and while it's falling it still adds
seconds I think
you were set at the wrong place wasting
time
yeah
did I
I need to go to the idol meeting
uh
I think I'll go now okay
I'll try to be back ASAP should I make
some tea too
oh I really didn't take a while
um
I think I'll make something yeah okay
I'll be I'll be BRB
maybe I'll ride something
oh
[Music]
text
oh this was just some credit
making tea BRB
okay wow so pixely
I'm still here
can you see me am I invisible
don't
don't bully me like that don't make me
think I'm invisible I'm here but now
okay I'll I'll be gone for a moment but
I'll be right back
just imagine
I no frog supporting here
wait the water is still not finished
we are being
foreign
oh you're sure
[Music]
I'm here I'm here
Hello Kitty I made a big jug so I should
have done that from the beginning on
a big jug of hot water
I'm drinking from a Pikachu cup
cute
so cute Pikachu
Pikachu
okay so we have the tea bag we have the
honey I wish I had some big drugs in my
life
me too me too
and then honey and then some hot water
um
I saw you know those YouTube videos that
I was watching
um actually I got some more inspiration
again
um for like a air fryer uh cooking
stream
I want to make some easy things in the
airfryer one of the things was actually
Korean
it looks so simple and it looks so good
um
I'm wearing my Korean brows I never when
I was in Japan I never tried those
Korean rice cakes but do they taste like
like Japanese rice cake like mochi
or is it very similar because it looks
kind of similar it looks it looks kind
of different actually but not not
completely different yeah it's a Korean
like rice cake uh
uh like uh uh on on one of those like
what do you call those
uh
um with some hot dogs
and then you know like a very specific
sauce
on top of it
rice cake was sausage yeah yeah yeah
yeah
it's like Korean German collaboration
creamy rice cake is a little bit
different than Japanese recipe okay but
it's it's similar right then if it's
similar then I think I I will like it I
mean Japanese mochi is not my favorite
thing
um but I can eat it I can totally eat it
it's fairly similar okay then I think I
can make it because in the in the um
recipe it also looks really simple
like basically you take your your
Korean rice cake and you slice out the
sausages and then you just put it on the
the Skiller Skillet was the word I was
looking for
one by one and then uh you top it with
the sauce but I think you top it
after you put it in the airfryer or
before I'm not sure I forgot but it's so
simple
I want to try it I wonder if it's yummy
I feel like the combination of rice cake
and sausages and then the low-key spicy
sauce you make for that is seems like an
interesting combination yeah
only one way to find out yeah so I want
to do that and then some other airfryer
recipes
um and then maybe maybe we can even like
make it a theme like on one day I make
Korean Air fryer recipe ideas and on
another day I try something Mexican I
don't know
um
maybe once per week or so I mean not
really gonna make it into a series that
I'm forcing myself to do every week but
I don't know I was inspired
what's what kind of Mexican thing could
you make in an air fryer
um
and also I hope I can make something
Japanese Maybe
I feel like you could make like koroke
even though kuroka is not even Japanese
but but I love Japanese koroke with the
koroke sauce that they sell in the
convenience store
foreign
um I feel like tonkatsu will turn out
better if fried properly and a lot of
oil
[Music]
it's having back in here and hearing
that music is like 10
10 Illuminati
[Music]
oh I can remove the text
okay okay okay I'm back I'm back I'm
back with some tea I'm like TT uh
[Music]
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no
okay okay so we do air fryer sometime
soon okay because you guys were missing
my cooking streams anyway and I have
used my air fryer like once since I got
it so it would be nice to use it a bit
more often I guess
okay so what are we doing
um
refresh oh I guess we start here and
then the stretch is this the time that I
was wasting
where did I waste time
I say I wasted time where did I waste
time
and start sorry just wait for a minute
what am I supposed to do here I just
I drop it right I just drop it
it's at 26 seconds that should be okay
oh that's way less than before
[Music]
I was I was low-key making tea even
while I was tangenting oh as I was
nice okay
okay
safe
it's
it's uh at 35 seconds okay so now
I will
raise it
up
and Let It Go
through
the blue one or the red one first
[Music]
I can't reset before dropping it
not not in how I was thinking about
doing it
now the beam the beam is uh right there
that's where I need the beam in the end
but
I wonder once I'm up there can I not
just
like hold it through here and then it's
red but that would be too easy then it
doesn't it wouldn't even make sense to
put that there in the first place if it
was that easy
yeah
so I was hoping that
I could
let's go through there twice somehow but
um
that's exactly it
I'll just be on that side and I hold it
to go through here ah but then I kind of
need this thing to be back up again and
it's only up as long as I
stand on it or have something stand on
it
yo if you place
this really smartly
it isn't this a cheese Strat like
at some point you have it as a laser on
top of here
shooting for there I don't know if that
would work in any way
you should experiment for a bit first
yeah I'm just hoping to get it right
like cleanly without messing around too
much but I guess that's too much to us
go Kai
so let's
Let It Go through the blue one first
but I don't want to get it right
now
um
I will
Let It Go through here first and then
back again
I don't know why
hmm
maybe I do
need to maybe all of that was not
even necessary
but I guess my idea was that even if it
goes through backwards
it will still be what it was
and if I were to just let it go for the
blue one and then rewind it after it
went for the blue one it would go here
and then it will
go here Lift Me Up go there I jump
and then the only question is how do I
get it to be right again oh well I don't
know
[Music]
that's exactly how you do it okay see
brain works but then I just don't
understand the ending
well
I guess we'll try this for now just just
to you know get the feeling in my body
of having
it executed once and then everything
will be so much easier to understand
yep okay but then yeah this is this is
the question
foreign
let's see how far back we can
audit ah
that was kind of close what
yeah oh my God
I'm like such a genius
wait can I
tomato
but wait how do I get back up
why do I get back rewind yeah but uh how
do you see the path again was it what
was it
yeah
look at it like this
that's as far as it goes now I've done
like too much
I've done too much with it
but
so basically
um if I
rewind it
um
[Music]
and then drop it so I have the laser
version of it
I could at least get up here but that's
really not it
uh
reset before dropping mm-hmm
wait should I restart everything no
from like zero
I just need to waste less time yeah yeah
but also get back up there
don't reset
I'm close to the answer Skye
you
you understand though
rewind and drop it down take
tutor jumped and Rewind back to wait
wait wait wait let me think about what
you just wrote rewind drop it down yes
take to the jump
rewind and back to the top yeah but then
that way it doesn't go for the
trampoline anymore so I cannot make this
jump
if I if I if I
um if I were to refresh it here
oh I can't maybe if I refresh it while
it's on on here
and make it go
[Music]
can I refresh it when it's like there
and make it go through here
[Music]
maybe that should that should be okay
oh wait no
[Music]
okay
wait a moment
pink gather yourself Kiwa will bring
yeah I'll just um
you little [\h__\h]
that was not the intention
Ally
it's intimidating me
it's like doing what it wants it's not
properly on the conveyor belt
[Music]
foreign
I guess we needed
oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] no
don't reach it anymore now
[Music]
[\h__\h]
I was trying to get it for the blue one
okay
um
yeah
I hope see is this like at this point I
wonder if it's normal to take this much
time hey I did take a break to make some
tea
um
yeah I have the right idea you think so
but I don't know how to end it
um
but okay that means that
it doesn't the time doesn't matter
uh like at this point
we just want to drop it once
and get up here
and then
get this thing up here
and then we have it go
oopsie
for a red first wait
first and then blue
all right
and then I reset it now though
do I reset it no
do you think this is enough time because
how much time is on this thing now it
won't tell me
tell me I don't want to pick it up that
just wastes time
foreign
okay 36
.
okay testing testing testing testing
testing wait I need to think uh
um
[Music]
in my mind I had it before but uh I need
to go up first and then it needs to be
here so it goes
okay
yeah it's too much time I know
how far will it go back
it's stopping there is there is a
problem
why does it not why does it it goes all
the way back up here but not there
even though it was there once
I can grab it from there you think so
that's where I stopped the kill I guess
so
foreign
[Music]
and I'm supposed to like grab it from
here
how is that gonna work
get it
okay okay chill like if it goes back
we're gonna have a problem wait I can't
really reach you from there
foreign
[Music]
grabbing it from there is that really
the way to do it correctly though
it took a while but I knew how to do it
from the start
I knew it all the time I always knew it
ah
foreign
to whom it may concern I just want to
report an incident on puzzle 1203
Tommy's foot is now partly a cube he
stood next to a transformer for too long
and now look at his foot he says he's an
agonizing pain but it is kind of
enjoying his new foot how do we fix this
sorry to hear that the Transformers are
still causing some adverse effects they
should have been recalibrated not too
long ago it's never affect organic
matter we will do another check in the
meantime one of the puzzle operatives
should rewind Tommy back to his pre-cube
stage we don't recommend keeping the
food as a cube as this could have
adverse effects on himself
well yeah
as much as I like these cubes I don't
think I want any body parts of mine to
become the cube
[Music]
Steve
I mean Minecraft Steve
become Minecraft
so we have a a bridge portal and a
zombie portal
Bridge goes through here most likely I
see that as a sign
but wait what more
why would it go over there
why wouldn't go yeah investigate
here we have a button that close that
turns off the forget forget to forget to
laser
oh and in the end it has to be here okay
I assume because that opens the door
that's the last spot guys
okay let's let's try to experiment our
way through this
that always seems like the best way of
doing it
um wait jumping jumping platform
I guess
jumpy platform
maybe oh maybe
not sure where I would place it right
now I guess here
is there something to get out there oh
there is okay
please
ah
can I
[Music]
oh God it's so blinding do they want me
to place the jumpy platform
on top of the air so that I can also
jump on it and go up here
and then from there
what do we do from there
well wow wow wow
40 hours in there Thomas
around here
oh you're gonna study wow
proud of you
yeah
that jump is not high enough
how do you think
[Music]
it feels like it's not high enough or
what does that mean
oh no it's okay it's okay
so then it would be amazing to have the
bridge right here and just walk all the
way over there
that would be too simple especially
because it actually has to be there you
well if I were to reverse it
no I I was thinking and and put it
through
um the purple one ones but apparently it
ends there
not a little
so
oh oh
good night bye bye bye
I shall refresh it
I mean this is this is probably the
beginning right
oh no where to go from there and how
you're fine
keep it
as a jump platform it doesn't really
help me because all the other ones are
too far away
ah but I think
Maybe
if I am first make it into a bridge
platform
if there's enough time bring it up here
and
kind of like place it right here
I know but let's say let's say I place
it here
uh for a moment then run run run run run
place it as a jump platform there
no first first I place it once here and
then there
is there enough time to do that so I'm
thinking that
um the bridge that I create here
I walk on then jump down pill and jump
up here
that's my idea
but then we're still missing
the fact that I even need a jump
platform no I do need to jump platform
there how I only have so much time to do
all of that in 38 seconds
[Music]
mm-hmm
that is the one more step so
holy [\h__\h]
what
or never mind uh no no
doesn't go through this window the
bridge does not go through the window
otherwise I could just place it once
here and then once here
start from the end yeah so
um
I
I take Cube
I take a cube
place it there refresh
bring it
uh through here
jump up
place the bridge here
take it run through the blue
place it there
I know first [\h__\h] [\h__\h] I'm thinking I'm
not thinking reverse um place it run for
the blue place it here
place it there
kind of like that
I'm correct yay
you have to think like in you have to
think ahead like so far
to do this
so uh uh we're talking jump platform
right now so it starts here
first try might be not enough
I'm just gonna I'm gonna save some time
here oh wait
never mind I don't need the bridge at
the end here because I'll be jumping
anyway
because this has to be here at the end
okay
it's so it works the way I'm thinking
about it right
okay okay okay okay okay
go
I wish there was a dashing button
it's already 11 seconds
okay perfect 20 seconds
I have
19 more seconds to go
to go for a blue
place it
in the green
[Music]
like around here where my cursor is
does that work
at the bridge closer to both edges oh
[\h__\h] time for that
oh wait if I do it like this then I
don't need the jumpy one in between I
could probably jump from here to here
walk and then ah this
[Music]
ah maybe it's if it's a bit diagonal
as I was actually pointing out before
okay we're just testing this now so
forget the time but if it was like
work
Coaster song
okay okay
okay then I don't have to stop twice
okay
that's redo
that was important an important
um realization
then then the time seems more realistic
yeah I need to place the bridge block
fast that is true
action
uh I still have time I would say
to replace it
that is very off
uh
that could work
I think
I think that will work okay
21 seconds we have 30 about 38 maximum
don't [\h__\h] it up
[Music]
hi
the best I can do
what
all right
wait I can do it again I can do it again
don't worry don't worry don't worry this
is not a thing that makes you redo
everything don't worry don't worry
Don't Worry Be Happy
okay
oh this is exciting
except brainer for figuring that out I'm
like oh
so proud
what just happened oh yeah
uh drop it right is that the right place
to drop it though
yes that's perfect
that's why there's the Gap so I can see
what I'm doing so I can control it from
here I was wondering there must have
been a reason why this Gap was there
no more
oh
amazing and now we just bring it to the
very end ready
it should eventually end up right there
don't mess up the jump what's what
happened there
don't mess up the jump you know how to
do it now
um oh wait oh it's because I didn't stop
rewinding but I've landed would I have
landed properly otherwise
I'm so sorry I thought it was fine [\h__\h]
ah okay
it's okay it's already in the position
that we want to end it as
we can do it again
[Music]
hmm
not so bad
I think that works
it works right
that looks good
well next
[Music]
okay you would have more time left than
I had before
yay
anymore
[Music]
go back
I did it right right I didn't forget
anything did I
know
okay
that's it that's it
hey
and
meet you on the flip side
run off the spacing for jump pads
position fits run you mean instead of
jumping
yeah and again thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
oh no time to celebrate
[Music]
oh we're gonna reach like they represent
by the end huh
oh then we're not so far off anymore
[Music]
it's a Japanese swai song
I really like that song
I'm running out now with fine time as I
said is an imaginary concept that does
not really exist unless you make it
exist don't worry
[Music]
there is no such thing
time what is time I don't know time
I only know
t-h-y-m-e because I'm such a chef with
ass
that all I think about is herbs
yeah
I thought of a funny joke yesterday do
you want to hear it
I think I wrote it down where did I
where is it
on it
let me let me think what was the two
I forgot it what was it
um
I forgot it I know I got it here it is I
wrote it down here okay
yeah yeah this is this is very funny so
please get ready be on the edge of your
seats
um
everyone
always asks
wait
everyone always asks where is UK but no
one ever asks
UK
to UK
what
[Music]
is funny right like you you can't me
like you good
you're good it's a it's a joke about you
know like everyone always asks
where is kiwawa but they never ask how
is kiwawa you know kind of like a joke
like that
hahaha
[Music]
no I was
here
Jordan come guys
it's funny
I was so proud yesterday that I thought
of that okay I was so proud I'm like all
right I could tweet this out right now
but no you know what I'm so proud of
this
this is texture I'm so proud of this I'm
gonna keep this until tomorrow write it
down so I don't forget it and then
showcase it to you guys proudly
yeah
it's just your reflexes that are too too
slow yeah yeah that's it that's it
okay anyway ah that activates the jump
pad okay
one of those cubes I guess
has to be sent through here
ah and then stops the laser whatever the
laser does oh
laser does that oh wait we're actually
working with two cubes for once
I had a sensible chuckle
that's all I wanted
I take it back maybe you're an idol
another comedian after all there you go
so for saying that my theme song in
trombone champ is Gladiator so much for
that I'm not
I'm not to make it into the circus so
honestly I deserve an apology
wouldn't you all agree
so many Clips by the way from the
trombone champ stream it was funny
I
mean you're getting it you're
understanding it anyway I need to think
um which one let's just test it out
whatever
uh
oh yeah let's just put one here and send
one
this is I think the difference today I'm
less experimenting than yes like
yesterday then last time oh
okay I will need the
never mind I don't need anything here
this is funny
well this is interesting oh it already
becomes what I wanted to be
and then I need a laser hair in the end
okay
that one
what do I bring it with me
[Music]
what
choco
wait what happened
well I think I
I accidentally heated it up here
uh oh I need the bridge
here in the end
bridge bridge
John Bridgestone
which one was Bridgeton where you bridge
Chan well then I have to reset it
already Okay so
uh tsumari
first step is
that
because the last step is putting the
bridge there
Let's test it out
it's fresh
number one
so in theory I could already walk over
there but this is just the last step
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
and then
um which one are we sending through the
trample ah we're sending this one
through to make it into a trampoline
because I need a laser one on the other
side
but
don't matter let me check
good night
oh I can't go together with it so I
guess it has to go through here
and then
it just stops right there where I want
it am I missing something it's probably
fine this way oh but the only question
then is
nothing I have no questions
I am okay
we'll probably want to go out of time
and have to do it again but that's okay
it's all okay
so do this
and uh
[\h__\h] wasting
wasting my
what
come on one more one more one more I
am confident in my Solutions in my brain
just watch this
okay so refresh
wait no yes this is this is the end
point for this cube right I'm pretty
sure
okay
um
we're good we're good we're good
what the [\h__\h]
um I don't know which ones this Cube's
ending point if there if that even
matters
but
um
wait did I just um
no I think this
is looking pretty good so far
if I bring this one up there
rewind this one too where it was here
by the way I will stop this now
and I can jump
uh
[Music]
but wait how did I turn this thing off
ah just by blocking it
I guess I didn't place it nicely enough
I don't think it was ever blocking
though
or yeah I grabbed it too early
I mean if the time on this one does not
matter
then maybe not I don't need it
I think I'll
think I might just try it again
it did block it you think so
wrong wrong wrong wrong
no I never did
never did
okay redo
maybe wait maybe I can
oh
[\h__\h] why did I go down okay
I thought it was already like unsavable
um
no
um I mean I had I needed a moment to
think
oh yeah this is
um Point refresh
no let me do it again I was not ready
mentally
okay
now I bring it there
because I need it for later there
okay
like I need it now
if this all works out then it was pretty
straight
forward and simple
uh wait it's okay
[Music]
it's okay
that's okay is it okay did I like delete
the time
thank you
is it over
is it too late to apologize
deals meals
I know right
but I
I had this
point
where I was thinking
[Music]
nah
um
One Step missing so
oh
before played refreshing is there it
does have to be
no
after
hmm
so put it there refresh
bring it down
here
send it through
bring it here again
Maybe
let's reuse the jump pad to go back
don't jump jump jump jump and
what's up
bounce back the same way oh
[Music]
true
okay okay well then I think we have
finally
found an understanding
okay
that is so very simple
um
I just needed that last hint
and okay
well I got quite far with it on my own
so
I am satisfied
I promise to watch the rest of that
thank you
oh perfect uh stop
okay
okay smooth as hell ooh if only my
pickup lines were as smooth
oh can we make the jump back or are we
gonna mess it up
you will see in three two one
[Applause]
[Music]
where's my Applause
here he comes here comes
oh
that was amazing that was actually like
a big brain time from me very clean
solution very easy
relatively easy felt easy
I know it still took some time but you
know how much energy do we have
oh 76 oh last time I checked it was at
50 so we're making good progress yay and
this looks like a chapter
11. chapter 11 is done Transformers
cubes in disguise
it's like soonish so I can make my
burgers
what happened here oh
hmm what are these what are you guys
these are explosive cubes oh these are
not part of the puzzle exercises most
commonly used for demolition purposes by
the engineering team you just have to
get rid of that like these how do I make
them explode ah now it tells me in the
launch
button
but but we're not really using them
for the exercises
maybe they will be useful
another way
more than just here oh my God I'm gonna
like kill myself but can I also launch
them from a distance let me see
no at least not this distance
time to Break Stuff yeah oh god oh
[\h__\h] I was gonna turn around and say oh
my God I feel like I just saw a person
there and I guess I really did see a
person there spooky
foreign
hour
[Music]
is area first shiny
does that mean that's probably me right
a previous old meme
[Music]
huh
what
oh there was a normal door but it's only
unlockable from this side
memories of my past yeah
I can keep my distance before launching
them
didn't work
anywhere
why I thought that would lead me to like
a lower room but it didn't anyway I
think I need to bring a cube
I need to bring it with me one or two
I can launch them pretty far
[Music]
oh maybe if I like charge it
I guess if I like stand back uh that's
what you mean from a distance I thought
you know I have to stay close but then
we can go away you know I just go away
and then shoot it
foreign
[Music]
elevators
protecting multiple entropy pods in the
vicinity we stay on high alert
maybe the solution is to destroy the
Moon
I don't know man it just feels like that
might be the right thing to do
they just don't realize it because
they're up here and they think they are
the solution but maybe the solution is
to get rid of the Moon and tired
[Music]
oh my God I thought the leaf was a
person
what's happening
I don't like
oh
violence but permission granted wow
[Music]
do I get more
oh oh [\h__\h]
there's a couple more over there okay
[Music]
oh there's there is even more
but what if I need even more than this
because I missed again is there more and
more coming or is this for once not
endless spawn because usually it's
always endless long
oh
[Music]
okay then we're just running is this
Laura no okay uh
at least we can protect ourselves a
little bit oh ah we're having this kind
of situation together
always keep an eye open for lower guys
that was easy
they're already going home oh this one
was simple
no worries what is this
why is it so shaky
[Music]
[Applause]
what was that
this top this part took you a while the
Wonders now
new puzzle element introduction entropy
fans entropy fans will create a
photographer away from its origin rewind
entropy fans to reverse wind Force no
not even more
is always stressful when they turn on
that music and they make them follow you
but I feel like we had enough Elements
by now I don't like wind I hate winds
they're all staff members uh we want to
thank you for your hard work put in last
week all puzzle operators worked all the
time we managed to generate enough
entropy energy to enable reversal events
2043. this event rewound over five years
and the purpose was to say
the bees
without bees
Earth's ecosystem completely failed
causing huge food short okay but maybe
it's still not connected to the
cataclysmic event though
but still
in any case
causing huge food shortages
crop failure and civil unrest
now Earth has a second chance in Saving
the bees we have sent this information
to Earth and hopefully they can reduce
their rapid decline over the coming
years
is that really like would the bees like
in reality really be a cause for
everything to completely fall apart
inevitably
that seems like crazily excessive
scientists say yeah other animals
pollinate too
why do we need to pollinate to make
flowers go Bloom but what if what if
they just don't does it really matter
oh I guess they pollinate the crops too
oh
like like wheat
they pollinate wheat too
not just flowers or crops
I do I do remember like I had to
pollinate my balcony fruit
the the berries
with uh with a little
um
brush it didn't work too well but my mom
told me to do that because she thought
maybe I don't get bees to come up to
come by
oh so even you could do it yourself but
I guess not in
that amount of
uh yeah not that much maybe but wow bees
are so important wow
I mean I always hear it you know oh B is
so important we need to save the beans
save the beans
I didn't think it would be really that
bad
you don't save them
what is this ah
we can bring the cube here cool
the laser killed why is it a laser cube
out of all things
what does it do
nothing but it also just stops that
which is nice too oh no we cannot oh
oh
[Music]
what if
we send it up like this will it stay in
this position
uh why am I oh
I guess it's the wrong way there we go
okay and if I now just reverse the cube
stay like this
then that's pretty good already can it
also suck Mia
but I need to bring this one up again
[Music]
that is strong as hell holy [\h__\h]
why why why why is it so strong how does
it do that
he's just quite some power
so that's another element we have to
consider
while we're solving these puzzles hmm
as starting to become quite a lot
of dog
what is this
thank you
all these components yo
that's the accept
you can hear something sizzling for them
like it really
uh
but I think that's pretty quiet
um
I mean I hear it too but with bgm
I can't like it completely rid of it
[Music]
uh
maybe better now it's in the game okay
then you guys were
maybe hearing this wind sound
oh yeah oh yeah
okay let's do this guys let's solve the
puzzles
yes the fans in the game
I guess so what is this about
huh
oh no what what what is this for
it's already too much for me do I stand
on here
like hold it and then send it there oh
yeah that might that's mine
where does this one get turned on oh up
there
um
[Music]
I don't think that one is supposed to be
there
[Music]
but let's just
put this here first because that seems
kind of obvious right
ah
so it might really be me
who has to be ventilated up there
oh what if I first place it like down
there so I can
shoot myself onto the conveyor belt
but actually no this comes first
yeah shoot myself on the conveyor belt
next
um walk over here and then let myself be
blown up here or sucked up here
something like that
oh
yeah no I have to go up no
foreign
could be wrong though of course
[Music]
uh
wait how do we how do we turn that one
on again up there oh yeah
oh see
okay
and I mean it has to be me but at the
same time I need to bring
the cube here too ah eventually
I will
bring the cube up here too okay I think
I think I got it yeah okay
good
she master
[Music]
I've been drinking so much more tea than
usual these past couple weeks damn
making progress definitely
haven't been telling you guys any
tangents though
I do have tangents though it's not the
lack of tangents it's just I don't know
when to talk about it
you know the past two days you want to
know what happened there when I was like
on Twitter and I was like oh my God I'm
so [\h__\h] stupid
I'm telling you
so the reason I took two days off in a
row
was because I thought
I was
having someone overs
AKA I thought
was coming over
but
bye
completely got the date wrong
and like we were like apparently talking
um
we were talking about it but
without realizing that we were talking
about different dates even though like
it's not like it was so unclear
but at some point I just assumed it was
these two days
and I
was planning it I put it in my calendar
and and yeah I on the day before I then
started booking things I booked a train
ride and uh
a restaurant reservation and then I was
gonna book another train ride and then I
was like I'm gonna book this for nappy
Chan too so I write to her and I'm like
I'm gonna Reserve this for you I need
some info from you
so then after a couple of minutes she's
like
question mark exclamation mark question
mark
uh and I'm like
and she's like oh [\h__\h] did I not like
tell you properly when
I'm and I'm like and I scroll up and I
scroll and I scroll and then I
understand that I am misunderstood
something
um
and I'm like I'm so sorry I'm so
because then I was like [\h__\h] can I I
probably can't refund the things I
already booked right but I was able to
refund pretty much most of it so all is
okay it's just I was very confused but
for this reason
I kept those two two and a half days
open
and then I realized that was unnecessary
[\h__\h]
um
wow
you know
you know it will be like that
it's okay though I only lost like maybe
24 Euro or something like that from
something I could not cancel but
um the rest I was able to cancel I'm
just gonna book everything again when
the time comes
yeah
rest time is good yeah I mean I tried my
best to use the time well and
um as you guys know I was like working
on setting up something
which did that really work out so well
fever
I had I tried everything you know let's
just talk a little bit I tried
everything I
I watched a million tutorials to set up
the thing that I was gonna set up
and um I got it to work you know I also
bought like specific
um equipment that I needed to buy like
certain things
um that would help with the performance
of what I am needed to set up and I
wanted to set it up this week because I
wanted to record something specific with
it
um which one's not in 100 necessity
um it didn't need to be in 3D but I
wanted it to be in 3D
so I was hoping I knew it wouldn't be
perfect but I thought at least you know
a decent performance would be nice I
didn't have too high hopes but my hopes
were so
devastatingly destroyed
so I set up everything right and I was
up until like
um 4 am setting it up and then I was up
even longer because I still had to cook
but I really needed to get it done
um
and
I eventually did get it to work
which I was so proud of and it was
quite frustrating I must say
uh the 3D suit for home 3D
it's what I'm talking about
um and then I tested it a little bit and
that's what that video was
and at that point of time
honestly dancing still looked very very
scuffed
but I thought it's so it's okay-ish like
I can't accept this amount of scum just
for the sake of it being in 3D
um so
I was like okay I'll record the whole
thing on the following day
properly like I wanted to so
I cook something I go to sleep I wake up
I just you know
do my things and then in the evening I
tried recording it
so I set up everything again and then I
ran into some troubles again for some
reason suddenly things just were not
working as they were working the evening
before of course
like the software was not doing what it
was supposed to be doing even though I
was doing it the same way as last night
and then when I finally got it to work
somehow
by jumping through some hoops
um
the performance was
absolutely terrible
and after a while it was already so late
again that I had to kind of stop again
so
I was hoping that since I kind of was at
the end of my wits at that point
that on the next day things would just
work properly and on the following day
one problem kind of
one small problem kind of seems to have
solved itself but the other problems
were still very much existing and it
kind of seemed partially even worse
again
um and I tried a couple things but I
just could not figure out what the
[\h__\h] problem was because suddenly my
motion capture results where
like so insanely laggy
everything I was recording
was
with low FPS for some reason and with
um like
a bit delay a big delay like the moves
were like three two to three seconds
delayed and really like slow motiony
kind of
yeah really not in sync and I think
maybe
it could have in theory
it could be the internet but I don't
think so because I bought a dedicated
router and I bought uh anyway I actually
have very good internet I tested it
don't really think it was the internet
connection itself but maybe it could be
many things
but I just couldn't figure it out
somehow it just did not work like it did
in the first night
and I got really sad and upset and I ran
out of time so I gave up
and whatever I had to record I just
ended up recording it in 2D
so I kind of wasted two full days
on trying to fix something
yeah
and that was kind of hope
is a suit for some cool things and the
only thing I really ended up using it
for was since I was already wearing it I
was like okay you know what I could at
least take some
screenshots for thumbtails so I took a
video where I in very slow motion and
with lots of delay just did a lot of
poses cute poses for thumbnails in the
future which
it's great to be able to do this in 3D
but I
to be honest like in my default outfit
I don't even want to use it much in pump
nails
so
that's not even that helpful either I
mean I got some cute poses now and looks
cute and all but
I wish I had like a different 3D outfit
well
oh well
ah it's okay I am
I will try to make use of the thumbnails
and and I'm hoping now I don't know I
can still somehow fix the issues but it
seems very like
finicky like one day it will be good one
day it will be bad
and I can't rely on it so I can't really
plan with it
no
I do hope you can get access to Future
outfits in pretty yeah I asked like it
seems like
um you know I just can't get it like out
of nowhere there has to be an occasion
like 2 million subscribers which is so
far in the future
or like one of those concerts
like you know the Cali concerts
and that also
seems very much out of my reach oh I'll
just have to
take what I have
um
anyway so that was overall very
saddening and frustrating for me the
whole experience I
I felt like I wasted two days
and
um yeah I wanted to make good use of
those of the mistake and scheduling but
not happy with it
um
I was like
I was kind of happy with how it worked
on the first evening so that I even
planned on like doing a ring for the
adventure stream
in the upcoming week but now I can't
rely on it like I don't know if it's
gonna be even
like a tiny bit
okay looking or if it's just gonna be
complete scuff
scuff scuff
yeah
yeah uh well well well
I
just wish I had access to
a studio a proper Studio
a decent studio
[Music]
anyone anyway
myself and go Japan next month in
December
January yeah yeah I kind of
um yeah of course why would I not be
planning that
um no no one
except amen really knows how to work
with that suit that we got but I don't I
don't want to endlessly annoy Ahmed with
my problems but I mean if the other
members need troubleshooting the
question is like what are we gonna do
then like not everybody yeah
should and the way I'm in with this kind
of stuff and I try to avoid it as much
as I could to
um but yeah I asked to get like some
kind of
contact point
contact person to contact when I have
troubles with this thing
but on such like sudden short notice of
two one or two days I guess it was not
possible
uses something different
no there is no one
no one
let's go back to the
back to that that was my tangent just so
you know what I've been up to the past
couple days I tried to make it work and
for now for now I'm giving up because
it's [\h__\h] pissed me off but
I wanna see if at least for ring for the
adventure
Maybe
I can get it to work decently yeah
anyway so um we kind of figured it out
we just have to do it in practice not in
theory
also also also in theory in theory I
need to know it to
um
so
uh I don't know I don't know where to
start
uh probably
this one goes here
right
oh oh
yeah [\h__\h]
went back
I don't like that let me redo that that
landed like [\h__\h]
make a European Studio that will
probably never happen I we will never
have enough
EU members
to make something like that actually pay
off because we would have to pay rent
for whatever Studio we're building
and all the equipment and it's just not
worth it for
right now it's just me
if the if there was a Next Generation
that was just five members of European
members which we all know is not gonna
happen
then maybe
standard six
but I think we all know
how that one's gonna go
[Music]
yeah
oh well let me let me try to focus
um
this one moving right now
no okay good
land smooth
um
Yeah well yeah
it's
moved to America I don't want to move if
I would move to either America or Japan
then it would be Japan
but also not forever like
neither of those places I would want to
live forever
but also
oh
like it's not easy to go for longer than
a month
either
[Music]
huh
okay cube is there how do I get there
you guys said bring the cube first
I don't think I can go
pull him up the other fan
to drop a bend down uh and then reverse
but this is probably already too much
time on there uh where am I bringing it
here right
ah
that one won't take me either unless the
cube is up there too
song
first
ouch
I did not see that one there
first bring it here
it's really decent and stream times
I know I know I know
yeah don't worry I'll be staying in
Europe for quite some time I'm sure
um
uh
oh
oh first here and then there
I think
or the other way around
because now
I wouldn't be able to jump over there
okay but that's definitely already too
much time
hmm
oh let's go
[Music]
beat me up Scotty
okay now please
this [\h__\h] has to stop and this please
come back come back come back to me can
you make it oh
and then
oh yeah okay that's it
that's it
oh
[Music]
we had time to spit on it
got me nervous then for a second oh
[Music]
thanks guys for like trying to give
advice to like trying to help me
but yeah there's like
some things I can't explain well
reasons and behind the scenes things
wow chill
oh God
[Music]
please chill you guys are so cute how
can you be
so [\h__\h] mean wow
stop
[Music]
I'm just gonna go up here I don't know
if that's
I don't know if that's where I need to
go but I'm trying
I'm more cute too
these actually may not be
endlessly spawning because I don't see
oh where they would be coming from
what do you think
yeah
[Music]
I think
yeah it seems very quiet now
hooray
can I just go up here
don't leave me behind
everything's broken
no respawn yeah
it's a good thing
even the fixed state is kind of broken
thing
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] that one sounds fast oh
it's time guys five percent we're so
close
oh yes step one of 93 to fix an
overarching or overloading reactor just
Engage The entropy laser capacitor
nodule pictured image 20 feet titanium
rotation axle pictured 31a then by using
a machine power oh God we're gonna die
like an Ikea guy don't know how to build
Furniture I Believe In You Are oh well
I'm glad someone does
huh
so sweet but then soon she will
disappoint me and I will know she's evil
after all is she who knows Jared I'm
going to keep it simple but I will only
say this once play to clean up your desk
more the very reason we stand for is the
very thing you're doing
clean up what
what
how can you sit there with a big view of
Earth criticize them for polluting their
oceans and being wasteful and yet your
desk is just covered in litter mm-hmm
please I won't be cleaning it up anymore
I'm not your mom from now on I'm going
to put a Post-It note on everything that
you need to clean them from oh
where are the Post-it notes I don't see
them
we're okay
it didn't do it so of course you didn't
clean it
huh
how could he know what to throw out
this is a cute comparison
this desk everything perfect beautiful
and then yeah okay yeah that's [\h__\h]
messy what the [\h__\h]
why is there like a [\h__\h] ton of trash
bags just right next to this table
I mean that's really just too much
you could just take those out if they're
already in a trash bag anyway
yeah at least it's in bags but that's
exactly why you should just throw it
away
[\h__\h] maniacs
oh yeah
what are we doing this time
[Music]
you know what would be fun if I just
randomly like run around and then
accident Ally solved the whole puzzle
just by [\h__\h] around a little bit
wouldn't that be so fun
I would be mad oopsie I guess I solved
it
what's this dude oh Bridge okay
okay oh and we want one here to stop the
laser ah
isn't this
simple except for the fact that
that laser will re like um forget make
me forget everything I've done
right
all my rewinds
[Music]
yeah okay
so
[Music]
it could be
simple and bad
but
what is it
it's not
[Music]
aha I mean I can bring it back so that
it ends up here but I needed to be the
other way around so what if I
wait wait
how fast
what if we start
Here Comes that's the last one refresh
bring it here
refresh
not literally it
now it cannot be
that easy
[Music]
this is my problem because I I can't
bro yeah
unless
whoa
it created a new rewind even after I
went through there wait wait
it
after that until he's solving [\h__\h]
I just do the fan
why was it so simple
[Music]
I am unsure
but have hobaria you have proven
yourself very capable once you rewind
Earth you could safely return home so
desired
what about you what are you gonna do I'm
not sure what my purpose is if there are
no Puzzles to operate and manage that's
really depressing I may like to see what
exists outside the internet you want to
go to Earth together
what I remember yes
I think I would like that
oh I wonder if this like rewinding [\h__\h]
the gun itself would work on Earth too
because we can rewind Earth but does
this gun work there too
sentient she
is that's a problem right
but she's kind of been sentient from the
beginning oh
oh
sentient I feel like I've heard this
word before
but I feel like the game is
making me really acknowledge it as a as
a word
[Music]
uh
this is not gonna work is it gonna work
she's this one for no reason well did
you make this Jump by accident because
it doesn't seem like it should be even
possible
was this
ah these oh
oh
[Music]
I need the cube to come with me
I need the cube oh wait is there another
platform there Perhaps Perhaps Perhaps
no way
or nothing
hold on
remember that there's a fan
I didn't realize that one there but um
what can we do with that one
it's bringing us nothing new
interesting how how the air goes through
that
is that realistic
I don't think so
no no what I mean is that I have not
really included the word sentient in my
vocabulary
my whole life
I feel like actually it might be the
first time I heard the words after all
in this game so
that's why it feels weird to me
I'm not very familiar with it
okay yeah
[Music]
well
I ah maybe we just launched it before
this one already arrives right
uh
but we bring it relatively close
oh rewind oh yeah
oh yeah
thinking too much again
that's that doesn't seem
um possible ah why did I rewind it so
early
what am I doing
launch it again
man like the even the simplest
oh nice
wait wait how do I get rid of that again
uh
does the cube disappear when I step
there
and how do I how am I how can I be on
both
because I I never mind it just moves
there never mind never mind never mind
never mind we're good we're good
it is so simple
where is Cube
huh
oh it's over there ah okay and now I
bring it over here
wow I like this puzzle I like it
Zach
kiwawa suckerberg
[Music]
I'm so happy to see you right now
wow
John wine
I guess that was bound to happen
oh wait
I guess I I should have known but I was
just hoping for it to not be true
oh okay I guess I forgot
I thought it was just the one that gets
rid of the memory but not of the cube I
don't know I don't know
so can I bring this one down and then up
or does it have to be the other one for
some reason
do I need
cubes up there was a the door is already
open right
yeah
oh this is actually quite simple again
um
I just have to be
launched at the right time
use another block to close the laser
door
wait if I walk through here now
oh we're good we're good we're good okay
okay why why what
uh
[Music]
don't I have to bring this Cube over
there too
I'm not sure what I'm doing but as long
as it ends up back there again aren't we
happy
time
okay
let's go oh but wait I don't uh if I
move this one I can't move it because I
didn't
didn't do anything with it okay
you just have to make this one movable
and that's that
[Music]
okay I see now
I see now
[Music]
was there enough time to do that
foreign
[Music]
and maybe I don't have to
on it which one is the one I brought
from the other side this one right
um that is this one that has to be
sacrificed
oh I still need both cubes to get the
new cube with the memory because I
deleted the memory Sorry by going
through that damn that really sets you
back oh that's annoying
okay well how starts over
uh how do we do it oh yeah okay
launch it maybe I should have refreshed
it though
it's okay
hmm
no
I said that a nice set oh
I forgot what to do here [\h__\h]
uh
[Music]
and here there we go there we go
you got it you got it
bring it back
well
you know
the fairy of doing these things often is
easier than the practice so
I can imagine you guys must be sometimes
looking at my streams and molding and
morphing like oh why doesn't she do this
and that and this and that and to be
honest like I watched a stream
the other day
of someone playing a game
and I feel like
you know I I can have definitely similar
feelings I can I felt a little bit
frustrated
um as well and also like
low-key annoyed by the streamer also
being
annoyed uh and angry
at the chat even
four not
telling the answer I guess stuff like
that so I felt like I was like on on
your side oh how long have I been sad
felt like I was on your side
um for that moment I was a viewer
who was
trying to deal with a a moody streamer I
guess
I get you but yeah it's important to
have two perspectives
so whenever you guys are mobbing out at
me remember try
my perspective okay
try to
think about
how much I'm suffering
while playing these games not even this
one in particular but
other more stressful games okay let's
focus so I can actually do this one
right this time
[Music]
um
foreign
Cube needs to have the memory of being
both here and here maybe
right so if I is it okay to rewind this
one I think so
so it will be
here first rewind and then
here right
wait that one is that one even necessary
that case
um we're willing to get rid of that I
don't know
it's probably fine yeah so this one I'm
safe to reset I think
I will bring this one to the other side
okay
so
[Music]
let's say I I need I need this one over
here too though right
ah [\h__\h] wait until
uh no
yes yes I do wait
[Music]
wait did I [\h__\h] up should I have thrown
them both down first
I'm good really
but
I only need to rewind one cue
but I need
in order to be launched up there
don't I need two cubes
[Music]
yeah I can time it
like I was saying before
I don't know about that
[Music]
um
which would mean that
wait okay
yeah okay so that's there now
but it also has
[Music]
I think this is really possible you need
to transfer both Cubes at both times
timing isn't gonna work
was transferred to where
those are cute for both buttons
well yeah but like it's not enough time
because once I let it go it goes back so
fast
this is not realistic
my setup earlier was correct yeah I
thought so too but I just accidentally
deleted one of the Cube's memory and now
if I really wanted both cubes again
I
[Applause]
at it
no wait I'm good
um I can go through I just have to redo
this whole thing
right yeah okay okay
that's okay
is this the right order so I bring it
over there I put it there
jump and
immediately while I'm jumping perhaps
I
don't know the one thing I was missing
at that point was the fact that this one
needed to be moved I guess
as well
and then once I'm
whatever let's just do it
I hope
it's going to work
[Music]
please
okay okay
I
just need to
do this
for safety and you know what why not
twice
for extra safety
[Music]
so I jumped down
we're good about that right we're
feeling good about that
um I need this one now to go all the way
back to open that
all the way AKA I don't see where it
will that's that's okay that's okay
and now I let go of this
we pretty much cooked to go this one's
currently blowing not sucking right
yes okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
and last but not least
see this one also was very obvious from
the beginning kind of what takes time oh
God that's so scary
I feel like I've seen this in a
different game before this kind of like
ghost
so scary
why
[Music]
oh
that's so scary was that outlet was it
an outlet really
was here rewind the cataclysmic event
we ride the cataclysmic event why does
it always like
you know
make this word so important question
you're not question not a question look
Noni
why did they leak leave
why did they leave oh can I read this no
why did they leave does she mean her her
colleagues
probably because we can't save the Moon
we gotta go
to the Earth
leave the moon in order to save the
Earth I don't know all they all just
died they didn't leave they died
hmm this is an automated message please
do not reply Jackie tool Unfortunately
The Interpreter Center has rewound Earth
to a date that is
birth
20 Australian 1999 this now means that
unfortunately you will be unable to
return to Earth due to potential
duplicate person
ah oops
oh oh
unfortunately what a what a
nice thing to hear
that you will never be able to go home
can you not like kill the duplicate
person
sign up for emotional support and
well-being class
oh
um
that's that's uh sad
maybe they did that from like everyone
who is working here
and maybe I don't know yeah it would
also could be possible but probably not
the case here is that by making the
Clones on the Earth
due to um
uh timeline Paradox
the they eventually disappeared because
two of you cannot exist at the same time
I think I've heard this in like Umbrella
Academy or so
yeah
please no more fancy bubbly ghosts
anymore I don't oh my oh
head to the reactor control panel I'm on
my way
no
I think there's no more
sheesh
is an evil evil ones or a friendly ones
please be friendliest
oh it's gonna blow up again
another good one okay
oh no that one's evil
you're evil right
are you oh
platform for me almost missed this one
oh
what do we have here nothing
I thought I was
huh
oh
okay okay okay okay
aha it's even marked perfectly why as if
they knew why did they build it like
this
they broke it just to have some fun with
jumping
blame you jumping is fun once you have
this down
[Music]
when we have an explosion one
for what
oh wait no this is just normal kill wait
what
how
ah I'm blind I'm officially blind
oh
I need a another
cute
nah
I just have to think with rewinding time
[Music]
there we go whoa that honestly that's
dangerous that should have killed me
that should have done some damage to me
at least
that did not look safe on me oh we're
getting like a a test whether or not we
remember everything we've learned so far
I'm sorry I'm sorry
please please please please please don't
make me do that oh again
the game anticipated this moment
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] I forgot that ah
and I'm dead am I even supposed to go up
there I think so
maybe if I just go a bit further
[Music]
why it's I'm so difficult to make is
because like that thing is like a little
bit too high it's it should start a
little bit lower so that I don't like
get stuck
foreign
[Music]
it's a pretty easy jump it's not easy if
I can't do it easily then it's not easy
hey oh I made it
it's hard to do it's not that easy
oh
[Music]
one one percent
oh [\h__\h]
wait give me some time like what where
am I supposed to go
all down here oh yeah
what the [\h__\h] no no no that's stressful
please do not do that um suck me [\h__\h] me
[\h__\h] me
um
hey oh I'm getting better guys
I'm learning
is learning to fly
[Music]
okay
what if I already make it like do this
now oh I can't I could like actively do
it okay okay
[Applause]
please use all your power thank you done
uh
[Music]
oh oh oh there's one coming right there
yeah where do I go where do I go
I felt that
I didn't know when to go
yeah he doesn't shoot anything at me so
I can't shoot anything back either
man
what what
Pac-Man Bobs just like Pac-Man
I don't know
Pac-Man gives me more happy vibes
less stressful vibes
my nose has been so itchy this whole
time I just can't get like cat hairs
out of my nose
I will go this way and then down
yeah yeah yeah
looks right now oh okay so Bridge cute
oh
perfect placement uh
is there is there something
they don't follow me of course there was
something
can I rewind that can I ew I can
oh [\h__\h]
fun
fun where to go next
help
oh
[Music]
whoa what do I do uh here
no am I rewinding it
I think I am
I'm like I'm pushing my mouse
it doesn't feel like it's doing anything
[Music]
I just had to go there okay
what the [\h__\h]
rewind the Reactor Core there is no
other alternative this car okay
suddenly I can't do that
immediately
[Music]
rewinding entropy course
foreign
[Music]
protocol
three wait are you guys not making
joke and it's supposed to be portal we
just have Auto auto correct correct you
four sneezes [\h__\h] who's spanking of me
it must be Astra
the door here
any luck
Cubes but no lower
where are we
this is the surface of the Moon
how am I here without uh what the [\h__\h]
what's going on
more more
I see her
Springs first priorities yeah uh just
ignore what's going on in the background
hey
professional 800 kilograms of moon rocks
with excavation to be turned into
concrete do you think you may be able to
turn this over in a couple of weeks they
are needing it to build a new structure
around puzzle area 16.
this was so worth it
um
where where where am I going to just
straight
[Music]
wanna
and up there I guess
oh no don't break don't break I didn't
promise I'm supposed to go up is that
timed oh there we go there's like a loop
happening
constantly oh wait
all right tutorial done
read zero Kara hajimaru
hey what is that
[Music]
um
okay
what the [\h__\h] out of here
have you seen
that's right
on short terms oh baby so cute come with
me Hayden follow the weird robot follow
how to follow oh wait let me step on
that can I oh
look
look the last bits of Lord that I can
get
uh you
hey wait you you was me
hey Jonathan regarding our conversation
last week about creating a new set of
puzzle areas what about the Zone just
underneath the reactor section 10B I
think it is there's loads of space there
now that area isn't going to work I
think we tried building some stuff there
a while back but it just didn't work out
the terrain is way too unstable and it's
become a bit of a Dumping Ground do they
mean like this area right here
also it's way too risky being that close
to reactor maybe we could expand onto
the beaches instead I think puzzle
operatives wouldn't mind catching some
rays whilst doing the puzzles good to me
I agree
this is tell me right they mean this
area yeah yeah hi
I just jump again
you sure okay
[Music]
oh
nice they're still implementing these
kind of things randomly on it
wait I have no more reverse gun though
how do I reverse ah doing it on its own
now yeah yeah yeah
just have to wait for it
oh
Lord I've sensed lore oh no there's no
lore here what
what place that like that
and not expect me to expect something
what do we have here
yeah
okay okay
oh oh
huh
and when it's um in its normal state it
would make me jump there
ah cool
when it's broken you jump down when it's
normal [\h__\h] but it's normal you jump the
other way
I couldn't make it I was panicking
Panic moments
very calculated yeah
oh [\h__\h] okay I thought we turned it
around I know I guess that was the door
oh someone turned the lights back on I'm
scared of the dark
okay maybe I was not supposed to jump
jump off of it [\h__\h]
ah don't worry I can get back up
oh [\h__\h] how many seconds is this like
five one
two three four five
oh I feel like I'm in Minecraft now
where the diamonds
research
oh it feels safe in here
oh never mind never mind it was just
quiet for a moment
foreign
[Music]
tell my cat Puffs and some birds talk
like that too
it really sounds like a cat
cute
oh wait wait wait
not as though yeah you chickens no you
don't really chirp much
you could practice some chirping I
wouldn't mind I thought that was pretty
cool
look how about some chirp chirp
[Applause]
you're gonna turn into a pigeon if you
do it a lot
hilarious might not hurt
no
you already speak fluent in English
besides [\h__\h]
so I think you guys have potential
you have the necessary intelligence why
am I I'm like still looking for
computers in every corner
in the last 20 bits of the Intel
just call a pigeon a flying rat
paintings can be really pretty and
really cute okay don't call them flying
rats
they're your fellow Birds species
let's not be so mean
what's this I can't read
oh
it's a different cataclysms
strategies kind of goes on data center
everyone's Earth from the back minus 100
years and further from severity of
cataclysm urgent appeals sent to
governing body what what's next
huh
oh that's it okay that's all the info we
got
meeting thanks they come from the top or
from the bottom
oh [\h__\h] I lost track
oh
the top did I
no I didn't
Came From the Bottom
yeah I'm climbing I'm climbing I'm
climbing
is this the right way
other oh okay
what I have to wait for that one
probably
what
I'm supposed to jump on that like when
it's like coming back up or so
let's jump down what
what
that's what I call a faith jump
wow that could have gone very wrong I
wonder how much they would have rewinded
me
nice
sick trick jump
what
honey oh I hear some of the evil ones
those are evil right
I haven't launched very well
wait don't don't detonate right away
oh why are they different these ones too
oh [\h__\h]
okay one is dead nice
oh
[Music]
I got it
against the robots they will not take
not take the world
the human race
[Music]
hey look at me look behind you yeah
hey come here never mind we'll do it
this way
foreign
[Music]
I wish I could launch them a little bit
further and they would like do it
immediately
okay one I can take there we go there we
go
maybe I didn't even have to fight it
just felt like it
um I want to go that way too
all right
rock climbing it is
are we sending these first oh oh it
comes back to me
okay I will go with them no maybe not a
good idea
[Music]
because I don't have the gun they work
differently
really
I'll just hey how come you get these
hope this works
this time it fell down and
okay
oh I didn't I didn't launch it
launcher
yay
oh
there's no one there but
maybe someone is there by the time it
reaches it
oh
okay my turn
noise
thank you it felt like bowling
oh
bye
oh [\h__\h] what is that joke
uh
okay so sometimes it rewinds the wind
here maybe now no
[Music]
[Applause]
uh no yeah okay okay
how are they still alive what the [\h__\h]
that was the right timing
uh let's look at the little particles in
the air does it help
no
the particles just stay
they're like completely
um
well I'm out of bombs it would have
helped if these particles would move
um what are we gonna do do I have to
kill myself
um there's no more bombs here
and the one that actually oh never mind
I got one the one that did go up
did for some reason missed them I can
see the wind yeah
yes
kind of
what
it just went that way what the [\h__\h]
okay I'm gonna risk it
[Music]
whatever I don't care they're not
following me right
come on what
I'm supposed to be
flying over this wall I killed one of
lanes yeah I don't know how I did not
even did not even notice it all right
let's go
oh
what
what I jumped into the void and then I
turned around
and I guess I was falling down I guess
that was the wrong timing uh
ah the right timing is when that thing
is gone
wait for it
[Music]
hey help
okay redo why am I still alive
hey let's do some exploration as long as
I don't touch the water I guess I won't
be dead
maybe there's a secret here
no I think I should be dead all right
professional game test
yeah I should be hired
but normally in other games
I I rarely have this like
happening that I find some
some kind of bug or loophole or
something I wish it would happen more
often it's actually kind of exciting
I landed there too
ah
why oh she did this time I landed
perfectly fine all right then oh I guess
here we're doing the same thing here
the lights are so beautiful
all this way
so quiet every time the
the cookie tomatoes
tomorrow
[Music]
I never watched it by the way I'm sorry
I can't relate
but I definitely
heard that before
they had a place they placed the jump
pads like so perfectly didn't they also
it's quiet now in here damn really sound
proof perfect for a vtuber to stream
oh I was thinking this was a special
room of a special computer right in the
middle
doesn't seem to go anywhere from here
it's supposed to read
something
oh oh it just opens the door
that's it
count as an Intel
nice
no lore
what do you mean that
I have entered
enter a loop
after
what that should be 49 don't you think
why does that still count as 48th wasn't
the one before
foreign
can I go back
no
Nani
oh okay I think I had to do it at least
a couple times
foreign
[Applause]
center staff as you all know the ongoing
recurring cataclysmic event has been of
deep concern to us here at the entry
Center our humanitarian and prosperous
progress in being a gatekeeper for
Earth's timeline seems to have met an
unfortunate and unsettling block
unfortunately our hands are tied if
Earth cannot correct their course on the
timeline then we will simply meet the
same outcome of the timeline no matter
how much data we send to Earth or how
many times we rewind Earth please note
that we are an ongoing and complex talks
with world leaders
on Earth in an aim to put a stop to this
seemingly endless loop that we're going
through we greatly appreciate all your
hard work during this unsettling time
take care all
hmm
okay
49.
still the same [\h__\h] Corridor is this
the same room are we looping or
oh it gets darker and scarier every time
at the music even added a Beat
again
let's find attach the orange generated
rewind log of reversal two two four five
seven even spotted device charge device
enabled or every one five years prior
sent to Earth
corrects projected course on timeline
failed Earth what the [\h__\h] you had one
team job
don't you [\h__\h] understand like
where's the problem why does it fail is
it just like like physically
impossible for Earth to fix it or is it
because it's just something they don't
they don't learn from
they don't take it seriously enough or
not
kill issue
issue
why why or a fly [\h__\h] stupid oh
there's two emails now we do get a lot
of lore here at once
operatives due to the current
unfortunate events in the entry Center
is enforcing a six day work week to
increase our entropy yield during these
unsettling times we understand this may
be frustrating for a lot of you please
understand on your Hardware is extremely
appreciated thank you
okay that's understandable
hey Arya
come here where are you we're done at
the transport base are you coming we
don't have much longer to wait
[Music]
they are flat they
Moon didn't they maybe they like gave up
after hearing all this
yeah and then I didn't make it so I'm
the only one left they left early
[Music]
oh yeah
I had a big office all for myself
I was going insane
how many times have I been here
you've been here before
maybe I should add something cool maybe
I'll scribble something little notes for
the next Aria
or can we make this one
be the last
oh
end of the world end of the world party
do they do that every time
fun
how does the world end why does it keep
on happening
oh yeah don't worry so much about it
don't worry about the Earth's problems
just chill on the moon just ignore Earth
man they don't know how to fix
themselves so then we have to maybe stop
trying to fix them
please note that the entropy Center has
now entered a lockdown State and is
preparing for the launch of the
evacuation transport base
huh they're locking down but they also
want to evacuate
what
I don't understand though
oh
what oh it's not even oh there we go oh
yeah I known as my office by now thank
you for telling me so obviously
oh oh oh
[\h__\h]
bam
that's freaky
oh my God
it's made me go insane
my game crashed is this normal
it's just like
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] I'm so scared it says
that
ue4 project cable game has crashed
and will fatal era but you guys don't
say it
did this happen to you guys too I'm
scared I'm scared
who's everything is this like one of
those things like with um Doki Doki
literature what what's it called
it looks so scary
oh it crashed the quad oh it was
flashing before that message showed up
but the the music was still playing and
so scary
[Music]
yeah dokie Doki literature Club but they
recognize when a streamer is playing
their game I don't know man
it's freaking me out
oh that sounds like a like the Among Us
how how far did I go back ah no it's all
good it's saved in one of those doors
oh we have to go for the whole thing
again
that looks like it
please don't crash again that message
was so weird it felt so weird
I think we have to read the messages too
read I know what I mean
Felder is finished yeah because it's
like well this is where it ends for you
Arya you can't say that
the remission has failed
try restarting the game I guess
[Music]
that's scary the lore saved that it
didn't do it before it didn't
happen
what wait is it even more than we had at
the end of the left what
it gonna be rising yeah I feel like this
is getting spookier than it needs to be
no it stays at 50 free it's like capped
now
[Music]
Mommy
how did you turn this into a homework
game you know you know everything's a
horror game for quinoa
yeah I guess the lore saved
every time
and really then maybe I don't have to
look at this but this is weird I feel
like I had to look at it the previous
times
[Music]
okay it's not nothing to be scared about
this is all normal there's nothing weird
about this
Halloween is over oh
that is not scary I've seen this before
don't crash please
dude I know I'm making this scary by
myself I don't want to for now it's 55
please let me go please let me
let me
oh [\h__\h] things are floating
you've been here before Loop Number oh
over nine thousand
[Music]
find Astra oh okay well she's somewhere
deep deep down under
in Australia
this isn't real how does the world end
this isn't what do you mean this is not
real
what is entropy anyway right
so I saw some argument
we're here already I saw some argument
about how what entropy means and how it
doesn't necessarily fit like the game
title I don't know what's it mean again
why is Earth on fire I stay
why did they leave yeah why
rewind the cataclysmic event I know
trying
I skipped the last lure
oh no
I think this might be the end for me I
found and lost a really helpful
companion who was with me doing all the
puzzle exercises
area Adams have you read an email from
her before I can't really continue
without her I'm stuck beneath the
Reactor with all exits broken I have no
way to escape I've commandeered an
office where I can maybe start some
research and perhaps find an Escape
Route if I can maybe find the cause of
the recurring cataclysmic event
I could find a way to stop it
wait that's myself
to have a companion is Astra right
[Music]
okay I I don't know for some reason when
I read Arya Adams I thought it was
someone else
can I go back
let me try ah no it was locked down
there
[Music]
did I really not it was the two pieces
of lore that I just lost
God damn it
oh
that's the beginning
[Music]
of the game
normally water would kill me
I wonder if I step over there
if it would kill me but it's so calm
right now it's not real it can't be real
where's the Earth
I got a lot of points but I didn't read
them oh okay
huh
well
well well well well
wake up this isn't real yeah yeah it
doesn't seem real because it's too calm
to be real
door
which door I didn't see a door wake up
Arya now wake up hurry up oh oh there's
a door now but it didn't open it didn't
it didn't open hey
didn't open
Island
things are floating I can't open the
door
wake up
oh
[Music]
you're looking kind of find from this
side like
I don't know if there's the other side
that's exploding but you look okay
maybe the exploding was a dream
maybe we've never been to the Moon
please don't kill me
[Music]
cute butt
what's over there you see something
monster Maybe
hello is that Astra where where the [\h__\h]
do you see Astra
how can you see it from there
what
how did Arya say it so fast
[Music]
[Applause]
also last time I watched this I played
this game that we there were like a
couple things that I just did not see
and really could have never seen so fast
okay okay that works too I love this
thing it's so cute
Oh I wanna I wanna see what's down there
I wanna Crouch
ah
you know what no lie
I'll take the normal door thank you
oh thanks music why
oh okay we're playing uh dodgeball oh no
oh no
oh we did that okay good
nice yeah
[Music]
literally bunked my leg against the
table out of shock oh
too far
oh
[Music]
yeah that was not far enough
all right
[Music]
did all the evil is
[Laughter]
[Music]
[\h__\h]
oh that worked on one of them I don't
know how many are there I'll take
I'll take this one with me
I probably didn't have to but wait lore
lower no lower
what
I have to walk out nice
[Music]
nice [\h__\h] Dodge
uh hi don't mind me they're making out
no more no more making out
[Music]
float
okay
no no no I'm gonna launch it maybe I
guess can I not launch this thing alone
oh there we go
[Applause]
[Music]
interesting I I was gonna see if I can
fall down but
[Music]
I felt to save and then I was able to
fall down after all
[Music]
not safe working environment
what never happened at kfp oh they're
already dead
no mobs
oh nice they stayed dead
huh
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] where did that come from
laughs
[Music]
that scream
hurt my throat
yeah I saw it at the end
but it was not uh here right
there you are
[Music]
oh no
it's not very convenient for me turn
around please thank you
hey hey look freaking hell
[Music]
yo this is not a fair fight
hopefully
[Music]
why is the music so different now
come on come on
got him got him
incinerator
oh wait it's like my gun on the other
side
[Music]
I'm just I'll just turn this on
oh I'm still alive
as much as a robot gun can be alive
hello hello
handheld injury device systems now that
was smoother and easier than I thought
it would be I think I lost you forever I
thought you had died I miss I miss you
lots
here and then a painful tickling and
everything went dark
um same thing I remember my sisters were
rebooting
levels around 87 did something happen
yeah I can't quite explain it I was just
worried reality kicked in something like
that you're pretty handy to have around
you know a stop flirting you two
I can rewind
a few more puzzle areas before the
entropy device is fully charged
let's do it
good to have you back Astra
a few more puzzles really now we're
gonna do more puzzles now
it was kind of weird
now
didn't we realize kind of that
everything's [\h__\h] pointless
I guess we're still not giving up
chapter 13 done
hey we should have taken the bunny with
us we are two areas away from the main
control deck now that the reactor is
stable we just need to finish charging
the entropy device two areas doesn't
mean two chapters
down there I discovered a lot
um
oh there's me these elaborate I don't
know I don't I don't think this is the
first time we've been on this journey
definitely not
hmm
she's gone I'm gone
[Music]
kind of sucks like she has nothing else
to say about that besides
[Music]
last round
how come you don't remember
how come
[Music]
oh no no no no no no
no
I wanted to pick it up not to jump on it
that's true yeah but I want to believe
that she's good because she was so
kind you know
like especially at that moment where she
was like goodbye
bye forever now bye-bye
uh
yeah
I die thank you forever exactly
I just felt her love on it yeah
her genuine
love towards me
oh
oh there's no computers down there right
I don't see
I don't see any lower
[Music]
definitely better than like previously
what is this for
huh
why am I what is this oh
we're playing with containers again okay
[Music]
lunch
you can eat lunch
I only have like some cereals and some
one kiwi
but I'm not yet hungry I'm still doing
quite okay
surprisingly oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] is this
okay yeah
can't wait to make some Pearl guards
making a cheeseburger this time with
actual meat and actual cheese
exciting spooky ghosts I can see them
too
oh hey Connor so yeah ghost exist I'm
telling you I've seen them there used to
be one in my house maybe not here at ECE
but on Earth definitely
I don't think anyone has proven it but
I'm sure but I think I have a theory I
think one
with something too much or too often
previous timelines start to overlap with
hours and we start seeing visions of the
other unused timelines
oh I guess that's what I'm seeing
because I was jujit thank you it's
actually been six hours and 46 minutes
uh I know it sounds a bit weird but it
makes sense right yeah it makes sense
it's a little French science though
don't you think with French science
come on man we're on the truck
on the moon in a facility that can
rewind time on Earth and you're saying
my ghost fear is too French you make a
good point beer I'm Peter in five
yeah I mean in the fantasy world like
this I would believe in ghosts too
but personally
me no I don't believe in ghosts
oh the door is opening that was it
that was I guess this was not considered
a puzzle area what comes next is oh
analyzing surface temperatures it's hard
30 Celsius to cook an egg from 20 000
miles away what
it's incredible wanna test it out any
eggs that volunteer to be cooked right
here for the sake of science
cooked by this by the Earth
by the share
hotness of the Earth
wow
wait is there some secret lore somewhere
hmm
already fried it's too late for you huh
use Astra to rewind you back into an egg
hello man we really want to do that if
we start doing stuff like that I feel
like we're never gonna find the end to
it
typically I guess
Phoenix life I do be like that
study area ecological research puzzle
area is 14 up there why is it so high up
there
[Music]
um
is there a lore there
[Music]
can't stop myself
I did fall a lot earlier I am true and
yes they just hire up there in general
it's pretty
nice design
although I wonder if the plants were
already supposed to be there wait I
forgot something apparently
huh
it's one below oh there there that that
thing there
um
I wonder can I cheese it like can I
control how I fall while I'm falling
okay
let's try to stop this like midair
go go go go oh
this sometimes happens where you kind of
accidentally kill yourself while you're
trying to rewind the platform you stand
on
yep they did not think this was gonna
happen
um
gotta be more careful when rewinding
time guys [\h__\h] tester I wouldn't say
it's a bug but it's just not really
smartly placed because you have to stand
on top of it that's what they anticipate
you to do
but some pieces are safer than others so
I'll just staying here
okay stop a bit more
awesome
[Music]
there we go
you got it
I'm on the Casual six hour mark almost
seven almost seven we're past
6 hours 50 minutes give me the credit
that I deserve the following puzzle
exercises are rated extremely hard
sections one two three four and eight of
the answer the entry Center are
currently destroyed and not accessible
oh this is the fastest route okay then
really hard okay guys we have to really
concentrate and use all of our brain
power for this
turn on the brain juices guys
need your help probably
this is the real [\h__\h]
it's getting serious now
good luck thank you
[Music]
let's see how hard it really is if even
Astra warns us about it
huh
it's very the door is open there and I'm
so close
how
[Music]
I guess
uh I don't know
what does this do oh it activates the
jump pad
okay
easy looks manageable I don't think this
will be too difficult but who knows
I will regret saying this
let me just check it out
put this here and I'll take the jumpy
thingy with me
oh
maybe I can leave it like
here for now
Ice Cube on the desk behind
it's an extra height I don't know man I
don't think it's really intended to be
done this way let's be real
[Music]
definitely
means though that both of these cubes
have to end up on those two at the very
end I think we understand that oh
what
why
why would I want to jump down
there
huh
Bridge
what
double bounce
to go where
only Bridge the bridge here
or maybe not even necessarily here but
it doesn't look so complicated though
like I can
see us solving this
bring everything back
okay
need to rewind the jumping pads yeah
yeah yeah
let me just in the hopes of
you know it's not really being that
difficult even though she told us to
and anticipating a quick solving
let me
um
okay okay
sense it
you slept at a two-hour Mark but that
means you only got like five hours of
sleep
oh I do not envy you
okay so let me just look again so here I
would need a the jump pad and then I go
up and then I make the bridge right
[Music]
uh
but
ah wait okay
[\h__\h]
I guess we are still just testing after
all let's say this ends up there
after
I've used
this yeah yeah
what no
that's not quite it
um the bridge instead
control yourself
we've got no time to waste
waste quit I could I wonder if I could
even like while I'm jumping I tried just
now but it didn't work but if I could
like eat it over there
but in any case on it
[Music]
so
then I would make this bridge but
[Music]
maybe if I
ah if I have the
jump pad starting right here and then
I'm I'm here so I reverse it back
to this state
and then
I reverse this to be here okay yeah
that's simple Infinity
yeah we just have to plan it out nicely
and save some time
so okay
oh yeah
41 seconds on it did we get more time on
this again actually this one seems to be
good to go in theory but we have to fix
this one because this one will not go
back all the way
fortunately and I need both so okay okay
restart
more than 49 seconds yeah
we got upgraded I don't know when and
why but
no complaining here
so that is your last placement
and
you would go here last okay
so next
[Music]
um
I bring the jump pad
or on that
button
no can I uh actually wait
it has to be right
this is look at it
oh we can probably do both yeah
you're ruining it
Let me refresh this one
actually that's one thing that we never
really experimented much with having the
cubes bounce off of each other
stuff like that
okay
and now
I
bring the
[Music]
um
wait I bring
jump Cube first I would think
yeah and back down again Joe
bring it back down
hey
[Music]
ah
it's so hard to wrap my brain around
this
because
No it should it will be fine it will be
fine it will all make sense once I'm
doing it right
so now I bring it back it's here
then I jump put the bridge up there
that's pretty much it doesn't rewind
anything
yeah I didn't she say these ones would
be hard I've had harder ones
harder riddles so far
okay you can go now bye bye bye
maybe the bridge is not perfectly placed
though
foreign
's good to go this one still has a lot
of time on it let me try to place it
I don't know like this
[Music]
oh please don't fall down
okay
don't mess up the jump
[Music]
oh that's good did you see me let's move
around a little bit there
okay come on
yeah
I started like underestimating how smart
I am
almost insulting
okay yay
[Music]
not bad
they're more forgiving this time no no
no no more smart let's see how much is
charged I want to see only 10 minutes
yay
mm-hmm
how much
81 percent
oh dear what
so need so much
such a kind calm voice telling you that
you're about to die it's really the only
thing you really need chance of survival
is currently
4.4 oh that's pretty high 224 yeah what
how are you calculating my chance of
survival
why is this room tilted
[Music]
what is that button for ah for the dorm
random number generator So Okay I uh
first of all
and
you go through here make you into a
laser one no no no
no oh okay and while you're trampoline
let me just
experiment and see kind of like
go anywhere with this
no I don't think so
okay one more and go
and now you become Lazy Boy
[Music]
wow
power I have
nice I couldn't even take that with me
oh but then I guess it wouldn't go up
okay and then I need to jump out here
okay okay but this is also really simple
oh can I go there though
oh there's no
one which I think it would show up in
Orange if there was lower okay okay
um
[Music]
no exactly what to do
that's where I came from
okay
so the last point where we need it is
here as a jumping pad
no the last point where we need is here
it can be a jumping pad though second to
last is here as a jumping pad and a
third to last is here as a laser boy
so
uh we send it through
first to make it into uh no actually
into the jumping pad
right smart correct
[Music]
uh what did I just say I am
first this then
this
yeah
and then I send it through
well I'll do it again
I didn't want to jump together
yourself
ruining it
[Music]
better
laser laser okay
wow so easy
sounded like Kobo
uh wait
okay go go go go go go go
that's it
that's all that was necessary
[Music]
oh wait uh yeah yeah we're good we're
good we're good we're good
move
okay now we only have to make this jump
to work
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
I thought we were up to 41 seconds and
it was like only around like 44 or
something huh
not Day on in
I feel like that's broken
foreign
yeah I'll try to be a little bit faster
I guess
okay
look
yes
you can't tell me that that took too
much time no way no way that was a speed
Facebook
huh oh yeah
yeah let's see it ends up over there all
is good
foreign
[Music]
to your Finishing Line
yay what did you say about the coming
puzzles being hard no they're so totally
not
uh
thanks guys
okay now I'm starting to get really
hungry what is this
extremely large cataclysmic Collision
approaching the center recommendation
speed
wait are you for real eggs you don't
understand
don't have legs
stop saying that that's weird creepy
creepy wait when she says you know time
is of the essence she does not really
mean I am being timed here right
it will be fine yeah take my time okay
I'll go okay this looks a bit more
complicated not gonna lie
now
so that creates the bridge
does it
probably
um let's see
it does
smart
[Music]
but you may notice that my brain has
been fried and I don't know what I'm
saying anymore
[Laughter]
ah
I'm hungry
oh yeah
I feel like I have to look over there
huh
I
understand
I hope this is ending soon
because I don't understand
can I bring this freeway for God
okay I can't
you kill please ah
you are the important piece puzzle
puzzle piece
that I needed
to yeah do really anything at all here
okay
still playing of course I am I'm Kim
Wawa
oh
there's a couple more even
no I will not eat now because I have to
cook and that takes quite some time and
I feel like we are getting there so
yeah
yeah huh
oh
oh I can go right I can go I have to go
it has to be here but first it has to be
here oh is that what the bridge is for
oh oh wait easy what the [\h__\h] is
Santa there has to be a catch
them
so I think this is where it begins for
this Cube
this is this Cube's Destiny oh wait
never mind I might need like the jumping
pet Hero at some point to jump over
there okay we can look
stuff uh
[Music]
yeah get what I'm saying
oh wait what if I go through it leaves
the history of what I just did
oh never mind I have I forgot I have
this you can really know this and I've
been playing this for a while
and I can't think straight anymore but
it's okay I'm still having fun
so ideally
I
want to turn this into a jumping pad
first and then put this here
oh yeah did I mess up
because if I walk through I'm deleting
the memory okay I should have made it
into a jumping pad before
but wait this one also has nothing left
yeah okay okay
it's okay
these steps are important
thank you
we're almost at the golden path huh
where the [\h__\h] did it go
huh
huh it flew away I don't know where it
is
let me do it again I have to do it all
again anyway
see where it went
look like chocolate
okay so watch this kfp
reset
I hope that was okay please
placement wise
wait
[Music]
I can't do that until
afterwards
because now it's deleted again
oh I think I think
that
huh
what
oh I could just jump oh well I mean I
think it's still good
uh
I think it's still okay I can still do
it now right
refresh
refresh refresh refresh
tight
here okay okay I somehow did not see
that as an option
okay
okay well wait this was also really
simple
if that's really all there is to it then
[Music]
it's the yeah it's up it's up it's up
okay uh you stay here for now right
oh that jump is difficult though because
it's like so close
I guess I just fall down
I'm scared why call it oh cool
[Music]
huh
hold
ah what the [\h__\h] yes ah what the [\h__\h]
someone's lit
ter
one more time
we're gonna celebrate oh yeah oh yeah
all right one more time
Solutions I came up with was correct
it's all right recommendations
I'm saying that
it's weird
okay the first puzzle piece is in place
that's gone next
uh ah wait I can't put that there right
now because I literally have to I do
have to do that this uh last
do I or maybe not I just I'll just put
it there now okay
so understand oh yeah oh yeah all right
okay now that make it better do it
better makes it stronger
[Laughter]
Pentatonix remix
hey
okay this is always like in the way
okay
go next go next
[Music]
it's so mean why is the I would actually
appreciate it if the bridge was if
anything on that side
it was okay
okay okay have confidence guys
number one rule thank you for the
memberships
uh
okay next it doesn't matter which one I
send first
yes maybe it does I don't know
you just go go go
okay
okay oh
oh I didn't realize this would be like a
path for me on this side
[Music]
I saw the solution like so fast too
wow
okay okay
let's go
hey I feel like The Riddles have become
easier
[Music]
confidence boost
thank you for giving me a confidence
boost let me look here first though oh
yeah
[Music]
this is the happy ending that we've all
been waiting for [\h__\h] the Earth we don't
care what happens in the Earth but
nibbles that's the real [\h__\h]
nipples is back I know apparently he
wanted too close to the entropy core and
everyone thought it was dead but he's
wandered into my office just now what's
even weather
he looks like a kitten again
oh cute
I wish I could do that with my kitties
I'm gonna turn them back into bubble
bubbles I think the intimate core did
something weird to him he seems okay
though
foreign
[Music]
this is a happy thing
wait you want to escape I saw that no oh
that's that's supposed to be down here
for a big jump
don't get crushed
don't die for a stupid reason again
oh that light is fancy push
okay
everything's so tilted man makes me want
to tilt my head too
oh no
I wish I could throw my cats inside an
unstable core
not more of these guys
are they reproducing again oh okay she
said three of those right that was one
oh
wait
maybe it can lift me up don't look at me
[Music]
well it's gonna look at me
no
[\h__\h] hell you little [\h__\h]
okay okay now nothing's in the way
I forgot to take me away but yeah
just like those buses in London
I have bad experiences with buses in
London
I told you the story before
but it was that time when I was standing
at the bus stop and I was like standing
right like in front of the
like right next to the road obviously
like waiting to get into the bus
and yet like after five buses still not
a single one would stop for me
bullying me or something I have a
problem with me I don't know what it is
yeah I didn't put my hand out because
here in Austria I guess
I guess our bus drivers just know how to
read my mind and my body language like
you don't even have to be able to read
my mind you just have to read my body
language to know because I am trying
to enter
hello
please thank you especially like I feel
like in a city like London that gets so
many
um like tourists
I feel like you should not assume that
you're just gonna you know
have everyone
put the hand
out
so that you know for sure wait this is
why the the other one goes
right like London
no better
but maybe it was because it was a bus
that was like a little bit like
I wouldn't say on the edge of the city
not at all but it was I guess not a
really busy area
[Music]
London buses can be rough it was even
though you know I thought I was safe
because they speak English there I speak
fluent English can't be so bad right but
no I felt pretty lost in London
um no they just really did not stop
because
um I did not put out my hand that was
literally the whole reason
okay so I'm assuming
this is maybe hopefully all that the
jump pad has to do
and but I do need them no I don't need a
laser Cube never mind
ah but wait this one cannot be rewinded
so there must be another
huh
no never mind that one is not necessary
to Open Door
so they don't have to be pressed at the
same time at the end I thought that was
the case okay never mind so you maybe
just stay there
how do I get there though
oh not there
wait first things first why am I uh I'm
like five steps ahead
which might be good might be bad
I've had buses drive past me even after
putting my hand out
well that's weird
that's my I have to ask you maybe you
were at the wrong bus stop or like the
the bus was just not supposed to stop
there for some reason
wait let me redo
wait no there is another thing over
there that's necessary to open the door
so we will never know
just testing out some options here
there's no way that this one Cube has to
go to so many places
there is no way we're probably gonna get
another Cube behind that
I don't believe that I don't buy it
[Music]
oh wait
Korean buses just stop when people are
standing yeah I think that's like normal
in most places when there's no people at
the bus station and no one wants to get
out either then they just don't stop but
if there's someone waiting at the bus
stop
normally see there's another one oh
normally
it will just stop when they see someone
waiting
like I understand if a bus doesn't stop
even though there is a person there
waiting because the person doesn't look
like they want to enter the bus because
there's different buses that go by the
bus station so
the person will maybe just like
keep on sitting and look interested not
interested enough into the to enter the
bus like that makes sense if the bus
passes then I get that I've had that
before I appreciate it sometimes I just
felt like awkward when a bus would stop
for me no one gets in no one gets out
it's literally just me and then I'm like
oh sorry I I did not I did not intend on
getting into you I'm sorry
so I prefer
if they just drive by
oh
it's a bit awkward
sorry for wasting your time I guess
Okay so we've done this so now we can
maybe start thinking
five steps ahead
like we wanted more
bus always stops at regular stops oh and
there's oh there's two different types
of bus stops
I can see at the on-demand ones are just
the ones that are less popular where
less people get up see that makes sense
convey a long jump wow
it's a bit weird here oh wait
that's why there's a blue one on top
they want me to place one of those on
top of that
oh this one is best
and never mind
uh that was actually connected after all
one
preferably actually this one but
whatever
goes here
and then there
and one
ah whatever at least uh one more step
because it needs to bring me up then I
go
there ah
wait let me think which which steps come
which Step comes first why does this one
have so much time on it
um this is where it needs to be last
this is where it needs to be second to
last
okay we're good we're good can I just
lift it up by
doing this okay
yeah
and then over here
yeah I mean that seems
corrects to me might not even
no I don't need that I need both
the whole structure
ah but the other one
huh
money
[Music]
wait
oh
but wait how do I
got a bit wrong I got it a bit wrong
I think oh did I oh wait don't I was
good that I chose this one to go there
oh
this might be fine
foreign
I was just testing okay I think
I think I got it
quick
oh
Dennis if I did it right then it's just
supposed to be one here and the other
one
yeah 45 seconds that's not that's not
the maximum yet so
stop it just go back to your original
place and no playing around
hey my brain did all of that
I'm so proud of my brain oh
oh
[Music]
yay even while doing a bus tangent yay
how much percent do we have
88.
[Music]
a couple more a couple more
I know
stop stressing me out I really
hate from the mirrors now it looks like
a I didn't want to say anything it looks
like a volcano sweating all over me for
the past hour
don't say that it's embarrassing I have
so many people watching I'm saying so
clearly
honestly
what the [\h__\h]
consider a a lady's feelings please
okay I guess
we're gonna put this here for now check
out what's on that's on
I feel like I needed a lot of time to
warm up into these puzzles today but now
now I'm good I'm on the road
[Music]
announced that the entropy Center is now
following a system-wide evacuation
protocol please stop all activities and
head to the evacuation transport Banks
CEO Cole erican oh Cole was a CEO
has declared company-wide evacuation
protocol due to a threat to life at the
entropy Center this must be followed by
all staff members thank you and good
luck
that's the one definitely needed that
was just for the lore I guess okay
uh
is this not actually a puzzle worm
what the [\h__\h]
ah no
wait no no wait
let me on first
this works
oh yeah I guess this is not is it is it
it is
[Music]
I forgot this bridge because I did not
know
ah how do I get over there
rewind time
[Music]
okay
it's so easy but sometimes it's so easy
and so obvious and I've done it a
million times before but sometimes I'm
still like oh how do I do this
with the
simplest thing
[Music]
so that's
hello over there but
I'm kind of scared of jumping
[Music]
I wish that if you already set
everything in place like this that it
would stay the way it is after dying
I was kind of bound to happen though
oh that's better maybe
should I get the lore again
oh I'm really starting to feel the heat
from the earth now we just get it just
in case sorry
[Music]
all right 60 out of 76. who knows maybe
it would have been 60 nonetheless but
I don't understand this system
thank you
would be weird if she made a first try
hey
it would be natural
okay actually this is good because I can
literally just drop down
right here
okay
baby
what do we got what do we got what do we
get
um
oh why is this just like almost
set in the right position but not quite
have a tall Cube
wow it could be a model cube with those
long long balls that you got damn
beautiful why am I doing it this way
this makes no sense
they're probably yeah there's gonna be a
bridge Cube connecting this and then
I think
could be wrong
but I think I think therefore I am
#philosophical Phoenix I came up with
that was me
no I have to do all that within like
here
I like that
do I also have to rewind it like from
they're interesting so that was probably
wait I can't rewind because every time I
do this I'm I'm deleting so
we have to think a little bit
differently this time oh yeah
how would I do that if I can't like
rewind
huh
yeah yeah
[Music]
oh
s'mores guys I got that one from Chad's
thank you
all right oh
okay there's another one
what did that do
what
is that cable going is that not
ah get up there so I can take it out oh
what about this one though
I told you talk Cube
tall Cube
[Music]
freedom for
them
uh-huh okay
why did I do that
Freedom something you guys will never
know what it's like
but you're you're happy with that right
you don't mind it
you don't what the [\h__\h]
the [\h__\h] bugged into that is glitched
into it I think
oh man
I wonder if that would kill me if I was
to stand underneath it when it's coming
down
I feel like it would
gosh now don't don't mess around now
I'll never be free of potential and I'm
happy freedom is overrated so true so
true I agree 100.
outside scaring dangerous yeah yeah be
safe at KFC yeah yeah yeah
okay
that's all democracy dies
well that is not like you guys had a
problem with it you might regret it
later on but um
for now
seems like we all have no problem with
that
so where's the the bridge Cube that I
have been anticipating
weird
something's missing
I know I guess I'll just lift myself up
with this boy
you just have to
uh
figure out a way
ah I think I need this one first to help
me put this one in place
uh you'll see what I mean
no no I need the box to lift me up as
long as there is no uh Bridge Cube then
this is how we're doing it
I think I'm doing it correctly I think
trust me because perhaps
it has to be here no
hmm
such a weird way to place this Cube
that was probably too difficult
it's more like
oh what
weird placement
but okay yeah yeah so
um that's what I wanted
and then
ah
we don't need that door to be open
anymore so
big thank you
you see free possible solution
[Music]
this is the only one
who knows that could be other Solutions
but
maybe if you cheese it
taboo
a couple no couple oh
that's not how I did it really that's
the one I used ah high five same brains
we have the same brain frequencies
oh
wow oh that's me
where'd you go where'd you go I follow I
follow
yeah tell me how to play the game oh
that's it that's all the backseating I
get
did I miss something down there because
I just was looking at the shadow
like oh pc pc
I know what I know it I knew it don't
worry I got you
oh okay I'm not gonna read that but it's
okay something happened
that was not really lower that was just
um computer
blah blah blah
foreign
that one
ha
[Music]
that could have been such a beautiful
Landing
you I think you have to do that jump
from here maybe not Maybe not maybe not
that is to return okay
okay now we're reaching kind of like
portal like scales
so excuse me my brain is starting to log
out
[Music]
oh wait
I was like we need something to make me
go over there that's right oh wait I
need the cube here
wow
okay it's rewind time
my brain can do it yes I still have some
power I think so too
so I guess I reset you here
then I am bring you there
I put you down one second
but this probably doesn't count as a as
a puzzle does it
for the game just like
normal in this world
is there any lore
no what
okay oh
wow it's starting to look like the eye
of Sauron to me
yeah you'll go like oh what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] is going on
there was one more PC
ah
[Music]
oh well hey
sounding like hobo again
I just want to spend more time with you
guys I'm just stalling every time I
stall it's because of you
cause of you I stole until your brain
melts because of you it looks like I
don't know what I'm doing and it hurts
because of you I just wanna spend some
time with you that's why I am stupid
because of you
I am afraid such a beautiful song Kelly
Clarkson let's go
I will
see how fast that was
[Music]
that's a long one damn
I hope you are all doing well and
preparing for the imminent evacuation in
a couple of hours for many of you this
will be a Bittersweet moment to return
to your families and enjoy the remainder
of the time we have here
oh oh it's gonna make me sentimental
please note that I don't take this
decision lightly nor is it a mere
decision by myself alone the decision
has been an unanimous across the entropy
Center board after meetings with the
Enterprise Embassy on Earth earlier
today in this clear that our operation
is not working as officially as it used
to as you all know we initiated rewind
event 6293 last week damn and
unfortunately it has led to the same
cataclysmic event occurring just a week
later this has happened thousands of
times now over and over to spend of
several years and it has felt like a
never-ending cycle for many of us
unfortunately Earth correcting their
course on the timeline is out of our
control no matter how much data and
predictions we send them
hahaha
wait so when they say they're like
evacuating are they going to enjoy the
last couple of years on Earth and just
accepting that they will be in
yeaded or what you should read the Super
Chat why
ah the lower skin was important oh thank
you for telling me the most Chrome left
the center with a shuttle but they lost
connection shortly after implying its
destruction the shuttle's destruction
what kind of struggle is that though
like
where is it taking them to Earth
and join the last
week on up
is it Earth okay okay so they literally
go there knowing that they gave up and
the Earth will expose explode but at
least they're getting like
a little bit of time on Earth before it
happens okay
okay
and then it will literally look like
Umbrella Academy
spoiler alert
that was quite something that someone
does someone know what I'm talking about
eh
I'm gonna make another team
bye guys
no yes
let's go
to reference like literally
um
wasn't gonna watch it anyway I
that's worth a lot like if you're into
like fantasy kind of shows
especially
some action
but it's already been a while so I don't
quite remember but I like what was wrong
with it but I do remember like not being
super happy with all of it
there was some weirdness
something was not right
not perfect
with the show to me and
I'm gonna talk about Umbrella Academy
yeah
I guess that writing and the acting yeah
yeah I can
remember saying something like that
um
I'm so critical
weird because like it has so many good
moments but then
some stuff just doesn't add up
it's like
as if someone else wrote parts of the
script I mean that's probably how they
worked there in Hollywood
yeah yeah they don't write it all alone
obviously obviously but why would they
hire someone with such like big
difference in quality of writing
I don't get it
check out the comics
yeah yeah yeah I didn't finish
the Lord shake my head
go back is this going back
okay nice
I thought that was over
what they hire people who hate the
source between why would they do that if
I hire someone like that I would
hey guys I finished it I I said I guess
I didn't really finish reading it okay
and yeah wouldn't you like ask them oh
do you like this like
project
and then if they say no then that should
be
an immediate immediate sign to kick them
out right away what the [\h__\h]
it happened with the winter they openly
hate the source wait wait that's like me
auditioning for an akb48 group saying
that I don't like them
and you know I applied the lyric and the
logic that that this will
help
improve the group because I don't like
them so I will only be able to improve
them
[Laughter]
my bird is the same logic that they use
for using directors like that or it was
just a matter of cost and fame or
whatever who does
hmm
because I do think that it gives you a
different perspective not liking
something
but like really [\h__\h] hating it
is definitely dangerous to like
completely
destroy the original
charm that it had even if you admit that
there were things wrong with whatever
we're talking about
that is probably not the solution yet
and if anything it should be one
director who loves it and one director
who doesn't like it working together
making compromises
um
maybe that could work
but ideally it would be just someone who
loves it because if it's already popular
and is popular for a reason
and then there's no big needs to change
it up so much anyway let's read
um
where was I I'm probably there
it is now at the point where we can't
generate enough entropy energy quickly
enough to repair our own defenses well
especially not if I'm all alone here
which is why we are declaring a threat
to safety
oh we will be rewinding of two years
using every last bit of entropy energy
we have we know our future now but I
hope we can enjoy
these final years two years on Earth
enjoying what we do have I've heard it's
Anarchy down there so please stay safe
everyone
another photo
this is so interesting
but I need to go to an island meeting
again and I'm tired I guess and I'm
hungry sheesh I hope we're finishing
this soon
and how come that junk
made me go
backwards are they
what
maybe I'm supposed to land exactly on it
I don't think I can
see it goes in and goes out and just
like for the moment that I drink it
that's when it helps but then
seconds later it hurts again
rewind the thing in the middle
the blind
one thing
ah
something there ah why is it so hard to
see that that was rewindable
Sparks
box
hmm oh that was supposed to stop me I
wasn't supposed to get on top of it I
want to know if I get on top of it can I
get some lore or is it too late now
because like I don't know how to get
back
did I miss out on some lore
I hope not
okay face first into Steel
oh
yo
you're a Super Chat the place that I was
gone for so long it was just normal days
off I wasn't even like taking time off I
just
really normal oh scary
but thank you and it says something like
um
two years thank you
the next project any troubles and then
you and the rest of your life have
everything goes smoothly you're so sweet
you're so sweet
thank you I will read all the super
chats properly another time but now you
know I just wanna Oh chapter finished
final charge
just want to make sure you know that you
have been acknowledged
thank you
[Music]
if I could Escape I would well yeah
escape this [\h__\h] Moon and go back to
Earth even if I just got two ears I
don't care what happened to the Earth
anymore because [\h__\h] it just
meaningless I need to get out the door
or if I could Escape
Escape
[Music]
it's a perfect song approaching shock
away from the cataclysmic event on earth
oh we're almost at the main deck we
should hurry come on bring it bring it
happens if that hits us
I shall refer back to the egg I
mentioned previous egg
we're gonna become Phoenix
[Music]
oh
foot huh
I thought that was supposed to hold me
up
week
let me create my own world
[Music]
Sweet Escape
oh [\h__\h] my throat
[Music]
I'm doing something wrong
oh
no mother didn't hmm
and now
cataclysmic event on Earth we're almost
at the main deck take me hurry I'm
guessing nothing good happens if that
hurts us I shall refer back to the egg I
mentioned previously pick me ah yes
cooked got it cooked
foreign
I feel like
fun the way they're using them now is
like you know like ropes swinging around
it's cool oh what
the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] you know this be
kind of late what the [\h__\h] man I thought
you were a friendly one because we were
so late to the party what the hell what
what am I doing what am I
what am I connecting to
I think my my gun is bugged
uh
hello
my my gun's definitely bugged I was
aiming at that thing but
wait let me try this oh never mind we're
good I saved it I fixed it
I'm a game developer
now
thank you
see me you don't see me you can't see me
how fast did you see me
try me try me
okay okay
[Music]
sorry I really like that song
why is
that there when I'm supposed to go there
must be a way to [\h__\h] it up somehow even
though I don't see it because I'm a
genius and I don't [\h__\h] up things
yay
[Music]
stop sounding like Michael Jackson I
feel
kind of insulted
even though I know we all love Michael
Jackson yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
I also detected the entropy device is
almost charged enough to be activated a
few more puzzle areas and it should be
ready good to hear because a few more I
am bringing out the really difficult
ones out of all the puzzles in the
center oh you're doing great
okay that's good because I was wondering
like if the more difficult ones will
give me more entropy energy because
we're we were still like not like
getting so much
out of the previous couple ones
hey applause applause
okay but that also means maybe we're
getting really difficult now also
tilt it
how is that supposed to work
won't things like fall over
God
hmm
uh
okay if it will help you
he will help me
I need you
oh
oh I see when this like goes up that way
it will first hit that and then hit that
I suppose
that's not the only thing that I needed
to hit though
right I need ah that one first so
basically
we just start by turning it all around
that is possibly the last position it
needs to be in yet because it's
connected to the door okay okay
eight hours already it feels like
fourth
man the only way I'm feeling that the
time has been passing so much is that I
what did I say possibly possibly maybe
is that I feel like I need to go to the
idol meeting again and two idle meetings
in one stream is something that has
never happened to me ever before I think
okay maybe it did in like my 12 hour
streams
[Music]
anyway
but will will this work
it has to
meet them
yeah yeah because I've been drinking so
much yeah
what's up what's up is that it well then
how do how do I get out there
hey there's like
way more to that there's like stuff here
[Music]
huh this egg so cute but Bird's Cube
okay cool cool cool maybe then we should
not focus on this part yet
let's see
no I'm okay for now let's let's just
finish this puzzle maybe then I'll go
how far does this go
stops there
that doesn't help me reach the puke
oh
that will be necessary to open those
doors one by one
positioning is off yeah Light Beam
doesn't have to be perfectly in the
middle
foreign
like maybe here that would be ideal if
that was really how it's supposed to
work
thank you Curry Gohan for that info
the first one worked but the second one
just
doesn't want to work
the more you know indeed
um let me look at it from a different
angle
yeah wait I can't look at it from a
different angle I need the cube too
what
guys let's figure this out is it going
oh a little bit too high like
so so
oh
when it goes back I can look at it I
guess
move forward
I'll
I'll try like moving it a little bit
it's just slightly
ah it worked so what do I do with this
information
look how how do I get there
huh
you have rewind but should I stand on
top of that thing or
[Music]
I feel like I'm blind now
springboard did you see a springboard
okay
so that means I have to first uh open
the
this one right
ah but it cuts off there oh and I also
kind of wasted some time
[Music]
because I need to reset it I suppose
or did I do it correctly
I don't know okay so it was something
like
oh my God maybe
it's how was it even like cutting off
there like it resets every time I walk
through here anyway
oh well go go
it missed both of them
okay one more
foreign
if you place it exactly in the middle
it's finicky
missed the first one
oh it's quite low
and that one's also too low
so how do I make it higher
more left Which is higher oh I guess so
like maybe like things
I was lucky that time yo photo free does
this look like Are you seriously asking
I wonder if some people they walk in
here and they're like like they just
woke up and they're like what what the
[\h__\h] portal free what did I not know
about portal free coming out what the
[\h__\h] valve
like the style of the graphics
[\h__\h]
I feel like you could mistake it
if you were kind of sleepy
[Music]
once the placement so difficult now
I feel like wrong I'm one of those
people really
huh bubble
[Music]
you can't get a ride man it doesn't need
to be straight okay
so how about this it's straight but it's
on the left side so it's higher
oh
okay I think it worked both times
[Music]
um
oh
[Music]
foreign
a little bit too far I don't want to
mess up
there it goes
Bridge Cube where do we want you
do I take you with me
oh
Companion Cube
see that's already quite a nice
Bridge we got here but I guess I'll need
you with me come here
oh
let's say
we bring that Cube over there here
and ah and Laser from here yeah yeah
and then oh
that's the bridge have to be
can it be
even on the left
how can I bring it there without
going through the laser
turn off you need to remove the laser
one first
okay
I'll wait there was on this thing here I
completely forgot about that one ah
wow
I'm Amazed
okay
let's reset you here
and now I can move this again right
probably don't need it like
anywhere else I never mind
you go
oh
that is interesting
I don't know what I'm doing oh it will
reset if I walk through I forgot
true
[Music]
oh I hate my bridge is already there
oh
can I
[Music]
um
is this a cheese strap oh no when I move
it it's
okay okay hi hi
what why is it like that
never mind me resetting
why does it like look up like that makes
no sense
I'll just put it like this
it was a bug
but but in any case if it's moving the
bridge will disappear nonetheless right
okay testing
um
I think uh
here and then
here no it might have been the other way
around
okay okay okay
oh that's kind of hard to activate there
uh
let me bring it out a bit more
[Music]
let's go uh
next is the
that one yeah okay and then and then and
then I just wait until the end until it
settles
oh it has settled every movie a little
bit oh I can walk over oh my God
well okay this level is pretty cool too
and it was also like manageable to
figure out
foreign
[Music]
allowing them to realign their future to
a more positive outcome
never gonna happen
never ever going to happen you have to
give up just accept the energy
but I feel like
this makes me curious as like if if
something if Earth is our real Earth
with no
[Music]
it's ending at a certain point of time
and they could do something to fix it
how
how close does Earth have to be
to
really take it seriously and then do
something about it five years
probably too late
10 years
that probably does not scream
urgency enough yet yeah we probably
wouldn't
because like we cannot get the mindset
of all people on earth
to be the same for some reason even if
it's about something like this
[Music]
yeah yeah that is like stupid then
honestly we just deserve to die if
if not even then we are motivated enough
to do something then we deserve to die
yeah
is that the sun no that's the Earth
um I know it looks a little bit
different than usual
oh yeah because she used a different
liquid foundation
yeah looks a lot very glowing today nice
highlighter you got there no it is
really Earth blowing up in our faces
right now
yeah
what's wrong with just existing well
wouldn't you want to like exist longer I
guess
don't care huh
okay
we've got time
don't care
the bees did that
yes
the [\h__\h] bees
it's their payback they're taking us
down
all right what is this does this site
matter
there's a cube there
see can you not know
[Music]
well well well
thought that would
do something else
okay
so far so good well I need a bridge here
am I supposed to do that
[Music]
I
think
hi what's that okay
back there
and then the red one
and then
I think one okay
okay let's go
hey Smart Cookie
the order did I do it wrong
I did
I did it correctly before so
you know I can't do it I have the
capacities to do it correctly
okay fresh
uh
uh wait wait let me think stop moving
[Music]
yes
is that not what I just did
foreign
no it's wrong it's wrong it's wrong
I can't anymore
thank God we're like
at the end
pretty much
um
am I not repeating myself
this probably first
okay
wait oh yeah all right okay
can we watch Fellowship of the Ring
extended edition after this room are you
[\h__\h] kidding me
no do I look like I got time for that
huh I'm gonna make bird guys
I like how you can literally see my
train of thought
[Music]
isn't that nice
and see how kiwawa's brain works
oh
foreign
[Music]
what did I say
I'm just gonna uh
nothing
this is not
quite correct
you think you're funny huh you're not as
funny as me I came up with that UK joke
I heard literally all of you came
laughing
outside my door all of them I heard them
hey I'm Danny with the funny
oh wait oh there's another one there oh
what
you see that until now Okay so
um
one is lay down
that ends up here
one is whatever but let's make it a
bridge
no the bridge went
rewinding time Chihuahua
think in rewinding time and it will be
okay
and position
almost nine hours yeah
eight and a half yeah
okay so then I will bring
um one Cube here to lift me up
then oh it has to be uh this one
so chocolate
[Music]
do
you join me
you go up here
foreign
[Music]
you understand right why I would think
like that
okay
okay and I walk over
and then I just move everything back yo
this game is no match for my brain power
no it's cutting off there
because of those stupid shenanigans that
I didn't notice it was going up and down
and up and down and up and down
now why
[\h__\h]
[Music]
it's okay
I fixed it
something's weird about this now
the there's some parts missing there I
think I don't think I can stand on it
oh
what oh
never mind never mind
okay
uh I hope I didn't waste too much time
already it's on 29 21 seconds
it's gonna be all right
but I will redo this one
just in case
oh wait I don't even have to
stop doing that because I mess up
everything
yeah I don't even have to go like far at
all
just realized
but I can't see it from here
okay yeah
[Music]
okay yeah it's already too much
ah
okay
it's already 11 p.m what the [\h__\h]
wait
what is ah
okay okay okay okay I was like where's
it going
what's that should be fine now
I see no problem no issue
oh shh
okay
let's do this
no it's not about sleeves it's about
just it being so late and I still have
to cook
yeah
it's just something about that that I
don't like
my confidence is boosted endlessly here
how much energy do we have
14 minutes that's not so bad
come on how much
[Music]
it's like so laggy holy [\h__\h] the system
it's like they're making it really
realistic
okay five more percent so I'm guessing
one more puzzle
she fits perfectly because
just exploded one more time
two more okay
oh what is these
um
I'm gonna speed around this [\h__\h]
she's been
but did not quite understand what she
was
about to experience
[Music]
foreign
just end up teasing it before looking up
the real Solution on the interwebs
interesting chicken
but wait
oh
at least bringing the bridge Cube over
there was the right thing that's for
sure
looking up is equating the feet
I did that like once in a different game
right what game was that where I ended
up looking up the solution
I need that to be there
uh yeah okay
we all know why and I don't think anyone
is mad that I did that
um
so
this is interesting because I can't
like rewind this how I rewind the other
thing
the bridge kill for the button uh by
rewinding after I've walked over
so this man
I understand though
so
that still means I have to bring it up
one more time
one one time I wanna I survived to enter
the path shirts what no I don't think I
agree with that because that implies
that this was unbearable and just
suffering and I don't think that's
really true I survived kiwawa's tunic
playthrough would maybe be or I survived
the making of the golden path would be
more fitting in my opinion
but not that
not this one
I don't think so
yeah I have not been molding the
beginning was a little bit like yeah
warm up but a good streamer
always needs some warm-up yeah
okay I guess we're just repeating
this
like we will go up again
up here but we also need the laser
killed oh I have to pick it what
make it never mind maybe it's not by
jumping
we are no I'm Dreaming now
I was thinking I need to rescue that
kill but I mean I don't need the laser
Cube
that's what I did
you did it this way kind of
I mean what might also work
um
like can you really consider that cheap
thing I don't know I can't jump like
that though but I can make the bridge
over here and walk over just what the
with this one
what it's not always so complicated
okay okay okay
I'll just move the bridge oh
uh because I don't currently need to go
there anymore I'll just have to put it
back properly again
sure
and that is the real it's simpler than
that
foreign
but this feels like the real solution I
was about to say that
no way but this works and this is what
came to my mind
so who says it's not the real solution
eh
yay it feels right to me
oh
[Applause]
I don't need yeah the reason why I
thought this was the one is because I
don't need the jump pad anymore after
this if I'm making
another bridge and but I'm not making
another Bridge
rewind rewind
[Music]
oh
I guess I could like rewind this one too
[Music]
okay
um
do this
and uh
I mean I can even do it with a jump I
guess
where do we put bridge is it both
possible
in that case no
huh
I think I'll do it with a jump yeah
I don't know if it works the other way
but he said this will have to do now
will be that
[Music]
I'll just do this and
huh
oh
what how do I get up
I guess I understand Mom okay
wait we can still can we still hit it
If We Hold that and Rewind it
does that work
just hold it in the air
yeah it works out
neat
okay
smart okay
where's my where's my jump at
the [\h__\h]
oh it's here
[Music]
I messed up but does this maybe have a
history of being there before
let me see
no no it doesn't
I knew that I had this
in the back of my sleeve
I know it all along
the Panic was just for dramatic effect
also this is kind of far away oh there
I feel like I [\h__\h] up
[Music]
maybe we're like ads
7.5 or so
I don't care takes too long next one
please just detect that this should be
the last puzzle area once this is
complete the entry device should have
sufficient energy to be in
being away
finally it's almost been nine hours
holy [\h__\h]
how has it been so much time
[Music]
five
oh God last puzzle
I must say the difficulty Spike did not
Spike at all
that's good for me
as a streamer but maybe not so good for
like people who
expected a bit more
oh well I'm happy
okay uh best I don't know I don't even
know anymore but this is the last one
come on you can do it
this is the last one
foreign
it could also be just a bridge there
[Music]
I get this one first Maybe
oh wait this is a glass wall
oh
it goes through here but I guess I just
can't reach that Cube yet okay that
would be too easy
if they would give that Cube to me so
early what does this one do
you add the bridge
okay I feel like
maybe for now
it's like
laser
[Music]
then
jump pad
like I can literally read this game
like my favorite book which doesn't
exist now and then
this one
ah [\h__\h] we're missing one more jump no
wait no we're not ah
oh
I might be missing one step but that's
just because I could not have possibly
seen that stuff
but for now I would say I was thinking
quite forehead yo [\h__\h]
one more redo
that one time I messed up the Jump Man
why did it have to be now
doing great thank you
foreign
and then there's one something missing
here right
like I I thought so but um
[Music]
the thing is missing
the thing that is missing is I need a
jump pad I guess
Maybe
or the bridge
just a bridge wait no but this is a
window
maybe a bridge that goes from here and I
just fall down on it
that could work
I don't know if I can like bring so much
time into this
bridge to fall down on okay okay I mean
I don't know how much time did we have
left on this one
uh
I don't know we will never know
okay
we'll see we'll see
so I would stand
here
oh interesting let's kind of tilted
okay how about this we should be able to
fall down on that
or preferably a little bit closer though
this is this is the best I can do
lost my foot what
after I am done thinking
[Music]
calculated steps like a Pro Gamer oh
I wonder if I have to save time
by not making it into a bridge here but
just jumping twice
probably
[Music]
hi
yeah definitely we only have like we
have 46 seconds on the clock
[Music]
but still
hey
nice timing
believe in the Chihuahua
uh next is
before that was ready
well you know it just it just you just
gotta be like that I'm gonna you know
you know I want to spend more time with
you I told you that
you started damn
you should be a fortune teller
[Music]
huh
okay done
did I forget any steps
this literally yelled at that time I'm
sorry
my my focus is just you
it's been literally nine hours
somehow I always have to make some noise
when I jump like that
I don't know why
but
night forget the bridge part
no no no no
you done
no no no no no I didn't I didn't I
didn't
foreign
what is that supposed to be
what's that supposed to be
[\h__\h]
it works works
toilet
can you
okay fine I thought I thought it would
like
messed everything up
okay I'm guessing one goes there
you guys were also worried
I thought like I put it in the exact
position that would make me unable to
ever go back thank you butt arcade
so uh
uh bridge this car
breach this car
yeah I think they still want me to
suffer a bit more
uh wait
um
foreign
[Music]
was not even necessary that last step
was not necessary
was it
I'm confused I can do the bridge from
the corner
[Music]
a that one oh true true
so I can take this now right yeah
I need to I need to I need to
hmm
oh
I need to
we need to go to another meeting
so hi
what
I need to jump
hey yo
[Music]
can I take it without undoing this
like use bridge to bring the jump pad
across
[Music]
Bridge across this Gap
but then the time is
foreign
[Music]
I can reset it though
um
do you guys remember
which one was intended for the for this
one I think it was this one
I think so
no no it's because I ran out of time and
I still need to bring it all the way
over there
almost feels like I can make
and this way I'm saving myself like the
time that I spent putting jump pad down
there
this one though oh dangerous dangerous
dangerous
kid it was like already maxed out wasn't
it
can only hope for a lucky
something oh I could have just reformed
it [\h__\h]
let's see where it goes
foreign
I was so close
I was so close oh Sheena
can I leave this here
no
bring it huh
bring it
yeah
no it ends there
it's okay
no I wouldn't have worked don't worry
I can do it fast
Sanic I did by the way watch like quite
a bit of a lot of gameplay of that new
Sonic game
I don't know what you guys think about
it did you play it yet are you planning
on playing it
oh wait
[Music]
nope not interested
nope
enjoyed it a few hours I love it oh
okay some Sonic static enthusiasts
today
reset this one over there because I
don't think I did
it's not a Sonic fan
[Music]
I don't know I have never played a Sonic
game before I think so
can't really judge
but
the one person whose gameplay I've
watched was don't handle and uh he was
like raging so much at the game
it's it was like
wow this was one of those moments where
I was thinking oh my God this is how how
my viewers feel about I feel like when
they watch me play sometimes and they
get really frustrated
because he got so angry at the whole
chat was like roasting him like hey you
should know why you're so mad at the
game you just missed all the hints
that's why you don't know how to do it
blah blah and I felt sorry for him
because because as a streamer you just
sometimes even if it's like obvious for
a viewer you just miss certain things
sometimes
and then you just don't know you know no
no hate me
man as a streamer your focus is just
somewhere else
yeah and you're
like even if you focus more on gaming
than entertaining like I'm more more the
type of person that focus on focuses on
entertaining rather than gaming in my
streams
and I think Dom tando is the opposite
but still
even then
I think it's totally understandable
especially in the in a game that you've
never played before in a series that
you've never played before where
everything just feels so new and
overwhelming to you and there's a lot of
info and you have the pressure from the
audience and the stream to do well and
all that anyways
it do be like that as a streamer 100 of
[Music]
it's gonna be bad ending anyway
oh
[Music]
the entrance to the main deck oh I can
launch them nicely again
wow
yay big
[Music]
nice John nice shot
now for the finale hell yeah
okay I'll kill you normally
I really need to
[Music]
go Bond I am right at the ending so I
don't wanna I hope the ending will not
be too challenging
[Music]
with me
what where's that
suicide robot what the [\h__\h]
what
might be worth thinking quick one really
oh [\h__\h]
no I don't wanna
foreign
what do you mean it might actually be an
island meeting if they are both gone who
is both
but another Idol go to an idol meeting
at the same time as me
fauna
oh yeah we had a meeting yeah
I didn't want to say it unless she you
know didn't say it herself
oh
yeah I saw her and we talked a little
bit for like five seconds yeah it was
important very important
now back to even more important things
that goes really fun never mind I guess
it doesn't go that far
ah it looked like it went really far
oh
great oh
okay that was slow anyway
oh yeah yeah we are like rescheduling
that Minecraft thing
um but honestly it might take a little
bit
longer than
uh anticipated because like
yeah my coming week is I think too full
what's going on here oh
I'm supposed to jump on that thing right
maybe like here
now
yeah
hi
do you mind
you don't even want to attack huh
we post a schedule tomorrow uh ideally I
would like to post I would have wanted
to post it today but I might not yeah
um there will be a thing tomorrow though
that's for sure oh
it was going to be wrinkled but I guess
I'll do something else perhaps
yeah I don't know maybe I'll do
um
a cream
I'll plan for ring fit and a ring fit I
can I can pick you up
and launch you let's go I didn't do that
until now and yeah and then I'll test
out the suit right before the stream and
if it's shitty oh my God any ideas if
it's shitty then I'll just switch to a
different plan none that don't involve
dying
please
yeah
he's trying to convince them they are
withdrawing couldn't you have done this
earlier all this time
thanks e the [\h__\h]
why why was this not
possible in previous times
a little [\h__\h]
Boop him
you have such a weird name it's like too
short
in like interact
thanks I guess
yes
also thank you thank you for the rest of
the chat
Tai Chi is the robot
I know it
that's why he doesn't talk he only makes
like noises like
no lower disappointing
come on
here the main deck should be right up
ahead
[Music]
you're stuck here this has all happened
before no
no enable the entropy device
this cannot be oh this cannot be all I
can possibly do
so true that's probably really true
yes I don't know about that
you could
Aria Arya don't keep apple this is game
we can save it unlike reality
still has like the magic and the
possibilities to it
the potential
lack of
I have the explanation lack of order or
predictability gradual gradual decline
into disorder a state of disorder or a
tendency towards such a state chaos
that you don't
that's why we are always meant to
end up that
can't fix this Arya well at this point I
don't think it's Arya anymore
because
if she already if Arya really thought
she couldn't fix it
then
she would have like just done something
to not rewind it anymore just let it
happen herself like
there's I don't know go go jump into a
space or whatever
is this really Arya at this point huh
is this the place we've been to before
where there were like openings on the
side
[Music]
like we just kind of rewinded it I guess
we started telling these work
beam
go
to the other side because this thing was
on the opposite side last time
and a good look
s
[Music]
what do you mean directive travels at
the end of the entropy device and
proceed with required maintenance
okay on it the end I knew this wasn't
going to be easy
the end of the entropy
the end is never the end it's going to
put the end of the end
of the end okay I just wanted to check
what's there never mind
it was anticlimactic yeah
oh wow so spicy
this is not the end
okay
oh we're really going in
[Music]
look at that that looks like a honeycomb
interesting isn't it
[Music]
so proud
foreign
too loud I'll turn it down a little bit
wait one second
I think I can make it in 20 seconds
hello
one two three four five six seven eight
nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen
fifteen
sixteen
Seventeen eighteen I can't make it
20 seconds I think
floor was that Laura I don't think so
which way let me go back
right it didn't look like it was lower
on the sides
it didn't look like it no it's these
kind of computers never have lore okay
okay we're good we go go back go back
continue do not abort Mission abort
aborting the mission
what the [\h__\h]
she has no sense of urgency
man
okay I'm at the end of it
rewind the entropy device where
he like oh like what here
oh
wow wow
20 seconds in Dragon Ball Z
it's working is it
what interesting
or whatever we're being exposed to the
interview
it's okay but I'm not sure you'll make
it it's my direction it's okay I think
Aria wants to die
oh trust me I think I
70 percent okay I trust you Arya it's
been nice having this journey with you
what what do you understand I think I
understand too I I do I do
it's just we don't we're not supposed to
leave anyone behind on moon Maybe
wake up
[\h__\h]
hey
we're back here at the beginning of the
game maybe there was something here that
we missed
something that we were
supposed to but now we really know how
to do it
someone's speaking to me that wasn't
there before I think
question this is new this is new
whoa
that's me that's me that's me doing that
[Music]
this is cool
Thanks for the Memories even though they
weren't so great oh some Arias were
sitting here just looking at the stars
one last time
foreign
why does this booba have two nipples
those are the real questions
solve puzzles so puzzles
no puzzles
puzzles soap puzzles
rewind the cataclysmic events so puzzles
so puzzles puzzles
[Music]
puzzles rewind rewind
ER
from mind
[Music]
foreign
can we not save the Earth
[Music]
oh I'm moving one step ahead to the next
timeline
oh I
imagine
[Music]
Murphy's okay
let's just skip this I changed her
find Astra that's good
somewhere
[Music]
wake up
wake me up
[Music]
can't wake up inside
why can I not wake up is it because I'm
dead
huh
[Music]
what
so
what was that mean
I mean I I I implied I I assumed that
she jumped to the next timeline
like kind of just skipped something
[Music]
wait that was all of the credits even
though huh
[Music]
oh did we just loop again is that really
it what was that
good morning
Adams we hope you had uh
what where am I please find your
timetable for today's puzzle exercises
black was started a new game okay what
is going on
I did not skip the credits I think
it's just a small team yeah
maybe if there's a message for me
timetable still looks the same
almost the same too
did that count as a new Intel
what
anyone wait are we literally just
looping is the game literally endless so
continue after the end is just new game
basically or are we still getting like
something this isn't
[Music]
that would be funny though
bet she understands she didn't
understand it's just the same [\h__\h] again
[Music]
it felt like she was doing something
different
okay
there has to be someone around
that's it
it literally just loops
[Music]
the life out of me
afraid of you okay
um
okay
I think that was worth repeating and
starting another loop
[Laughter]
[Music]
in history of streaming on YouTube
hey I mean
time I'm not surprised that I'm
surprised but I'm surprised I guess that
um
I was this surprised again
well okay
um I mean if you guys the ones who
played the game are telling me that
there's really like nothing new
coming then I'll just end it here
check my achievements
it did say the last achievement was um
it said Loop
so
that's it
no that's like so unsatisfying
what does that mean she returned
um to like
a day before so but it's like jumping
over to the next timeline
I mean it kind of feels like all this
happened in one day but uh
so she's just rewinding it again even
though she kept on telling her to
not rewind it and I felt like she
understood it I thought she understood
it
huh
but I mean I think it's a funny idea in
itself to like
have this literally just be an endless
loop
I think it's funny but
because it makes sense of the whole
story
but uh
she accepted that she's in the loop but
like couldn't she end it too
but I mean there was some drastic
dramatic ways to end it
but you know isn't that like better for
her
[Music]
like just let it happen
and just let the explosion happen
can escape by not reloading you safe at
all whole
so I did not do her a favor of that is
that what you're saying
yeah I guess she thinks she's solving in
it but no like a previous Arias told her
to stop it because they understood
but even though they claim to understand
it they still choose to repeat it
maybe because they thought that step
they were taking at that point
was the way to end the loop but they've
they thought that was to step a million
times
and took it a million times over and
over again
thinking they understood but they really
did not understand
that is interesting
oh no I'm embarrassed no
the developers won
watch my playthrough no I'm so sorry if
I like you know criticized a few points
but I I did definitely enjoy it and it
did make me feel very confident
yeah they were the The Riddles the
puzzles were
challenging as I said last time but not
too difficult for me to absolutely morb
and always completely rely on the chat
like in Portal I had to rely on you guys
instead and I felt so pressured all the
time I felt so stressed out for my whole
portal playthrough
and I just wanted to like do well but I
couldn't and then here like yeah I think
I I did much better
wow that's
that any person seems to be
the wife Daniel completely understands
that the end is polarizing
where's the alternative ending
alternative ending we need an
alternative ending
we need Arya to do something about this
but it it makes sense like you can't
tell yourself really to do things
differently unless
yeah if you don't remember what you did
but it's weird because like she kind of
remembers and then she writes it down
but then huh
some some things confuse me
there is no good ending yeah
yeah
I guess so bam
there's endless Loops infinite Loops
over and over again is the better choice
over ending it for everyone
eternally
I mean maybe at some point the aliens
will be like a yo
annoying they keep them like looping
this [\h__\h]
and it's really screwing up our business
here and then they come by and the UFOs
and they help us and they stop it
because we could do it at their Superior
as long as I do not give in there's a
chance
it is a moral do morally difficult
situation
yeah
but I do want to think that Arya when
she like jumped over to the next
timeline thought that she was not
starting another loop but instead
just doing something that would end it
would stop it or fix it
that's for sure I hope I hope I hope
she said she understood no
oh anyway wow that was nine and a half
hours I didn't think it would be this
long but thank God I started the stream
so early today holy [\h__\h]
yeah good morning sea time zones
good morning
8 A.M in Japan Ohio gozaimasu
Dear God
I'm gonna go
make a burger now I guess
and uh
think about what to do tomorrow
[Laughter]
it was a lot of fun I'm really glad that
this came out this game
it was really satisfying for me yeah and
I feel like besides the warming up I
needed to do in the beginning I feel
like part two was like
um dialogue and script wise
better than part two the first half of
the game
like the the the weird feelings I had in
the first part I didn't have in the
second part of like towards the dialogue
between Astra and Arya some how and this
time it just felt way more like
harmonized and it made sense to me
what did I say a party was better than
important no I mean part two was better
than part one in terms of dialogue and
story
um
one can never complain about the game
being too long such
gamers are like a game too long
you should be grateful you should be
thankful drag it out go go do please
board tracking out Developers
if it's a good game then
okay I mean I understand if a game maybe
is like 100 hours long that's perhaps
too long but this is still totally like
in the green zone
yeah
no please I made them shorter no
[Music]
no games to be long long games
especially in therapy genius
as long as possible but I mean maybe
from the point of view of a streamer
a little bit shorter
depending on the game would be good and
on expectations because I did take quite
a bit longer than I thought I would take
overall
yeah I guess it was in total like 17
hours or so
it's all right 17 hours not so bad
as a professional tangenter but here we
go another game
finished
can we
consider it finished when it's an
endless loop can we add this to the
finished games of takanashi kiwawa whole
life English
yeah yeah yeah check it off yeah yeah
it goes on a little yay I did roll the
credits
okay wonderful
thanks for watching Everybody also
um
props to the developers hello if you're
still watching I don't know how to say
this in English but good job
it was a great game I had fun with it
and also thank you for providing some
codes I gave them out a couple days ago
I think everyone received them and
hopefully also already
um redeemed them
and played it with alongside with me
[Music]
um
thanks for the stream thank you thank
you for watching everybody
we made it did not give up
oh
Daniel is glad you enjoyed it hey
so when's portal 4 coming
or when's entry Center two coming eh
two
and two percent
it's just the beginning
just to start
gonna apply some pressure
um
just finished this yeah then they should
go go get going start working on the
next one
of course
I demand
sorry no that's disrespectful since
since they they are here I cannot say
such things I I do not demand I kindly
um ask for a continuation
if you um have time and um
are motivated and feel like doing it I
don't know you know
anyway if anyone everybody for watching
and I'll leave you guys here
um
expect a stream
in the evening time I guess
tomorrow on Monday
uh like I don't know 6 p.m 7 P.M 8 P.M I
don't know
somewhere around that time
I don't know what yet but I first have
to eat and if I still feel like you know
putting everything up setting everything
up then I'll do it otherwise
otherwise we just have to wait
I'll swim tomorrow I I had like two days
off the day before yesterday so
I think I'll stream some more mm-hmm
okay and then thank you very much and in
German we say I'll be nothing yeah that
was awesome time what I said yeah yeah
[Music]
um
oh [\h__\h] I just remembered I have some
work to do
let's hope I get that over with fast
shouldn't be too much
yeah how did you
how did you okay this movie is here it's
a sign that I have to end my stream
[Music]
foreign
that's the right way that's it that's it
[Music]
foreign