[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
this is
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
do not scream
do not scream do not cry do not fear you
are in my bag
[Applause]
you're mine I don't know what I will be
using you for yet but you're in my
possession now I got two you're my
second one I think I don't or you broke
your back completely no no I think
that's two chickens in there
yay
hello
look I like I have so many things wow
blue thank you so much
it is so cute
so adorable oh
I am so ready to Thief except for the
fact that this is German why is this
German
why they're
uh en
better
[Music]
um
I have never played a like a Simulator
game before I think like you know one of
those that have simulator in their name
I don't think I've ever played one
before
simulations
why did I never play this before or
something like this because
While most of them I don't know I was
always busy playing my own I guess yeah
the sad Sims I was busy ah cooking
simulator true that was one
one okay okay okay so this is like the
second one
but I
yeah I was always busy thanks for the
memberships with playing like my games
and now we have finally come to the
point where Chihuahua needs to start
playing some Simulator games in order to
have games to play
yeah why do you need to steal it was the
frail why do people I think a lot of
Thieves
uh burglars just
um
mostly Do It For The Thrill Ride I mean
sure they probably need money too rough
times yeah it's rough times but a lot of
people do it for the frail right because
I mean they could probably get their
money elsewhere too but they choose to
do this so a lot of them probably do it
for the front as do I
uh welcome everybody
do I look cute
I think I look
very cute
right say it
yes thank you
favorite in the world
this is so cute I love these asses
yeah I got a mask I got a hat I got a
pokey crowbar I got chickens in the bag
and I got gloves I'm ready to be fifing
[Music]
let me film uh but I'm a bit worried and
is this game difficult I don't know how
to play this game we will have to learn
music
playing it a little bit because I was
looking for Clips you know
I think I saw Connor playing it
and I'm gonna play that before but I
never
I never watched her play it I just saw
that she did play it
um it may require stealth and waiting
okay yeah yeah no problem stealth I'm
aware I'm very stealthy
was are we already what we're already
breaking in
oh wait that's my crowbar that's my
pocket crowbar but it's the same as I
have
wait where did it go oh there
wait what answer hey
hey it's me Vinnie Vinnie pick up that
crowbar and listen up
we got a lot of ground to cover yeah
please be nice to me and and explain
everything very slowly how do I pick it
up e
oh
the Lombardi's paid your bag
they're generous men but they're all
about reciprocity if you get what I mean
see if you're up to the job knock over
that house for me the last one
the last what do you mean the last one
this one
wait what's what's quick slot
quickside you can add items to the quick
slot for fast usage go to inventory
select an item and press the quick
thought button okay how do I go to
inventory Escape
okay a quick slot
uh
here I guess
is it now in my quick shot and how do I
open my quickside I have skills and
stuff what
what
whoa what you can learn stuff like lock
picking agility you can throw bricks
climb vines carry big items faster
um backpack oh more space to steal more
things
appraisal uh is that like yeah finding
out if something's actually like useful
and good
car theft still cars without the lamps
yo
what you can do that with one SP I have
to be level 14. oh
remove security from devices using
hacking tools disable Powers which okay
cool it's like yeah it's a championship
wait did this this is an RPG because
there's levels right we have we have
found out that an RPG has to have levels
and maybe a skill tree maybe not
necessarily but maybe okay
quick slot ah
okay I'm scared but the first one can't
be so hard right how do I go over this
oh yeah on it
can I double jump no
wait what oh wait wait I have to why can
I not jump over that I should totally be
able to do that break the planks
sneaky sneaky sneak sneak
sneaking allows you to make less noises
but it will make you slower you can also
lean
uh wait wait wait wait sneaking as of C
and uh leaning is with a right Mouse
button plus left or right
okay
wait so C
what
ah
that makes me dizzy
okay we're crouching now
now crouching
what
I'm crouching
oh God there's someone in there oh
no it's okay I won't hurt you um I just
want to steal some things for the frill
avoid the light oh oh oh yeah okay I go
through the bushes but doesn't that make
a lot of sounds
how does she not see me okay now he's
looking away very good very good he was
looking right at me how do you not know
this
some dope left a flashlight on the
ground
just take it but don't let nobody see
the light and call the cops
that's terrifying that's terrifying I'm
so scared
I told you guys today this will not be a
long or I told you before this would not
be a long stream because I'm I don't
know it was supposed to be a shortest
stream and also this is terrifying to me
anyway so I don't know how long I can do
this unless it gets fun like GTA who
knows
um
right the window
uh break but that's like loud are you
sure
I mean that sounded real pretty quiet
but open slowly hold e
ASE okay everything with e
hug a flashlight isn't it my quick
thingy or do I not need
a good job time to redistribute a little
well okay this is just tutorial I
probably can't even fail no no not
teapot no there's nothing good here I
think unless these are like what do you
well a lot of Fancy Shoes like I mean
Gucci okay but that's not Gucci what a
fancy expensive sport shoes
Thomas
I thought you had my thing off again how
do I turn the the light off again
yes yes okay
okay steal some stuff money money
doesn't take much space
oh toaster
Air Jordans I was that's exactly what I
was thinking I wasn't sure though
what what the name is besides Jordans I
thought they had the first name
is it that was the first name air
maybe there's something
I can't see I can't see it's taller than
me
okay close it
I'm not even crouching and it's taller
than me
why is it empty should I just leave
with the money
well
do you honestly want me to steal like
some useless like the toaster nah
hey the good stuff is probably in here
no there's nothing in here
still the toaster and I don't need a
toaster I have a toaster and I have a
toasted lamb for a long time oh that it
really wanted me to steal the toast
that's useless what kind of
old toaster not even a new toaster
don't let nobody see you with that
crowbar
um what's uh what's the quick uh switch
again uh foreign
who remembers
cute oh thank you
okay uh climb
off
easy maybe I should close it
okay that's good
leave no Trace I mean
a garden door they could think that oh
go away go away they could think that
maybe you know just uh
why am I parked in the right am I stupid
how do I get into my car
there we go
I thought we were gonna do stuff in the
dark you know didn't we learn don't do
in the in the bright I can drive
can I drive
start the engine
oh God how to do a car oh yeah yeah you
move the key
I really miss
hi what's up
where do we go which way maybe we go
this way
is there a goal drive out of the
location that is the goal I suppose oh
this is nice uh we're on the trip again
press F now probably doesn't even do
what you think it does
f for Boost
[Music]
C right now because that took so long or
what
why why only see this was a tutorial I
didn't do anything wrong
okay
nice though okay okay that wasn't too
bad that wasn't too difficult
good job this just might work
go get some sleep and we'll pick this up
in the morning okay is this where I put
my stolen stuff
jewelry Workshop cool
wait what I can carry the show what
games I can move things
put it back yeah yeah what exciting
close this please don't need privacy
okay but no I'll go upstairs
Oh I thought it was peas but it's uh
wait it looks like peas though the green
ones look like peas
I sleep on the couch really
what I can afford the super cool like
was it iMac
but I'm sleeping on the freaking couch
what I have and I have a laptop I have
this thing and I have a laptop and I
can't get myself a freaking bed what the
priorities I guess
um damn son you live like this
damn oh
sleep until
I don't care what time is it now
us wait now it's 1am uh
uh let's sleep I mean we should go out
in the evening right
I'll sleep at like until
9 P.M
that's a lot of sleep damn
what a what a nice life to have
is there like a like a like a health bar
so I know how much I have to sleep who
is it like whatever check the computer a
few things I need to tell you
okay which one though tools for thieves
let you buy new kit online
takes to use them all
click on steal your forum
still your forum
oh here you can buy
I swear who's guarding it who leaves the
door unlocked whatever check out what I
wrote on Greenview 109. hey I wonder if
thieves really have like a network like
this
well maybe like a secret Discord where
yeah they they say oh this person leaves
their door open this person is going on
vacation
we do we do
[Laughter]
wait what uh new known all
okay so now we have
oh how secure oh this one's free but is
this this is not the one that we just
visited right
for free easy to break the damaged
wooden fence in the back
all TV worth a buck
bear door key in the drawer ah this is
like aha lots of hints for me
there's no one home all the time
what
that's too easy did no one even lives
there probably
what's this
golden goblin
why are these things are this is for ah
other other people are selling those
other thieves are selling this
uh what toy cars 13 000.
so much
is this for my home so I can decorate it
I think so
house rip off
new items
can I get help here
still in games
interested in only the rarest video
games they just don't make them like
they used to
[Music]
is that so
okay okay okay okay then let's go to our
next
thing how do we go
all TV worth a buck yeah let's get the
the TV
maybe for yourself
oh
okay
uh do I go with car to pawn shop
let's go let's go let's go let's go
let's go
to the pound
s i really
um feel weird about doing this today the
Stream
uh I just watched yesterday
some you know you know interrogation
thingy again and it was about you know a
robbery gone wrong and they also went to
a pawn shop also
yeah
yeah yeah
you watch that yeah because it's a new
video on one of those channels
um
it just came out
yeah okay what's uh pawn shop
pawn shop okay
we have a junkyard too
you have your notifications on for that
channel you subscribe to that one
this garage is My Sanctuary oh sweet
potato do you also have like some
magical crystals that heal your soul and
your heart
um
is there something in here no okay I'm
going in excuse me
um I'm gonna sell some things that you
know totally I had laying around
stealing them
um okay I may need this you may need
this really you're gonna buy the whole
toaster for free bucks okay
right or wrong thank you it's time for
green View
don't pawn it off
oh he wants the old TV okay
I'm gonna go get it for you even though
I don't really know who you are what a
steal
uh okay
where is it
[Music]
left on the right side
we're in America right is it uh wait uh
where do you normally I think right said
right
where should I park last time
yeah this last time we parked
we parked there we shouldn't do that we
should really not do that
maybe in the dark here but then I um
[Music]
probably
I mean both places are kind of weird but
there's no one home right so whatever
like
this this doesn't really matter how we
enter but maybe we shouldn't answer too
obvious maybe they have a camera you
know
I mean they probably don't
ah wait is it the brake damaged wooden
fence it said
and what about this
when sticking around at night it's best
to avoid well at places you flash out
will also make you easy to spot
flashlight will have you see the loot in
the dark remember you're easy to detect
with the flashlight on I don't want to
detention unequipped tools and turn off
the flashlight to avoid unwanted
attention from other people I already
forgot how to turn on the flashlight but
I remember the the quick thingy
to steal a big item TV printer put it in
the car's trunk I have to carry it over
and drive home to sell big items at Pawn
you need to put them next to the shop
owner oh okay
can I go dumpster diving
what is this
truly they have nothing in there
ah hiding spot okay let's leave it open
he said he died
the TV won't fit in your bag why why RPG
but no bag fit TV
ah normally
fit everything in non-existent bag
that I carry
lame
music bathroom okay okay
yeah we can just cut it in half and tell
the dude to reassemble the TV on his own
money
the ground in the bathroom
but that is so unrealistic
there's another toaster
should I look I wonder how much I can
carry there's a bag on my
dad anything anything counts
spent um
should I bring a saucepan
oh a key
I look so spooky
I didn't get jump scared I just I just
I'm just genuinely scared right now
okay we take off the old TV oh I really
have to carry it
um I want to see what's in the other
ones I don't even get
when I carry this is this the main door
oh
wait
how do I leave how do I live
how do I leave
this is this open can I throw it through
open first and place that okay I thought
so then maybe I have to have to do that
yeah okay
oh it just falls down I thought I had to
put it on the surface nope
put it on the ground okay
I was here oh
should I
mean they said there's no one here
can I go
oh God
oh go I'll go for it
uh door lock I have a key though
what's the key for it why is my TV go
here okay I guess we'll go we'll go the
other way
what was the key for is that like a
secret word there surely is something
to use the key on in there I'll go back
there's no way that there's anyone
coming from me
uh what's the flashlight again
oh
he was for house no oh
for the safe oh
yeah but that was not
okay no
is there something in the bread box no
maybe there's something in here
can't open it okay
I don't know I guess I'll go
uh
uh okay Master Thief you stole my heart
you guys stop
break the toilet no no a toilet is like
very very very necessary for life so
let's not do that okay they don't need
the TV
I'm I'm an ethical Thief
I only take things that you don't really
need oh wow they have sprinklers over
there
so we've done it see they will be shook
over to the core when they come back
home
no car coming
oh no I'm I'm jaywalking someone
no way I couldn't open the bread box
would have been the most most important
thing
huh
what's happening
oh I went in there automatically I
thought I had to push something
how do I get into the car again there we
go okay
let's go let's go let's go
ah
bye bye suckers
you should have blocked your home up
better
I mean I guess I mean okay I broke the
window so it's not quite on you but
I got back with
[Music]
sing oh
oh
yeah I got the front door key but I mean
did that really help me yeah
yeah look I did so wow wow I have a pro
Thief
hello I see you got my screen
go to Black Bay what what was that is
was that on the TV on the on the on the
PC
oh
am I selling it online to you what what
now
I am on black Bay
hacking laptop
what else you want from me
go to your computer I'm on my computer
click the thing on top
oh wait I've listened on BlackBerry I'm
there for the TV go there and sell it
okay okay
I feel like I have a gun to my head but
okay I'm doing this of course
on my own will
oh here they're taking it oh that's
pretty
pretty worth one buck
height now
I'll put one on there just for you I
thought I could rent one to help me
no and one break their dishes
why does someone have a like was someone
triggered by their antique dishes or
something like that it's like
half those I don't like it
what I guess I'll take it
drive back to 110 and break some dishes
with the Crowbar why why
I guess they were too lazy to wash them
yeah so their cooking was good they need
to learn a lesson I don't understand
this like we could we could still do
this now I will break them we'll break
them
anyway
no I think I want to bring almost all of
these things to the
um to the to the to the pawn shop first
before we go to the next place I can do
that right
[Applause]
eat those dishes a lesson how dare they
be so flat
they say flat is justice but I say no
no no no you must be more curved they
were not curved enough
okay you can have another toaster
and this food selling for good money
bye-bye
hey I'll even close the door I'm such a
gentle man
everything needs to needs to be in order
but I need to I should probably put the
money in
uh
in my home
don't let them cook time yeah
okay okay
how do I put the money I guess the money
huh is it okay to get to keep the money
like at all times
I thought maybe I should put them
somewhere here I'll put the key door
there
it's not we're not going to the same
house we can hurry
the dishes at 110. okay
[Music]
6 a.m oh oh should I not be thiefing now
oopsie no Thief
true I mean I would still be sleeping
100 percent
[Music]
okay
let's sleep what's a good thief in time
1am I would say
[Music]
it could cost but thank you it's not
cosplay I'm a real Thief
don't you dare underestimate me don't
you dare call me a cosplayer
so rude
so fruit I'm real
I'm the real
what is this by the way oh my box okay
let's go
[Applause]
time uh green view I guess
I am a menace to society and to this
neighborhood
and then imagine this thief playing
Kelly Clarkson on the radio other drive
to the
to the thiefing home where is this home
where are you
is there a star on it
do I have to find out myself where it is
what the is it
where is it I don't see any stars
huh all right that's not me
is it is tutorial time over it just
won't show wait that's a Johnson's ah
sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry sorry sorry sorry
I am European uh the Williams uh-huh
but here
over here
and now it doesn't show me food app 104
105.
and you have to get to know this
neighborhood
hmm
this was 109 right
I think
what about here oh
hey I went on 108
one uh seven
out repair cars
what
what got her for bumping into a tree
okay
uh
so
is it here
I'm wasting so much time on finding this
home
you who
there's someone there
why are you awake
oh my God it goes in minutes oh no
it's like Sims time
is this the house please tell me this is
the house no it's not
it's not can I run oh yeah
what the
what
about this one but that's
that's 109
this one
is it there's one ten at One Eleven
use the map
huh
what there's one in
where's my car
oh there
um kind of far okay hope we will not
regret this
and we're gonna really enter through the
front door
I guess if I'll be
I'm breaking dishes
um
blocked
no
uh
I'm coming in
just a little bit yeah
why do they all have the same or is this
the tutorial home
the dishes
[Music]
what you don't even know how to pick
block
go learn the basics I'm sure you've got
enough skill by now
the stuff they have is so lame
oh wait and I can't even see the shoes I
guess okay they used to want that yeah I
can't pick a lock
um
would be nice to learn that eventually
okay am I leaving already because I
didn't really seem like they had much
more
small house hello
okay
let's go
let's go where's my where's it there
I left the door open lock pick eh
I can't do it yet right I mean I have to
go back home to learn it right on my
skill tree or so
I did my quest
learn the skill
uh yeah oh I would like to how
I can do it here
but I did the quest I can go all right
or should I go back inside oof
um
right now go buy yourself a DIY stuff
yeah okay he wants me to go home thank
you Jim stop thank you
ah it's the weekend guys it's Saturday I
think yeah
it's beautiful weather these days so
nice
go to the pawn shop first
what are you doing on this weekend guys
waking up so early to watch My Stream
here see
hmm
it was a s tier for me
great day for freezing right
understandable everybody likes the FIFA
on the weak hunt
early she says yeah okay maybe not
really for everyone
midnight Australia gang oh thank you for
watching
you started decided the day by working
out to Sparks let's go Perfect workout
song nice too
okay what now what did he say tools for
thief okay
lock picking pick locking
uh uh Aya lock pick 70 bucks
okay
how to buy oh
wait I need lock picking level two
I have no skill points for that so I
cannot do that yet
I guess I gotta go
DIY simple lock pick there was one
oh okay
it was grayed out ah it's grayed out
because because I can buy it
okay
yeah
[Music]
I have a very girly Name by the way
oh
I've never picked a lock before
will this actually teach me how to do it
oh oh
what the hell
rotate ah
actually I have to do this
by myself
oh
is it not just like no break a pick lock
press e
what do you mean more to the left
oh what
the I hate it
what
do you mean
Skyrim flashbacks why don't why why what
what is it what
no I'm going left this is for me is left
because it goes new left
the left
should we go the other way I can't even
what's the right now now more to the
right now more to the left
uh-huh oh what and now
and we'll do the right more to the left
wait what
I don't I don't get it
I don't get it
[Laughter]
I almost had it really I don't know what
I'm doing though
I can't do this like in a stressful
situation
I'm guessing left is here actually
now
and now
wait is a bobby pins oh
the close of the pain goes to a correct
angle more the more the local rotate
it's just going back and forth what
slowly
oh
[Music]
don't rotate the PIN
all right
well how do I know it's a sweet spot
but this is a really terrible
explanation of how to pick a lock are
they expecting that everybody played the
log before so they know it like but
already by Nature because they learn it
in real life I didn't learn that I
didn't ever have to break a log before
and then I got maybe my lock picked
before when I
yeah uh locked myself in
but
huh
no idea maybe everyone has played Skyrim
before maybe that's what they expect
what the what I
[Laughter]
yeah
[Music]
yellow dot yellow Dot
yeah it was done
Skyrim explains it better
stop moving it so fast
it moves I can't move it slower
specific angle for each lock find the
angle that's the puzzle
I need a tutorial
onion tutorial I need a tutorial for the
tutorial
ah what
oh
Santiago
I stole your heart yeah
[Music]
I didn't
but I don't understand how I did it
go to 111 by 7am and
what go to 111 by 7am and watch just
watch
it's Greenview 1117 and mark the tenant
Mark the 10th
Mark the tenant by what peeing on him or
what
what time is it now oh already too late
okay
can I practice it again because I don't
understand
uh 7 A.M
everything takes so much time so maybe
I am should be fine I hope wait yeah now
that I know how to read the mini-map
surely
I am on my way
to Greenview 111.
when it says more don't tell me
now it's Rush Hour
um
oh yeah I know I know I know it's over
here
nothing suspicious going on
I'm just a friendly neighbor in the
friendly neighborhood
where are the lesbians though
okay here what am I what am I looking at
should I stay in the car
let's go here
what does it mean to Mark the tenant
does that mean
I'm Mark a mouse button free
huh
oh I didn't
accept me y'all
wait for them to leave and get me that
oh okay
now do I just wait until he's gone
I tell no one is home still the
important box from 111.
okay
[Music]
there's a box in there a book are there
also some books and some book box
[Music]
um
this dude that's like worse than
a Sims algorithm
he's just like no no he's just not doing
anything
I can sleep in the car oh
this is so suspicious car just right
there
how come they're all not like at home at
night shouldn't they be sleeping at home
at night
I'll hide myself in a better spot
how do you sleep
sleep
have to sleep
I'm closing your eyes
[Music]
maybe in the trunk
can I sleep in that
you're crouching in a weird place what
do you mean
I don't know how to sleep can you just
leave please
oh hi
oh
use parking
all right let me read this when close
enough you can Mark a tenant to discover
his daily routines default middle Mouse
button you can also Mark cameras to show
their rearrange check tenant routines in
top Corner a top right corner blue means
they're out
oh
slipping or parking lot sleep in the car
at the parking lot to pass them aha
this is a parking lot to me
I don't know why it doesn't count
where is the parking lot
is this a parking lot
parking lot
this is the parking lot how convenient
I wait oh
there it will I sleep in the car I
didn't even
have to park properly okay how long
[Music]
um
8 P.M
okay exit
you're talking about
chat
Super Chat
now there's a different tenant God damn
it
uh wait there's a time where no one's
home but uh how do I like see what time
that is if now is like
half past 8 P.M
that that blue
uh time is when they're not there but
when is that
um nine eight nine A.M
[Applause]
sleep in the car
I am eight to nine
sleep until
oh
[Music]
yeah
oh wait what huh
I pressed space to sleep
there you go
right now
we will watch them leave hopefully
oh he's still there now
hi
walking out the window anything nice out
there any nice scenery oh yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah the the woman is not here
and soon
he will also leave I think
yawning guys
because I just woke up
from the car I just slept in the car
am I expected to oh
pick the lock this time because
there's
um like
iron gates in front of the window oh no
oh no
sleep another hour
what I want to I need a mirror I need to
see what I'm dressed as am I actually
dressed in like burglar clothes
because I see I have black gloves on
I can't be running around in the daytime
like this
what a idiot
[Music]
um
okay
I think he's gone oh no here we go
um
[Music]
uh
I was just playing with you guys
ah I was just trying to make you guys
rage
oh and maybe I shouldn't take this right
now
[Music]
she makes me Ranch you're ready to go on
a rampage
hahaha
[Music]
box of shady content I got it
Mani doko
where the money at oh I have still a
little bit of time
um what do we take I think
I think I guess we'll take the pot
and that I'll take the TV
let's go
should I hey when someone comes home
will they like notice when their lock is
picked should I like
re-lock it for them free service
um
he like what the is this
neighborhood
nope nobody cares nobody gives a
this is such an unsafe neighborhood
literally just walked by
shitty neighbors man
okay we got another TV
at the Lock
oh
I did steal it right because it still
wait it still gets me to
The Prompt though
on the top right
oh hello
pretty sure I did it
we went straight into my bag I think
oh boy here we go the Watsons oh what
you guys are like ah it's gonna take a
long time it just doesn't get it she
just doesn't get it what a shitty gamer
she is
Mama's house yeah eventually we'll be
stealing from Mama's house I guess
sorry Yama ahead of time I apologize
let's go to pawn shop
let's sell the TV
why b i I stole some extra things even
was there something I missed out on
oh wow it's not too bad welcome
okay we're selling it for 40 bucks no no
I think I shouldn't be selling the box
right do I need it send the Box via
Blackberry okay okay
all right we shall do that
thanks for the membership welcome
[Music]
yay
it's so far it's not so scary yet I saw
uh on on Corona's stream that she kept
on getting like
caught
or like she had to hide like so much
because people were coming
where is the frail
where's the frill
okay what am I doing
where am I
hear this one a hundred bucks
oh
let's see boys
one they got's fine go prove them wrong
would break a window and then hide a run
away
what if I also want to steal
okay
let's
sleep a little bit
um
who I am
that's the implication wait I forgot
what I said already
why why does it always show the car when
we sleep when actually we're sleeping on
the sofa
okay anyway okay let's go
Broken Glass fairy steal something first
then break a window on the layout oh
okay
uh green meal streamed once again
recently there has been a rise of
robberies in Greenview Street let's all
have a look out
I'll be helping too of course I am just
one of the nice neighbors I'll be
helping out I will let you guys know I
will be taking care of the night Patrol
how about that
I am so nice I'm offering myself and my
precious time to take care of the night
Patrol in this neighborhood
greetings to you too fellow neighbor
you're gonna get cleaned up for your
haircut but isn't the haircut gonna
clean you up
have fun
oh new house
where should I park
maybe here
you've got some nice pretty bushes
bushes
oh wait that's a you need to start the
car to exit yeah I stopped it
there's a
trunk here to hide
is someone home
because we probably
shouldn't enter a Wonder someone whole
but it looks
looks pretty empty looks like a nice
house wow I have by the way changed my
mind again
the third time
because I realized
oh God we don't have much time
I realized I calculated wrong my brother
like helped me realize
no no I don't want to really get a house
but but but I realized
oh oh it's that easy is it
and I can't hold it I need agility oh
no no
fro bricks
how do I get it
oh I need this one first
um
[Music]
no I got no more so
all right crowbar it is
really
[Music]
get it
oh my car's there do they care about my
car
should have gotten into my car I had to
run away it should be fine here oh
GTA GTA GTA
[Music]
you're not gonna
you're not gonna check the dumpster
right like why why would anything be in
the dumpster
wow this is no way that makes no sense
would quickly
make herself a hole in the ground and
yeah
hide in the Earth
never heard of that one have you
oh oh are they going is he already going
back into his car
oh
what
police absolutely useless that's how
fast you give up
no way
they're still a little bit around and we
should wait until they're completely
gone
the music was nice though
yes
how do I get
what
I guess they saw me
[Music]
but he's not
is he wait I say his wheel is like he's
having trouble
oh no oh no the other one well we'll
just have to hope that they won't use
communication
that the one who stuck tells the other
one who's not stuck hey the dudes just
he just jumped back into the dumpster go
get him
should I run
uh
-huh
today I'm fine they're looking over
there
on foot
and this one's oh
[Music]
no no can I can I hurt him can I
Bonk him
hey do I get busted immediately
[Music]
this is my first time I got caught
okay next time
I either hide longer or try to drive
away what's the best way of doing it
[Music]
why is there a photo spot here
Place camera
hide until they're gone okay
I'll I'll hide in the same spot though
because that had a good view
bail money for cute feet thank you thank
you
for bailing me out oh
does this person live here
car parked in Springfield yeah
did you notice that
should I move it there's someone there
looking at my car
hi sir the police no no it's okay
I'm gonna move don't worry don't worry
sorry about that so don't call the
police now please
no no no no more about it don't worry
about it please don't tow my car
what
switch please
oh no oh no you can't hold my car no
no
no why are they following me
no no
the senpai
[Music]
up that's messed up what on Earth
where do you care why do they care so
much now about where my car is located
ah can I be on the side of the street
is that okay
like I guess
um
I mean
the street
um
I parked on the sidewall yeah I mean why
not
these are all shitty places to park
I don't see a Park plot
I don't know if I can if I'm allowed to
park in houses like Flats
God damn it
what about what about here
you need to stop the car
seems fine for me
okay okay
thought
s what
what
holy
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
really quickly to get a head start but
okay okay now okay now we wait so yeah I
I apparently calculated uh it's
completely wrong
uh I don't know how
I don't know
but in theory I was talking about
brother I'm like yo I changed my mind
I'm just gonna rent for the rest of my
life because it's like way too expensive
I calculated it like so and so much
he's like hmm are you sure like
did you calculate like you know
12 months one year per like and then and
times whatever 50 16 so on I'm like yeah
that's exactly how I did it but then he
did it on his phone and it came out
completely differently and I'm like yeah
but like for real that's how I
calculated it or at least I wanted to
I was I was thinking that's how I
calculated it
I don't know what I did but then I
calculated it again and it was like yeah
okay you're right
for me it came out like
really not worth it eight times as much
or so
um
yeah and now I have realized it it may
actually be worth it
so I'm back in the market baby
um I should hire him as my accountant I
don't need to hire him he he would he
would do such things to help me onto his
own I'm sure
hmm
yeah math
well let's change my mind no no no no no
no no no no not this time
let's read while we're waiting
stealing stuff and returning home if
Luke gives you experience points the
first time theft will give
10 times more experience if you're not
sure what to do at first time theft in
one house
check your computer for hints and
additional jobs why are those
whoa
man
yeah bro Tony bro Tony thank you I've
been asking him for a lot of
um
advice
because I don't know he doesn't even
have experience in like buying house or
apartment but but at least he has like
logical thinking because he worked an
accountant kind of job before so I guess
um
it must come from that
Brothers know these things
surprisingly yeah I guess my mom
um
would would know too yeah
you know yourself roasting right what do
you mean
yeah and I decided like I mean I mean
you know I don't even have to live there
forever like I can just sell it or rent
it when I don't want to be there anymore
um
oh oh
because I said he thinks logically well
uh you can run away from police by
leaving the neighborhood or you can hide
in the closet a dumpster outside and
wait until police leave if the
visibility eye is red someone saw you
and the police will find you okay
I'm I'm still waiting for this one to
leave
the other one left no the other one's
there
is that one even moving
he's not moving
go somewhere what if he's stuck again
one star for that long yeah
and it seems like they really have a
neighborhood watch now
hmm
that one's gone yo they're gone they're
gone
good morning
[Music]
oh that thing over there is pretty what
a nice pool porch pork porch
porch pouch porch
and I guess we're not stealing anything
lame do I get a reward for
[Applause]
for uh
doing the thing I should get a reward
at least we had some
arresting
police action
hi Williams
I chose to not see anything oh
because I couldn't
they were inside and police was outside
like what
I think I already did
um
like I did this
open normal locks with a lock pick
and next is hard one but I want I wanted
the agility all right now I have a skill
point so now I should be able to
oh wait what if oh wait I learned it
before I got reset
right
okay there you go
oh oh oh oh we're gonna train again okay
okay okay standard training lock so
simple well wait wait wait simple
training lock no no I don't want this
exit exit exit
this one
eh block pick I need to buy one again
okay
standard one not the DIY one
ooh no more bobby pins
lock pick there we go aha
why I liked the Bobby bin
oh Bobby Bean was fine is this by the
way for like training or
nah
for the car
Giant
wait no it is lift
Oh I thought I could lift you know do
you even lift bro
okay that's for cars
okay okay
what the is that
uh
uh okay
s d a
oh
um
lock the pin now
do we start with this one
lock lock how do I ah with mask I did
though
oh cool this is easier than the bobby
pin one
ah
oh
is this how that works
interesting
[Music]
from Skyrim's world living this is it
with a crowbar
word on the street is the toilet in
Greenview 113 is not broke
what's up with you guys you just want me
to break things instead of stealing them
with kind of thief am I
lock pick is it lock pick to open
standard locks press the butt button at
the exact time when the pin is at the
bottom
stealing stuff and returning home with
loot gives you experience points I
already read this before
and Benny what the hell lame
who do you think I am buy hints for help
eh how expensive are they
uh where was it
break or steal oh
and at the Bakers
and where where are we breaking the
toilet
13 okay
it's up to you to also steal stuff while
you're at it okay
possible loot location tenant routines
for 100 bucks
[Music]
maybe a house security there's a spare
key for the front door in the bedroom
I don't know these hints don't seem
worth it
in my opinion
still before you break okay okay I'll
try
but
last time they were at home at night I
wonder if they'll be home now I don't
want to do it in daytime
I'll go at 1am
we'll see how that goes
on
too close to Emma's house
I'm supposed to mark them
well maybe we'll do that
uh okay
that's Emma's house
I'm gonna break your toilet
toilet
Miss houses
well then she surely wouldn't mind if I
just you know say hello
stop by for a little
a little tea and coffee session
surely she wasn't mine
is it really her house
no it's the powers what are you talking
about
I was getting excited
man
okay
are they in there hello
doesn't look like it so far
is there a bedroom where they could be
oh
no no no I wasn't
okay I was too careless I have to be
more careful
where should I enter from
oh there's an open window here
ah later you'll be able to climb vines
okay
watch out for Bubba
um
okay so they are inside
am I really supposed to
go rob
what
one thing after another guys where's the
door I forgot
maybe I can open this
uh
what am I doing
I really don't know what I'm doing
is it okay if I just run away really
quickly
as long as the
sound reset
oh there's someone oh it's at the bed
ah
tenant root discovered they are now
sleeping okay
oh oh that's why the window is open
oh no
oh that's so scary
so the window is open there though am I
supposed to enter for there while
they're sleeping
no way
is this
taking that itadakimasu
I have to no way
okay okay I'll try
not so much too it was so
why is she sleeping in a skirt and in
shoes
oh really
should I just wait for another time okay
okay
we took we took the headphones
for now
I don't want to have now
they seem away they're the lights on
there
oh
and no one in bed
and the light was on
oh
it's right there okay thank God
oh man
oh my God yeah I mean I didn't really
try you know it was just the scouting
scouting
I was just scouting oh good morning dog
they don't look like headphones that
would be worth 86 bucks in the pawn shop
okay
we will go there again
and for fantastic f for fave and we'll
go there again and we'll just you know
be um
scouting we're doing this professionally
I'ma stays up late yeah that is very
much like her I guess
weird sleep schedule just like me for
real for real
oh why is it that thing green
so sing me out
fine I want to see what they do during
the daytime it could be that they're
gone during the daytime
just
just scouting
maybe they go to work
in the morning
step
did she just go back to sleep
oh
interesting
did he like
you have to lock unlock this again
oh someone's coming though
no no no no no I'm not trash but no
no I don't know am I did she report me
no right no okay
was that really hiding me
what is it with this house why is it so
difficult
I need more skills
I need to learn how to
how to climb over things like this I
can't climb over that can I
and and window
I need lock picking level four to open
Windows like that um
TV yo they got some good stuff in there
should I sleep some more
maybe
I'll be visiting her neighbors
what's your business they're still
sleeping please leave them alone I am
their personal bodyguard hi
and talk to you
hi Amy
oh man you're looking a little bit
difficult different from YouTube why are
you standing in my car are you gonna
steal my car I'm gonna report you I'm
gonna call the police right now
okay
you're in a strange place you are in a
strange place
not me
um
yeah I don't know where to park like
what about here
here is good right maybe
I feel like I see a lot of people
parking like this in real life
okay but just like me casually walking
around like this doesn't seem to bother
anyone
it's hot hey hey
I'm gonna steal everybody's heart
oh God I'm not towering over her I'm so
tall
where are we going on lady
hi wow pretty
nice shorts
I got the same ones
so we go shopping in the same place huh
you you you come here often huh
maybe we could maybe we could go Jean's
shopping together next time yeah
no
why not
you got a problem with me do it not look
fashionable enough for you
discrimination
date simulation flood simulation
come on
do something wake up already
they're so critical of me
I'll I'll sleep a little bit in my car I
guess
spend some time under
no I want to sleep I have your sleep
again
I'm fine I have to
order
is it because I am parking lot again
what's the closest parking lot
[Music]
I'm blocking God there's one right
behind me
just just drive drive past me
don't stress me out
okay found one
[Applause]
sorry I'm like so stupid
there we go
gonna sleep until
1pm
for now
I'm so far away from from their home
Circle the house till night time
uh you mean like Scout their house till
night time
just want to see what they're doing
during the day
are they still sleeping
oh I'm such a good scout I just like
keep on jumping behind their fence
I think they're gone now
they didn't they didn't seem to be in
the bed also I already have like a
little bit of a Time window
up there I guess
they're not they're not here right now I
think
we shall commence the fee thing
eh hurt my tenant so there's someone in
there someone in there
let me Mark you
let me Mark you then
wait oh there she
but if I was there like a little bit
earlier there was a time when the word
they're not here right the blue time
window
would be when they're not here they just
came home
okay okay okay so now is uh 2 30
so
maybe if I go there at one o'clock
it's a pretty short time window though
damn
is there no no bigger time window
1 30.
okay let's let's uh
sleep until 12 P.M
long time sleeping
whole day
that'll be fast yeah so no time for like
stealing a lot of other things
what was my main quest to break the
toilet right okay
is there a good place to hide after I do
that
okay she's leaving right now
she's leaving right now
no they're both out
what about my proper one do I have to
buy another one
have I used the other one
no
I have to hide somewhere I have to hide
somewhere
um
no now my car was so far away I think
it's better here but
um okay maybe nowadays they all have
window alarms okay I will stop
I'll stop with that but I gotta I didn't
think I had to buy more uh locks lock
picks pick locks
I thought I could reuse the same one
again and again
[Music]
if only I would have had a first try
like last time
okay
uh I still have one star no there we go
ahai can I Mark you
for future purpose
big ass Garden you got there ladies
impressive
okay this one also
right by 10. I'm not doing anything I'm
just marking people now
leave me alone just want to Mark in in
peace
bye
because conspicious what what's their
conspicuous nothing conspicuous here
and I once again I once again missed the
time window no no no no not I didn't
just miss it I spent the whole time
window
running from people
okay
we gotta sleep another 24 hours guys and
actually I guess I should go buy uh lock
picks right
Lauren left at this position it looks
like she is eating Chad eh am I am I
looking weird
I fixed it
okay I'll go I know it was
very disappointing but I'll go
I'll go once
ow
and bye
uh
lock picks I guess
next time just reload
no no that's too easy
that would make it too easy
for 40 minutes and counting to break one
toil amazing
it's quite difficult
this one
they're always home
and they sleep at home how dare they
um I'll buy
a
proper one and a simple one and another
simple one and another proper one to
have money yeah
damn because I guess that this this
stuff I'll be needing a lot
so it's okay to get a couple right
okay okay
let's go again practice ah why I keep on
first trying it I'm fine
I'm fine
what time is it now oh p.m for
I don't know what they're doing around 4
P.M but
I guess we'll find out
I'm gonna Park
here
maybe also sleep what did I say
1pm
no 12 p.m and then we see them walking
out probably
yeah but the the simple lock picks are
they just won't try they only come with
one bobby pin or what what
[Music]
what
oh the tails are out now too
nothing suspicious here I'm just very
very uh scaredy catty
just how it is okay they're
they're leaving now right we're out now
um okay
I know how to do it
yeah and let's enter
here
wonderful wonderful we don't have much
time but I want to look a little bit if
I find something there we go let's just
take money
mostly
they look fancy how much times oh God oh
God come on I'm running out of time
um uh where is it oh God no wait
they said um what was it what was it uh
uh there's a spare key in front of the
door the bedroom what front door
oh God I don't know what uh I don't know
I remember I don't remember how to do
this uh
it is okay it's behind me
foreign
what am I looking for
the the toilet right oh God
are you coming back
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
I'm really out of sight I'm out of sight
I'm out of mind I'm running faster than
Sonic
[Music]
look at a tiny ass trash can maybe
can I handle the Bulls herself
oh there there's one there's one oh
thank God thank God Oh I thought it was
over because I was
I was like oh I could just walk out huh
could I just walk out of the map even
without my car
hahaha
like a headless chicken
oh my God whoa the frill the adrenaline
is crazy
oh
Mama Mia I broke the toilet and I think
I heard her scream so she was she came
home right when I did it I think
oh my God yeah right like she was
watching me I I had a feeling that
um she was like
you know I felt it I felt that she was
like behind me or so well I was like
I gotta do it now like I can't I
can't just like leave it at that
where's my car
what the hell I I if I leave my car here
and just leave the map what happens
I need to find my car oh there it is
oh man I feel kind of bad but I also
feel very very excited
this might be my new hobby
I should definitely play this game a
couple more times after this
let's go
go baby
my song
new career out the whole life
I feel like you know I already panicked
so much inside the game I feel like in
real life it would be much much worse
oh
so many things
whatever not like I care about your
opinion
you'll learn how to climb a lattice Like
a Man Spider you know oh okay a lattice
a ladder what is a lattice oh those
don't sell well but okay
at least I was able to pick them up
quickly
and I got some money
D4 don't get caught D for DB yeah in
German Thief is uh deep
mm-hmm
that's right
deeper dumpster diving Divine dumpster
diving
okay he wants me to learn the climbing
oh
we're where was that
or do I just learn that without a skill
because I have one skill point I think
I'll put it into
Vines
he doesn't say Vines but okay
then I can't learn that yet well he
keeps on asking me to do things that I'm
not ready for yet
okay I'll just I'll just go and steal
some more things maybe maybe we can take
the one Quest
what was it oh yeah here
break or still the painting break or
steal the kiss painting the oh many
paintings okay the Watsons
this one looks easier so let's first do
this one the bakers will be back at the
Bakers they're haunted they're
absolutely haunted
okay
we're gonna go ah I wonder don't time
wise
[Applause]
[Music]
um
I don't remember when they're home and
when they're gone
can you just ask am I why still
I think
she would like find it funny and
entertaining
if I
you know you know it's like teasing it's
a fun little
um cheese
you know I steal something from her next
thing she'll steal something from me I
went on the tent right here
well still each other's things
it'll be a giving and taking and back
and forth thing
where is a good parking place Park two
or four didn't I
but they won't like it
they're so picky about it
don't get it
and just stop here please
don't be so picky
okay
is there someone here I can like
tag no
okay I don't know if they're home but
break or steal the painting okay
complain if you block the road okay
hello
I don't think they're home are they ever
home at all
oh wait that's uh 11 right
oh you marked him
did I
did it work I think it worked
Oh I thought she was on the toilet
okay I don't care about you guys
care about the this one how do I get in
you have to go for the front
so
it seems like it
really
oh it's open
excuse me
anybody home
they don't have an alarm right we
brought this before
do they maybe maybe they installed it
now
they don't have an alarm okay I see like
these weak looking Windows they don't
have alarms okay
oh uh break or steal it um if I if I
steal it I don't have to give it to them
right right
sure
and I can just uh
there's no one home here what is the
challenge here
[Applause]
uh I have to go for the front door oh
where's the front door
is this the front door
because otherwise I can't carry the
painting out
oh yeah
it's already night time
there is a patrol there but no he just
he just left oh drop it
time
all right
all right myself and looking yeah yeah
now I get it I understand the lock
picking now but I feel like their
explanation was bad like they should
have kind of
there's someone in that car
yeah it's because they're blocked by me
sorry
ah hell I need my painting
though
[Applause]
sorry sorry just just drive by
just try
okay okay
where's the painting
I wonder if she could have busted me I
wonder
bringing the painting with me though is
the more difficult than breaking it I
think so I had chose the more difficult
way of doing it
all right
yeah I just dropped it and burned
because I didn't want to see and to have
her see me putting the painting into my
trunk
that would be dangerous possibly
um
all right so I can probably sell the
painting in the pawn shop right can I
are they happy that I did yes yes
okay writing isn't even so bad either
there wasn't really much to steal
I did it it's complete now right I got
extra money for it too so now I can I
can sell it that will be good money I
think extra money
[Applause]
the best theme
welcome you guys can hire me too if you
want me to feed someone
40 bucks okay
noise
no it's bombastic
by the way guys uh next week
not much streaming going on probably
I'm not sure if I can stream on Monday
if I if I will then it will be very
short during the day
uh in the evening I got something to do
with my bro and my mom
yeah and then weekend I'll be gone so
basically
only a couple days short not much
streaming going on but it's it's a
little bit I'll be fine
yo
you do you Kiara
um how many do I know how many I have
now that I am so good at the DIY one I
feel like the DIY one takes less time to
pick than
the lock pick
maybe it's a skill issue
okay let's um
we need more exp I guess let's try this
one
this one's probably more difficult they
surely have an alarm
um
The Watsons do I have any info about the
Watsons actually
house security tips possible loot
location 10 14. these are not so
expensive I'll buy the 10 inch routines
there's no one home between 1am and 4 AM
where do they go do they party what do
they do at one to four A.M
hope you enjoy the family time thank you
yeah now my brother
and lives like
way closer to me than ever before
forever
so yeah
40 bucks to steal my heart
you already have it
yeah I I
I'm giving my slow cooker to my brother
by the way I was like let's see if I
have something useful for you
and uh
I realized I I bought the slow cooker
which also functions as a rice cooker a
million years ago but uh it I just I
never used it ever before
I don't know why I bought it probably
because I just wanted like a couple of
kitchen appliances that match with my
others because I buy them all most of
them I buy them from the same brand
and they look so pretty and they're so
cute
so my slow cooker matches with my juicer
and with my toaster and with my water
cooker
uh maybe I have one more thing my pizza
maker is from the same brand but I don't
have they didn't have it in the same
color so that's kind of sad
uh oh
a little bit
we don't have to sleep
but I'm blocking traffic if I'm like
this let's not do that
[Applause]
yeah yeah he seemed interested he said
he has a bunch of slow cooker recipes
that he wants to
use to make so
I think
he will make better use of it also he
doesn't have a rice cooker either see if
I didn't have a rice cooker maybe I
would use it more often
but I do
I do have a rice cooker
so I'm waiting for you guys to leave
thank you
are we entering from here maybe
have I been on the Watson house before
no right
I tried to break the window right
okay she should
leave soon
oh wait it's still an hour
still an hour
never been in a home without a rice
cooker
yeah in Japan like when you
um
get like a like a monthly weekly or
yearly like partially furnished
apartment they or like pretty much
furnished they always come with a rice
cooker it's like standard but here it's
not
oh she be leaving
Watson Amelia if it isn't you goodbye
where are you going at this late hour
young lady huh
for real maybe she's thiefing herself
probably has something to do
all right here we go
oh careful
what the
what's that what's that
I'm not doing I'm not doing anything at
all
what if I go home now like what happens
how do I get back
you don't even see the map when
you're doing that
oh please
yeah I'm just fixing the lock I'm not
breaking it I'm fixing it
Cairo teleport back okay cut damn it
zyna why are you so annoying
this this lock was acting up a little
bit maybe um
I'll buy another normal uh DIY one but
because I want to trust in them
they're kind of sassy
stop noticing me
um
actually I would like to sleep I guess
because I I want to start from
to have plenty of time
I'd sleep until 12.
if you keep the mouse further away yeah
I noticed I had it like in the middle so
it's like wobbly
wobble wobble wobble wobble
yeah
sign up for my brother
because this is the first time
he's my older brother but this is the
first time he has like his own apartment
that he's not sharing
can you believe it
was crazy
I've had like a million apartments by
now
but my brother has been sharing more or
like living with my mom mostly
this is his first one and it makes me
feel like it like it reminds me of the
first time I had my first own solo
apartment it had like the cheapest of
the cheap creme de La Creme Ikea cheap
as Furniture some now Ikea was actually
a luxury for me I was more like
um
I was most of my furniture for my first
apartment
came from
um like a second hand big second hand
place
is this okay
um
everyone leaves the nest in different
times I suppose yeah don't bag Ikea some
of it is yeah that's only totally I like
Ikea furniture I mean even now some of
my furniture is from Ikea yeah
like my closet
and I think my my my entrance
hall closet thingy not really closet
it's an open thingy
yeah but I was so happy to have like you
know my own dining table with my own
dining chairs even though they're like
so cheap but I at least got myself like
some cute uh Pink Ikea cushions for my
dining chairs to like you know make them
a little bit cuter
okay let's not do this now I guess he
was the one who you're the one you're
probably the one who paid who baited
bailed
who told people and then there's another
one coming uh
please don't come this direction
no he's coming
hey boss hi Sandy Sean how you doing
walk faster
I don't have time
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
having your own place you can like
design how you want things to be on your
own
I had like the cutest
curtains that I brought from Japan
because I guess my first very own
apartment was actually
um
in in Japan should I keep it open
will they know this
in Japan
um
I think
I had my own apartment in Japan before I
had it in in Austria
there you go
so what was the thing here I have to
stay on another painting right
how much time do we have
I think we have enough time
what's that
a hiding spot oh imagine hiding there a
whole day
until they leave again
this is looking for valuables golden
goblets
the
a nice face I'll take one
uh how do I turn on the there we go
foreign okay now now I'm starting to run
out of time I think
okay I think the golden goblin and all
that was like cool enough
maybe this one too what am I doing what
am I doing where's that where's the
painting
painting where even is the painting
where's the paint
oh
yeah
the TV
break it break or steal wait it's okay
um
okay
actually I have a bit more time but uh
it's okay there's one coming back a
little bit earlier
now it's now safe now it's safe oh
I did it
quick
okay
let's go let's go whoa
[Applause]
[Music]
oh God
um
what if I leave my car somewhere
oh no this is GTA now this is pure GTA
come on kiwawa there there there's a
there's a good Escape
we're like
um
Loki GTA
[Applause]
ah the Perfect Crime let's go
ah the TV though the TV looks so good
but there's no way I could like since
she came back when I was about to leave
if I would have tried to steal two big
things I have to carry there's no way no
way that would have failed miserably
we got the painting we got a decent
rating and I think we're going some
some good items
all right I'll sell them now
[Music]
[Applause]
see for clean steel my Sudan right I was
gonna block picking too
oh 70 bucks sell 46 but wait can you
actually keep the camera because I saw
you can take pictures and stuff but do I
need it don't sell yet eh
why
didn't I already got the like reward
foot
oh online ah the I think the Golden
Goblet was wanted don't
so I can keep the the goblet
oh okay okay okay
I'll keep that in mind
the golden gobble though yeah
maybe the camera too who knows
all right I'll be right back I'll be
right back don't worry you'll get some
good stuff from me
nahone
okay
how much would they have given me
uh
maybe they didn't have anything
oh wait they do also pay more for this
kind of stuff what
oh
wait I don't have the painting in there
I can sell the Goblet yeah yeah but the
glass cups they would have taken the
glass cups for eight bucks not instead
of two bucks
what about the camera they don't want
the camera
[Music]
okay but remember pot saucepan teapot
all toaster all those things they will
take for good price
but that's it
does this change sometimes
black and white base the glass cups
flower vase
tall vase and The Tear trophy okay
um
but then I don't feel bad about the
painting because they wouldn't have
taken it actually
I think things got added when you
cleared them oh okay
[Applause]
well I'll go to the pawn shop downstairs
uh still sell this stuff
welcome
I guess
do you think they'll want it I mean
these are these are decent prices I'll
just feel more things
alrighty
[Music]
okay might be tough to steal from the
pawn shop
[Music]
all right all right all right let me go
back and see if they have a new quest
for me
no pawn shop guy probably doesn't think
about it too hard because
no cannot ask questions cannot think
about it needs need the things oh
one of these
in different house I think
okay okay okay
have I had a level up yet by the way
I do I did I did oh okay let's go I can
climb the Vines Now
I guess I'll take that
all right how do I take it
what
oh wait I need to be level six
and level five
what only having a skill point is not
good enough
I could take the
no I can't take that one either oh okay
I really need another level
okay
I thought I was being stupid all right I
should buy some more lock picks
let's buy
I'm using the cheap stuff still
because I can because I don't have a
skill issue
hey
one of my mission should probably do it
all right all right all right and
I don't know if they'll be home right
now because it's morning time but I
guess I'll just check and then
and then no where are we going
howls were they like
and well they were somewhere around
there right
Scotland just scouting
um
[Music]
the powers 14 this one
is it 14 again
no I just recently steal something from
them
oh did I already know uh soon
they will be
gone
I mean not really soon but I wonder if I
can fill up the in-between are they just
at home in between
like what are they doing now are they
home now
can I just like ring their doorbell and
check
Moshi Moshi
are you guys home
maybe in the garden
well
they might not be home now
I have the keys to just go in front of
wait I can still do that I don't like
lose them afterwards
and I really don't they don't maybe
they're not around but I wonder for how
long
hi
I'm scared will I take it away from me
huh
I think I think they're there does that
sign mean they're here
what am I here for anyway
[Applause]
you don't know
what the is that a Nook oh Nokia
oh God this is so scary I don't want to
be here while they're here
oh God
foreign
okay
they turned on music
I want to get out of here I'll I'll
wait here until it's until they're
actually gone because this is freaking
me out
we need to break we're still the pear
decoration okay
the pears the pears keep an eye out for
the pair
um
I walked in around around here like I
owned the place
sure
I'm just gonna wait yeah that's the time
and we should talk more about
um I think it was a nice topic first
ever apartment yeah let me let me think
I think it's really I I was living with
my family
and then
I think my first appointment was like
when I was like 16 or something
in Japan
what
oh but can I still hide in here are they
gonna open up this they just discovered
that the Nook is missing right
but they don't know that I'm in here I
could already be miles away
that's pretty incredible right I know
what wait well I'm just gonna
I'm just gonna wait here um we're just
having a casual uh info
conversation uh I'm gonna stick to this
oh God
no don't please okay
please don't open the
shut up please don't open please don't
open
oh and then and then and then oh yeah I
think so I think my first like living
alone situation was I think
um in in like
um
like a dorm which it was kind of an
apartment a one-room apartment more or
less and yes
uh but I had like a little tiny
a kitchen and the the item that I was
the most proud of that I had like
Furniture item was a kotatsu because
that was my first time you know living
in Japan for or living somewhere on my
own and living in Japan so I was like um
I really want to quote that too
I was like really really really into the
idea of having a kotatsu you know it's
those heating tables on the ground and
because I didn't have like uh like a
dining table or so because it was like
really small room
I decided I'll get myself a cool tattoo
but honestly there was like not much
space the whole Space was then taking up
taken up by the bed the kotatsu and the
desk
for my laptop or so
but I was so happy with it and I had
like a pink blanket for it
um
I was so happy and then I just chilled
in the kotatsu forever why am I hearing
someone talk to themselves in the closet
I'm on the phone okay on them on my new
Nook
um painted closet okay
uh yeah yeah yeah unfortunately
uh when I had to
move
I think because I was in Osaka at the
time
and then I think eventually I had to
move to Tokyo I probably left it behind
or or I moved back to Austria I'm not
sure anymore
but I had to leave it behind
oh so sad
so sad so sad but that I guess it wasn't
really quite my own apartment yet
because I didn't have
most of the furniture was already there
um
eventually
I had
not yeah more or less my own place in
Tokyo
but not quite not only I was like
low-key sharing even though most of the
time I was there alone
and I had I had the cutest bed sheets oh
they're gone the cutest bed sheets the
cutest they're gone right yeah
cutest curtain Tunes like I had to buy
everything in pink with flower patterns
and frilly frills
and lace and everything I was so happy
with it
you know the best thing is when you live
in Japan
oh this would bring good money but I
have to carry the vase but the carry the
vase doesn't fit oh
doesn't fit in my normal
oh
what do you mean
what's with the store
what do you mean sorry I'll run
away
come on because I'm
don't even rate me I'm not done I'm not
done
but I did get some vases
yeah the best thing about living in
Japan is that Daiso exists I mean it
also exists outside of Japan but it
doesn't exist in Austria I wish it did
but like there's so many cool things
let me sell this
why why can I not sell it
um
do I need another one
I need two didn't I take two
I feel like I picked up too
okay let me put it in my storage right
now
oh babe I feel it got picked up too and
the milk
I'll keep that one for now
oh okay okay
um
because dinosaur has like everything
everything like it has stuff for your
washing machine you know and the hang up
thingies like hangers that doesn't mean
hangers I mean the the things to like
hang it up to let it dry and and and and
they have the bags to put your like
smaller stuff into into the washing
machine and they have dishes and they
have so many cute dishes actually like
really cute looking ones cute designs
and all that mm-hmm
[Applause]
uh yeah yeah I got like so many things
they got like doormats they got towels
you know you know like uh like a you
know it's just 100 yen shop but some
things are a bit more expensive
they're they cost like maybe 200 yen or
so
if they're like a bit more fancy I loved
going shopping and die so even today oh
sorry
sorry sorry even today I still whenever
I see a Daiso I'm always very tempted to
go in
and get something for me
the stickers are so cute you know the
stickers I use for like my studying
notes
where's the parking spot the closest one
over there
and we have to sleep like uh
24 hours maybe one one pm
yeah those are most of them are like
usually from Daiso they have the pewter
stickers ever
okay you cannot complain about this oh
wait down
um
that was in America too yeah yeah yeah I
went to a Daiso in America I was like yo
you guys have died so what life is not
Fair
[Music]
I want one in a like
somewhat close
range as well please we don't have
Baskin Robbins we don't have Daiso a lot
of life is just not worth living in
Austria man
so not fair okay they're leaving now
I guess now that the car is safe over
there remember Kiana you gotta leave
kind of through the back
okay but now we'll enter through the
front again
and we'll leave for the back
excuse me
um
okay uh
what am I doing the paradigris what
about this painting though
my ears is gone I see this is what do
you mean let me pick that one up oh
baptism
oh wait uh what am I
hair decoration I wonder where it is
Wi-Fi router
is it in there in the locked door
probably okay
um
yeah what do you mean
what's it
no what's it this time I I hate
this menu so much
now please stop
no problem this time
I don't understand
I keep on taking like one thing and
running away on the foot
what what was the problem
is it did they see me for the window
part no the parking was fine I
was never a problem the parking meets us
straight across the parking lot that was
never a problem
remember to crouch hmm gotta be more
sneaky maybe did I not close the door
behind me was that the problem Maybe
we can sell this now
nice do we need a Wi-Fi yeah
yeah
they don't need a milk yet though radio
microwave
there is only one dinosaur in Canada one
in all of Canada oh it's probably like
in the capital right neighbors saw me
for the window
damn I need a bed of Disguise I need to
camouflage myself better
or just
ah man
okay
that's rough those snitches
you're gonna get stitches and I'm gonna
get the
oops I didn't want to go there
got nothing to sell
I think
[Applause]
okay here we go again guys
here we go again
um
I should put this in my GTA playlist
I mean there have been more unfitting
things in my playlists before than that
this actually feels like GTA light
doesn't it
I should
oh man I really missed it yeah I wonder
I shouldn't get perms for a different
GTA but like I haven't been requesting
anything for months now
because I told you right that there's
this new way of doing things that I just
I just don't
I I I I I more or less haven't figured
out it's just like I don't know I'm too
lazy to really figure it out
wait I need to sleep again don't I
yeah what did I
1 pm today no 12 12 p.m I think is a
good time
Hitman 3 will also give you the same
thrill not really
yeah I should play today online
I should
um
I'll get to it but like for now I think
you know I still have a couple of games
you know in my
back up
that I in my list basically
so
once I got really really desperate and
I'm like I don't have any games to play
then then we can consider
did they leave I think they left
okay I may have forgotten to close it
last time now I'm going straight to this
one oh yeah there can I close the
curtains
oh no oh
they're coming
oh wait there's money there
can they really see me for the window
because I guess there's a window oh okay
of course I'm trespassing you don't have
to tell me that as long as they don't
see me
um okay
okay is it not open yet what at least
oh
keep on looking at the map too
they're coming back home soon
I'm just gonna break it this time
I don't care
and I guess I'll leave because I'm
scared as I just wanna I wanna take
one more thing
alarm clock okay
can I there we go
yeah I'm not happy with that
but oh God
is it running while I'm doing this
I ah
I don't have time to uh I have time
for that
another already there
I'm just gonna waste a lot of fun
[Laughter]
[Music]
no
I was working so hard on the log pink
so
I got my my lock picks back right
where's the house again
oh damn it
I got him back though right because I
restarted from the checkpoints
not even the stairs are on my side
okay
I have a skill point for agility
really
but I'm still level six
oh it's already it's already open what
oh
nice
take it
I'm tired
okay I'm leaving
no I have so much time now
I have so much time now I can't take
anything more big blood
I just saw that thing jump
[Music]
I'll take the painting
I just have to
be careful
I think
I think I can make it
[Music]
I I got this um from a shop uh
no
oh God if they come home and they see it
missing they'll automatically probably
right away activate the alarm thing I
read my car is right there I'll be fine
I'll be fine I'll be fine I'll be fine
it's either
inside this paint I actually painted it
myself in in the Art Bar thingy with
Cali actually I still need her to send
that to me I need to remind her because
like I left it at her place
um so that she would send it to me
via post
I'm still waiting for it
I'm really proud of that one it makes me
want to um five dollars
makes me wanna do more
with acrylic painting maybe that should
yeah but now I don't have
I was thinking maybe that should be our
member stream but now I don't have the
supplies for it um and and tomorrow is
Sunday so
I mean I have some acrylic colors but I
don't have like a
a proper
um you know thingy
did I take the Oh Yeah I broke the vase
because I thought I'd have no time but
then level up
oh I did let's go
all right let me see what I have here uh
I don't know
should I keep the milk wait my thing is
so full I'm gonna check the online pawn
shop
level six yeah finger painting stream
nah I'd have to do that with gloves too
I think
um
anything
they have vases but not the one
the painting they don't even want the
painting
microwave radio
[Music]
I brought that one with me it even fit
into my bag I didn't have to carry out
like the painting
oh
shake things up over here uh should I
keep the
fancy vases for now in my storage
until maybe they show up in the
maybe until I'm short on cash or until
they show up on them
in that menu
um
people don't want some random artists
but it's not a random artist it's a me
of course I made it
they didn't want the alarm clock either
but waiting for everything until it's in
the internet is that really worth it
um
it's like holding off for good sales but
reverse
should I I would just pawn it
okay the bread-based saddle pons the
milk I have hopes for the milk
and the alarm clock I saw the alarm
clock
I don't think that would be worth that
much anymore
[Music]
yeah
if you made it why was it in someone
else's house because they still they
stung from me oh how the tables turn you
didn't expect that one right they stole
it from me
20 bucks now I'm keeping the painting
that's for sure
selling this
alrighty I'm keeping the painting thank
you
for now
but will they ever want it
will they ever want it
[Applause]
told me to wait you know but now now I
want to wait for everything endlessly
maybe I'll just be waiting endlessly
oh yeah I was rescuing my painting yeah
they don't appreciate it enough why
can't I not put the painting into my
storage
what
will it stay in my bag then or is it in
my eyes just in my car oh it's in my car
can you put several things
ah
can you stack things
I just for now like oh well I can put it
on the wall okay wonderful Ah that's
that's good I'll keep it there until
it's really like
worth something
um
my painting
is that like an actual
like real painting from a real like
artist out there somewhere in the back
in the day
definitely mine
nice
yeah it is yeah because it looks like
something someone would have thrown
before
foreign
It's gotta be Leonardo DiCaprio
wait isn't that an act
[Laughter]
s like it could be an artist like
Michelangelo
Leonardo da Vinci
it looks it sounds like a like an artist
name It just fits in perfectly
the binky funny
I don't know how many I have but I'll
buy
I'll buy I really like this one more
it's faster for me
ooh break a window that's it break their
sink break or steal their TV
breaking a window and just running away
for 200 bucks is like easy bucks
the Jones
wait it looks like we're going to more
um expensive houses now too
so maybe the police is like right at
their doorstep
[Music]
okay I'll I'll try I'll try to see
what's up with that
thank you
yeah I guess yeah I could have just
thrown a break too but I don't
can I throw a break and that way I can
right oh yeah right that's the thing now
oh and wait I have two skill points I
have two scale points
um
I can learn this
disassemble jewelry with special tools
I can
I can learn ah okay now I need the
backpack space because I did actually
run out of it and I guess I learned this
too
okay
never felt like appraising something but
it a pretty so would it show me what the
pawn shop would buy it for
so I can think about if it's worth
taking it with me
is that all this
the story though
does the story move on oh yeah agility
[Laughter]
I'm going to 103 or something am I
okay I mean the story
little difference we're just having fun
which house am I going to
the house is this
hey Dave is 105.
okay actually I'll park here and I'll
just um
I'll just
inspect everything
let's see if we can get some Intel
oh but these houses are harder to look
for are they
so
maybe I can't get my own Intel that
easily
anybody home that I can mark
maybe not wrong house anyway this is the
Millers this is the Davis this is the
Jones
break a window this is the one
how can it be so difficult my car is
right there too
and I could even hide in the dumpster
oh but is there any breaks lying around
where's the cameras there is that for
Gathering Intel like when they go out
and when they come back
rocks
should I just smack it but I can't get
directly to it there's a fence around I
guess I'll have to walk peek
uh can I switch to the cheap one
oh
hi ah
oh they're different locks hmm okay
well
does that count as a window
okay so they're home
they even have their their window open
suspicious at all
sneaking is suspicious I don't want to
be suspicious I'm just thinking right
now I'm just thinking about what to do
I guess
I guess I'll try to open this one
aha
I clicked
no no no please don't misunderstand I'm
I'm a gardener I'm working in their
Garden
I would tend to their flowers and their
grass yes yes yes yes
this looks like something you can later
on climb with skill points if you have
them
see crouching is apparently illegal guys
there we go
master lock picker
nice to meet you guys
come on
there we go
I kind of just wanna
when I turned on music I just wanna I
if I crouch here
if I just Crouch here
would you come out and check if
somebody's there
I think we're good
if I do this
shoot first
in my house I'm
gonna
I want to mark them
before I do this maybe they're going
discover different she's looking out the
window
anyway that's is that a different house
what that's a
h
that was a different house
he's at the window
Mark him without him seeing me
uh she's already sleeping oh
okay I got him I got them they are here
well while I'm here let me like
she moves away I want to walk over there
and see if I can find
um the third house someone there
just to also mark them as well while I'm
here you know
why do they keep their window open
or not I can't mark it up
I like him
oh he's on the second floor
I'm not entering this one though don't
worry
okay the middle is the melons will have
my Mercy for now
is that like is she trying to do bird
watching or something I am indeed a bird
I do not want to be watched though
okay now is maybe the time and then
run away
um my car where's my car
there
is there is there a good hide there's a
there's a dumpster there
why do you froze so aggressively let me
oh there's a person there
I want to open it
so I don't panic but
she wakey wakey she wakey wakey now
should have done them
should have done it when I had the
chance oh God ah
ah
[Music]
but like if I throw it in there now
throw it in his face maybe he dies
that would be good that's I suppose
now I can't walk by now you'll see me no
no no no no
no no
no no run
[Laughter]
oh my jaw oh oh man
please do not close the backyard door
afterwards oh
without
there's a dude standing right there oh
zooming
because it's still Smash It wait but
Adam I mean
that means difficult situation I threw
it and I absolutely missed and then he
saw me hmm
and you know you know how I act when I'm
in panic mode
do we really expect me to do
some good thinking there no
um
must have been the wind I am just a
dumpster okay okay
um let's try it again
they should just go to sleep it's 1am at
least the door is still open
oh
you're not on this floor anymore
it so seems
speak
throw the brick
huh
it's not breaking like what kind of like
how many layers of window are there
foreign
[Music]
they got like bulletproof glass maybe I
had oh I have to use my crowbar huh okay
fine detect detect it why does it still
said
what
why does it still say detected I'm not
detected
no no no
laughs
[Music]
oh
God why is this so difficult
I wonder how far he is
okay
[Music]
okay okay
[Applause]
oh man
oh man okay
[Music]
the police will never learn they will
never learn to dumpster dive just like
me
they don't have the
knowledge they're lacking critical
information guys
[Music]
monkey
did you just call me monkey
how many times have you been nearly
caught now well this is just how a thief
lives
we live for the frail this is on purpose
I want to be almost caught as long as I
don't get caught
monkey wow my throat hurts man oh what
stop driving so recklessly he just drove
through the field what's the matter with
him
we're done
yay
okay I'm not I'm not done though
I'm not done
let's see what else there is we can do
while this door is open for us
then the window's still broken
so I figure we we could break in they're
sleeping
shall we risk it we already got the
money for breaking the window so what do
I have to lose nothing
right
the light is on though
um expect Panic guys
there will be panic
footsteps
foreign
[Applause]
bulky and big
it's a closet here
hurt
can I hide
[Music]
okay okay
it's freaking me out
she went down didn't she
oh man what am I doing
what am I doing
and why am I doing it
frill
[Applause]
Clark
box
oh that's gonna be worth good money
just gotta run now she's gonna leave now
I steal a car eventually okay
let's just leave I have I'm satisfied
let's just leave
I don't see them
I think she's still downstairs
on the second floor where's the car in
the second floor
[Applause]
oh
whoa
wow
I'm ready
oh my God that was incredible wow
I'm so happy with that
the game saves if you enter what if you
enter
your car so you could steal more stuff
oh really
um
but I think I have to leave it here
because I have to prepare for whole
talks and things
and I also have to go to an idol meeting
actually
and I want this to be shorter anyway
that was really good though why am I not
there you go we'll just go home
and then call it a day and we'll play
this again again let's play like next
week I wanna play it again it was so fun
yeah on the C4 I want the frame for
don't you dare raid me don't you dare
that was incredible what I did okay I
got a bass guitar hey no one expected me
to steal that y'all sick ass face guitar
can I sell it does somebody want it
in the black Bay
maybe Electronics
no
they don't expect me to have something
like this yet probably
well why would I have it okay they don't
they don't want it yet so I will keep it
I could use a new base
I'll learn it I learned how to play it
a story for now okay guys
sorry I gotta go to an I don't meaning
like right now so uh I'll see you guys
tomorrow for Hall of talk and then a
member stream in the evening okay I'll
think about what to do I I did only a
hand cam stream okay yeah sorry no super
tight reading I will prepare some more
for hollow talk I'm so excited for
tomorrow please all be there for her
attack with corny Senpai
thank you so much for the accents blue I
love them so much I want to do more free
things thank you for watching and in
German we say I'll be
off yeah be careful guys lock your doors
and everything and get like bulletproof
windows otherwise kiwava might come for
you tonight
Pro Feet No One Is Safe anymore no
matter where you live I'm coming for you
and your home I know where your house
lives
[Music]
thank you