[Music]
hello
the [\h__\h] is this rat doing in my kitchen
i could cut hello oh no
okay goodbye
guys good stream it was it was nice
meeting you goodbye i told you to come
into my kitchen i told you babe
it i was just hoping i just would i'm in
desperate need of a job pencil
jack you didn't come for food you came
for a job uh i mean you get the job you
get the food right
right
that is actually true yes yes yes
[Laughter]
everyone that who works at kfb gets a
free supply endless supply of foof
indeed
what's your favorite kind of burger
burgoy
i like
um
cheeseburger
cheese
of course of course of course of course
cheese is that is a is that a cheese
patty with cheese on it um yes cheese
patty with cheese double cheese
sandwiched in cheese
that sounds
like i'm not the biggest fan of cheese
what's your favorite cheese
[Music]
oh i i just yesterday i made uh i made
pasta with carbonara
and when i when i bought ingredients
um i was too lazy to find the red cheese
so i picked up just what i what was in
front of me i picked up mozzarella
cheese
you're not supposed to make carbonara
with mozzarella no
once you put it in there it immediately
like like it turns into
a hot mess of cheese it's
not a good idea but it was yummy anyway
you would probably eat it
i would totally eat it yes your
teeth
fascinate me
did you see like uh during your debut i
was like putting your mouth on other
people was that okay for you i didn't
like
i was kind of scared i'm not going to
lie the pig
the bluest images kind of scared me but
it was funny
thank you for blessing me they actually
don't even look that bad on some people
i mean there was some you know everyone
is meant to have bottom teeth i guess
but just the the unsafe the ungodly
images of bottom teeth you know
who did you put them on again
um i put them on like cali and myself
and uh i think oh did i put them on
gouda as well yeah you didn't like
people
i distinctly remember senpai yes yeah
yeah i think that's the one i i put on
on twitter i think and i put some other
cursed ones on discord only to
to
amuse ourselves sorry i i i just found
it really really fascinating and i kind
of like when i look at you i kind of
sometimes i wish that my teeth were a
bit more visible ah
it's beautiful
you can see like inside look it did look
beautiful
yeah
hold on sorry um i've been hit by the
internet probs again hold on i think are
we okay oh my god
i think we're good
hold on i just needed to refresh i just
need a refresher
myself also from australia you know
i can confirm
australian citizen right here
what's up man
what's up my bloody hell mate you're
looking gorgeous uh uh wait uh
um help help me out
you you i've been having some
australians uh uh teaching me some words
every now and then i'll do tell
um
well there was this one mate and one
that would make a mate
keeps on teaching me words why are you
right now
i need help for communication
frankie cricky cracky froggy
cranky crunchy nice
that's a good word right mm-hmm
that's mcdonald's right
yeah what's the word for like doing
something like
uh
really
really strongly
ah
what was that word
come on my australians
where the australians were
wow okay even that's a word i haven't
heard in oh my god
you're freaking out
no i think we have already proven from
the get-go that i am the real australian
here oh definitely i mean it took me a
while to remember but
i've been getting used to speaking
proper english with my viewers here so
and what's what's your
what's a word that you can
teach me that i don't know yet
[Music]
oh that's a good question
australia um
yes do you know
let's jet
yes
actually actually i remember when we
were in discord voice chat oh yeah oh
wait yeah
you said that and i was like oh yeah
hell yeah i'm gonna use that before she
debuts in in my streams and i used it
but they didn't my viewers didn't even
notice um
how about
my show
what
when we go out to food and then you say
oh don't worry about me my shout
do you know what i mean shout yeah your
shout
you're gonna like invite them for food
um it's like you'll pay
yeah yeah yeah my oh my god there's a
huge drill drilling into my apartment
right now oh okay okay
my munch out wait how did you how do you
spell it shout like shouting shelf
ah okay okay okay well my dear dear bae
since you are my little kohai
uh no matter how many bombs we make boom
today
it's my shout out i'll pay for the the
cost of repairing everything around this
don't worry is that food involved
no oh i think um i think shout is
normally used for food or like
purchasing of
items yeah i'm purchasing i'm repairing
the car
yeah the repair card the repair cost
okay
right yeah let's look at the gaming
screen screen
okay oh is that volume okay can you guys
hear kiara okay
you guys hear the rats
perfect okay we're good okay let me
learn
you carry diseases don't you
no i keep myself very clean thank you
very much really yeah really what do you
watch yourself with
cheating
um i
cleanse myself
as
well as everyone else what does everyone
else use body soap yes oh well i use i
use gravy
and you have the nerve to talk to me
about hygiene
it makes me
smell very nice okay okay okay okay
okay
don't i hear some doubt there i hear
some x's but no no no
o's
no x no x's
today my dear bay is our first
collaboration yeah and um i thought we
should uh
choose a game that lets us practice uh
our communication skills oh yeah and
today we will not only be playing this
game in normal english but we will do a
round where one of us speaks japanese
and we will do a round where i speak
german and we will do a round where we
will speak english but we will ban some
words that uh
also the chat uh provides us so if you
guys say bad the word
uh
it doesn't help that i know zero german
but that's okay
google translate help me
well
uh
you know what we're feeling your
feelings probably will understand it's
feeling maybe sometimes it sounds a bit
similar didn't you know that the word
kindergarten is originally german oh
i
no but okay but that will not happen in
the bomb diffusion but there are some
german words in english language the
only german wait is that german
yes the only word i know how to
pronounce i'll say in german is berga
which is bugar
is that right
no not german oh that's not german what
how do you say burger in german
i mean there's a word uh that sounds
similar which is a burger but that means
um uh
um
a person who lives citizens is
and the people from there you call
hamburgers
[Music]
today you'll go out of here with maximum
german knowledge yes don't worry i'll
teach you some good words okay
so
senpai
since you watched empire you gotta you
gotta i will be guiding you on how to
defuse
the bomb now on okay my perspective
you'll be able to see the manual uh this
round and also you will hear this lovely
elevator music yeah this empire was just
saying how amazing this elevator music
is hell yeah
it's a gym okay it's lit okay look i
will start with uh is it okay i mean
this is probably already going to be a
bit difficult but i will start with the
2.2 which has six modules 2.2
okay let me just yeah
manual
manual or should we start with an easier
one um yeah you're cool
ah
okay let's start with 2.1 2.1 2.1 do you
like my job mouse everyone people keep
making fun of my mouse people say my
mouse is ah are you using uh yourself as
a mouse no i've just got a giant arrow
oh what the hell
hey
that's disappointing you gotta use
yourself you're you're around wouldn't
that make sense to use yourself but i
haven't found one yet didn't you use
that in your debut stream why am i
imagining things no i used a giant arrow
okay okay i'll get you one we'll get you
one then let's start with normal english
for the first round okay
okay
please lead me through the bomb
diffusion okay mrs mrs rat
mrs
uh
let's start with the like there's uh
four buttons with some uh hieroglyphical
signs let's start with that part okay
can you tell me the four sides you see
please
yeah it says one of them is a star one
of them is the copyright thingy one of
them is a upside down y with one line
crossing through it
and the
last one is
it looks uh
like a
cursive
[Music]
okay sweet can you please press
copyright sign
yes
uh the the cursive
the y and the star
very good
very good we have the same thing again
but with different signs oh my
so one is a c with a dot in the middle
see with the dot see what the dot uh is
the backwards or actual c actually
it's it's the right direction okay
and then there's a p that's that looks
in the other direction and is called
black
then there's uh there's a there's the
trident trident trident
oh try dead yes there's a free that
looks the other way and has a tail and
has bunny ears yes
yes okay so trident
then
c
then pier than three
genius
very good
i was like hearing sounds i thought the
game was doing it but now my my room is
currently falling apart
and we have uh we have a we have a field
with four colors they are blue yellow
green and red
oh is it in a diamond shape
yes oh okay um uh which one is flashing
the blue one the blue one
okay the original video
i don't know how to read this okay
does the serial number contain a vowel
ah
serial number
uh
yes yes it does okay
uh yes
uh
okay press uh
wait uh
follow wait
um
okay can you press the red button
yes
beep
now now now after i did that the blue
moon beeped and the red one beeped okay
telling me something
um
is there a new new color
no but but it keeps on beeping at me
blue and red blue and red
in between
i think maybe blue next
yeah are you sure no okay big wrong
wrong wrong okay i'll press red again no
oh [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] okay ah
[Music]
i shouldn't have done that okay blue red
is beeping
okay blue red
okay we've got one strike a blue
two two strikes
okay we repeat oh we need to repeat the
sequence okay one minute left okay so if
it's two strikes so blue
okay can you click blue red green
[Laughter]
it was blue and red was already
activated right but i i don't know i
don't know
this one confuses me because it doesn't
say which
button
to press but okay never mind
hello this is the australian internet
mate oh my every time i boom i swear
every time i boom this is what happens
so often for you um unfortunately yes
okay we're back we're back
i think you should uh
leave australia and move to australia
oh my
wink
i can't i have i have an extra veggie or
you can sleep in my bed
i'm not i'm not trying to flirt with you
i i i want you to be like my little
sister maybe yeah
i mean i am callie's little sister
doesn't that make me technically your
little sister as well
excuse me what your cow's little sister
yeah
what when the [\h__\h] did that happen
what the [\h__\h] did that happen
when the [\h__\h] when the [\h__\h] did that
happen and why
we have the same we have we have the
same father in uh oh that does not
matter
no no no okay let's go back okay no no
no no
no
okay now i i will read the manual to you
in german is that okay for you well we
haven't even completed the first level
okay you need to can we can we try um
actually uh disarm one bomb before we
move on to
okay okay
manual again yes i'll do the manual one
more time i don't understand simon says
i don't understand
oh that was like ah
ah well simon says it's basically just
remembering what has been said before i
know but it doesn't say if we're meant
to press the original button that's the
only thing oh you know what this time
that one is not here i can ignore that
perfect
let's start with some wires okay
i got one two three four five six wires
six wires i will now tell you from top
to bottom
which color they are okay
black
yellow
red
white
and blue
thinking time for okay so there's one
yellow
how many white
and one
uh
is there a red wire
yes
indeed
okay can you cut the fourth wire
one two three four
okay
are we good
very good
now something that looks very difficult
we have a maze
with like dots and and two green
circled
squares
and one white dot and one red triangle
that is probably me
oh
i think this one is difficult oh oh
should i tell you where the little green
circled ones are oh yes where are those
oh wait wait wait wait wait there should
be two
so you are the triangle and then there
should be two like circle thingies on
the map right yeah okay can you please
tell me
uh where the circle thingies are
uh
one is at the very top row second from
the left second from the left second
over there and one is the second from
the left on the very bottom
oh okay and where are you
i am
wait am i the white square or am i the
red triangle
um
maze with matching must navigate the
right okay so you are the white light
whereas where is the white light
that one is and on the very very left
side uh from top to bottom third row top
to bottom third height okay and we're
trying on the very left the triangle is
in the same row so
top to bottom third row but it's uh
from the left side
oh
four one two four three four oh
okay so can you go get up three all the
way to the top
one two
three
yes okay i'm at the top yes you're in
the very left hand corner right
yeah okay sweet now go to the right one
two three
uh okay one
but you mean you mean
um to the third one from the left or i
should actually click the button three
times and be on the fourth fourth oh oh
sorry yeah yes you'll be on the fourth
one
okay
okay okay and then go down one
one right
one
one wait why am i getting lost oh wait
no okay we're good up one
up one right one
right one okay and then down two
two yes uh one left
yes down one
yes
uh left two
yes up one
yes and then the right should be the the
triangle right
[Music]
i don't have much left on here i have a
button a white button that says press oh
i press
hold hold code okay oh my god they're
drilling so loud baby can you like
destroy them or something boom boom
there you
go maybe let the bomb explode so it
explodes on them oh wait there's only
one left okay what do i do wait the
button is white
yeah it says press okay um is there a
link indicator with the label car
uh no
oh um so on the side there's no like oh
oh
oh my god no
[\h__\h]
okay this is nsa nsa on the side oh it
says nsa is there batteries in this bomb
uh
yes how many one one big one okay
okay 20 seconds 17 seconds okay hold the
button and then um let me know what
color comes up
red
um when it has a one in the timer you
can let go
[Laughter]
left so the only one that i could really
wait for was one second left what can i
say chaos we like to live on the edge
you know
yeah that was all i got time remaining
1.69
amazing
very nicely done
oh that was all all according to keikaku
exactly it's all about the tension guys
that's how you build
engagement
yeah
it felt chaotic that's for sure uh-huh
very good
i was just taking my time all right okay
are you ready for a german round
no i'm not don't worry i think i think
with watson when i did it in german i
think we were understanding each other
better than when we communicated in
english so uh-oh oh you should be good
why is it loading so long game
okay why are you loading so long uh-oh
hello game oh no my game i think my game
is dead oh i mean that's okay cause i'm
not the one playing now i'll be the one
reading all right yeah let me close the
game
what's it what's it recently with my
games crashing
uh
[Music]
yesterday apparently it was a part of uh
it was it was a common bug though anyway
so which do you know which you want to
do an easier bump please
can we do the first bomb
should we do the first bomb or two point
one no
no you'll do the the third one
two by two
oh no
no no no no no no no from from one point
yeah so the first round so 1.3 right
okay one more yeah we'll do one point
three okay okay yeah no
one that would be too boring okay
okay okay
okay wait a second okay
my manual when i'm back in the game but
i won't be the one doing oh i see
crazy
oh
sorry
yeah where is she where is she
oh no she's just she's on my leaderboard
you're friends with crazy ollie on steam
oh yeah but not with me yet
we'll change that out
all right
okay uh
are you ready because i'm ready i think
i mean
lessons lesson stories
[Laughter]
look at the bum okay
how do i turn the lights on
okay i've heard automatic okay it's on
okay
okay we've got the first i got the four
symbols
um
in a row oh sorry the four simple yes
okay one is a copyright symbol
one yeah looks like a nose with a really
big pimple on top
yeah yeah and then
one looks like they were gonna write a
three but then the hand died yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah and the last one looks
like um a butterfly with an eye in the
middle
okay so my description about the button
about the three was very long so i'm
guessing it's the butterfly
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
um one white
one blue
two black
one red and one yellow
er escaped kind of water
is okay that sounded like is the white
imported
come again
[Music]
nine
okay so
red
how many one
oh oh okay okay okay
uh again
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah yellow this is one yellow yeah
okay
uh-huh
um two black
one blue
one red one yeah a one white
[Laughter]
[Music]
we've got a button that says white that
it says press
[Music]
um
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
hold on it's gonna be a while
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
how
you did a good job so
uh you i think one one word that you
will take away from this is
schmetterling it's butterfly shmeddling
i've forgotten that already i just
remember nine
nine nine yeah nine is no no no
yeah that's right that's the only word
you really have to know okay okay
we we did it
german rounds completed round completed
very good okay
then uh
should we do the the english round where
some words are banned
yes um i wanna have a look at this
so i think we came up with no saying
colors like we have to just describe the
colors instead of like you can't say red
blue et cetera et cetera canal
yes
still speaking german
how about yeah we say we don't say wire
okay no wire okay
and we don't say button
okay
okay so no wire
no no yeah we should we should write
this down i'm going to forget it uh no
no wire
um button
no um
we're gonna make it really difficult no
button
no colors talking at all no talking
no game
um
what else do i have in the menu
i mean something something that makes uh
explaining those
hieroglyphic uh symbols
uh more difficult
um
i mean i feel like that's already pretty
difficult but yeah i think maybe we can
start with these three and see how we go
okay
okay okay
no no
okay i'll pin that as a comment in my
chat oh me too why see it big ring
no one
[Music]
i lost myself okay
oh should we do a 2.2
um okay
okay are you ready hold on hold on let
me change back to the menu
okay
oh we could do a singing only around two
let's do that afterwards
let's go
[Music]
lie down please
hello
hello there we go why does it take so
long
okay uh
four
uh
the four the four things with the with
those with the
signs on it yes yes oh yes i have two of
those
okay good so let's die let's start one
of them is a star one of them is
uh
a boobie with a belly button on top of
it
okay the one that you the one that you
called knows yes the then we have the
disney squiggle and we have the why
that's so
the other way around before upside down
tell kiara we can't see her screen
eh eh
oh [\h__\h]
i still have the menu
okay
okay okay um so remember what i said yes
it's the boobies and then
and then the
half walt disney and then
upside down y and then the star
okay
works next one
next one also has a upside down y and it
has a butterfly it has a copper rod and
it has a bubba
that too fast
okay copyright
bubba
butterfly why
nice oh speedrun speed round
then we have some pretty strings strings
wink wink oh pretty straight you know
what i mean very good yeah we got four
of them two black two blues oh you got
it
[Laughter]
well i'll just cut some random ones here
okay it's okay
[Laughter]
it came so natural okay one more time
one more time one more time
lights on please forgot sink
okay okay uh okay
uh we have uh two two panels with
strings two panels with strings yeah
okay one has one two three four
five six six okay
and now now listen there's two that are
the the the color of the blood okay okay
two color of the blood i'm allowed to
say the word color but not not any
colors okay and and one is the color of
the sun one is the color of the sun
exactly one okay
yeah one is a two are the color of uh
darkness two of the color of darkness
okay
that is what is the color of the sea
one is the color to see okay cut the
fourth one
oh i know we didn't say no numbers okay
we could cut
cut the four you pretty straight i
didn't
i'll give you that one the first one no
cut the fourth pretty little string
the fourth one yes
nothing happened
i didn't say anything okay okay we have
another panel with four strings four
strings we like strings are the color of
sun and two are the color of c
are there only four strings in total
yes
one indeed like two other color of the
what
to work the color of the sun and two
other color of the c
okay
what color is the last string
[Laughter]
color of the c color the c okay
i'll cut the last string
done okay around oh my god there's so
many we have three minutes left okay two
panels with uh
things yes with sick girls oh yes yes
signs
hero gloves okay one is a c copyright c
yes it's a butterfly one is a three
that's not finished writing and one is
the turn around why okay
c butterfly three white
oh that's exactly the
way i told you okay very good then we
have another one that's a star star and
a bulba with a belly button and a
copyright and a butterfly oh okay um
butterfly
and the last one i can't remember what
you said
stop
it
and we have two big
big
things that you can push
two big things we can push out
separately yes both say abort
but one is the color of blood and one is
the color of uh
[Music]
the sea
okay um the gural the gulag the gouda
okay uh we got how many left and by the
way
batteries i have uh four batteries
four small ones okay
one is the color oh no wait there's more
there's four small batteries and one big
one oh okay so the one is the color of
blood did you say
uh yes okay um and it what does it say
abort a boy oh
okay can we start with the color of the
sea let's start with the color of the
sea yes okay um can you press it and
tell me
what color shows up right
oh
a little bit yeah
[Applause]
can you just hold it tell me what color
comes up
[Laughter]
of
of a bright brightness
color and brightness
um release when timer has a one in any
position
okay
oh my just finishing this now it worked
very good
oh my god
i just said with so much confidence it
was like white but then i was like
five ten seconds later i was like
i thought you said right and i was
waiting for you to say the color and i
was like is she struggling is there a
color she can't describe
[Laughter]
that you had i thought you were getting
mad at me for saying the color oh no i
didn't even hear the color
[Music]
okay okay okay um what was the next
round
oh you get a thing
you're gonna you're gonna defuse and i'm
gonna sing the manual okay
hold on let me find it where did i put
it here we go
all right which one should we do
uh
whichever you desire i think did you get
two points maybe two point three
two one three
okay
[Music]
let's see
all right
oh she got the reverb
okay and the heart oh god help me okay
uh we've got simon says
because we got to figure out how to do
this one oh
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
uh okay yeah let's go
it's flashing oh we both have to sing
it's flashing red
it's it's oh
wait a second i've never read this one
before
[Music]
that's
i don't understand
um
what's up red flash okay
please press blue
if wash red again
double red
[Music]
now please let let press blue
red red
oh
well please press blue
is that really it what's going on i
don't know
did you press blue again
wait
oh press blue
oh i see i understand okay sorry
um
[Music]
one of the four colored buttons will
flash using the correct table below
press the button move the corresponding
color the original button will flash
followed by another repeat this sequence
in order using the color mapping the
sequence will lengthen by one each time
you correctly enter a sequence and
what color should i press if it's
flashing blue
please press red
[Music]
if there are no yellow wires and the
last digit of the serial number is a cut
the third wire
yellow ones exactly one yellow white one
yellow one yellow one yellow
and
this is the more than just one white
wire
there is only one
we only have one minute and 30 40 40
seconds left oh [\h__\h] just cut just cut
the full fire
[Music]
very good second one
no
[Laughter]
[Music]
we got a big number
and then we've got four numbers below
i've got one minute to save my life
i don't know what you're talking about
this is one big number
yes yes what is it three
press the button on the third position
start position
third position and this is three
press the button in the first position
oh now it says
um it says two
[Music]
okay
press the button of the same level you
press in stage one so the front position
okay now it says
three
i'm going to die i'm going to die
press the one that you pressed at the
second stage
[Music]
singing wastes too much time i thought
this would be easy but it wastes too
much time we went boom boom
[Music]
[\h__\h] singing
let's do
let's do japanese rounds nihongo me home
of us okay only one of us so
i can read the manual in hong kong to
you and you try to defuse in english
shoot okay
[Music]
keep singing and nobody
um
okay
uh shall we do the same bomb yes that's
so much pretty difficult but okay okay
retry
um so we've got come on light come on
like
what is this okay i'm gonna start with
the numbers one that we just did because
it takes a long time
hey so the number in the top is two
[Music]
that's wrong
there were three stars okay says three
but in which stage are we now no restart
restart yeah number three restart okay
okay now it says
okay
now it says one
ah
same label
uh
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
um
okay so the two green circles um the
first green circle is in the third
column um and second row from the bottom
wait
put the mud
okay so third column and then second
from the bottom row and then the second
circle is the first row first row um
second column from the right
okay so third column
and then second row from the bottom
it's the one up down
okay okay and the second row from the
bottom yes
and then the other one is first row i'm
going to die second uh column from the
left up from the right from the right
from the right side
no no what
where where is
[Laughter]
[Music]
should we do it the other way around you
do you want to do the manual in japanese
to me oh sure
okay probably gonna fail yeah it's okay
2.3 is so difficult yeah and here we
were saying we're gonna do like level
three ones yo who are we kidding
never never happening
okay okay
yes you speak nihongo to me please
let me
know when you're ready
okay so um
the circled ones are one is second row
on the very left
height and one is on the third row on
the very right
that one is uh on the very left uh
on the
fourth point from the top
at the very bottom row
and uh
on the on the fourth point from the left
very bottom
fourth fourth spot
[Music]
hit
uh
[Music]
that
well i mean i'll be explaining them to
you so no we'll be fun so we have one
star
we have one disney squiggle disney
we have one
round e
that looks the other side and with two
dots on top oh hi
and we have a tennis racket yes
oh hi hey
[Music]
okay then we have a yellow button that
says abort
[Music]
my thing does say nsa and frq
is
[Music]
hey
now we have a we have a panel
with a big number at the top
okay
this one's gonna [\h__\h] us up okay so i
have more numbers at the bottom yeah
right now it says three in the top oh
[\h__\h]
uh it's pretty that low what's up what
page was that
it is uh it should be
[Music]
yes yes remember that chat remember we
have to get this one it says one now big
one big one
[Music]
um one third position for second
position one third position four seconds
four four four one third position four
second position four four
okay okay one third position four second
position
[Music]
oh
happening
[Music]
each number was and i remember the
numbers well except at the very end i
was getting a bit loose on that freak
but but your your nihongo
she didn't take it like that all right
all right
uh
do we wanna try the last one in proper
english again just so we end up on a
high note
yeah let's try to we've no we've no
nothing to stop us just do normal
english and see if we can do it this way
okay
okay should i be diffusing or do you
want to diffuse um up to you
okay i'll refuse let's go
let's do this baby let's do it
if you help me defuse this bomb i will
let you work at kfp okay game face on
good okay we got wires oh [\h__\h] there's
so much here holy [\h__\h] wires one two
three four five six wires
six wires three of them are blue
one is red
one is uh white
one is black the last one is black
does that help you wait how many wires
again five six uh six six okay
um there is
one yellow
no no yellow no yellow um
and the last okay what what's the last
digit of the serial number
oh
uh zero
zero okay
is there a red one
yeah okay cut the fourth one one
oh one two three four
[\h__\h] okay
let's do symbols
c boobies turn around why butterfly
all right okay copyright c
boo-boo
butterfly did you say
easy okay done
that's we're good with that one okay now
we have a new one that we haven't done
before ever it's a panel with words uh
it says like there's a there's a screen
that says you were
and then
six different words
wait how many more little panel um how
many more do we have so we have this
uh we have one with the colors the four
colors oh and we have
yeah this one okay that's it yeah all
right we'll save this one first okay so
what was the word on top
uh you're you're how do you you i you
wait oh wait does it say
you
are
it's spelled like how can you read out
the exact letters for me please yes
y-o-u apostrophe r-e
apostrophe can you say that again
the thing that i think on the top
i know can you say it again
um what is the word on the second row to
the right
middle
middle oh right very right okay um and
push the first button that appears in
this corresponding okay okay so i'm
gonna read
out a bunch of words and can you push
the first one you hear
oh okay
okay blank okay
ready blank note
no okay
spelled okay a y
no what
yes
very good
okay okay yeah
now i see display on the display oh wait
don't do it again okay okay okay okay
just
display
yeah okay
um can you
what's the word on the bottom right very
bottom right
sure
s-u-r-e s-u-r-e okay so um
press the one that you hear first uh so
you are like two words y-o-u space a-r-e
next one they are t h e y space a r e
they are they are
yeah
wait wait t h a space a r e
yes okay um what's the middle one to the
left
right
right um
okay
uh yes
no nothing
no ready
no
um
[Music]
no
no press
yes okay okay okay there are four colors
panel we have one minute left and the
blinky one is
come on green green green is blinky
simon says oh [\h__\h] this is gonna fall
okay green
um yes flash can you please flash
uh oh does the serial number contain a
vowel
no
no it doesn't contain a vowel
it does not okay
okay green can you press yellow please
yes and we have 26 ah it was wrong wrong
it was wrong oh what
it's flashed in green and we have 20
seconds left oh no
oh oh
zero
oh um zero is this okay um
can you press green
green okay no wrong that was wrong [\h__\h]
okay congratulations ray you did not get
the job at kfp
but i did prank you
what
sorry today is my one month you know and
i had to prank all the myth members that
i could and i may have read you the
wrong instructions
are you making excuses because you
actually
read the right manual but you didn't
know what you were doing get pranked get
pranked get pregnant don't delete it
okay buy it okay you can watch the re
you can watch the the archive get
pranked wait why would you read why
would you read the wrong manual so i can
prank you you can go boom
did you not want the job at kfb no
because i'll get in anyway because
i'm a rat
you little [\h__\h]
i'm sending you to the usual room
you can't you're welcome at the usual
room you'll see it you'll see how fun it
is there you little stupid rats
[Music]
well my australian mate uh
from the future yes you better not prank
your senpai
it's okay
i think we need someone like you uh to
you know bring some life
into whole life you're welcome to prank
any of us oh create some chaos we need
some chaos i mean that would the whole
myth was always always chaotic but we
need more more chaos well your wish is
my command hold on let me let's go back
to the main to the talking all right
i'll also go back to my
although i don't want you i don't really
no i don't really want you in the
kitchen anymore here i'll
i'll i'll put you in the fryer
is it hot over there my dear face not as
hot as
no flirt is not in my shoes
it's okay i'm just chilling here
in some oil we did
that
because actually should be done here
that was fun
yeah it was fun i'm glad we did a collab
together and i'm glad that
i could
be your first one
okay
are you not happy that i was your first
one no i was very happy i just
remembered that you also said the same
thing in in discord and i responded with
an inappropriate joke and i'm not gonna
do that on stream
oh well then let me read out what you
said
so i said i said on the first september
uh
i will take your senpai collaboration
into dough smug emoji and then she says
omg dodge
and then i say your mind smug emoji and
then she says please treat me gently xd
i love how you use xd and both in cable
capital letters by the way that's uh i
don't know i have um
that was a face for me too
i was a face a certain point in my life
i was writing xd and capital letters as
well but that time is over
we're just gonna use xd what's wrong
with xd it's a very good expressive you
know
i like it
i think you you're okay you're good to
go you can use it did i treat you gently
enough though
no that was actually quite rough what a
rough night um
[Music]
i wanna i wanna put you i wanna eat you
wait no no cat
no i am a cat after all you're sure
now okay well thank you babe for hanging
out with me you're gone now no more
kitchen for you
uh you're from now on band from my
kitchen and we can still be friends
though but yeah you're just not welcome
in my kitchen
you can order from kfp via ubereats or
something if you really need some food
you're welcome to give us money uh but
we we can't let you into the restaurant
anymore but the delivery is okay we can
deliver to your place i don't know if we
really deliver to
um fake australia we'll see about that
oh i'm sorry i was putting coffee up
your nose okay i'm stuck
my queen
stop playing around with me
okay
be good
um i'm looking forward to many many more
fun collabs with you my dear baby me too
this is really funny this is really i
hope you're feeling uh welcomed and
happy in her life and if there's ever
anything that you're worried about or
that you have problems with or anything
you want to discuss i'm always here for
you bae oh thank you
thank you i'm a good senpai okay i can i
i can help you oh
okay
okay i can help you in many ways
um
with that being said thanks guys for
coming
my ending greeting um i say goodbye in
english japanese or another japanese and
then korean and then ice cream
oh my god okay you today you can add uh
one more language to that because my
ending greeting is actually in german so
you can say that as well
oh
okay
yes uh in german and in german we say
thousand
auf wiedersehen alvita zayn
yeah you can actually make it shorter
you can just say truce but no we're
gonna make you say the difficult one auf
wiedersehen
[Music]
wait
uh hopefully not at the same time as you
oh okay
just kidding
i don't know if you want to meet my mom
you're welcome to come by oh no it's
just i'm also streaming tomorrow
minecraft so
we'll see if we're overlapping we'll see
we'll see well if we overlap i might
have to hire you after all from my
construction company
oh
well
i guess we'll see you tomorrow in
minecraft guys
yes
very good
bye bye
see you tomorrow
[Music]
you