[Music]
a
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
welcome
yay uh it's my birthday I'm sure you
guys know by now
[Music]
yeah so
um
I'll be uh
singing with all of my
friends um but they're pre-recorded I'm
just going to dance yeah so so so
so yeah I guess you guys can see it as a
birthday life kind of one day I'll do a
one day I'll do a proper birthday life
but for now I hope you guys are okay
with something like
[Music]
thisday sorry the the zombie body tends
to get a little bit weird when I move
around to too much also what do you guys
think about the
stage stage I even have a new microphone
and it has boom why is it why is it not
coming out
boom ah there we go it has spider
legs it's so cute vji made this V the
vtuber so big shout out to viny please
support vji the link is in the
description below follow
viny is a cool person
yeah it's going to be dope I'm going to
be singing with everyone uh on this
stage and there's like a lot of
variations so you guys can like check
all of them out uh
yeah so I think it's about time we start
with our first
song flaming pants and who's that uh
buy thank you happy birthday Alie thank
you
[Music]
I think I'll be singing the first song
uh now after I zombie body
myself yeah it happens
sometimes
okay are you guys ready first
song
[Music]
fore
for
[Music]
for wo
let's
go let's go yeah let's go let's
[Music]
go
[Applause]
for
[Music]
fore
yay
[Music]
e
don't forget to like And subscribe my
channel instag
TI
I
got yeah
it's by the way I saw the raid H I
wanted to think but I was like uh in the
middle of dancing so I was like what
should I do first but I saw I saw the
bre
in the chat welcome to the stream
everyone hi how was the how's the watch
along I didn't I didn't get to watch the
was in TR because I was too busy getting
ready for my
[Music]
own bet it was
fun we cried a lot I I I would I can
yeah so yeah welcome back hey welcome BR
welcome everyone to the stream this is
crazy Ali from H life in an second
generation I'm having my birthday
currently uh I can't do a birthday life
because um reasons but I'm trying my
best to actually uh accommodate Myself
by doing this semi 3D Live not really at
thoughts of karaoke
yay yeah we just sang number one by me
no actually it was by honeyworks Mona
and I sung it with Kayla kosia and K
from H life Indonesia third generation I
thought that that would be a nice song
to start outfit since you know it's
number one get it number one being the
first song
cuz
number
yeah it was fun it was really fun we
still have a lot more other
um performances coming up uh let me just
zombify myself real quick quick it
happens all
right happy birthday Al thank you masi
Maki so cute all right so next up we'll
be we'll be uh changing the uh what's it
called we'll be changing the settings
right what song are we doing again
next
[Music]
um I actually
forgot actually forgot what song uh I'm
supposed to be doing I have have like a
set list going
on oh
okay we're going to move okay
say it's green
now
ging uh gang I I I think is is that is
that the right word not sure and to
zombify ourselves one more time cuz we
don't want to look weird while we're
doing
it you guys ready yo this is dope
right okay next song Let's
Go
[Music]
[Applause]
Boe
[Music]
fore
[Applause]
[Music]
foree
[Applause]
fore
[Music]
for
[Applause]
[Music]
foree
fore
[Music]
h
fore
[Music]
foree
shoot wait wait wait just a moment I
accidentally spiled
water on my on my on my sound
interface oh not not on my
birthday shoot whoa that's a lot of
water it's s that's what she said um no
it's not the time
to I was dancing too
hard okay sorry about that um let me
just uhhuh won't take too
long
oh that was crazy that was that one was
a crazy
song wait we got
to sorry about
that that
was
by I'm sorry I don't know the the the
the original composer I bet you guys
know just write down in the comment
section I sang wait m is an innocent pie
from H life
F yeah pretty cool uh pretty cool song
pretty sick it's kind of it has that pop
going on pop rock is that is that is
that how you say
it
disappeared yeah yeah yeah and then uh
we still have more songs ahead of us I
feel like it's a good time to also
change like to a new color so let's
go
okay now
it's oh my God yeah another theme you
have like a theme for each song they
fall under one category
each
yeah who uh
let's
go yeah so next
song I'll be singing with fellow ID
members this
time it's going to be a hype song so I
hope you guys enjoy here is
e
[Music]
for
Fore
[Music]
take
foree
[Music]
fore
[Applause]
[Music]
for
spee
[Music]
yay that was
yeah uh me you be S by and we s by sing
it
together
yeah um I fell in love with the song
after I heard K Senpai and Ena senpai's
cover of it it's super super nice uh I
really like it and I thought it'd be a
groovy song to actually um sing to with
MAA S and yui S by so that's exactly
what we did uh I love like the dance
moves I like how simple it is like even
if you guys watch like the original MB
it's
like no
[Music]
jpai
birthday I'm singing while I'm dancing
um and if I sound weird well it is a
karaoke after all nothing is perfect in
karaoke unless you're s is in by then
that's a different uh that's a different
story
guys
hi all right next song hope you guys are
ready here is Romeo and
[Music]
Cinderella
boo fore
[Music]
fore
fore hi hi hi hi Hi
[Music]
H
speee
for
heig
[Music]
spee
foree
[Music]
for yay
woo hey hey hey
[Music]
he
yay and that everyone was R and
Cinderella it was That's a classic right
there H if you guys are Vocaloid fans
I'm so sorry I'm so big I don't know why
it does that but if you guys are
vocalite songs you guys definitely know
the song it's everyone's Anthem next to
World Is Mine definite classic I'm so
happy that I got sing it with narissa
and Caris by h
I don't know I feel like uh um they're
like the perfect people actually uh
singing uh R and Cinder with me I'm so
sorry I'm so out of breath I'm trying to
hold it in I've been practicing this a
lot I'm trying to practice my uh breath
holding that's why I didn't sound so
quavery while I was dancing
[Music]
right it's a technique I've learned
and that technique is called just
holding it
inie let's let's zombie ourselves a
little
bit oh that feels so much better all
right well next up we'll be singing
another hype song um wait not a hype
song an old song actually
um if you guys are fans of hokago tea
time you guys should know and I'll be
singing it with very uh very special
people they're my favorite people and uh
it's funny how we don't do collabs that
often but they're very special to me so
let's move to a different overlay
first
right uh
oh all right oh
nope like this like so and then let's
actually put this down here because it's
kind of in the way all right are you
guys ready next
[Music]
songing
the
[Music]
fore
the
we
[Music]
attention
for
[Music]
give
Mee
[Music]
fore
foreign
[Music]
yeah that has been
uh uh from H tea time I sang it with aai
and V both from Indonesia um uh sorry
about the technical issues ma only
I don't know if you guys heard it but it
got a little bit a what's it
called
yeah it was weird I was like what the
heck is going
[Music]
on um I think we can do uh two more
songs before the announcement oh you
guys already know what announcements are
but we're on a tight schedule so as much
as I want to redo that they
[Music]
can't I wonder if I can sing this one uh
this one is going to be a hard song yeah
let me let let's just zomb fire
eles how to
explain there were some static sounds
right during the
fen and it's it's a bit of a shame I
want to repeat it but I can't I hope you
guys
understand all right we're
moving all right we're back
here let me just
move myself to the
middle because it'll be yet another Trio
most of the songs that I'll be
performing it's going to be a trio so
yeah all right uh here comes the next
one deal with the Devil by
[Music]
Tia
up why
not
[Music]
the
fore
[Music]
spe
for
bab my
[Music]
honey
[Applause]
[Music]
spee
foree you me the let
[Music]
down
[Applause]
about com after came
before
[Applause]
[Music]
take
[Applause]
foree
[Music]
foreign
foree foreign
[Music]
spee
all right um sorry about that that
was there was a lot of scuff and down
when the most like I suddenly turned big
I tried my best to sing like I don't
know why but then my face froze and it
didn't show me singing I promise I was
singing I was right next to the
mic it was weird that's okay hi ah so
many hype songs I guess we should tone
it down don't you
think
[Music]
next song yeah we're going to tone it
down a little
bit here we are why are there two
mics wait wait just a
moment there we go
[Music]
by I forgot the composer but uh en has
covered this once that's already big of
a hint so let's just get on to it
[Music]
n hi
for
[Music]
me
[Applause]
[Music]
come
C it eat eat
[Music]
[Applause]
more down
[Music]
[Laughter]
I don't know stories I don't need
Str there's no love story no
[Music]
doubt
fore
[Music]
night
[Applause]
[Music]
that was
oh we'll have to do that later you need
like it got better because I tried I
tried fixing it in the middle well well
B was singing I was like okay okay okay
I I I got to work fast I got to next is
my line I'm sorry about that Mafia but I
I don't know why it was like that why is
it it's getting more worse and
worse see
like yeah take two would be taru but for
now we have announcements yeah so
so it's time for
announcements this is what you guys have
been waiting
for why is my mic suddenly there I'm
supposed to drag it
here
announcement times 3 2
1 Alice birthday celebration 2023
special
guests
yeah so um starting
from um 800
P.M
there's a lot of goods are prepared uh
especially for you guys so um yeah yeah
yeah yeah let me let me actually let me
actually just show you guys um bam so
this is the key
visual can can you guys guess what this
year's theme
is so we had this sleepy Oli theme on
2021 then we had uh the princess Ollie
in 2022 and in 2023 we have office olly
o so what do we have olly well I'm glad
you asked so uh here's the
list B bam so we have a tapestry an
acrylic clip and a card case we also
have skipping that uh and we also Al uh
if you guys buy the whole set you guys
get a get um a file
folder yeah so cool so let's look at the
products one by one shall
we whoops sorry
Senai so uh this is me as your Junior
and
office
it's like the the clutch but not really
it's like the TIY clutch kind of that's
the
visuals this is the acrylic clip so
basically you can use this to like clip
your folders uh clip your documents and
whatnot
uh and you can actually turn it around
so it can turn into a clip but it can
also turn into like this chiby acrylic
that you can just hang on your uh shelf
your your merch shelf yeah yeah yeah so
it can be useful but it can also be like
a collection item as
well and then we have uh we have the
office worker card case yeah so if you
guys buy uh this one you guys get a card
and you guys also get a lanyard
did and if you guys realized uh this
year's Twitter icon frame was inspired
by this it was a spoiler to this
icon yeah I thought it might be useful
can I wait let me
just me I look
weird I got to do this a lot in the
Stream I
apologize like that like
that and then we have the
uh and then we have the uh uh individual
voic Sals so we have situation voice
pack um there's all of all of the script
for The Voice packs they're all the same
it's just that there's a Japanese
version an English version and an Indian
version that's the only thing that
differs from them there's no change in
plot so you guys can like choose the
language that you want to hear Ali
speaking so don't worry about missing
out at
all
and then uh is that all oh yeah and if
you guys purchase the whole set you guys
get this purchase bonus which is a a
clear
folder A5 it it's it's kind of tiny but
it's cute and I bet it can hold like
postcards your beloved um
oi
[Music]
um
Goods cards yeah there we
go oh yeah these are the voices your
belov
[Music]
Jun it's your birthday happy birthday
Ali thank
you
no no no we uh no we we we we we got
everything so uh please get ready
because this will be on sale at
800m please buy it please
[Music]
announcements let's move on to the next
song I feel like you forgot to show
something
no no I showed everything oh my gosh
what what are you guys talking
about
[Music]
all right let me
just Rec collaborate before the next
song okay
awesome all
right so the next song it's um do you
guys watch
Naruto yeah let's
[Music]
go
foree
he
[Music]
for
foree
[Music]
spee
for
foree
[Music]
w w w w w w w w w w w
w
[Music]
be and that everyone has been silhouette
I sung it with Senpai
uh from Hol star CP and Haka from Hol
Tempest Hol
staren why am I Frozen uhoh
this oh
H okay
so apparently my my body has run out of
energy so I don't think I can move
[Music]
anymore
um what do I do okay uh just a moment
how about I
[Music]
uh so so let's do
this um yeah by the way reminder guys
the merchandise is now on sale so please
be sure to check it
out
[Music]
on yeah FLD out soon I don't know who
knows but you know it'd be it'd be good
if it sold out right sold out
uh yeah
um actually wrote me like the things
that I should say when I'm like uh oh
here it
is uh yeah so you know how there's a
tapestry uh you can you can uh maybe you
can hang the tapestry with the acrylic
clip see it's useful like that and then
you can use your ID card base for daily
use um uh for work or for college uh
it's useful for
anything uh and voice pack yeah don't
forget um it comes in three different
languages if you guys want to hear the
Japanese language uh we have that and if
you guys want to hear the Indian uh
version we also have that and the
English version of course yeah
mhm yeah that's all of the merchandise
that we have
uh right right right
[Music]
right looks like my body is out of
energy so uh unfortunately we'll have to
go on with uh
[Music]
this
see I believe we still have one more
pair that we have to sing
with
yeah so yeah uh let's move to a
different
overlay I I um let me
just uh move my mic because it's so far
away okay it is time to
sing you guys already know who I'll be
singing with so I hope you guys enjoy
this is our three together
k
[Music]
spe
that'se
[Music]
baby
spe
[Music]
forab
there
[Music]
maybe
fore
[Music]
yeah you know what I'll I'll just upload
all of the uh static
ones oh
dear
[Music]
video I'll try to like re-record the
whole thing and then uh upload it I'll
see why it's so static I don't know if
it's my OBS if it's my mic or if it's my
interface after I got um water all over
it interface
why not on my
birthday get a checked after this I sure
will yeah sounds like CPU Overlord maybe
I'm not
sure but yeah
um just a little bit more guys and then
um we have two more songs left so um
hopefully it doesn't turn out static I'm
so stressed
out I feel I'm so stressed out right now
I planned this so far back I
I everyone they did their best to record
themselves it's
it's disappointing to say that um this
karaoke has not been doing Justice yeah
maybe it's because it's Friday the
13th yeah well let's just hope that the
next song won't be so
static yeah now we're back
here let's hope for the best here it
goes a
it's funny how it became a sad song
right after so many Statics let's
[Music]
go
for man
[Music]
foree
[Applause]
foree fore
[Music]
fore
spee
[Music]
me
fore
[Music]
[Applause]
fore
[Music]
foree
fore
[Music]
[Applause]
thank god it
worked
I was going to unive myself right then
and there if I couldn't sing well with
as Senpai s
Senai S as heal the internet you got
that right thank goodness it worked in
the
end I was getting
so I was getting so
frustrated
like
[Music]
I'm so happy to celebrate this wonderful
day again this year be well forever give
me
[Music]
Papa I really tried my best I wanted to
give you guys so
much
yeah I got a little bit frustrated
because uh I I can't give much to you
guys this year there's a lot of things
going on so uh I really tried to make
the best of it so it's a little
frustrating when I try my best and it
just go static
the but yeah anyways the the the the
next song is the last
song I believe that the static is no
longer with
us so
uh I
think it's about time we go to the last
song and end it on a happy note so so
let's go let's do
that please no more static hopefully
there's no more static I'll be I'll be
I'll be flipping myself off if there's
like more
[Music]
static happy thoughts happy thoughts all
right last song please give us a happy
ending
yes Glory steady
[Music]
go 1
three
[Music]
what do you want to do what like what do
you want to
[Music]
do
it's time to out it's time to Showtime
to
[Applause]
[Music]
show
you want to do what do you like what do
you
[Applause]
[Music]
sing
let's it's short
[Music]
CL
sh
Show
I want to
be it's time to It's
Time
I hope it was okay I hope it was okay I
had some uh I'm sure you guys Noti this
I recorded myself because there's some
like yells
right uh up W up I had those
pre-recorded uh just if you guys were
wondering
pred that's perfect though I hope it was
yeah I wonder if we can actually sing
the others as
well let's see should we should we redo
some of them
now which one had
the to be honest this is supposed to be
the end but I I don't feel good because
there are still some that I feel like we
could have sang Better B better better
yeah the N night right right right right
so let's go
here I would have been so cool with the
3D so then all of us would be
3D yeah yeah yeah yeah B an okay got it
so those two uh songs what else what
else what
else
uh
so did silhouette go well
[Music]
too okay uh we're supposed to end it
here but I'm not ending it on the bad
note so we're going to redo n
again uh uh uh it was hard to sing n n
because I had to like adjust to the
sudden Rhythm change I had to go I know
n so hopefully we don't have to go
through that anyway night let's
[Music]
go
for
[Music]
for I come on
night
[Applause]
night and
[Music]
I
more
[Music]
I don't know stories I don't need Str do
do do da da da there's no love story no
doubt what's
[Music]
right
fore
[Music]
go
[Applause]
[Music]
tonight
it it
work it work it
work okay so my
hypothesis is
that um my OBS could not handle how hot
my body
was
oh my God so
sexy I feel like now that I'm more
cloth that's that's my hypothesis
anyways I don't I I don't actually
know OBS down so bad yeah which means oh
you know what I feel like this is a good
way to actually end it because we Havey
right it should be okay now right
see on last
try haven't I already changed my clothes
when we were singing well I don't
know now I'm getting
skeptical what if it doesn't turn out
good anymore what if what if it's bad
again fingers
crossed let's go
[Music]
fore
B that's
[Music]
for
baby
[Music]
fore
[Applause]
baby there may be mey one to show me
down
[Music]
for
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah okay um I was thinking about it but
oh shoot you guys did not hear anything
um I was thinking about it and I I
thought that I kind of figured out why
like I know I had my hypothesis but I
actually had like one more um thing that
I want to confess to you guys remember
last year stuma where I had some
pre-recorded ones and one that I
actually sang
livean
I think it was because n and ready wait
no not ready n and I I kind
of I pre-recorded
that so maybe the files were corrupted
that's also like another um that's
another thing that actually came to mind
so uh didn't want to lie to you guys
about that part but the others I
actually sang Live okay the others
I so so to confess like you lied to us I
lied about that part which is why I'm
coming clean but just for the record I
sang the others live
okay yeah lies of fallly oh we lied to
us
no but but the others the others
yeah I just thought that I s lie to you
guys about that part cuz you know what
uh people will people will know
anyways
yeah I felt like uh I mean people would
know anyways so might as well just come
clean about that part I thought our
relationship were special but you know I
don't get
why was a little bit
static but
statica like at the start it was very
static
right so so so but I do feel like there
is a corrupt in the
files yeah sorry to burst the uh magic
bubble you are pre-recorded Oli how did
you know that I'm not actually live how
did you know that I actually
pre-recorded all of this you might be
corrupted oh my
God I mean the whole stream was
pre-recorded right yeah even the chat is
pre-recorded uh I made like thousands of
accounts with all of your names and
profile pictures like like the ones that
are chatting in chat those aren't real
people that's me
pre-recorded yeah the chat is
pre-recorded uh this isn't
real I just happen to know what words
that you guys will be saying
next yeah so you're multitasking all of
us
yes yeah that's about it
then n uh again would like to remind you
guys that uh my merch is
out please please get it please buy it I
put a lot of effort into thinking about
the whole
theme
I I hope uh I hope you guys enjoy it
please buy the set it'll be cool I I I
feel like I did well too on the voice
acting not my best one but I do feel
like um I did pretty
good and just a reminder for you guys
um hello Heroes uh Generation 3
oh I mean h life ID Generation 3 Hol
Heroes they're having their treating
showcase
soon yeah nobody asked me to actually
promote
them um Zita uh Kayla and Kobo they'll
be debuting in that order and the day
after tomorrow it'll be Z showcase so be
sure that you guys don't miss
it
yeah so just a little reminder thank you
and I think that's all for me
actually thank you so much everyone for
coming to
the it was a fun birthday oh wait I I
should get rid of this
first yeah so it was a fun birthday uh
karaoke some scuffs but I feel like the
scuffs is just like my karma for
pre-recording I feel like that's karma
for me not singing live that's why it
was kind of scuffed I guess the universe
didn't want me to lie to you
guys
yeah wait is ending yeah I was expected
the stream to be much longer man I
regret not joining sooner don't worry
you're always the VOD
right yeah even this is recorded yeah
you were punished for lying I really was
yeah and um you know I don't want to get
teasy but
again I'm glad that I got to celebrate
my third uh birthday with you guys it
was it was really really fun to be
honest when my birthday came I didn't
expect that many people to actually
uh I didn't expect you guys to
actually still be hyped about my
birthday because we've been going for
like three years now
and it makes me really happy um I'm glad
that uh I'm still loved I'm glad that
I'm still
relevant I'm sorry it's getting dark so
soon yeah sorry
uh I hope you guys continue supporting
me and I hope that you guys will still
be here on my fourth birthday as
[Music]
well thank you for the pink supera yes
and for every Super Chat I'll be reading
on another on another
stream yeah we're still here don't worry
so yeah uh I hope that you guys will be
there then
also I think that's all for me I hope
you guys enjoyed the scoff carrier
Yi uh and who knows maybe next year I
might have my a birthday live also we
don't know no promises but who knows
right thank you so much everyone for
coming to
the this has been crazy and I am signing
out or to Crazy
bye-bye
[Music]
[Applause]
e
[Music]