[Music]
a
happy
[Music]
Halloween
a
[Music]
5% sorry I'm not moving smooth is in
front of the camera she's smoothing away
right right
now okay okay
5% what do you mean only
5% what Mason what do those 5% numbers
mean what you mean only
5% what there's a lots of Collectibles
okay cuz I would have been shocked that
just I played for 3 hours and this is
supposed to be like a what 14h hour game
something like that according to Google
yo gave me a heart
attack
5% yeah for completion but even then oh
wow so if you're if you're one of those
people who want to collect everything
who wants to catch them all then have
fun with this
game oh
[Music]
k k KR uh no k h
yeah I was that person I gave up oh you
played this game and you tried to
collect
everything and you gave up was it so
tough oh man I never do that when it
comes to
games ah welcome guys
[Music]
welcome I have to say I'm a little bit
tired uh
rly uh unfortunately um I will probably
wake up for the for the um the
stream maybe I should get a do pepper
maybe water is not good enough Dr Pepper
has coffeine in it right sleepy Jo yeah
I got enough sleep uh actually so my my
plan of waking and sleeping and waking
up earlier is so far
working
decently uh which means uh I'm a bit
tired cuz uh not that I didn't sleep
enough but I've been awake for maybe
longer than I usually uh am when I start
a stream no not even like I haven't been
awake for that long it's but still I
don't know I feel like U also my my my
apartment is still too hot and it makes
me feel tired as well uh well today so
will today be short should you really be
asking me that cuz then I say yes nobody
believes me
anyway no I don't know maybe until
midnight uh which is like uh 5
hours still no fix for the he heater no
well what the actually that's a
good question like what what I was
supposed to get a call and I didn't get
a call makes me mad I don't have time to
like run after all these
people uh you know what let me go to get
a Dr pepp the Dr
maybe open the
[Music]
window wait I don't have a cool one let
me get ice
cubes
[Laughter]
I
I hit my
[Laughter]
[Music]
toe what a great start uh I hit my toe
when I came back I know that scream did
you hear this scream I screamed because
I spilled I spilled ice Cubs when I
flipped over the tray cuz I'm not one of
those cool people who has a ice
dispenser like I don't I don't know
anyone who has that in my country like
I've seen it in so many TV shows people
having you hear that that's my Dr Pepper
people
wow oh people
have who needs an ASMR microphone right
who needs that super expensive ASMR
microphones who needs that yeah isn't it
like a pretty common thing in America
that's so cool you guys have cool things
there anyway I flipped the ice
tray I st
again my
[Music]
toe
to
am American always had one wow isn't
that like only expensive fridges that
come with that seems to be a given in in
the Glorious am American
land wow okay um I probably uh will need
to mess around uh and try to figure out
the controls again because I don't know
if
I uh
oh my toe hurts I think I broke my
[Laughter]
toe I need I need an
ambulance I
need call call 112 I need an
ambulance oh I broke my
toe
isn't it like pretty like frequent to
break your toe it does happen quite
often doesn't it you don't sometimes I
heard that people don't often don't even
know about it when they break their toe
right but you wear an ambulance oh hell
yeah
[Music]
baby hell yeah baby I
am oh where the hell am I where did I
get my s into what is this where am I
how do how do I play this
game
SN no is is so
loud oink oink oink
oink eat this
would be a waste to let the pepper
go to waste so okay what are we doing
what just happen how do I play this game
p
p and uh I'll turn it down on my end a
little bit you guys let me know if it's
too loud for you guys ever oh yeah this
is how you fight oh don't fall down
Alice uh today we'll have a little
giveaway uh what is
this
WOW golden
teeth which is
funny because I was just watching uh
desperate house wbes and i' I'm at the
part right now
where something happened with teeth you
know someone's teeth might have been
pulled out and it's uh pretty
[Laughter]
disturbing Pap your enthusiasm for
photography makes the library smell like
rotted fruit I'm certain these Solutions
are toxic
what what what does what why does the
liary smell like toxic fruit CU of his
hobby for
photography what what is
wow what is this is that
clock oh my god
um what was that H um The Game's ah a
bit quiet really oh God oh God
wait um these cockpits will be our mcham
our road into
assemblage the the Hat
guy we're going to have a little
giveaway this stream is not sponsored
however
uh
American
American Maggie mag
Maggie so kindly um is uh helping us do
a little giveaway we we is that a secret
is that a secret is that a secret ow ow
ow ow has a secret on how to die H help
my
health okay wait actually one second uh
might have been smart to prepare a
picture for you
guys with what you can win let me show
you ow my room is hot my room is so hot
why is it so
hot
oh can we win you no you cannot win me
so sure okay uh apparently
everything uh uhhuh so okay um for
example for
example oh thank you oh thank you JMA oh
yeah yeah I was I was already there but
um which one do we show so cute oh so
cute how about this one okay let's show
this one
safe oh okay so what do you what you can
win today is not necessarily related to
this game however it is related to the
creator of this game American McGee and
uh he has this homepage where he sells a
merchandise which looks absolutely
adorable for example that plushies these
plushies these plushies so cute if you
have a girlfriend you could try to win
one for your girlfriend or for yourself
if you like these kind of things I I
would love to have one they're adorable
and they are kind of like you know in
the aesthetic that American M Mr
American McGee seems to have mhm
adorable so how to win this basically
today throughout the stream I will be
telling you some letters some letters uh
um that
will end up
becoming
um your key your password for winning
these I will be giving away or we will
be American mgee will be giving away 10
of their plushies but these specific
ones the plushy dreadfuls they're called
plushy dreadfuls there's like uh they're
like the the word Dreadful is important
because it's like written in each um
item's uh name in the shop mhm mhm and
then uh yeah 10 of them so you must
however do the following things well I
will be throughout the stream giving you
the the letters so you must stay from
beginning to the end of the stream easy
you guys are used to that and and you
collect the letters it's like a puzzle
and then and you must follow me and
American McGee on
Twitter and and uh you
must mention um the online shop oh no
wait I will mention sorry I will mention
the online shop which is called
mysterious. American mge.com let me
write this down
here here you can already look through
it and see which plushy looks cute to
you what am I writing here
mysterious mysterious American Mech
g.com that's the website there there you
have like a choice of like Plushies that
you could get possibly so
H uh wait let me
check yeah
uh for now for now you just collect the
letters and then you will write a tweet
and I didn't decide down the hashtag
should we have a hashtag JMA should we
have a hashtag we we said the hashtag
right one
second we ah oh wait that we said we did
set a
hashtag American kiata I am Australian
excuse me one second let me put this
away cute they look
soft okay um let's say well
then American American K like what
what H what's a good what's a good uh
dreadfuls oh something with dreadfuls is
good no don't give me his last name that
sounds weird uh Ellis Kata returns
Ellis
Ella kada and the is that long Ki and
the dreadfuls is that long it's long but
who
cares okay it will be
um uh but do Jemma do we want them to
like use the hashtag and send a reply to
me and American Mickey or only the
hashtag is that enough
with the
hashtag k and the
dreadfuls just a hashtag okay and then
plus a
keyword
okay
giveaway okay okay understand though
we're doing a giveaway you can get uh
you may perhaps get a plushy uh from
that website mysterious. american.com
if you afterwards after the stream with
the keyword tweet out with the hashtag
kada and the dreadfuls doesn't matter if
it's capitalized or not uh and then uh
we will go through choose randomly 10
people and it doesn't matter where you
live in the world it will be shipped out
for free to anyone anywhere in the world
and it will go through American Mickey
so you need to follow him so he can DM
you to get your address and stuff uh but
yeah anyone can participate doesn't
matter where you live it it's not
limited to anything
okay okie doie great so thank you
American M for doing that it's so cute
normally I can't really do um giveaways
like that but yeah it's a nice way to
engage with the community so I am very
excited Japanese people can participate
too on my Korean Bros as well if you
want anywhere where you live doesn't
matter
American
Mac photo St should I wait let me write
the the person's
uh uh
Twitter very good you have to follow me
and American
Mickey
fall
follow
follow okay was the keybo given already
when to expect throughout the whole
stream okay I'll I'll give you the first
letter it's l like uh
London let's
go hry jealous I'll get this door open
oh thank you sir so kind of
you oh dear throwing A Clockwork bump in
common has multiple
benefits I
see uh it will divert enemies and damage
them when detonated I don't know have to
throw it anymore though how do I throw
it again I don't remember it's been too
long only actually it's only been like a
week or so where
where what was my key for
that Q
L gosh I hate it when all the windows
all the tabs closed sorry it's a little
bit scuffed right now
everything I'm a little bit over elmed
uh cute
cute cute ah oh thank you for telling
me
explosion oh there's still alive
[Music]
though I know I don't need the bombs
I'll just kill them like
that give me back my health thank thank
you what's your issue oh this is how it
get smaller again how do I
uh what's it out okay out for like uh
dodging this one to get small
oh okay okay we're remembering I
forgot oh no issue no issue here I'll
throw you some bombs I wonder how much
damage Mak oh what what are you what are
you what do you think you're
doing wait wait wait wait
wait always look where you
going always look where we're
going
okay well at least we got some distance
from that
give me those teeth not the head
no need for the head thank
you oh oh
ow what do you think you're
doing oh did that hurt you little face
oh my God uh I forgot how to do the
umbrella thing by the
way oh who who this was the guy with the
umbrella right oh wait see he doesn't oh
ow ow
he doesn't want to talk to
me
n what was it again with this
dude eat for umbrella okay okay come on
oh there it goes
and wait my e didn't work e didn't work
what you me I trusted
you why is it it's not
working
wait controls please control go
uh
controls
umbrella umbrella block e what is my
keybo like broken or
what n smash just smash smash all the KE
that's what I usually do thank you for
the advice I would have done that
anyway what's going on didn't
work lock on lock on then ah w Wait how
do I lock on again F
okay okay okay
buddy oh is that it again oh you can
shoot okay I was too
late let's
[Music]
go okay just give me your let us let us
do it again okay I want to do it again
come
on that was not it
okay here he
comes okay
okay yes of course I would like to
continue this is warm up warm up warm up
warm up
this oh no we're here
again okay the stream just
started welcome everyone so today we're
doing a
giveaway uh isn't that exciting I know I
know I know so we're doing a giveaway
with American McGee thank you so much
for letting me do
this what what uh we will be giving away
super cute Dreadful plushies by the
courtesy of Aman mck the website is
written down below
and uh yeah you should check it out and
then throughout the whole stream I'll be
giving away some letters uh what the
hell I'm giving away letters that you
have to put together and then put them
in a
tweet with the has Kiana and the
dreadfuls it does doesn't
matter uh what for phph Capital
capitalization or so you do with that
doesn't matter you can caps it all if
you want and then there will be a
lottery we will randomly choose 10
winners and you can choose whichever
plushy you want as long as it says
Dreadful on the name and it doesn't
matter where you live cuz it be it will
be sent for free to wherever your
location is oh my
God okay yes and now we will um play the
game the way it's supposed to be
[Laughter]
played yeah already have it all written
down I'll probably make a proper tweet
afterwards um but only the people who
are in the Stream who know the keyword
will be able to participate that's
that's why I'm doing the thing with the
keyword I I only want you guys to
participate not some
randos who want the cute plushies no no
no you need to work for
it
right it's not that
easy my audience deserves it deserves a
little Halloween
present okay okay it's the big gu
already there waiting for me please
don't shoot me now I'm on the rollong
now oh you're over there I didn't
realize I want to kill the small ones
first no what the hell where am I what
oh my
God
W it's cute how he whenever I drop that
bump they will pay attention to the bump
instead of me that's pretty
adorable okay so now what about you uh
uh wait sorry okay shoot
me
oh come
on okay here here
[Music]
I'm done with your
time to die time to pay your
bills I can't bebble K bubble is that a
real word follow me ah I will follow
you all righty all right all right uh I
need some help though that would be
nice yeah know that was totally my first
try
uh okay what are we going to do Mr Mr
mad earthquake what's happening I really
look like I know your judgment must be
severely
[Music]
impaired where are the Doos
though Sorry Sorry KF for scaring you I
didn't mean to scare you guys with the
title it's just uh I want to help the
Dos you guys are you're usually open to
sacrificing yourself to me anyway so I
don't know what you want from me how do
I do this again um that
way oh that feels good m a little bit of
a spy visit treat yourself treat
yourself before you wreck yourself treat
yourself before you godamn wreck I went
down too early I thought I was already
done okay small
small
Alice uh over there I
suppose have you guys caught a little
bit of the sports festival practice
today I didn't stream but a couple of
others were streaming BS was streaming
from my
team did you catch it yeah I what is
this have to blow it
up
no being small doesn't help me oh wait a
second I mean I see signs
here did I miss
something I need to shoot
something
shoot shoot that
thing
yeah great flying
bus well you know I practiced beforehand
and like flying for the Hoops itself is
not so much a problem and apparently
getting hit I I didn't get hit by the
arrows at all but I need to practice a
strategy a flying route to be able to
fly through all three of them in the
middle cuz that's what the others have
been trying to do yeah my flying was
consistent I didn't die at all the
others did die a couple times because
apparently I didn't think it would be so
easy to uh you know shoot someone down
while they're flying that fast it was
apparently
quite
manageable that was making me feel
pretty uh pressured
oh what you I was I was quite under some
pressure but I mean it was decent I got
what 40
points um at least I didn't die that's
like the most important thing and maybe
the only important thing oh
ah kind of the only important thing
there because if you die then you get
zero points and that's worse than
everything else and I think during the
actual sports festival there might be a
few people who are that unlucky to have
an accident like that and I want
to avoid
that so like you can do two TR tries you
can try two times um but if I get a
decent score the first time I will not
try the second time cuz that's so
risky right way too
[Applause]
risky wow what a
train
wow impressive train beautiful let's go
see we found the source of the shaking
but are those two quaking what are they
up to you'll never stop us silly Hatter
and Alice it's left you're too late the
arrogance the incable table maners they
are destroyers of Wonderland defilers
denuders der Rangers
Delight actually create that infernal
train to destroy Wonderland what does
that matter they deserve to
die put me down this put down no don't
steal him from me again battle time Miss
yeah hav't I been through enough
battles
o o what what what what what what n
abandon false hope forget the past the
damage is done let the Madness begin
resume the
Hing uh uh feel like I'm in a different
game right
now oh uh Bonk a
bonk it's falling apart
no B and pck H rodent let's
[Music]
go oh he took it apart well okay cool
thank
you that's so very
kind oh precious domain and the guests
all I really wanted was another
party where is that train going what's
its purpose tell me now there's no time
for whatever it is you want to talk
about it's time for tea talk train will
it's always time for tea last
night come on you although now it's time
for Dr Pepper friends got a pine
ding
ding my memories are shattered I'm more
of a green tea type believe the train
impedes me sometimes camel you promised
ask the one who helps them what helps
themselves often fruit te yummy fruit te
yes very pity he deserved to die and I'm
about to drown in tea in
ignorance ignorance tea what kind of tea
is
that ignorance
tea that sounds uh not very yummy we
must help her get out of
there caught me very own
ribon excuse works in mysterious ways
got oh I'm back on the real
world to bed AR wo a girl M bro what do
you think you're doing what comes
natural natural to me get away yeah get
the hell off of
me no no no Alice has other things to do
I see a
cat reminds me of my snow drop ly knew
her C but is there something here that I
I shouldn't be missing out on like a
secret no okay just wanted to check if
the game tells me it's only 5% completed
it feels like there's like so much I've
been missing out on like secret
collectibles no idea what those crates
contained it's the stuff of dreams as
close as I'm likely to come to exotic
places well don't give up your hope yet
maybe one day you'll be able to
travel soon soon the sea thing will be
over and you'll be able to travel sure
let's go to Japan
Alice where the sea the sea thing ice
can oh that's ice ice can reflect an
image and like Amber trap and preserve a
thing forever or until it melts aha UHA
yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah I thought about that
[Music]
before wait are there are there things
trapped in all of these oh there
are there's something in there too like
a sea monster is that
fish Ang oh that's an angle fish oh cute
I guess I don't know the teeth are not
looking that
cute
well that's how you keep Fish Fresh I
guess when you deliver them overseas uh
to countries who do not have the
pleasure of having their own ocean like
Australia the mangled mermaid I thought
we were not going there was what what
Alice change of plans would you mind
tell me about that I thought we were not
going there with some rough edges likes
everything rough are wager a handsome
offer have no idea an appointment like
speaking like different language how old
do you want to make this you should know
that doctor says I have a terrible
disease good
excuse so we're not going there okay
good good good Alice because I don't
know that's a smart idea we on to finish
dreaming paralytic addiction
disqualifies drunkards from any honest
means to acquire strong drink it
inhibits fear and shame and emboldens
the commission of desperate acts wonder
what became of
Chris
ah is this poster Carnival of
oddities oh is that from T
Bri with C the other the other day the
other week the East ends lousy with spec
spectacles and exhibitions fire eaters
and freaks this planet is likely to be
bloodthirsty flamboyant and melodramatic
with Saucy songs the audience will be ro
ro Rous and rowdy as the performance oh
de I don't know I me money you
spunk bucket e e e get those fat ass
whes out on the street or I'll come up
and brain snip you'll never get past
long
T what that word you just used L see if
I done maybe you Noti I'm not pissing me
drawers at the
prospect F little you'll make a nice
change bring you just several
no I don't want to and we have to go in
here after all
nah it's so
dark oh we're going from that side
huh
okayy okay well
um he's uh done for today I want her Tim
say say he'd likely died from a social
disease poor man never dreamed its name
was Jack splatter who is Jack
splatter is that wine or
beer oh I don't know it seems like the
atmosphere is actually kind of nice I
don't know it looks very warm and
uh the music is cute the piano music
cool is actually playing the
[Music]
piano that was time is in the piano here
because I don't see the piano player for
one moment reminded me of Luigi's
Mansion wasn't there like a piano
playing ghost and you didn't see like
who was playing the
piano you can order anything on the list
but don't expect to be served anything
but stale beer or Rock good chin yeah I
would like some Dr Pepper anyway you
know that's why we can't see the piano
player cuz it's played by a
[Music]
ghost yeah
surprise you won't give me what I want
I'll burn this dump of yours down to the
ground go away what do you want she's
done no
harm she hurt me feelings she hurt me me
feelings a oh she hurt you little
feeling I'm so sorry for you do you need
some soup some milk or some cookies or
something need a blanket
a
she hurt me feelings you burn someone's
place down because they hurt your
feelings that's not a good
excuse he koed me now I'm back in this
hell hole oh come on oh oh that's so
cool we're getting a new
[Music]
outfit oh what is
this that's funny it's like a underwater
level
huh makes sense because we just died and
in or not died we we we we we lost our
Consciousness in a restaurant called
wait what was what was it something with
mermaid
w
w oh oh nice moon what is that Moon
smoking W pretty
Aurora orora there's this really nice
song um from an artist that once
participated in uh the Euro Visions H I
want to go up there how do I get
up and yeah and I think it was called
Aurora was really pretty
song you guys should look it
up a
hello
um uh hey is that is that an
owl what the happened with that owl
no not that enemy again no no no no no
no no no no I'm not
ready not the house no I love my house
no don't do that to
them okay okay he's going to shoot some
at me again this time I will not
up right
[Music]
first
R thank you for the membership welcome
oh you got a cute cat picture tell me
more about your cat ah Dam it I was
distracted
oh I couldn't block he knocked me
out oh he's doing it
again that hurt
yes
uh isn't that called Bigfoot what are
they
call what am I thinking
of but this is a way more disturbing
because I love owls I have a special
connection with owls okay it's not cool
what is this horse doing
there can I like blow it
up I can oh that was
a that was just like I didn't even think
that would really work but okay I got a
bottle
was there a hint there ah there kind of
was oh yeah yeah
bottle what do you mean is that why M
turned out the way she did what do you
mean with that she turned out
fine close
one I helped myself there a little bit
by Leading myself to death
free movement no movement is fine that
is not movement wait wait wait wait wait
I want to look at that
what
oh it looks
friendly how do how do I
even that's so close I almost feel like
I just need to give it another
try I don't need to
jump really oh wait a second I just need
to go h
there we
go I don't know what's more beautiful
the moon the Aurora or that bottle that
chip in the
bottle it's all
beautiful okay hey buddy let me pass
please
well thank you for at least not oh
that's why you said I don't need to
[Laughter]
jum uh well thank you now I finally saw
that and don't have
to embarrass myself anymore what do you
mean I'm lagging is the stream
laggy no no no no no no
no
we're in nice bir bread mode thank you
stream is fine okay good good you can
break the Stars what I didn't know oh
well do they have uh do they have um uh
teeth
inside okay let me break these
ones was there a dash button no right I
asked that before and you guys I think
said dodging is basically dashing go go
go go go ah
what the hell did I just do there is
there something secret
no okay after a couple tries we made
it another bird what's our problem with
[Music]
birds new weapon a horsey stick a horsey
broomstick the torturing all these birds
what what does Mee have against Birds
yeah
right what have they done to
you who the hobby horse destroy all
obstacles with unbridled power Stampede
through the opposition and smashing hit
I love that I love that advertisement
the hobby hor smashes for weak surfaces
with ease ooh it's like a hammer it can
also break for enemy defenses oh cool
also that stupid annoying
enemy now hold on I don't have to wait
for his Fireballs anymore ice
SN Hello nice to meet you you got cute
uh uh
socks strip socks huh cute um can I how
do I even use the the the hammer how do
I even use
that did I tell me the button on how to
use
it
no does he not come out when I'm close
to him no I I would need the hammer now
he doesn't do it ah
R oh but there he came out for me thank
you so r
r oh no mercy
oh get smashed no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no you can go back into
the ground
buddy what if I want to go back to my
okay okay no more
playing ow ow ow what is that cold
breath does that hurt me a
lot oh it kind of like freezes me for a
moment but it doesn't really seem to do
damage where's Bo oh
oh remember to spend your teeth within
the weapons menu oh thank you for
reminding me I actually forgot and
weapons I got 700 oh should I upgrade
the hobby
horse what's more
important can knock back and knock down
even the heav of enemies blade knife oh
you guys also say blade
okay
hi
okay it's the main weapon so I guess
it's
smart all
right any
secrets
I don't know is that supposed to be a
secret is that supposed to be a
secret oh I hear a
snot is it here there's something up
there but I guess I can't go there just
yet snot are you
here
uh
oh oh that feels good oh no what
happened with your bills I thought they
only have problems with h toi but it
seems like they have problems with Holo
rodents as well oh that is unfortunate
where is that stupid snoot where is that
snoot did I miss the
snoot not
yet go get that golden
tooth but how do I get up
there
can I can I even I don't think ah not
not waet go
back okay take
this this
s and jump from here to here oh glasses
a memory grave news the ship was crushed
and her crew lost she was not built for
navigating the Arctic Ice Fields the
recent competition of governments in
fitting out polar Expeditions is a
needless waste of human
life all right wait we came from here H
but I still later have to get up
there am I going to get a way to get up
there
later another bird now what's that bird
is that a
doodle don't they look kind of
different I'm waiting for the day when
we get a doo
for that's duck a doo for whole life I'm
waiting for
it couldn't I blow this up with the bomb
as
well
hello ah
ah yeah two at on oh no problem I'll
take you
all but the the the hammer I mean it's
nice and feels powerful but it's kind of
uh
slow ow not again not again buk bunk
hammer it doesn't even feel that strong
but it's probably because I'm used to um
my sword huh my my
knife BK
Bonk
no what happened with you my friend what
happened what did they do to you or did
you just come here for a
vacation just came vacation and then you
were like that's a little bit too
cold not
quite not quite the right temperature
for
me the knife has higher DPS
[Music]
H I don't want to give up on the hammer
just
yet oh do I want to fall down there
already not yet
there's one here
too ah aha okay first we go here cuz
there's a a
bottle o there we
go
oh oh
okay and then we go down here
m is that an auto save can I
see Dy sh dear
game all right I'll give you guys a
second letter
now oh Like
Oxygen write that down write that down
but don't say what the other letter
was only people who are here from the
beginning must
know oh y what do I
do aha oh there's a secret platform
[Music]
there tee tee tee H what does that
mean Alice Watson is this girl's name I
know you think it might be Alice mecky
no it's Alice
Watson just one letter just one letter
just one
letter
[Music]
o and
go
okay picnic
basket I said I would do more picnics
this summer and I ended up only doing
one picnic I got this cute picnic basket
and I only used it once how unfortunate
did I miss something
no how unfortunate was that not just up
there wait something something
here oh it only pops up when I'm close
to it all
right one is a lot for you what you
mean I
mean it's more than I ever did before I
guess I think that was my first like
proper picbe oh what is
this oh I want to did I choose the wrong
direction
[Music]
is wow okay um excuse
me okay at least now we get a second try
cuz this is
fun maybe I go right let me check out
what's on the right side those CBS those
CBS
man save save save save safe save save
oh those curves are almost as big as no
way to S by curves y
oh
oh nice nice nice gra slowly slowly oh
yeah oh yeah oh oh who left that poop on
the road
disgusting you got to pick up your dogs
poop for God's sake that's the wrong
direction it but I arrived
hello
fishies they reaction to me am I not
scary I don't even need that am I right
now he went into the ground oh and you
are here okay let me try
this break the defense oh no no no no no
no no no no
no okay okay no I have one I thought you
only do two for
God okay I broke his defense I
think no not again no no
no why no it's so
slow you piss piss me off don't you know
that by now you you
pissed me off so
much can't help
man oh oh I've had it up to here I've
had it up to here with this stupid
mob
you're lucky I spawned so close to
you you're
lucky you're lucky little
you hear those
blers I hear a
snoop can you
not
uhoh
uhoh I really I really don't like
fighting this dude no I don't like it it
says it breakes his defense but it it
kind of
like okay I'm getting really mad I'm
getting really mad I'm getting really
mad it doesn't it might I mean it the
damage goes through
but it doesn't like break his
shield oh
oh
en
stupid you are such an
idiot think that's going to help you
ramming your body on me I don't like you
any more than
before no no no
no I never want to see you again yeah
little angle don't know I don't know
about those camera angles sometimes it's
really difficult to deal
with destroyed him
finally snail oh it's got cute flowers
on it what a pretty
shell where is
your where is your snake snail I only
see the shell or do I go inside am I
going to become snail am
snail it's kind of spoopy oh I went
in I went in oh should I have not oh I
went intoo early maybe I should have
first jumped upwards oh no oh Alice
riddle me this haven't seen this game in
forever yeah it's nostalgic how is the
Queen of Hearts like a typhoon
you a ridd how is the Queen of Hearts
like a ton typhoon both are powerful
both are
indiscriminately destructive both are C
isn't all of this in all ways but the
typhoon doesn't mean to
be I suppose this is the right answer
you never cease to
amaze thank you oh I'm getting a reward
for that Rose paint paint the rose red
oh what is
this uh oh did I do something
stupid I'm so sorry don't cry don't
cry what that made me go outside what
did I miss something now it's closed
what a piece of
heart what was that about
get four you get an extra life oh I want
that I would like that can I go back in
let me in let me in let me
in
okay well I ridd is fun oops whoop
whoop wouldn't mind getting some more
rles they seem fairly easy if it's if
it's that easy to get a piece of heart
more
please
oo
okay
uh tooth
teeth should we go over there first did
I not miss a
snoot no well I mean I heard one over
there already though I guess there's one
here too or is that the same
one I
don't I don't see it I don't even hear
it but it's already telling me about it
maybe it's over
there you're really bad at hiding snooty
SN this
not oh Golden
Tee my favorite do we get a memory or
something like that as
well
m
oh yes we do
so model making all fine and good but a
waste of a perfectly good bottle I could
fill it with gin for thret oh she would
love delans cuz they also really
value uh botles I love her accent I love
that accent I want to speak English like
that thank you for the membership
welcome egg you are now
egg I would love to make scrambled eggs
out of
you you you you would you would you be
interested in that
too scramble eggs for
breakfast I need more than one egg
though I need more than one one is
really basically nothing why does one
egg feel like so much more when it's a
like a like a fried egg rather than
scrambled egg why and it feels also much
more when it's just a cooked egg
fascinating isn't it wow that jump was a
million times
better oh
hello can you not dive into me I didn't
give you permission where are you where
are
you don't
don't I hope that death was painful for
you lot of protein egg surface area is
larger with what scramble eggs lose
their water while fried egg ston oh we
got some actual real knowledge
here I come for the membership thank you
which way should I
go there's teeth over there
help help help help
[Music]
help is this a
secret is this a secret or is this the
real path uh looks like the real
path ah can I not get back up come on
come on
yes J Jump
[Music]
JP I don't think I can't go back unless
it spawns me
there yeah I don't think it did
H that was that was a good
encounter no I can't go
back heard more eggs we needed oh
welcome thank you egg egg egg I want to
go back back is that not an
option oh but there's something
here oh oh wait oh is that the other
side if I went that one path
first I want those golden te come on I
could have uh
come back for that door wait wait what
what what here here here give me the
golden tea please
[Music]
please ah they're on the little platform
okay
hold okay okay okay I got them I got
them please take my piece of
my yeah you know um um eggs are very
versatile just like glasses but eggs are
even more versatile I would say because
you can get like you can make a chicken
out of it you can did you know that if
you have an
egg you could get a chicken out of it
and that chicken could give you more
eggs it's like an endless Source an
endless sorts of eggs and with those
eggs you can make more chickens and then
you can make a like a whole Army of
chickens did you know you can eat the
chickens and the eggs it's like a a
paradox the whole existence of an egg is
a paradox did you realize that guys did
you know about
that o it doesn't want to break is it
too big do I need to do I need to
upgrade my hammer for this
one know
[Music]
hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi what does that
mean
oh a cow there's a cow over
[Music]
there do you think it will see me I hope
it will not come
[Music]
you better come aboard Alice you're
doomed of course we're doomed of course
well how motivating how reassuring but
not for us get there's an infinite
amount of Hope but not for us wow that's
that's such a nice thing to say they
want my ship I think no Iris for me ever
we are almost relatives you're related
to soup Admiral super what I have an
idea we'll leave this man and go to
carpent his show it's better than Gaff
Carpenter promises done quite seriously
can't please stop best now Admiral or
the Sharks will have us for lunch oh no
no the bottle broke the ship is free
you're not supposed to free the ship
you're supposed to stay in the
bottle oh
no well oh now we're going to be
underwater before we were not is that
like a griffin shape in front of the
boat avoid shipwreck sharks Canon fire
and mines oh are we going to be
controlling the ship that sounds like
fun press left Mouse button to fire
cannons and right Mouse button to fire
Death charges death charges
okay
cool oh this point of view oh that's
F I can't hit them a do I get points for
hitting them it's like a different game
now I oh
Dam that's cool it gives me a little bit
of
a time to calm down because I was so mad
at the
mobs it lags for a
moment oh come
on wait 2,000 oh it does give me points
wait is there like a minimum of points
that I have
to
accomplish it's getting more more
sh why do I go into why do I Ram them I
don't
know I don't know
oh no why did I do
in might sa help me please I'm not good
with controlling
shits I and Takami
too
sorry this is what you call uh self
irony you got to make fun of yourself
sometimes you know oh dear how do I hit
that
crab I did oh um um how long is
this this how long is this uh-oh uhoh oh
oh
oh I know she need all this Skittle oh
the crab on the bottom I can
hit well at least I
thought okay okay okay
no it looks like it's about to end
though the clutch the clutch
guys
oh
the clutch we're
[Music]
safe T
lips
H self bur
yeah
ow my body aches all over oh that's a
pretty dress to quickly my sheeps are
wrecking and I am to I love that that
might be my favorite their
ships you for a sailor if memory serves
you a station Master of the Looking
Glass
Line This is just noyal cosplaying as M
redundant the NIT said never holiday
loyal as a bulldog going in a different
direction my aunt fny if I had one going
off the rails more like bloody disaster
now I'm shess the old rail rout dead and
this new thing's a monstrosity he never
runs on time Engineers asleep at the
trains never are on time can't hurt me
say no more Nots as good as a
wink he talking we avoid speaking about
the thing whose name should not be
spoken hearing something useful about
this new train would make for a change
you don't respect of others go ask your
questions and smart remarks to
Caterpillar H caterpillar Admiral really
please I remember the C train I'll just
say we've escaped a contaminating
corruption I don't remember cow in still
but I don't want cow and ell I want to
stop it I must stop it to save myself
she looks gorgeous look at her nonsense
speak more nonsense diversions Rule The
Day The Show Must Go On And The Show
Must Go On baby we weren't yeah well
never mind here's a ticket for the show
turle Turtle I don't remember a mock
Turtle it's a goat it's a mock wait it's
not a cow that's not a
cow I guess so I guess the body is uh
wait which which way am I supposed to go
first okay you want me to go there so
but wait I did I is this just where I
arrived are you
crying a I mean okay the body here that
that's a turtle but his face that's a
cow that's not a
goat he looks so
sad
a poor
boy uh I think it's good that I came
back cuz there's a secret
nice
yeah what do we have what do we have
oh super special memory scoundrel was
fitted with grotesque headgear if I have
ever owned an accessory that unseemly
I'd burn it destroy all evidence of it
and deny its existence I value my
reputation look at that beautiful dress
I'm in love where can I buy that what
brand is
that is that GUI over sa
huh how much was
that maybe I can get like a sponsorship
deal or
something sponsorship with
Gucci
Taki
okay wait why did it show me this in the
first place Ah that's the that's the
front part of my ship ah another bird
dead bird down bird
down oh no
fishies again I don't know which way to
go I'm going to go here
first wait wait wait what what what ah
there's a path here I was like hey am I
floating is this like a gimmick on this
level
okay is K down she sounds
different I was reading you comment and
now I'm really
down K Down K down h no what i s
different from usual do I do I I I don't
really think
so I sound like Tel okay good
good to
know
[Music]
uh smart smart
J you sound good to me you sound fine
come on
on I might have sounded a bit different
uh the practice though I don't know I
was just like you know I knew the others
were streaming but I felt like maybe uh
I don't know I felt like cuz I wasn't
streaming I was just like vibing and
chilling I was
uh you know how uh
yesterday yeah yesterday I played a
little Minecraft didn't I it already
feels like 3 days ago I don't know why
but um is there nothing here H what did
I come here for did I just was there
teeth here or what I already forgot
short time
memory break chest
H wait what chest oh those are ah things
I can break with the hammer probably
oh okay okay is there
more no okay so I was saying and
yesterday I play a little Minecraft
right and then M stand by yesterday in
my secret stream I don't know how she
knew about it she found out about my
stream and then she was like helping me
out a little bit and then yesterday she
already kind of like asked me to perhaps
uh if
possible help her today with
translations
so and I was able to come to the
practice thankfully
today secret stream yeah yeah yeah I
didn't stream I didn't stream what are
you talking
about H and then H yeah I came in and uh
into the voice chat and M Senai was like
ah stay stay in this channel stream is
about to start uh would you would you
help me a bit with translating I'm like
sure sure sure sure but I don't know it
felt um I didn't want to everyone cuz
there were so many people everyone was
like talking and I felt bad I didn't
want to interrupt anyone so I ended up
typing almost
everything ah oh it was it was two days
ago it wasn't yesterday right okay now I
remember yesterday was uh for S by the
collaboration oh that's going to eat me
isn't
it I'm not going to fall for
that maybe I am maybe I am going to fall
for that
the Tye translation seemed to work well
I was like speed
[Music]
typing maybe like
this what
die why do you not die what's what's
what's what's what what I'll just try
to okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay okay
okay
yeah I was typing typing typing typing
but for my team only Bales was there
anyway and Bales Japanese is pretty good
so I don't think she really needed the
translations no no wait I'm a I'm a join
too yeah yeah yeah so it was I was only
really translating for they had Iris in
the other team so I think Iris was
translating for
them
yeah Amma did so well in the obstacle
course she was like so fast but then at
the end she was kind of stuck in the on
the in the last part in the magma oh did
I skip something things I feel like I
did are we going uh back
home n
is it a
memory yeah Iris was also streaming so I
supposed she was just trying to explain
to her stream in the library the night
of the fire the added to the great was
dead when I went upstairs to bed with
Diner if it wasn't I may be responsible
for my family's deaths H
oh oh we got a second
key what does that
mean
what was that me I'm
back hello thanks for waiting I was just
uh having a little idle meeting behind
that door don't mind Alice she also
needs to go for little little girls
[Music]
sometimes
nice what what what what who are
you who are you excuse me can you not no
not another guy that I have to block
with my umbrella oh are you done
oh what how do I fight you you're a
ghost shoot him you can shoot
him oh
no doesn't feel like it does damage but
he doesn't shoot shoot any more Bots at
me
oh oh it did work this
time
oh
uhoh how many times we going to do this
huh oh there we go the bong Cammer
worked now now he's a real ghost we
helped him we did a good thing guys he
seemed to be
stuck he was having a little time Loop
moment
there uh I was over there already right
wait I was trying to get over there but
I died didn't I there's still chests
over there what it or am I mixing up
things right now how would I get over
there from here not really
a it wait that must be
secret yeah okay
okay
hold oh wait I should have maybe checked
before I jumped all
right all
right anyway um so practice went pretty
well I would say
m i I didn't really participate in the
PVP because I'm not part of the team the
only one that participates in PvP from
my team who was there was Bales the
other ones are uh GAA
and Ena GAA and Ena uh Ena said she
would practice or try to
practice on her own
time but well PVP you kind of need other
people to help practice with you so both
on S offered herself to um help I think
she did or did she do that uh did she
offer to help
me I'm pleased you love my with my
elytra I'm not sure she offered to help
with something else great painter
captures a true likeness the camera
helps an amateur
come yeah uh I think I think it should
be fine
[Music]
though
we just need basically like we just need
you good and you know we need them to
just kill
everyone both on I said that the best
thing to do in that
PVP uh game would be to just one person
should focus on getting the ore and the
other person should focus uh the other
two people should focus on killing the
other
team I think that was her strategy cuz
Bon zba was apparently really really
good at it last year what what just
happened I can't focus on two things at
once uh no no no no don't go don't go
down so fast oh wait I should just stand
on it why am I hammering
it
eh how do I there we
go yeah Bon ire was uh winning in the
winning team last year against super
Senai and super Senai was
like last year Senai you destroyed me
this year at least we have you in a team
so we got a really strong predator in
our team although wait but ban
Senai wait is she even in the team for
PVP she's she's one of the Birdman darts
participants why is there two flowers
was
here does this one do something
something
else oh that wasn't done
anyway axes are good for PVP I think the
only weapons that they get to use are
the pickaxes right I think that was the
only thing that they were able to
use uhhuh
Keyhole oh I see I see thank you thank
you
as far as I was able to observe only
pickaxes were a choice and everyone got
a
helmet
yeah oh it looked like a lot of fun but
they were practicing afterwards a lot
too
so yeah kind of need
to get a good team coordination going in
order to win that
one so maybe good on Ina and Bales can
practice a little
bit uh
together before uh Saturday I hope they
will I hope they
will good seems to be like kind of busy
though all
righty got some special teeth for my
grandma
here yeah yeah beautiful teeth thanks
Grandma they need practice Yeah they
need practice other ones have been
taking it so seriously and practicing so
much I didn't think everyone would take
this whole sports festival that
serious Anan is uh I don't know how
serious they're taking
it I think it's it should be mostly
about having fun but uh the the Japanese
members are just really really good at
this kind of stuff maybe because they
already participated last last year it
makes them feel like very
motivated for this year they don't just
want to
lose they can't have that no no
what What Lies Beneath this patina of
Civility Something Wicked I'll wager oh
dear should I be worried it looks
beautiful
though oh
oh are the seahorses going to attack me
oh no that looks
nice we could maybe live here huh what
do you think fish
lady oh my God You' got a nice body but
a really freaky
[Music]
head let's check out that stuff over
there comp is what makes it fun
yeah yeah I am looking forward to it
very
much I hope that we will not be a big
disappointment to subu
Senpai super Senai is uh kind of feels
like the whole team white leader to
mea is not the whole team white leader
but she's she's the leader of her own
team at
least she was very very helpful
today it felt like she was uh my
kindergarten there's no time to waste
there's no time at all ah there's never
a time I know I'm timeless after all can
you survive the pass what what is this
is this like a a a challenge of course I
can survive
it no I don't think I can no I don't
think I can
if if this is like a thing where you
have to uh battle a ton of people
uh not so sure about
that do they give me HP
back that ah oh I'm going to
lose this no no no no no this is a one
time only thing I see I'm already losing
no no no let me get out of here no no no
no
I need healing and I need a better
camera better camera
angle that's a papa grinder even work I
don't know
man oh yeah it
does success what what what wait wait
wait wait wait come don't double you've
already missed the
train um
oh thank God I thought I wouldn't be
able to get my
reward oh is that the second piece of
heart ah nand
CLE nand thund what the hell man that
was so unnecessary nailed it I thought
there would be more enemies I was about
to like just throw the towel give up
from the
Geo
oh it was surviving a certain amount of
time not killing all of them that is
very very nice I could have just run
away the whole
time I did not realize that that was
what that
meant sorry by the way guys I feel like
today like I'm trying to tell you guys
stories and all that but uh
[Music]
if I keep on losing track of what the
hell I'm trying to say is this even is
this where I came
from
memory Thanks for the Memories even
though they weren't so great this is
kind of like Alice's theme song I would
say just watching you play as Fone thank
you thank
you here's the f
d did you guys learn some
German yesterday even though we weren't
speaking English I hope I hope you were
able to pick up a little bit I was
thinking while I was putting together
those slides I was thinking I got to do
another German teaching stream where I
teach you guys the Australian
dialect where am
I want to teach you German Australian
dialect words cuz like I was looking up
to be honest like I I said I said it
myself I think during the stream
yesterday yeah I said it in Japanese but
like I normally when I speak German I
don't speak dialect to be honest at
least not very big noticeable dialect a
lot of my friends do my or my for
example in my school most of my school
friends did did I just miss a
snoot or is it
above it might be above yeah
um probably because most of my school
friends came from the countryside but
but even if you're raced uh in the city
in Australia a lot of
people still speak quite a lot of uh
dialect my mom
does I know how you feel snooty
snoot I know how that feels come on let
it out let it all out it feels so much
better thank you I need to sneeze again
I feel like I need to sneeze again
oh this is something I must have missed
uh in the beginning
[Music]
H uh where was I oh yeah German German
German do I need to go back here I don't
think I need to okay where do we go next
German and forai actually uh stayed with
me in voice chat for so long after the
stream we were talking for
hours I don't know it was just like
really easy to talk with
[Music]
her I don't know we were like talking
like a freaking water uh fall wait
that's not the word wa wait wait
waterfall
no wait it is drifting ruin no don't
ruin me no not what are you what are you
what are you what are you going to
do okay chill ouch
what oh oh oh oh that was easy that was
freaking easy are you just uh showing me
a new enemy I guess so thought it was a
boss
monster um yeah yeah so I was saying
fora me we were talking for so
long we talked about so many different
topics and I just felt
like with I don't know the for f i felt
like we both really can relate to one
another so
well oh dude come back what you I guess
you're just gone now
huh like there's I feel like there's
certain worries that
but other other gen mates maybe don't
understand that
well and with I felt like I don't know
we understood each
other
yeah it was really really nice we talked
a lot of about a lot of things we talked
about uh some things that I will not
tell
you and we talked about oh yeah there's
a secret path
there
what we talked
about uh
equipment and about the streps and about
the audience and we talk
about whole live in
general and about all worries and all
kinds of things and it's so weird
because like we don't even we didn't
even like know each other that well
until so recently but we connected
immediately like we clicked
immediately made me really
happy did you say good things about
us of course no it wasn't really much
about the viewership or so
wasn't much about kfp it was kind
of like I don't know a lot of things but
it was more like private
so yeah I just want to let you guys know
that I feel like I found a friend in
forai I hope we'll see more of us
together a yeah I think you
will I want to get that memory excuse me
thank
you I would like to get my memories back
wait did I oh yeah I
did oh oh my my bottles I I dropped my
bottles here and there I need to recycle
them okay I'm sorry for dropping them to
begin with in this beautiful
ocean
aha a theater a future how
wonderful I wonder know what's playing
tonight I can upgrade my horse soon do I
want
to look forward to holot talk oh yeah
yeah yeah yeah I am almost done with the
second gen and Gamers I actually already
did uh fubuki sampai so with if I do
four more holot talks I should
be uh able to start with the F gen
and in the first I already did Min Senai
as well cuz she was my first one but who
knows maybe I'll um do another interview
with her again
eventually not so soon though I want to
give it more
time oh another path here I don't want
to go in here I didn't want
to I didn't want to go into the
flower no no I want to give them their
own episode one each no no no no no no
no no no no no I don't think
it's
fair they all sh should have their
moment their episode to shine and talk
about everything uh about their
themselves and their history and all
that I don't I feel like you
know having whole talk with two people
at once we we
I've considered it before because of
like h of stars and stuff but it it
feels like it would be a really
difficult thing
to manage
cuz having the spotlight on two people
at once and giving them questions that
mostly
will uh oh God
ah mostly will have to
be
about both of of them as an individual
even though you have both of them on the
on the couch I don't know there will be
so many times where the
other uh guest would just be sitting
there and nodding and nodding and
nodding where is this
dude
sh why is not
working where are
you
oh oh now there we go
oh oh
yeah come on trying to throw some bombs
at
me bunk bunk bunk and he's uh ascending
descending ascending he's
ascending h
huh I think you guys know what I mean I
think you guys
understand I think the the one person
per episode is the smartest way to do
it
yeah
otherwise uh I don't know I can't quite
focus well on them how do I get up there
also is that a nose over there that's a
nose did I miss
it didn't I come from there how do I
should I go should I go back I feel like
I have to go
back
no okay I'm coming for
you where are you where are
you so around the corner isn't
it how did I miss
that one might eclipse the other
guest yeah I don't think it's fair were
you here since
before do you come here often
snoot
oh
oh Asylum when oh don't ask me that you
got to ask that American me son
he
probably doesn't have an answer even
though as sces but
I wouldn't
mind playing that whenever that comes
out Asylum that sounds like a horror
game if you ask me when I think of
[Music]
asylums I don't know there's some some
experience that I had recently in Asylum
that kind of ruins all of that for
me I don't know if I want to go back to
an asylum that
soon ahuh bump
ah I need to shoot it from the other
side or
what
oh wait what from
here okay I've got the right angle fill
it up quick
nice no no I'm I'm aware that it
probably wouldn't be a horror game
but you know I still don't like Asylum
that gives me uh
flashbacks so I'm okay with him taking
some more
time as long as it comes out eventually
that would be nice
[Music]
yeah the for the people who don't know
what I'm talking about this game is
supposed to get a sequel at some point
but isn't it a prequel anyway supposed
the series is supposed to get a new uh
Edition at some point and American mege
has been working on it for a long time
with the support of like uh people on
patreon I guess
h yeah yeah a third game this is the
second
one oh wow that looks
pretty
wow kind of reminds me of the theater
that I went to in London but I guess all
theaters kind of look like this I don't
really go to theaters often so I don't
have many examples can I not open that
up let me in I what do you mean I don't
have a ticket well yeah but I want to
buy how much is it I I brought teeth you
can maybe exchange them for
money teeth yes teeth you need teeth no
you got your own
huh yeah how about you add some teeth to
your hands or something who says teeth
must be in the mouth look at how pretty
my dress is
glowing what what the
hell wait wait wait why can't I not go
anywhere what is
[Music]
that
I need to talk to
you
hello
hello there miss something
here teeth on hands yeah what's the
problem oh wait oh I thought this was
where I came
through I thought this was the
entrance C KY
uh uh a Alice delighted to see you again
my dear your rival filled with fortunat
ality itself oh really I didn't even
know my pregnant show is about to pop it
requires only pregnant your velocity I
don't have much experience but I do need
to reconstruct but my we can bar have a
nice screwdriver Nearly New or a nice
Hammer if you There's A Train That's
corrupting Wonderland she doesn't even
listen she's like I don't have time to
destroy it most vitous no doubt will
address that monstrosity directly as to
say eventually now let's intermediate
more she's really good at dealing with
all these crackheads hysterical foul-ups
some of the show's requisites need to be
gathered what look the munificent script
needs fetching
the right is overly imaginative in
exploring several
endings then you'll need to assemble the
show's tuned Deft music and finally
gather Our
Stars the show's Tasty N tasteful
performers you should leave now the
essentiality of H can you not stress me
no hardly seems you're ready for the
show why can't you assemble these things
yourself exactly has Arrangements ducks
in a row fish to fry calls to
newcast WR then we can batter or clatter
or matter is the case b or clatter or to
canorus to a person distinguished
repudiation I blush at the nationality
he's an octopus by the by lives over
that way T
octopus all
right I will uh be on the lookout for an
octopus
then what about this boy here couldn't
he do these
Rands unbelievable inconceivable I
say okay let's go camping we got to pick
up the taco dais yeah yeah oh oh wait oh
all the way over there
okay the quest to
find know my oh hello you're
sufficiently fortified to kick some ass
boot these creatures never reach these
creatures
never why why are you feeling like you
can't
swear is he aware that I'm streaming
this game but I'm already swearing so
much doesn't
matter you're welcome to swear oh
crab con con can crab
fun and we're going to do this first try
right
guys
does this
work nice Dad I thought that might work
I thought that might work you
know Got a Feeling I've got a
[Music]
feeling thank you for the membership
message that tonight come on shoot
going to be a good night that tonight's
going to be a good night I'm going to
send the remains of this crap over to
Callie's place cuz I don't really like
crap but but cie really likes it you
can't shoot cannons anymore can you a
too
bad get down get on your knees and breay
to You Queen oh another friend all right
no
problem let me deal with that M it's a
Crab
Festival another one oh two at once what
oh okay I could I was trying to open my
umbrella I
swear ow that didn't work who I one is
not
fair the time is of the essence
guys
quick quick destroy him crack the shell
crack it crack
it get down come
on well excuse
me oh God come send another one I think
if you're like if you open your umbrella
too early it doesn't work so I kind of
need to wait a little bit but sometimes
I wait too
long okay come on round two ding ding
ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding
light it with your cigarette that's fine
see this doesn't work when you have it
open too early ah and then he does it a
second time oh I don't have time for
this
buddy come
on smoking is not good for you
God come
on how many times do we do this umbrella
has to spin to work how how
oh oh that's the key thank you I didn't
realize the moment when you open the
umbrella it still spins but it doesn't
do that forever
huh
[Music]
okay all right we did it well that what
was indeed first
try I'll give you guys the third
letter V like uh
Victory oh like
V
VBA
[Music]
could you already guess the first word
there's more than one word guys and no
it's not love
kiata which makes me think maybe I
should have uh maybe I should have said
it to love kada
hm but you guys tell me that every day
so it's nothing new to
me
yeah I don't need you guys to tell me
that
I already know it La
Lau
La can can small Alice open the door
now what got to get up
there how would I do that
oh am I being stupid here what what am I
missing ah over there
what can I climb up or
what it says go
up after killing
everyone
what love
smoy oh there's another red clo
ah okay so first get up
here and then from there shoot
the second clock all right all right
from here already
no perhaps from
[Music]
here all right by the way you know we
haven't talked about at all
[Applause]
yet
is the Halloween collaboration stream I
just now realized those things look like
faces those stones the Halloween
collaboration stream yes yes yes you
guys wanted me to talk about the dja cuz
I didn't have my own point of view no
no
GA you left your hoodie here for someone
to clean it well good because it's it's
hella
dirty am I supposed to go in there
should I go to the other side first
here
uh is this just an extra will I be able
to come out again yeah the bottom
teeth oh should I I know I could I could
sell you I could deal you some teeth if
you
want try
platform first
really should I I love you crazy dances
fck thank
you should I go there
first the fish is the main way oh
okay all right I'll go here
first
uh
no oh it's going to be a pain in the ass
there better be a good reward wherever
I'm
going okay I don't even know what to say
about the the Halloween stream I talked
about it a little bit but uh
anyway it was an amazing stream wasn't
it oh yeah
that was only the second time I used VR
um but I'm so ready to figure out how to
use it for like a k stream or whatever
however I do want fingers so I do want
to get like a like a like a Model A
different one I did mention that before
as well you're sure
okay yeah and we are is however
extremely what extremely
exhausting
that helmet that VR helmet the goggles
they're so
heavy and by the end of the stream I was
like again covered in sweat at least
this time I wasn't covered in tears cuz
it was
all uh well I mean the one year
anniversary was was not I wasn't crying
because of sadness I was C because of
happiness I guess but
uh so this stream the hell way
the Halloween one was
uh
um fun
too but I didn't need to cry at least
should I go over there is that a
possibility what am I doing what what am
I collecting these for is this only tiny
small teeth really can I go over
there how no way it's only those couple
of teeth that I'm getting from
this that's it's not even worth it that
tooth is a
clue to
what oh look at that Landing I got all
of them so what
now
H oh wait no I didn't get all of them
maybe if I get all of them maybe I I get
some
reward I was a little worried about
what I actually I got to be honest I was
for um a lot of the stream I was pretty
like
overwhelmed because
um it was just too much uh
everything that was too much going
on I'll give this stuff
up and yeah it it was really good that I
didn't stream because I would have
stressed myself out so much I actually
had a lot of moments where I was just
chilling somewhere in the background not
talking at all and sometimes I found
gura doing the same so I joined her
smells like a ripy with a whiff of
halosis and Y wait I found the octopus
of unrecognized Genius a piss off more
empties than a Dublin Brewery the
carpenter sent me for starters the
carpenter is a pucel animous
parsimonious Petty foggy
such AIC sent me for this script I
need your needs are shy I need a drink
who cares I need those responsible for
my abortive career in Chains No Joy I
need to know what love is the world is
oh I cannot tell you that I need a do
some hide and seek hide and
seek we can play a little bit sure we
can deal what the hell do you want from
me we can play that's fine but I don't
know about
love time hiding his true colors gives
him an edge but can't conceal the way he
moves
okay uh ah okay that's a hint on finding
him or what a performance to die for the
daily
wallus
huh is that hint
to writing is an apt occupation for an
octopus he never runs out
of
funny that sounds like something Ena
would
say which is actually wait I didn't even
say that uh considering cuz she's a
she's a
tackle I didn't even consider that part
but I guess that's true too ah no come
on come on
on so yeah uh as I said there were a lot
of moments where I felt really really
overwhelmed as soon as Council joined in
it was like a council and hope it was 11
people 11 people at once being super
excited and going
like and I mean I have to agree they
were all super hilarious those those
outfits if you can't call them outfits
those I don't know what to call it those
uh uh appearances where gorgeous
fabulous
absolutely wonderful Divine
Exquisite um
yeah but I I was a bit stressed out here
and there um oh
my oh
my my favorite I think was
bails
bailes the way she looked like I don't
know a lot of people have been um
comparing it to Mike right Mike from
monster Inc and I agree I I see that I
can see that but I feel like not not
only that like not even considering that
just in general the whole design looked
like a freaking genius game character
design
like s was super cute too
yeah s the worm I I think yeah Bales and
S were my favorite s just being a
freaking gummy
[Music]
worm kind of need to go there
too
all right cracky mate that's hella
cracky getting all those teeth all right
and now we can I guess just jump over
there son of being small
fors M do I need that too
nah what is this one night only
Toons that's ding featuring The Fabulous
oyster sisters oyster
sisters interesting I hope they're cute
seeing all the models just made me burst
out
laughing yeah they looked amazing I'mma
is such a genius like I don't know
there's something about her art
Dad it's just the work of a genius what
is this
sus
I that is pretty sus I must say why is
there so many bottles there am I not
supposed to break them or am I supposed
to break
them there's a lot of flowers too are we
going to have a fight here he must be
like hiding in one of these bottles
no
oh is there a
hint I mean the cat did say that it's
like easy to find find out where he is
because of the way he moves and
stuff in
there in this
one can I actually break this
[Music]
one I don't think I
can but it points right at this one or
kind of maybe
not what about this
one no he's in the red one okay okay
perhaps oh wait I can see
him I can see
you well byebye yeah yeah I'll get you
again I'll play a bit more with
you this is
fun is there anything else to gain from
killing more of
those
bottles destroying more of them
what okay good stuff good stuff anything
else that's why what what about the
teeth what about the
teeth I see the teeth you don't have to
tell me about
it who guy just needs some love oh he
must be
lonely nice
bathtub all right wait what else do have
say it's already been so much
time I don't remember anything
uh so well nice Mir uh yeah uh I was uh
a lot of the time I was just chilling
with with gooda somewhere
because I don't know it was just too
much going on I uh I didn't want to talk
over the girls but everyone was talking
over one another anyway so I figured uh
yeah I'll just be quiet then
um and was I was just watching the
chaos enjoying it that way and sometimes
I found GAA chilling somewhere I think
she had like she felt pretty uh nauseous
from the
VR this is this is not the first time
that she feels like that with VR she had
the same issue with phasmophobia
right
damn damn must be
tough m
later on she changed though so she
changed to desktop mode so after that
she Felts better
thankfully what is this big gap
here we are can take some time getting
used to I don't feel nauseous from it
but I definitely feel extremely
exhausted from it cuz it's so heavy and
and it never sits right on my head
somehow ah not a okay I see not
a okay
okay hi hi hi hi hi can I shoot her from
here maybe
not oh
okay safe safe safe not made for onion
shapes excuse me excuse
me youa actually has two VR sets did you
know she has the Vive and the valve
because she originally I think she
ordered the valve and then then it
didn't come on time so she bought the
Val all the other way around the one
that you can buy on on
Amazon as opposed to the other one that
you can ah that you cannot buy on
Amazon I got the one that you can buy on
Amazon yeah which is like that's like
so uh she did that cuz it was about our
uh first year anniversary stream and it
was
like it would have been fine too even if
she uh how do I get there even if she
wouldn't have had the VR in
time it wasn't like a 100% necessity
okay take me diff take me it's not
like I'm not used to
it I want ah there's a elevating
platform come here wait
wait yeah anyway she says that one of
them fits her head much better than the
other so I wonder I don't want to
buy uh wait I think I have I have a Vive
right or do I have a v they sound so
similar I don't want to buy another one
of those just because of the head shape
or something I don't know I feel like
there must be something I can do about
although although the microphone
quality the M the microphone quality is
uh not so good with
my VR headset isn't it I've I've
listened to
the um to the Vault
sometimes
and the the ones with my with my headset
I think I'm not the only one though um
sound pretty low quality even though
it's so
expensive it's too late to send it back
cuz I really like used it
all where is you I don't really see
you where are you squidy
squint where are
you come on let me give you some love h
maybe there's a hint
oh do you see the Snows what the actual
hell do I have to send you over some
peppers as well
no no all right you are immune to it I
see that's how it is I don't see it
through the
bottle all right I'll just smash
everything
then no
problem he
hey
go where are you there's a
keyhole oh is is he in
here how did you get in here you sneaky
oh I guess there's other ways to get
here not you have me now you won't have
me again oh come on don't be so T there
about it I know you want me to have you
but I don't want you
though
I'm not going to humor you for much
longer you
understand I have to forgive him he
probably hasn't seen such a pretty girl
like me in a long
time
do we do this
again oh yeah okay wait was I not here
before what what am I doing come on
quick quick there's no time there's no
[Music]
time perfect timing this was all on
purpose I just wanted to stop on you
guys
[Music]
theut what where's the platform oh this
is the platform is
it this is where I came from right
okay so so so so so anyway H did you see
the new additions
to to my map it was in a in a different
season and I got that umbrella as
well yeah my map is really
cute really cute
map yeah the people who worked on all
that stuff I don't know they're
incredible like on in such a short
time they've all been creating these
things with so much passion memory
offers it and so much love and so much
so much
detail you
again
ow for example kanuru the music video
creator he made it in like a in like
a a week or so right the music video
so holy
but yeah he had like complete freedom to
do whatever he wanted with it
and it still it turn out like more than
we we would have ever imagined more than
we could have ever asked
for the music be yeah I love it it's so
funny it's I I feel like fans like real
fans who actually watch our streams
worked on that you can really feel that
and it's a big difference from someone
who doesn't watch your streams and
creates like I don't know a video of us
it's a big difference and I think
like the the
I laughed when you sang because I
actually can't blush what do you mean
you can't
blush I mean let's be real it's it's
really difficult to see blushing in
humans in general but you guys are
chickens so are you saying you can't
blush because you're a chicken all right
okay I understand that makes sense I
guess yeah I've seen you guys blush
before though seen your chicken's blush
before wait wait
close that was a close
one chili powder chicken
what no no no no you guys can blush you
just don't see it uh because of your
feathers but I can see it I can feel it
I can see it I can taste
it
are you in one of
these buddy come on don't hide from
me what are we doing this for stop
wasting my
time you need made it
seem hey hey don't use it on me who gave
you permission to use that on me huh it
was for for senpai's
chat not for my chat a fair cop You've
Won you're a good sport and no one died
join me in the light not yet unlike some
I don't Welsh what does that mean Welsh
what does that mean why is there battle
music no are we
good music fun music the carpenter
commissioned a strong and dance number
on morality art and good sense be damned
he demand mer silliness and arra the
B to a hero turn as death imagine I'll
bring the script to the theater you'll
bring it on your thank you no doubt
Caron has got you
collecting
musal good at the dentist be like please
give me some bottom
te she's still talking it's okay he's
done you talk a lot no wonder you don't
have
friends was there anything else I wanted
to mention did I write down
anything no no I'm not
sure my memory has failed me I don't
remember
anything from
the Halloween collab more letters oh let
me give you the next letter e like
um eat food I'm not terribly musical but
you the pipes are obstructed I can see
that why not do something about the
pipes are obstructed
you might do it for everyone here has an
excuse for doing nothing reminds me of
the
Asylum come on please help me I need
some help I sound
[Music]
weird what am I supposed to talk about
about the Halloween stream there was so
much going
on
did you guys like my costume I was
actually originally
thinking um or planning I think my first
thought was
um uh I I think it was
uh I wanted to be wanted to be a a a m a
maid girl I wanted to have a maid
outfit cute ma outfit maybe with cat
ears uh but then I realized wait a
second I'm releasing vampire
wouldn't it be kind of smart to have a
vampire outfit then so I ended up
changing that into vampire
quickly and it ended up looking so
cute kind of gave me um idle master
vampire Vibes if you know what I
mean what was that song again what was
that song again that idle Master song
was this trident Trident
Trent
what what does that mean what does that
mean vampire
girl how does the song go
[Music]
again
I love that
[Music]
song
okay chill chill chill I'm going I'm
going to stop singing you don't like the
song I don't know why it's a super cute
song how do you switch targets again
there was a button for switching targets
I don't remember which one it
was ah
huh t t okay
okay I was just trying to sing one of my
favorite songs for in the days and
you disturbing me like that what's your
problem huh what's your problem with
me think I'm not a good singer well I
think I am and that's the only thing
that matters and I know I am I know I am
you have something in your ears buddy
you know some people are toned and I
don't realize when people are good at
singing but I know I good at singing I
don't care what your opinion about that
is I don't care about your opinion on
the
matter okay here he
comes are you done complaining
now I guess
not
Oh Come Out me
bro hi
hi crack that shell real
good crab meat not really my thing but
H Exquisite
nundus
nice oh oh cute trumpets
trumpets I love
trumpets oh music the
music hey Mr
music
can you talk
normally that one do I guess all right
are we jumping up there huh wait where
are we going where are we going did we
come from
here I don't think we were here before
all right let me take care of
this Finding
Dory ah
Dory that reminds me of that clip from m
m Senai saying she always thought it was
fighting Nemo oh my God that's a bit bit
too many enemies don't you
think
uh okay focus kada
focus yeah focusing on the characters
would be a good idea as
well huh oh
God
ah who are you fighting ah you're
fighting the one on the
ground switching between weapons is not
my strong suit
guys oh we made it I didn't even go that
low on health what's with this dude
though I got to break you
huh oh I have a feeling and if I break
you I have to fight you no
oh well that's
funny
you've seen shark teeth we've seen the
Trident now just waiting to see a statue
of feet around you somewhere and it's uh
pretty
sus
function all right I'll get to you
Orchestra where do I have to go this
way no is this not where that's where it
came from no yeah yeah wait wait wait
over
here
what is there a secret
no oh
death okay dead beats let's
go dead beats are waiting for
us American
makea
no uh uh tab or maybe not I don't
[Music]
know
get out of here get out of
here I'm doing bad in this fight I don't
know
why holy
come on give me some help please
thank you okay okay okay okay uh
what
okay kill
him okay we need some
distance I thought I had my umbrella
out whatever doesn't matter DPS Rush D I
needed
that uh and smash it real
good
oh more
music and
Orchestra what is
it the N it's surely not lost perhaps
mislaid I suppose I'll have to help you
carry the tune better be light oh am I'm
going to be the I'm not ready know how I
don't know how to do
that
how is this a rib game
now
okay oh God no no
no it's lagging it actually
helps nailing it
easy
I messed up one and that's that's a
problem come on you can give me some
slack cut me some slack
please what's happening where was my
first try one mistaken repeat is that
fair guys you tell
me no
no I don't know guys if you're seeing
this on stream but it is
lagging every time when I'm in like
dialogues like that okay
you every
[Music]
time you see it
too should I push it later am I pushing
it too
early okay okay okay okay next
one up up right down left right R up
down
up I almost thought I pressed it early
and missed it there for a moment but we
good you need more volume in your voice
if you want to be a singer you to
quiet I've noticed that like my voice
I've noticed this like since a long time
ago since like years ago you might not
really notice uh with like these
microphones I think this is a thing that
you probably only notice when you speak
to someone in real
life um cuz the microphone I mean it it
boosts your volume when you speak but
I've always
been I've always had a a good volume in
my voice
see one day singing coach
Vault praised me for there's some people
who are like really really quiet huh and
then there's others who have this this
power in their
voice and it makes a big difference in
some
cases I see a cat where down one to go
oysters are the presumptive stars of the
show if you can wake them the world is
my oyster they say is that an oyster or
a clam it's two different things
right
wait break grid on the right you mean
you mean the one I just went through
right or did I miss
something it's a little bit dark in here
aha n hold on now let me heal myself
first
though that's a
clam what do what do oyers look like
then if that's not an
oyer people my voice is low and deep
what deep people never notice I'm
talking deep
people but yeah yeah yeah I see what
you're I understand what you're talking
about let me get that tooth I understand
though but but I think it's a thing that
you can kind of train to have a louder
voice if that's what you
want I think generally it makes
things often way more easier I just
can't think of a proper situation right
now but but it is it is uh a good trait
to
have if you know when to be quiet though
like my mom she's probably watching this
but my mom has a very loud
voice my mom has a very loud voice we're
doing this again
okay and and I don't think she uh
sometimes sometimes she uh doesn't quite
notice when she's being a a tiny bito
loud you know uh I hope I'm not getting
WhatsApp messages right now from my mom
holy that's a lot of sharks shark
attack the
movie dead beat sharks these are wait
what do you call the combination of dead
beats and Chum
buds Chum Beats
dead
Butts oh my
God dead butts is that what they're call
do do they even have a name cuz I know
we call like uh we call fans of Calli
and me
kmbs but I never heard like combinations
of the other fandoms names before Oh my
God
oh my
yumy Dan
Shams did you see that stopped for a
moment oh my God oh my God no no
no help
me
be GL yeah froze for
woman am I
[Music]
done perfect
indeed oh another piece of
heart oh we almost getting our a new
life okay last time I felt like I left
this place too
early what now you kicking me out oh I
wasn't done I was not done I wanted to
look at
it well wor it good morning T good
morning apparently you were done yeah
apparently was rude but
okay wait from which side did I come I
think that
side
it's looking like a jungle in here
Trident again I have a bad feeling about
this guys was that what was that oh wait
I came from here I don't know what that
weird sound was though wait a
second weapon upgrades oh do I have
enough for
that 900 oh what should I do what should
I do I feel like my my hobby horse is
super weak I kind of want to upgrade it
once nice
[Music]
color and we we're close to getting
another upgrade soon
anyway knife we already got a upgrade
for the knife last time oh dear
here what was that bed who who who
sleeps in the
air sounds interesting
though dad reminds me I've seen like a
like an ad or something I think about
like a hotel where the rooms are
basically on a cliff oh on the mountain
side
have you guys seen something like that
it was basically
built inside a cliff looks
fascinating but it looks really scary
too oh my God I'm rocking
this would you stay in a hotel like
that I mean it's not about how how
pretty the hotel is it's really just
about the location the weird ass
location
ouch oh okay now let's take care of
you there we go there we got try out for
the experience yeah but I I reckon it it
would probably be super
expensive so was kind of special
experience H tells I've also seen oopsie
I've also seen one or many that are like
kind of like underwat like my my
colleague at work years ago was looking
for
hotels and was honestly considering
booking that even though it looked
super
expensive definitely was super expensive
I think it was somewhere on like I don't
know the malades or some the mives or
something like
that crack that shell
open you got to come out of your shell
if you want some more
friends yeah the mold just interrupted
my dream what you
adorable after the show are you the
oyster
cute kind of reminds me a a little bit
of sana's Halloween
[Laughter]
form
gummy worm for
him that's a nice
bed I like that uh the shape of that and
the Engravings really
pretty
M beautiful
beautiful oh by the way guys good news
my mom has a floor
now my sister and my brother were over
at my mom's place over hell and I
couldn't join Unfortunately they were
like hey you want to join but I was like
nope I got streams to do um but yeah
they were helping my mom to put down her
floor it looks so nice now looks like
it's renovated like before um like I
don't know there's a huge difference the
floor makes such a huge
difference yeah that finally yeah she's
so happy with the
floor she's so happy with it better than
falling infinitely yeah cuz that's what
was happening until now my mom was just
I don't know floating in the
void in the void no floor no no n i mean
it was just like uh like concrete or
something like that I guess up until
then and the winter is coming it's been
getting really cold outside really cold
insanely cold it so much wind outside I
hate
it I like it when it's cold but when the
wind is blowing so strong too oof that's
a big oof for
me uh excuse me
what I guess I go
here
yeah oh camera
okay what that sound what was that
sound wi coming
down Mama toy fell out of the
world isn't that the message you get
when you uh fall out of the the
end in
Minecraft I'm making scarves for people
this year apparently it's going to be a
really cold winter oh really where where
though I guess it depends on
your location too I would say but every
winter gets colder and colder doesn't it
and the snow always comes later and
later I feel
like oh should have stayed one more
second in but I got no chill uh where we
going what
it
sus very very s it
oh
Pi there's no snow here never saw it all
where are you from that's sad like for
me having Four Seasons is so
normal and such a
given it's crazy to think that some
places don't have four
seasons
Tas unusual perhaps even
extraordinary but nearly nothing is
unique Al
yours was not the first brick home to be
destroyed by fire I mean that might be
true but so what what are you trying to
say
but that's where I came from no no let
me go
for what what what what why are we doing
this was I not here before I recognized
the
v wait wait I'm not I'm not I'm not in
the right state of mind right
now uh
uh that gave me a gave me a heart attack
I was like I'm fine today with all the
heart monitor maybe I should have turned
it on there they
go melting like
chocolate
yeah okay okay okay okay okay come on
come on show me what you
got
I want to get closer what a waste of
time need to stream hard monitor some
more uh let's too lazy to set it up it's
really easy to set it up but I thought
well it's not a horror game anyway so I
hope you guys are not too disappointed
here by the way is the next letter which
is not a letter it's just a space in
between
space okay you know what I'll give you
I'll give you a oh it is another oyster
I'll give you the next letter as well so
it's a space and then it's a the me the
star the star the star aren't you the
star or maybe I'm the star cuz baby I'm
the star and the like um
demonetization or
dmca why is that the first thing I'm
thinking
of the no not you guys are stupid why
these is that all you can think of guys
really really how
unoriginal B MC a
MC
hello
[Music]
hello are we playing a game here star is
right
there oh
cat help me Alice this poster for the
show it's ruined if I can't put it back
together carp what the P looks
fine the cubes okay okay okay all right
but it's a poster even without the
cubes how do I bring that over here do I
have to push it
what oh no I hate these kind of
[Music]
puzzles collect the four blocks in the
surrounding area to start the
challenge eh
is there is it is there a time limit
Slide the puzzle pieces on the board to
form a complete
picture it must be done in infinite
amount of moves
five okay but I need that thing over
there too
right oh wait there's a cat cat
cat hello the proper order of things is
often a mystery to me you
too I don't know
I will give it a
try don't like these puzzles too yeah
they're difficult H sometimes you just
don't get
it uh hey I'm in the middle of a puzzle
can we not do this right
now oh dear do you protect the puzzle
pie
though make it worth my time at least
please
oh that was
close that was
close
ow
bastard they look like merlocks
somehow ow
owow I don't want to be
frozen I'm a
phoenix my element is
fire but I guess the ice level is over
yeah the fire level is over are we going
to fight up
here uh all right can we really do this
up here can you come down for a
moment in German we say
come we don't say Al in not right now
okay I BR forced
[Music]
it ah you did protect
something I
see thank you stream hard monitor
challenge I love that you guys still
think about hard challenge oh wait I'm
supposed to collected not smashed okay
quick before the show begins what I need
one more what are you talking about give
me some time
lady did you guys listen a lot to
vampire it's already like what
250k views at least the last time I
checked it was something like
that it's doing well so far I don't as I
said before I don't expect it to be like
a miracle like a goodbye declaration
again but it's doing well and I'm happy
about
it although I do got to say um something
bothers me with back together with my
voice in some some moments of the
song Maybe should have
uh I don't know if it's just me or if I
should have sent uh it back to the
mixing to fix some H now it's too late
so I got to just got to accept it you
think you can do better yeah and and and
uh one or
two issues with the mixing maybe so
sometimes just sometimes like um certain
parts are like
still a little bit rough like a like a
diamond in the rough you
know well I need two more pieces no wait
one more one more
did I go here before ah you sound good
you were great sounded cool best friend
PR song of those of heard really thank
you it was great but good to aim for
Perfection M yeah we just uh we're kind
of in a time
crunch uh for both the music video and
the the um
mixing
I'm going to stay in here for a
while I love you singing I'm a vocalize
fan thank
you coming out so close to my street
made me a bit split on which to Loop my
you got to Loop them both and it's you
have to because that way you won't get
uh too sick of it too
soon how will I make it over there that
quickly you get walking
all my place is vampire Sparks myth for
treat e n that sounds
good glasses a memories over there all
right I I'll go there first I
guess and yeah so you should Loop it
all myth or treat is a freaking fun song
it's a short one too so keep troubles
and torments at a distance it's good to
mix it in forgotten in between some
other of my
songs faran makes really cool songs I've
noticed like I've I really loved
reflect reflect reflect already so
much and now with Myer trat again he
created such an interesting
song I'm really really
uh Amazed by
it
oh okay I did
[Music]
it he did a stream going over the
process with him
what
really oh okay uh we only have five
turns or what in the time limit no or 24
turns uh excuse me um oh dear what if I
mess
up I would
say
toon this goes to the left how do I move
it
it oh there's in what what how did I
move
them how did I move
them
yeah
oh I'm trying Arrow creas maybe wsd oh
okay
um I would say this
goes ah space bar
and this goes uh left cuz to 10 tons
this goes up and then this goes ah easy
easy easy
easy done
ah
done first try baby first try
baby are we done now collecting all the
things was that the last thing I had to
do did I go through here before I think
yeah right
pretty sure I went through here
before toen Dan by the way means Dance
of the
death which worries me a little
bit I feel like they want to kill
me oh I think I was here before no yeah
I was
sorry vampire really great you shouldn't
worry B really thank you thank you
I don't think it's like completely bad
but for some reason there there are just
some moments that bother me about my
voice in in that song cover that I would
like to fix now but it's too late as I
said oh fun can I be on the wus as
well valus of course you're not an
impressario you're a killer The
Mastermind of a criminal Enterprise this
world is not so just like Alice and I've
done your bidding you did a few errands
got your hands dirty big deal the show
dist dracul Ates the crowd shame you'll
miss it you need to deal with these
Sailors it's your time what time time
the time was come to talk of ships and
uh and and vegetables and royalty and uh
and where the pigs have wings and so on
enough of that wus you start whing about
there being too much sand on the beach
I'll have your BL for breakfast shame on
you Carpenter you made a promise I had
no choice got to protect your promises
one would like I'd have thought You'
know that if you can't do that
then you are not
worthy uh what are we doing who are we
fighting you ghost ghost time all right
I know how to fight ghosts drown sailor
easy I've already fought a couple of you
are you like a bigger
version he's like following me so
quickly come on out throw some bombs at
me that's what I like to see it bnk bunk
let me fix your headache I'll be your
doctor for
today I will prescribe you with some
good fat bking that's the only thing
that can help with such a
severe uh headache I don't see you right
now but I'll give you I'll give you a
bonking anyway all right wonderful going
well so
far no no no no normal medicine will not
help you trust me trust
me got to listen to what your doctor
says AOW that hurt
buddy where are you there shoot shoot
shoot Sho Sho go
go yeah his hand
I'll take your brain out if you even
still have
one I'm in desperate need for
one should have waited for the boms I
guess we shouldn't be playing around
here this looks like a graveyard it's
kind of disrespectful don't you
think oh now you did this to yourself
buddy you did that to yourself
oh wait wait wait no no
no
I was distracted oh no no no no no
no no no no
yeah who wants to try this therapy guys
now if you H start therapy with takanasi
kiar Dr takanasi kiar and then suggest
the therapy to a friend and that one
also ends up becoming my patient then
you get one thy therapy session for free
doesn't that sound like a
deal if that is not a great deal then I
don't
know one fairy session for for free is
really good because one therapy session
costs you 100
bucks wait actually you know what that
might be cheap I don't I don't know how
much like therapy in general costs uh
usually I actually do not
know the is the matter with you oh
he
did 100
bucks 100 an hour is ridiculously low
okay you see what you see I I thought so
the moment I said 100 I realized wait
that actually might be kind of
cheap 100 for session well the session
maybe I didn't say how long the session
will be maybe it's only 30
minutes
and all right we killed
him I think that was one of my best boss
fights cuz I don't know I kind of got
this boss type down this monster
type got it down um I know
it it opened up over there did it and I
should check out this Keyhole
first Keyhole Keyhole
K this angle is weird Okay that's a
friends in our secret cells Alice your
too I'm sure Dina was a confidant always
about wasn't
she pets are FR yeah pets are
family I recommend everyone to get a pet
for yourself could be anything doesn't
necessarily have to be a cat or a dog if
you feel like you can't really take care
of one
you could even get yourself a fishy or
or a bb or a hamster a lot of people who
start out getting pets get
themselves yeah get themselves a a
hamster or Rock no a rock does not count
you can tell me a lot about what a pet
could be like a tarantula okay whatever
a snake Okay sure some people really
like those type of pets but um a rock no
no no rocks are not pets you can have
rocks in your home if you want to but
you shouldn't call them a pet it's not
it's
delusional also if you draw a face on it
no it doesn't make it any
better okay I'm back
here is that chest
here
nice okay now where do we actually
go did I not just come out of
there what if my rock is running my PC
for
me what ah what what I want my pet rock
Mama wait mama is busy right now mama
mama got
lost there we are
okay pet peep with o o I got so many pet
peeps you know what I you know want to
know a pet peeve about TV shows I got so
many pet peeves about TV shows another
one would be
and when in TV
shows someone Rings someone's doorbell
and they open in the first
second it grinds my
gears who who is like why are they
always
camping in front of those doors even
though they don't know like how would
they know that they're getting uh uh
visited I missed the did I miss a snoot
did I did I
really or did I miss a snoot I didn't
even hear
one you find the silliest things
annoying but it just doesn't make sense
who camps right in front of their door
like it takes me so much time to open
the door first of all just because I'm
most of the time uh half
naked at home so when someone rings at
the door it takes me so much time that
sometimes they're already gone by the
time I open the
door actually I have to say though that
they're uh they leave so fast like can
you give me at least like a few more
moments like delivery people from Amazon
or whatever they really don't wait long
do they ouch
ow wait wait wait no why why no why are
you focusing on that monster you ruined
it I we tried yelling at them that you
will be there in a minute I don't think
they really can hear me I think my walls
are too
thick
switch to the
Hammer okay po this
[Music]
so
no it's only you and me just the two of
us we can make it if you if you what
[Music]
one go Dam it
go back go
back
oh we can make it if we're trying just
that two of us yeah know that part we
can make it if we're try just the two of
us just the two of us building Castle in
the Sky oh is that really the
lyrics oh my God K we have a rock now
what that's not a real pet that's like
you talking about your friends even
though they're only in your
imagination finally friender friend of
course please Alice friend fulfill my
pledge I need my men they may be hostile
at first but their true souls are
trapped you must release
them do they want to be at peace they do
not know their own minds what's true of
the living is often true of the
Dead I love those Gates though cie would
be digging those oh they look really
cool if Cy ever gets a mansion I'll send
that design to her and we'll get her
those
Gates if she ever gets like a castle or
something I need help help I need help
is there any secrets
no would love this game yeah generally I
think it's like her
aesthetic cie played that jump King game
again huh didn't
she is she done with it now is she
finally free from it released from the
suffering I hope it I really hope it for
her she she says she likes it but I
would much rather have her play games
that uh are not so
much
suffering uhhuh okay E I have to go in
there but e feels like a trap
oh
yeah oh only 20% for the map oh oh wow
that's a long DLC
then yeah I knew she started the DLC I
thought it was already finished today is
this another challenge are we getting
our new
heart after this battle I suppose I feel
it I feel
it
uh yeah wonderful
angle just a mini boss sadly no no just
boss enemies oh wait no rewards no nice
reward
there must be some reward oh Falon punch
I see I see I see how it is see when I
when I think of Falcon Punch I somehow
for some reason have to think of this
GameCube game what was it called again
uh Star Fox Star
Fox Star Fox the GameCube
one kind of want to play that one
again give it a
try I think we have permission for it
but I currently do not own a
GameCube Starbuck Adventure yeah I think
it was that
one Adventure I'm pretty sure it was
Adventure ow oh my God uh okay I need to
get my
together sorry I I knew you came in for
a head uh headache but I I seemed I seem
to need to fix some other things with
your
body no get closer to him what are you
doing no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no
no
okay hi hi hi hi do you own a Wii you're
backwards compatible no I don't own a
Wii either come back here I used to own
of A Sort ghost bu is it
bu oh that reminds me that was this
funny moment in in the Halloween stream
oh now I finally remember something I
can tell you um you know when when we
did that maze Amelia led us into the
maze
first what what what what
what what what who's hurting
me
what what what what's hurting me what
what's going
on am I was I just there for too long I
need to be faster or something like that
I need to stay where the light is oh
okay okay okay I'll
try
[Music]
okay okay okay
understand so during the the Maze part
of the Halloween stream um
uh the Senai were the first ones to hide
somewhere in the Maze and she told us to
not go uh past the dark part so I
thought uh um we just really have to
hide somewhere in those
Hedges but I think I misunderstood we
were allowed to go through the dark
part but not like like after like not
exit it but I thought we we weren't even
allowed to enter it at all so there were
not really many hiding places uh in in
my mind at least so anyway I was hiding
somewhere pretty close to the beginning
of the main
While most others went quite a bit
further I think and I was hiding alone
but I was hearing gooda a little bit it
it sounded actually pretty close to
me wa where is where's the ghost
uh-oh sound like she was pretty close to
me grateful thanks but I didn't see her
I never dream so I was just like sitting
and waiting in a dead end of the Maze
and waiting for someone to find it
because Amelia said AIA said that we
have to wait for them to find us and
then spook them and surprise them and
we're not really like we can't move but
we should maybe try to stay in the same
spot so I was like waiting and waiting
and in my mind I was was thinking about
how to surprise them what I was going to
say and I was so ready I was going to be
like I was sitting down on the ground
waiting for them and I was going to
stand up jump up and be
like I was going to be like really loud
but I waited and waited and no one came
to find me and I waited and waited and
waited could I wasn't even hiding what
really but I was waiting so long but I
was still feeling all right because I
heard gura somewhere close by and I felt
like relieved because of that was like
as long as gura is still here I guess
I'm at least not all alone so all good I
kept on waiting and no one came and then
I heard like
in in the really faint distance I was
hearing these voices that people were
uniting reuniting they found each other
and uh they were all
like yeah like having a lot of fun
together while I was still all alone and
and and I thought they were going to
forget about me but I already I was kind
of like giving up oh my
God
I was already kind of given up so I
I I don't know this is too many
enemies I'm so strong
wow amazing okay uh how can a soul be so
ignorant I'm unanswered
[Music]
prayer anyway I I didn't uh I didn't uh
uh uh give up as in I just went and
joined everyone else I still kept uh
staying there but I just uh I didn't
expect that anyone was still coming for
me so out of nowhere
mumay comes to me in her ghost costume
right she comes around the corner and I
absolutely did not expect
it and she gave me a huge shock she was
just she just came around the corner and
she didn't even see me apparently but I
was like
ah I literally uh yelled and screamed at
her are you staying here no wait what do
we what do we
uh I need
[Music]
to okay yeah I wanted to tell you that
because that was uh not on camera
anywhere cuz M wasn't streaming no one
saw
it but I thought it was so ironic that
we were supposed to scare them but M
with her cute adorable ghost costume
scared me
oops I thought it was so
ironic it was
clipped but you didn't you didn't see it
though right no one saw it I
think hry along it's just perfect cuz M
normally is like the least scary thing
ever and even with the ghost costume
she's not scary she's just adorable
but she came around the corner at a
moment where I really didn't expect it
and she scared the out of
me I was so R scaring the co eyes but
then it happened the other way around
Lum is terrifying no she's
not but she I guess kind of fulfilled
the role of her
costume
uh-oh
okay let's kill those
slugs because before I'm going to lose
my
mind slash slash slash are they
recreating themselves endlessly cuz
that's going to be a problem if that's
the
case no no no no no no no no focusing on
[Music]
the okay okay uh I think they are
endlessly
spawning okay well okay I'll try to
focus on him them no no no
no come
on you can do
it yes you can do it kill him
yeah oh he's coming plumy the
ghost he's coming for
me where are you where are you there are
you no no no no no no
no well my focus was not on him but I
did at least some
damage next letter is O like
uh or
organization oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh where where's where's the gos
oh God where's the ghost you're really
messing around here with me aren't
you
uh-oh oh come
on I just want to focus on
him this is like an endless fight no no
no no this not
fair you are not allowed to kill
this would just not be
funny he was right behind
me oops
no tapped out of the game no I did it
again no I did it
again a not around where I you
no I see you I see you but it won't
focus on him am I the only one suffering
here right now let's I guess I have to
fight without a focus oh God oh God
no oh oh it's on
baby oh it's on that was leeches
if it weren't so that was
leeches
no no no do I have a by the way could I
upgrade
something Tik
Tok I could but do we want to wait for
the blade again I haven't upgraded my
grinder in a
while we could upgrade any of those
we're using both of those in the fight
you're playing
what H keyboard controls yeah maybe I
should have played with a controller
from the getg go I didn't want to switch
to controller now cuz I'm already like
kind of used to the uh keyboard controls
oopsie I no no uh no I'm switching the
target maybe you've seen it but it kept
on switching to the leeches and was
really difficult to get to the guy horse
I'll go with blade knife grinder
wait for the knife wait for the blade
okay unless if we lose again I mean it's
not really my fault because of
slugs but if leeches but if we lose
again I might upgrade even the hammer or
the pepper
grinder
yeah anyway besides that story of
M personally I
think off
stream uh off off screen uh nothing in
particular really like I don't think
You' really missed anything from my
side uh can we not do the hammer right
now
no I am going to lose my
mind okay we're going to do this without
Focus
yeah yeah I'm going to do it without the
Focus well now I could focus yes yes yes
yes yes see now it stays on him like
someone said that you can't focus on a
ghost but if there's only him around
then it stays focused on
him I feel like wait no why am I why do
I keep on tapping
ah ah don't let me shoot you come
on
please
yeah baby yes yes I guess worst case I
just have to wait for those moments when
he attacks me with his
PCH where are
you oh nice nice nice that didn't
count you for real Z right now
oh
she he's going to the usual room after
this I am so done with you come on
attack me with Falcon Punch please make
it a little bit easier for me will
you FAL punch
please
oh there he is no
no
bastard
oh I'm losing it I'm losing it
guys the the Le the leaches they just
keep on respawning so it doesn't matter
if I kill them they will keep on
respawning but the problem is
that I can't focus on this dude if the
leeches are around that's the problem
chat it's okay we can make it
eventually oh that hurt you
[Music]
bastard I'm decapitating you in front of
all of your friends and family hope that
was worth it
buddy thank you for the member support
trouble what oh my
God are we done are we
[Music]
done light come with
me don't attack me please uh-oh uhoh
please please faster it hurts it Hur no
no no no no no no no no no no it's I'm
in the dark it hurts it
hurts
oh oh thank you for watching oh thank
you good
night okay now the timing is okay wait a
bit
more
yeah maybe now oh oh
and
too
fast oh we did it okay I think It sped
up a little bit at the end
perhaps oopsie oh that really counts as
it's directly on top of it
really
ooh let's go save
back uh y
bye yeah bye what excuse me what where
was I supposed to land on
what at Super Chat what what exactly are
you talking about I need to read it uh I
think again close closely need to take a
closer look at that super gentle oh wait
I didn't see that
before a what exactly was that for
though the the bomb that I placed there
what did that
activate thankfully that one is still
staying with me for a little
while taking its damn sweet
time bombs distract what bombs would
have distracted the leeches oh
no that could have made it so easier
hi hi hi hi I have to start from the
beginning I think I do oh
God that
way what what what what is that for
let's
go what's sa fat again in English what
was the name again
two what are we
counting nice landing y it's too dark
it's too dark it's to dark too dark it
hurts come faster oh seahorse that's
easy oh my God
no it's not
flower let's just get the
teeth we can get the upgrade on my blade
soon wait which way did I come from this
way okay
uh
no not from the beginning please not
from the beginning
please
I is this the beginning no I don't think
it's the
beginning it looks different yeah okay
nice we got a
checkpoint
[Music]
[Laughter]
jumped off the edge T you why you do
this it's not like I want to do it but
you seem to be enjoying it cuz you're
drinking
something it's nice that you're enjoying
yourself are we going there or what
isn't there something missing
there so cool did I go the wrong
direction was there something
H this platform was
missing excuse me was that a bug or
something or or is or is that I missed
the pressure plate and that's what it
activates the first platform oh
okay that's not that doesn't miss
it
but what it's not coming up
though it didn't come up and it was
definitely 100% on top of the pressure
plate look at
that why is
it
[Music]
hello
hello it worked the first time oh there
it wait it's going down shouldn't it be
the other way
around wait wait wait
he no
is that a bu did I break the
game what what if
I well maybe I can make it let me try
it I made it pro game but what about the
there's more platforms that should be
there
no oh wait maybe it's running out and
it's will come back up cuz it ran out no
no we're not doing the opposite thing oh
dear I think there's supposed to be
platforms
here wait
but it came up it came up oh it's up
it's up it's up it didn't break this
time okay okay come
on okay let's let's not mess it up this
time would like to go up
please uhoh the time the time Alice the
[Music]
time no
oh
okay that's way it's back to the ship
for me all right see you there again yes
thank you first try first
try be as good to yourself as you been
to us anchor and Men the wide and
glorious oh my God it's almost 11:00
p.m. almost playing it for 4 hours I
feel like I haven't done much progress
today
h
or have I you're actually close to
finishing this level H the water level
okay let's hope I can
and which way that
one I'm getting hungry I made I made H
spaghetti yesterday I got still a bunch
of servings I think I'm going to put one
serving in the freezer cuz I when I
make uh when I cook I make
when when I cook stuff like that I cook
enough for
like um I don't know six servings or so
at least at least for me cuz I don't eat
that much uh in one serving usually so
every time in the past
every time in the past when I uh
made pasta sauces or whatever or or
chili con car that was the same
issue
I uh can't eat all of it before it goes
off so I think I'm I'm probably better
off if I freeze some of
it and I would probably get sick of it
anyway after eating it for 3 days so a
fourth day it's not very welcome anyway
thank you
Kaman for renewing your membership or
like for yeah that that's what it is
right no
no I can upgrade it I know wa one second
one
second give me that Golden Tee
please give me give me give me your
golden teeth I am the two fairy please
trust
me I want to sing more ABA songs in my
k sorry I'm I'm not being very accurate
focus
focus yeah baby okay come here come
here M oh my God I'm so hungry I'm
looking forward to my
pasta
timing okay nice whoever destroys a soul
destroys the world there is much wisdom
in that Alice whoever destroys a soul
destroys our world how would I destroy a
soul I mean we in the game okay a
fantasy game sure but can I apply that
wisdom to real life I don't
know I wouldn't know
how I've always I always have Ser few
servings of two to four different left
of Miss in the freezer very convenient
yeah that's so smart I should do that
too I want to make curry like the Tha
Thai style Curry again but I can't find
the red curry past that it's that is not
too
spicy really I really really can't
handle spicy food even when I add a
coconut uh milk to it it still is way
too spicy for me I wasn't at home before
right oh I'm hungry oh oh the hunger oh
the hunger is calling
me hungry yeah that's literally where it
came
from
paste paste I want to say paste curvy
paste is that not what it
is very
Pasta Pasta past it Pasta
Pasta no spicy Noles for me no no no no
please
no where am I where am I going I got I'm
lost my
oh what about
there
a I think that's where the story
continues should go to the tee
first ah but wait no is that not where I
came from
ah perhaps
not what
what sorry you really don't have snacks
at home like chips or whatever I do I do
I went shopping as as grocery grocery
shopping mhm
I got all the good stuff at
home I got instant noodles and stuff as
well
but uh why would I eat that now when I
have uh proper pasta sauce in the fridge
right now wow I love this I love this
slide like I love all the slides in this
game but this one has a nice snake
design slow
slow yeah
see even without def
fences I'm rocking it baby there were a
lot of tooth down there I want to get
them
W and here we
are huh who are you oh no oh no no
no colossa
ruin
oh you scar me buddy I should have
upgraded my weapon let's go let's go
upgrade
time yeah baby 800
teeth some of those teeth might have
been for my viewers
oopsie since you're your milky
milky baby
te oh my God oh my God
chill ow
he picked me off ow e don't just spit me
out like
that how am I supposed to fight
you it's raining bombs hallelujah it's
raining boms how am I supposed to find
him is this doing him any damage wait
I'm supposed to to uh H do this
[Applause]
huh one more no
okay
uh-oh mommy mommy mommy oh could i k
that to please
help W I'm too
close what what are we
doing
up El almost
pushing I almost
[Music]
pushing okay I understand I understand I
understand shoot
me wait I can't shoot them I cannot
shoot them back is that what you're
telling me you're kind
anal oh wait but I I guess I just have
to keep on using my pepper grinder
you
you cuz it did get rid of one face so I
guess I have to get rid of all of
them oh dear oh
dear oh de no no no no
no oh wait I can already hit him oh
never
mind okay go away go away go away no
you you
you I don't see but okay let's
go all right I activated it in the last
moment no
no I don't like being in your tummy I
like being a free
person okay okay get away get away
healing there's no way to get okay I'm
dead uh next letter is a uh wait what
was the last letter I gave was it an O I
think it was an
O it was an oh right okay
uh no it was B last well last one wasn't
oh yeah
yeah oh my God oh
my and next one is uh D like dmca again
yeah not again you let me out how
is there like a way to uh make him stop
that oh I want to I want to maybe get
the those uh boxes cuz they probably
have have
uh some stuff that could help me oh
never
mind when he does that it's probably
safe to just stay close to
him no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no
come on come on come
on I need help not
te wait a second I because I died my
knife wasn't upgraded all right all
right all right hi hi hi hi
sh I love
dut love
dodgeball dodge ball can't get enough of
it
can literally not get enough of
ited
oh okay I think almost all of his faces
are
gone if he catches me now he's going to
kill me uh-oh get away go go go wrong
weapon uhoh he wants me he really wants
me but I don't want him no
no mommy Security Police
anyone
okay I'm doing most of this fight see
with my Peppa
grind thanks
too oh no we're done we're done I think
where are we yeah we're done
wo all right all right all right all
right that took me a few no that took me
one
try thank you
chat that looks like
Outlast that looks like
Outlast I don't like
this oh my God and that looks like
Outlast help me
no snoot ghost
snoot oink oink oink oink oink
oink me likey me likey likey likey me
like it likey likey
huh
H what where are you Every Picture Tells
a Story I don't see you sometimes we
don't like the ending sometimes are you
hanging here somewhere where are
you ah there you are uh I hear someone
suffering no
yeah twice
baby that's right
girl got to love me some
twice
twice I when I was in Japan I often
tried to sing twice songs in Koka but
first of all cuz I my Korean was
non-existent and second of all because
their songs are actually hard to
sing I never really uh nailed it super
difficult their songs I don't know why
twice uh songs so difficult to sing at
least alone maybe that's a thing cuz I'm
singing it alone and it's a grape song
No but not even just The Melodies
are like they're not I don't feel like
they're made for being sung
live The Melodies of their songs uh
hello um I'm I'm here but but you're not
sending me straight into the boss battle
are you cuz I my screen is
broken five vocals are hard
yeah why you guys are popular here
gentlemen welcome to the
show P Senai let's go I can't here for p
Senpai if you know have P Senpai I'm I'm
out of here immediately this better be
worth my time
they got nice legs
though that's quite enough of that I
think enough preliminaries here's the
performance you've been waiting for
proves I without prejudice and have a
fine sense of humor no give me the
ladies sword and Crown are worthless
here I invite everyone to dance laborers
lawyers church and gown all make their
little FR this life is full of random
deaths heaps of sh so few are soed by
making sushi out of them want someone to
blame fire plague and strange disease
drowned murdered
you Beau P down the basement stairs is
this porry slam I came in for future not
porry slam very hard sweat running down
my skin after the dance I then must rest
and the eating can begin no you eat your
performers no time to eat death is the
ultimate I didn't bring them here to be
eaten I'm the right to be eaten wa this
reminds me of us push all wait what is
that
eting while Wonderland is destroyed I'm
not the enemy you seek Alice IED to hide
this be like all right the audience is
gathered now time to eat my
chickens I can even do tricks when
eating them an idot look at me however
this turns out consider the a flip
chicken before you enter my mouth do a
flip then ask by whom oh no I set that
Bloody train in motion where does it
come from it arrives when you arrive and
it's more horrible even than it could
come I like these story Parts where they
show these
like
sketches pieces of art it's beautiful I
love
[Music]
that paper cuts
yeah paper
dolls wait we're done with the water
level the blood in my mouth tastes like
bile where's the briak that hit me Nanny
nasty pratts out cold not dead and more
is the pity what did he want what they
all want money didn't earn what level
down y maybe a good time to end theam I
don't know my mind's in pieces I still
have terrible visions and I need to know
about the fire same as always you need
to move on how many levels do I have
left then well at least she's not
spewing that as Sil nonsense my past is
De i k save them I should have died my
past is dead my past is dead too
Radcliffe thought familiar faces would
bring around after out five four more
three three levels and a final boss okay
three levels and I just did one today M
say but the best policy in this life
when she wasn't comes she GED ties like
penguin drooled occasionally
squeed never uted a sensible sound and
like the child she was she how many did
I do today only one did that only count
as
one
what gone off some Lous Comm cockroaches
those poor takes of food for perverts
like the blameless ants that wasps
consume or spiders feble
pray the thing is I actually have to get
up really early um you visited my room
at rutage what were you call that so I
really should me end it before midnight
at least woman alone sometimes does what
she doesn't particularly feel like doing
Daniel redcliff P said you'd fall I'm no
drunk like her I'm hurting no one hin
not a bad life I have a feeling I know
for what she also said you might have my
rabbit please nanny about the damn fire
never seems to help look Alice I can't
give you what I don't have Radcliffe
wrote the inquest report I'll take you
to him besides he's got your damn rabbit
you should remember that all right but
Mr red Cliff's useless don't I know I
wouldn't say
that yeah time to use your German skills
guys well hm let's play this part in the
real world until we get into a dream
world again I guess cuz it shouldn't be
too long these parts are never that
[Music]
long just end shut up it won't be that
long don't worry I I end the stream when
I say I want it to
end what happened here who
died actually the city feels so
dead feels so lifeless
[Music]
sh yeah is in control indeed I am always
always in
control just like real London no real
London I've been there before and it
didn't feel dead F by
life also so cold as
knock
knock knock knock yes who is it Alice
little Mr
Radcliff one thing in London that I
suppose you better come up confused me
so much was the
buses cuz me and roommate JN we were
like in a hotel quite a bit away from
the city
center um so we had to take a bus to get
into the city center and uh
you know those those double double
decker double double decker what was
what's it called in English double
decker uh the the the twostory uh buses
so cool right but
butd
um double de oh it is double deer okay
okay uh me and my roommate we were uh
standing at a bus
[Music]
station
donkey skin donkey skin donkey what did
you do to donkey oh my God Shrek you
didn't protect donkey what the hell why
you so rude to donkey always this room
is beautiful anyway I was saying we were
standing at the at a bus stop
and we were just trying our best to get
get the right bus but millions of buses
passed us and they just didn't St like
stop and and and and and let us in and I
was wondering like why the hell I
thought that was the righted bus next
one 10 minutes later freezing in the
cold another one comes and I'm like this
must be it maybe this one will stop for
us it didn't stop we waited for
like maybe 40 50 minutes for one of
those buses to stop for us and I was
pretty sure they were that was the the
right bus but they wouldn't stop and it
was so freezing and we were so confused
because it was literally like we just
arrived and it was just our first
experience of the traffic in in London
and turns out that yeah you have
to give them a signal to stop I thought
it was pretty obvious and also that is
that is not very nice like for for
tourist like how the are you
supposed to
know yeah and I I think I even like I
was like so confused and I was um I was
dming my friend who um lived in London
was like girl the B buses are not
stopping for me I'm so conf confused do
I have to give them a sign or something
and then I actually she was like no I
don't think so
actually apparently only in certain
places in London maybe it's a necess
maybe it's only necessary in certain
places anyway so she said not really but
I did it anyway and I felt really
embarrassed doing it because you don't
do this in Australia and we use buses a
lot you don't do it they stop when they
see someone standing at the bus stop
they stop
anyway I did it and he didn't uh stop
for me which I think was actually
because that bus was supposed to pass
that bus stop and not stops doesn't stop
there at all
but because he didn't stop for me the
one moment when I had enough courage to
put out a
Thum wait no I didn't give him thumbs up
I think I was just like hello
please he drove away so I was like okay
maybe it's that's really not
it then I lost all my courage but then
eventually after another couple of
missed buses I finally I did it again
and that one finally stopped took me a
whole hour to get into that
stupid buz me and my friend we were
dying anyway here's some Japanese stuff
I guess redcliff who can make even
fascinating subjects boring says the
curved blade is a 16th century M Katana
and the shortest sword is called vakita
both used by Japanese
Samurai I don't
know is this like
a doesn't really look like Japanese
furniture is this uh uh
Chinese style
furniture
looks pretty though it's a mix it's very
pretty I like that shelf looks expensive
Shu porcelain Mr ROV says is the Ming
Dynasty's finest beautiful shapes best
colors and most priced decorations well
that sounds uh that sounds Chinese
[Music]
again both is
beautiful oh I wonder if uh
if American meie mixes these these
Chinese things in there because he lives
there I
wonder his personal I mean this whole
game is his personal taste I guess so it
makes
sense you do have my rabbit give me my
rabbit that's a dog that is not a rabbit
AB it at that is not a rabbit that's a
dog Alice do you not know what a rabbit
looks like oozing with attitude and
accusatory fling
[Music]
the girl who always sings star the fire
today did I rip his head off I wanted
to understandable have a nice day what's
left of my brain will
explode is it mad to pray for better
hallucinations perhaps I'm fed to expire
right
here understandable all movables and
effects are gone nothing but dust stains
and the smell of tobacco no sign of the
coroner
cor report or my rabbit e damn him F
godamn thank you so much for the stream
oh thank you thank
you H we're still not in the dream world
though interesting I have a feeling
we're going to enter it
soon look at what happened with this
beautiful place it's all
ruined
the barricade discourages
squatters suggest he didn't sell up just
left quickly I can't get through this
way but I recall the place had a door in
the back that opened the lane M so no no
squatting in this house all
right sad piano music oh
[Music]
no oh is it
snowing snow
level
it's burning over there is that
[Music]
mushrooms yeah I feel like we're slowly
entering entering a dream world or we
are already in
it yeah yeah okay we're already in
it all
righty looking good um let me have a
little look
around oh the
train I missed the train again
every
time this Ru it's corrupting all of
Wonderland seeking Refuge from the
Wicked World perhaps things only look
like they've gone to hell you're not
that good a liar and I'm not that stupid
but something a bit less calamitous
would have been welcome this unmitigated
disaster is your doing and it will get
worse your train keeps a h get moving
time waits for no got to stay on the Hop
train yo the train stressful perectly
capable of terrifying keep with the you
find another job is there really so
little hope there's even less and if
fear paralyzes you we are
lost veil of of
Doom oh I changed my outfit again I
likeed the one from before so much oh
no apparently we need to fight guys
uh oh lag oh big lag and I'm still
alive okay I want to switch Target
though okay
hello oh
K go
[Music]
Tak ow ow
ow help
me
[Music]
and almost got him there we
go okay I'm going to end it here I
suppose
H what's that called again what's that
called
again oh what's it called
again the BL BL machine journey of a th
miles begin single step single step off
London Bridge could end my journey
failure your EP I'd H you were more
courageous all right
uh it probably saved before that battle
huh we might have to redo that battle
but that's okay just a tiny
battle Aisha oh yeah that's the name I
know for it mhm whoas
Bales you know what I've noticed the
Japanese uh whole life members tend to
call Bales by her last name they all
call her hak hak hak
Haku oh last letter by the way oh
like oh
so guess what that
makes you
knew love Dojo ball ball
b
ball love do so basically let me explain
again cuz JMA wrote it together nicely
so that I can get my together
how to join the plus your Dreadful
giveaway 10 lucky winners I will write
this on Twitter again afterwards just uh
what I want you to do is put the words
love dodo like like implemented into a
tweet without making it too obvious that
that's the keyword do you think you can
do this guys cuz I only want the people
who watch the stream to enter so don't
make it too obvious like the keyw is
love Dole but be more like so I know you
love Doo wait wait a I think it's Doles
wait did I S it to Doles wait never mind
there's another letter It's
s okay it's supposed to be love
[Music]
Doodles I want you guys to be like oh I
know you love Doles but please don't let
them take over
kfp uh or or like I know you love Doles
but I don't think uh that they taste
that well so please continue eating us
instead or something like that I don't
know
make it into a sentence please so that
it's not too obvious as the
keyword
understand and the
dreadfuls and uh follow hell both me and
American me G on Twitter and oh I guess
you kind of need to include the URL in
the Tweet uh mysterious. amm.com
apparently that's a
necessity yeah you might not have many
letters in that tweet but mm so I will
um I will post that on Twitter one more
time afterwards yeah so sorry sorry it's
a a little bit too um
complicated but you get free plushies
yeah I was in a restaurant since then I
love
dodos are you telling me you ate a Dodo
in a restaurant aren't they like
instinct since like a million years
ago Kiana the dreadfuls would be a dope
name for band right it kind of sounds
like reminds me of a certain band's name
which one is
it uh uh anyway it was fun today I'm I'm
awake as I expected the tiredness from
before has kind of passed by now
um where's my oh there it is I think I
can try my best to to read the super
chats 45 minutes for how
[Music]
many it kind of seems man
manable I mean I don't have to end it
exactly at 45 minutes but wait I didn't
read the ones for the German lesson
though did
I it's not the only thing
anyway that I have to
read no no I don't have to wake up in 5
to 6 hours but I do have to wake up
early wait and secret Minecraft did I
read no I did read the secret Minecraft
uh secret sh secret ch
H well tomorrow is a collaboration too
so I do want to read at least some of
them let's go to my
office still Halloween office oops sorry
for denying
you still Halloween office sorry about
that and let me fix the
chat
no denied you're denied of a stream
ending that's what it
is no no no no this will not end here
your shift ends when I say it
ends got
it what about this
one can't I like this one did you guys
hear this before did I play this
before really like this
one
[Music]
I did
h
[Music]
thank you what
what thank you 1 months wow thank
you
wow thank you for being here for one
year yo appreciate it we're reading the
super chats from yesterday's collab
ation stream with f Senai who was such a
pleasant person to be with she's so
sweet I love
her F punch no what what what what you
did not understand how this works at
all I'll read a little bit
let's
[Music]
go for the
red
[Music]
um
for
Shadow pencil dce Crown D thank you for
the r Super
CH after that day oh wait
what
[Music]
oh that's a sweet Super
Chat that's a sweet super
chat okay your name is not even but now
it's at the
first uh spot and I keep on reading that
Trevor
G after that cute Ian collab I wanted to
Brave something truly spooky but I made
a mistake and witnessed a nightmare from
watch along I missed to do to work I
hadn't known true horror until suffering
for cats
2019 never have I experience since
you're frightening Halloween I have
literally no idea what you're talking
about this is somehow not coming through
to me now forever scarred my dreams
haunted by monstrous cats these past few
nights I've found so
soce by emmering myself in my or treat
and V vampire on Loop yeah good idea my
sense is blessed by boom vampire are you
cute and giggle cute Giggle and voice
thank
you what is it wait I don't
understand I don't understand what are
these English
sentences is he just complaining about
cat
the
movie what why why would you do that
what's what's the matter with you hey
come come come thank you thank
[Music]
you
what doesn't know what the hell he's
talking
about thank you Trevor
te I know you love the cats movie you
don't have to lie about it I can see
right through you h
Patrick D update heck playlist please I
actually
did I actually did I just didn't share
the link in a long time it does it not
look updated to you guys I definitely
added
vampire I
think I did I did I actually did maybe
it was after
no I feel like it was before that Super
Chat was
sent you just didn't think I would did
you
yeah yeah I think it should be updated
but I don't know what else is in there
besides
vampire Felix toing for the red super
chat Felix K once again a stream I can
watch live I have to say for some reason
flare Senpai goes really well with
German I don't know if it's because I
have a dirty mind but I think El speak
German might be a new king speaking
German might be a new king well if
that's a king for you you should watch
uh Lord Lord of the Rings in German uh
voice over
with English subtitles
maybe no but she is quite Charming when
she speaks German indeed
[Music]
yeah oh my God what are you doing there
snatch b
b are you
okay Material Girl is in the microplan
still really o o o o o o o o o there's s
b how many are you playing to send of
those pinkies you don't want me to go
[Music]
huh H so Felix yeah by the way I was
wondering you seem to be able to catch
the streams that are like like in the
early early early early early morning in
like na time zones but I thought you
moved to the na time zone from an s a
time zone or something like that that
was my
understanding maybe it was the other way
around was it the other way
[Music]
around he's sending all these super
chats with no messages in it what's
what's what's wrong with
you H oh well anyway I'm glad you were
able to catch these early streams Felix
thank you I have a I have like like some
people can watch the streams in like the
early streams and some some people can
only catch them if I stream later like
around this time and but it's good to
have an audience in any time zone and
then there's some people who watch the
streams no matter what
time yeah thank
you
how did I give Felix a
kiss thank you for your
[Music]
support Val and P D flame X dang for the
pinky my two favorite holos are
collabing and being extremely cute
together I can die happly know AR go
thanks wow there's quite a bunch of
people who like f and me
as they
ois good for
you good
[Music]
choice
Angel Prime thank
[Music]
you
you two really hit it up yeah we
did as I said I just feel like we had a
lot of things in
common like when she we just kept
talking so much like a freaking machine
gun and it just went on and on and on
and when she said one thing I was always
like oh my God I can so relate to that
oh my God girl I have the exact same
thing and then I was like yeah and me I
did this and this blah blah blah this is
how I feel and she was like yeah yeah
know I get that I get that totally get
that
yeah yeah yeah we hit it
off oh congratulations on being
fried
[Music]
I missed the red one he which
one which one the BGN is that the red
one is it the
BGN oh it is okay oh is that Bel Belgium
money they yada y keep coming and they
don't stop
coming
uhhuh they don't stop coming and they
don't stop coming and they don't stop
coming thank you for the red super
[Music]
chat I'm happy you finally have someone
to talk about these things with that
seem to be a problem for you
before Yum Yum Yum yeah not necessarily
a problem just I mean
h I would probably still feel a little
bit
like a little bit how to
say hesitated
to go to F sire whenever I have like
issues
or when I'm worried or whatever but it
was fine it was nice to finally feel
like uh someone really really
understands what I've been going
through
[Music]
pkk
11727 dangan and again pkk 11727
dangin h
[Music]
t t k d pkk 11727 D oh wait it was your
birthday today is my 24th birthday I
hope everything will be all right in the
coming year and so do you I'm so proud
of being a member of kfp love you happy
beled
Birthday
[Music]
yeah what is
this
[Music]
Mouse I'm done with
this see that was
fast let me try a couple from today's
[Music]
stream let's see how far we
get without tangents can she do it can
she do it can she do it without
[Music]
tangents
sorry I was reading
it Ace D kak looking for the top d g d
also I spaced out for moment detective
bigs oh thank you for the two pinkies
which is a red
chat hello Kiana straight Ed shorts
Master takanashi due to your persistence
habit of teasing like recently with
vampire everything you've said and will
say we be under investigation I'm now
half convinced your new outfit is made
of
burans and that old fake water
Obsession wait that's too long ago what
could that have been teasing I'm on to
you birdie lastly I'm also investigating
The Disappearance of Mrs
vapa what the was that
again and supreme say of sweetness wife
of goddess ala
kiaha how is still here I shall save
your other use for from
[Music]
you oh I'm hungry K's outfit is just
Oreo shake
[Music]
cup you can eat a chicken of your choice
if you read all the super chat T you're
saying that as if I don't do that every
day without reading super chats even
detective bigs I don't have anything to
hide so I don't mind working with you
[Music]
but I will call my
lawyer thank
you detective patri
Sky pink super chats
Pink as
Christian I finally found a way to send
super
chats
[Music]
for
than
I agree what I don't
understand learn
German there was a feather in my burger
you call that
food angry what angry customer
24 than trustworthy do than for the
pinky dear t n it seems chicken are not
suitable for this kind of job I propose
an offer
to sacrifice those useless chicken and
employ the Donal I promise we will do a
much better job Perry has five kisses
each day what do you say Don kiss is I
don't know that sounds kind of
cute sounds kind of
cute let me think of it that sounds
really good
[Music]
I would
never I would never leave you guys
behind I would never do that to you guys
my chickens have been there for me for
so
long you've always supported me so
kindly and
passionately the Doos I know I said
love Doos but him no just kidding
the the the key word is still love
Doos Raa dear s for the pinky can let
say that you s Ollie s and Ollie see a
giant monster attacking a town oh my God
that's another one of those super jets
that let me choose
things you have a ray guy that what Ray
guy what does that mean the more loving
towards people the shooter
is the more powerful it will be which of
you should fire the ray gun oh oh that's
a tyo a ray gun you have a ray gun that
the more loving towards people the
shooter is the more powerful will be
which of you should fire the ray gun at
the most
oh
[Music]
s oh maybe Ollie but probably not
me I think they are more love loving
towards people than I am and Mary casig
Danish looking for the top D doctor Dr
Arc KN dun nuclear Rover dun sandwich
dun pineapple stex thank you for the red
super
chat I'm finally back for my trip ooh
welcome back I was working in New
Orleans for a month and a half oh I had
bad internet and missed so many streams
I want to catch up on everything but I'm
also looking forward to the sports
festival thank you for being awesome K
and good luck thank you well welcome
back nice to have you here
again please enjoy the streams 1 month
and a half H you might have missed some
cool cool things yeah definitely but uh
you should maybe start by catching up
with
vampire uh my new song cover on my
channel released on Halloween and
joy thank you
looking for
[Music]
the
D thank you yeah my part is so cool in
the music video
froggy oh
yeah that is the wrong froggy though
that one here down here is way cuter it
imagine her making those sick moves
those sick dance
moves she would be so cuter so much
cuter no no no no no this one is better
trust me once you see her and frie you
will you will agree with
[Music]
me
mhm D thank
you yeah call gave me a great showcase
part really appreciate
it Kelly what a
chat Nick s thank you for the pinky yeah
one of my favorite Parts about the
Halloween party as a viewer were the
side conversations people would have
when they weren't the focus of one of
the camera people there were some really
heartwarming moments also vampire K that
was
[Music]
cute yeah uh I don't
know I was like trying to stay on the
side uh for most of the time once I
realized that I couldn't really
um how to say couldn't really add any to
the stream that much most of the
time I was just chilling on the side um
but yeah I sometimes I felt like oh my
God I
am I am uh
old was so exhausted because of the VR
and the excitement and all of
[Music]
that oh yeah I'm was like ah
I was looking out for me but I was also
trying to look out for her cuz uh must
have been really really difficult to
coordinate all of that and um you know
keep the keep everything organized and
follow the schedule of things that uh
she wanted to do with
us so I also wanted her to have some fun
but I think I think she had fun anyway
even when she was yeah
wrangling no she wasn't really rangling
myth if anything she was wrangling
Council
council is like they're like those those
super young kids that are like super
excited because they're I don't know at
their first concert ever or whatever I
don't know their first party
ever oh my God I felt like I was 100
years older than
them I can't keep up with them at least
not in VR I don't know the VR like makes
me
uh I don't know it turns me into a
different person
almost I'm was like a kindergarten
teacher yeah yeah yeah
yeah
yeah I'm such a genius though I love all
the ideas and in the in that stream and
she added so much to the map again I
mean I mean she had a lot of things
added again I don't know where she gets
all those ideas from that map is turning
into a whole game like you could you
could base a whole game off of that
map
yeah I really thought that the new
additional Maps were really really
pretty very welld
designed
yeah
[Music]
amazing plans to use small vampire K
again oh I mean I guess it would be a
waste so even if it's not really
fitting uh sure why
not via chat is actually dope it is I
see it as a special way for us
to kind of
like satisfy ourselves for the time
being um because I feel like you know if
it weren't for the
seing we I don't know who knows maybe
maybe we would have gotten 3D already
and um also the fact that we can't live
we can't meet up that easily to do off
collabs so it's kind of like our way to
make up for it for ourselves not really
for the viewers for
ourselves that we can't meet and we
can't just do 3D like that like the
Japanese members can do it so it's our
special
thing and and and yeah for now I think
it's really cool that we have it and it
it does a good job at making up for it
cuz the streams and the clips and the
the screenshots and all that that come
out of it are really great memories and
so hilarious
and I feel like like you know those
those 3D deut streams in in whole live
as much as I love watching those now
that we've done VR chat stuff I I feel
like the VR chat collapse that we've
done so far kind of show our our
derpiness and
our charm way more than like one of
those 3D streams could ever do cuz those
are so perfectly organized and
everything must be perfect and and and I
don't know everything must be planned
and and I don't know it's just it's just
has to be absolutely perfect right so
with the VR chat stuff it's just us
derping around having fun doing stupid
things that we want to do being
dorks
and I don't know it's so it it's it's
probably so much more entertaining
than you know a normal 3D debut stream
or whatever could be I mean those are
always legendary don't get me wrong and
I can't wait to do one of those
on my own I love watching those I would
love to have one of my own one day but I
feel like that matches the style of
whole life Japan a lot and the vrj stuff
matches the style of whole life English
a lot you know what I mean both are
beautiful but if I were to say which one
really shows what H life English
is and how how we we
like Vibe together and how we want to be
a feel like the VR chat things so far
have captured it very well yeah the
personalities as well it's super chaotic
and the whole I don't know the the even
though it was just supposed to be
something scuffed and small it turned
out to be so beautiful and big like the
whole map is like so high quality and
the Wy
models the style from Wy is like so
simple and yet I feel like those Wy
models capture our Essence so
wonderfully I love being the wfy
model it's just so
adorable yeah but but still one day I
want to show you my full body in its
full glory in a proper
perfectly uh recreated 3D
model and with proper trackers proper
sensors and everything I want to be able
to do a proper choreography for you and
I want to showcase it all of my body I
want to showcase it beautifully to
you looking forward to that day me
too yeah and I think like once that 3DW
is over with we can like use those
models maybe in VR chat as
well maybe I I think it should be
possible or like just for like home 3D
and stuff like that
too and and even like afterwards I feel
like because we don't have an easy
access to a
studio like the Japanese girls do I
think I would I would want to do my best
to make like something like a full body
stream at home possible as well and I'm
sure Amed would definitely want to work
on something like that too but that's
for the future that is for the far far
far away
[Music]
future but but imagine imagine if Amma
has that power where is she going to
stop no one can stop her
Amelia with a proper 3D model that she
can use anywhere anytime she wants oh my
God she cannot be
stopped
Yi vo and sod already do that but you
mean only the hands right I mean like
full body like with with feet and
everything unlimited power yeah can we
really give her that much
power oh my
[Music]
God sorry yes I may I may be sing about
M
again I mean the best the most amazing
setup would be uh a setup like that what
what's that chick called that girl I
forgot the name but she has a really
amazing setup with like really
expensive stuff at home the girl who can
like
seamlessly yeah yeah yeah yeah uh yes
yes Cod
M that would
be I
think something
to
Aspire anyway I wanted to read Super
Chat and there were some really
heartwarming moments also vampire K was
cute thank you Nick s I'm glad you guys
liked vampire K I think you guys would
have uh probably died if I were made NE
Mimi made or cat ear made Kata so I I
guess it's probably good that I kept
that from you vampire Kata was super
cute as well but
Catgirl made Ki would have killed you
guys Kon D Rocky the kfp pet rock I want
to cry but I have no eyes oh my
God jump King please play
me nine dun tyen
dun
I don't think we've been disunited in
wanting to see you totally delete
someone ah that was about that
boss thank you D influx 27
Dan thank you good night Baron man D
there snatch their snatch
B oh my God what are you doing uh like
that those ones are not pinkies where
did the pinkies are this one is wait is
is this like a
[Music]
huge wait what what's going on no those
are stickers 50,000 is a pinky okay okay
but this is
the all of those together are almost a
[Music]
pinky uh Let me refresh this though cuz
I'm pretty much at the end of my
list oh you're here in the chat too I
mean of course you
are do you all understand English
can I ask you why you send super chats
without any message do you want to
trigger
me I'm a shout a fried trim frd model
that was scrapped so she can be a
dinosaur are there any scrap frd cans
that could have been already no no no no
nope nope not that I know up
no my chat is broken there we go he he
wrote something in
Korean
my browser is so weird right now Korean
translator what does it say Can
English okay
[Music]
okay
for hi
[Music]
baby
she's on the chair next to me how does
she
always she knows she has a feeling for
what time it is my
cat so what's the answer was there an
answer to what I just
asked my baby I'm a
baby 3D models for your cats well of
course I'm working on just kidding I'm
not working on it yet but it's a goal
for the
future you cannot tell me that cats
don't know the term I like how much
trust you have in cats I like that
you're one of the good
people where was I here here here
there's snatch
ban wait does your Korean name say the
same
thing let me
see B
snatch Bender snitchy Bender snatchy
sounds so different Bender ah because
the order is different their snatch b b
their snatch what kind of name is that
thank you for your many many many many
many many many many pink super chats you
don't understand English but what if you
don't understand English you understand
what I'm what I'm
saying uh
uh can H can you understand
[Music]
me
please open Camp be dur in Korea look
around the corner it might already be
there oh yes yes
really wait I knew the word for really
[Music]
a it's not working
thank
you thank you you for your
support did you know Po in h German is h
a cute word for
but po po but you wouldn't pronounce it
so uh like with a double P it's actually
just p o p o popo
popo please give me no don't give me
butt no no no give me Papa POA
shut up don't think about I know I have
a nice butt but don't no no no it's
embarrassing St D of L thank you for the
r
that I'm finally fried after 13 months
in kfb all I want to say is besides
being part of a great Community I'm also
grateful that you're my aie of course
you are
I'm also glad that you are oting me
you're so sweet and kind maybe that's
why after Year my love for you has only
grown a I love this job and I love my
intenal I'm so happy to hear that you
know I'm always scared of people losing
their interest in me I'm always scared
of that because it's just a natural
thing so thank you I'm I don't know what
I did to make you love me more but I
love you
too I will always love
you I will always love
[Music]
you and
I will always love
you Will Always Love
You DC come at me come at me bro come
try to get me come try I have an army of
chickens that will kill
you Felix thank you cute cat in your
profile picture Del when what the
any wait Korean name
[Music]
who's do who is the girl I love only
Kiana understandable but the keyword uh
is still the
same
[Music]
nice
oh my God why is everything so
broken you were listening oh
sheit oh sheit oh oh oh sheit oh
oh
sheit are you still
here I was like um because I was trying
to um you know be a bit on the side uh
uh where uh there's not too much chaos
going on during the Holloween stream um
I was able to look at some beautiful
details I mean all the memes and stuff
were funny too but there's like it's not
all just memes it's like generally a
beautiful
map I love especially I think the part
uh where we were sitting in a in a
circle to tell ghost
stories yeah yeah yeah as Kellie said as
well you know Stars she didn't say it
like that but the Stars was were
beautiful I was I was trying to figure
out if uh the stars were actually um
aligned in like a St a a star sign star
sign that's not what it is right what's
it called again I was trying because it
looked looked like it to me a little bit
constellation yeah it looked like
constellations to me but I generally
don't know much about constellations so
I wasn't sure but it looked like they
were constellations maybe made up
constellations yes they are aligned
constellations at least oh are there
like real constellations or or like
madeup constellations yeah s would know
I wonder if she ever looked in the sky
during the stream you looked at the star
map
oh see there's a lot of people who can
look at a sky and find like simple
constellations and be like that's this
and that's that I'm not one of those do
you guys know if you would look at the
sky if you were to see actual
Stars cuz in some places you don't
really see them but if you would look up
to the sky and you see a constellation
would you be able to recognize some of
them nope nope
some nope nope nope yes I would have no
idea a couple yeah there are some simple
ones it's really interesting I uh I
remember when I was younger I think
my my my
my my parents maybe tried to be like oh
this is this this is this and that I
heard it before but I don't remember at
all
[Music]
oh oron Little Dipper Big Dipper what
were those called in German again Little
Dipper Big Dipper I feel like they had
those are uh feel I I remember the
German names if I were to read
it it's a
[Music]
SP you should recognize at least 16
constellations at the very least what do
you mean me why me why would I be able
to recognize at least 16 when I just
said I wouldn't be able to recognize any
at all what are you hinting at something
are you making a joke is this a
meme thank you unit 1 E I'm almost done
anyway what
what oh my stomach oh it hurts I need to
finish
[Music]
this do they mean for Survivor oh is
that what you
mean to find your way through the
Wilderness huh anyway anyway anyway
anyway
life you sent you sent it in Japanese y
but you're right in Coran
interesting H oh no wait I read
that oh
fighting fighting yeah Salas beat thank
you for the red super chat I enjoyed
your vampire release so take this to
help fund the future projects thanks for
doing y I decided to make a trip for it
and was glad I did oh
wonderful yeah I saw you there you do
stand out a lot you've been a lot of
these things now and you you also show
your face in hotam must stream so yeah
yeah you have a you're like the face of
kfb soon you should at least no big dip
or no star from that it can come in
handy oh if for finding directions or
what
H I need to I honestly just need to know
it to flex I want to know it in order to
flex anyway even got to hang with the
panel organizer and see his unlicensed C
be what wait no he just showed you
pictures right he didn't actually bring
you to his house did
[Music]
you right but yeah nice that you met up
with some other kid people I like that
it sounds like fun just pictures oh yeah
he told me about about that too like
before the panel started we were having
like a chitchat and he was telling me
about the his 10 chickens or his I think
it's his wife's 10 chickens and uh yeah
we talked about that it was
funny meeting up with cave people is
amazing you would know wouldn't
you I want to meet up of K of people
too one day concert I will have you guys
there right one day we'll have a
concert sorry I forgot again to send the
recordings it might never
happen oops no no no no no and Rogan
stri and I think I forgot the kiss for
cous
beats thank
you last
refresh well if you couldn't there in
person you can probably watch it online
so so it doesn't matter where you
are thank you for the pinky no text of
it are you sure are you sure is there
like a Emoji nope no emoj okay you do
you you do you thank you for your
[Music]
support
mathio Gonzalez
D thank you thank you thank you for the
support black FR thank you for the pinky
sub's trash can remembers well where you
are where where where are you are you
can't speak English show your face in
the chat come on black FR come on come
on come on come on write something I
want to give you a kiss you might have
sent a pinky but let me give you a kiss
come on show yourself Show Yourself show
there you are come let me give you a
kiss uh
or it might have been something else it
might have been the 300 second block
oopsie wrong button
oopsie my finger
[Music]
slipped Elbert
sco I'm more obsessed with you each day
by the way that Doo question took a
while to
answer wait what Doo question oh oh oh
no no no no no no I was just distracted
no no no no no all right we're done guys
we are
done I need to bring back the kiss
button yeah or like the hug button oh I
I need to clean up my my office yeah
yeah I want my button again but wasn't
it wasn't the problem that the button
doesn't work well in my office isn't
that the
problem yeah Applause thank you you guys
applaud for me just finishing my super
chats even though it's my duty okay it's
not really my duty but I want to do it
because it's my
my my heart it's my duty my heart tells
me I have to do it thank you for the
membership
renewal made me no I did I I skipped
skippity dood no well wait wait wait
wait wait did I did I really skippity
doodle I accident I accidentally did do
that yeah sorry about that what the hell
how did I do that oh wait I skipped a
bunch cuz
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I uh continued
at the wrong spot sorry about that sorry
sorry I skip the punch all right here it
is Tanaka thank you for the red super
chat K thank you so much for the stream
it's been an absolute blast and it's
exactly what I needed today I would love
to see you play more games like this in
the future they really suit your
swimming cell really you're the best K I
keep being awesome thank
you I will try also my brows are just
broken need to fix my
CH give me back my Applause no you can
you can keep
it or I will keep
it I will keep it for later okay I'm not
that far
off do I get a kiss or what of course
you're going to get a kiss why you feel
like you need to
ask I love giving kisses to my
chickens
thank you you're awesome too than from
the bottom of my bro
Coco
than Korean
[Music]
name there we
go7 RP w n KT uh sent
three was it was it red ones or
pinkies those that red ones or pinkies
anyway let me start reading K you played
Alice one year ago you did a p drawing
bunny connection
aha uh I think there's more bunny
connections than that one last year you
kept me company as I worked home I left
and returned a few hours later you were
still on I saw your dedication and also
everyone's in h
life it was pinkies oh okay I went deep
on H life and YouTubers in general after
that day you were crucial in me
appreciating you all oo I also relate
with your experience of living and
working abroad in a second or third
language I am too an ESL and work in
English oh cool
respect M I admire your dedication and
everything you do for your community
being an idol whole life YouTubers on
and off stream and of course
kfp thank you for everything love you
forever a see I wouldn't want to miss
that Super Chat that's really really
sweet
[Music]
than thank you love your drawing streams
too yeah I was thinking of doing one
again at some point yeah yeah and thank
you thank you um yeah I think like if
you able to do a job or get hired for a
job in English even though it's not your
first language then that really means
that your English is good so
good job good job to
you and thank you for supporting me for
a long long long time I hope you will
not leave me ever you must
not and again there snatch Ben wait did
I even give him kisses B there snatch
no I did I definitely did I remember I
gave lots of kisses but he deserves even
more he sent like a million super chats
thank you I think now I read them all
unless yeah this new one bamos thank you
for the pinky text thanks for organizing
the big Ian collab Oh you mean the the
Among Us one it was a lot of fun I hope
you all had as fun uh playing as we did
watching I love to see I love that I
love to see that game again movie all
thank
you yeah yeah yeah I definitely had fun
I want to play it more but I don't want
to tire out the girls too much with
Among Us so got to squeeze in some other
games every now and then thank you
though black FR thank you for the pinky
time out this Shin Queen here I love
where you back get out of here get out
of here ah you keep on following me then
I must leave then I must end the
stream I cannot escape from black fre
help me I must leave I I'm I'm being
stalk just kidding love
you yeah it's fun to spread it out I
think so too it seems like that now the
proximity uh mod is now like a must
because just uh the other
day just the other day the Japanese
girls were playing it right with the
proximity mod as well like M Senai and
so on I was watching them was
funny was a scream
o h on
come I'm waiting for you waiting for you
to succeed in music you can do
it thank
you
tomorrow's stream mayday
mayday listen up tomorrow's stream is on
aqua's channel don't stream on my
channel I guess and the day after is a
day off too right I think so yeah sorry
I love you I will miss you I don't know
how to live about
you oh no maybe
gorilla no I shall not I cannot I cannot
do it I already did a gorilla on Monday
we will see uh how I
feel we will see what happened thank you
though I love you guys I feel like I
missed
[Music]
something wasn't there one yeah yeah D
Trevor I'm not addicted I am I'm
addicted not to streaming but to you
guys thank you yes Aqua Aqua Senai
tomorrow on her Channel I'm giving her
um a tour for the uh Ian Minecraft
server M
K
what
what what's your problem what's your
problem
[Music]
next J Monkey
D hi Casper
Aqua is usually too shy to collab yeah
I'm actually now it's been a while since
the Hol talk we got along so well in Hol
talk but now I'm kind of nervous again
cuz it's been a while and I feel like
she will be nervous so that makes me
nervous uh I got to prepare some talking
topics for for for tomorrow I guess but
mostly I think the the whole tour will
be the topics so that usually um gets me
to talk a lot anyway so should be fine
but she already saw a lot I I should
maybe watch her stream again to see what
exactly she
saw N I don't have time I need to go to
sleep
ASAP I will eat I will eat food now and
see we didn't even um go over midnight
that much we finished the Super
[Music]
Chat
one reason why I'm not doing the
Minecraft collab on my channel is first
of all because you guys have already
seen it a million times I've already
given a million tours and I feel like I
don't want to repeat the same content
over and over again and second of all if
I don't stream it on my channel I don't
have to feel bad about
[Music]
Shrine or in front of good secret uh
Garden you guys probably know what I'm
talking
[Music]
about see you guys on channel I really
need to go I need to go to an idle
meeting and eat food thank you I love
you
guys oh yeah the
hole maybe I'll show her the hole I I
wonder if she'll think it's
funny oh bye
bye oh bye bye byebye oh yes me good
night good night I'll enjoy my pasta my
bologa my spaghetti now I can I can cook
it now without a recipe and yes that's
not even that
amazing I think last time I cooked it I
could have probably also done it without
a recipe but I was just making sure I
was making short now I did it without a
recipe completely and it was really
yummy
yeah what what do you mean
no you just Add Water I'm not talking
about the noodles I'm talking about the
sauce the meat sauce I was making meat
sauce
pasta all right and in German we say you
really want me to say it don't you
Brian you can't kicking me
out are you kicking me your boss
out and in
[Music]
j
byee
no no you're not sorry I love you I
could never say that to you
guys you said all of this
in you're
stupid
my name d made it
s oh wait the music
oopsie oops oh wait there's no music
here anyway what happened why is there
no music you guys hear
music when did the music disappear why
did I do
that all right look out for my tweet on
Twitter please if you want to take part
in the give away although yeah you could
already do it without the Tweet
[Music]
still okay byebye yeah fixed it
I already tweeted ni
nice don't forget to follow uh American
Mickey so that he can give you uh send
you a
DM okay
byebye