[Music]
look up at the Horizon together as one A
Star Is On The Rise and it's only begun
the pivotal moment we're clamoring for
and infinite Futures at our door it's
time with story with a new field not
just it's real wake up big dreams about
to come true that means it's time to
break through never knew we could make
it so far but we're striving thriving
here we are for achieving the impossible
we're virtually Unstoppable we can't sit
still we just keep moving now everybody
sing we're making our way to the next
Dimension we'll reinvent the world that
we live in we'll G every day with new
intentions break conventions run right
through the Smashing barriers left the
RO strong as we ever were scaling home
so get together let's reunite Reach Out
reach out the future bright we've been
together for what feels like an eternity
the times are changing but we're ready
for Infinity yeah our story is in line
we're going to go far when we come by so
look at the Horizon and then look Beyond
we'll marel at the skies and the
strength the B we're making a vow in the
smileing Stars a powerful moment that's
all
our seasons change but we keep shining
now everybody see keep it going we're
making our way to the next Dimension a
million drills in every direction we'll
give every mile or full attention
breaking tension breaking through with
them most energy stronger
we PR a perfect time we div we prise so
clap along with me time to rise the
future's right before our rise a new
dimension of Freedom that we found yeah
we've made
it we're breaking out of the mall no
longer B we're we're going to Spring to
life and break chain turn up the hype
can't be contained we're shaking up the
St qu no time stop we're good to go wide
world is listening so everybody
sing we're making our way to the next
Dimension we're living out the trees we
believe in excitement Beyond a
comprehension there's no question we'll
break through don't relax we keep the
smiling to ex it's our insir ring going
R so like the fire R let's reel the
future sper we can tell
[Music]