[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
and get out of your head life is only
what you make it you're gonna be okay
[Music]
everybody's gonna know your name
cause spikes
[Music]
keep your feet
take a step
s
[Music]
hey hey
[Applause]
[Music]
got a fire today
hi everybody
my voice it works it's working
I can't feel oh oh wait wait you have so
much to react to you have me to react to
but you have this place to react to
right oh my God yes we started with a
banger we started with Sparks one of
your favorites I think right same for me
[Music]
English first generation myth yeah it's
real oh my God yes this is KFC
wow so many details we shall look around
oh
hahaha
[Music]
yes oh while we're here
hi uh what's your name
Harry Harry oh nice to meet you Harry
how are you doing today what are you
eating
uh he's eating the yakub burger which is
also on the menu up there yeah and also
the chicken bucket oh my God how are you
eating so much alone
I can't even I can't even relate it's
eating way too much two pieces of fries
Jungle Burger oh a shake probably Oreo
shake and the chicken bucket damn oh I'm
also getting hungry hungry let's look
around a bit more
we have the menus up there oh
oh inspired by of course the real Cafe
menu because this is the real deal there
is hot dogs hamburgers smart what the
hell is a smart Burger I don't know who
the hell
is on I don't know anything about the
smartphone or do I get smart if I eat
that and we have a phoenix Burger of
course Diego Burger apparently it's
black I didn't know about that so much
good looking stuff
and we have a kitchen in the back
everything yeah
yay
it's so cheap it's I think it's cheap
all right well
let's say hi to Jimmy who just hatched
again
people always worry about you to me how
you doing your life again yeah you know
I ate you recently so I felt like you
deserve to be reborn to me my sweet boy
yes aren't you cute little boy look at
him look at him look such a good boy
oh he's in his uniform he's ready to uh
work right as he has been hatched
immediately he wants to get to work he's
frightened he's not frightened
you're not scared Yes Yes actually he
can I think he can walk a little bit
I think he can walk
let's go let's go Jimmy let's go to work
let's go to work Jimmy
he's so cute okay I pick you up because
you're still a baby in your heart play
twice if you need help no he cannot
blink he's incapable of blinking
don't say that well actually he's not
the only one right there's more people
working here
where's all the others where are you
guys
oh my god oh so many so many you're
ready for yourself hi hi hi
hi
oh so many gave me maybe some new ones
some old ones
yeah you're ready me too
Timmy Timmy Timmy this is Imagine This
is you guys it might be Jimmy but just
imagine it too
sure so proud of you don't feel proud
ready for yourself well actually I think
there's more okay bye bye go get to work
go get to work go get to work I'm gonna
go
get to work too
[Music]
[Applause]
uh Smiles are for free I guess
[Music]
so we have a register
so I can you know take your
change oh no you I take your money I
give you change here five cents there
you go
um
don't do that on me okay don't do that
be quiet don't ding ding ding ding no
Karen's allowed either no no only good
customers and good employees yeah and
then up here I already showed you the
menus and the buyers menus the kids are
not working hard
are you working hard or hardly working
what was that
I could also go back there but not right
now
I think we should play a game okay
play the game
[Music]
love is just a game I can't complain I
do the same
well actually no no no not a game it's
real business it's the real stuff I am
essential after all so I think we need
to prove it because you guys sometimes
doubt me right no doubting allowed
I I have all these ingredients prepared
we have some
yeah the famous One
[Music]
oh that's a good stuff it's perfectly
seasoned it's perfectly crispy as it
should be we have the bucket
it can't be rocking which is it still an
emote if it's so remote you guys gotta
post it but did I take it down
it at least used to be a chatty mode for
a long time
[Music]
I I had to get rid of it oopsie wow
imagine and then we have some
ingredients we have the tomatoes salad
and pickles and we have cheese with
um onions
and we have several patties and now this
is the difficult part because there's
three pieces of bread we have the top
one the middle one and the the bottom
one I've never had a burger before which
has a middle part because I know I can't
eat it alone oh well um before we play
the game can I drink some water
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
[Music]
what does that entail I think you can
guess but looking at the stuff I'm gonna
be looking at the screen to see what I
have to make for the customer and then
I'll make it and we'll see if it's right
but I have to remember it
will my memory hold up
all right quicker ready bring it on baby
Bring it on Bring it on Bring it on
[Music]
bottom Patty middle
okay I think I have to read freestyle
some of this
I think it was another Patty maybe and
then some something green but not all of
it I don't remember and then look at
that
[Music]
I'm not sure about this one
I it was almost right it was just oh it
was this this one
[Music]
this this would have been
I think right yeah
but it's not fair it's not fair one more
one more one more
oh
let's put it back
and then we'll do the next one
all right this time this time this one's
warm up okay
round two go
[Music]
can I already started
I really don't remember I'm so nervous
you can't do this to me I think there
was like at least one chicken in there
[Music]
I just the wrong one
because that was not the top one I mean
who knows what they do to bamboos on me
but no way no
give me a break please uh well I don't
know so let's just go with this
[Music]
I don't know okay
laughs
yeah the real thing is
how was I even supposed to build that
like there's it's it's impossible
you're you're making me create things
that are not even possible I'm so angry
I have to go drink some tea
and we have one more round I think
[Music]
yeah
let me take this apart
Angry T what the [\h__\h] okay let's not
let's not swear in my in my
big big 3D stream let's not swear on
this one okay
let's try
more difficult from the sun right
on this oh
okay
we're on free please
bread salad bread meat meat chicken meat
bread okay
which one is it uh
red if I say it out loud I think I
remember bread salad which one breath
I'll just go with this one because I
think I would have said cheese if it was
the other one right bread salad bread
um meat
chicken
meat
oh if I get this right you guys
enlighten me for a burger right
[Music]
I think you're not maybe not sure what
order this is but
[Music]
okay guys
no what was it
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
there's not even cheese in the picture
how am I supposed to remember that she's
a knight on Castle
[Music]
but besides that I was right
well I mean
in the end this is your job this is your
job not my job I'm just here to observe
that's my job okay well
so I think it's better if I just do
mostly Idol work and dancing and singing
right
mainly
[Music]
and you can still look like okay well
then with that
next song let's turn this place into a
disco
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
I'm tired of the same song
everyday like it's on repeat I need a
Escape breakdown
oh honey
the night is now
[Music]
take me away like it's just the two of
us
[Music]
[Applause]
come alive
[Music]
foreign
Don't Look Away now it's just the two of
us
[Music]
come alive
thank you
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
that was on purpose that was a
transition guys like a commercial yeah
did you and I Fever Night in my own
personal disco hmm basically it was like
if you guys were saying it in the in the
chat I think but basically you get food
and you get a performance it's like ah
is there is there something like this
already existing if not then absolute
Gina genius and even if that's still
genius right yeah yeah that was like a
disco ball and the floor was disco
everything was disco
10 out of the 10 established one thank
you thank you please uh vote 10 out of
10 for kfv and come back okay and
actually you know what that's not a
choice anyway
Studio Movie Grill what what does that
mean
anyway Kelly Kelly speaking of Cali
um I think I'm gonna maybe need to talk
to her personally and actually all of
the myth members shall we talk to them
yay
I'm just gonna pull the voicemail prank
what no no voicemail no you're really
here right now right okay
thank you really quickly let's do
introduction here this one is
onion ring and this one is Maury except
[Applause]
out of these ones this one this Taco
already had her reveal the rest I did
are two three
yeah I'm really nervous right now but
you girls being here helps me a little
bit
it doesn't happen once yeah finally you
are amazing so far Kiara
[Music]
thank you
thank you well
um there's actually a hashtag up there
right hashtag Kiana sleepy party and
with that if you guys are wondering what
should we tweet well how about some
screenshots and I'm gonna I already
posted something yeah the hashtag is
hashtag Kiara 3D party yes yes
you heard exactly but in order to take
some great screenshots I think we need
your help my DMs members so are you
ready to you know do some stuff with me
I've been waiting okay I'm ready Kyle
okay let's start with
[Music]
oh I can go back there I have permission
yeah if it's you yeah okay okay my pose
is the the fetal position
feet tall did I hear correctly fetal
position yeah yeah you want me to become
feet
us I said it's like a baby right
[Music]
yeah
I guess it's more like more closer yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
can you give me something that's more
safe for Twitter please
um yeah
um okay I would like you to uh give me a
pose that would entice me to buy all of
the chicken
to buy all of the chicken oh okay I
guess it's not that kind of chicken okay
okay
seven challenge
[Music]
how's that doesn't it smell nice
um
is that enticing do you feel like buying
some Andrew yes thinking about it how
about the buckets
okay
[Music]
there's like 12 so pieces in there sure
combo the combo
it's number nine please
for free today it's on me
what a deal
oh speaking of Ina
[Music]
the special deal on your belt too you
know maybe perhaps take out your weapons
oh my goodness
what's she doing oh hitting the ground
I'll go get my sword and my shield we
got biscuits here stab me
[Music]
oh
powerful okay
this is a familiar scene
oh no all right feisty I want you to
take your sword
and lick it huh no actually okay licking
is okay too but I'll I'll give you a one
up here how about okay you know the
sword sword eating thing
yeah
oh my God
like you know the camera that went down
my throat yesterday that's enough yeah
it's a bit sensitive right now okay
but we're seriously for real for real oh
for real I would like you to make the
letters K F and P okay using away with
my away with my stuff okay
kfp yeah okay
um
wrong side
there we go
[Applause]
I'll take it okay
not least
what do you got yeah I want to order
some chicken some chicken legs
um I want to see those chicken legs uh
trying to balance in the cutest idle
pose that you can for the longest time
oh balance so one leg challenge one leg
on one one chicken leg here we now let's
go so we got idle pose we're gonna talk
about everything
interesting have you ever been to
Medieval Times before medieval times
yeah yeah
that's what I was thinking when you said
dinner in a show besides Studio Movie
Grill yeah
you don't mean the Medieval Times Like
many thousands years ago you mean like
there's a place like that no there's a
place called oh of course we mean the
medieval times right yeah yeah hey I can
do this forever Kelly oh my god well
stick your okay you need to put your
other foot up higher
you're cuter pull it up
higher higher
higher higher oh higher higher higher
higher
let's go yeah let's go can she stay on
one foot ladies and gentlemen well
that's fine
I really don't know how that one works
so I don't know you do something it's
not just this yeah you like it turn you
like do the hokey pokey and you shake it
all about or something like that yeah
I hope that was enough for the
screenshot again
I was too happy I was too happy
don't worry there will be more
opportunities
that's it
thank you so much for coming girls
[Music]
all right
okay so wow
there is still more to come though
because this is where this is where my
jam mates right
but I feel like I need something that's
not cardboard how about we bring in some
pretty guests all right but for that we
have the same location
let's change
oh
[Music]
thank you
hello hello
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
come on
[Applause]
[Music]
tomorrow
my life
[Music]
calm down calm down okay
please introduce yourself this is the
legendary survival
[Music]
[Applause]
my name is
nice day
[Music]
finally we're together
yes
my showcase
um
especially you are here
yes
[Laughter]
oh
Canada body is like fruits beautiful oh
which fruits
[Applause]
[Laughter]
you probably have you have said before
the famous Subaru dance
what I want to do it and then you guys
put it together please you guys just put
put the song on there all right okay
okay let's go okay
it's me
it's easy
[Laughter]
yes
after
okay but after this oh after this
I have a question
[Music]
why this song why do you choose
[Laughter]
a song from my favorite Idol
groups because
[Laughter]
[Music]
let's go
oh
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
can us
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
as soon
forever
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
la la
my second question
generation
[Music]
so actually
um you guys probably know together
people call us a name which is
[Music]
so thank you for calling us I I knew
that if I had to call a guest for my
show okay
yeah
[Music]
so this is basically the first time that
orenzo is dancing together
we are Idols so I want to create some
kind of like I go to a boy uh greetings
okay
[Music]
Global International okay so how about
we make the whole world Orange
we need some movement
[Music]
um
what is this okay
[Music]
okay
don't forget this is our official
greeting now
it's ah one more thing let's talk about
the song and our practice and all that
um
I love hello project and this is from
cute the idol group
yeah and it's very dramatic sad song
with a strong dance moves draw Strong
choreography
foreign
we had two hours of dance lessons
together yeah the dance dance teacher
was like oh you guys are learning it so
quickly and she was happy
um
[Music]
she's saying it was morning time so she
was so tired but it was way past morning
um
[Music]
but it was fun and I hope we can do more
okay
[Music]
welcome back to kfp guys I'm sorry it's
not over yet I have something really
important for you guys and that is
could it be that's right merchandise
nice okay
let me introduce to you I mean you know
there's burgers and all that but this
time very special time limited offer for
you guys
time it is the beautiful hot Phoenix
thermal bottle and bottle case set
that's right it comes with like kind of
like a bag for the firmest bottle I
already saw it in reality and it looks
so good yay and of course it's firmness
which means your hot drinks will stay
hot and your cold drinks will stay cold
perfect genius oh my God so that's my
special 3D merchandise for this
occasions and and there's something else
that I want to tell you about tomorrow
yes tomorrow at 6 p.m jst my very first
is coming out hasta local time
there's well
um and of course tomorrow is also the
3DW of
so go check her out okay it's Taco
morning weekend yay so besides that I
have one more song for you guys but we I
think we should change location is that
okay change change all right what is
this one more station I haven't shown
you guys yet which is the big whole life
English stage let's go
YouTube
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
I did not give the permission to show
that video
I wasn't slacking I was practicing wow I
am here on this beautiful en stage right
now to perform one last song but before
that I want to say thank you guys so
much for waiting for such a long time
two and a half years I think roughly to
till we got to this point which is
unusually long but yeah we all were
patient and I think it was worth it I
hope so it wasn't worth it well I
practiced really hard for this day and I
tried really hard to fix my route for
this day so I hope you guys enjoyed it
it was a very special day for me I was
really nervous but
um I hope I could show you all the
beautiful Parts all the good things
about takanasikiara yeah let's do more
in the future okay
okay so with that the last song
do you
oh yeah
I Don't Wanna Stop it yet playing
English
[Music]
[Applause]
baby you decide
do you do you say
don't ever let yourself
[Music]
[Applause]
let me stop
I've hate all the same if you know play
that game baby
[Music]
[Applause]
don't pick me up just like you do always
[Music]
I don't know
hey
[Music]