[Music]
so
cakey
[Music]
you guys need to get the greeting right
i mean
it's not that hard it's kitty king
don't get that wrong
let me turn up the echo
[Music]
hi everyone
oh have you been waiting for this guys
um i think it's uh pretty obvious
that uh today super chat
was enabled
[Music]
how am i clapping
how does she do the clap oh i never
showed you guys before that i can
aware i can carry like one chicken leg
at a time as well
because uh you i showed you that when i
uh
carried two chicken legs at a time
but i can carry also only one because i
also already
ate the other one
hi thank you everyone for
all the super chats already um
wow that was um very fast
how long has it been
not even a week issue
oh my god everything's going so fast
hakunai it's what five days
i think i my debut was i think on
saturday
without the show
oh my god
oh my god wow yeah i am i am
pretty uh overwhelmed by
how fast things are going
but it's a happy thing a good thing
that these things are happening
[Music]
thank you guys thank you thank you thank
you
thank you i wanna um
i wanna say uh thank you to
um all the senpai's in her life
who have made this possible because it
wouldn't go this fast that
if if they weren't our beloved senpai's
from previous generations so big shout
out
i i don't think they understood that so
i'm gonna say it in japanese
[Music]
templar
oh my god what what do i do
with all these super chats
i will tell you what we will do like
that
and i have an idea
i have i told you in my
debut stream
cathy's on oh
okay visa made my life today
i should be the one giving you the super
chat kefi song
i should give you the super chat
why are you giving me the super chat
thank you oh my god thank you everyone
oh
i don't know if i am deserve all
this love but uh i'm really grateful
thank you so much everyone
well um
as i mentioned i i i
in my daily stream i have a dream which
is um
opening a worldwide fast food
chain a fast foot empire you might say
and i think from today on
i've seen i've seen it happen i've seen
the possibilities
[Music]
so i have i have already
invested with the with the super chats
that came before the stream start
thank you for everyone who already
invested in my business
before the stream uh
i have already opened
something
[Music]
we have opened a small version
of the future kiara fast food empire
wow
for now for now this will have to do
and with beauty super chats
we shall grow bigger and bigger and
bigger
and then i think
we will dominate the market
all over the world we will
oh yeah please invest in the stock
market in my stocks
please
[Music]
only selling um chicken
as it says fried chicken
but i'm i'm aiming to
sell much more to you guys because
chicken is just not enough
there's so much more fast food
i wanna sell so many things and i wanna
i wanna make a bigger restaurant
i wanna hire people to work for me
and i wanna be represented
in every country all over the world
we shall name our chain
[Music]
[Applause]
wow chiara fried phoenix yes
i shall name dao do
yeah we have fried phoenix
we weren't able to make a proper logo
yet
so yeah for now there's no logo on my
story
please just remember kfb
so today we will uh
no no no no no no no kfb
i'm not serving phoenix it's just
because um i am the one who's frying the
food
don't misunderstand
there's no there's only one phoenix in
this world and that is me so if i would
be selling phoenix i would have to sell
myself
we can't do that
it will mostly be young chicken mostly
but um we might have some beef as well
some beef burgers
maybe maybe some what could we do we
could do some hot dogs as well we have
to think about the menu
menu kangai
thank you thank you investors
you are all from today on investors
in the next biggest
wealth dominating fast food business
i hope you all like fast food because
that will be the only thing
selling we're selling the only thing
oh
[Music]
a good papa i see you also would like to
invest in my business
thank you oh i got such sweet papas both
kefi papa
and ruke papa have been so kind to
donate to the cause and all of you what
cannonball phoenix no there will be no
phoenix on the menu
vegetarian options ah
i will consider it
i will i will consider okay
indeed i have not thought about
vegetarian options before
but i will consider because i mean
yes we shall please every single person
all of the world will bring to you
everything you need we will bring you
all kinds of
burgers all kinds of nuggets all kinds
of
wings all kinds of uh drinks all kinds
of potato fries
and everything
everything you can think of so
let's move
thank you for the super chats
please invest in my fast business
wait i need my store again okay so i can
see the future i need it
so i can see the future
[Music]
well uh yes today
uh we will be using the program of the
wise
intellectual people which is
uh ms paint
only smart people use this program
what do you have a problem with that
atomic
smart gang intellectual gang
yes ms paint
yes my best friend actually
i i actually have a graphic tablet but
for like a week i have lost my
my pen so today we
will be again conducting this with mouse
have you seen my pen i wonder where my
pen is i've looked everywhere
ben where are you
i miss you ben i need my band i've been
looking for you such a long time and i
just can't find my pants
i looked under the bed i looked under my
pc
i looked under the bed i i looked under
my hats
you ate it did inna steal it again
i think she has enough pens i don't
think she needs my pen
but maybe she wanted the pen because
there was some chicken
juice or something on it
amelia i need your investigation ticket
well okay to tell you oh my god
to tell you what we've been doing
what we're going to do
i have i have realized
yeah we are hiring we're hiring from
today on i have realized in order
to be successful we must be smart
and we must be organized so
we are making
tiara a
fast food empire
[Music]
phoenix hi i don't know how to say this
word
hierarchy
is this how you say it i i looked it up
how you say it
before the stream hierarchy
okay let's make this prettier oh let's
make it orange
did i say it right close enough
hierarchy
that must have been it in german you say
wait even in german it's difficult
here it sounds so weird i never used
that word
so we must
create uh this chart
to um to get a clear view
of what we're gonna do you know
you know the scary screen is cut in half
oh wait how did that happen wait
oh
[Music]
like that yes how did that happen
okay thank you for telling me
dear fellow employee investor
big big brain bird
oh yeah okay okay okay what are you
doing obviously
this phoenix has no experience in making
a business like this so i need your help
[Music]
i'll be using some difficult english
terms
okay so let's start i think thank you
for the super chat
you can call me colonel
[Music]
here we go here we go k of p
k s p k f
colonel kiara or chiara
yeah okay so i have i have some
references okay so let's get started we
need
corporate executives
right whatever that means
i don't know what that means but we need
it
okay you know we need and it probably
should be small how do i
kind of like make something smaller that
i selected
oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah make it small
can you even still see it it looks kind
of um weird now
don't make things small first and then
make them bigger don't make them bigger
and then small you know that's how it
goes
then we need
okay then we need kfb forever yes
you take my entire stock well thank you
we don't have much
yet chief executive
officer whatever that means
make it smaller please a bit smaller
ah no go away go away i guess you can
stay there
i guess you can stay there
microsoft paint phoenix
we need a chief financial officer
then we need um
how then we need a
board of directors
and then we need a
president yes shall be me of course
by the way i will be reading all the
super chats
in a in a stream that will be
a bit later not today because after my
stream the
uh cali will be streaming and i don't
want to overlap
how do i get back to penn how do i
do i just how do i only okay now let's
make it
ah why is it bigger now
and hopefully i will not take like 10
hours to read all the super chats
okay does this look professional
looks professional right 10 out of 10
business plan
okay so we will have more
but all of this
since i don't have any employees yet
all of this shall be um
yes i
uh all of this
i will do leave it to me
leave it to me yeah
okay okay okay how do i get back to pen
i forgot again
hello hello how do i get back to pen
ah there we go i'm a paint beginner
and i probably should um get some advice
from paid professionals
maybe like i don't know is there any
paint professional
in whole life
eh maybe cali can do a bad job
i need a dog thank you thank you
oh my god
funny super chat okay now then
uh we need to we need some
smaller people oh some less
important people and uh we need
heart
that's a shitty heart i know i know i
know i know
we need marketing managers
and now we need um
wow nice heart
beautiful this is how my heart looks
after kiara uh after cali beat it like
every day sorry i didn't say
that
sales managers
stop beating my heart
oh thank you for the super chat oh
i want to read all the messages i can't
wait to read all the messages
please write nice messages okay
no bad messages we also need some
advertising
managers okay
and then
[Music]
i did not swear i did not swear
i did not why would i am a pure idol
quality quality controllers what
is it like a ps5 controller
that that's that looks really sexy did
you see those ps5 controllers they look
like a
robocall senpai
yes okay so
here i will uh i have to i can't take
any more rolls
it's a a little bit too much for me at
this point
so
wait wait wait wait where did it go
okay okay okay okay okay
bye thank you this is so
weird so many super chats
thank you thank you thank you thank you
okay so why is the pen smaller now
anyway so this these four posts
unfortunately we cannot afford to hire
so many people yet so um
starting from today i will hire
one important person to take care of
these roles
it shall be jago
please work for me guys
[Music]
please please from today on
when it comes to chiara fried phoenix
empire
um our turns
tables oh how the turntables
you shall work for me
oh how to turn tables
so jango will be taking care
he'll be he'll be the marketing manager
the sales manager
the advertising manager and the quality
controller
[Music]
i think he can do a good job
i hope he has some time he seems a bit
busy but uh
you gotta make time for these things
just when you don't have any employees
just hire your boss exactly it is me
it is me colonel kiara
well actually we should add that here
colonel
kiara how do i get rid of that one
how do i get rid of the other one where
are the paint professionals
wait can i delete that onion let me
write it again
[Music]
okay now
we kind of need some more like people
for the smaller things you know
we have some more things to do
thank you thank you morning super chat
so
let's uh let's do some we need some
some cooks and chefs okay
we need um
[Music]
we need some weight waiters
we need we need some
accountants and we need
[Music]
cashiers okay i'll think i'll think for
now
what
i am not sure if i am in the position
to hire my senpai's yet
if they want to work for me possibly
please send your application to kfp
management aka yago
i shall review them as well because of
course um
my opinion is the most important
yes please send all your applications to
yahoo if you want to work
for me you have to talk with bianco
first because uh he's kind of like um
he's kind of guarding
he's how do you call the people who
stand in front of the disco
i've never been to this school how do
you call the people who stan
in front of the disco a bouncer jago is
my bouncer
he's not only these things he's also my
bouncer
yeah so he'll be there in a suit
with his muscular
body
to protect me gatekeeping yeah
oh yeah okay so
these are four rules and
as i said i don't feel like i can give
these roles to
my senpai yet but
you know who i could maybe force to work
for me
the other halo live en members shall
work for me
for my kfp empire
so konohan
conditional money
no no no no kelly please i need your
help
please you can't say no you can't escape
yeah you can i know you can you can't
jump
uh no not you can juggle so many things
you can do this too so who do you think
would be the best as a cook
and chef from the whole life english
members
tell me now
i will use all of you you cannot escape
you know
you know enough a lot of innas
but don't you think maybe ina would also
be good as a waiter
because we only would have one waiter
but so many arms
are you sure guys
i guess we could make an extra stop
extra spot for a bloop
inna can do no no no no no no
yeah ah in a best way
yeah i would say so too don't you agree
makes sense right
so let's do ina
[Music]
as the waitress
for the first uh first first fast for
the
restaurant that i'm building you know
just the first and
afterwards we can hire people we're
taking applications
starting from today
so back to the cooks and chefs
who would be the bestest cook
or chef in whole live english
amelia emilia
oh why would you think so has she talked
about cooking before
i see she has indeed
some cooking experience
tasks
indeed i am i agree
thank you for reminding me
emilia will you take the position
as cooks and chefs you cannot say no
congratulations
congratulations congratulations
yes yes yes very good very good
so we still have left accountants
and cashiers
[Music]
what do you say thank you for investing
in kfb my friend thank you for the super
chats thank you thank you
what do you say who would be good for
accountant
someone with a big brain i would say
kelly
you say callie has a big brain
amelia again no no no no she can only
handle so many things
kelly kelly wow wow wow we all agree
okie looks like everyone wants it to be
cali
ah i wanted to
add some lettuce what i am the ceo now
yeah you know
the cooks and chef ceo
very nice everyone is getting a job and
you get a job
and you get a job and you get a job and
you all get a job yay
isn't this nice i'm providing jobs for
the world
i think for cassius we only have
one small girl left but let me confirm
with you
who would be the bestest to be a cashier
to take care of all the money of all the
money
and then probably give out the change
i think it must be jack
and um we still have
space for one more
and i think we will add one more
position because there's a secret member
wait wait wait wait wait how do i type
again
i told you guys i cannot let the
senpai's work for me
no coco senpai is probably gonna do
a hell hella good job if she works in my
restaurant
but i don't i can't i can't ask her to
work for me no no no no
please all the all the um
applications please to jago please send
them to yago
wait send
send applications
why you do this to me yes
okay very clear
okay there's another position
it is um
branch manager
yes i have made one more
well there's so much to do guys there's
so much to do
we have to become an empire we have to
be
available all over the world we need
some branch managers
yes yes indeed i think you guys already
know who i will pick for this
uh one second
can you guess
also i'm guessing wrong it is
[Music]
yay everyone got a job
from today on you are part
of the biggest the biggest fast food
empire
you're you are an investor
of the kiana fried phoenix chain yay
[Music]
okay oh
i shall save this and uh upload this
on
the thing called twitter
thank you so much everyone for for
wanting to work with me i uh
i i happily accept your applications
amelia in a cali
thank you for your applications i see
you have a good feeling for
what will be successful
you have good sense
eh luke has
escaped what what is the big news oh uh
i think uh some people have
maybe misunderstood the big news is that
the super chat is enabled
and that i am opening my
uh fast food empire here the other fast
food empire kiara fried phoenix yes
yay are you ready for all the
all the things that we will make happen
okay one second how do i make a new one
can i just delete i think i saved it
this phoenix is not good with paint
let's
this is gonna take too long how do i
delete uh
how do i make new
one second i just don't wanna show
anything that you shouldn't see
like my secret plans for world to the
domination
world domination how do i make a new one
again
okay okay
okay one more thing
now i really need your help with this
one
i don't have any references for this so
i took a nap before the streams are like
i could not look up
these things but what do we need we need
some
we need a menu for kfp
or the starting menu at least
okay now
this is uh just as important as all the
people
who are uh working with me
at kfb this is just as important
right okay i think we got some basic
things already down
it's obviously fried chicken
so what else
phoenix burger oh we can call it that
but obviously there will not be phoenix
inside of that
i think uh that is clear but what is in
the phoenix burger
i think it should be chicken meat it
should be um
salad salad is very important
take your vitamins and
what else is in here oh pineapple
this is the phoenix burger that will
take over the world
pineapples my microphone needs to be
adjusted
okay i hope that didn't hurt you guys
no yes yes yes yes yes
what yes yes yes yes
yes what kind of sauce should be there
do you have a problem papa with a
pineapple burger
is there a problem excuse me is there a
problem
uh barbecue sauce yeah sounds good
yeah barbecue sauce and
onions i guess oh
what else is in the burger
hot sauce i'm not such a big fan of hot
sauce to be honest we can have hot sauce
for other burgers but not for the
phoenix burger
tomato tomato
no pain only only only healing only good
stuff
chocolate mmm bacon okay bacon
bacon probably makes up for the
pineapple for a lot of people
cheese
[Music]
cheese i'll be very specific here
because i like mozzarella cheese
okay i think i think that would be a
wonderful
main burger our main seller
i will be selling it will be selling so
well
uh let's have one more burger we
shouldn't make too many burgers
yet you can of course send me ideas for
burgers
but maybe just one more burger
what do we do this should probably
should this be a beef
should this be beef
fox burger oh no yes you have to cook
this
amelia i believe in you just don't
don't mix in anything weird
okay we want our customers
to come into the store with a clear mind
and then leave the store
with a clearer mind
amelia understand
we want them to come back or maybe maybe
if we want them to come back you should
maybe mix in something funny
i'll leave it to you you can have some
creative freedom you know
i'll leave it to you i know you you're
good with those bigs
okay
do you have any um ideas for
the next burger veggie burger
maybe not yet maybe first uh something
we can we can add that to the menu later
but not right away
ostrich burger taco burger oh no
uh duck burger
rabbit burger no no rabbits will be
harmed
in this restaurant hamburger
maybe a classic before we go too crazy
but we can um it should maybe be beef
but maybe it should have like a
a special name what should we call
uh a beef berry what would be a good
name for beef burger
jackal burger yago burger
it is i mean now that he works for me
he he deserves to have a a burger named
after him
after everything he's done for her life
he deserves a burger named after him
tayago yagobaga
not one but two beef patties
two we go double
yes can you handle
two what yes yeah go burger yes yes
oh
what uh oh yeah salad i think is is
important
no pineapple this time but
but what could we put in instead of the
pineapple
say so sauce mushrooms ew
ew caramelized onion cheddar cheese oh
yeah we'll add that later
green pepper pickles i guess this must
have pickles
ah carrots egg
egg eggs
what sauce do we go for seiso sauce
you will never know what's in this
secret say so sauce by the way for the
people who don't know it means i'm
pure innocent
i even don't know what's in the say so
sauce
should there be a tomato maybe not
because we already got pickles and eggs
probably doesn't fit right
to have tomatoes maybe something instead
of the bacon
garlic oh mustard oh
should we have more than one sauce no no
no
you cannot mix things with the seiso
sauce it will not be say-so anymore
hash brown oh onion oh yeah onion
onion onion rings oh onion rings
yes i think we have
successfully created the yago
burger two beef patties salads
pickles egg cheddar cheese
and secret saco sauce and onion rings
oh yeah oh yeah
that sounds so good i'm getting hungry
oh my god i need to i need to
order some uber eats
all right now i think obviously we need
some
um
thank you for the super chat my friends
my investors we need some potato fries
potato fries
and yes nuggets yes yes
nuggets and for the nuggets and the
fries
we need some we need some sauces
now i've traveled all over the world
and i've seen certain countries with
certain sauces
and certain countries don't have the
other sauces which i think is ridiculous
because
why so i would like to add my favorite
sauce
besides obviously ketchup mayo
barbecue my favorite sauce for nuggets
is sweet and sour
okay but we can add more we i want all
the sauces
oh give me all the sauces i want to have
everything so nobody is like
why don't they have that sauce stupid
kfp
so okay what what do we need honey
honey mustard oh that sounds good that
sounds that sounds good
honey mustard what else ranch ranch
is there is that ranch dressing or ranch
sauce
i guess it's ranch sauce chili
chili chip is it with two out no it's
with one right
chili sauce
potato food
honey garlic what i've never heard of
that but we shall add it
garlic mayo oh yeah all the garlic
you can't have enough of garlic oh say
so
yeah we can have seiso sauce as an extra
in case someone wants to dip their fries
and nuggets into the seiso sauce
awesome salsa sauce oh
sorry well why not lemon pepper sauce
well that's
fancy oh so many sausages i want all the
sauces if you we would almost think
that this story is about sauces and not
about fried chicken
wasabi sauce
gravy
gravy blue cheese that's disgusting but
okay
but even maybe just like a normal cheese
sauce
why the hell does it have to be blue
cheese sauce
shiracha how do you say that sriracha
should love is that how you write it
what is sriracha sauce is that how you
say it
what what how do you write that
how do you write saturn songs is that
how you say it
say
how do you write saturn songs
set what is that statues
what is that that's a lot of sauces we
need more
we need more sauces
oh no don't tell her
what is sauce why are you asking for
lamb sauce what is lamb
sauce
sauce i love tonkatsu so much
psycho indeed good
a good choice my friend a good choice
carrot sauce of course
i shall add it mushroom sauce
we have all the sauces you can dream of
yes
[Music]
pineapples don't think you guys are
giving me good ideas anymore i think we
ran out of good ideas
buffalo stuff that sounds that sounds um
decent
lemon
you're running out of good ideas
barbecue sauce is already on there yeah
yeah
hot sauce oh yeah okay i guess we don't
have that one yet
i've seen the word sauce so many times
now that i don't even know
like when i look at it it doesn't look
like a word anymore to me
okay okay okay do we need anything
else oh by the way i'm not i can stream
longer
than one hour today it's not like i i
had to
uh stream one hour in the previous times
i just kind of felt like
only streaming for an hour but i was i
was free
to stream longer than that of course
so today if you would like me to stay
longer
i can stay longer oh we can do drinks
yeah
do you want me to stay longer go on
really okay
if you want me to stay then i'll stay
we have so many things to plan
pizza okay of course i want
all those things in my restaurant but we
have to
we have to you know wait a little bit
until we have enough investors money
so let's go for them drinks uh
can i can i write i probably can't write
the
the double c word i don't know maybe i
can i'll just write
oh hello i can't stop anymore
i've lost the ability to type for some
reason
oh dr pepper drink up the intellectuals
very cheery lady i have a like a monthly
pack of dr pepper always in my apartment
iced tea oops
iced tea dr oopsie what is dr oopsie
what is that why are so many people
writing about dr upsin i've never heard
of that
ina loves dr oopsie
eno's favorite beverage well let me let
me look that up
doctor oopsie does that really exist
eh if i google dr oopsie ina comes up
did you troll me guys did you troll me
ina comes up
ah you're right it does say that on that
little uh
can that she had on her desk
true i didn't i didn't i forgot that it
said that
your trolls i did see it before and i
was like oh that looks like dr pepper
must be a reference
but i forgot about it oh my god i
thought you because all of you are
writing and i thought it was like an
actual drink no no i did see it on her
desk i did i did i was in the stream
before i commented
okay but now for some real drinks
mountain dew
i've never uh drank mountain dew before
but okay but we have to make that longer
[Music]
sweetie yeah that's what i mean with
iced tea
can i say those can i write that just in
case i'll write
but i guess i already wrote dr pepper so
what the hell sprite
what was the other
maybe i'm a red bull
ice coffee iced
coffee milkshakes oh
milkshakes yes yes yes
hot chocolate you want hot chocolate
i love hot chocolate but not in a fast
food chain
orange juice yeah i love orange juice
let's do it apple juice
um what what else what other juices
there
california you want me to sell alcohol
we have to get some more investors to
get alcohol
bubble tea okay if you really if you
really want bubble tea
i guess so pineapple juice
indeed necessary for our success
lemonade isn't sprite lemonade
do you mean something else lemonade
water
water what is water emilia's favorite
drink right
which is a lie by the way it was only
her favorite drink in that collab
because of the other choices
but in reality her favorite drink is
sweetened iced tea
or mango juice what is diet water
idle bath water uh
no guanana
yes i have tasted this in the country of
another country and i was thinking wow
that is amazing
okay okay it cannot be water it must be
say so water say so omizu
nice phoenix tears
okay somebody also wrote yago's tears
but jacko ain't crying anymore because
we are here to save him
but i sometimes cry so let's add the
phoenix tears
milk
milk root beer okay i guess that's not
real beer so we can add it
cantaloupe oh yeah for cali her favorite
fruit cantaloupe
juice are you happy cali
for you i've got some cantaloupe juice
oh green tea
how do you write udonja in english is it
this
or is this how you write it
bacon soda zero i'll add monster
that's how you write it okay good good
good good good
okay this shall be the last for now okay
that's so many drinks and so many sauces
but this is the thing you know
especially sauces they're really
important to me because like when i go
to certain places and they don't have
the sauce that i want
it makes me so sad made me so
sad so we really i think that this was
necessary yes yes yes
yeah small menu
yeah there's really not so much food
here huh uh
maybe let's let's add maybe hot dogs
otherwise there's not so much choice
is there anything else that i
desperately need that i was forgetting
about
onion rings we can add that to the
potato fries
onion rings
pizza okay
okay we shall add pizza
okay maybe
no there's no more space i wanted to
make a fox burger but yeah
yeah this looks difficult we have too
much on the menu now
chicken ice cream oh we need desserts
we need desserts what do i do
should we resize it and make some
desserts too
how do i resize it
ah no no no i deleted some of
it no
thank god i wish i could um use this
sometime eh
it's not working wait
what oh no
oh thank god i wish there was an undo
button in like
my life
don't you wish there was an undo button
in real life
panic calm
okay but still how do i make this
smaller wait
if only there was a undo button man if
only okay this looks
weird now but deal with it
i hope so one of my employees will write
this on a proper
nice looking menu got it
got it kfp employees
make it prettier thank you for the super
chats
thank you
last one is a dessert well you got a lot
of stuff to write on those menus good
luck with that
oh banana split hell yeah that's the
good stuff
a salmon burger in the future i think we
can
manage to do that
carrot cake
carrot cake ice cream
everything you can imagine
pineapple sundae oh
ooh
[Laughter]
yes yes yes yes
why is it suddenly german
cheesecake orange muffin
chocolate muffin
oh honey toast
[Music]
phoenix flurry
thank you for the super chat good idea
brownies oh my god yes
more
chocolate chip cookies chocolate chip
cookies
cc cookies raw pasta
you have a very interesting taste my
friend
yeah gorge sorry i i
i lost the line we have to make another
one
yogurt yeah
frozen yeah
frozen yogurt oh my god yes
yes yes yes yes
you all have to invest in frozen yogurt
donuts
indeed indeed yogurt
anything else oh chicken and waffles
that is uh
interesting i tried that before it was
really um
interesting i would i would prefer to
eat those things separately so
waffles no not there don't do it there i
messed up i messed up when we have to
[Music]
um
to waffle to toe up
what was i just gonna write i forgot
uh waffle okay tall apple
what are you i trying to say torah plus
waffle
waffle okay we have a little bit more
space
pancakes pancakes
pancakes matcha pudding
that sounds delicious
but now let's make pudding and then you
can have it in every
every taste okay do what
juice pancakes what churros
oh no it does the thing again
okay takoyaki
that's not a dessert my friends that's
not a dessert
is not a dessert i know i know i know we
all want takoyaki but that's not a
dessert
red red velvet cake
chocolate cake all the cakes
carrot cake is already on the list it's
the second one
do i not have cupcakes okay well i think
okay mochi there you go there we go
we have made it successfully
yay okay employees are you ready to
to this is this is what i give you and
you must create a nice venue
oh that actually looks nice because i
can't give this to the customers
this is a bakery no no the main thing is
fried chicken the main thing is fast
food
but i just love desserts and sauces
oh craps oh no i want crabs let's add
let's add it
okay gel banana
oh i don't have space
[Music]
how about i make it smaller
okay okay okay bye
now this is the final thank you thank
you everyone i shall save this
i almost
[Music]
okay thank you everyone for
participating
in the first step of creating
the kiara frye phoenix empire 100
penny customer last video
thank you thank you thank you for now
and we will be adding
many more things to the menu and we are
taking
applications as of now send your
applications to yahoo if you need a job
go for it if you already have a job
credit
and work for kfb kfb
kfb kfb kfc
[Music]
you can work for me colonel sanders quit
your jobs
we have a quite a nice working
environment i would say indeed
why would you not like to work for
hololive english
members we are obviously um
we are always obviously very good
employers i would say
how much do you pay i think you
misunderstood something
foreign
oh how to turn tables oh how to turn to
people
but i mean you can also just be a
customer and just
uh wait that that way you also
don't earn any money huh
well you win some things and you lose
some things
[Music]
you know that's just how the world is
that that's just that's just how yeah
amelia coupons do work yes yes you can
use a million
coupons
we should put smiles on the menu
one smile is free see this is the only
thing that is free
it is my smile
my name
i will is you my smile
will you accept my happiness
and my smile and spend
all of your future together with me
[Music]
is it a yes
yay
oh i i i i wasn't
i wasn't proposing or anything
you're you're misunderstanding smiles
are free
you'll get a smile and you'll get a
smile
too late oh no i have been married
oh no
thank you everyone thank you for the
super chat some today's stream is uh
coming to an end um
thank you all today um
i was i was happy to see a little
rainbow
um oh yeah what else i wanted to say um
uh
there will be i have one announcement
i have an announcement
a thing that you have been waiting for
oh thank you for the super chat
thank you
one announcement
3d is a bit too early i would say um
this sunday on kiara
channel will be the second
whole life english full member
collaboration yay
[Music]
on my channel
consciousness
[Music]
everyone will come over to my place and
we'll party
[Music]
with you on sunday sunday sunday
so put it in your calendars
on sunday we will all be together here
and do some things um
by the way if there's anything you would
maybe want us to do you can
send in some suggestions as well
there might be a possibility that we'll
pick something up
the time uh will be uh
i'll let you know about the time uh soon
but i think it should be at the same
time as the previous collaboration
okay
so most likely most likely will be the
same time
also uh
as i mentioned before i will be reading
the super chats in my next
stream tomorrow tomorrow i'll be
streaming i think two times
it should be one super chat reading and
then later on maybe around the same time
as today i'll be also streaming again
and playing some games
and wait i'll tell if you want to
put a new calendar so you can hear your
name
and their reading stream is a
friday japanese time friday
uh it starts from 12 o'clock
okay so i will be reading
the super chats and the messages um i'll
have to see how many there are
if uh if i can manage to if it's not
two to two to too many because i really
don't i can't imagine how much it is
right now but if it's not too many then
i'll try to read
as many messages as possible but if it's
too much i might
only be able to read uh the messages of
the rad super chats we'll have to see
how it goes but i'll try my best to read
as many as possible
so that will be a long stream where i'll
just be saying thank you to everyone
again and again and again and again and
again
i hope you still come so it won't be too
lonely i hope
i hope you will come yeah 12 12 o'clock
uh japanese
standard time all right
um and one more thing after me
you might already know but cali will be
streaming
on her channel i think in 30 minutes her
stream
should be starting so she also
uh is now able to receive super chats
yay so maybe you can
come over and see her stream i'll be
watching it too so
let's enjoy cali stream
and support her okay
ah but no no no weird rating please okay
okay
just just you know i just want to make
sure
okay now don't don't spam or anything
okay
be good be good
i'll be doing my best from now on as
well and uh i'll see you tomorrow
in my stream i'll be i'll go and eat
some fried chicken now
one second
i do want to play minecraft soon maybe
this week even
i have never played minecraft before so
we'll do a first time minecraft stream
this
week for sure but i think tomorrow i'll
be playing uh
uh fall guys again because i gotta get
that chicken costume and i only played
it for like 30 minutes previously
so i hope it's okay if i play fall guys
and then i
might play minecraft on the next stream
after that would you like to see
minecraft
maybe tomorrow i'll get some nice
and helpful stream snipers again as i
got last time or from now on since i got
the controls you never helped me again
thank you for the super chats we're
coming to an end so
yeah you want to see it nice
okay and greeting do you remember the
end greeting
this is german it's auf wiedersehen
some people already write it wrote it in
the chat so
arigato
[Music]
thank
i'll you nice and see you tomorrow
super chat reading at 12 o'clock
japanese standard time and then in the
evening i'll stream again
yeah i want to build my restaurant in
minecraft
[Music]
thank you
so
[Music]
do
thanks to everyone who's still here
i love you
thank you so much
i love you guys
[Music]
foreign