​
​​​ ​Today's the day, huh...​ ​​
​​​ ​The Kiryu Group has grown so much.​ ​​
​​ ​It's become such a powerful organization.​ ​​
​​​ ​It'll be hard leaving you all,​ ​​
​​​ ​but know that each one of you​ ​​
​​​ ​will live on in my heart, my brothers and sisters.​ ​​
​​​ ​This happens to be...​ ​​
​​​ ​my graduation stream.​ ​​
​​​ ​And for this event, I've called over​ ​​
​​ ​all my friends in hololive​ ​​
​​​ ​to this HQ for a bit of fun!​ ​​
​​​ ​Saying goodbye to them is painful,​ ​​
​​​ ​but I want to use this last chance​ ​​
​​​ ​to have a cheerful talk with everyone​ ​​
​​​ ​before I leave.​ ​​
​​​ ​With that, please listen to​ ​​
​​​ ​what all of them have to say.​ ​​
​​​ ​Generation 0​ ​​
​​​ ​1st Generation​ ​​
​​​ ​2nd Generation​ ​​
​​​ ​Gamers​ ​​
​​​ ​3rd Generation​ ​​
​​​ ​5th Generation​ ​​
​​​ ​(Due to scheduling conflicts, Gawr Gura will be appearing separately.)​ ​​
​​​ ​4th Generation​ ​​
​​​ ​All right...​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's get this graduation concert started!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's gooooo!​ ​​
​​​ ​We took our hands towards the brightest screens​ ​​
​​ ​onaji mirai o miteitai​ ​​
​​​ ​All we wish are shinin' dreams​ ​​
​​ ​ano yume te ni shitai​ ​​
​​​ ​We make our choice​ ​​
​​ ​sorezore​ ​​
​​​ ​with different voice​ ​​
​​ ​chigatta​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh yes we know​ ​​
​​ ​kokoro de​ ​​
​​​ ​Get set and GO!​ ​​
​​ ​hashire GO​ ​​
​​​ ​English lyrics: Kiryu Coco​ ​​
​​​ ​You were the one who set this light of smile​ ​​
​​ ​doko o mite mo makkurana​ ​​
​​​ ​it was a dark and hopeless place​ ​​
​​ ​basho ni mebaeteta​ ​​
​​​ ​It was your shiny eyes that caught me​ ​​
​​ ​honno chiisana kibou ni​ ​​
​​​ ​Filled with hope, THIS STORY STARTS NOW​ ​​
​​ ​kono hitomi ubawareta​ ​​
​​​ ​Notice the fear inside me bouncing up?​ ​​
​​ ​fuan de yureru kokoro o​ ​​
​​​ ​That's when I tune my heart beat down​ ​​
​​ ​umaku chuuningu shite​ ​​
​​​ ​I will shine, I will smile, my wish will come true​ ​​
​​ ​honno chiisana yuuki o​ ​​
​​​ ​the first page of my history​ ​​
​​ ​furishibotteita yo​ ​​
​​​ ​Voice telling me to "Give it up"​ ​​
​​ ​akirame no moji​ ​​
​​​ ​Delete that word my heads are up​ ​​
​​ ​deriito shite susumu​ ​​
​​​ ​I will never be alone, no, not anymore​ ​​
​​ ​kurushii toki mo mou watashi wa​ ​​
​​​ ​We are the shiny, smiley star!​ ​​
​​ ​hitori janai kara​ ​​
​​​ ​We took our hands towards our brightest dreams​ ​​
​​ ​dakara motto yume oikaketai​ ​​
​​​ ​Giving all we are now a team!​ ​​
​​ ​wakuwaku tomaranai​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll blow your mind! Now take my hand!​ ​​
​​ ​souzou koeteku​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's show this world our dreamland!​ ​​
​​ ​sekai misete ageru​ ​​
​​​ ​Access through my heart, you will see​ ​​
​​ ​akusesu shite mitai​ ​​
​​​ ​No regrets with hottest degree​ ​​
​​ ​koukai nante sou sasenai​ ​​
​​​ ​We make our choice​ ​​
​​ ​sorezore​ ​​
​​​ ​with different voice​ ​​
​​ ​chigatta​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh yes we know​ ​​
​​ ​kokoro de​ ​​
​​​ ​Get set and GO!​ ​​
​​ ​hashire GO​ ​​
​​​ ​Glow to the top of my sky above​ ​​
​​ ​kasou no sora ni kagayaku​ ​​
​​​ ​My pecious shiny, smiley days​ ​​
​​ ​mabushii omoi wa​ ​​
​​​ ​It's a light you have never seen before​ ​​
​​ ​mita koto no nai hikari o​ ​​
​​​ ​Sending for you, C'mon and get it!​ ​​
​​ ​riaru ni todokeru yo​ ​​
​​​ ​Do you remember all the love that you gave?​ ​​
​​ ​itsumo kikoeru eeru wa​ ​​
​​​ ​It's all here with me, I saved​ ​​
​​ ​koko ni kyapuchaa shite​ ​​
​​​ ​Every voice, every word I get from you...​ ​​
​​ ​mata atarashii hikari o​ ​​
​​​ ​But not enough, I want it more​ ​​
​​ ​sagashitaku naru yo​ ​​
​​​ ​Your precious smile is like a spell​ ​​
​​ ​kimi no egao wa​ ​​
​​​ ​A magic dust that makes me smile​ ​​
​​ ​hozon shite susumu​ ​​
​​​ ​You'll never see my tears​ ​​
​​ ​kanashii toki ni​ ​​
​​​ ​We defeat despairs​ ​​
​​ ​mikaesu yo​ ​​
​​​ ​'cause it's my shiny, smiley life​ ​​
​​ ​chikara ga waku kara​ ​​
​​​ ​We took our hands towards our brightest dreams.​ ​​
​​ ​mune o hatte yume oikaketai​ ​​
​​​ ​wonder story, ready to scream?​ ​​
​​ ​kiseki no sutoorii​ ​​
​​​ ​Together we​ ​​
​​ ​issho ni​ ​​
​​​ ​Can make it free​ ​​
​​ ​tsukurou​ ​​
​​​ ​A never ending story​ ​​
​​ ​owaranai yume o​ ​​
​​​ ​Everyone's a star in this tale​ ​​
​​ ​dare hitori kakasenai​ ​​
​​​ ​Filled with love and shine and a smile​ ​​
​​ ​ai ga matta kono sekai​ ​​
​​​ ​We made our choice​ ​​
​​ ​sorezore​ ​​
​​​ ​with different voice​ ​​
​​ ​chigatta​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh yes, we know​ ​​
​​ ​kokoro de​ ​​
​​​ ​Get set and burst!​ ​​
​​ ​irodore​ ​​
​​​ ​When I'm sad, you'll be here​ ​​
​​ ​kanashii toki mo​ ​​
​​​ ​When you're torn, I'll be there​ ​​
​​ ​sabishii toki mo​ ​​
​​​ ​Touch my screen and you will feel my heart here​ ​​
​​ ​shinji aeru mono ga aru​ ​​
​​​ ​Whenever you're near​ ​​
​​ ​wasurezu ni​ ​​
​​​ ​There would be no fear​ ​​
​​ ​kono kodou​ ​​
​​​ ​This beat will dry out every tears​ ​​
​​ ​narashi tsuzuketai​ ​​
​​​ ​Look at my future, shine and glow​ ​​
​​ ​owaranai sekai ni​ ​​
​​​ ​make every world to know​ ​​
​​ ​afuredasu yo​ ​​
​​​ ​My shiny smile!​ ​​
​​ ​egaotachi​ ​​
​​​ ​We took our hands towards our brightest stage​ ​​
​​ ​akogare no butai tachitai​ ​​
​​​ ​This is me, in my shiny page​ ​​
​​ ​rashiku kagayakitai​ ​​
​​​ ​Tear of joy and gold happy days​ ​​
​​ ​toki ni namidashite​ ​​
​​​ ​Just a start that we had just made​ ​​
​​ ​mata warai aitai​ ​​
​​​ ​Hold my hands to see our "MIRAI"​ ​​
​​ ​onaji mirai o mitai​ ​​
​​​ ​Please my dreams come true for my life​ ​​
​​ ​ano yume te ni shitai​ ​​
​​​ ​Let the legend start​ ​​
​​ ​fumidasou​ ​​
​​​ ​step by step a miracle​ ​​
​​ ​kiseki no ippo o​ ​​
​​​ ​We took our hands towards our brightest dreams​ ​​
​​ ​iki kirashite yume oikaketai​ ​​
​​​ ​Giving all we are now a team!​ ​​
​​ ​wakuwaku tomaranai​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll blow your mind! Now take my hand!​ ​​
​​ ​souzou koeteku​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's show this world our dreamland!​ ​​
​​ ​sekai miseteageru​ ​​
​​​ ​Access through my heart, you will see​ ​​
​​ ​akusesu shite minai?​ ​​
​​​ ​No regrets my heart is now free​ ​​
​​ ​koukai nante koko ni nai​ ​​
​​​ ​We made our choice with different voice​ ​​
​​ ​sorezore chigatta​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh yes, we will create our WORLD​ ​​
​​ ​kokoro de tsukuru WORLD​ ​​
​​​ ​Guys...​ ​​
​​​ ​This is the first time​ ​​
​​​ ​all of us together​ ​​
​​​ ​stand on stage in our idol outfits!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yaaaaay!​ ​​
​​ ​stand on stage in our idol outfits!​ ​​
​​​ ​This is the first!​ ​​
​​​ ​We did it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Lemme see them!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hehehe!​ ​​
​​​ ​I wanna have a look!​ ​​
​​ ​Hehehe!​ ​​
​​​ ​Lemme peek!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ooh, I see, I see!​ ​​
​​ ​Lemme peek!​ ​​
​​​ ​Is it cute?​ ​​
​​​ ​It's adowable!​ ​​
​​​ ​Adowable!​ ​​
​​ ​It's adowable!​ ​​
​​​ ​Damn, you flat.​ ​​
​​​ ​What was that?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Who's flat?!​ ​​
​​​ ​My eyes keep getting drawn to the artwork at the back.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hold on!​ ​​
​​​ ​Who... is this?​ ​​
​​​ ​Ah! This was drawn by yaman-maman/papan as a―​ ​​
​​​ ​What? A graduation present for me?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Whooooa! It's amazing!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's so cute!​ ​​
​​​ ​It doesn't look like you!​ ​​
​​ ​It's so cute!​ ​​
​​​ ​What do you ​mean it's shooped, huh?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Your profile picture looks different!​ ​​
​​ ​What do you ​mean it's shooped, huh?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, okay.​ ​​
​​​ ​This doesn't look like you.​ ​​
​​​ ​Diffewent person?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yep, totally different.​ ​​
​​​ ​Who u?​ ​​
​​ ​Yep, totally different.​ ​​
​​ ​You're looking at her!​ ​​
​​​ ​You're looking at her!​ ​​
​​​ ​For real, though, it does look like you're going​ ​​
​​​ ​on a journey, with such strong resolve.​ ​​
​​​ ​Mama, Papa, thank you!​ ​​
​​ ​on a journey, with such strong resolve.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's so beautiful!​ ​​
​​ ​Mama, Papa, thank you!​ ​​
​​​ ​Luna's there! Everyone too!​ ​​
​​​ ​We're all here!​ ​​
​​ ​Luna's there! Everyone too!​ ​​
​​​ ​All of 4th Gen is here!​ ​​
​​ ​We're all here!​ ​​
​​​ ​All of 4th Gen―Hold on.​ ​​
​​​ ​There's something there!​ ​​
​​​ ​Something at the back?​ ​​
​​​ ​Looks like some beast.​ ​​
​​ ​Something at the back?​ ​​
​​​ ​There's a monster in there!​ ​​
​​​ ​There is!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ain't that a Tatsunoko? Are you guys coming along?​ ​​
​​​ ​That's a Tatsunoko?​ ​​
​​​ ​They're coming with you?​ ​​
​​​ ​Haha! Why the heck not, then?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm going on a new journey, guys.​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't wike it! Don't go!​ ​​
​​​ ​So sad! We'll be so sad!​ ​​
​​​ ​The heck are y'all crying for?!​ ​​
​​ ​So sad! We'll be so sad!​ ​​
​​​ ​We still have​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​one more song to sing together, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​Right?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah...​ ​​
​​​ ​We do.​ ​​
​​​ ​We do, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​We've gathered today in​ ​​
​​​ ​our idol outfits, after all!​ ​​
​​ ​Watame, let's pose.​ ​​
​​​ ​We match!​ ​​
​​​ ​Our outfits match!​ ​​
​​ ​We match!​ ​​
​​​ ​Especially at the part around our collar ties.​ ​​
​​​ ​Your collar ties?​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh no, it's Ms. Plains!​ ​​
​​​ ​(Battle of the Valleys and Mountains)​ ​​
​​​ ​Begone, poor woman!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's check Luna's outfit.​ ​​
​​​ ​What do you think?​ ​​
​​​ ​Her outfit also has it.​ ​​
​​​ ​Luna has the stuff.​ ​​
​​​ ​Luna has the boo―She has the curves.​ ​​
​​​ ​Seems like we have an odd one out.​ ​​
​​​ ​Shoo, shoo!​ ​​
​​​ ​You're in the way of the camera!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh hush, you're no fun!​ ​​
​​​ ​Good stuff!​ ​​
​​​ ​Watame, let's do ​that.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh?​ ​​
​​​ ​This is our time to show it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Can I?!​ ​​
​​ ​This is our time to show it!​ ​​
​​​ ​This is our time to show it!​ ​​
​​​ ​This is what you call a graduate sideboob!​ ​​
​​​ ​Smell it! Smell the pit!​ ​​
​​​ ​How's it smell?​ ​​
​​​ ​Sour♥​ ​​
​​​ ​Sour?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Was it sour?​ ​​
​​​ ​Kanata said it! Kanata said it was sour!​ ​​
​​​ ​But yeah, I'm gwaduating, Luna.​ ​​
​​​ ​No! Stay here fowever!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll be the only one graduating, though...​ ​​
​​​ ​She's still in denial, it seems.​ ​​
​​ ​I'll be the only one graduating, though...​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, that.​ ​​
​​ ​She's still in denial, it seems.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll be staying, then!​ ​​
​​ ​Yeah, that.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ah―Ah―Ah―?​ ​​
​​​ ​Me too.​ ​​
​​​ ​Same here.​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh―What―?​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's all stay together.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll be here forever!​ ​​
​​​ ​I-I guess I'l stay―​ ​​
​​​ ​You know, I wanna stay around​ ​​
​​​ ​and perform more with you guys,​ ​​
​​​ ​but we have no time.​ ​​
​​​ ​Kanatan...​ ​​
​​​ ​This will be the very last time​ ​​
​​​ ​all five of us will get to sing together.​ ​​
​​​ ​I wrote the next song​ ​​
​​​ ​wanting all five of us to sing it together.​ ​​
​​​ ​That song is "Kiseki Knot."​ ​​
​​​ ​Thank you, Kanata.​ ​​
​​ ​That song is "Kiseki Knot."​ ​​
​​​ ​I was already crying a while ago,​ ​​
​​​ ​Towa! No crying!​ ​​
​​ ​I was already crying a while ago,​ ​​
​​​ ​and now I feel like crying again,​ ​​
​​​ ​but I'll hold back for now!​ ​​
​​​ ​We gotta keep smiling in this concert!​ ​​
​​​ ​We're still smiling, yeah!​ ​​
​​​ ​No crying on me!​ ​​
​​​ ​Everyone, please sing it with us,​ ​​
​​ ​No crying on me!​ ​​
​​​ ​"Kiseki Knot."​ ​​
​​​ ​L​e​t​'​s ​m​a​k​e ​a ​p​r​o​m​i​s​e​, ​h​e​r​e ​a​n​d ​n​ow​ ​​
​​​ ​y​akusoku shiyou yo​ ​​
​​​ ​y​a​k​usoku shiyou yo​ ​​
​​​ ​y​a​k​u​s​oku shiyou yo​ ​​
​​​ ​y​a​k​u​s​o​k​u shiyou yo​ ​​
​​​ ​y​a​k​u​s​o​k​u ​s​h​iyou yo​ ​​
​​​ ​y​a​k​u​s​o​k​u ​s​h​i​y​ou yo​ ​​
​​​ ​y​a​k​u​s​o​k​u ​s​h​i​y​o​u yo​ ​​
​​​ ​y​a​k​u​s​o​k​u ​s​h​i​y​o​u ​yo​ ​​
​​​ ​T​o ​n​e​v​e​r ​f​o​r​g​e​t ​t​h​e ​m​i​r​a​c​le​ ​​
​​​ ​b​okura deaeta kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​ura deaeta kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u​r​a deaeta kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u​r​a ​d​eaeta kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u​r​a ​d​e​aeta kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u​r​a ​d​e​a​eta kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u​r​a ​d​e​a​e​t​a kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u​r​a ​d​e​a​e​t​a ​k​iseki​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u​r​a ​d​e​a​e​t​a ​k​i​s​eki​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u​r​a ​d​e​a​e​t​a ​k​i​s​e​ki​ ​​
​​​ ​T​h​a​t ​b​r​o​u​g​h​t ​u​s ​t​o​g​e​t​h​er​ ​​
​​​ ​w​asurenai you ni​ ​​
​​​ ​w​a​s​urenai you ni​ ​​
​​​ ​w​a​s​u​r​enai you ni​ ​​
​​​ ​w​a​s​u​r​e​n​ai you ni​ ​​
​​​ ​w​a​s​u​r​e​n​a​i you ni​ ​​
​​​ ​w​a​s​u​r​e​n​a​i ​y​o​u ni​ ​​
​​​ ​w​a​s​u​r​e​n​a​i ​y​o​u ​ni​ ​​
​​​ ​Gathered in pursuit of a dream​ ​​
​​​ ​yume idaite tsudou​ ​​
​​​ ​Like in a coming-of-age anime​ ​​
​​​ ​seishun anime mitai na​ ​​
​​​ ​We jump as high as we ​can at a happy end on the horizon​ ​​
​​​ ​happiina endo ni naru kanata e tobu yo​ ​​
​​​ ​happiina endo ni naru ​kanata e tobu yo​ ​​
​​​ ​happiina endo ni naru ​kanata ​e tobu yo​ ​​
​​​ ​Still not awake, yawning away​ ​​
​​​ ​nebokeme akubishite​ ​​
​​​ ​Wondering what to do today​ ​​
​​​ ​kyou wa nani o shiyou ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​Maybe run across the seas ​toward all eternity​ ​​
​​​ ​towa ni tsuzuku umi o kakenukeru​ ​​
​​​ ​towa ​ni tsuzuku umi o kakenukeru​ ​​
​​​ ​Be brave and don't sigh no​w at a mental block​ ​​
​​​ ​ima wa tameiki yori mo yuuki o​ ​​
​​​ ​ima ​wa tameiki yori mo yuuki o​ ​​
​​​ ​ima ​wa tame​iki yori mo yuuki o​ ​​
​​​ ​Giving up would be ​lunacy, let's sing now​ ​​
​​​ ​akirameru nante nai no​ ​​
​​​ ​akirame​ru nante nai no​ ​​
​​​ ​akirame​ru na​nte nai no​ ​​
​​​ ​As ​coconspirators​ ​​
​​​ ​koko de utau​ ​​
​​​ ​koko ​de utau​ ​​
​​​ ​C​a​n ​y​o​u ​h​e​a​r ​m​y ​v​o​i​c​e?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​oku no koe wa kikoetemasu ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u no koe wa kikoetemasu ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u ​n​o koe wa kikoetemasu ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u ​n​o ​k​oe wa kikoetemasu ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u ​n​o ​k​o​e wa kikoetemasu ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u ​n​o ​k​o​e ​w​a kikoetemasu ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u ​n​o ​k​o​e ​w​a ​k​ikoetemasu ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u ​n​o ​k​o​e ​w​a ​k​i​k​oetemasu ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u ​n​o ​k​o​e ​w​a ​k​i​k​o​etemasu ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u ​n​o ​k​o​e ​w​a ​k​i​k​o​e​t​emasu ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u ​n​o ​k​o​e ​w​a ​k​i​k​o​e​t​e​m​asu ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u ​n​o ​k​o​e ​w​a ​k​i​k​o​e​t​e​m​a​s​u ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u ​n​o ​k​o​e ​w​a ​k​i​k​o​e​t​e​m​a​s​u ​k​a?​ ​​
​​​ ​I​t​'​s ​f​r​o​m ​m​e ​t​o ​y​ou​ ​​
​​​ ​k​imi ni todoke!​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​m​i ni todoke!​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​m​i ​n​i todoke!​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​m​i ​n​i ​t​odoke!​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​m​i ​n​i ​t​o​d​oke!​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​m​i ​n​i ​t​o​d​o​k​e!​ ​​
​​​ ​We wouldn't have forged these bonds as school friends​ ​​
​​​ ​gakkou no tomodachi ja kitto nai deai datta​ ​​
​​​ ​F​a​r​a​w​a​y ​o​n ​t​h​e ​o​t​h​e​r ​s​i​d​e ​b​e​y​o​n​d ​t​h​i​s ​s​c​r​e​en​ ​​
​​​ ​g​amen no saki no haruka tooku made​ ​​
​​​ ​g​a​m​en no saki no haruka tooku made​ ​​
​​​ ​g​a​m​e​n no saki no haruka tooku made​ ​​
​​​ ​g​a​m​e​n ​n​o saki no haruka tooku made​ ​​
​​​ ​g​a​m​e​n ​n​o ​s​aki no haruka tooku made​ ​​
​​​ ​g​a​m​e​n ​n​o ​s​a​k​i no haruka tooku made​ ​​
​​​ ​g​a​m​e​n ​n​o ​s​a​k​i ​n​o haruka tooku made​ ​​
​​​ ​g​a​m​e​n ​n​o ​s​a​k​i ​n​o ​h​aruka tooku made​ ​​
​​​ ​g​a​m​e​n ​n​o ​s​a​k​i ​n​o ​h​a​r​uka tooku made​ ​​
​​​ ​g​a​m​e​n ​n​o ​s​a​k​i ​n​o ​h​a​r​u​k​a tooku made​ ​​
​​​ ​g​a​m​e​n ​n​o ​s​a​k​i ​n​o ​h​a​r​u​k​a ​t​ooku made​ ​​
​​​ ​g​a​m​e​n ​n​o ​s​a​k​i ​n​o ​h​a​r​u​k​a ​t​o​oku made​ ​​
​​​ ​g​a​m​e​n ​n​o ​s​a​k​i ​n​o ​h​a​r​u​k​a ​t​o​o​k​u made​ ​​
​​​ ​g​a​m​e​n ​n​o ​s​a​k​i ​n​o ​h​a​r​u​k​a ​t​o​o​k​u ​m​ade​ ​​
​​​ ​g​a​m​e​n ​n​o ​s​a​k​i ​n​o ​h​a​r​u​k​a ​t​o​o​k​u ​m​a​de​ ​​
​​​ ​Even the most pointed of words​ ​​
​​​ ​sasakureta kotoba mo​ ​​
​​​ ​Can put smiles on faces​ ​​
​​​ ​dareka no egao ni naru​ ​​
​​​ ​O​u​r ​f​i​v​e ​c​o​l​o​r​s ​c​o​m​e ​t​o​g​e​t​h​e​r ​t​o ​d​r​a​w ​a ​m​i​r​a​c​l​e ​s​t​ar​ ​​
​​​ ​s​orezore no iro de hoshi musubu kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​r​ezore no iro de hoshi musubu kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​r​e​z​ore no iro de hoshi musubu kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​r​e​z​o​r​e no iro de hoshi musubu kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​r​e​z​o​r​e ​n​o iro de hoshi musubu kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​r​e​z​o​r​e ​n​o ​iro de hoshi musubu kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​r​e​z​o​r​e ​n​o ​i​r​o de hoshi musubu kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​r​e​z​o​r​e ​n​o ​i​r​o ​d​e hoshi musubu kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​r​e​z​o​r​e ​n​o ​i​r​o ​d​e ​h​oshi musubu kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​r​e​z​o​r​e ​n​o ​i​r​o ​d​e ​h​o​s​h​i musubu kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​r​e​z​o​r​e ​n​o ​i​r​o ​d​e ​h​o​s​h​i ​m​usubu kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​r​e​z​o​r​e ​n​o ​i​r​o ​d​e ​h​o​s​h​i ​m​u​s​ubu kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​r​e​z​o​r​e ​n​o ​i​r​o ​d​e ​h​o​s​h​i ​m​u​s​u​b​u kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​r​e​z​o​r​e ​n​o ​i​r​o ​d​e ​h​o​s​h​i ​m​u​s​u​b​u ​k​iseki​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​r​e​z​o​r​e ​n​o ​i​r​o ​d​e ​h​o​s​h​i ​m​u​s​u​b​u ​k​i​s​eki​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​r​e​z​o​r​e ​n​o ​i​r​o ​d​e ​h​o​s​h​i ​m​u​s​u​b​u ​k​i​s​e​ki​ ​​
​​​ ​A​n​d ​t​a​k​e ​y​o​u ​t​o ​a ​s​p​a​r​k​l​i​n​g ​s​t​a​ge​ ​​
​​​ ​k​irakira kagayaku suteeji ni​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​r​akira kagayaku suteeji ni​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​r​a​k​ira kagayaku suteeji ni​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​r​a​k​i​r​a kagayaku suteeji ni​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​r​a​k​i​r​a ​k​agayaku suteeji ni​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​r​a​k​i​r​a ​k​a​g​ayaku suteeji ni​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​r​a​k​i​r​a ​k​a​g​a​y​aku suteeji ni​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​r​a​k​i​r​a ​k​a​g​a​y​a​k​u suteeji ni​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​r​a​k​i​r​a ​k​a​g​a​y​a​k​u ​s​uteeji ni​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​r​a​k​i​r​a ​k​a​g​a​y​a​k​u ​s​u​t​eeji ni​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​r​a​k​i​r​a ​k​a​g​a​y​a​k​u ​s​u​t​e​eji ni​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​r​a​k​i​r​a ​k​a​g​a​y​a​k​u ​s​u​t​e​e​j​i ni​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​r​a​k​i​r​a ​k​a​g​a​y​a​k​u ​s​u​t​e​e​j​i ​ni​ ​​
​​​ ​On which we perform​ ​​
​​​ ​tsureteku yo​ ​​
​​​ ​Filled with laughter, tears, and joy​ ​​
​​​ ​naite waratte hashaide​ ​​
​​​ ​Every day is a roller coaster​ ​​
​​​ ​mainichi jettokoosutaa!​ ​​
​​​ ​So it's okay to stop and take a breather sometimes​ ​​
​​​ ​tamani wa nekoronde ohirune shiyou​ ​​
​​​ ​When I'm feeling down​ ​​
​​​ ​chotto jishin nai toki​ ​​
​​​ ​Singing a duet with the tweeting birds cheers me up​ ​​
​​​ ​kotori to dyuetto shite​ ​​
​​​ ​But let me cry a little, just for today​ ​​
​​​ ​kyou dake wa naichau koto yurushite ne​ ​​
​​​ ​When I open this album a long time from now​ ​​
​​​ ​mirai no boku ga arubamu hiraku​ ​​
​​​ ​The photos may be faded and scratched​ ​​
​​​ ​kizutsuita shashin datte​ ​​
​​​ ​But they'll still be priceless treasures​ ​​
​​​ ​takaramono da​ ​​
​​​ ​C​a​n ​y​o​u ​s​e​e ​m​y ​l​o​v​e?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​oku no ai ga mieteimasu ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u no ai ga mieteimasu ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u ​n​o ai ga mieteimasu ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u ​n​o ​ai ga mieteimasu ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u ​n​o ​a​i ga mieteimasu ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u ​n​o ​a​i ​g​a mieteimasu ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u ​n​o ​a​i ​g​a ​m​ieteimasu ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u ​n​o ​a​i ​g​a ​m​i​eteimasu ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u ​n​o ​a​i ​g​a ​m​i​e​t​eimasu ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u ​n​o ​a​i ​g​a ​m​i​e​t​e​imasu ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u ​n​o ​a​i ​g​a ​m​i​e​t​e​i​m​asu ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u ​n​o ​a​i ​g​a ​m​i​e​t​e​i​m​a​s​u ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u ​n​o ​a​i ​g​a ​m​i​e​t​e​i​m​a​s​u ​k​a?​ ​​
​​​ ​I​t​'​s ​f​r​o​m ​m​e ​t​o ​y​ou​ ​​
​​​ ​k​imi ni todoke!​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​m​i ni todoke!​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​m​i ​n​i todoke!​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​m​i ​n​i ​t​odoke!​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​m​i ​n​i ​t​o​d​oke!​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​m​i ​n​i ​t​o​d​o​k​e!​ ​​
​​​ ​Our backgrounds, personalities, and quirks are all different​ ​​
​​​ ​kako mo kosei mo seikaku mo chigau keredo​ ​​
​​​ ​B​u​t ​w​h​e​n ​w​e​'​r​e ​l​o​s​i​n​g ​h​o​p​e​, ​w​e ​g​r​i​t ​o​u​r ​t​e​e​th​ ​​
​​​ ​y​owakina toki wa mabuta gyutto tsumuri​ ​​
​​​ ​y​o​w​akina toki wa mabuta gyutto tsumuri​ ​​
​​​ ​y​o​w​a​k​ina toki wa mabuta gyutto tsumuri​ ​​
​​​ ​y​o​w​a​k​i​n​a toki wa mabuta gyutto tsumuri​ ​​
​​​ ​y​o​w​a​k​i​n​a ​t​oki wa mabuta gyutto tsumuri​ ​​
​​​ ​y​o​w​a​k​i​n​a ​t​o​k​i wa mabuta gyutto tsumuri​ ​​
​​​ ​y​o​w​a​k​i​n​a ​t​o​k​i ​w​a mabuta gyutto tsumuri​ ​​
​​​ ​y​o​w​a​k​i​n​a ​t​o​k​i ​w​a ​m​abuta gyutto tsumuri​ ​​
​​​ ​y​o​w​a​k​i​n​a ​t​o​k​i ​w​a ​m​a​b​uta gyutto tsumuri​ ​​
​​​ ​y​o​w​a​k​i​n​a ​t​o​k​i ​w​a ​m​a​b​u​t​a gyutto tsumuri​ ​​
​​​ ​y​o​w​a​k​i​n​a ​t​o​k​i ​w​a ​m​a​b​u​t​a ​g​y​utto tsumuri​ ​​
​​​ ​y​o​w​a​k​i​n​a ​t​o​k​i ​w​a ​m​a​b​u​t​a ​g​y​u​tto tsumuri​ ​​
​​​ ​y​o​w​a​k​i​n​a ​t​o​k​i ​w​a ​m​a​b​u​t​a ​g​y​u​t​t​o tsumuri​ ​​
​​​ ​y​o​w​a​k​i​n​a ​t​o​k​i ​w​a ​m​a​b​u​t​a ​g​y​u​t​t​o ​t​s​umuri​ ​​
​​​ ​y​o​w​a​k​i​n​a ​t​o​k​i ​w​a ​m​a​b​u​t​a ​g​y​u​t​t​o ​t​s​u​m​uri​ ​​
​​​ ​y​o​w​a​k​i​n​a ​t​o​k​i ​w​a ​m​a​b​u​t​a ​g​y​u​t​t​o ​t​s​u​m​u​ri​ ​​
​​​ ​And give it one more try, one more time​ ​​
​​​ ​mou ikkai mou ikkai​ ​​
​​​ ​We never give up​ ​​
​​​ ​zettai ni akiramenai​ ​​
​​​ ​W​e ​m​a​y ​b​e ​l​a​g​g​i​n​g ​b​e​h​i​n​d​, ​c​h​a​s​i​n​g ​a​f​t​e​r ​o​t​h​e​rs​ ​​
​​​ ​m​ae no senaka ou hetappina boku demo​ ​​
​​​ ​m​a​e no senaka ou hetappina boku demo​ ​​
​​​ ​m​a​e ​n​o senaka ou hetappina boku demo​ ​​
​​​ ​m​a​e ​n​o ​s​enaka ou hetappina boku demo​ ​​
​​​ ​m​a​e ​n​o ​s​e​n​aka ou hetappina boku demo​ ​​
​​​ ​m​a​e ​n​o ​s​e​n​a​k​a ou hetappina boku demo​ ​​
​​​ ​m​a​e ​n​o ​s​e​n​a​k​a ​ou hetappina boku demo​ ​​
​​​ ​m​a​e ​n​o ​s​e​n​a​k​a ​o​u hetappina boku demo​ ​​
​​​ ​m​a​e ​n​o ​s​e​n​a​k​a ​o​u ​h​etappina boku demo​ ​​
​​​ ​m​a​e ​n​o ​s​e​n​a​k​a ​o​u ​h​e​t​appina boku demo​ ​​
​​​ ​m​a​e ​n​o ​s​e​n​a​k​a ​o​u ​h​e​t​a​ppina boku demo​ ​​
​​​ ​m​a​e ​n​o ​s​e​n​a​k​a ​o​u ​h​e​t​a​p​p​ina boku demo​ ​​
​​​ ​m​a​e ​n​o ​s​e​n​a​k​a ​o​u ​h​e​t​a​p​p​i​n​a boku demo​ ​​
​​​ ​m​a​e ​n​o ​s​e​n​a​k​a ​o​u ​h​e​t​a​p​p​i​n​a ​b​oku demo​ ​​
​​​ ​m​a​e ​n​o ​s​e​n​a​k​a ​o​u ​h​e​t​a​p​p​i​n​a ​b​o​k​u demo​ ​​
​​​ ​m​a​e ​n​o ​s​e​n​a​k​a ​o​u ​h​e​t​a​p​p​i​n​a ​b​o​k​u ​d​emo​ ​​
​​​ ​m​a​e ​n​o ​s​e​n​a​k​a ​o​u ​h​e​t​a​p​p​i​n​a ​b​o​k​u ​d​e​mo​ ​​
​​​ ​B​u​t ​w​e ​w​a​n​t ​t​o ​s​t​a​n​d​ ​t​a​l​l ​b​y ​y​o​u​r ​s​i​de​ ​​
​​​ ​k​imi no tonari ni ikitakute​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​m​i no tonari ni ikitakute​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​m​i ​n​o tonari ni ikitakute​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​m​i ​n​o ​t​onari ni ikitakute​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​m​i ​n​o ​t​o​n​ari ni ikitakute​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​m​i ​n​o ​t​o​n​a​r​i ni ikitakute​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​m​i ​n​o ​t​o​n​a​r​i ​n​i ikitakute​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​m​i ​n​o ​t​o​n​a​r​i ​n​i ​ikitakute​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​m​i ​n​o ​t​o​n​a​r​i ​n​i ​i​k​itakute​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​m​i ​n​o ​t​o​n​a​r​i ​n​i ​i​k​i​t​akute​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​m​i ​n​o ​t​o​n​a​r​i ​n​i ​i​k​i​t​a​k​ute​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​m​i ​n​o ​t​o​n​a​r​i ​n​i ​i​k​i​t​a​k​u​te​ ​​
​​​ ​So we'll keep running​ ​​
​​​ ​hashiru no​ ​​
​The unspoken dreams
​da​​re ni mo iezu ni
​dare ​​ni mo iezu ni
​dare ni ​​mo iezu ni
​dare ni mo ​​iezu ni
​dare ni mo i​​ezu ni
​dare ni mo ie​​zu ni
​dare ni mo iezu ​​ni
​dare ni mo iezu ni
​I had all along
​e​​gaita yume ga
​ega​​ita yume ga
​egai​​ta yume ga
​egaita ​​yume ga
​egaita yu​​me ga
​egaita yume ​​ga
​egaita yume ga
​May never come true
​ta​​toe kanawanai toshite mo
​tato​​e kanawanai toshite mo
​tatoe ​​kanawanai toshite mo
​tatoe ka​​nawanai toshite mo
​tatoe kana​​wanai toshite mo
​tatoe kanawa​​nai toshite mo
​tatoe kanawana​​i toshite mo
​tatoe kanawanai ​​toshite mo
​tatoe kanawanai to​​shite mo
​tatoe kanawanai toshi​​te mo
​tatoe kanawanai toshite ​​mo
​tatoe kanawanai toshite mo
​My shoes may be dirty and falling apart
​bo​​roboro no kutsu demo
​boro​​boro no kutsu demo
​borobo​​ro no kutsu demo
​boroboro ​​no kutsu demo
​boroboro no ​​kutsu demo
​boroboro no ku​​tsu demo
​boroboro no kutsu ​​demo
​boroboro no kutsu de​​mo
​boroboro no kutsu demo
​And I may not look the least bit cool
​kak​​koyokunakute mo ah
​kakko​​yokunakute mo ah
​kakkoyo​​kunakute mo ah
​kakkoyoku​​nakute mo ah
​kakkoyokuna​​kute mo ah
​kakkoyokunaku​​te mo ah
​kakkoyokunakute ​​mo ah
​kakkoyokunakute mo ​​ah
​kakkoyokunakute mo ah
​What would my younger self say to me?
​o​​sanai ano hi no boku nara nante iu?
​osa​​nai ano hi no boku nara nante iu?
​osana​​i ano hi no boku nara nante iu?
​osanai ​​ano hi no boku nara nante iu?
​osanai a​​no hi no boku nara nante iu?
​osanai ano ​​hi no boku nara nante iu?
​osanai ano hi ​​no boku nara nante iu?
​osanai ano hi no ​​boku nara nante iu?
​osanai ano hi no bo​​ku nara nante iu?
​osanai ano hi no boku ​​nara nante iu?
​osanai ano hi no boku na​​ra nante iu?
​osanai ano hi no boku nara ​​nante iu?
​osanai ano hi no boku nara na​​nte iu?
​osanai ano hi no boku nara nan​​te iu?
​osanai ano hi no boku nara nante ​​iu?
​osanai ano hi no boku nara nante i​​u?
​osanai ano hi no boku nara nante iu?
​​​ ​Don't stop, never stop​ ​​
​​​ ​tomaranai de​ ​​
​​​ ​I still remember the day we first said hello​ ​​
​​​ ​hajimete bokura deatta hi marude​ ​​
​​​ ​It feels like just yesterday​ ​​
​​​ ​kinou mitai ni omoidasu kedo​ ​​
​​​ ​But it's time to go​ ​​
​​​ ​mou ikou ka​ ​​
​​​ ​We sing our last song​ ​​
​​​ ​saigo ni ima​ ​​
​​​ ​A​s ​t​h​e ​f​i​v​e ​o​f ​u​s, ​b​r​o​u​g​h​t ​t​o​g​e​t​h​e​r ​b​y ​a ​m​i​r​a​c​le​ ​​
​​​ ​k​asanaru gonin no kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​k​a​s​anaru gonin no kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​k​a​s​a​n​aru gonin no kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​k​a​s​a​n​a​r​u gonin no kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​k​a​s​a​n​a​r​u ​g​onin no kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​k​a​s​a​n​a​r​u ​g​o​n​in no kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​k​a​s​a​n​a​r​u ​g​o​n​i​n no kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​k​a​s​a​n​a​r​u ​g​o​n​i​n ​n​o kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​k​a​s​a​n​a​r​u ​g​o​n​i​n ​n​o ​k​iseki​ ​​
​​​ ​k​a​s​a​n​a​r​u ​g​o​n​i​n ​n​o ​k​i​s​eki​ ​​
​​​ ​k​a​s​a​n​a​r​u ​g​o​n​i​n ​n​o ​k​i​s​e​ki​ ​​
​​​ ​C​a​n ​y​o​u ​h​e​a​r ​m​y ​v​o​i​c​e?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​oku no koe wa kikoetemasu ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u no koe wa kikoetemasu ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u ​n​o koe wa kikoetemasu ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u ​n​o ​k​oe wa kikoetemasu ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u ​n​o ​k​o​e wa kikoetemasu ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u ​n​o ​k​o​e ​w​a kikoetemasu ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u ​n​o ​k​o​e ​w​a ​k​ikoetemasu ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u ​n​o ​k​o​e ​w​a ​k​i​k​oetemasu ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u ​n​o ​k​o​e ​w​a ​k​i​k​o​etemasu ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u ​n​o ​k​o​e ​w​a ​k​i​k​o​e​t​emasu ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u ​n​o ​k​o​e ​w​a ​k​i​k​o​e​t​e​m​asu ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u ​n​o ​k​o​e ​w​a ​k​i​k​o​e​t​e​m​a​s​u ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u ​n​o ​k​o​e ​w​a ​k​i​k​o​e​t​e​m​a​s​u ​k​a?​ ​​
​​​ ​I​t​'​s ​f​r​o​m ​m​e ​t​o ​y​ou​ ​​
​​​ ​k​imi ni todoke!​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​m​i ni todoke!​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​m​i ​n​i todoke!​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​m​i ​n​i ​t​odoke!​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​m​i ​n​i ​t​o​d​oke!​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​m​i ​n​i ​t​o​d​o​k​e!​ ​​
​​​ ​G​o ​b​e​y​o​n​d ​t​h​e ​s​c​r​i​b​b​l​e​s ​o​n ​t​h​e ​b​l​a​c​k​b​o​a​rd​ ​​
​​ ​a​n​d ​t​h​e ​f​a​l​l​i​n​g ​c​u​r​t​a​i​n ​o​f ​s​a​k​u​ra​ ​​
​​​ ​k​okuban no messeeji sakura no kaaten kugutte​ ​​
​​​ ​k​o​k​uban no messeeji sakura no kaaten kugutte​ ​​
​​​ ​k​o​k​u​b​an no messeeji sakura no kaaten kugutte​ ​​
​​​ ​k​o​k​u​b​a​n no messeeji sakura no kaaten kugutte​ ​​
​​​ ​k​o​k​u​b​a​n ​n​o messeeji sakura no kaaten kugutte​ ​​
​​​ ​k​o​k​u​b​a​n ​n​o ​m​esseeji sakura no kaaten kugutte​ ​​
​​​ ​k​o​k​u​b​a​n ​n​o ​m​e​sseeji sakura no kaaten kugutte​ ​​
​​​ ​k​o​k​u​b​a​n ​n​o ​m​e​s​s​eeji sakura no kaaten kugutte​ ​​
​​​ ​k​o​k​u​b​a​n ​n​o ​m​e​s​s​e​eji sakura no kaaten kugutte​ ​​
​​​ ​k​o​k​u​b​a​n ​n​o ​m​e​s​s​e​e​j​i sakura no kaaten kugutte​ ​​
​​​ ​k​o​k​u​b​a​n ​n​o ​m​e​s​s​e​e​j​i ​s​akura no kaaten kugutte​ ​​
​​​ ​k​o​k​u​b​a​n ​n​o ​m​e​s​s​e​e​j​i ​s​a​k​ura no kaaten kugutte​ ​​
​​​ ​k​o​k​u​b​a​n ​n​o ​m​e​s​s​e​e​j​i ​s​a​k​u​r​a no kaaten kugutte​ ​​
​​​ ​k​o​k​u​b​a​n ​n​o ​m​e​s​s​e​e​j​i ​s​a​k​u​r​a ​n​o kaaten kugutte​ ​​
​​​ ​k​o​k​u​b​a​n ​n​o ​m​e​s​s​e​e​j​i ​s​a​k​u​r​a ​n​o ​k​aaten kugutte​ ​​
​​​ ​k​o​k​u​b​a​n ​n​o ​m​e​s​s​e​e​j​i ​s​a​k​u​r​a ​n​o ​k​a​aten kugutte​ ​​
​​​ ​k​o​k​u​b​a​n ​n​o ​m​e​s​s​e​e​j​i ​s​a​k​u​r​a ​n​o ​k​a​a​t​en kugutte​ ​​
​​​ ​k​o​k​u​b​a​n ​n​o ​m​e​s​s​e​e​j​i ​s​a​k​u​r​a ​n​o ​k​a​a​t​e​n kugutte​ ​​
​​​ ​k​o​k​u​b​a​n ​n​o ​m​e​s​s​e​e​j​i ​s​a​k​u​r​a ​n​o ​k​a​a​t​e​n ​k​ugutte​ ​​
​​​ ​k​o​k​u​b​a​n ​n​o ​m​e​s​s​e​e​j​i ​s​a​k​u​r​a ​n​o ​k​a​a​t​e​n ​k​u​g​utte​ ​​
​​​ ​k​o​k​u​b​a​n ​n​o ​m​e​s​s​e​e​j​i ​s​a​k​u​r​a ​n​o ​k​a​a​t​e​n ​k​u​g​u​tte​ ​​
​​​ ​k​o​k​u​b​a​n ​n​o ​m​e​s​s​e​e​j​i ​s​a​k​u​r​a ​n​o ​k​a​a​t​e​n ​k​u​g​u​t​te​ ​​
​​​ ​A​n​d ​h​e​a​r ​o​u​r ​v​o​i​c​e​s ​a​l​w​a​ys​ ​​
​​​ ​b​okura no koe o kiite zutto zutto​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​ura no koe o kiite zutto zutto​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u​r​a no koe o kiite zutto zutto​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u​r​a ​n​o koe o kiite zutto zutto​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u​r​a ​n​o ​k​oe o kiite zutto zutto​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u​r​a ​n​o ​k​o​e o kiite zutto zutto​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u​r​a ​n​o ​k​o​e ​o kiite zutto zutto​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u​r​a ​n​o ​k​o​e ​o ​k​iite zutto zutto​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u​r​a ​n​o ​k​o​e ​o ​k​i​ite zutto zutto​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u​r​a ​n​o ​k​o​e ​o ​k​i​i​t​e zutto zutto​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u​r​a ​n​o ​k​o​e ​o ​k​i​i​t​e ​z​utto zutto​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u​r​a ​n​o ​k​o​e ​o ​k​i​i​t​e ​z​u​tto zutto​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u​r​a ​n​o ​k​o​e ​o ​k​i​i​t​e ​z​u​t​t​o zutto​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u​r​a ​n​o ​k​o​e ​o ​k​i​i​t​e ​z​u​t​t​o ​z​utto​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u​r​a ​n​o ​k​o​e ​o ​k​i​i​t​e ​z​u​t​t​o ​z​u​tto​ ​​
​​​ ​b​o​k​u​r​a ​n​o ​k​o​e ​o ​k​i​i​t​e ​z​u​t​t​o ​z​u​t​to​ ​​
​​​ ​O​n ​h​a​p​p​y ​d​a​y​s​, ​o​n ​f​u​n ​d​a​ys​ ​​
​​​ ​ureshii hi tanoshii hi​ ​​
​​​ ​u​r​eshii hi tanoshii hi​ ​​
​​​ ​u​r​e​s​h​ii hi tanoshii hi​ ​​
​​​ ​u​r​e​s​h​i​i hi tanoshii hi​ ​​
​​​ ​u​r​e​s​h​i​i ​h​i tanoshii hi​ ​​
​​​ ​u​r​e​s​h​i​i ​h​i ​t​anoshii hi​ ​​
​​​ ​u​r​e​s​h​i​i ​h​i ​t​a​n​oshii hi​ ​​
​​​ ​u​r​e​s​h​i​i ​h​i ​t​a​n​o​s​h​ii hi​ ​​
​​​ ​u​r​e​s​h​i​i ​h​i ​t​a​n​o​s​h​i​i hi​ ​​
​​​ ​u​r​e​s​h​i​i ​h​i ​t​a​n​o​s​h​i​i ​hi​ ​​
​​​ ​O​n ​s​a​d ​d​a​y​s​, ​a​n​d ​o​n ​d​a​y​s ​o​f ​p​a​r​t​i​ng​ ​​
​​​ ​k​anashii hi wakare no hi mo​ ​​
​​​ ​k​a​n​ashii hi wakare no hi mo​ ​​
​​​ ​k​a​n​a​s​h​ii hi wakare no hi mo​ ​​
​​​ ​k​a​n​a​s​h​i​i hi wakare no hi mo​ ​​
​​​ ​k​a​n​a​s​h​i​i ​h​i wakare no hi mo​ ​​
​​​ ​k​a​n​a​s​h​i​i ​h​i ​w​akare no hi mo​ ​​
​​​ ​k​a​n​a​s​h​i​i ​h​i ​w​a​k​are no hi mo​ ​​
​​​ ​k​a​n​a​s​h​i​i ​h​i ​w​a​k​a​r​e no hi mo​ ​​
​​​ ​k​a​n​a​s​h​i​i ​h​i ​w​a​k​a​r​e ​n​o hi mo​ ​​
​​​ ​k​a​n​a​s​h​i​i ​h​i ​w​a​k​a​r​e ​n​o ​h​i mo​ ​​
​​​ ​k​a​n​a​s​h​i​i ​h​i ​w​a​k​a​r​e ​n​o ​h​i ​mo​ ​​
​​​ ​O​u​r ​f​i​v​e ​c​o​l​o​r​s ​c​o​m​e ​t​o​g​e​t​h​e​r ​t​o ​d​r​a​w ​a ​m​i​r​a​c​l​e ​s​t​ar​ ​​
​​​ ​s​orezore no iro de hoshi musubu kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​r​ezore no iro de hoshi musubu kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​r​e​z​ore no iro de hoshi musubu kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​r​e​z​o​r​e no iro de hoshi musubu kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​r​e​z​o​r​e ​n​o iro de hoshi musubu kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​r​e​z​o​r​e ​n​o ​iro de hoshi musubu kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​r​e​z​o​r​e ​n​o ​i​r​o de hoshi musubu kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​r​e​z​o​r​e ​n​o ​i​r​o ​d​e hoshi musubu kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​r​e​z​o​r​e ​n​o ​i​r​o ​d​e ​h​oshi musubu kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​r​e​z​o​r​e ​n​o ​i​r​o ​d​e ​h​o​s​h​i musubu kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​r​e​z​o​r​e ​n​o ​i​r​o ​d​e ​h​o​s​h​i ​m​usubu kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​r​e​z​o​r​e ​n​o ​i​r​o ​d​e ​h​o​s​h​i ​m​u​s​ubu kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​r​e​z​o​r​e ​n​o ​i​r​o ​d​e ​h​o​s​h​i ​m​u​s​u​b​u kiseki​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​r​e​z​o​r​e ​n​o ​i​r​o ​d​e ​h​o​s​h​i ​m​u​s​u​b​u ​k​iseki​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​r​e​z​o​r​e ​n​o ​i​r​o ​d​e ​h​o​s​h​i ​m​u​s​u​b​u ​k​i​s​eki​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​r​e​z​o​r​e ​n​o ​i​r​o ​d​e ​h​o​s​h​i ​m​u​s​u​b​u ​k​i​s​e​ki​ ​​
​​​ ​A​n​d ​o​n ​t​h​i​s ​s​p​a​r​k​l​i​n​g ​s​t​a​ge​ ​​
​​​ ​k​irakira kagayaku suteeji de​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​r​akira kagayaku suteeji de​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​r​a​k​ira kagayaku suteeji de​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​r​a​k​i​r​a kagayaku suteeji de​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​r​a​k​i​r​a ​k​agayaku suteeji de​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​r​a​k​i​r​a ​k​a​g​ayaku suteeji de​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​r​a​k​i​r​a ​k​a​g​a​y​aku suteeji de​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​r​a​k​i​r​a ​k​a​g​a​y​a​k​u suteeji de​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​r​a​k​i​r​a ​k​a​g​a​y​a​k​u ​s​uteeji de​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​r​a​k​i​r​a ​k​a​g​a​y​a​k​u ​s​u​t​eeji de​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​r​a​k​i​r​a ​k​a​g​a​y​a​k​u ​s​u​t​e​eji de​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​r​a​k​i​r​a ​k​a​g​a​y​a​k​u ​s​u​t​e​e​j​i de​ ​​
​​​ ​k​i​r​a​k​i​r​a ​k​a​g​a​y​a​k​u ​s​u​t​e​e​j​i ​de​ ​​
​​​ ​L​e​t​'​s ​m​a​k​e ​a ​p​r​o​m​i​s​e ​t​h​a​t ​s​o​m​e​d​a​y​, ​i​n ​t​h​i​s ​s​a​m​e ​p​l​a​ce​ ​​
​​​ ​y​akusoku shiyou itsuka koko de​ ​​
​​​ ​y​a​k​usoku shiyou itsuka koko de​ ​​
​​​ ​y​a​k​u​s​oku shiyou itsuka koko de​ ​​
​​​ ​y​a​k​u​s​o​k​u shiyou itsuka koko de​ ​​
​​​ ​y​a​k​u​s​o​k​u ​s​h​iyou itsuka koko de​ ​​
​​​ ​y​a​k​u​s​o​k​u ​s​h​i​y​ou itsuka koko de​ ​​
​​​ ​y​a​k​u​s​o​k​u ​s​h​i​y​o​u itsuka koko de​ ​​
​​​ ​y​a​k​u​s​o​k​u ​s​h​i​y​o​u ​itsuka koko de​ ​​
​​​ ​y​a​k​u​s​o​k​u ​s​h​i​y​o​u ​i​t​s​uka koko de​ ​​
​​​ ​y​a​k​u​s​o​k​u ​s​h​i​y​o​u ​i​t​s​u​k​a koko de​ ​​
​​​ ​y​a​k​u​s​o​k​u ​s​h​i​y​o​u ​i​t​s​u​k​a ​k​oko de​ ​​
​​​ ​y​a​k​u​s​o​k​u ​s​h​i​y​o​u ​i​t​s​u​k​a ​k​o​k​o de​ ​​
​​​ ​y​a​k​u​s​o​k​u ​s​h​i​y​o​u ​i​t​s​u​k​a ​k​o​k​o ​de​ ​​
​​​ ​W​e ​w​i​l​l ​m​e​e​t ​a​g​a​in​ ​​
​​​ ​"​m​ata aou"​ ​​
​​​ ​"​m​a​t​a aou"​ ​​
​​​ ​"​m​a​t​a ​aou"​ ​​
​​​ ​"​m​a​t​a ​a​ou"​ ​​
​​​ ​"​m​a​t​a ​a​o​u"​ ​​
​​​ ​That's done...​ ​​
​​​ ​We sang it!​ ​​
​​​ ​(TowaCry)​ ​​
​​​ ​We're all lost for words.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm so glad we sang it.​ ​​
​​​ ​You okay there, Towa?​ ​​
​​ ​I'm so glad we sang it.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm so glad we sang it.​ ​​
​​​ ​Of course!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm so happy we all got to sing it together!​ ​​
​​​ ​Cut it out!​ ​​
​​​ ​(playing around)​ ​​
​​​ ​I feel loved.​ ​​
​​​ ​We love ya!​ ​​
​​​ ​I love you all!​ ​​
​​​ ​To think that song started from​ ​​
​​​ ​Kanata oversleeping...​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, I paid for it.​ ​​
​​​ ​All on you.​ ​​
​​​ ​All me.​ ​​
​​ ​All on you.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's the best song ever...​ ​​
​​​ ​God-tier!​ ​​
​​ ​It's the best song ever...​ ​​
​​​ ​Best song ever!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's such a good song!​ ​​
​​​ ​I really wanted to make sure​ ​​
​​ ​we could sing it here on this graduation stream,​ ​​
​​​ ​even if it was the last time we'll ever sing it.​ ​​
​​​ ​Um, if I could butt in for a bit,​ ​​
​​​ ​there's uhh―​ ​​
​​​ ​Kanata said on her streams that she wouldn't mind​ ​​
​​ ​if this song were retired after today,​ ​​
​​​ ​but personally,​ ​​
​​​ ​I'd want you guys to​ ​​
​​​ ​continue singing this song even without me!​ ​​
​​​ ​We've got no choice now, don't we?​ ​​
​​​ ​We'll sing your parts too, Coco.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, you can all sing my parts together.​ ​​
​​​ ​Though, well,​ ​​
​​​ ​our parts are all separate,​ ​​
​​​ ​and my name's in my part of the song, too!​ ​​
​​​ ​But yeah,​ ​​
​​​ ​I love this song, and it was made by all of us,​ ​​
​​​ ​so I want to keep hearing the four of you singing it.​ ​​
​​​ ​If Coco says we should do it, then let's keep on singing it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Please do!​ ​​
​​ ​If Coco says we should do it, then let's keep on singing it!​ ​​
​​​ ​If Coco says we should do it, then let's keep on singing it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Cheer up!​ ​​
​​​ ​We'll sing it while cwying!​ ​​
​​​ ​We'd all end up crying!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, wait. Hold on. Isn't this―?​ ​​
​​​ ​Hold on a sec.​ ​​
​​​ ​I remember this formation!​ ​​
​​ ​Hold on a sec.​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't you guys remember?​ ​​
​​​ ​Line up, guys!​ ​​
​​​ ​One of us had this as a Twitter header!​ ​​
​​​ ​We had a picture like this, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​I think we can recreate it.​ ​​
​​​ ​Take a seat, Luna.​ ​​
​​​ ​It shows what happens when we line up our heads,​ ​​
​​​ ​and just how big the height gap is.​ ​​
​​​ ​Closer guys, closer!​ ​​
​​​ ​I remember this.​ ​​
​​ ​Closer guys, closer!​ ​​
​​​ ​It went like this, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​Post your screenshots, okay?​ ​​
​​ ​It went like this, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​How nostalgic!​ ​​
​​​ ​This takes me back!​ ​​
​​ ​How nostalgic!​ ​​
​​​ ​I had to suffer to take this pic for our debut!​ ​​
​​​ ​It hurts the knees!​ ​​
​​​ ​I wanted to do this one last time.​ ​​
​​​ ​Luna's tired!​ ​​
​​​ ​What happened?​ ​​
​​​ ​It's hard to maintain your balance while sitting like this.​ ​​
​​​ ​That's true!​ ​​
​​​ ​I almost forgot to do this. Good thing we did!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's a good thing I remembered.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh wait, I remembered another thing.​ ​​
​​​ ​Didn't we say that when we get our 3D models,​ ​​
​​​ ​we'd all wrestle each other?​ ​​
​​​ ​Wrestling?!​ ​​
​​​ ​We did say that!​ ​​
​​​ ​Right?​ ​​
​​​ ​We'll be westling?​ ​​
​​ ​Right?​ ​​
​​​ ​Brawl-for-all?​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's go? Let's do it?​ ​​
​​​ ​You won't be fighting, Luna.​ ​​
​​​ ​Aaaaaagh!​ ​​
​​​ ​So strong!​ ​​
​​​ ​(dragon > sheep)​ ​​
​​​ ​Come at me!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ah.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh. No, not you.​ ​​
​​​ ​(gorillaangel > dragon)​ ​​
​​​ ​You almost got crushed.​ ​​
​​​ ​Come back when you've grown a bit more.​ ​​
​​​ ​Man.​ ​​
​​​ ​The time has come, guys.​ ​​
​​​ ​This will be the last time​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll be standing up here as an idol.​ ​​
​​​ ​I want to show everyone my best performance!​ ​​
​​​ ​You all would call me an idol, yeah?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm not too sure about that.​ ​​
​​​ ​At least be one at the end!​ ​​
​​​ ​What do you mean "at the end"?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Were you always one...?​ ​​
​​​ ​At the very least...​ ​​
​​​ ​Shut it! Not another word!​ ​​
​​​ ​Pose like one, then.​ ​​
​​​ ​Like an idol?​ ​​
​​​ ​(Idol pose...?)​ ​​
​​​ ​A new age idol, maybe...​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, that was fun. But let's cap things off​ ​​
​​​ ​with my original song.​ ​​
​​​ ​I want everyone​ ​​
​​​ ​to listen to Kiryu Coco's original song.​ ​​
​​​ ​How about a change of scenery?​ ​​
​​​ ​Sure thing! That stage, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes, that stage!​ ​​
​​ ​Sure thing! That stage, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​All right, let's go!​ ​​
​​ ​Yes, that stage!​ ​​
​​​ ​Move yer arses!​ ​​
​​​ ​You're all too slow!​ ​​
​​​ ​Y'all just fast!​ ​​
​​​ ​(docking... docking...)​ ​​
​​​ ​Y'all still full of energy, right?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, we're here! Take your spots! One, two...​ ​​
​​​ ​(Docking complete.)​ ​​
​​​ ​We've arrived!​ ​​
​​​ ​Welcome to the Kiryu Group runway!​ ​​
​​​ ​I, Kiryu Coco, will use this stage​ ​​
​​​ ​for my last stand as an idol!​ ​​
​​​ ​What are you gonna show us?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Listen up!​ ​​
​​​ ​Could you guys hype up the stage?​ ​​
​​​ ​Heck yeah!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm gonna stand here proud!​ ​​
​​​ ​Complete with crossed arms!​ ​​
​​ ​I'm gonna stand here proud!​ ​​
​​​ ​Fine. Y'all get front-row seats.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yaaaay!​ ​​
​​​ ​Watch over me like proud boyfriends!​ ​​
​​​ ​Sorry, guys!​ ​​
​​​ ​All right, you front-row-hogging superfans!​ ​​
​​​ ​Listen up, and make yourselves heard!​ ​​
​​​ ​This is my original song,​ ​​
​​​ ​Weather Hackers!​ ​​
​​​ ​Woohoo! Yeaaaah! Coco!​ ​​
​​​ ​When you're about to lose hope,​ ​​
​​ ​let me perk up your day​ ​​
​​​ ​makesou na toki wa yuuki o ageru yo​ ​​
​​​ ​With a shining bright smile​ ​​
​​​ ​kyou mo mabushii egao de☆​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!​ ​​
​​ ​With a shining bright smile​ ​​
​​​ ​You're the best!​ ​​
​​​ ​You're the cutest!​ ​​
​​​ ​Smile, please!​ ​​
​​​ ​Do you remember the time​ ​​
​​​ ​hajimete deatta toki no​ ​​
​​​ ​When we all first met?​ ​​
​​​ ​koto o oboeteimasu ka?​ ​​
​​​ ​We would look to a place beyond the sky​ ​​
​​​ ​yume to kibou afureta me de​ ​​
​​​ ​Our eyes filled with hopes and dreams​ ​​
​​​ ​sora no mukou itsumo nagameteita yo ne​ ​​
​​​ ​We don't need anything special​ ​​
​​​ ​kitto tokubetsuna mono nante iranai yo​ ​​
​​​ ​As long as we got the courage to move forward​ ​​
​​​ ​mae ni susumu yuuki ga areba​ ​​
​​​ ​That brave step you're taking right now​ ​​
​​​ ​kimi ga ima fumidashita chikarazuyoi ippo de​ ​​
​​​ ​Will make the sun shine on all your days​ ​​
​​​ ​donna tenki mo hareteyuku yo​ ​​
​​​ ​(Up we go! 1, 2, 3, Jump!)​ ​​
​​​ ​(tobu zo~! 1, 2, 3, Jump!!)​ ​​
​​​ ​Good morning, Weather Hackers​ ​​
​​​ ​Good morning, Weather Hackers☆​ ​​
​​​ ​This ray of morning sunshine is​ ​​
​​​ ​asa no hikari o abita​ ​​
​​​ ​Gonna brighten up​ ​​
​​​ ​minna no haato ni​ ​​
​​​ ​All your hearts​ ​​
​​​ ​genki o todokeru n da​ ​​
​​​ ​Good morning, Weather Hackers​ ​​
​​​ ​Good morning, Weather Hackers☆​ ​​
​​​ ​As you continue to chase your dreams​ ​​
​​​ ​yume e to hashiridashita​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll open up your minds​ ​​
​​​ ​minna no kokoro ni​ ​​
​​​ ​To the big blue sky​ ​​
​​​ ​aozora o todokeru yo​ ​​
​​​ ​When you're about to lose hope,​ ​​
​​ ​let me perk up your day​ ​​
​​​ ​makesou na toki wa yuuki o ageru yo​ ​​
​​​ ​With a shining bright smile​ ​​
​​​ ​kyou mo mabushii egao de☆​ ​​
​​​ ​If you think you've done a pretty good job​ ​​
​​​ ​sukoshi dake ganbattara​ ​​
​​​ ​You can always stop for a rest​ ​​
​​​ ​ashi o tomete yasunde ne​ ​​
​​​ ​Nothing in this world is meaningless​ ​​
​​​ ​mudana koto nante nai kara​ ​​
​​​ ​If you look back, you'll know it all comes together​ ​​
​​​ ​furikareba subete ga tsunagatteru yo​ ​​
​​​ ​Let your sparking feelings ride the wind​ ​​
​​​ ​kagayaita omoi o harukana kaze ni nosete​ ​​
​​​ ​As it spreads its wings toward the free blue sky​ ​​
​​​ ​jiyuuna sora hane hirogetara​ ​​
​​​ ​You'll know that you can always move forward with life​ ​​
​​​ ​"itsu datte mae muite aruiteikeba ii!" tte​ ​​
​​​ ​And your heart will shine on all the days​ ​​
​​​ ​kimi no kokoro mo hareteyuku yo​ ​​
​​​ ​(Up we go! 1, 2, 3, Jump!)​ ​​
​​​ ​(iku yo~! 1, 2, 3, Jump!!)​ ​​
​​​ ​Good morning, Weather Hackers​ ​​
​​​ ​Good morning, Weather Hackers☆​ ​​
​​​ ​This ray of morning sunshine is​ ​​
​​​ ​asa no hikari o abita​ ​​
​​​ ​Gonna brighten up​ ​​
​​​ ​minna no haato ni​ ​​
​​​ ​All your hearts​ ​​
​​​ ​genki o todokeru n da​ ​​
​​​ ​Good morning, Weather Hackers​ ​​
​​​ ​Good morning, Weather Hackers☆​ ​​
​​​ ​As you continue to chase your dreams​ ​​
​​​ ​yume e to hashiridashita​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll open up your minds​ ​​
​​​ ​minna no kokoro ni​ ​​
​​​ ​To the big blue sky​ ​​
​​​ ​aozora o todokeru yo​ ​​
​​​ ​When you're nearly down and out, I will pick you up​ ​​
​​​ ​tsukareta toki ni wa iyashi o ageru yo​ ​​
​​​ ​So go on, spread your wings and fly​ ​​
​​​ ​tobou hirogeta tsubasa de☆​ ​​
​​​ ​Lightning flashes up above​ ​​
​​​ ​sora ni kirameku raikou​ ​​
​​​ ​Our roars echo all around​ ​​
​​​ ​hibiki watatta houkou​ ​​
​​​ ​Glory rests at our fingertips​ ​​
​​​ ​mirai ni kagayaku eikou​ ​​
​​​ ​So don't give up on your dreams​ ​​
​​​ ​sono yume o akirameru na​ ​​
​​​ ​Bring on all the trials and tribulations​ ​​
​​​ ​konnan rifujin mo joutou​ ​​
​​​ ​Stare 'em dead in the eye and let the sparks fly​ ​​
​​​ ​matomete hanekaesu gankou​ ​​
​​​ ​Go your own way!​ ​​
​​​ ​Keep going right now!​ ​​
​​​ ​susume Right now!​ ​​
​​​ ​Toward the sky yet unseen​ ​​
​​​ ​mada minu sora no mukou e—​ ​​
​​​ ​Thank you!​ ​​
​​ ​Toward the sky yet unseen​ ​​
​​​ ​I love you!​ ​​
​​​ ​You're always in my heart.​ ​​
​​​ ​You fought well.​ ​​
​​​ ​Good morning, Weather Hackers​ ​​
​​​ ​Good morning, Weather Hackers☆​ ​​
​​​ ​This ray of morning sunshine is​ ​​
​​​ ​asa no hikari o abita​ ​​
​​​ ​Gonna brighten up​ ​​
​​​ ​minna no haato ni​ ​​
​​​ ​All your hearts​ ​​
​​​ ​genki o todokeru n da​ ​​
​​​ ​When you're about to cry, I'll wipe away your tears​ ​​
​​​ ​nakisou na toki wa genki o ageru yo​ ​​
​​​ ​So let's go, wearing a wonderful smile​ ​​
​​​ ​ikou sutekina sumairu de☆​ ​​