com
to
[Music]
com
to
[Music]
know
to
[Music]
know
oop oop hello everybody this is a
jailbird here being the bouncer for the
whisle waving qu super a cool s party
2024 I wonder what guest is going to
show up first at this party I wonder who
it could
[Music]
[Laughter]
be oh my gosh is that Elizabeth W's
blood flame yes roses are red the fire
of my heart is blue also known as The
Scarlet Queen the harbinger of water a
leader of Justice I am Elizabeth Rose
bloodflame lovely to see see you to see
you lovely thank you so much for coming
today but you know I need proof that
you're actually invited to this party so
could I please have your ticket and your
ID to confirm that you're not just a
cosplayer you look at # blood Raven I
mean I mean oh I'll oh that kind of
proof okay okay here's the ticket okay
yes okay okay it looks like you are who
you say you are never mind what I said
I'm I'm going in okay bye okay have a
good time at the party
whatever that was that was a that was
interesting well oh my goodness is
thatu oh my God you know who I am you
talk like that so I want to talk like
this to hello oh hello it's so nice to
find out we meet you I'm a jailbird oh
hello ja boy
I SP for and darkness of H life
English your pajas are so so cute oh
thank you you're so fluffy I would
squeeze the juice out of you oh my well
uh well maybe give me your ID and your
ticket so I can make sure that you're
actually invited cuz that sounds a
little menacing I don't know if that's
something be you would say I I'm a
criminal I can't just show you my ID it
over fine do all okay it looks like it
looks pretty good okay you're welcome to
go on in be okay don't don't call copy
my ID and anything give it to the
government okay thanks okay
bye wow what a cutie
pie I'm not a i h i h I'm together
we and we want into the SL party oh you
want into the SL party I feel like oh oh
you can't just go on in you have to go
ahead and give me your
IDs did you bring it I don't know are
you authorized to look at our ID hard of
course I am I'm the jailbird bouncer of
this party are you questioning my
authority yeah I'm questioning I'm
questioning a lot of
things with be in charge I can't wait
you win without
[Music]
it IFA says so I guess you can take a
peek okay okay thank you very much here
you go oh wow you got a shed ticket
that's so
cute card that seems not Wile but all
right I guess if you're a pair have fun
at the
party wow they're so
cute g
g g is this where the cool girl girls
are at I heard there's cute girls in a
tent can I see them can I see them H H
that that's a little menacing Gigi I
guess if you will we want why are you
keeping the woman the women the women I
I I don't know if I should let you in
after you said that actually where are
where are they where are the woman the
wom in the cute in the cute pajamas I
want to see them your pajamas are quite
cute too oh really thank you oh yeah
you're naked yeah that's that's how I wh
my wife oh disgusting oh give me your
VIP ticket okay here it
is okay I guess you will we were invited
even though you're mean I you how f with
the wom woman woman woman woman woman
let me in let me in let me in gosh what
a
weirdo w
W welcome to the party it is me a
[Music]
jailbird you look you look tasty oh
please don't eat me I'm just a little
bird I'm not
[Music]
tasty can I take can I take a bite uh no
no no I'm I you wouldn't like it you
wouldn't like it I taste I taste like
letter no no no but you know I need you
just why don't just give me your ID you
need to get in there oh right I came
here for slumber party is is there is
this the party yeah this is the party at
the white
place
okay okay what it is I I lost it did I
drop no no no it my ticket maybe I have
maybe I have no ticket where's the
ticket oh wait there it is here we go
okay oh wow such a pretty picture you
have on here so cute can I take a bite
can I take a bite now no get in here go
have fun at the party take a bite out in
a whistle or something it's her birthday
you're right okay I go bite cute girls
then byebye bye have
fun oh my
God what's up I am chaos the end of end
the Ste is trapped in a cage of ice your
best friend B go from my life English is
witness me
popcorn popcorn the the party is popor
there's popcorn I want popcorn okay okay
if you want popcorn you can have plenty
once you get inside but first I'm going
to need to see your ticket and your ID
all righty I think it's got here
somewhere oh no that's oh that's not it
oh that's
okay there it is here you go
oh thank you so much oh look at that all
right it looks very pretty have a good
time eat lots of popcorn
pop oh my God she was so [\h__\h] cute
what the heck oh that was a bad word
oh hello need to well I heard that
everyone is going to sleep in this party
it's a sleep party yes it is indeed a
swim party but if I if I have to be
honest with you I don't know how much
sweeping is going to happen what there's
no I woke up just for this because I
heard that I was going to be going to
sleep with other people it was what I it
it'll be fine I think that will be
sweeping eventually and plus you have
your pillow what yeah I mean I came
prepared I heard it was a slumber party
and that everyone's going to go to sleep
and there's going to be some nice little
lights and I don't know I feel kind of
scammed oh just it's okay just get in
there give me a ticket and you can go to
sleep once you get inside okay really
are we really going to sleep just sleep
yeah totally I wouldn't want to I'm just
a deal bird really if you lie to me can
I can I eat you I'm feeling I'm not
tasty you don't want to eat me there's
plenty of food inside want to pluck your
feathers and eat you you look mighty
tasty and fresh no hand it over fine
fine here it
[Music]
is okay looks like you're confirmed
guess please don't eat the gilbirds
inside the tent okay I I can't wait come
on come here let's get some oh yeah
Fried Chicken have
fun oh my God
my I am walking here all right I there
was a slumber party there's a slumber
party and you you are invited aren't you
yeah I think I am do you got any popcorn
there's plenty of popcorn there's some
dwinks there's some Che off wind
Cheetos your your accent brings me back
to the the streets of Brook Brooklyn
Brooklyn I've never been there you sound
like you've been
there no I have't can I can I have your
ID
yeah all right here it is I'm walking
I'm walking on inside this T I'll W you
in Walking In okay get on in get on in
there have fun miss B now I'm walking
wow oh that was kind of scary I couldn't
I couldn't control oh my God hi wish
it's I wish I wish it's IIs is that the
most famous fat
food that in front of me right now yes I
am the famous fat FL member
I'm a jailb it's so I'm meeting the most
marketable plushy
ever thank you thank you no autographs
please no autographs I'm wearing these
sunglasses yeah I I need your autograph
of why would I need your autograph it's
not like not like I want to squeeze you
to death or anything no oh yeah yeah no
I understand it's okay you can be a
widow soon to way about it I get it yeah
anyways I heard that there's like the
most famous like uh the party that
everyone wants to be a part of going on
right now and I am you know specifically
invited because I am just that famous
yes oh of course you would be you are
like the famous death wom in the whole
wide world give me your ticket an ID
we'll get you right in what I I need I
need an ID yeah an idea and a ticket
isn't it just really obvious who I am
like at these horns and everything I
need a confirmation just in case you're
a beautiful
cosplayer I how you would ever mistaken
me the actual ual thing in cosplayer I'm
hand it over hand it over okay okay okay
okay fine fine I thought I could just
come in with just a pass and everything
like with a just a face pass like this
is absolutely like insulting I well
you're confirmed just get get in there
and have fun with your
friends okay goodbye goodbye goodbye
beautiful she's so funny and
cute hello
hello it's a I think you're a last guest
Cecilia oh I'm the last guest hello I've
come to this party because I want to
braid everyone's
haira gooo Gaga I want you to braid my
hair but I made a hair I'll braid
everyone's hair and then I'll ask
someone can I can I please can I please
get a massage and then I'll fall asleep
is that okay uh yeah I think so as long
as you got a ticket and stuff anything
you do is okay I have a ticket hair TI
and a hair brush okay what about
9d you do you have an
ID yes okay hand it over okay
here ah yes yes okay all the credentials
work right all right get on in there and
have a good time at the party yay party
time well I think that's everyone I
wonder how things are going in the party
[Music]
[Applause]
room hia Darlings this is hollow live
English advent's devilish Jaa The One
and Only narissa Raven coft thank you to
hollow Ms and my darling jailbirds alike
for coming to my slumber party as you
know it's my second time having a
birthday here in hollow life so I I hope
we can have lots of fun
together hi everyone thank you so much
for
coming happy
[Music]
birthday Happ
[Applause]
[Music]
happy
[Applause]
birthday that was amazing um well thank
you all for coming as as I already said
uh however I I must point out we do have
uh two two a few guests I think three
who were not able to attend who uh made
something a little special so do you
think it's okay if we if we watch some
quick special things from from our our
little our little friends who couldn't
make it
tonight let's do
it all let me just let me just set up
this uh projector you know it's a little
difficult being in this pillow for it
you
know it's a little cranked but it's okay
it's comfy though it's so
[Music]
cozy
futuristic happy
birthday you think oh you might think
I'm a my but I'm actually pasta this is
this is
pre-recorded I really wish that I could
have spent your birthday with you and
everyone uh I'm sorry I'm I'm stuck in
the void
but uh I just wanted to drop by to say
happy birthday I hope you have a
wonderful day a wonderful stream a
wonderful year and I hope we get to do
lots of fun things together
yay happy birthday bye bye thank you
byebye
[Music]
I know
she's next we have one from my genid who
couldn't be here miss shiori Nolla I I
wonder what she has to say for my
birthday what kind of excuse she'll give
for not being here
todayi hey Risa sorry I can't there I
have to chase Justice down before they
can get to our
headquarters I'm just making sure that
all of
you know I'll probably be gone for a
while but just want you to know that
you're in my thoughts somewhere there
instead of paying attention to like
where I'm going and driving and all that
you know hope you're having a grand time
you go make out with all the hall life
girls if you want whatever makes you
happy wow Hall life straightest remember
narissa ravencraft let's go
okay I should pay attention to the road
now I'll see you when I get back
bye-bye she does realize all of justice
is here at this party right objection
you're
on is here too right how is she going to
protect this if
she's a will there's a
way unless PO on the road trip we have
one last message from takanashi kiata
yay
let's
seea hi narissa hi my darling I'm here
to wish you a very special birthday
sorry I can only be here in a message
but
well I need to contain myself because I
will sing you a birthday song with a
very special extra dance are you ready
let me get in
position ready as all ever
be here we go Marissa let me Riz you
like you Riz all of us is said happy
birthday to you happy
birthday oh my God happy
birthday your
pant happy
birthday
choreography God oh my God
oh my god did you like it I didn't
realize it was this kind of slumber
party I didn't realize it are you are
you Reda you feel I'm very rised I'm
blushing oh my gosh do you need
something to help calm you down uh I'll
I'll be okay I'll be okay
[Applause]
uh well um let's get this party on the
road first off I I've already said this
like 50 times thank you for coming it's
so nice see all your beautiful faces and
your cute
pajamas so
cute I love
it today is a day for games as this is a
party after we're done playing the games
of course as per crony's request we will
all have to have a big sleepover
together but first we will be gaming
will we cuddle of
course I mean look look how comfy this
whole room looks it's all made out of
pillows and blankets so it's premium
premium sleepover
Fair uh today I have a few events
planned uh we're going to have three
different games as well as at the end we
have two members who have very
graciously decided to tell us some of
the spookiest stories that they could
conjure up so please look forward to
that at the end I didn't know we were
doing horror song
why be scared yeah don't be scared you
scared I I heard this was aai party not
a kaai
party yeah I wanted a yoai party it is a
y partyone to hold my hand I'll hold
your
hand holding your
[Music]
hand um knows what a u bu party is it's
a sleepover
right sleep sleepover yes yeah just a
sleepover seems everyone's been told
different things about this
party it's it's okay it's I needed to
get you all to come somehow so you lied
to us false marketing never Li to
us uh I back back back on track anyway
uh I've split everyone into groups uh I
will introduce the groups now just so
you all know and uh obviously since I'm
the birthday girl I figured you'd maybe
all want to play with me a little bit uh
I will be in every
group yeah group a is going to be
fuaa
G yay
fa and Liz let's go uh Group B is going
to be motan
M Yi
and and me and I think I think we had to
put someone else in there because we had
a last minute having to leave so sorry
in advance I I don't remember who it is
at this specific moment in time but I
think it's someone from Group C Group C
is going to be
KIU b b sen
by
ir and still
perfect um I realize answering to names
okay uh there is going to be a prize If
you overachieve or win or just do well
enough that I am impressed you are going
to be getting a pillow throw as it
wouldn't be a slumber party without a
pillow throw
um rules are when you get a pillow you
uh can tell us who you want to throw it
at and all the throws that you do will
be scored by some beautiful lovely
jailbird judges at the end all the
scores will be tracked and whoever got
the most uh the the the highest score uh
will win best sleepover guest award so
please impr
me uh let's I I'll show you an example
so I can entice you with with the pillow
throws jailbirds I need your help
okay so
as holy moly I thought it was aill not a
laser sorry I'm just really good at
pillow throws but don't worry I I
shouldn't get any in this game so you
guys are all safe for me absolutely
delated from existence wait is this a
murder
party no no no it's it's just no one
will die it's just a pillow it's just a
pillow if you a Mur are you I don't see
that gilberd anymore no he's he's up in
the in the upper right corner see why
is he's
[Music]
not he's not breathing he
sleeping let me out um now I will say if
you underachieve fail or choose not to
do things you will be punished um for
your first offense uh you will get me
dry on your face uh your second defense
there will be a secret batsu game so
please uh do not win all the time cuz I
would like to watch you get
pess bless
you uh now we actually have our first
game I must tell you only three people
get to play this game I have picked
people from group a b and c uh please
respond to your name uh representing
group a will be drum roll
please here I'm here miss miss Nissa
Raven I'm here am right here when do I
get extra credit you probably will from
this game whoever wins will confirmed
get like at least one pillow throw um
representing Group B will be
M yeah
M and representing Group C will be K
beu I will bring Pride to our group make
us Pride I believe in you
child power my comrad they will be
destroyed let's let's transition over so
I can show it to you as well as explain
the rules shall we
welcome to the jailbird popcorn game so
cute in this game you guys will all have
access to a button uh with this button
you can click throw popcorn and your
goal is to hit a jailbird uh there's
different points depending on what you
hit of course so first off it will be if
you hit a blue jailbird anywhere on
their body you will get one point if you
hit a blue jailbird on on the mouth
properly feeding them you will get three
points if you hit a gold jail bird
you'll get two points and if you hit the
gold bird on the mouth you will get four
this is going to go with a first to 10
points will be the winner and get a
pillow throw so you will each have three
test throws and then we will just get
started uh there will be probably a
little bit of of leg so good good
luck wishing you luck uh you guys can
just go in order so Gigi Moco and beu
we'll get three test rows and then we'll
move on so the other two can test and
then we'll just get right into it
intering one at a time okay okay what
did these jailbirds do to deserve being
fed by Hol members by
hand deserve it okay that was go in a
different direction than I thought it
would yeah yeah yeah it's it's okay it's
okay it's a test it's a
test okay am am I doing it uh you you're
testing the lag so you're goal is to hit
the jailbirds somewhere on their body
[Laughter]
preferably you get one more test I'm
testing I'm testing does it show you
when you hit them yeah see there you hit
the jailbird the popcorn's on the
jailbird all
right your turn to test you get three
throw
oh okay hey don't laugh laugh laugh
get the wasn't laughing I just had
something in my throat you
sure
okay here's your three 10 one more than
oh sorry can I not count moo do you have
one more oh I think I did one more okay
I'll do
it get the gold one get the gold one
yeah okay now for sure be's
[Applause]
turn oh
no you got this make us proud she's a
gamer come
on bring Anna to the it's it's okay it's
okay on you on the
board do this for you guys Group C
[Music]
woohoo testing it's just testing it's
yes this was a test
okay now we do have a scoreboard so
it'll automatically be updated uh as you
can see here so just do your best good
luck have fun GG uh you'll go and again
it'll be one at a time oh wow
M many
um
referee
it's an example an example cheating all
right so it'll be gig goes M mang goes
and then
goes bro I'm sorry I'm so nervous okay
GG get
gone gets gone get gone I'm going to go
no
youing my turn okay yeah I got gold or
nothing it's the gold or Nothing Gold or
Nothing Gold or
[Music]
nothing the timing is not
right here we go come
on I believe I believe you major wait
wait wait I'm timing it I'm timing it I
[Music]
believe GG gold or Nothing Gold or
Nothing Gold or Nothing Gold or nothing
okay okay wait wait wait wait wait gold
is a really good color and then o not
this one not the next one next one okay
gold
gold no
my
turn Sil don't you want food let them
feed
[Music]
you f oh wait a second is not the
timing that
was okay
[Music]
I this is not the timing this is not the
timing this is the timing
this is the
time you hit you're really good at
aiming
there all right g gold or Nothing Gold
or Nothing Gold
nothing wasting so much
popcorn look like that is the lead
winning no
way hold on hold on hold on hold on hold
on hold on hold
on okay okay I'm imagining it I'm
imagining it yes I'm going to hit I'm
going to hit CeCe I'm going to kill her
you're
right her and she died
that was look at that that was only two
points though I'm almost there
yeah you can do
[Music]
it none of us say mo today
huh is it does it count does it count
count grave grave bonus grave bonus I
know yes yes yes
wait I
think are M and G are tied and beu is
not
winning that who's where are these
points
theion anyone got a point I'm a su I see
how it is
remember if you a in the the
mouth
Focus the gold one in the mouth gold one
is gold though yeah
gold that's a foot that's definitely a
foot very nice let's
go wow wait wait wait wait did my point
go
you don't get
your all right GG do your best remember
when we were everyone's on two points
remember that sh yes I'm remembering the
I'm remembering the sho I'm going I'm
going to kill him I'm going to kill
him we need to go back yeah I got to hit
C wow confidence Happ
confidence L that's not a j that's the
end all right all right come on feel I
feel I'm so I'm so
[Music]
mad not yet not yet not yet not yet not
yet not yet okay okay feel your
anger it's the Ping it's the Ping the
ping yeah it's definitely the Ping
don't don't don't use the Ping as your
excuse just cuz you suck it's the Ping
it's the Ping going to join every single
game so why don't you join this one yeah
why AR this one because I can
acknowledge that I suck you should join
this
game you don't want me no you guys good
[Music]
luck we put down
Focus okay
strateg switch now and go for the blue
one on the left you will win no
[Music]
[Applause]
get no get the gold one hold on hold on
hold on get the gold
one wait wait hold on hold on I'm going
[Music]
okay okay I'm imagining Cece's face I'm
imagining it if I can imagine ce's
face right in the mou right in the
[Applause]
mouth the point the
[Music]
MVP let's
go come
on in the
mou play like always does yeah she she
is it's a
surprise and steady SL and steady wins
the race
yes
the I'm going to get him
[Music]
one yeah they're stream
sniping yeah stream snip stream snip
they do that no I would never cope yeah
I never once
C go
[Music]
family think about your
Che to
them about the ping I have to
accommodate for the ping you you become
the ping when you become the ping you
can hit it okay everyone become one no
you're going to miss you're going to
miss you're going to miss you're going
to miss you're going to miss you're
going to miss I'm going I want to make
it save us from our suffering pretty
well yeah those who I usually B are
really
good
no just one go
Wow Let's
[Music]
Go a in the mouth that is three points
no now why would I want to do that I
want to feed him why do I want to hit
the blue jailbird when I can hit the
gold jailbird yeah can
you there you
go that was good yeah that was yes yes
yes yeah nice one
incredible all right I'm eating I have a
noodle on
wait your game Legacy to it's
the one point for Kaku was that that
that was that was me that was me foro
that's the best she can do right now
he
gor only gold gold or nothing I have to
wait for my hand to line up I the line
my hand that's not it this isn't the one
all right but maybe this one it's not
this one either maybe the next one it
might be the no it's not this one it's
not this
one one maybe this one maybe it was
that you do
it
[Music]
got strong
gamer this this one not this one not
this one not this one not this one not
this one no this the
okay ggot we're wasting all of your
popcorn can I just eat the popcor de
ground son come on my son
get that was the Ping that was the Ping
that one was the Ping it was the Ping it
was the
Ping
miss you got this hit the gold one
become one with the gold one I'm trying
close your eyes
become close your eyes closed your eyes
I almost closed my
eyes
no I closed my eyes were you closing
your eyes with I was closing my eyes I
was closing my
eyes
no guys hurry up and r
get serious
[Music]
everyone that popcorn out that jail guys
come
on M go do
it hit it in the mouth hit it in the
mouth all right bi you you got
[Laughter]
this it's up to me to hit it in the
mouth
all right you can you're ceding I'm you
can't do
it oh my
God the good
one I'm going to do it I'm going to hit
it yeah I believe you can do it
[Applause]
Miss all right you feel it you feel the
gold one going up and down you feel it
you got this I I I feel it in my soul
yes you feel it the mouth the
mouth okay okay G I'm trying
gold I am gold I in my soul I'm golden
League of Legends so I too can hit
this why did you say
that it's not it's not this one it's not
this one I'm going to I'm going to hit
the skill shot no
go end our suffering all you have to do
is h a blue jailbird in the mouth and
you will win the game all I have to do
no hit the gold one hit the gold why
would you not why would you not hit the
gold one the gold one yeah the gold in
the mouth don't you want to be cool yeah
don't you want to get the cool
[Music]
point no you're not cool yet be
cool Style Style Style play style coin
style
Point
miss me too all
[Applause]
right that was very strong M they're
catching up do it
again okay okay okay okay Powers my
grand powers
they're
adting that going win no
pressure in the mou pressure in the
mouth You' been training all your life
for this to hit the g in the mouth in
the mouth now R in the mouth not this
not this not this not this one not this
one not this not right in the
mouth bring it home Dy all right I've
been working all my life to hit this
jailbird in the
mouth have we fed any of them they're
still
hungry it's
okay good
job okay
in the mouth in the mouth in the mouth
the in the mouth theth okay not this one
not this one not this
one uh the so cooked
man so
close Okay GG I'm channeling it I'm
channeling it this isn't the one
channeling channeling my gramlin
Imaging good though good time this is it
you win it you win it okay you win it
get the gold get the gold get the gold
go for go in the mouth in the mouth in
the
mouth
anyone my heart my
heart my heart says not yet my heart
says not yet my heart says not yet my
heart your heart my heart says not yet I
need it to go up go
up feel it with
wait wait wait this is it can you time
yourself better bird fly down
[Music]
hello her heart it was your heart still
winable still
wable count
[Applause]
and no one got to
eat you have a pillow hungry so who
would you like to throw it at LED now oh
who wants to get obliterated you get to
pick whoever you want to hit most who
made you the angriest during that game
crony why what did I do all
right by by G I mean okay it was League
to be fair I'm on your side I know I
have no regrets if it's Le hit me hit
me hard oh
that's
know hard it was that was really some
truth in that it's deep down those are
some yeah wow Gigi I I expected better
from you honestly I fell I fell down my
bad I get it oh well I us all my Pop
Eyes on you next time that took a bit
longer than expected so we're going to
go straight into uh group a playing the
next game which is going to be spin the
bottle for the rest of you Group B and
Group C I have a special surprise for
you popcorn welcome to baby jail
yay now can we here what the heck was
that if you want to take a nap you can
uh but in the meantime you will be being
kept in
here you are relying you're relying on
the jail Birds who will be keeping you
alive if they aren't active enough in
chat you will
die terrifying what can't
I I thought you said no going to
die group a walk out like these arey
uh I should I should explain how this
works I get to start so I'll just do an
example this is going to be Truth or
Dare um so we can go ahead and start the
timer we have 10 minutes okay so I'm
going to go ahead and spin are we going
to be kissing I hope
so wait I need to I need to respin it it
landed on
me don't you want to ask yourself a
question f f truth or dare um um um um
dare I dare you to be my
girlfriend okay honey honey you have to
yeah okay as my girlfriend you have to
call me honey for the rest of the stream
okay honey heck yeah okay now it's your
turn to spin the
bottle okay I hope it lands on my on my
honey I dare you to break up with me
g g m dare dare dare dare dare dare dare
dare dare dare um dare dare
dare I dare you to give us a kiss okay
everyone all that's for Nissa for f for
Liz you more tender
[Music]
oh my
[Laughter]
god well do I spin the bottle yeah spin
the
bottle
awkward what do you
me okay there truth dare a truth damn
it
um um um I I didn't prepare any truths
here what what's
the what's the um worst thing you did in
the past uh in your
childhood um what do you mean the worst
thing I did what's the naughtiest thing
you did did you steal anything did you
no but you know what I did do me and my
sister Mala were jumping on the bed and
she pissed me off so I bit her until I
broke skin and then my parents wash my
mouth out with soap oh that makes sense
yeah yeah yeah it's salid I deserved it
uh okay I'm
spinning this is so fun yeah
Co truth or
dare dare I guess uh you know I didn't
think of anything in advance for this I
really should have uh I dare you
uh to recite a a love Soliloquy to me
right
now uh a
[Music]
love uh what life through yonder window
breaks it is a beautiful Ang devil demon
with the voice of an
Angel who is beautiful and uh she has
lovely hair and you are lovely person
happy birthday happy birthday
thank
you it's so beautiful
jealous it's my girlfriend you're
talking
about honey I was dead all right it's
it's your turn Liz oh yes okay let's
go spin that bottle I'm spin spin spin
spin me this feels rigged uh dare I dare
you to dump for
yes Y no no I won't I will take the
punishment I will take the punishment I
will not do that all
right well it was nice knowing you
guys I have to draw on my own face
oh this is silly I I feel like I'd like
these big eyebrows I really like
rocki eyebrows are a mustache she look
so Ang the mustach IDE you know I I want
I want vampire teeth not a mustach of
course you do of course you want vampire
for your girlfriend of course I got I
got to have something for me is this a
punishment or a reward for you h a
punishment for
me yeah Nom Nom I'm going to come get
you okay
spinning
huh your girlfriend so lucky
uh FAA I dare you to dare fuaa to do
something oh my
God fuaa I dare you to pinch
mococo oh that sound like it h
so
bad you did this don't feel bad don't
feel bad part of the Dare with love it's
okay VI you know it's going to be a bit
pink for a little while you know that's
the
love pink for a
while yeah sorry for breaking the rules
this means fua gets a spin I'm sorry fa
oh that's okay okay okay my first time
spinning the bottle ever okay fluffy
fingers spin
is when I say Truth or Dare truth this
time okay oh
truth ohun you say truth no truth no you
you you tell her a
truth what you want to know the truth to
this is my first time I'm not used to
this kind of parties
um tell me the truth about the anime
that you hate the
most it's very controversial because
it's a really
well-rated
isi or from the new world and I I hate
[Laughter]
Squealer Reas wait what why he's it's
just his whole
deal rails the
whole M you're in the cage stay in the
cage stay in the cage
Wan you
again I think it's really sweet that
your first time playing spin the Bott is
with us for
WAOW yeah you spin
me honey honey I'll do
truth truth um what's your most
embarrassing anime guilty
pleasure oh that's a peach
girl oh I love that anime too I love
Peach girl but every time I tell someone
I like Peach Girl and they know what it
is they're like oh you've got bad taste
huh
good yeah I like beach girl they say
that I don't know people I like this
wasn't embarrassing enough give us
another yeah I another oh no I don't uh
toxic yahi I I liked a toxic yahi Once
Upon a Time like which yeah which one
toxic
y name it name it the one with the cat
booy no no we didn't have a catboy
what is Loveless what um if you don't
know Loveless I feel like your answer is
not going to be embarrassing wa wait why
can't IUN Junjo Romantica Junjo
Romantica okay anyway spin spinning
spinning spinning we're not talking
about this
anymore okay GG Truth or
Dare
Truth uh I truth you to drink in entire
water bottle right now what if I don't
have one can I drink my cup of water
that's in front of me and maybe this
chug chug chug chug chug
chug
think did you hear that yeah good
y okay we got
one that's okay G spin the
bottle wow is going to be
okay a okay I wanted to give this I
wanted to give this this one to fuaa but
it's yours now since the last one you
can tell me to dare fuaa to do the thing
that you want I dare you to tell fuaa to
do this uh okay wait wait wait wait wait
okay a
fuaa uh what the heck is this
um I I need you to do wolf girl hops
until you run out
ofy oh you run out of
energy what was that I the video in the
chat there's a video you need to do wolf
I need you to get up and do wolf girl
hops until you run out of
energy WF wolf girl hops they're Link in
the in the party chat you got to look at
the
video my best to do the
W okay good
luck I think she's
dying
oh it's not good enough
I we're moving on we we're we're out of
time so group a good job it's time for
Group B to have a
turn oh we're still alive yeah no not
for long jailbirds better get
typing
no be in
[Music]
here one never said the
D
what all right hi this is Group B oh
yeah mo mo welcome you're back
again or FAA you're back again oh my God
I can't tell you guys aart it's
over okay I'll I'll spin the bottle to
to say who goes first cuz I
yeah okay fuaa you spin and go first I
won't make you do anything I'll just
give you first
go there we go
no
no I Dare
You touch's
[Music]
tail come here come here no no no no no
you can't ly you can't ly you can't you
can't you
can't no no no really really you really
really really can't you no no no no no
no no no no no this is my tail my
tail
my
my pajamas you can't you can't grab
anything out of my pajamas okay don't
don't
noan if moch Chan's denying it then
mochan it sounds like you're in for a
punishment no all right time to get her
face drawn on since you will not let her
tail be
touched all right let's drw on moch
Chan's face I was good I was good at the
the the game with the popcorn what you
it's too late it's too late why do I
have lots of bubbles you have I'm
drawing a pondering
oh on I can't count I can't
count wait maybe you can count 6 eight
these are some really nice circles my
goodness thank you thank there you go a
Ponda monacle yeah Ponda
monacle okay now get your
[Music]
spinning
oh dude do you need some help oh do I
something El wait I try again oh
yes spin one more
time hey hey what I do to myself uh you
can just spin again again you don't have
to do to yourself I'm
going yeah I SP
again or
Truth uh oh man oh I'm so
indecisive oh
no uh um uh uh there thereare you
thereare okay okay um
[Music]
try try to touch your nose with your
tongue
oh you know I can't do you don't have to
try she said
try how far can you
go oh I look so stupid
no you're so
cute no definitely not right
now no it's not working I can't I can't
this is
rigged okay since you can't do it you na
only said try but uh everyone in group b
do we think that we should give crony
the the face drawing on
punishment wait what if I pull my tongue
like no no no that doesn't count
sleep sleep over party
Ru I just want to sleep well I'm drying
on your face now I'm going to make you
really
cute you know it's hard to improve upon
Perfection
so you're glaming me up yeah you want me
to sleep in my mascara more eyelashes
more eyelashes want
eyelashes look at look at your eyelashes
are so go so
he looking a little death
metal oh my
God look at you
clown
clown spin spin the bottle it's your
turn to torture
someone
[Music]
spin okay Truth or
Dare uh
Tru
truth truth I didn't expect to get this
far I was thinking dare truth
truth 12 the truth
is do
you do
I truth truth do you
think pineapple on pizza is
good I don't like
pizza okay I think that deserves a
punishment I have the
pineapple no that that's unacceptable
fuaa don't the pizza keep the
pineapple you need to match your sister
you don't eat pizza you don't like pizza
no pizza just a pineapple please yeah no
what the hell con but you can eat the
pizza what sharing Shing yeah no
no you you will be you will be punished
for your you okay
iow it's over for
you my face
okay
pepperoni peoni
croni
peoni it's a moi donut that's
donut yeah you guys
[Music]
are yeah then it's okay
right
okay is it going to be who is it
[Music]
there
oh you don't have anything cuz you can
just ask me anything anytime
anyways I dare you you
uh make this the best birthday ever for
NOA
[Music]
H am I not already doing that get out
your Tomy what Tomy touch no no no no I
saw oh to give her another ticket hot
her birthday get hot it's not how it
works bird well I'm still waiting for my
present from you what do you mean this
this my birthday is the time Telly time
I not a present enough to you every day
you are but you know I expected
something a little more special spin the
bottle
motan
M no there's still the whole birthday
left to make it the best birthday ever
[Music]
spin again did I did I disappoint you
war with my no no spin again spin again
okay sometimes you know it's a game of
chance sometimes that just
happens what the
heck the Twin power the
twin truth truth I don't need a truth
from you I know you're getting a dare
you're getting a dare yes I like this
okay dare is you have to say this okay
is I love love love my baby darling best
poy dog dog M she is the sexiest ever to
exist I will hug and cuddle her until
she falls asleep b
b that's embarrassing M why would you
make me do this huh this is not okay m
get it over with unless you want to be
punished I don't want punishment so uh
uh
I I love love my
baby thanks I want to exist I will hug
you C heart to you he falls asleep
ba mochan does that
suffice I wanted somebody else to say
it you
got that
no I would rather CR by say it it's okay
thoughe no no time is up actually I'm
giving crony a pillow throw for being a
good
sport thank you
okay I'm so happy cuz I look like a
freaking I don't know I look like I'm in
a midle band anyway you look
beautiful uh I'm going to who who would
be good who would anyone
anyone yeah you you you told me to yeah
me tongue with a nose yes you you come
here goodbye da you get crony's wrath I
love
it it was nice knowing you oh my God I
didn't I don't want to go that hard
wow are you are you okay pretty kitty I
kill her
I Al Al well it's time to transition
it's group C's turn to go
[Music]
so turn to spin the
bottle back to the cage back to the cage
indeed hello okay I'm going to spin to
decide who gets to go first
okay wow spin the
bottle all right that means I get a spin
yep okay okay
[Music]
okay oh no oh no TR or dead oh crap I'm
dare dare I want to DARE I'll do it yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah do the wor no it's just
there's so many good dares I just don't
know what to do I dare you
[Music]
to
h
Huh do
it go to your fridge grab the spiciest
condiment that you have and take a
spoonful
what what she made myself spicy in a
fridge
okay be I was pretty clean run fast run
fast I'm timing
you be right back be right
back so you please someone take a turn
while I'm doing I'm going I'm going okay
okay uh I'm I'm going to spin it and
we're just going to go from
there oh God uh I'm going to spin it
again okay Iris truth or
dare dare
uh I dare you to uh say something nice
to uh
Bae the nicest thing you can conure up I
mean I'm waiting FL flirt with her rise
her
up can I
um can I can I get that that can I can I
can can I can I possibly say no to this
uh yes but you're getting your face
drawn on all right Iris are you
[Music]
ready doesn't want to say it in public I
hear it every day it's fine don't worry
about it c c c c c I like funny eyebrows
for you oh did I just super quickly what
oh it's your eyebrows you got squiggly
little little eyebrows yeah they're
white right Iris there's no need to
worry about being Advanced age those
great hair happen to everyone yeah
everybody everybody gets the beauty of
life oh what is that do I have is that
like a shiny nose or something yeah it's
a nose oh my God even your nose has a
you know it's nothing to be
self what did we get what do we find I I
found a bulog packet like oh my God the
sauce the Bulldog sauce packet I found
one bful let's go all right I don't have
a spoon so I'm just going to suck it out
of the
[Music]
pack go go go
go how is
it did you just turn into what wait
[Laughter]
doing to the
baby are you okay you know that young
children actually can handle spices
level way you know younger than you
think they have a pretty Advanced
palette you're calling her a baby yeah I
think we need to punish Bae for that
that was really
mean it's not SE it's not the spice it's
just actually really gross to eat sauce
straight out of
P it's making it's making me it's making
me gag it's not really that spicy I'm
just gagging from the the texture of
dying
babe come on that was the that was the
most day like day we've had so far are
we drawing on Ba's face yes we are
you're going to draw a mustache on her
like a full-on a mustache and a beard on
her uh I'm not sure I'm not sure but
let's do it that was so
mean she's
fine oh
y my hands have have blood on me though
because my hands all orang out oh no
don't touch your eyeballs yeah don't
touch your eyeballs nobody dare me to
touch my eyeballs
please we won't don't worry we hold back
this once don't worry
yeah I mean I kind of suit spay actually
I like it yeah
yeah
to I get to spin you you get to spit oh
where's where's her face
drying she
became just Shadows it's okay we're
going to keep going uh beu just uh just
spin it'll it'll show up eventually I'm
sure all right spicy mouth
oh I feel it like going down hey not
myself I feel it I Feel the Fire slowly
burning through my
system
i y I dare you wait or wa I haven't
choosen
yet um dare okay I dare you to do your
most embarrassing love confession to me
give me a love confession embarrassing
yeah okay
give it the most cheesiest corniest love
confession you've ever done one you did
like two weeks ago two weeks ago I don't
remember what you're talking about what
um yeah cuz it's embarrassing you know
I'm ready okay okay um dear koseki beu
you are the most shining beautiful um
polished rock ever in the world that
shines and games like an absolute Pro
and um and would not be anything like
scum or you know um she said scum yes
and and she's and she can definitely
wield a katana I can just imagine her
with with the most shiniest um um
sharpest Katana that could absolutely
murder anyone in this roomie she ever
wanted to if she ever wanted to but
she's just too kind to ever want to
actually murder someone but she has the
power to and I am just so absolutely
smitten with the fact that she has so
much power and but she still wants
actually more power
that's the thing she always says more
power and that's just like absolutely
like you know that's like the TR
want okay that's good that's keep going
keep going keep going about
my I feel like I should get punished for
this why what it's not embarrassing I'm
a compliment my it's pretty embarrassing
it's pretty embarrassing okay not for IR
body yeah what Doan what not for me then
um you have the flattest
chest well and that is amazing cuz all
can I get punished for this I feel like
that was a punishment I feel like can I
can
I can my face reflect the punishment
that I just God please thank you okay
punishment
time okay she gets punished for having a
flat chest what
[Music]
yeah St
a love
conf that's a
line and I grew a mustache too she
mustach that's how made her feel she got
she got she got her second one sorry I'm
slow oh wow my stomach really Burns what
did he do to
me okay I okay I I will spin the bottle
spin oh wait I have to press something
right oh uh I here I can I'll do it for
you I'll do it for you oh
than oh my gosh CE in the corner it's
okay I'm eating
popcorn hello babe what would you like
Truth or
Dare give me your worst dare dare okay I
have one that's perfect for you um since
we can't actually show your body
movements um I i' like you to express
yourself dancing something for the next
20 seconds with
words dance for us with words with words
explain your dance movements that for
for 20 seconds Dance and yeah explain
what you're doing explain with explain
what I'm doing okay you put the arms out
to the side and then you do the wave one
one side to the right side to the left
and then all we go back again and then
oh you go down you you you do the you do
the you do the butt pop the butt pop we
do thek something that you know how to
do and you asked me how to do the other
day but that's fine and then put the
arms around the head we go around we go
around we go around do the whack back
and then we do the side kick and then we
do the the hips roll the
isolation it's been 20 seconds all right
thank you oh my God okay well uh SE yeah
yeah spin spin that was that was great
Bee thank you thank you thank
you oh was it my turn oh
sorry please land on
CeCe or
dare dare
mhm
um I want you to
go
onto um your fan art
tag and the wait okay depend use your
judgment go to your fan art tag the
first art that you see I want you to
quote retweet and uh write uh a
paragraph praising the art uh until you
run out of
words the first one I see what is the
first one you see I mean it's a nice fan
art do you what about the spiciest one
you see oh the spiciest one you see oh
that's good yeah the spiciest one you
see oh my God spiciest one that you
see oh I think I see SP no do
I it's not the chest size is not
accurate I bet
not in accuracy do you want a Batu game
instead then I guess it's a Batu for you
okay it's a Batu I'll theu
Batu draw her face say goodbye to your
beautiful face CeCe it's okay I would I
would have but it was I can't if it's
not accurate I can't guys I'm sorry you
hear that if you want to do spicy I got
to be accurate yeah be accurate I can't
I can't make those wishes come true it's
just not reality okay guys you have to
wake up wake up oh she bleed
Pinocchio little
puppet one for your little gu oh even
not God
one too bad and that's all wow all of us
all of us ended with our faces getting
ground uh Vu for your exemplary example
uh I'm going to go ahead and give you a
pillow throw cuz that that was I would I
wouldn't have done that so that was
amazing so uh who would you like to
throw get that rat in the face get that
baby in the V cars you B get it was
content baby content come on it wasn't
that
bad that bad throw her just
[Applause]
exagger good oh wow wow I mean I did
knock her off pretty far and that's
pretty good for my my noodle arms you
know so yeah yeah pretty good you at
that spicy sauce it probably you know um
weakened your throat a little bit yeah
yeah yeah you were Nerf but that was
still really good two t the jail Bird
yeah wow thanks jail bird H all right
well very good good very good uh welcome
back to baby jail how are you guys doing
still alive in there
[Music]
help uh oh God
scary we're going to be transitioning to
our next game now thank you all for
being great sport next game is going to
be who am I with uh we're going to go
ahead and go with uh group number a a a
group letter
A so please please uh come out of baby
jail and let's let's
prepare fight and I'll expl I'll explain
the rules once we're there thank God
welcome back to baby jail you
guys all right let us out okay so uh as
I mentioned there's little chats that
you guys have it's going to have a name
over everyone else's head do not read
them aloud obviously um we are going to
be guessing Who We Are okay so I'll go
first it's going to be like kind of 20
questions is um so for example I'm going
to open with the question am I a member
of hollow
en and you guys have to tell
me is that is that your first question
yeah yeah that's my first
question yes okay okay um do I have long
hair no no no no
um uh do do I have am I pet on
no oh okay so I I don't have long hair
and I have big boobs okay um and I'm I
am Hollow Ian right yes yes um am I Oro
crony no
oh you two wrong guesses uh and on your
second wrong guess you get a batsu game
and but you can keep guessing until you
get it uh okay so uh okay um oh no I'm
struggling I'm already struggling oh God
uh you have 17 more questions am I tall
am I
tall um Define really Define tall not
really compared to really hey wait I
have short hair compar missing I'm I'm
medium height and I'm not Pon so I have
big
boobs
yes yeah yeah am I green no no um am I
known one am I am I known for
singing no not yet not
yet okay oh oh no I'm really bad at this
I'm oh God uh
uh and am I red no
no how many I'm not counting the
question it's funny cuz it's pretty
obvious I feel like I'm struggling she's
calling you bad you're almost there
calling
me
um um I can't keep all of this
information in my head am I
[Music]
purple
Nolla my w yay okay you are her I am she
okay perfect uh great well uh who wants
to go next in this group this little
rank tag team we have going I do okay
okay um I part
of whole L English yes yes yeah I I'm F
full English but I'm not um
um am I good or
bad you're so bad you're good you're
good really good bad good you're a baddy
H okay okay uh I'm going to make my
first guess I call so by no no no I
thought it was for sure you know being a
wrapping Reaper and
everything
a
[Music]
um uh what a good question am I
short no no okay so I'm tall okay
[Music]
um is is the other person in the room
right
now M that's that's going to we're going
to make that an illegal question you
can't ask that I can't ask jail not just
got out of there
again go back to the baby jail I have my
second guest Okay and like 40 sub by no
no what punishment punishment well we'll
do the punishment at the end of the
round
okay all right fuaa continue guessing
I'm
[Music]
tall I'm tall
and kind of bad
[Laughter]
very
bad H do I have
shoes yes
yes tall I have shoes and I'm kind of
bad yes darl uh what kind of shoes do I
have are these yes or no question
questions
chill do I have running
shoes no
no does anyone have running shoes does
anyone do has running
shoes and
I'm okay I'm going to guess okay am I
IIs so by no
no of English
ask better
questions you can't believe
me okay I'm tall and I'm kind of bad and
I have not running
shoes and uh what the
other I mean you have running them I
have run
them yeah does anyone here want to give
huahua a free hint since she's
struggling no
darling yeah struggle more uh um am I am
I animal likee
no yes so sort of why why did you say it
like that yes huh according to the lore
that I have learned
half yeah you're half an
animal her mother was an
animal mother was an animal her mother
was an animal
oh are we are we sure yeah positive mean
the father is an animal don't worry just
just just keep asking questions it's
okay am I the wha
[Music]
yes my mom is a raven so you w the room
H
yeah animal yeah I'm half Raven half
Raven your dad did it with a bird no he
turned her into a demon
oh
Rena happy
birthday okay uh let's go uh G
Gin Gin m i e
n yes
yes am I Orange what no if you get it on
the first guess you get a pillow throw
oh there's incentive that's crazy well
I'm I'm pass my first guess am I pink no
no am I purple yes
yes isn't it kind of easy
no but if I want to get on the without
messing up
I don't think we answered her first
question
correctly did um uh
do do am I Ena
Senpai
yes
yay you did it
yippe the
rainbow the rainbow you're so good that
was your first guest so looks like G do
you want to do your we'll do the pillow
throws at the end okay okay
B okay am I allowed to look at a
list yeah yeah yeah of okay it's like
guess who yeah yeah yeah guess who okay
am I part of hollow live English yes yes
yes
oh am I
short
yes yes I mean
am I am I shorter than
CM I don't know centimet I don't know C
no I'm taller than
155 yes
okay do I have a twin
sister
yeah that's
illegal well it's am I blue
[Laughter]
am I full
y it was the confidence that you
answered are they above 155 C when
everyone else was confused I feel like
for that twin question we're going to
have to draw on your face wait what I
see you'll still get a pillow throw
don't worry you'll still get a pillow
throw but we're going to draw on your
it's a valid question we're drawing yay
face drawing
time oh go
easy not a
unes yeah
yeah nice one got I got to give her
teeth too oh now your mouth looks like a
nose oh you made my mouth a no
[Laughter]
yeah there we go H to say
it
perfect all right Liz you're up yeah
okay am I in h live English no no no am
I in Hall Live
ID no
no am I inoss
no
no okay um well there's only one left
there's only one left now no I I know
that I don't need to ask it no you
should ask it too you should be sure are
you sure um uh am I in uh Hol Hol live
Japan yes
yes oh my God good luck yeah you weren't
sure am I
po amol no
no all right am I a
demon no
no am I
human yeah think so yeah I'm pretty sure
yeah you think
so think oh wait am I a robot no no no
hm
what could you think is kind of
human am I witch no no no
no am
[Music]
i h do I have brown hair no no no huh
okay do I go uh uh
do I go do I say PCO PCO no
no okay am
I
H am I am I like fantasy-esque
I am um someone answer F fuaa answer it
depends on each person maybe no no
no
no everyone has a little bit of magic in
them little bit of magic human a little
bit of magic do I have
Bings not
really nrows it down okay uh uh let's
see
human no brown
hair H do I have blue hair yes yes oh am
i s say
yes oh oh no the pillow throws are too
easy we have three we have Gigi fauna
and Liz all have a pillow
throw the same and a pillow yeah and
then uh Gigi you're the only one whose
face hasn't been colored on I'm looking
for a reason to to color on your face
can you make one I tle for on to the
ground with my pillow no okay punishment
time me punishment for G help I'm
getting dragged
[Applause]
away help
me goodbye to your cuteness gig Mooney
now they're drawing on my face all
because I tackled
fuaa tackled fua like that how could I
do that you're part of
Justice ah a oh you look so cute cute my
large nose big no and my whiskers you
look like a pig what
you oink oink oink
oink you too you also don't but I can't
think of any valid reason to punish you
so birthday I'll allow it oh okay we're
drying on her
face as it's your birthday yes thank
you I really need people to get this
second punishment you
know thanks for and my dog joined too oh
yeah yeah of course Bob's very cute so
good he looks so cute in his little
pajamies yeah because your music your
musical I'm just I'm out in John
yeah beautiful
I need these
glasses yeah they're
cool heck yeah oh I have a little goatee
okay uh let's uh do the pillow throws
really quick GG who would you like to
attack anyone it doesn't have to be on
the
field catch this
[Music]
[Applause]
sorry I Don't Know My Own Strength
goodness gracious
Gigi that was a powerful attack sorry I
didn't mean to hit you that hard okay
next up Hana who would you like to
pillow throw moving
[Laughter]
on yeah no I didn't do anything wrong
look look at
mea please please pleas
talk he's
Invincible why so strong my nerd
strength
no
okay um can I throw a pillow at you
birthday girl yes you can anybody you
like y
okay let's go oh boy it's over for me
for the blood flame
Kingdom oh oh pretty good pretty strong
that's pretty good that's pretty good
yeah yeah it's good okay and uh I I I
almost forgot but fuaa has gotten our
special punishment game what it is time
for it to be revealed that the
punishment is going to be 77 seconds
with gigg
moodin get in the
closet do does everyone hear us or is
this private everyone can hear but just
go on everyone oh go off so D you really
like League of Legends huh yeah I like
League of Legends we should play League
of Legends together not only that oh
touches your hand how about you touch
the controller or something is leue of
Legends you know games all games I love
all games games you love games except
the only game I really don't like is leg
Legends
why just keep talking don't let her
talk
leg so if you play League of Legends
they have three lanes in League of
Legends and you can go top or middle or
bottom and when I say bottom that
reminds me you know bottoms not only the
bottom they look really strong we but
you have to find them the same there's a
dog and then there's his name is
war
and chasing you down he's like oh the
Dell of blood in the heart oh is that Vu
I
smell legs
leging play leue of Legend wa wait and
then and then you can play war with cuz
you like and then and then only Warwick
he's a he's a
dog there's kma who's also a dog and he
goes and he chases down and he throws up
and he vomits everywhere and not only
that not only that um uh uh I see that
you really are you're really interested
in League of Legends maybe we should
like
get got vomited
on before I what was that noise
oh hello who's
there oh hi hello terissa and her
friends you all look so cute in your
pajamas m mom
hi do you guys have anything you want to
say to my mom I brought yall some snacks
to help you have an even happier
birthday love you
[Music]
yummy was hry your mom is cute I
mean yeah of course and there was this
thing here that I brought just for the
jail birds so make sure to show them by
you
Darlings bye
[Music]
mommy well well you guys are M on these
cookies I I might in this present box
for the jailbirds
huh will you guys help me off this this
present never guess what's inside do
they be let's see let's open it
yeah
okay
merch merch which is going to be
dropping in 14 minutes all the links
will be updated and stuff to include it
uh is that a booby pad yes that is my
boa mouse pad with art by Nardo I know
you've all been waiting for this so
please uh look forward to it so
beautiful yeah and then we have a
jailbird key ring for the back of your
phone you can go ahead and put it on we
also have a raven narissa raven coft a
onesie plushy that you can hang up take
with you anywhere it'll be pretty pretty
small so it can go with your jailbird
plushy uh in in case you wanted to carry
me with you places you know in in a
small cute form uh there will also be a
mouse pad or like a big not a not a
mouse pad what are they called a a gamer
mat one of the gamer mats with art by my
mama including the same art on the
Cy that uh will be in this set as well
so please look forward to all of it did
do any of you guys have comments on this
this merch what do you think girls it's
so cute
the mouse pad is it
soft yeah no the is it going to the
gamer wrist of course it'll support the
gamer WR is the bump going to be cuz I'm
pretty sure there's multiple sizes I
it's not I don't I don't
remember how accurate is the
feeling you'll just have to find out for
yourself oh okay exia bang tidy very
nice very nice yes there will also be
limited ones that are hand signed by me
so if you want that don't uh don't miss
out make sure you buy it right away
before it sells out so uh please buy my
birthday Burch coming out in 13
minutes get it get go go
go more League of Legends I might need a
mouse pad so you know yeah yeah who
doesn't need a mouse pad you
know the merch link is in the
description now by the way so you can
you can refresh now to get the link
ready
or bless you but it's time for Group B
to play who am I so let's get this show
on the
road no I don't want to go back into
baby jail sorry you got to go back into
baby jail keep it
going
me
please we got to go back in first
we're so tiny compared to the jailbird
in here I know a big boy he's so small
but if we take him on together we could
probably fat could probably murder him
yeah murder it yeah then we had we would
have food inside here too so oh God I
have to play
again okay uh let's start we we'll go
from right to left so we'll start with
ar yeah
hello I'm a big cat you're a big cat
sure the
question no um am I in h
English yes yes
yes okay am
[Music]
I am I very
tall no
no am am I sure
like very short super short
no
okay
[Music]
um I don't know what to um am
I do do I have do do do I have blue
eyes yes yes yeah
oh
okay uh do do I
[Music]
have do I have short
hair yes
yes
uh
okay uh I forgot
you
forgot
um uh am I am I
evil yes the evil is
no am I evil no
yeah no
[Music]
do I see
b
[Laughter]
sometimes Emma
[Music]
you that was your first guest who
congratulations
[Music]
yeah you'll get a pillow throw at the
end okay M that means it's your turn to
guess my turn Okay mhm okay here I go
okay am I in whole life English no
no am I in all live
I no
no am I in all life
DP yes yes
oh am I
pink no no no am I cute of course yes
yeah very cute am I
cool yeah sometimes
how cute and cool yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah do I have ears
no no no ears no earss does everyone
have ears wait I I figur I mean yes
yes do I have animal shaped ears
no but ears yes yes ears yes yes yes yes
sorry I forgot humans have ears it's
hard being a
[Music]
demon am I short
kind medium yeah like short
medium do I have
horns no
[Music]
no do I have long
hair no no okay no
short is short was was it shsh short ha
yeah short hair short
height yeah yeah short hair short height
short hair short height no I
ears
[Music]
no do I have
wings no no no
come on M you got
[Music]
this pillow yeah you get a pillow you
guys you guys need to stop trying to get
pillows okay I want the pillow okay oh
wellow all right it's my turn
uh am what what oh no no let's go let's
go okay okay am I Hollow live English
please say yes yes oh thank God um okay
uh am I
blue no no um am I
red no no no am I
orange yeah yes okay that really narrows
it down
uh am I a
phoenix no no am I a
gremlin am i g
mood oh yeah
g yeah I will gift my pillow to someone
later no no no no no uh anyway uh
koni heck yeah let's go let's get it
okay so am I Hol live
English yes
yes
okay am
I
um am
I a c SOI
[Music]
yes
okay am
I so
[\h__\h] who's so
gy am I
blue no no
are you
pouring no yeah what kind of noise is
that I'm thinking I'm thinking think let
her think am
I am I okay no okay not
that am
I okay so [\h__\h] okay
M okay I think I've narrowed it down
okay uhhuh uhhuh
does okay yeah uh do
I do you do I do I
have pink
eyes
yes
okay pink guys
yeah yeah okay okay do I have short
hair
[Music]
yes
yeah short enough you know enough for
you
maybe wait that only to that doesn't
make any sense am
I wait just to make sure
we we only have one guest right no you
have as many as you want okay am
I am I
GG yes yeah yeah why is it GG again I I
don't know I didn't I didn't I didn't
set my
own that would have been cheating it's
like a trick question oh okay yeah you
did it
yay okay
I have a request would you like my
pillow throw in exchange for me drawing
on your
face if you draw something cute yes of
course I'll draw something cute fingers
crossed behind my back pillow let's
go punishment punishment punishment this
is not a punishment for me yeah I'll
make you extra cute then I was waiting
for this
moment meow meow little
[Music]
kitty I'm a big cat I said little kitty
TR me I'm a big cat big cat little cat
it's all the same to me I love my
lashes I'm making her
beautiful yeah like a beautiful clown
yeah just like
you y all right are you calling me a
clown well that is without us two pillow
throws Moco one and grony
one I'm
excited pillow let's let's start with um
both ofas who do you want to kill I mean
throw a pillow at I I want to I want to
throw pillow to to the birthday lady if
possible and then who second who second
you got two second
is
uh is Iris
okay let's go what what why me cuz
you're cute
obviously oh god well give me your worst
I'll I'll be I'll be I'll be nice
okay oh that was that was okay that was
just okay yeah yeah yeah that was nice
okay it's iris's turn come here Iris
here this pillow is going to be hit hit
her hit hit her hit her get her get her
get
[Music]
her you're
evil oh my goodness
gracious well very nice okay
who uh Moko you you're next you're next
with a pillow throw I'm going to throw
at Nissa me because you can now get your
Nissa birthday wish yes there's one
right now it's live my m so I'm going to
go and uh obliterate Nissa and you go
get your birthday it's okay yeah here we
go
B
wow perfect
go go okay and then
croni well I also got to give it to the
birthday girl oh I'm I'm such a popular
Target today okay I it's the birthday
bead man it's the classic yeah the
birthday Beatdown let's go let's go
don't you guys have any enemies come
on all right hit me with
your
yeah um
thank you that was so
nice because you're number one thank
you good one you're so sweet what the
heck well you know what time it is now
it's time for Group C to play who am
I
out out we got to get them out of the
cage starved the jail I have imposter
syndrome you have impostor
cuz we're somebody else right we're
we're somebody oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah you're right you're right
smart
yeah okay uh good luck to you guys in
the cage have
[Music]
fun I'm ready I'm ready I'm ready okay
let's do this this time we'll go from
left to right so we'll start with CC and
end with B okay am I part of whole life
English no no am I part of whole life
Japan
no am I part of ready yeah yeah oh okay
okay
okay am
I am I un too easy um am I is my main
color a primary color yes yes yes yes
okay am I primary
color um is it red yes
yes okay um yeah okay am I
Undead yes
yes wow easy game what heck easy easy
what the heck
wow I was even going to ask but then I
thought no that it can't be it can't be
well there's a pillow throw for you so
congratulations o I'm ready okay okay uh
let's go to
Iris hey okay um am I whole alive
Ian no no am I whole alive JP yes yes oh
that makes it so much harder
um okay um
um
uh do I have blue
eyes no no no okay
um am I an animal no no
no okay
um am
I do I have a a big
chest yes yes yes yes
yes am I
short yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
big chest short not animal not blue eyes
I think I'm I think I'm getting it wait
but I want to just make sure okay
um am I
red yes yeah yeah am i h show money
[Applause]
good job you're so on top of it I know I
wasn't expecting to be so on top of it I
know and now it's my turn oh god oh oh
uh hi guys please go easy on me am I
Hollow
Ian no no no no am I Hollow JP no no
well no no why' you say no what I do
well am I Hollow ID no no no am I Hollow
device no no what the
f am I yo excuse me
like what did I
miss is that an official guess
yeah hey damn another pillow throw for
me that was good yeah
G yeah W
beu
okay uh well let's start am I an e
n yeah yeah yeah
okay colors is good
[Music]
uh am I
pink yes yes
oh wait how many no more questions make
a guess I'm kidding kid
what
joking
um pink actually wait there actually
quite a few pink
um do pink pink do I
WAP yes yes oh why are you hesitant
though
cuz I'm getting thrown off by the
hesitant
see uh do I but I want to look cool and
guess right without too much help but I
don't want to lose my pillow I
[Music]
want am like Callie
yes so good at this dang it I was with
the hesitancy I thought you I thought
yeah I I was like well well I was r
or can rap yeah M can rap too so like I
was like wait why did they
hesitate okay too easy too
close Okay ba now you also have to do it
first try yeah
what everyone in this group got first
try yeah am um okay am I hly JP yes
yes I gave you this battle because I
knew you could handle
it am I an
anamal no no no oh okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay do I have long
hair yeah yeah yeah yeah you do yeah
[Music]
that doesn't errow down at all
um you have two more questions B what
what you have two more questions yeah
we're counting we're counting what you
have two more questions only two more
you got to get it this please make us
proud yeah because probably just two
more questions since when are we
counting questions what yeah what like
people had more than four questions it's
okay just just keep doing what you're
doing fine fine fine you get five that's
that's the maximum I'm giving you you
get five go H I'm the one who gives out
pillows so don't
worry do I a big hair
accessory um no no
no yeah no no not big not big okay yeah
H okay
okay okay okay
okay am I
pink no no not really no okay okay okay
okay okay someone said not really okay
okay
okay okay
okay you have one more question you said
five learn how to count yeah no you
because this is that was your four that
was four questions so far right mm if
one more question yeah one
more hold
[Music]
on come on ba you got
this trying to think what okay so
longish hair not an animal you have the
cards doesn't have
accessory do I have big
Boa yeah yeah
yeah guys I think she needs a hint no I
don't need a hint no no you don't no I
need hint okay okay the hint is you got
this you got
this you got this yeah you got
this am I
blonde yes yes
yes okay blonde not pink okay okay that
okay I mean she's kind of pink pink okay
okay she's not pink
okay either her you need to answer
now what did I say long hair big booa
not pink and blonde and blonde yeah no
big hair accessory wait that could be
either of them what well ask another
question she doesn't have anymore she
already has she got six it's 20
questions it's six questions six I don't
know got six you you had six questions
and we answered within six questions so
that is your limit yes that is a rule
it's 5050 okay hold on either her I mean
she's not really I mean she has pretty
big
but I
mean okay mean she's not really she's
got some pink it okay
um am
[Music]
I I never felt more anxious in my life
am I
hot
[Applause]
y she was blonde it's like yeah it's
right there well I thought it was well
technically n is also
blondish that's true well uh well good
that that was really good I I realized
that was kind of a hard one but also
flare is also blondish yeah so true yeah
I was you SL thank
you okay pillow pillow time uh CeCe who
will you
attack I'm going to
attack I'm going
to don't suggest anything they should
make their own
choices um I would like to hit
um hey
yeah yeah let's do it she suggests evil
things she deserves it yeah yes uhhuh
uh-huh uhuh yeah yeah punish for your
actions get her CE with your atomicon
arm so weak there's no muscle it's just
all con probably
[Music]
Rusty wow it was like even oh my God was
without a fly's breath my goodness oh in
reality I just want want to give you
ammunition so that you can throw at
someone oh thank you I got charging me
up for the throw yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah nice nice nice okay Iris
you're
up um I that's not how it works but uh
who do I want to throw it
to who deserves a
throw B
[Music]
sure you sure about that you're charging
me up I I yeah charging you no that's
not you're charging up it's not work
that's not how works so yeah I will I
will use all my all my energy and my
power and my soul and my life and I will
I will yeat okay yeater yeat hard yeat
her out of oh so that was what's with
these
weak you know like I I can tell you know
she used all her power or her soul no I
just I just woke up mhm 100% y i I just
woke I mean with those noodle arms I can
believe it you did your best it's fine
yeah yeah okay Kaku your turn I feel
so I still haven't forgiven the flat
thing so let's
[Music]
go I wish I was flat I it was a
compliment
well maybe if I hit you with this pillow
it'll hit you in the chest it'll make
you
flatter okay no nice oh oh again please
make me a pancake what you're getting it
thrown at you again no IR no Iris Iris
oh
Iris sorry wait one more one more time
Iris I died once already I cannot die
again yeah don't don't
kill her kill
her go go go
go
bad not bad okay A little over to your
left and and you know cuz you got
another hit
coming oh oh very nice very
nice I to see another day my chest lives
to see another day okay uh and then last
but not least ba who would you like to
throw at oh I've being thrown so often
what is what is with this group and me
all right like everyone agrees maybe you
know come on come on baby right on the
no go go
go
yeah very nice
yeah destroyed knocked out
this with that we finished the Who Am I
game we're going to be moving back to
the main area with
everybody so shall we head on over take
everybody out of baby jail your time is
[Music]
over to be in jail good
job uh now I have a pillow throw left
who hasn't gotten to throw a pillow at
anyone I haven't I haven't thrown any
pillows and I'm the flus is there anyone
else who hasn't thrown any
pillows just just for I haven't thrown a
pillow yes you just did what do you mean
what you talk
about yeah no she
has what do you mean she has I am giving
you a free pillow throw who would you
like to attack I'm going to attack you
again I like you yet let's
go okay give me your best
Shota did a really good job before so
I'm going to do even better job here
okay
by oh
noise wow that was amazing uh that was
really good really seriously good
um well I think that was amazing it's
time to move on to the next part of our
show
um so now that we're all here together
uh we have two special girls here who
have prepared some horror stories for us
today oh yeah the horror stories I
forgot just to get us really prepped to
sleep tonight I think it's my bedtime
I all
right mood
scared I welcome you to the floor wait
wait can I go first because the tality
the tality CE Cece Cece wants to go
first what do you think is is is that
first yeah I think I want to go first
okay good for for um tonalities effect
for dramatic yeah yeah okay
wait that's not that's okay
now G I'm scared I'm scared I I didn't
actually prepare a horror story I was
just going to Y cuz I don't have a I
don't have a Horror Story your face is
plenty horrifying
alreadying this this music's kind of
upbeat for a horror this music is just
just a little upbeat
uh just just wait just wait uh we we're
we we we're having a a
moment just a moment meanwhile we can
tell another I'll tell another Horror
Story
meanwhile okay short scary story yeah
short there you are oh
guys
scary
okay SC me your story terrifying the
scary story thank you the scary story I
will be sharing with you all tonight is
based off of a true story and oh no
that's the worst one wait is it one of
those stories that you say it's based
off a true story is scary but it's not
actually story no this one is actually
based off of a truth story and it's it's
it's particularly horror fied H for
narissa and for everyone else
here okay is it a
experience I'm sitting down yes sit down
and um hold each other's hands guys
because this is really terrifying okay
okay holding
hand it's Saturday morning the sh sun
shines through your blinds and you
slowly shut up open your eyes feeling
slightly disoriented and like usually
you actually woke up on your own your
alarm didn't even need to ring for you I
feel kind of sweaty and clamy I wonder
why that is something strange you feel
off balance but maybe you just had a bad
dream you're sure it's nothing after all
you can't even remember it so you decide
to go get up instead of staying in bed
and scrolling on your phone as you
usually would and go into the kitchen to
prepare your morning drink and get some
breakfast you open the fridge
and you have no food
this is odd because you precisely
remember buying some milk and eggs H
where are they where are they thinking
about eggs and milk you might
immediately want us to pancakes M soft
fluffy fluffy slightly warm and
deliciously moist M toed with your
favorite topping which
is not
Nutella blueberries and Nutella one of
the most delicious things in the world
your stomach grumbles and you take this
as a sign to do something you usually
wouldn't to go outside go outside and
then to IHOP for some
paks nice Uber oh my goodness yeah she's
very brave today it's incredible she's
touching
[Music]
grass Nissa would never wow she said it
was a different day she just felt
something was different you know you
have tly get ready in order to be on
your way as fast as possible your tummy
grumbling more and more after short work
walk you are finally arrive ihob pancake
Paradise something's off you're about to
enter ready to be hit by the smell of
extreme sweet slogan what what I didn't
want to Google it what's the slogan
International House of Pancakes oh oh
International House of Pancakes that's
what the door oh go sorry and then you
try to pull the fight the push sign
that's kind of embarrassing but nothing
[Music]
happens looking around
frantically your eyes find a closed sign
closed closed but why would it be closed
you're hungry why is this happening to
you why you guess there's nothing to be
done so you go to a local kiosk and buy
some bread instead stale bread and you
plan on making bread a quick breakfast
sandwich once home deject it you make
your way back still thinking about
pancakes H what's she going to do next
later that day you conclude you need
something to lift your spirits after all
you finally went outside to treat
yourself and you didn't even get what
you went went out for what's the point
okay it's time for a different meal then
guys what are you craving what should
nous again French Toast French toast
cheeky chicken chicken and french toast
okay chicken and French cravings it is
Chicken and Waffles chicken and french
toast and Waffles it
is um you call your local chicken and
french toast and Waffles place for some
um the phone rings and rings and
Rings no one's picking up what is going
on you keep trying you try a different
place no one's picking up another one no
what's picking up it keeps going all day
you finally decide this has to stop now
it can't be happening so you take the
matters into your own hand narissa and
what do you do you grab your car don't
know yes yeah I drive I drive yeah and
you go to
Caz I'm on my way you think to yourself
oh my God oh my God that's her other
Horror Story you don't know what cver
is cuz I love Nora oh my god do you even
like watch my content like
no that yes yes K is a fast food chain
that narissa loves yeah K wouldn't
betray you all these fast food places
and none of them are reachable but you
can always rely on cul it's been with
you for so long picking you up on a
rough day fond memories with your family
and friends spent there and your
favorite fast food place of all time
culs we finally get there the parking
lot it's empty oh God the lights don't
seem to be on God no I'm scared this
can't be no not covers but how why you
could always rely on this place Nissa
this is where you were able to treat
yourself and distract yourself oh no
this is impossible you feel sick you
need to distract yourself somehow get
your mind off of this you sure there
some explanation and you'll figure it
out and tomorrow everything will be all
right everything will be normal again
but right now you can't really think
about Solutions you need to get your
mind off of the whole thing so you do
something you won't usually do and turn
on the radio you don't even feel like
radio you don't even feel like you have
the energy to take out your phone and
pick up music so this will'll have to do
slowly you lean forward and rest your
forehead on the cold steering wheel
which feels kind of soft kind of like
the mouse pad that you should definitely
buy right now from
wow the whole life shop oh it's so nice
and nice and Cooling and
flush the radio crackles and a lady
whose voice you vaguely recognize
announces some news in a professional
tone you usually don't listen to the
news but right now you're too exhausted
to change this channel and she
says after much uproar and to the dismay
of many citizens today on November 21st
regulation 21 finally became became
active due to the highest worldwide
cooking illiteracy of all time the
government decreed a new regulation with
which allows no more fast food no more
takeout in the entire country businesses
are being shut down effective
today uproar happening as we speak stay
inside stay safe and most importantly
learn how to cook and with that there's
no more no more CS no more take out no
more
food more easy food to get and you will
have to cook
[Applause]
forever let her
cook wow well were you terrifying Nissa
yeah that was really
scary are you crying
yeah oh someone someone pull her hand or
something happy birthday with you would
you hor she is subjected to cooking hell
the rest of her life no it's all right
it's all right we we we we'll shout
we'll shout you
covers after after the make make your
own
cover home okay you can do like a coffee
cat
recipe look for me okay if
you what no source
we
can't we can't eat jailbirds they're not
tasty would you put jail on a kis
Burger huh why do we feed them if not
the
Harvest yeah what's the point they eat
garbage and so do chickens probably I
don't know no no chickens do not eat
garbage it's because they're Ravens
they're carrying Birds they eat dead
things and garbage oh oh yeah they don't
taste great you should only eat Ravens
in Extreme Survival situations where
there's no other food
available
SAU extreme yeah yeah just put hot sauce
on it there you go taste deep fried hot
sauce I I I think it's time for our next
scary story
from my
God I'm so I'm I'm so scared now I know
I'm so scared and now are you going to
fr us even more GG
no I hope so G please I don't I don't
know I don't know I'm to scare you guys
it's okay we all
together I when when AA told me to make
a scary story I I couldn't I couldn't
think of one but I there's like
something that's been going on and I I
don't know I thought telling it at um a
slumber party with so many beautiful
women as I like trauma jump to them and
cry would probably be like the best
place to tell it cuz then you can
comfort
me thank you anyways it all starts my
league or
something no it's not about League of
Legends oh thank God cuz I was about to
leave the the trauma dump you can't it's
locked you okay that's the beginning of
an actual Horror Story all right
all right go on DD okay um I'm I'm
probably some background information do
you guys know about the The Wailing
woman what wailing no The Wailing woman
you guys don't know what the Wailing
woman
is cult sorry I don't have many
opportunities to say something like that
please let me have this one thank you
continue well I think there's like this
popular story of like La Yona who she
she's like this this lady who roams near
the water to like mourn and cry over the
children that she
drowned thereal a lot of um variations
in the storytelling but I think the the
gist of it is that she killed her kids
from like either an Unfaithful husband
or she just had like a fit of Madness
but she regrets it deeply when she
realizes what she's done and and she
cries for them and and I I don't know
how much I believe in the story because
you know it's like a folk tale to wor
children away from the
water but you know it is it is it what
fol Tales are to like scare young
children into behaving and then have
their like overactive imagination run
wild and they're like I'm not going to
go near the water because she's going to
come out and kill
me yeah yeah yeah I know I know uhhuh
I don't know if if I was I don't know a
child right now and someone told me that
like if Liz told me that that a creepy
spooky woman would come out and kill me
I I think I would believe her I'd run
straight into the water why why Pretty
Woman going to drown me that's kind of
you don't want to
die I well maybe I could you know raise
her up and then yeah wow yeah maybe I
could like heal her trauma yeah we can
fix her yeah exactly free woman we can
fix
[Music]
her maybe maybe that's the best course
of action is she pretty I don't know
I've never seen her yeah I'm running
straight
in I don't know there there's like
things happening
lately that that's been kind of scaring
me I I'll be honest I haven't shared
this with anyone in Justice cuz I I
thought I was going crazy but I'm I'm
sharing now because I'm surrounded by so
many beautiful women to come for me and
and I it's it's going to sound a little
crazy which is why I didn't tell justice
but since huh I'm here we we might as
well so I'm stalling I'm scar this is
thefe space I'm not judging you yet I'm
really judging you right now so please
please I I'm I'm I'm a little scared of
of saying it because what if I say it
and it becomes real you know like when
you manifest something so hard that it
happens and like what if I share it and
then it actually happens and then I die
prot protect you it's a safe space it is
it is it I've got the smudge
sticks are you there are you
here
yeah wait are you talking to the ghost
or I feel I feel safe Happ oh okay
here's my trauma dumping know I don't
have I don't want to summon
it okay the the past few months ever
since justice has um infiltrated H alive
infiltrated I don't know we're allowed
to say that are we to say that
infiltrated nothing nothing nothing move
on move on scary
scary keep going keep going
ever since our debut I've been having
some trouble sleeping and it um I
thought it was like you know the
adrenaline and the anxiety from all the
things that were happening and it would
take me a really long time to fall
asleep and I'd be like laying there just
trying to do whatever but it I I just it
just felt like plastic insomnia you know
but after a couple weeks of really
struggling to fall asleep I I started I
started hearing some
[Music]
noises who's turning off the
light I don't know ghost that wasn't
you keep going keep going um I I thought
it was Liz at first cuz you know she
does a lot of Koke streams so I thought
she was the one making the noise cuz it
was just really faint and counted bless
you oh bless you bless
you yeah it thought it sounded a little
bit like humming and then it was also
kind of comforting and I started to like
look forward to
it because it it helped me fall
asleep but I don't know I think
recently the noise started
to to change it it it I don't know when
it really started to happen happened
it's hard to pinpoint when it happened
but like that humming noise started to
turn it I I don't
know I don't know how to describe it
because it sounds really
crazy it's it's a very vulnerable
moment I I would I would I don't know it
just like the product of sleep
deprivation and like the insomnia like
I'm definitely hearing things but
um very recently I started to hear it
like when I wake up or just like
throughout the day I would hear the
noise
and sometimes it just sounds so loud
that someone's outside my door and I
didn't want to say anything when it was
happening because I was scared of
manifesting it into it becoming real and
I I don't I don't know I I don't know to
do I'm scared you hear like knocking or
like it's just huming through the door I
just I just
hear this knocking I hear like like some
it's like a melody almost at first I
thought it was just like comforting
humming but she kind of sound it sounds
distress I don't
like was that knocking in the background
of your
talking is
that who's doing that wait this is not
you's doing
it okay you knock all the tent just it's
okay just keep just keep going
huh I I don't know I I that's that's
just basically it I haven't really
confronted it cuz I'm I'm scared I just
want if I have you guys here at at least
there's there's that right yeah there's
if I die you're I at least I told people
what who was that huh that who was that
you guys are joking I know you guys are
playing with me right now no way we
heard something there something
[Music]
[Applause]
turn on the light turn it on turn it
on pleas pleas oh no well GG I I maybe
have bad news for
you what I I think that voice you were
hearing might have just been me
what yeah what are you doing in J as
heck what are you doing are Liz Liz do
you have something to
say been going crazy for
months I get it anyway what do you what
do you mean it was you anyway moving
along
stories let's let's go back to everybody
shall
we it's okay G there
there it's
okay well thanks you've made Gigi go
crazy yeah she she look
crazy begin
with well very good very good job
everyone uh we have two more pillow
throws for ggn cc for being so kind as
to tell stories this was this was
optional so uh appreciate
itaa
okay you got this okay warm up your
arm's next warm up your arm G this is
Revenge strengthen yours throw I'm
spitting my arms in a circle you got
this you got this go go one
two very very good it's it's okay I got
you standing back I'm looking at I you
had so much power her fists I guess and
then it's going to be CE want to talk
yeah on you H okay meet me too meet me
again really that's so boring no no
there's so many other people here with
like very pillow throwable faces no no
no no come here Justice okay punish
punishment punishment throw it away go
on g wak me
up w
PR good good
throw okay uh so now can we have one
more no that's it what about for the
emotional
TR there will be one more pillow throw
however it will be awarded To the victor
of whoever got the highest the highest
scores they'll also be awarded a crown
uh give us one sec we have to get the
point
there
were points first prob uh I'm going to
award the punishment to the person who
got the lowest points which
um give me one sec the lowest points are
awarded to drum roll please ladies
[Applause]
Sarah you are going to be going into the
closet with
Gigi oh oh oh well if that's if that's
only punishment and yeah it's okay all
right get in there wait so G like
talking talk about the Omega birth or
something good good luck have fun can
you tell me more about Teen
Wolf okay so so this okay do you know
what the Omega vers what do you know
about the Omega verse anyway so the
Omega verse is split into three
classifications there's Alpha betas and
omegas yeah and then sigas that's not a
part of the Omega verse and you have the
alphas and the betas and the omegas and
then the Al I don't know I have to keep
it say so so I can't go into detail what
what else do you want to know I am the
grin of wisd humanisms use like
different words words words words bottom
kid
uh The Working Man has to work every
single day like a cog in the wheel but
the top and the bottom can go on leaves
because they are allowed to by the
government and this is why we should out
rule both the the tops and the bottoms
but the Working
Man there there's an option toid top or
bottom I thought it was one or the other
d d what's
nodding hey
we're coming out of the
[Music]
closet yet I
was did you enjoy your
punishment well when you put it like
that I feel like I can't possibly answer
it uh well I will announce the winner
first I'm going to announce top three so
I'll go three two and and first place so
uh but second and third place I'm sorry
I I don't have anything for you in third
place we
have Cey are
[Music]
[Applause]
Aon you got 46 points on your first
throw you got nine points and your
second throw you got 37 so great work
wow holy moly second place is drum roll
please now the big cat of hollow live
English with 50 points getting 13 on her
first and 37 on her
second very strong and first place
winning uh her prize is drum roll please
with 60
[Music]
[Applause]
points most those points were from
obliterating
faaa yeah you got 38 points on your
second hit which I think is what really
really did you in uh first hit was nine
points third throw was 13 so very very
good y
[Music]
congratulations is almost as big as your
head
yeah now before
[Music]
we
good he's heavy but just deal with him
okay yeah it looks good uh we need to
thank everyone who made this party
possible who made our cute pajamas who
made these cute this cute uh pillow fort
for us the logo who ran this show so uh
I like to give a shout out real quick if
we can pull up the
credits thank you to vonie Rhea NOA and
eni yeah en noo uh for helping these are
my thank you Arts of jailbirds I drew
them myself uh they're not
cute
cute thanks I can't draw I have a mouse
but thank you guys so much for helping
make today's special and fun for
everybody
um yeah thank you thank you so much
please be sure to follow all of them on
Twitter and give them lots of love yeah
thank you so
[Applause]
amazing all right and then uh thank you
everyone for coming I need to shill one
more time so it seems like my limited
merch is already sold out but you can
still go ahead and buy it so please
please purchase it if you would like of
the normal of the normal set go go go go
go is the chance is the time also
further uh I need to show one more thing
I have a cover of espresso up on
streaming services and Liz has one of
Blackbird so please be sure to go stream
those as well as all Hollow Life
original music on
[Music]
Spotify want to anything real quick
today's birthday happy birthday
happy
birthday you guys are so sweet what the
heck do do any of you have any seriously
what any anyone need a shill like Iris
Iris you got a anything um I mean yeah I
do have an original sock that I
released yeah it's
[Music]
really I didn't want to mention it but
you were okay too late the gun is at
your head talk the gun is at your head
advertise your song I Can't sh
stream Twilight thank you it's a nice
song Thank you go check it
out stream Twilight yeah stream Twilight
stream everything stream Hollow live
music yeah
yeah if it's okay yes it it's not about
us but another
s has a big new stream coming up a
special stream yeah
oh it's going to be tomorrow at 8:00
p.m. PT or 12 p.m.
jst so it be cool if everybody could go
check it out big
[Music]
new tomorrow tomorrow is B's 24hour
stream be there or be sare yeah we'll be
I'll be just there4 hours uh we
celebrate 3 years 3 months late but he
yeah got some fun collabs with some of
the lovely ladies here as well
yeah thank
you don't
die I will try yeah well thank you all
anyone else before we move on anyone
else have anything this is your last
chance don't be
shy Nissa Nissa
[Music]
happyday I love you too well thank you
guys so much for making me feel special
and love today that goes to you lovely
ladies but also to everyone who helped
make this possible and of course my
darling sweet jailbirds so thank you all
for making this h a smashing very fun
slumber party we're going to go to sleep
because uh crony has been waiting to do
that this whole
time so it's time right pile
[Music]
CLE darling Good
night
darling
[Music]
byee who's snoring
hit them with a pillow
snoring I can't get my bey
sleep my skin is going to be so bad
[Music]