[Music]
so emotionless
feel it R me
[Music]
sh feel it right me
B
[Music]
honey night is
feel it
me
intoxicating DJ keep playing
it
oh wait that's me oh wait that's me
first I saw that it's me ah first I saw
myself and then I heard myself and then
I saw myself again okay K get it
hello why do I what happened man
I can't hear myself
anymore my settings ah there we go
there ah k a sorry I'm confused my
settings are up uh
K hello welcome back to
our our what football watch along oh God
why is it peeking what's happening I
don't know what's happening my my
broadcaster is acting weird I don't
understand no hardcore yelling yes I I'm
probably gonna throw this piece of
out
soon do I sound weird I've I've lowered
my audio like by half of what I usual
have usually have because today when I
was setting things up for a
panel like if if when I had my normal
audio settings on it was like peeking
like crazy and I don't know why like
something's weird and it's just pissing
me off that I just don't know I can't I
don't know what I'm doing with this
thing so I want to throw it
out seems fine yeah well yeah it should
be fine now but if I have it uh up on up
on my normal settings
yeah I will apparently blast your ears
out but wait let me adjust this okay I
do
this so okay uh I'm back from
Japan uh I'm not in my best form
honestly I don't feel so good right now
I felt a little bit better during the
panel um but then that probably
yeah I'm a bit tired which is probably
just because I got up early at like 7:30
or so
because I I fell asleep so early which
is a good thing um yeah so I'm a bit
tired it's like 8:00 P.M
now my throat
um I got apparently I don't have Corona
although I only did one of those quickie
tests so honestly I could still have it
cuz they're not really
accurate um wait I was going to play
some
music uh it's starting at 9:00 p.m.
right we have have a lot of time to
tangent this was the purpose of me
starting
early
[Music]
um hey
Vian VI you guys know our tanker
right I want to talk about
this I want to talk about a lot of
things hope it's just a cold I don't
even know if you can call it a cold when
it's just like my literally just my Ro I
mean I think I okay so here's the thing
on my last day in Japan which was the
day uh that I collabed with Shi Friday
Saturday I was flying oh so
unpredictable who would have thought
that I was on a plane on
Saturday
um on Friday so I did like a lot of
dancing in the first half of the day M
and I was still fine then and then
uh I had a few hours time to set up the
stream for
shii um I was like setting up
everything and I no in between we also
me and a a new unassigned
manager uh we went to get some food too
and
[Music]
then like like 2 hours or so before the
shiy collab I
noticed I've I got like a huge headache
and and my throat started
hurting and I knew immediately
newma
unma Noob
Ma I me I mainly noticed that the the
pain that I had in my throat it was not
just like pain from like getting a
little bit
horsey from talking too much or so
no it was yeah oh hello chunky wonky
thank you for joining us here today
cutie patootie C she misses
me hello she just jumped
up yeah so I got suspicious
immediately um but the headache went
away after like two hours or so before
the shodi stream and oh my God she's
like rubbing her face aggressively
against my
phone camera
[Music]
um sorry I'm like all over the place cuz
there's a lot of things I need to talk
about because I just have not been
around much
obviously um but yeah I got sick and
then mostly mostly I've been stop
playing with my
camera mostly I've been free of the
headache and it's just like um like SW
swallowing my food or um my own
saliva hurts like
hell I took like painkillers and I've
been drinking tea with honey
constantly and that makes it a bit
better but it's really bad it's like so
bad that I thought I maybe have Corona
and it's just like I'm only showing one
simptom and a little bit of headache
here and
there um I don't know apparently it's
not that maybe it is this thing that you
call strep fro I don't know I don't
really know exactly what that
is uh it might be that shall we look it
up I want to look it up oh it hurts
like the good thing is it's not
affecting my voice as much I tried
singing today for Japan Expo on the
panel I sang do
you and it was it was fine probably it
sounded fine to you guys
but I I did struggle a bit like giving
like pushing
out like a powerful voice was not really
um uh working for me um but it sounded
okay right that's just because I limited
myself um but yeah by the end of that
during during singing I definitely
noticed like ah talking is okay but
singing o not good right now
um strip
fruit IO and he oh it's just a oh it's
just an inflamed throat okay that's what
that is strap fro strap fro sounds so
funny yeah and so I mean I was
thinking listen my body is like amazing
the human body and your mind
is amazing once
again I'm proving to
myself
that like if you have something to do
that your body really knows oh I need to
do this I need to get over this I need
to get through this and then I can get
sick if your body knows that if your
mind knows that if there's something you
really have to do that you can't move to
a different date or so your body will
wait and then hit you really
hard this is not the first time that
I've managed to do this the timing is
just so obvious like right at my last
collaboration okay it hit me like 2
hours before that I guess my body was
like I can't take this anymore but it
came so suddenly too you know that that
felt so weird it it from one hour to
another I had a really strong pain Thro
that's now been going on for 2 or 3 days
[Music]
no no yes sometimes I get sick during
important times too but I do believe
that I'm able to um like hold out for
the important
things My Bonnie has been able to do
that again and
again yeah no no it's
true cuz I it was I was in Japan for 10
days and every single day I had some
stuff to do I was getting really
stressed I noticed my body was really
stressed
[Music]
out I really noticed it yeah and before
that also before Japan I was also
stressed out because I went to Germany
and all
that yeah yeah my fredd deut was one of
those times where I was already I was
already sick but I was able to kind of
like will myself into being able to do
it the live stream for 1 hour and then
after that it hit me even
harder that was
rough
so yeah uh I'm so in that sense I'm glad
that it hit me now at the end of my
Japan trip it made the it made also like
I was thinking oh my God I'm so smart
that I upgraded my my uh flight to
business like 2 days before it's like
for shadowing
because if I have to think about how
shitty it would have
been otherwise cuz even in business it
was a little
bit but I was able to sleep a lot
through the pain in business class and
um I had I bought I didn't have one with
me so I bought a new another one a new
um
Fus
bottle I found a really nice one at
Japanese Starbucks they had one with I
pacas I'm so happy to see that so I
bought that and then I had them fill it
up for me with Cam mild tea and honey
well I kind of mixed it myself but they
filled it up with hot water and then I
made a tea out of it wow potion
maker so yeah they kept on there was a
really nice flight attendant she was
very happy to do it and she was like oh
we also have honey would you like some
honey too I'm like yeah that would be
amazing oh my
God
yeah H 44 minutes you mean 44 minutes
until starting
right it's not starting
now it's know 9:00
[Music]
p.m. okay okay okay I have so much time
to tangent let's
go so yeah
um
why where was I where was I going just
so I'm happy that I upgraded because
that made it a lot more
bearable and then I came home and and
and RBF and BFF were still there I
thought they wouldn't be there
especially because um two days ago I
wrote to RV
F asking hello RPF on the day when I get
home M if you if you're like up for it
would you mind staying a little bit
longer so we can finish up the
curtains cuz there's still um curtains
that have not been attached to the walls
yet and I was ghosted I was ignored so I
thought okay he probably doesn't want to
do
that he probably proba doesn't feel it
he's probably not feeling it but then I
I land and I message um my best friend
and I'm like hey are you guys still at
my
place and she's like yeah we are and I'm
like I didn't expect this I thought I
thought y'all would get out of here
because before I come there so that I
cannot ask you to help me with the
curtains and then I get home and they're
both there best couple so cute and I
give my best friend some things that I
bought for her in Japan and we chilled a
little bit and um yeah we talked a
little bit and I showed her some cool
stuff and then we actually did it we
actually together we freaking did it we
did my curtains and immediately so I
immediately was active even though I'm
sick I kind of wanted to lay down too I
wouldn't have minded if there was nobody
there I would have just laid down and
chilled with my
cats but this way we got productive and
uh an important set of curtains has been
attached and that made me feel really
relaxed and it's amazing how much having
uh having
curtains um like adds to the beauty and
atmosphere of a
room m
yeah so that made me really happy and
then I was like okay now you guys are
welcome to
leave so I left but they seem to enjoy
their stay at kazadi kada they said it
it's it it was like way more um chill in
terms of temperature and honestly yeah
I'm back now it's uh middle of July and
it it's not unbearable like in my old
place
so maybe maybe I'll stick through it
this year for sure because I'm not even
there all of
August so it's fine I guess yeah if I
get Air ac I'm I kind of still want to
get it even though it's bearable because
it's like not comfortable it's just
bearable so I'm thinking about
it yeah my cooling solution it it's
generally working it's not like as good
as an AC but it seems to be working
it will it will be cheaper to get a seen
St in the winter really do they change
their like their work
prices do they actually do that just
because they're probably less busy in
the
winter
[Music]
oh probably demand last demand oh hi
chunky wony you're back again you fluffy
wuffy
so that's that um so me being sick uh
even though I was happy that it was at
the end of my Japan
trip I'm still kind of stressed out
about it
because at at the point of before before
I went into the airplane I didn't know
if it would get
worse and if I could be at Japan Expo
and do this stream and all that and the
following streams
before I F off again cuz I'm only here
for like 4
days approximately I'm sorry I'm I'm
sorry and I I wanted to make sure that
I'm streaming every day of those four
days so you
[Music]
know it didn't get worse seemingly but
it's definitely not gotten better it's
like kind of stable ized immediately
like it hit me like a truck and it's
[Music]
staying I don't know how
long um if it is strap froat even though
my voice isn't really horsey or anything
I don't think I should stream for long
hours talking talking talking it does
feel like a little bit
strain on my throat
um yeah
the worst is just like when when I have
to swallow
anything food or drink or
saliva or
[Music]
air but I'm so happy I'm so relieved
that I was able to do Japan Expo and
this because I was really looking
forward to doing this finale stream and
I was excited to see so many kfp at
Japan Expo
bro like even gura pointed it out before
we got started like we were watching
people on the camo while we were getting
ready and and GAA said wow there's like
actually so many French kfp huh and I'm
like so you noticed it too it's not just
[Laughter]
me we had a front view from like the top
of the screen downwards to you you guys
kind of there are so many of you I was
so happy to see that man and
then ah I want to give you many tangents
I have many but I should also take it
easy I AB yeah yeah I saw you guys I saw
you guys and and
um I saw like on in the front row this
is not kfp related but in the front row
I saw like somebody uh who was a Chum
Chum
Bud who um he was carrying a sign that
said you stinky or gooda stinky yeah you
stinky I think or oh good you stinky I
think and I just read it out
loud and
then GAA didn't see it yet and didn't
know the context and why I was reading
it I was just like a ah I was I was just
I just said you stinky good at stinky
or so and she's like huh what what did
you just say and I'm
like don't you see it's it's I just read
out the guy's sign look at the front row
it's not me I just read it out
loud and as when she was like oh and she
prepared like uh her a sign of her own
beforehand and got ready to counter the
guy imagine he hit it no but this was
like before we started so they couldn't
hear
us but yeah that would have been a
betrayal of the highest
[Music]
rank now unfortunately there was no meat
and greets but cuz I would have liked to
talk oneon-one with you guys but
um this is so funny to me
like the chances what are the chances so
our let me explain for people who didn't
see it and and who weren't there um we
were we had a okay okay let's start from
the beginning a very nice place to start
H life had a booth at Japan Expo in
France which is one of the biggest or
the biggest like anime convention Japan
culture convention I guess in Europe and
um we had a booth you know like we have
in a lot of events recently like a
square nice booth on one side there's a
big ass screen and a c a little bit of a
carpet and then people gather around it
and they watch what we're doing like
beforehand we will like sign up uh there
was like a a Google form and they asked
us uh okay these are the events these
are the dees who wants to do something
at our booth it's like completely 100%
voluntary um unlike uh like usual panels
in an actual panel room where the
convention might request somebody right
but in this case it's our Bo and we have
like a lot of
[Applause]
hours where somebody could do something
so they ask us hey who wants to do
something chunky wonk is back on the
table and so I was like I I saw like I
think I was a little bit busy at the
time when that came up and I I I saw
like a lot of girls planning um like I
think the the Cali panel was being
planned cuz they were like ah who's in
Japan let's do like an off collab K
together for Japan Expo and I was like
oh man that's like the day they're doing
that I'm on the plane so I can't even
participate so I was like okay if
they're having such a fun time together
maybe I should maybe I should plan
something too with other girls who are
not involved in that um and I knew that
it would be a little bit stressful
because I would just be back home I
couldn't do it on the first two days I
it would have to be 100% on
Sunday so I first I hit up
gura cuz I don't know I felt like I felt
like I don't want to do it alone I can
just sign up for something alone too but
I F I
thought who do I want to do it with who
has not signed up for a panel uh yet
seemingly and who do I think may be up
for doing it with me uh so I I hit up
gooda because you know we had a p
around the same time I think uh last
year a different event though
and yeah
yeah um so I thought ah she'll be up for
it a little bit of uh samon should be
good so I messaged her and I'm like hey
do you want to do a panel together I
don't want to do one alone and she's
like yeah let's do it I was like should
we also ask am so she was like yeah of
course so it became amam toy uh panel
because I didn't want to do it alone
thank you girls for joining me m mwah
Mah and then it almost became an amami
panel because I thought I might be too
sick to do it but it was okay um so then
I was like okay what are we going to do
what what are the contents going to be I
already saw a lot of other K things
happening so I thought we should do
something
else um and GAA came up with an idea
that in its final form was a little bit
different uh but I thought it was a good
idea um it just had to be a little bit
fleshed out by
jenma uh yeah her idea was um doing like
fren like uh somebody translating whole
life members names into French and then
we read those and guess who it might be
about um but then me and Jen were kind
of like preparing it and I was like
Gemma like I can't like 100% help you
with this because then I'll know the
answers but I tried helping her in a way
that I wouldn't know the answers and
just like suggested her like oh how
about you translate Elizabeth Rose blood
flame because you can translate rose
into French and blood flame into French
I don't know what you would do about
Elizabeth but that's like one of the few
names that would kind of like work and
then we realized most other names will
not really work like it's going to be
hard to translate into actual
words um at least parts of the
name so I see what jenma has come up
with to improve this idea a little bit
uh it was the the lore introductions of
like what we
are like uh the Priestess of the ancient
ones was translated
into uh French and that worked really
well because the words kind of
sometimes sound a little bit similar to
what they are in English and you can
kind of guess it and that worked really
well it's a really good idea like we can
keep that idea for the future if there's
a similar uh thing which I don't think
you can do this in American conventions
because English English and this works
because it was a French convention but
maybe in the future for other like
similar
[Music]
cases but then we were brainstorming
this all happened on like Friday we were
brainstorming a bit
more cat hair in my mouth we were
brainstorming a little bit more about
like how can we we have a whole hour
like doing this one game a whole hour I
don't know about that so I thought what
other like French game can we
create
and uh JMA said let's do something food
related I was like H okay French Foods
there surely are a lot of French foods
and then I think I had the idea that we
should put up like ingredients only
pictures of a few ingredients of Famous
Foods French foods and then we should
guess what you can make with
that which also turned out to be a great
game yeah but it was more difficult than
I
thought H and here comes the
sorry um one of my prompts was a kiche
and honestly when I saw the ingredients
I did think oh maybe it's aich but I
didn't say it out loud because I thought
it would would be like embarrassing if
it was
wrong um and all of us had a chance for
asking the audience one time if they
knew it what it
was and and the funny thing is for the
names because it was literally just like
French translation it was like pretty
obvious to everybody who could speak
French uh what the answer would be but
for the food apparently it wasn't so
obvious anymore to the French people
even um so when I asked like oh does
anybody know the answer to
this barely anyone raised their hands
like maybe two people legit there were
like a lot of people at our booth but
there were like two people raising their
hands
so
I cannot
believe it seemed like only one person
I'm sure there was another person around
who raised her hand but somewhere like
in the very middle of the crowd there
was one
kfp with uh like a a cap a chicken cap a
chick cap on his head there was one kfp
who raised his
[Music]
hand and
guess who the it
was can't believe it I I I I was
wondering if uh valian would be there
our
tanker people bring the microphone over
to him reach it over and and and he
introduces himself as valian the Cy
tanker and I'm like a no
way no way
because you guys know vidian in the
beginning was like a very active kfp and
then somewhere somewhat after a while
had to go to the military he's in the
chat right now but if I remember
correctly you can only be there on the
weekend or so like his time on the on on
on the Internet is very limited still
but for years now he's been going to the
military yeah in
France but I was so sad every time
people tell me I'm going to the mil
military bye I won't see you for years
bye-bye I'm like no what the don't
go I'm always sad about
it but even after all these years valian
is still our kfp tanker and actually
showed up there I didn't like expect you
to be there to have time for something
like that
[Music]
yeah I was so happy to see that
and and and let me tell you he's very
handsome a very handsome tanker
yo H and he had the answer to my
question yo glad he hasn't forgotten us
yeah you guys are all m m the best for
not forgetting about me but I feel like
when you're like robbed of the
opportunity to go after your hobbies
I feel like there's a high chance to
like not have in like lose interest in
it just because you're not attached to
it
anymore but he's still there just like
many others here
yeah yay I'm so
happy so because I was saying I'm sad
there's no meat and greet because like I
couldn't like identify many of you
I saw a few uh like familiar faces in
the audience but obviously like I can't
identify everybody who I haven't talked
to before at a meeting grade who I don't
know what they look like yeah but uh
this at least made me made it possible
for me to identify one person that I
didn't know
yet
yeah so so so so so so so so so and then
at the end uh we sang originally it
wasn't going to be a singing thingy but
when I realized that cuz I'm I was like
planning most of this out flashing it
out um when I realized that we were the
last ones in our booth to have a panel I
thought after so many hype as K is
on our
booth it might be kind of sad if we
don't sing at all so just at the end for
one song we all should sing a song so I
asked if GDA and am would be open to do
that and they were very willing to do it
thank you
girls yeah so we had a a hype little
ending I think I think overall it was it
was really good a really good panel with
a fun um French game like cultur related
game uh and then a a nice little finish
with some singing I'm
a
yeah what is the song I sing to you I'm
going sing chiku and goodna sang a one
piece song that I honestly don't know
very well at all I only I only yeah I I
actually really don't know it
like I maybe heard the chorus before a
little
bit uh but I really don't know
and actually U GAA and am sang before me
and when am started singing she was the
first uh staff was like writing in
Discord hey hey please um lower your
instrumental by 20% it's so loud we
cannot hear you and am wasn't looking at
that so I thought maybe I can get her
attention by like maybe she has our like
visual somewhere on her screen so I I
thought if I write in really big letters
on OBS to lower her volume maybe she
would see it so I did that and she
didn't react but I already was typing on
the screen in OBS and it and and and
people seemingly were entertained by
that by me telling Amed to lower her
volume so I continued like kind of like
hyping the crowd up uh writing life
subtitles I got really into it I I wrote
like I wrote the lyrics live and then
deleted them quickly and then wrote new
lyric and deleted them and and and and
did like clap clap clap I wrote that
kind of stuff on the
screen that was
fun kind of helping out the crowd uh
with the hype but I'm sure they were
plenty hype without me
[Music]
helping yeah but I saw I saw the
audience's reaction they thought it was
funny so then I did it for Gooby deba
too when she was singing but I didn't
really know the lyrics so it was a
little bit more difficult to say
anything um to write any lyrics or so so
I just wrote gooda cute
sometimes I just wrote gooda cute and
that seemed to do the
trick yeah uh I just wrote it on the
screen by the way the QR code I I I just
I did that was not my fault I was
controlling OBS but I was just sent to
QR codes by staff to use uh and then it
turned out that apparently both the Amit
Channel and my both am my QR code and my
QR code both LED to my
channel yeah we had QR codes on the on
the screen cuz like everybody else was
doing that in the hopes that maybe some
walking by people would find it
interesting and scan the code I don't
know but I'm I'm not going to go out of
my way and scan each code and check back
beforehand if they go to the right place
uh but it's okay I think most people
knew us like at one point during the
panel I asked who here doesn't know us
and nobody raised their
hand uh well I mean it makes sense like
the people that are surrounding the
booth obviously no I mean maybe some
people walking by will join the crowd
even though they don't know who we are
just because it looks interesting but it
seems like everybody knew
us yeah but I mean like when you when
you're like with goba you know most
subscribed YouTuber in the world I mean
I mean I
[Music]
mean
yeah people who are unaware are most on
this outside of the camera range yeah
probably probably like we there were
maybe some people on the very edges that
we didn't see mhm
yeah but it was a great panel it was a
lot of fun and um I'm I'm glad that we
finally got to be a Japan Expo because
kfb has been trying to get me to Japan
Expo for years now and now it's finally
kind of
worked yeah 20 minutes to start
yay yay yay yay let's
[Music]
go
yeah I
[Music]
I I actually I was kind of shocked
um when I first uh heard about
it that uh it wasn't like we were like
everybody can be a Japan Expo first it
was like uh justice would be a Japan
Expo as their like first
convention and when I heard that I was
like what that it's really good for them
and it makes sense because kind of
European
based um members you
know
but can I also do
something and then later it came out
that they were doing a whole Booth where
uh everybody can do something so yeah
yeah yeah
y y but that's why I couldn't really say
anything when I think there was like an
early
announcement uh about whole life being
at Japan expo at that point I knew we
had a booth but I didn't know yet if
like our suggestion for a panel would be
accepted or so so I wasn't sure yet yeah
yeah yeah and I wasn't I wouldn't have
been allowed to say it
anyway
yeah abof stop
stop stop
[Music]
stop
o
o let me re re I don't have enough tea
it seems I didn't make enough
tea one thing I learned during my Japan
trip I forgot who told me this but I was
shocked to hear
[Music]
that
apparently if you put a metal spoon into
a jar of
honey
uh it's going to like delete all the
attributes of
tea of
Honey is that like I can't even believe
that I mean it's it will still be like
kind of gentle on your throat
no that's like I think it would
even if it like deletes some of the
effects of the honey I would think it's
still kind of still
smoing
smoing uh out a little
bit it acidifies the Honey yeah it seems
to be true and that's why people sell
these or shops sell these like wooden
honey spoons for honey specifically
that's that's when I realized oh that's
why that exists and that's why it's
always made out of
wood oh but like how bad is it cuz that
so far my whole life and even now I've
been using metal spoons to get the honey
out of my Honey
[Music]
Jar thank you
Vian when are you done with the milit
when are you coming back full
time I think I think that was actually I
asked you that before the answer wasn't
really
satisfying almost more like more like a
[Music]
never yeah like cleaning a wooden spoon
I don't know I mean I do have like
Wooden Spoons like big ones for
cooking h
but yeah whatever my throat hurts H see
it's already already taking a toll on me
um my plan was by the way for
tomorrow to continue the mogali watch
along because I thought that at least
will not be hard on my
throat so sorry it's um on a Monday but
get ready get get ready get
ready I've been watching so many jetl
videos and now I just finished the the
New Zealand episode and holy New
Zealand is amazing New Zealand is insane
and
beautiful how the and I watched
their Japan season I watched the I
watched the uh I watched the Europe
season I watched the Japan season I
watched the New Zealand season and I
watched the Australia season all in the
past like two weeks
I've been binge watching them holy
so
good okay let me let me get my let me
get my football
ready yeah jet like the game yeah I
always root for what's his name
Sam I think they're all funny but I
never root for Adam and
Ben I don't know I I I can't root for
them I have to root for
uh
Sam
yeah okay Sam sorry I as always I will
have a
[Music]
delay mute time to mute my desktop audio
for you guys
there's a performance going on or really
I mean I I have ads for
now hard wants England headset Spain
same thing for me honestly um let's do a
poll uh I don't really have like a
special connection to either one of
these countries so I don't really care
who wins unfortunately I wish I cared
more
um but I think Spain is going to win but
also think England winning would be more
interesting because Spain is just too
predictable so I it would be fun if
England won that's my
opinion here is
leul leul oh oh I see the
performance who is
this what is
that sick
this looks like
a ice skating
performance cuz the floor is
white wait is there an ice floor
there what's that big Scarecrow in the
back the yellow scarecrow
there's no
ice One Republic is this One
Republic oh it's not a scarecrow it's a
a floating person
apparently yeah that might be the One
Republic
guy we're on fire he
says okay well while they're singing Let
Me mute them I have time to tangent I
make I need to make use of the tangent
time
uh um how's it going 68%
Spain oh wait who's this pretty lady
unmute
unmute she's
hot I meanly got distracted she's so
tall holy or those just kids bag
dancers oh oh those was are
kids cuz she might still be
tall
whoa she's pretty
pushy
oh she's tall
German singer
Leoni ah German
huh
okay somehow I lost interest
what no I don't know no no no it's not
because I don't like Germans it's
because I don't care much about German
singers and that's like kind of weird
because I was obviously interested in
her before I knew that she was
German
[Laughter]
um no you know I like Germany I go to
Germany all the
time wow these scarecrows holy
the way they're floating is
crazy whoa those fireworks that are not
really fireworks those are not fireworks
right they're like color explosions or
are they I don't
know they are on fire wow that looks so
pretty the shot from like the outside of
the
stadium with the the the the explosions
whoa okay the boys are going to the
studio the boys are going to the studio
and the junkers is still behind my
monitor sleeping
cute
[Laughter]
okay sorry don't read too much into it
don't read too much into it let me move
my TV screen over here as always I'm
going to be a little bit
delayed um so don't mind
that
please are we going to oh the kids the
way the kids looked up like
like he Y what the
cute I keep on forgetting what I'm
saying you
so the the red uh red jersey guys are
the Spanish ones the white jersey guys
are the English
ones
not I don't know these players at all I
don't think we watched a single Spain or
England game
so I only hear that Spain is really
really really good ooh the the
trophy the
trophy coming
in wait the guy is that an Italian the
way he smiles carrying the trophy and
it's kind of
cute kind of
cute what's his smile is so
cute oh
the guy just said Italy in this
Championship was
um uh what's
tioned um
disappointingly
uh blast what the is blast again
uh
plus pale yeah apparently they were
disappointingly pale but I think that's
supposed to
mean kind of
like they just were useless just
kidding Basta
[Music]
Basta I think I think I'll mute them
again I don't like the yapping right now
shush
sh sh
sh
ah are you guys ready for some football
in a
minut come come on England Eng England
let's go come on
England let's
go I heard uh in a video I heard a a New
Zealand person
talking and they said this word people
pleaser like P pleaser p p pleaser and I
was like what the did you just say
sounds funny oh wait they're
singing
England oh is this God Sav the
queen n n that sounds a bit
familiar I've heard this one a few times
oh now it's King I right it was Queen
for so
long W God Save the
King let's save the
king Spanish one I've never heard
before are they booing don't Boo for the
aam you
piss
heads disrespectful little shits
is there no singing they're not
like they're not
singing the the dudes are not singing
But I hear singing in the
back oh there is no lyrics are they just
going like in the back cuz I hear
voices I like that it has no lyrics
wow that those those dude's eyes are wow
who's that who's that who are those
people they look important is that like
a like a Spain president or so the one
that was standing next to a younger girl
who I assume is the
daughter no lyrics
huh Coca-Cola
Ed a I can't for sake wait so
it's like two two monarchy countries
against each
other that's actually
hilarious that's crazy that's that's a
coincidence that I mean not a
coincidence because they played
against there a final
countdown a royal
battle while two monarchies fighting it
out usually doesn't mean that they're
fighting it out over football but aren't
we happy that in this day and age in
this Century monarchies fighted out over
a little ball game a little ball
game a little a little ball games in
some cute little
knickers aren't we happy that history
has you know come to this point
[Laughter]
little shorts little
shorts is the monarchy in Spain
comparable to the monarchy in England in
terms of what they do and and how
they're
seen I'm
curious yeah uh-huh pretty
much well so the Spanish king showed up
I have not seen the English king yet but
that's the that that they're showing
right now uh a dude that looks familiar
to me that's like one of the princes I
think Charles Charles is
there oh he can't be there cuz he's very
sick I suppose makes sense I don't know
his current state of health but that
makes sense yeah he's like super old
after all
right okay ending the poll now I'm going
to end it I'm going to end
it so I don't know I don't really I need
to cheer for somebody I don't know I
can't really this is different because
I'm not as emotionally invested as with
Austria right so
[Music]
well I sorry that was a little burp from
my tea oh my God wa this is the first
audible burp ever I didn't even open my
mouth it was like a closed burp no I
must retire now have you heard it did
you hear
it did you hear
it don't tell me you didn't hear
it tell me you didn't hear it you didn't
hear it oh thank God
okay so I've been drinking so much tea
that I feel like I'm getting a little
bit sick from
it oh oh whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa this looks like I'm watching a game
this doesn't look
real ah forgot the
timer okay I'm only 9 second 10 seconds
late hell
mate 10 seconds Lane it is what it is
I was so distracted cuz I was yapping so
much
man so now it's 50 seconds
delayed probably I'm at 32 33 34 35 36
where are you guys how how far am I from
you guys 49 40 41 42 43
44 holy we're a minute apart
Bruh
Bruh s to you you're sinking to me yeah
please guys Sy to me syn to my level
which is so low as you know 1 minute 6 7
8 5 9 eh 10 11 12 13 14
15 syn to
me let that s
in you can't pause it oh man I'm sorry
that I'm again so
late uh is anybody else watching on
on shout
[Music]
of BBC
wow uh
okay the one other person who watches
also
SE seems to
be at on the same time as me yeah so
it's it's really just them being
late okay
so what are we seeing so far
I see motivated men very motivated
Mano
quo they are kicking the
ball they're looking
fresh they're running over the
grass they are touching the grass with
their feet
they're passing the
ball the are you talking about
commentator what the are you
talking
about
lxo who there's like a lot of white
colored shirts in the audience
lot of English England fans
huh I think even when I was in Germany
two weeks ago there were so many England
fans English
fans big
turnout
whoa ah can I tell you the funniest
thing that's so not really
ated but I want to tell you
man cuz like there's not much going on
yet
anyway um so
I uh arrived in Japan uh like 11 I'm I'm
back to Austria now but when I arrived
in Japan like 11 days ago or
so
[Music]
um I got off the airplane
and I go to the luggage thing to pick up
my luggage
right and I wait a little bit and I
noticed a few meters away from me a few
steps away from
me I
see uh a
guy who looks so familiar to me so
familiar to
me and he reminds me me of that only
reminds me but really makes me think
it's him of um a boss so to say from an
old job that I had in like a German
company that sometimes I would travel to
Germany for but I was mostly like kind
of like freelancing in and just like a
part-time small little thing a small
little little
gig
um and yeah it's just like a a a a
little little thing you
know
and so I I look over I haven't like
talked to this person in a long time and
so I wasn't sure but I mean I felt
pretty sure and I look over and our eyes
meet our eyes meet and I like smile to
indicate hey I recognize you you know
but the guy that doesn't smile
back and so I'm
like and then her eyes unmute and look
away yeah so I'm like huh it but I'm
like so sure and I'm still waiting for
my luggage but I can't get it off my
mind I look over again I'm like I'm so
sure that this is my like old
boss so you
know the thing is this boss this op was
in um Germany but the guy is
Japanese so him being in Japan would not
have been too weird cuz sometimes he
goes back to
Japan but I'm like I can't let it go
like I can't let it go I look again and
to confirm my thoughts I'm like nah this
is 100% him what what the so I open
up
my phone
messenger and I I I messaged him just on
the off chance that maybe sees it you
know right
away I I'm like hey so and so there's
somebody at the airport that looks
exactly like you
ha and he does see the message
immediately actually I see the guy
literally
taking out his phone out of his pocket
seems to have notifications on no he
takes the phone out of his pocket he
reads the message and he smiles and he
looks around
like and I'm like okay okay so it is him
like obviously why did he not notice me
like my face is very
recognizable and like you've seen me
many times in the past what the
hell so I like wave him over he comes
over and I'm like why the did you
not like recognize me and he's like ah
sorry my eyes are like really bad
apparently he has really bad eyesight
and he just didn't have his contacts
in and I'm like why the are you
even on this what you were on the same
airplane like what how because I had a
freaking direct flight from Austria to
Japan he doesn't live in Austria I don't
understand this
and what's the what's what are the
chances and yeah turns out he took like
a connecting
flight V and went via Austria but even
then what are the chances that you end
up on the same freaking airplane as me
and I see you at the airport and Japan
has several airports too you know and
and so many flights so many connection
flights if you're coming from Germany
there's a million different connections
that you could
take a million
so this is crazy honestly that was so
funny to me small world yeah
like holy haven't seen you in
ages so we caught
up
oh sorry that Spanish guy just
like um
oh I don't know how to describe
this I'm spicy Spanish guy did something
spicy to English guy in the
air um where was
[Laughter]
I wait I have to think about
it what what what what must have what
must the English guy have been have
fought in that moment what the just
happened I just got bounced on from the
back who was that who was that just
now okay um yeah so that was a really
funny story what are the chances
what a freaking coincidence right okay
we're doing like a what do you call that
again it's not a corner cake it it's not
a
penalty penalty
kick did he just say
gay or is somebody called Gay is
somebody's name gay free kick okay the
commentator just said gay and then
paused for a few
seconds he like two seconds before
nothing then said gay and then waited a
few more seconds
is that somebody's
name he's like
gay TIY
T okay is that really how you say his
name though maybe I heard it wrong GUI
GUI
GUI oh who
w sing
him why
there's a lot of
spiciness Spanish Williams guy falls
onto English
[Laughter]
guy Mama
Mia this is
some
spicy the energy on the field is spicy
whoa whoa whoa who
whoa the the the slow motions
are
sick like the I don't know if you saw
that if you know what I mean but like
the guy was like sliding back from the
edge of the field like slide hiding
while kind of with the with his body
down and then like bounces off the
moment he hits the end of
the the grass you know what I mean that
slow motion that they
showed what was
that he hit the coach yeah yeah the
coach was right there you good
bro you good
oh warming up is going
on they do be warming
up yeah yeah he probably hurt himself
the the way he like bounced off there it
was kind of
weird coach seems to be not a Peter
Griffin you mean because he didn't go
like
ah I watched the football compilation
yesterday uh I think it might have been
this morning
even um of like one of those football
compilations that has like a million
views of time
wasting time wasting like best time
wasting moments of football history that
was some ridiculous stuff going on there
too like a lot of a lot of like
Bingle bongle on the edges of the field
you know what I mean
where they like there was this one
guy who did it like a million times in a
row and got like a million Corner kicks
in a
row because like I don't know it's kind
of
weird yeah Neymar was also in that
compilation but I Harland yeah that was
Harland
yeah yeah yeah yeah I was like oh wait I
know that guy I know that guy from the
Netherland
match
huh he is lucky that he didn't try this
on my
team when we were playing against each
other if he would have tried that I
would have been real
mad these are
who corner kick for England
something weird happened apparently it
looks normal to me oh because uh ah
because the ball went
outside uh through Spain
Spanish that calls for some s pain
pain oh wait harand was not the oh
oopsie that was I no region team okay
but I still know that player somehow
I I guess he's a famous player
anyway I he played for Dortmund well
that doesn't actually that doesn't mean
anything to
me that doesn't necessarily mean that
that's where I would know him
from but yeah he's famous
huh they're all famous y
super doand super
doand
uh they look
funny the way they're moving looks funny
the the fact that England has white
uniforms and that they're a monarchy I
don't know something about that they
look so
proper and somehow their uniform from so
far away it looks so outdated it looks
like it's from like 50 years ago
sorry it just looks old out outdated
oldfashioned but elegant still but also
it looks English it looks so English
huh
right what are you talking about what is
this girl yapping about what
what in it
okay there's nothing going on guys I
have nothing interesting to say give me
some action give me some action
if Austria would be in this match there
would be some actions give me
some action give me
action I'm the director I say
action no wait action is it which way is
it is it clapping first and then action
probably
action and then clapping right
action come on come on England score
some
goals or Spain I don't give a
somebody score some
girls a it come on come on come on
England come on
England are we getting
closer guys by the way subscribe if you
subscribe my throat will heal faster my
throat hurts please help
me
subscribe
please please
I like the egg yolk uh uniform of the
pick Ford
guy it's very yolky I like
it definitely a good choice on that
one
Yol thanks for the memberships I said
subscribe not membership though but
thanks if you subscribe now you have a
chance to get a membership let's go guys
this is your chance this is your chance
join us tomorrow for the mongar watch
long even though we're already very far
not very far but very
far Williams Jor didn't have the balls
to kick a ball into the goal just now
you know why because cuz he's just a
junior where's his daddy huh we need to
get his daddy on the
field oh Williams Junior gets another
chance he's he's got the ball again but
he doesn't has the balls that's the
problem vamos Williams junor vamos
how how how are you already so drenched
guys go go go go go go go go go make a
goal score some
goals oh Williams Junior has sa ball
again come on score some goals
H he gave the ball again
away who's playing these drums in the
background is that like an official drum
player I hear some really loud
like drums that feel like they're very
ceremonial ceremonial
oh those are
fans they they're so loud like how huge
are those
Bonos don't don't don't don't
don't Santa
monic
ceremonial egg Yol is about to shoot
let's go Mr Egg Yolk show me what you
got if you do well then you'll finally
be promoted to leave the
goal finally you'll be able to leave
that area and go into The Big Field oh
one header after another header and
after another header everybody wants to
show their header
skills egg Yol is a
keeper well a keeper in my heart for
sure
he does he does have the egg Yol on
him future concussions let's go exactly
don't hit the ball with your head too
much
guys
careful who the calls me Cel how do
you get the idea that my name is is kcho
ky to you too sir or lady but my name is
not
kcho it's Tano in
it oh that cute hug that cute hug from
the two English guys TI a it very tight
TI a't
it sorry I'm one minute behind most of
you guys so you probably can't even
relate what I'm to what I'm
saying who is she rooting for I don't
even know I'm rooting for the ones whoa
Spanish guy just did like the the cry uh
C some more
baby
gesture whoa taunting
taunting no I'm rooting for the ones who
score some
goals cuz I don't have really a
connection to any of these teams so I
don't care but I want to root for
honestly I might root for the one who's
not scoring the goals but first somebody
has to score the goals so I can tell who
is not scoring the goals chunky wonky no
don't go no oh
[Music]
baby you s you are the best a yellow
cart
let's see what's happening that somebody
gets a yellow
card oh wow yeah okay what the was
that is that what that was that looked
that
looked that tackle looked weird but
maybe that's not what the yellow card
was for ah
okay okay is
it yeah
are they going to show the slow motion
of the
situation cuz he waited right oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh
oh
uh I don't know I don't know if that was
that hurricane hurricane
wait a second is that his actual
name obviously his parents are called
Kane right last name and when they
thought about his name they went for
Harry they knew what they were doing
huh oh my
God and then it's actually amazing that
he became like a sports person
he's like I Came In Like a
Hurricane he he sweeps a football field
according to his name well not yet but
that's probably what he's going
for should have been a weather man
oh that would have been even
better maybe if he doesn't score some
goals today maybe that's where
he'll be going
ooh ball possession England
30% pretty bad so far 70% for Spain with
way more
passes way more passes and ball
possession on Spain
bro that's not really a Korean England
is reigning every day you don't need
weather people when you already know
it's going to be raining
ha you just assume it's going to
rain yeah who cares about weather
reports you just
assume hurricane has been tress for
years he's a bad
player well then maybe today his eyes
will be
opened oh man I'm hating on these guys
what let egg you touch the ball please
he was so excited to go get the
ball no he's good he's good but played
for bad teams a he's unlucky oh he's
unlucky
a let's hope he gets lucky to T
night but in terms of scoring some
goals
period am I right I'm just saying I'm
just saying you know what I'm
saying we do want him to get
lucky I want I want all of these men to
get
lucky toight
night score some
goals
please they need
it we're all night to get lucky we're up
all night to get lucky we're up all
night to get lucky we're up all night to
get get lucky
[Music]
last night I had the stream about you in
thisam I'm dancing right beside
[Music]
you dancing all night long
oh I don't know what to
do about the stream with
you I hope the stream comes true
[Music]
one more
time celebrate oh yeah all right one
more
[Music]
time I know the non pentatonics versions
too but when I start singing one of the
songs Just because I listen to The
Pentatonics version so many times I keep
on like transitioning into the other
songs even if I don't want to just
because it's my head
Cannon it's just so
good
right oh many men on the
floor bro
yellow cart is being
consistent whoa those were some dance
moves from the English guy I'm just
watching the slow motion he's called
rice the way he like moved his body
there yo he should become a
dancer oh
sick he was popping and locking all over
the place
but it did look like it hurt a little
bit my throat
hurts yeah it's been half an
hour no gos
man come
on but this is good for the people on
the field they can't lose
their their um morals
yet and they can't stop start wasting
time and stuff
yet if there's no
goals there's nothing to
defend and there's just pure aggression
just score some goals moral yeah
moral morale
Mor goess
Behavior it'll probably go to penalties
yeah looking at how these teams are
[Music]
playing it's just a a slow slow
game who that dude's a that dude is a
massive unit
what does the Wawa mean I am 1 hour in
front of
her you apologize Sanda fun do you know
giki loves you you know go
go go go let ki know you love her too
but uh I'm not saying Go away stay
all I can conceptualize is Warhammer 40K
people have
been wondering ever since I made that
tweet I think if I which Warhammer I
played I honestly don't
know I honestly don't remember it's so
long ago I was so
young and my mom and my brother I think
were
mostly on that Hobby and I just like
joined in painting some
figures now honestly it was it I know
this is apparently not the answer you
guys want but it was probably the
fantasy
one woo the ball zoomed
out I'm going to ask Mama toi when I get
the chance
yeah well if Mama toi is watching this
feel free to write to me on
Discord but I don't have my phone with
me so it's got to be Discord
of course my mom has
Discord my mom my mom my
mom so
hip I mean my
mom she's just always like when it comes
to like messenger stuff using whatever
is like the the main thing before
Discord it was TeamSpeak yo love
teams speak and Skype and
IQ IQ
man corner
kakea I think team speak was more of a
European thing we we had this discussion
before oh wait
no Corner kicks are interesting because
I I think I've realized the guy who
stands at the
corner he doesn't really have to kick
the ball like I mean I guess he does but
he can also only just kick it one meter
to the side so that his friend who stays
at the side can take over it
kind of as like a a a fake
out it was common in the US too I I
guess so I think I remember seeing
like ah team speak like clips on YouTube
from like I don't know 10 years ago or
so it's probably even older but those
were the funniest things man were they
were like subtitle like basically the
whole video is just like the subtitles
there's no like visuals besides
subtitles yeah have way more than
10 I see Gatorade on the on the football
floor let's go get a
raid yeah yeah yeah everybody use team
speak
there's someone with a trumpet I hear it
[Music]
why is my ear suddenly picking up these
background
noises hi you guys are cute with the
trumpet you guys are cute lightning up
the trumpet emoji with the chicken looks
really cute
throat hurt equals better ears yeah no
maybe but my ear
actually I think both my ears hurt a
little
bit which I think is kind of connected
with my strep throat
then uh but my left my right ear hurts
more than the other ear because it's
also affected
by me having pushed in the ear wax too
much I think
although I feel like it cleared up once
but it's just acting weird my ear is
acting
weird yay I'm still streaming I have to
I want to I need
to all of these boxes checked all of
these statements are correct
come on score some
goals yeah
idiots
idiots egg
yolk egg yolk time to
[Music]
sh I rarely use cute tips that was like
cute tips that was like the one time in
a month
sometimes I I I would say I normally
just use it like once in two months or
so there the one time I used it and it
seems like I've gone too
far um Spain's defense is a pain in the
ass I don't know that that you would
only say that if you're cheering for
England I guess I'm I'm objective and it
seems like they're playing the same way
which is impressive I thought I thought
Spain would be dominating but I guess
England is
very good at keeping their defense up
right now even though they have low ball
possession who let's run run run run
run the way he tripped
backwards oh
man he was running so eagerly and then
he just trips on another guy
backwards so
man and you
guys must be feeling like you already
forgot the moment I'm describing oh
smooy
hello smovie and chuny wony are so happy
I'm back we're cuddling so
much we're so happy
where' you
go oh there you
are
smoovie 40 minutes no score yeah that's
rough we almost
halftime
you know why there's nothing happening
it's because Austria is not part of
this should have let
Austria get to the finale
yeah lost to
Turkey I think anaon can become real
now I think poni is no
more I need to switch out make some
reconsiderations after what happened
need to reconsider
sorry
way you Hur
me oh oh there's like a
cluster a I want to say that word but
it's not uh doesn't even fit there's a
cluster of Spanish bands on the right
right corner
huh whoa whoa wrangling they're
wrangling the men are wrangling these
grown ass men are
wrangling who who
who they're like going after the ball as
if it's like a bomb that's about
to go off and they have to stop
it oh look how the weather looks
those are some dark ass clouds Dark
Cloud remake when remaster
do random as
Des
[Music]
Pand is it raining in there it looks
like the clouds could be further away
it gives England a buff yeah makes them
feel at home
nice
nice that's so sweet of the sky sky kind
of biased what the Sky why you so
biased sky is a fan of England
seems and the goalie key
KY
kcks KCK KY
KCK he know to starts
[Music]
playing whoa hey be
nice that's
SL he slit like 10 m across the field on
his belly number two oh is that Kane
it's fcking Kane
Whoa We went like we this is
fun what do you think was it fun for
him hurricane more like what do you call
uh Avalanche hurricane more like
Avalanche his name should be
aan
lanche and I was Walker not Kane oh
now my joke doesn't
work
but my joke was funny
okay two
minutes is it green I want to see is
this un
what men
men these men are so oaba sometimes I
mean whoa when they were when they were
like waiting for the cake did you see
the those two men
like they were like what you stop don't
touch me don't touch me bro don't touch
me men got a oaba it's in there DNA
yeah like what do you want like y'all
are supposed to stand close to ever
so just stand
there boys be
[Music]
boys w i tired why I wake up so
early oh that header
that ano was so so
horizontal
or or the other one I don't know like he
the way he fell down
man he fell like straight
down oh should I stop the timer
here stopping it now
hey it's yapping
time mute mute mute mute mute don't mute
me I'm inan mute the game mute the TV
kill Master it's yappy time but my fro
hurts man I don't want to strain it too
much
ah okay I I can give you un
Uno tenta tenta
uh see I want to be hyped during this
but I can't like strain my throat too
much I feel like it'll just I'll make it
[Music]
worse um I met all of
Ru when I was in
Japan I met all of them
so basically I was in the
studio and I heard that regos was there
too in another room and I was like oh I
met only two of them so far can I go
over and meet the the rest of them and
they were like no right now they're busy
they're like in the middle of
something I'm like oh okay when are they
free and then like over the course of
several hours I kept on like going over
and Che in with their staff if they're
free they say no I go back I come back
again to them I ask okay are they free
now they're like no maybe later maybe
come again later that that repeated
several times and then finally when it
was time I was like kind of getting
nervous I was like ah now I had so much
time to think about this now I feel
awkward about just just like saying hi
like no real purpose just saying hi I
don't even have anything really to say
like now I feel awkward about this
should I really should I really but uh
new new assistant uh not assistant new
manager um who was assisting me uh
during this trip a little bit uh who's
not assigned yet
she uh walked over with me and gave me
some strength just by standing next to
me and and I I walk over and I I go into
their room and and and and they're like
the moment I enter their room they're
like kind of leaving from the other side
of the room so I only see their backs
walking away from me and I'm
[Applause]
like excuse
me hello and then they stop for me and
they turn around and the first one that
sees me
is and she's like ah and I'm like
oh and then ladin sees me and ladin
absolutely freaks out uh turns out ladin
had some
alcohol so ladin with alcohol is yeah
even more energetic she was already
energetic to begin
with uh she was so hyper she was like
bouncing around and also she was
carrying her pom pom pin plushy that I
saw her holding when we were streaming
from her home so uh I feel like she's uh
similar to shodi in that regard carrying
her favorite plushy around even though
it's a pretty big
one I just carrying that and like
jumping around and went like when she
saw me she was like jumping around like
oh my
God she immediately ran to me to give me
a hug and then she kept bouncing around
like the other good members are just
like standing there like silent
like like oh Senpai and like watching
this chaos unfold with ladin just
jumping and bouncing
hyperactively and I'm like what
the she's even more energetic than than
usual and then the staff told me that um
some of them may have had some
alcohol I'm like a that explains a lot
yeah that explains it she didn't even
smell like alcohol but she definitely
acted like she had
alcohol and then and then she
immediately she was like ah ah like she
already wrote to me like the day before
uh that you know she's like working on
getting the passport but um to visit me
in Austria and then she was like
updating me like St by stand by I'm
getting my passport right now so yeah
I'm on it right now and I'm like yeah I
know I know I
know and then yeah I don't know then
like it Cal down a little
bit so I say like hi to everybody and I
make them introduce themselves to me and
I'm like uh okay yeah yeah not I'm I'm
Ki and you know they say their name to
me and
yeah
um yeah they were they were sweet they
were sweet
uh uh and then like all the new girls
that I didn't talk to before uh you know
they were like oh s
Senpai I like you singing I like this I
like that and then lia lia I already
knew so it was more like a hi nice to
see you again so the moment I talk to
Rea Roden jumps over from the side like
they were they kind of were in a half
circle around me and ren was on the
right side of the circle and Lia was on
the left side of the circle and the
members I didn't meet before were in the
middle of it so R jumps over from the
right side of the circle over to the
side and completely covers zica and
bounces bounces bounces she's
like just like trying to get my
attention away from Lia back to raden
she's like look at me look at
me and I'm like okay lad calm down I'm
I'm talking to L now okay she's like
okay she's like
so funny oh my God I had to I had to cuz
like you know I like L too you know got
to say hi properly to her
too
[Music]
now
I don't know if I should say
this but after this
meeting that uh no actually l Thea
messaged
me
afterwards
and you know what she tells me well she
asks
me I heard a
cat know what she asks
me she
says K
Senai can I come to visit you in Austria
together with
in and can we both sleep at your place
and I'm
like oh both of you
together W that's two birds with one
stone let's
go oh they both want to come
together what what so we'll have to
flesh out those plans
but wait the footage that that's uh
repeat right yeah okay okay um yeah
we'll have to flash it out and plan it
all out but they already have a time
frame in mind those
girls and they're working on like ladin
is working on a passport so they're
serious about it I
think a I can't believe it these these
regas girls are serious
yo don't you underestimate their
eagerness oh smothie don't try to open
the door it is locked don't jump up on
the
handle no no no hey hey you crazy
cat you crazy
cat that
I'm already home you don't need to jump
up on the door to try to find me
outside oh my mom by the way she
messaged me I didn't
see
uh okay I'll be going back onto the
field
soon seems like
it should I start well it would probably
continue from 45 right so I'll just wait
until it hits 4703
chunky wonky see my cats are so needy
they missed me she jumped up on the
table again cute baby cute baby scream
when it starts soon
soon no no smoothie I see
[Music]
you okay chunky wony has made herself
comfortable on my table
my mom doesn't even remember she says
she was more busy with with mm
RPGs yeah it was more like my brother's
thing war hammer but I feel like it
might it must have been
[Music]
fantasy okay okay maybe
uh at the full hour it will go back
probably ask him then yeah yeah one of
those days I'll ask
him I just remember we had those little
color
pots and I was painting some figures I
guess I was probably just helping out my
brother or so I was like I saw him
painting and I was like I want to paint
P too can I also paint please this looks
fun I want to paint
[Music]
too
please I am an
artist
arti when WWA one to point
to
please what was our likeing that meeting
but honestly I really didn't talk much
to them I just like I felt like awkward
and they were busy uh so I just said hi
and like you know caught up a little bit
with that and then the and the the other
three were like you know giving a few
comments um not much uh but yeah alun
was very
handsome and blue and cool and chill and
was like the calming
presence
in L too though L also was a calming
presence I think I'm it's a great idea
if Lia would join uh the trip
because I had some thoughts if maybe
Ren's energy
might actually Tire me out over the
course of several
days of traveling
so I think this is a good
idea I I need Rica to be
there to balance the energy out
[Music]
R's calmest
Moment by the way I'm massaging and chy
won's front paw right now while she has
her head resting on my f
Keys you better not be pushing anything
of significance girl
F she wants to PR press
F how long are these ads what the
oh okay there we are I guess it was
until
2 because they had 2 minutes
extra wait it's still a car I still only
see a car and now right okay yeah we're
kind of
back kind of back
he's just yapping he's just
yapping yap yap yap yap yap yap yap yap
yep Yap yep yep
yep let me mute him
it's just too much yep y y y yep it's
just too much
yep rri is out was that a Spanish
player that's a big blow what happened
did he hurt himself or is he just
already out of breath when they thought
uh we we not going to score this time
huh let's let's exchange him
[Music]
the timer yeah I'm going to wait for
4703 and then I'm going to press
continue zuie meny is going in what a
name these names man interesting names a
star player who plays for Manchester
City what this is interesting to me
because right now he's playing for
Spain so I think I understand some
players that are really famous they're
like rental you can R you can rent them
out for some teams may you pay big money
for a good player but like the Austrian
team doesn't do that right that was
different that's when you guys are
saying oh these players they play
together for a long period of time
they're like you know they're they they
work together all the time so that's why
why they Vibe okay we're going back
in no
H that's Club football well now you
confuse
me okay it has begun don't worry about
the timer don't
worry I told you five times what I'm
going to do with the timer
chill I told
you what are they singing this sounds
like an
Anthem what the why they singing
the Anam
again isn't isn't that the
English
Anam I singing it
again that's
cute go what what the okay I'm not
looking who I'm not looking at the chat
saying who it is interesting finally
they score some goals
the commentator is saying we hope for
more spectacles and who would have known
immediately after follow a
goal wait they're still they're going
towards they're going towards the red
side
and and Williams Junior makes his daddy
proud EOL is crying
no there
goes
England goodbye England it's over go
home just
kidding oh don't give up England don't
give
[Music]
up no EG don't be sad I love you EG no
he looks
sad no wa I don't see the timer cuz
they're showing repeats
ah show the Tim you
idiots show me the
[Music]
timer
bro I feel like it's probably it's
probably time to
go it's probably time they they don't
show the timer but I
think let's
see ah oh my God
it's matching I didn't see the timer for
like 20 seconds or
30 it's matching by the second holy
my feeling the moment I pressed it was
absolutely perfect oh Pandora is
watching so maybe I should be cheering
for
England I just realized
okay that's
like ah I feel like the beginning of
either
half is like a good time to score a
goal
cuz I mean you would think they learn a
lesson from
it
whoa but it seems like it's easy to
score a goal in the very
beginning
[Music]
o what when did Ango get so angry there
at that almost goal did he get angry at
his own teammates that they're not
protecting him
better I I need to change oopsie
okay
Uno H his defense players he like
helmet we just got a goal in
there you got to like protect me more
what the are you doing
mate bloody helmate bloody
helmate protect me for sake
understandable understandable such a
close call soon after that one goal I'd
be pissed
too that egg yolk is going
to that egg yolk the
egg it's going to
crack okay
15 minutas
Spain is get is getting serious I feel
it yeah the energy is very different
right
now uh but automatically that changes
England's energy too cuz
now they are behind and they need to
catch up and protect be both careful and
aggressive is a
challenge hey stop don't push him don't
push and pull him
both attack and
protect you asked for goals we got goals
now yeah that's good that's good
finally it's like they were stalling for
the first 45
minutes
boring oo oh what where is that going up
M difficult he tried to rescue the
ball sh saw a
ball but he had to let it
go if you love the ball Let It
Go
Carval Carval Carval
vamos England also vamos
sorry I just saw the moment of the
headball uh of Spanish guy and English
guy standing next to each other and the
English guy falling down like a
puppet like a lifeless puppet
another yellow oh what happened
ingland
ingland score balls not
cards what is that he got a yellow for
that what happened that was
[Music]
nothing give me a repeat of that ah I've
seen worse nah the way he fell I feel
like
English guy didn't take like he didn't
use that much of his strength and that
guy just
used the moment to fall
down
easily I don't
know you guys don't agree with me all
right you're
fired he stopped the crew oh because it
was a counter attack specifically well I
mean
well England is desperate right
now doesn't matter like what we're
stopping we got to stop
it can't be so
picky I've seen I've seen yeah
worse stuff happening that didn't get a
yellow
but sure whatever if you say that's like
Fair sure okay cool fine don't
care make England more nervous do
it make him feel
it he ball
stolen a bunch of those English men have
some cute pink
shoes looks cute from far away
wow they're so
pink
Morata what
more I
what oh this time EG Yol is happy that
his defense stood up for him oh
oh
oh get that ball away from there
immediately get it to the other side
quick
quick to the West
hell Williams
Jr almost second goal in the
match egg Yol is sweating his spaghetti
off oh my
God that's intense that those moments
were intense holy
macaroni whoa hey what the did you
just do to that English
player cucurella
Kella chill the
out I'll just say again for everybody I
don't really have a team that I'm
cheering for specifically I'm cheering
for
both so
H although now that England is behind I
want to cheer for them you know I want
them to catch up
I want them to catch up and I I want the
egg yolk to be happy at the end of the
day I kind of feel with
him he y has captured my heart yes he's
he's egg Yol I
relate the ghost told me that Spain will
win yeah and I'm sure they will
win but I like to cheer for the
underdog just like back in the
day I Dr
up Let Me Take A I got some Australian
Manuka Australian Mana honey losandes
they look so
fancy let me eat
those let's see if they're
good Los Angel Los Angeles I don't know
Los Lo Los anges I don't know
L
loen lo loes I don't know fruit candies
yeah I can't open the packets the little
little plastic thing not the package
just
a I can't open
it y
okay I got
it who honey smell is
strong who
wo okay it's a it's a big
one
normally fruit candies are not big hey
let's
go
um so many ripped socks
really do need to look closer who has
ripped
socks oh I see it now
wow
England sock quality kind of
kind of
shite I don't think the Spanish socks
are
ripped uh England hello who the
made your
socks they rap it on purpose what no
way but you shouldn't be able to rip
them that easily
oh
Kane let's see what happens to
[Music]
Kane 1 minute
later what did he even do anything he
just got switched out naturally without
doing anything
huh I still can't believe the
name man
hurricane l chy
[Music]
hurricane do you think in school he got
made fun of with that even though it's a
cool
name Watkins is
in yeah
100%
although like like goodlooking
boys he was probably already sporty back
then already handsome as a as a young
boy young
lad there's a chance that he was not
being made fun of and he was one of the
cool ones honestly in
school then he's Untouchable ah he used
to be chubby okay then no chance then he
was
bullied okay he was bullied and that
motivated
him to unop himself and be on this
Berlin football
stage many many years
later whoa Williams
Junior Williams Junior Williams
Junior you little
I mean it doesn't look like he did
much but the referee says he
[Music]
did commentator says it was a clear
foul
so apparently it was clear I watched the
replay I don't
know apparently it's clear come on in
come on
Inland let's
[Laughter]
go no
wrangling okay close
really I see nothing Clos so far
that free kick was not
close oh it's going back it's going
back oh oh oh
ow was that Fen I don't know I just saw
F oh oh that was close bro that must
hurt
it's that's a really good shot in such a
stressful fast situation from Bellingham
and even being like wrangled by tuie
meny kind of pulled back at the same
time and he still went for it in a high
pressure
situation bro Bellingham come on score
some
goals wait his shirt says
Spain his shirt says Spain
the small letters he didn't read the
small letters he's on the wrong team
where is
he I'm confused now he's a double
agent read the small letters
guys all shirts say England Spain do
they oh do they
[Music]
amigos
amigos the go kind of looks smaller to
me than usual did somebody make it
smaller like by a few centimeters hoping
that nobody would
notice I feel like some manipulation has
happened here it's not just me right
it's looks smaller than usual can we
does somebody have a
ruler it looks smer to me the Spain side
looks smaller to
me smaller smaller
[Laughter]
go I'm just talking right now I'm
close again no
why a go good safe
[Music]
oh cute
trumpet egg yolk where are we going with
that
[Music]
one good job
EG good job UL man
yamal almost scrambled my
Eggman nice good
save oh what we got a free kick or what
for what for
what 17 16 who Yama
he's too young go to bed go to
bed do I need to read you a good night
story in German or
what I'll I'll give you a good night
story in
German in
[Music]
for
[Laughter]
it's a German song that is kind of a
meme right now in the German speaking
sphere but I think also outside of it it
even kind of went out
there
um like a German song that uses all
these words that kind of rhyme and sound
similar to Rara and
Barbara it's every right now
I want to sing it sometime in
K it was huge on Tik Tok a month ago
yeah I actually saw it like maybe almost
a month ago on YouTube on some
video on some like girl uh baking a
rabarber cake rarb rubarb
in German it's
rababa I like rarb uh pie if it's with
uh strawberries together okay free kick
no corner kick corner
kick he's got a little squ squ Squatch
on his face egg y again my man he's like
so in it in it ooh Pig for bro he's like
soloing this right
now
[Music]
Inland
oo that was way too
high to be a goal in any world even if
this goal wasn't manipulated to be
smaller although I would say it's only
the Spanish side
for
[Music]
minutes score some goals
yeah 70 minutes what are you
going to do what are you going to do
about it about
it what are you going to do about it
it I think I know why they're
losing it's cuz the herb
is
like streaming but not even watching
this sh is just streaming
undertale I can't do this alone herb I
can't do this with my own power
alone I
can't my magical supportive power as an
anime girl only reaches my own country
Austria every anime girl in this world
has an
obligation and an invitation to support
their country here yeah
yeah I'm trying to like Channel it
through you through me to them but it
doesn't work if you're not in it to Wi
it in
it go and you what I oh I don't know for
who I Okay one minute give me some time
guys to catch up with you
guys oh my god did my did my yapping my
ranting just work wait no maybe not egg
please EG please protect protect oh he
help he held it he's run he's holding it
he's running in the egg okay it's going
are we going to the other side we're
going to the other side engot it's scar
some
gos come
on destroy their manipulated
goal let's go
beautiful my R
worked let's go
[Music]
an
Yo God Save the
King God Save the
King hope is back baby
One Versus
One
hey okay I had to cheer for a goal
because I have
to but damn bro my
throat I need to be
careful but let's
chill penalty what
the guys in the pub nearby going crazy
oh you watching in England and you have
a pub close
by yeah I'm sure all of England is going
crazy over that
one the studio is kind of crazy Studio
the
arena is this holy they're Hy
they're Hy
of course they're going to do extra
time but for now we're still uh a while
away from that
anyway sneezing hurts so
bad
[Music]
that
hurts cuz it kind of go through the
throat with like full force
man
yeah I I I would like to see
England win that would be interesting
I don't care either way but would be
sick I think I think they they need
it yeah gunite is appropriate wish wish
me some health guys please in
German hello smoothie
[Music]
these people are so
hype so it's one versus one now if you
guys want your team to win you know what
to do
subscribe then your dream will come
[Music]
true holy o o o
o
o since when does Booking.com have
booking doy as their address the
subscribe since
nice part of the slogan what I never
heard it
before
sheesh I'm so happy that they evened it
out
because I just don't want them to lose
devastatingly it's anybody's game
now oh oh
oh thanks for the membership and thank
you for the super chats
guys thank
you one Zer isn't that devastating yeah
but I mean I would have expected there
to
uh be some more on Spain side by the end
of this
game okay egg Yol focus focus my man
Focus they're surrounding
you 50
memberships hey thank you so
much see guys you can get a free
membership you just have to subscribe
first go get yourself free membership
today they're discounted
today only
today subscribe gets membership
free oh I see the rain now I think I
think I saw a rain
raindrop is it
raining no maybe not
what a deal what a deal what what a
deal Day Zero
subscriber wait Day Zero how did you
know about me on Day
Zero I'm trying to make a stupid joke
but it's not
funny normally I would call it day
one thank
you thank you I guess they would mean
that you subscribed before my debut
stream like during the Twitter only
times
probably which is actually
crazy thank you thank you
hey
what what the commentators are
saying the commentators are saying some
English fans were like already leaving
because they lost their hope in their
team some of
them but then came back what the
they were actually leaving why would you
already leave you have you have tickets
to the finale of the
championship of
Europe you don't just leave like 60
Minutes in or
so like maybe if it's a smaller game but
on a big game like this bro if you go
out of your way to be there I don't I I
don't believe it it must have been like
one or two people who just went to the
toilet or something
something that
sounds like crazy yeah those tickets are
expensive and you're not even that far
into the game there's still a chance
you're not losing
devastatingly makes no sense I don't
believe it
yeah almost almost go close one
oo o on which
side did egg yolk save England
again is is it what skin the egg yolk
man or is it the other way oh where are
we going we're still in the middle oh oh
yeah yeah yeah it's going that way it's
going to
eggy let's go eggy let's
go oh yeah eggy my
man England's a soldier
Pig
for sheesh good good
goalie that yeah when the goalie is the
best member of your team this is what it
looks
like bro
your goalie should be good yeah you you
you better pray for that for a good
goalie Spain wants that goal
Spain Spain is reaching for the trophy
nacho in what his name is
nacho thanks for the membership and you
joined on your own with your own money
not a gift a
yo thank you seems like you really
wanted a piece of
this Le that's a French guy
no he just realized 82 minutes into the
game that he wasn't supposed to be here
he's like wait wait wait wait I'm French
not Spanish what the am I doing
here I'm out sorry play for the wrong
team for a little bit
oopsie
imagine hits you it just hits
you then and
there I can't support this anymore I
need to go back to
France duck another membership joining
with his own money yeah you got your own
money you don't need to you don't need
to take the memberships gifted to you
from
others self
sufficient grown
ass chicken
let's
go they are D oh
chicken yeah oh egg Yol
[Music]
eggy egy
protect that was really far from the
goal but he still he still went for it
my Eggman
the
Eggman yamal gets a corner kick oh here
we go uni now all the people are getting
memberships because they want to show
they got their own pocket full of
money I can buy my own membership thank
you I don't need you a free membership I
can buy my own let me show you
thank
you eggy
hey 's he's like working at like 230%
right now
man
W oh oh we're at 85 minutes
only 5 minutes left plus extra time
and I mean yeah as long as it's one
versus one it will go on forever
go Spain I got spoiled oh no
that's really bad that's really bad
that's really bad a goal now for
Spain not much time to catch
up
maybe offside oh oh oh
oh I'll update it on already even though
I didn't see it
yet no egg no I'm so
sorry you've been working so hard you've
been trying your best I
know but honestly okay that number 21
his face looks really nice like he's
really sweet
looking like I can't even be mad that
just looks
like a really nice guy who doesn't want
to hurt anybody H mate bloody H
mate offside still some
doubts could be could
be no now I don't want you to take it
away from him because he seems really
nice
[Music]
are they checking V
AR I don't know I I really can't judge
this kind of
stuff
[Music]
oo
o counts no offside
okay okay I'm kind of happy for him his
eyes are really cute
I'll give it to
them okay yeah I just got the
confirmation so I
shall I shall allow it
whoa
England
England come on
go
go I'm sending you anime energy
[Music]
does it help you think it helps are they
feeling
it power up
[Music]
Marino
wool his socks must be made of Marino
Wool Wool is so hard to
say close oh no oh
no oh
no okay corn a
[Music]
cake whoa
England bro
brh
brh the funny hair
guy funny hair guy that's the funny hair
guy right in my mind I've been looking
at his hair this whole time I'm like
that must be a lot of gel in his
hair she he does yeah that is the funny
hair
guy ooh
England I kind of want it for you at
least even it out so that we have more
to look at four minutes no that's not
enough no more
minutes Fu n that's really bad that's
the pressure now is too
bad
ah OK you shot it outside of the
[Music]
field br
brh
BR even it out come
on
come on England you guys think they
can even it out in these last
minutes you think they can do it come on
come on nice kick to the very very far
other side England scare scar some one
just one
go low
chance yellow card now we don't have
time for this we don't have time
for this
okay o right in the stomach of the
nacho nacho show should go into the
stomach not your foot
there's no time for
this come
on OE Watkins Oe
wait they're doing like they stalling
tactics now aren't they I mean
Spain I mean I don't care I kind of said
Spain will win so this is just according
to what I expected
but
no come on come on please I got no n
this show I hate the life last
moments of these shows
no just so
shitty it's only funny in
compilations not in real serious matches
please stop doing this in real serious
matches it's so over isn't it it's so
over a't it it's so over a it
it's okay I I I said Spain will win I'm
just cheering for the for the one team
that's behind but I knew Spain would
win ah
vamos oh now you're going to show me the
V commentators talking about the shoe
size 47 from that guy helping him in
this situation or almost not helping
him the Luigi board was
correct I still have 30
seconds it seems to be over
huh ah the other dudes they're already
like going to the team to the the
middle already ready to hug it
out hi England I'm so sorry
oh they already
whistled the royalty is
chilling oh
oh
yep it's
over
congratulations
Spain once
again the opponent are in
pain against
Spain Spain inflicting pain on
others oh
God that looks painful for the dude in
the very
[Applause]
bottom Spanish
or Spanish or
vanish do
dualingo is this a dualingo
conspiracy is dualingo behind all of
this did dual the dualingo bird make the
doors uh the goals
smaller is Du lingo behind all of
this the green
bird that's what Spanish or vanish meant
all along that song was not about
language
learning Mama Mia dualingo that's why
I'm not learning anything from
you they
are freaking agents in
Disguise I need a tin foil hat
accessory weird conspiracy um I think
very realistic excuse me what's weird
about
that
[Music]
Fades
congratulations SP good job I guess I
don't know England did really well
too okay let me mute this get go away no
go
away I think England did very well this
was not as an easy win for Spain as I
thought it would
be was pretty
good yeah it wasn't a blowout match as
you say I
suppose England did good this is what I
expected uh but not what I what my it
seems like my heart I wasn't sure in the
beginning but now at the end I can tell
my heart wanted England to win just
because it's more
interesting cuz it's like the unexpected
thing that's why I used to root for
Greece back then many many many years
ago when I was a
child was that was also a European
Championship I think not worldwide was
European I'm pretty
sure
yeah yeah I want to give a big shout out
to my man EG Yol if you feel like you're
sick and tired of this show feel
free to uh join kfp at any time uh if
you're not already you're probably
already part of it so you're always
welcome back home here at
kfp
yeah with the other eggs and the other
yolks yeah they're engraving the trophy
oh wow okay well should I watch this
like ending I have I see ads though oh
wait now I see it
ah
[Music]
Speedy Fiesta
Fiesta and then Siesta
Siesta ah the Spanish people are getting
a a my favorite word is back
a ay oh
there uh it's nice to see happy
[Music]
people what song are they playing I
don't even I don't even recognize
it some some lame ass song they should
play doyo or Sparks or
[Music]
kimoo ISO actually from
Spain just saw his face it looked so
German to
me yeah
oh is there going to be I think I want
to see the the moment where they give
the trophy to them so I'm going to watch
until that I want to see the trophy
handed over
and then I want to see at the very end
that they measured the gold size to see
that there was no funny business going
on
there
o
o first the medals for England they all
get like little
medals at least something I mean they
went to the finale well I I would say
that's like impressive but in their
bracket we know that that side of the
bracket it was like really
unbalanced all the heavy lifters were on
the Spain bracket
side and the more mid lifters were on
the England side which in a way was like
good for the
midlifers that they didn't have to go
against the heavy lifters
basically that was kind of
good oh
H they're going to the studio the TV
studio shut up guys tell me when they're
giving out the trophy I'm going to
unmute them just yap yap yap yap yap yap
yapping
[Music]
so Str so
tomorrow and as I told you you guys
tomorrow will be members only stream
we're going to continue wherever we left
off I don't know anymore uh I think we
were we left off in the middle of a
season second season we're going to
continue with that I don't know how far
uh but we're going to do that I don't
know maybe 5 p.m. W time or
[Music]
so and I think I think Tuesday or
Wednesday we're going to probably play
Fallout cuz I couldn't think of anything
else is there like I I think I saw a new
fotm game that like what part-time thing
I didn't watch what kind of game it is
but
uh oh wait they're interviewing the nice
guy is he
crying
a his eyes look so
glossy two hours maximum game I I would
appreciate like short
Time
games at the moment with my throat being
still
fked is that even in like fun is it a
horror game or is it a like I don't know
whatever no I can't play which spring R
right now like even even Fallout
is kind of a difficult thing for them I
don't know we haven't played it
previously like I'm I'm just going
to go go between them it's a silly
game okay
oh should I play it do you guys want me
to play it on
stream cuz I
mean I don't know I don't think I have
anything else that I need to play
urgently or so right am I forgetting
something
oh fun short game that's good I need to
I need to follow the fotm sometimes cuz
like I never do
it yeah and I don't really know what to
play otherwise so I wouldn't mind
putting it in
there I know I know I'm aware of the
Polar Wars but that's not something I do
want stream I didn't have time so far I
just came back from
Japan and today I had convention and the
Stream
but I know it's on my mind don't
worry
okay this is the second Euro Final in a
row that England lost you mean in the
final oh yeah that's what you said in
the finale
what e that hurts last time they lost
against Italy
2021 oh
man oh man England I'm sorry next time
I'll ask I'll ask herb to do a watch
along for y'all so that hopefully you'll
get some of that anime girl energy from
a you know a
local a these interactions are
cute Pandora was Shing them on at least
that's where that one goal came from
maybe but it wasn't enough it just was
not
enough is so cute see how T the Spanish
people
are very t
[Music]
now
um I don't know how much longer they're
going to take to give the trophy out but
I'm just going to say
subscribe uh these uh watchs have been
so much fun I kind of didn't expect to
enjoy it that much either from the
beginning but I had so much fun I got so
into it obviously now Austria not being
part of it I was like a little bit l
less hyped about it but it was still
interesting to watch and I still had a
lot of fun following
along um I wouldn't mind doing more like
this in the future and we already
discussed doing uh some Olympics watch
alongs this summer so I'm excited for
more Sports on Za waa channel it's this
summer already right maybe wait we're
already in summer though but when are
the Olympics starting when are they
starting we're already in summer
I should be able to do watch alongs in
like August and all of that if it's in
August ah 26th
okay yeah uh I think once we get into
August I'll be able to join into the
funsies
yeah I learned a few new things about
football rules as well I and I learned
about some teams and some players and
some
memes so I had some good fun here and I
must say this Arc has also been really
good for the growth of my channel so I
want to say thank you to everybody who
joined the Wawa grind during this Arc
thank you I really appreciate
it it's really really really really my
pleasure and I hope you'll stay uh I I
really think I'll do a little bit more
of like sportsy content I'm enjoying
this it's like nice to cheer on somebody
especially if my own country is part of
it o all the suits people are coming
out I guess those are the waa
[Music]
owners would you play a sports game I've
been wanting to play and I know this is
not really what you're thinking of I've
been wanting to play the the Mario
football game
um I used to play that on the
GameCube I know that's not what you mean
but I take it really yeah Mario Strikers
yeah and I think I even I I hit up uh
am like like two months ago or so like
hey do you want to play Mario Strikers
together oh it's the smiley guy
again smiley
Italian his smile is so
cute why does he look like a
puppy he's
carrying
the a Chini he's carrying the the
a the thing in a they're all claing for
him they see his cute smile and they
smile back because he's so
cute
CH ah echola
trophy shiny why is it not
gold lame cheap cheap how much
money are you making from this event ah
and you can't even make a pure gold
trophy ah
ah oh oh wait is a silver one for
actually for England
wait okay wait yamama is going
up what does he get
to what what's happening he's shaking
hands oh he's hugging one of them what
oh another
hug a
what e he gives a hug to the second to
last guy and then spits to the
side I mean I
mean I know that like sports people like
to spit around but could you not have
waited for a
moment
classy well he's only 17 let's give him
some time to get some manners I don't
know wait that dude is not wearing pants
number 16
Rodrigo oh that's what you guys meant
with
rodri that was a short version of
Rodrigo
huh see watch how Rodrigo does it he
doesn't spit to the side after hugging
these
guys
gentlemen yeah
that trophy I want to play with that
trophy on a
string a string between two
sticks you know what I
mean oh the referees are coming up
a yeah the devil
sticks
[Music]
diao the referees are some handsome men
too
huh they look so
proper as proper and handsome as you can
look in a uniform like that one of
honestly what he's so tall that
dude oh he's standing on top of a okay
that's not
flattering to the others they're
standing on a
stair okay they got some
nice
uh medals for just existing and doing
their job I don't get a medal for doing
wa never mind I I do have uh YouTube
plaques right in front of me actually
for doing my job I guess okay okay okay
okay but no I mean like they just got a
medal for showing up I don't get a PL
for just showing up I worked hard for
this okay it's a little bit of a
difference okay they bring an English
person up stay strong my man stay strong
oh actually all of them okay oh they
look very eager to go up
there heo come on get what you
deserve ah
[Music]
uh even the expression from the witha
suits are like sorry man sorry bro a oh
man oh
man yeah I'm caught up with h o t
d but I won't be able to watch oh it's
Charles on the
stage yeah he's really
tall yeah I won't be able to watch the
next episode live I'll watch afterwards
cuz I'll be sleeping comes out at like
3:00
a.m. I got your mom into
football
what
Mommy sorry
Mommy oh Charles
what do you think the football players
are like thinking about Charles being
there you think they
care cuz like generally English people
are very seemingly very connected to
their royal
family
seemingly uh William
sorry I don't know their names William
sorry I know it's the Prince I I mix up
the
name oh it's time for
Spain oh that's funny Williams Junior
will say hi to William well William is
still up there the prince will stay up
there I thought he was just up there for
England
I think he's still
there or did he
leave nah he left
right oh the king of Spain is also there
wait which one was the King of Spain the
one the one next wait I can't recognize
him hi smooy rolling on the ground below
me
ah he kisses it and now
kiss sorry I broke a little bit because
I was watching the the
Flawless smooth way he's giving out the
medals from uh taking them from behind
from the
guy and then giving them out to the
front how smooth that transition
is in such a nice Rhythm
[Music]
too
a wowers
what what's that guy's name he's just
like he made his pants into
panties it's not a good look I want to
say bro it's not it's not a good
look yeah it just looks more like a
nappy like a diaper
[Music]
this it's so
puffy well what's with
Morata
what Morata gets a he gets the trophy
all
right that is not gold I think that
trophy belongs to England because it's
silver ah look at the team look at the
bro
r
a
a that's where all the gold went for the
confetti you turned it into
paper gold and just shooting it out into
the air now kind of wasteful but
okay fireworks
oh I think the people who are leaving
the stadium I see
them in that shot from the outside
there's a lot of people leaving those
are just England fans I
guess or people who need to catch their
train cuz it's 1120 in
Germany nice
[Applause]
F oh
We Are the Champions is
[Music]
coming me meow meow meow my
friends we keep on
fighting to the
end all the
chions We Are the
[Music]
Champions that line hurts no time for
losers actually hurts that's a line that
kind of
hurts
[Music]
muffin
H poty poty poy po poty poty poty
poty the
Royal oh he's actually going to them
he's actually letting them hold it
that's so sweet of them because like I
was thinking they were just standing
there awkwardly for a moment and then
the Fabi on
goes to the Royals lets them hold the
thing a and they're probably also
like hey you guys only got a silver
trophy that's so lame like in our house
the literally the flooor and my bed
sheets everything's made out of gold
like this is like so cheap
where'd you get this from Teo what the
are the
champions no oh time for losers you
heard a cat yeah there a cat just
entered my room indeed oh she's rubbing
against my
[Music]
kney oh my God he looks like he's in
panties please pull down your
pants please is he trying to create a
trend or something
oh my
God I want to throw
up feel a bit
sick I think I'm
just overdosing on
tea yeah okay nice celebration I'll stop
it
there good for
them it's nice I wish I could have
experienced that with Austria that would
have been insane holy imagine I
would have I would have lost my
mind and I would have cried here in to
Spain people are screaming and singing
Bama it's good for you I'm happy for you
it's nice to see people happy like that
in an event like that that's amazing I'm
sad for the people who are sad man I'm a
empath
okay a I want to ah my tummy hurts
ah ah
man actually I wanted to go longer and
read super chats but I don't
know probably should
rest
yeah do it on stream yeah that's um
something would
say yeah well w s
this that was good good stuff fun Spain
versus England interesting match but uh
predictable
outcome uh however I'm glad that it that
it wasn't like o
c that it wasn't
too clear here the whole time actually
until the end it really wasn't too clear
who would
win both teams had a good
chance yeah and a good go at the ball
thank you smooy you sweet baby I know I
know I know I know yesterday at this
time I was already sleeping
deeply in bed wasn't a steamroll yeah
thank God that would have been boring if
it was
refereeing didn't look so bad yeah and
honestly even the time wasting wasn't
the
worst seen I've seen worse already so
that was
fine yeah I'm kind of sad it's over
[Music]
man smovie really wants me to end the
stream she's
aggressively rubbing against my leg
the Copa people keep on mentioning the
Copa America nah I don't
care what it's in two minutes or what
what nah oh 2.5 hours the
finale I don't
care was that what what was that that's
uh was that American Football was
it what Cup in two years yeah I know we
already said like oh guess I'm staying
for at least another two
years uh oh no it's just real
football AR Argentina verus Colombia a
Copa I've never even heard about kopa
America until
now probably because it's just like uh a
thing over there in the
Americas m H why are you guys doing that
at the same time
hello hello can't you find yourself some
better dates like maybe a week later
hello stop
overlapping it's like when there's two
conventions that you want to go to and
they somehow chose the same
date it to be like that sometimes
[Music]
well good luck made the best win in
Argentina versus
Colombia you guys going to actually go
watch that on TV you guys going to watch
it are you guys curious about it are you
into that
ooy yeah
no no no no no no most people say no I
only will watch it if I will watch it
huh I see how it is understandable Oh
smothie Canada got really close fourth
place oo Ice
movie Yes
movie yeah no I wasn't going to watch
anyway like it's way too late and I'm
not really interested I'm not uh I
didn't get into that would have been too
late um yeah guess I'll go
um I want to talk more with you guys but
it's late and tummy hurt and sick
tomorrow I will take it a little bit
easy but I'll still
stream I'll try to put up the
reservation right
after so thank you so much for following
this football I yay I want I I put up uh
the the little um uh clip of me H
animated from our first football watch
along uh in my shorts please watch it if
you haven't watched it yet and if you
liked that then go to the full version
the link is in the description of that
clip check it out check it out I really
love that
clip first even without the animation
the clip was already so good now with
the animation it's like even better who
would have
fought congrats Spain and good job
England love you
both Europe is the
best tolerate the
rest thank you and in German we say Al
day
yeah Wawa is back but only for a short
time but I'm back Wawa is back wa is
back thanks for the membership thank
you
wow thank
subscribe ah
[Music]