[Music]
hold on
you need to give me a moment hold on
that sound is very strange because it's
hardy and i don't like
that's a little better i don't like the
intonation that you had before
i just can't help it i'm just too sexy
can we end the stream now can you please
get out of my home
i'm having fun you're having fun
i guess i did invite you over yes we
should go to my room
oh my god
it's been such a long time actually not
such a long time i was
i was kind of in your room in the way
out collab but not
really yeah you were sitting on my floor
and it was rather annoying and i didn't
like it but now i'm sitting on a chair
yes yes i prefer that to you sitting on
the floor
hello everyone it's takamori beaches i
mean
if that's what you want to call it
that's it you can use the hashtag
if you want if you want to use it it's
up there it's up there it's
i mean yeah you can you can use it if
you want if it if it pleases you
you feel free to she approved of putting
it on your screen i didn't approve of it
i simply conceded defeat
i i let you do you like that do you like
the glowy all right that i brought with
me
yeah well it is rather nice and it's
rather warm
during these chilly times uh however um
i prefer
the darkness so this is fine i'll i'll
let you do it
you can continue doing it that's
frankel's factory sparkles
yeah are you enjoying your iced tea
uh yes last year i gotta be real
what's actually in there is uh we went
to
can i say where we went before yeah you
can do it we went to donkey hotel
don don quick quick
and picked up some stuff like yeah that
wine that's just drinking now
out of the bottle i got myself because
japan has all these uh
fancy like flavors for drinks like fanta
for example not hashtag not sponsored
but
i got myself a premium peach flavored
fanta
oh so i'm gonna try that now one second
let me open it up yeah try it let them
hear the
the noise hold on
you definitely heard their ears with
that oh my god oh it's not overflowing
they want to come by okay apparently
you're not allowed
to to come by with a non-alcoholic drink
really okay
i guess all right mmm drankies oats got
it for the week
[Music]
yummy it doesn't taste like fanta
because i mean when i connect well fanta
is just an
orange fizzy drink
[Music]
i'm kind of lagging like a robot oh my
god i mean
yeah i feel like i feel like our
yarikata is a little different from how
it usually is
yeah i love how you only speak sandoz
english words but you you purposefully
pronounce them bad right
yes i would hope sounds well i mean whoa
what no i don't ha it's really yeah
yarikata the way that we
i love it it's pronounced don quixote oh
really
it's not don quixote really i didn't
know that chet i didn't
wow thank you so much for for
enlightening me with your big brain do
you know the
the donkey hotel no i'm a big fan of it
why don't you sing it for us okay here
we go i like how we both always
challenge the the dmch tracks
don't get me dmca stricken
so it goes
[Music]
hit him with that freestyle though
they usually play that a lot in the
donkey hotel maybe not anymore
maybe they got rid of it but i used to
listen to it a lot when i wasn't okay
with that
don't do they have donkeys all over the
world
not in the underworld they don't oh uh
we just have i think it might be
how about it chad do you have a don
quixote where you live
don quixote do they no they don't oh
she doesn't know what it is it's like a
store where they have everything
like literally everything well one of
the things we we went there
to buy uh a bottle of wine
a drink for me some potato chips and uh
we wanted some
gloves which we're talking about but we
also randomly
found and i don't know i mean you
decided to buy that i wouldn't have
bought it but
we bought a a nose vacuum cleaner
that's right yes yes it pulls worms from
the top
of your nose yeah on the on the box
there are little worms coming out of the
holes that are apparently in
human noses yes and i suggested we tried
it on stream later
yeah that sounds horrifying and see if
it actually works but i guess we will
yes worms yes worms let's see if it
works i want to see if it works later
yes i'm curious i want to get i mean i
don't know if there's actual worms in my
nose well we will see
we'll see yeah it looked pretty nasty
and i feel kind of strange
about it because when i look in the
mirror i mean look at hold on chad now
you can see my nose
i want you to look at my nose very close
and my nose too
yes we'll look at kiara's next look at
my nose chat now you really don't
there are really no uh strange holes
that worms would come out of jeff
anything um yeah kiara you don't see it
you think well how about
wait wait wait go back to your nose wait
okay uh
let me ask you one thing uh-huh how do
you breathe when your mouth is closed
um now that we look well now we talk
about noses and
holes and noses you don't seem to have
breathing holes in your nose
me neither but oh that's a really great
question um that's interesting huh
maybe the maybe the dot that you see
right now that's not
it's a hole are you sure that is the the
shape of your nose
oh okay um so when my mouth is closed
hold on how do you breathe can you
breathe
hmm let me find out
oh wait a minute i'm dead i'm
a reflex from your body that you cannot
close your mouth because otherwise you
won't be able to breathe i mean i guess
not this human body is very strange i
don't
completely understand it well how about
you kusatori do you have nose holes
let me ask the viewers one question
okay are you ready yeah i'm ready are
you sure you're ready
yeah i don't know viewers are you ready
dear dad beats
okay and the kfb people who are also
here
would you like to suck my nose what does
that mean
hold on wait no we're gonna swerve wait
i didn't i did not give you permission
to
accost my viewers like that like the
thing that we bought
basically we'll suck worms out of our
nose that's what when it's
what's happening that's not something
chad should have
no i'm sorry that she hurt you like this
are you okay
chat that was so rude of her to ask you
that it's not rude
you don't just ask people whether
they're going to suck your nose
that's not a thing that you ask to
someone i apologize deeply i might have
understood
misunderstood you know english is not my
first language i was just thinking that
this is what that machine does the
machine that we bought it just sucks
uh snakes out of our nose right
snakes they're worms they're worms kiara
okay it's embarrassing to be in such a
close-up well i
just wanted to ask the viewers if they
saw any holes in your nose
where worms might come out of it can you
i'm trying i'm trying to stop it i just
want to show them your nose
oh my god what if i just zoom in real
close
now you can't run and hide now we're
going to find out that the skulls really
are there kiara i want you to show them
that they are skulls
you're moving like a powerpoint
slideshow hold on i'm trying to stay
still okay
look at me deep deep in my eyes they
look like skrellington's to me no
why are you so you sound very sure that
they aren't scrolling down because uh
i mean i i get it low-key
but no all right you know what
well i'm a bit far away from your screen
from your computer screen
so when i just looked over quickly i
thought the hashtag
takamori i guess uh was saying uh
bandicam
what does that even mean it looked like
bad accounts it's so
far away with this bat what does
bandicam even mean
oh uh what a boomer you are
what is a zoomer i don't understa i'm
none of those things i'm i'm older than
everyone here well that makes you i
guess
that makes me older than boomers but you
were just uh you were just hidden from
that part of the world it's okay but it
still looks oh my god every time i look
over the screen it looks like bandicam
i don't even know what that means it's
funny it's like a really old i think
did people use that for streaming back
in the days we're streaming our first
uh for like screen recording oh yeah
you talk about hypercam oh hang on one
second here hold on
hang on i have another one oh thank you
oh yes that's what i like to hear uh
when you do that though it makes me not
want to do it any longer
[Music]
when i do what when you say that you
like it because no because i also like
do that
the whole time in my streams oh really
yeah but now that i got my ghost alarm
the noise guy doesn't pick it up anymore
so everyone's like super disappointed
they can't hear my cracks at all
yeah it's like when my my my uh
deadbeats can't hear a ghost rider
anymore
even though i can hear ghost rider he's
always there in my heart but no one else
can hear ghosts in your height
well yeah i mean he was a very important
part of my
my neighborhood you know almost a part
of my lore at this point
one more thing then i was like
i was like um i felt like i wanted to
buy
gloves at donkey hotels oh yes gloves so
i picked out one pair of gloves and then
kelly was like oh
maybe maybe i'll get some gloves as well
so she also picked out
a pair of gloves no way and then i
looked at her pair of gloves
and was like ah my pair of gloves i
put mine back and i got the same as hair
so now we got matching gloves
i guess they match not like people will
see because it's not often that we hang
out i'm in the underworld and you're in
other places
yes but separately because it's not like
we haven't not separately we bought it
at the same time right which is that's
the only reason why i'm fine where i'm
fine with it why
i didn't go ahead and get a different
pair because i thought to myself well
it's not like we hang out all the time
so
it's not like people will see me wearing
you're talking very fast right now
i'm just trying to explain because
people might get the wrong idea i'm
going to eat a potato chip because i'm
stressed
out by you this is kind of a weirdly
shaped one
i don't know if i want this one yeah
what
no need to be dressed up
[Music]
actually the reason why we're here
together originally we just wanted to
hang out and eat dinner
but then when we were trying to figure
out scheduling it was like oh you have a
stream after that and i was like oh how
about we just stream together
no i should open you please sure
question go ahead and invite yourself
over to my house
hi you can't you invite him you said oh
yeah
i mean i said it was fine wait let me
get
oh yeah okay i'm getting the discord log
up right now
no you don't need to pull the receipts
i'm pulling the receipts right now i
don't need to
let me see let me see not in front of
the deadbeat
[Music]
i need a drink there
okay so uh let me quote i was like um
uh seventeenth dinner do you have
anything to do that blah blah or
18 if i joined okay i was inviting
myself there but
i told you one party that's them lol and
then he was like
oh my god yeah hey this is amazing let's
do that
okay but you were very excited about it
i probably was drinking something rather
strong at the time
exposed hey listen can we talk about how
you pulled the receipts on yourself for
a minute there okay hold on
you pulled the receipts on yourself you
did kind of invite yourself a little
bit yeah but bad but
you were the one originally saying that
we have to hang out again okay
are you gonna talk about stuff i know
you were the one who wanted to
originally hang out okay
okay there we go hey listen
no you can't shut up no
okay well anyway callie what um i have
thought of something
huh um so i was thinking
we should we need to we need to like i
i think we know each other for a long
time but did we ever
figure out the deep questions about each
other i have
found
couples quiz and i think we should try a
couple of them
not just in a in a sense of you know
couples which are working together
nothing else than that uh-huh
so let's go through that
okay there's a lot of questions so we
can skip a lot of them
all right but i'm gonna ask some this is
like a this is loki like a marshmallow q
a
no because uh people will find out the
questions
that they always wanted to know don't
worry it's not it's actually a pretty
normal question
really it's like knowledge questions
like what do you know about your partner
can we change it to friend yeah totally
shimmy shade that makes you happy hmm
okay you're fine i accept your challenge
because
you do what you must okay so number one
mm-hmm
what food does your part
friend god friends like to cook
okay do you know what i like to cook i
mean i really
recently i really don't cook i really
like around cookbook what do you think
it is
hmm fried chicken because you're tensho
you have a store don't you a restaurant
so you must regularly cook fried chicken
actually i let people cook it for me
okay well let's see how about curry do
you make curry
um i can but i don't okay
top ramen no it's something i offered to
make for you before
oh huh
i offered it to you guys as a thank you
for like helping you
oh wait it's a breakfast
ah wait hold on
french toast yes yes i am
i swear i didn't see i actually didn't i
promise you i didn't see
i'm not looking at the chat listen
listen
how would they know that anyway well
because i talked about you many times oh
you did
oh i i just guessed honestly i guess
for you i would say you probably like to
cook curry that's right that's the only
thing that i know how to make
a kitchen that's the only thing that i
know
how how to make okay next question
okay close close your eyes okay and i
close mine
okay uh what are you gonna do what color
are your partner's eyes oh um
purple and orange and skellington
there's a skull there are skulls inside
okay okay okay
yours are kind of like pink
yes yes okay
all right let's take it let's take a
deep dive into
kusa tori's eyes so that we can really
look at that i know but we're just doing
it again i was correct
okay everyone purple everywhere orange
and
do you want to suck my nose enough of
that enough
enough that we don't do that here we
thought we were doing the whole thing
over again
no not over
it's nothing wait it's not it's a it's a
treatment
to get rid of the the worms in your nose
every time that you say that kiara the
chad just doesn't
it doesn't stop moving
they get excited it's a popular
um facial treat are there really that
many of you out there that want to suck
kiara's nose
apparently yeah really i i don't
i don't i don't i mean i like the idea
of that machine
uh sucking the um don't just don't talk
anymore
sucking the dirt
you can't what is it you're making it
worse you're making it worse
no machines no sucking okay next
question
uh how about
okay which year this is this question is
important for no particular reason okay
would your partner a friend ever want a
long-distance relationship
[Music]
well let's see ah i immediately thought
of what my answer for myself would be
but let me think about you oh yeah like
you're you don't
let me tell me you're unsurprised oh no
no
that would be cheating i have to guess i
have to get yes i have to guess for you
so uh i think you would be fine with it
i i would have to say it depends on the
person
but if it's you then ah
wait
yeah but long distance friendship so
long distance friendship is fine
i i think usually it's gonna be
difficult but
for you i'll do anything in my power to
make it work
i'll fly over there anytime
you can come to the underworld at any
time no matter where you are in the
world
it's very easy you just have to you have
to make a blood circle on the ground
sacrifice a couple human beings uh split
them down the middle
remove the organs and place them in a
certain fashion i can show you the
instructions i'll send it to you later
there's a pdf
there's a pdf and i'll text it to you
later um but yeah you can come down any
time yeah
i'll try yeah for you
i think the same answer
normally it might be difficult but if
it's if it's a long distance
friendship with me then you
you'll be happy to make it work okay
i mean yeah that's more or less correct
it's not something that i've ever had to
think about because i don't care about
things like that
but however you don't care about me
leaving no no that's not what i meant
i mean like the the relationship and
whatever
i don't have time for those things um
but
yeah that's okay kelly
what will you miss me
i mean yeah i'll miss you of course
we've had a lot of great times here
and a lot of adventures that's why we're
going on on a trip and more journeys
more journeys we have more things to do
together so it's not the end or anything
yeah you know
it's not the end adventure time yeah
we're gonna go do fun things
we're gonna go on we're there's still
more journeys to be had so like don't
don't get sad just yet
it's not the end it's not the end yeah
next question how about
how about
are you running into many inappropriate
ones a lot of
interesting questions and i'm not sure
about if you can answer it
like do you have art did you like when
you were as adults
were younger did you have like
like friends in your childhood and are
you still on touch your thumb
let's see not really actually oh i don't
really have
it's interesting because a lot a lot of
friends that i had from a day
um they just kind of stopped talking to
me
and now it's like happening it's normal
though it happens it happens to everyone
but i don't know i feel like maybe if
they see me now
um they don't want to reach out because
that seems um
superficial maybe so they probably feel
a bit awkward
and i don't feel like reaching out
because i guess it's just like life goes
on
death goes on you know
wait are your friends immortal i have
various friends
some that are immortal some whose lives
i've had to have taken myself
wasn't that awkward to take your
friend's life i mean usually people know
if you're if you're immortal you and i i
mean
i don't try to hide who i am uh when we
become friends
they know that yeah they know it's
coming you know they're they're kind of
waiting for it
anticipating and i tell them you need to
wait because you all need to wait
or it won't be me coming for you it'll
be death sensei and that won't be fun
for anyone
yeah but yeah usually people see it
coming i suppose
oh wait we're we're still like loki
answering the questions by ourselves
well i didn't see i didn't hear what the
question was was there even a particular
it's pretty
pretty much um are they still in touch
with any friends from childhood
oh i mean i guess you would probably
know that but it's not like
it's interesting because we don't really
talk about things like that huh yeah
things like like the past and people
that we knew
back back then you know it's kind of
like just now
and like us and what we're doing now
which is cool because you don't need to
spend forever talking with
new friends that you make um or old
friends or or anything
or forever friends like me and kiara um
forever you need to talk you need to
talk about
about things like like the past all the
time it's like the new memories that you
make that are important
right very true yeah although i do like
to get nostalgic every now and then and
think back of my
past memories yeah do you still talk to
people from buckins a day
no they don't
the thing is like every time i got
reborn i get born in a different
dimension
so i can't really get in contact with
them
so yeah it's like they'll just sit but
but the only thing
that's always there and then he stays
with me and i can always go back to his
youth
ah we we do have that kind of
relationship i guess where you don't die
[Music]
death is not so bad just next question
she won't hear it she won't listen to it
if i tell her
we've been through this before
how does your partner feel about having
pets
oh do you want to have pets one day oh
well let me
let me guess for you oh yeah you like
pets
which one you like cats yes yeah yeah
yeah
i've told you many times and i'm gonna
get more cats you want many many cats
yes more cats easy easy easy rock
show for you i feel like i kind of
talked with you about this before
i know you would like that uh-huh i
think you're more
wait a second
no you you also want the cat no
uh-huh yeah you do i love cats yeah you
do you do you do
love them but i just don't know if i can
have them here in the underworld
yeah right here probably not they should
be real
i'm still like lagging i love it
[Laughter]
pets are awesome they're so fluffy cats
are so
lovely and i i like how they
they cats are kind of like you callie
huh because they act
soon huh they're like i didn't care
about you but then then they always like
some they have faces every now and then
when they're like
wow
[Music]
you said two things that are incorrect
they're number one not all cats are
fluffy
some of them don't have fur true number
two not all cats are tsundere
some of them really really want to rev
up on you and be close to you yeah
and meow in your ear all the time
[Music]
really i like mink they're huge yeah
they're big i like
big cats especially the male men clones
are huge
yeah they're so fluffy pink ones are
awesome they have a very
very interesting face structure yeah
i agree with that i like minkows i love
i love candles
fluffy cattles long hair cattles best
kettles huh i would be kidding
[Music]
does your friend consider himself an
introvert or an extrovert
let's see i think you consider yourself
here's what you would say you can act
introverted but you think that you're
actually quite shy
wait you mean you can act extroverted
but you think uh
like here's what here's what i think you
think
about yourself you think that you
can be extroverted yes but
you think you're actually an introvert
you think that you are shy actually got
him
i mean i don't think i am shy you know
you're shy
i know i'm shy and there you go like i
mean
at least like i feel like especially
after so many people
complimented me for the way i behave in
social
uh situations with other people i
realized that i might really be good at
such situations so maybe i am like an
extrovert attractive person
huh that's right i know even though i
always thought i'm like an
internet person but i do handle
situations like that very well
yeah i don't know i feel like even if
we're in a room
um or in a situation with people that
that feel like they're out of place or
awkward or they don't know what to say
or they're shy
because you are there um it's like no
problem and it doesn't feel
it doesn't feel awkward because you're
so cheerful and you always come up with
something to say
yeah thank you it keeps the mood light
yeah that's just because i hate
awkward silence so much yeah me too i
tried to get rid of it
by like any any method really
i just make up random to talk about
the way that i deal with awkward silence
is i pretend like it doesn't exist
because here's the thing
my motto is this it's only awkward
if you make it awkward and if you think
it's awkward otherwise i don't really
care if i'm silent and doing my own
thing i don't feel awkward at all i only
feel awkward if you're like this awkward
and then i'm like all right well you
just made it up i mean with you
it depends on the person if it was
revealed then i don't mind it being
silent
but if it's with like strangers then i
feel like i have to help them because i
don't want them to feel awkward
even if i don't mind i don't want them
to feel awkward so i will help them to
not feel awkward
it's a sense of obligation it does maybe
make me an extrovert but not like the
extra word who
who likes to go to disco and party party
party party
i already do that kind of stuff i don't
like that i don't like that at all
but i'm like an extrovert who can handle
social considerations
so for you what do you think
probably this like you probably think of
yourself as an introvert as well
yes i know i'm an introvert but i do
also think you
handle things also quite well like it's
almost like an extrovert yeah
i feel like um i i have social skills
in fact in fact a nickname that i've
come up with myself
for come up with for of myself of myself
is i don't know how to
speak uh no hold on wait nickname
gennakte
i don't know uh what am i trying to say
maybe it is a nickname
i thought for myself it's calliope nori
for kalayapinorinori
because i'm nori nori in many situations
ah
even even if i'm talking to people that
i don't know i know what to say but
here's the thing
i won't approach you if you approach me
and talk to me then it's fine and it's
not an awkward or weird situation at all
because i can handle social situations
but i won't approach you first
and i like to be by myself unless people
approach me and then i will talk to you
it's like that if you take my advice
yeah and you keep punching every time i
say
every freaking time anyway yeah that's
how it is
i see that kind of oh god he's like a
bunch of
questions about some more intimate acts
skip them skip them skip them skip them
skip them oh yeah i mean
seaweed no it's not that kind of the
reason
because nor because nori seaweed flows
with the ocean
it flows with the motion of the ocean so
nori nori comes from the seaweed thing
hey i know a couple things about
japanese language listen
let's take it doesn't really come from
that it does
nori is seaweed and when it flows with
the ocean
doesn't really come from seaweed it
comes from the word
from the
but i like your explanation too because
the naughty is also riding on the on the
ocean basically
yeah it
did you see that my chat is infected
sometimes yeah
through the greenhouse your shrek
infection
uh swamped me over oh yeah that's a nice
choice of words how do you cure it
kiana how do you cure a shrek infection
i was like the thing is i had a i had a
fire and blame stream the other day and
for a thumbnail i colored my hair green
oh my god for reasons that i related to
the game
but then i noticed that all those green
hearts are coming to my chest
what the is going on and they're
like now they're out from from cali
and i'm like thank you i love shrek oh
no i spread the infection dude
yeah i oh yeah by the way we've decided
that we are going to marathon shrek one
and two together with you guys
yeah i hope that after that the shrek
infection can be cured
it's like a ritual to like be worse
after that
no it won't it's a it's a ritual it's
like hair of the dog have you ever heard
of hair of the dog
after you drink after you drink a ton of
alcohol they say that the next day to
cure the hangover
you drink more alcohol and it makes it
go away or it makes it feel a little
better
well what if we what if we do hair of
the shrek
where we watch a little bit the dog is
the process of drinking to feel better
after a hangover yes
because think about it when you wake up
when you wake up in the morning
feeling like p diddy
i was about to play it off so smooth and
normal
[Music]
no
your body says oh no all of that alcohol
from the previous night is gone
um it has a deficiency of alcohol
your body feels like oh no where's the
alcohol i had before and it panics it's
like oh gosh i i need
i need what we had before it that is now
lost
and so if you drink a little alcohol it
makes you feel
better for a little while so what if we
do that with shrek
what if it cures the infection
well let's try that theory i mean i
guess we might as well
what if it's only great it's not about
curing the infection i just want to
watch track so you like shrek beyond the
meme
you you you like it unironically i love
the movies yeah
that's very special there was that's
very
i love this kind of sweet i especially
love when they sing hallelujah
i know you're right your feelings are i
understand
okay i can't wait to watch recognition
kelly kelly
you have brought this upon yourself no i
am
by singing shrek songs in you kinda
looking it's
your fault they they asked me to
so nicely the deadbeats asked me so
nicely
i think it's it's great to give them
that's
them apparently apparently some some
people were upset that i
that i was being very silly with holding
out for a hero
they didn't like that i was being silly
with it and many people were saying
you should sing the song seriously then
i thought to myself
never not on your life that was so fun
being super goofy
by the way kelly what you wanted to tell
me a story
oh gosh she heard about that tell me
about the story she was she was like
while we were eating
she was like i want to tell you
something i really want to tell you
something i'm going to wait until the
stream to tell it to you
uh no what is it
it's not even that hype of a story it's
actually an embarrassing story and i
feel bad even telling it
but it's about our trip yeah i started
to tell this story during my
my minecraft and then of course the
demons came and sabotaged my pc right
when i was
yes so i yes i know ah sorry
the dead beats came and they told you
about it whoa jeez
anyway i'm sorry um yeah so
basically i was just i was telling the
chat that i was doing the planning for
our trip
right um and how i mean
bakken's a day right i'm sure that you
also are in the same situation where
when going on trips you just stay in
whatever cheap hotel you can find
oh yes the cheapest of the team right
with like the wii
the the wii tennis playing couples
yes towels maybe aren't even included
exactly and it's
and it's that's what you get for for 10
to 15 dollars a night oh yeah oh yeah
just the most premium service really and
by that i'm exaggerating that's not what
you get
um you know cucarachas dancing on the
floor
that's a nice extra kakarashi dancing
show
what a beautiful extra amenity that you
can get at some of these hostels
you stay in any place that you can find
did you book a hostel
no no no no the opposite the opposite
thank god i was think i was thinking to
myself right
well you know kusa today you and i have
paid our dues right
we've stayed in our fair share of just
really kind of
ratchet places right just just the just
the lowest of the low i mean i still
play in a ratchet place i have a mouse
in my ceiling oh yeah
that is the word upon the street is it
not i mean
cast my wimp yeah yeah
hey big ups too and shout outs to casper
please do
please don't go into cusa tony's house
anymore ceiling
is fine during the the chilly winter
times but yeah
anyway so i thought i thought to myself
you know how about this time
how about this time we stay in like a
really nice place
yeah like um like a premium quality and
not just decent like
like like the best of the best and in
fact i thought
why don't i take it a step further and
why don't i just pay for everything
oh wow why don't i make it a present to
kusatori because
think about it think about it this way
right chad you all like to send me those
those uh ridiculous messages
yeah that say like oh get married here's
for your wedding what am i supposed to
do with those
i can't use that on a wedding that's
never going to happen right
hey don't act sad listen
listen i figured listen
at this moment in time we know that's
not going it's okay i'm confident i
don't want i it's okay you can keep on
talking like that i know
anyway so yeah so i thought that i would
i thought i'd put that to good use
right um and i thought let's let's get
us a really nice place
for our trip our trip to somewhere far
away
where we can enjoy many things that no
one will hear about until after it's
over
but but i went and i did some digging
because i'm good at finding
good places to stay oh and i found i
i went and i looked specifically for
five star places
yes i looked for a five-star hotel and i
found in the area that we're going to
the best of the best
yes i found i found the best of the best
and i was feeling i was feeling rather
rather um oh there we go
no no let me tell the story let me tell
the story that
here they go let me just tell it i went
and i looked
and i went on their site and i thought
to myself you know what
let i want to go crazy with kusatori
and i want to just get something nutso
once in a lifetime crazy
so i go and i look and i find i try to
find out how much the penthouse is
yeah yeah i go and i look at the
penthouse okay just for fun that's how
it always
starts right you're like oh i'll just go
look for fun and then
so you can just like the presidential
scenes yeah well yeah of course i looked
at all of them oh my gosh
all of this so so here's the thing so i
went and i looked
i looked at the penthouse suite and i
now as i read the price
i was reading through all the prices of
the rooms and i thought to myself
okay this is pretty reasonable and i
look at the pen how sweet and i
i say i say to myself okay about three
thousand dollars usd for a night okay
that's like a once in a lifetime kind of
thing that you do
you enjoy you enjoy that kind of place
three thousand dollars that's
not necessary
no no listen listen listen i thought to
myself why not just for just for one
night
just for one we just we just let
ourselves be
uh stupidly luxurious just for once
you and me oh okay we get we get we get
to be queens
yeah just for just for one moment so so
i go ahead and i reserve it for us
okay and i'm super excited and i
immediately receive an email
from the hotel staff themselves and they
they say
they say to me oh miss mori we're so
excited to welcome you and your
companion
to our hotel we're very excited yeah
yeah companion i guess i mean that's
what we are a companion
so so so they say if there's anything
that we can do any kind of accommodation
uh let us know in fact we'll arrange a
car for you
and i say wow really a car they say yes
we will pick you up from from the
airport and take you to our hotel
and and the airport is far from the
hotel and i say to myself wow
they really are going out of their way
and then and then
they they go ahead and they offer they
offer all of this free stuff
right they say they say would you like
would you like to visit our sounds like
a scam to me well that's what i thought
too but all the reviews said that it's
legitimate
so they start saying things like okay
we'll prepare a special meal they're
like we're having
a deal going on for this particular room
at this time we'll bring you your five
course meal and a bottle of champagne
and i say can i have children's
champagne that's
fine we could ask them for that so i say
well yes certainly that that sounds
fantastic and and they say in fact
to celebrate your special stay will
bring you a cake what would you like the
message to say for your companion
and i say is that really necessarily
like well we'll bring in a christmas
tree and i'm like but it's not even
it's going to be far away from christmas
and so i clarified that if i say it
we're not coming at that time they say
oh our apologies
oh our apologies we seem to that's what
i thought so too
right so they so that we get all this
stuff going on
and i get i get i start getting personal
messages
from from the person who is who is the
head of reservations
and i say here's my personal email if
you need anything you let us know and we
are at your disposal
that is what they said we are at your
disposal now i start getting a strange
feeling in my tummy because i'm like hmm
this seems very odd that all these nice
things are happening
so i go ahead and i start speaking to
the the head of reservations and they
say
all right well are you are you ready to
to pay now and i think to myself well
you know what
i don't want kusa toity to know that i'm
spending this much money on her
right so i don't want her to know how
much it costs so i say okay let's go
ahead and settle it now and so
they say we will need we will need these
pictures of your your credit card and
and your underworldian id as well
we need all we need all of this
information i don't have a credit card
well see that's the thing is i thought
okay well that's i mean that's that's
interesting but again i checked with
legitimate legitimacy of the hotel and
it's a five-star place and all the
reviews are glowing so i think okay
this isn't fake i guess that's true but
it's it's a renowned place
and so i go ahead i go ahead and um
and i sent i send them all of the
information they say excellent
uh our accounting team is ready to go
ahead and verify and verify all of this
information actually that is legit yeah
so they say we're going to go ahead and
charge the card and i say fantastic
and i see here once again is your total
and so i go ahead and i check over the
total again and i say okay this sounds
right
and then and then i stop for a minute
i'm like you know what let's just go
ahead and make sure like i always do
that i'm reading the price correctly oh
now as you may know deadbeats
this was going to be a place that i was
going to pay for it in japanese yen
right they're a little confusing
aren't they so i go ahead i go ahead
and i put my little finger over the last
two zeros
and i realized something different
i realized that the penthouse is not
three thousand dollars
the penthouse for one night is thirty
thousand dollars
for one night for one night
no i no i wasn't that's
as i mentioned i am a special brand of
not so bright
listen and i felt terrible because we
had been emailing back and forth for
about
two weeks of them making special
accommodations for us
[Music]
that's what i mean that's what i said i
said how embarrassing is that
that i read that i have to say them hey
i read the price wrong
you said sorry um i found the
presidential suite in a different hotel
yeah
yeah they only charge fifteen thousand
dollars a night for the president
you gotta say that they charge more and
that's better for you
oh that's right because now i've
revealed myself to be a dirty peasant
question mark you're a millionaire today
in order to not make the situation
embarrassing embarrassing you gotta say
i found the presidential suite for a
hundred thousand dollars per night
in a different hotel so i'm going there
no thank you no chief
i mean i guess i guess that's one that's
one way that you could do it
but i already kind of i messed up and i
said excuse me i read the price
list listen there is no there was no
they were very cool about it
okay they said understood no worries if
there's anything else we can do for you
if you'd like to downgrade to one of our
five thousand dollar rooms let us
know five thousand dollars is economy
yeah economy class
no but i mean here's the thing
what kind of hotel is that a
very fancy one
listen you do not spend thirty thousand
dollars on a
hotel room for one night that
it's a matter it's a matter of ethics
it's just a
i would never be i would go to sleep and
i'd feel sick to my stomach
you can buy 10 second hand cards with
forty thousand dollars yeah i mean in
some cases for for some people you could
pay rent for like five years with that
oh my god or more
it's just the principle of the the
penthouse no no penthouse fund we're not
getting we're not getting the 30
thousand dollar penthouse definitely not
i would feel bad about that i wouldn't
be able to sleep kiara
i wouldn't be able to freaking sleep
if you pay so much for a hotel room i
think
they um accept it if you trash the hotel
room like a rock star
oh that's true i think we kind of want
to do that eventually don't we
yes but not for 30 thousand
but yeah i'm gonna trash a hotel room
that only costs five thousand dollars
that's not gonna happen
oh god you gotta pay extra for that you
know what i think
i think in the end we're we're cool
staying in a room
where there's a couple playing wii
tennis next door and there are
cockroaches on
just kidding i'm not just kidding let's
just stand up
let's just stay in the middle a nice
middle ground just
let's just be normal yeah
i think it's okay i i really don't need
a penthouse sweet i'm happy if i just
have you
in this in i mean yeah in the same hotel
okay
i mean definitely with twin beds with
twin beds
okay no no nope you won't do that
just how i did it in minecraft that
makes me laugh yes but in minecraft it
doesn't require any actual strength it
requires two mouse clicks
but i mean okay one question if i would
have
stayed over tonight where would you have
asked me to sleep
couch oh well no i would have taken the
couch and you could take the belt oh wow
that's you that that is usually how i
how i used to do it
a day when i have instant
listen when other when other gal pals
would come over to
sleep i'd always let him sleep on to bed
and i sleep on the couch
that's just what you do it's it's called
being a good host
being a good host yeah i do
i i was thinking about staying over
because you also kind of
didn't seem like you hate the idea
because we also have a collab at 10 a.m
like the night like one night after this
collab
so you have to get up so early and i
know that you don't like doing that
yeah but the thing is right after that
we have the halloween collab
for everyone who doesn't know so that
might have been stressful to go home
after the way out collabs and then run
to the
uh other collab you know that's true
yeah okay how about
we vacuum clean your nose now
we have 10 minutes left let's test out
this object
i'm scared
no it's vacuuming my nose doesn't have
anything in it no
here's something you can see for
yourself zoom in on your nose zoom in on
your nose
all right let's zoom in on my nose
everyone let me know if it works hold on
let's see the legs
vacuum cleaner oh jeez all right chad
here we go hold on let me see if can you
hear it
i'm really doing this huh okay this is
oh gosh wait is it hang on is it
actually it's barely sucking hold on oh
oh there we go
there we go oh my gosh whoa yeah
it's working but how do i move how am i
supposed to
okay okay hold on i don't think you're
supposed to move it maybe
you just leave it there right and then
and then pull it away
probably okay and then go to the next
spot
i don't think it's getting anything my
nose is too clean
hold on hold on here we'll go to the
next spot
i feel like you have to move it though
or else the suction won't work
hang on read your instructions on the
vacuum oh okay i mean
yeah you need to go get the packaging
for it i may have disposed of it hold on
huh how
wait oh is it are you gonna start
working now
i don't vacuum too deep you might get
your brain
[Music]
are you gonna work for me now it might
be working i'm not sure
okay oh just uh put the thing together
step two after you blast your things
and uh get rid of the the obvious dirt
[Music]
oh you have to ah you have to you have
to like
um wash your face with hot water so that
your pores open in the first place oh
okay
and then the third step is
[Music]
don't make noises like that when this is
next to the microphone
ah only using like one
not longer than one minute on your nose
apparently in total but
um should i go wash my face you're not
supposed to move it around oh you don't
move
like pull it away oh you pull it away
well let me go wash my face really
excitedly
well yes i i want to do it properly for
the time being though you can look at
kusatori
hi here because the toy entertain them
while i go wash my face
i'm trying hard to not say what i
already said don't be weird
how can i not be weird don't make it
weird
[Music]
she didn't hear that she's watching her
face for real
she's washing her face yo
that beats what up when i'm that means
let me rap for you
let me rap on you uh
i don't like me when she's when she's
there
um where the on the livings
[Music]
oh my god those are translated to some
other language
there we go
oh and she might i'm not moving
she's probably gonna come back soon a
little faster lyrics
oh yeah
oh god this is without music this is
weird though
but the machine is still on what
oh yeah modern day kids really must hate
fun more of the people taking lives
recognizing us the real murder
connoisseurs in the rural japan got used
to learning in the audience
as long as i was cause to my surprise
that you might have stolen the kitchen i
strive to stop in the da
vinci of human erasure can't stop the
pastor make sure i'm standing off my
rhyme slave first
jealous haters out there high five i see
you no one's gonna buy this i
believe you cuz i'll have in a literal
sense it really pretends but the viewers
are all talented
don't mean none of the queen of fighters
another super radical toys this is your
hundred part at the scene still the
killer of your dreams
flip your souls to my bucket and
definitely the scene you find that
are my lyrics really on that site oh
they were everywhere
i also found like a really translated
one a weirdly translated one
oh look at them vibing your pores open
uh probably
maybe there you go there's your machine
you're sucking all right
jeez okay here we go hold on
if it's gonna work i wanna buy it too
all right
you're the tester you're the test i am i
don't see your nose
hold on there you go
pull it away okay i'm pulling it away oh
my god the luring sign is super chat
oh yeah the riverside view always gives
me songs to sing
thank you during super chat reading
how nice of him it's pretty dope so this
time it's hinotory but without rainbows
hang on here is it working
i just can't i love how you're just like
oh yeah this is normal he does it always
yeah i mean he just sends me some lyrics
to sing yeah you know it was just a
rainbow
it's always but it's always
i'm not trying to actually move it
around but when i pull it away it ends
up moving around
yeah that's fine i think hold on hang on
let me make it more powerful
there we go all right we'll start off
we'll start off at the low
[Music]
it's gonna pull my nose off hang on
it's gonna pull my nose off it's a
machine
hang on
i felt that i felt that
yeah on the tip just the hang on don't
say
no no
no hold on we're having a beauty session
here
ah this i don't know if it works or not
my nose is just too clean
i see you don't even have breathing
holes so
i mean yeah this is how it is i mean
the nose holes
[Music]
i don't i don't think it's gonna work on
me
my nose is just too clean i don't i
don't know
i don't know what else to say either
that or it's just not a good product
kind of got it i gotta give it like a a
one out of ten although
from what i've read because girls can go
crazy over like
having clean pores and stuff but i've
read it's normal to have in your
pores
oh yes normally it's absolutely normal i
think that's a part of being what is
called a human
yeah it's just it's healthy to produce
yeah i think that if you didn't uh if if
you if you didn't do things
um like like sweat and whatnot you would
uh you would perish you would die i
would know i'm the person that knows
that so everyone don't worry about it
don't don't
don't buy the product unless we get
sponsored then we will ask you to buy
the product yes yes at that time we will
ask you until then please hold on to
your your saifu's
your your oh saifu's please well then
i think dad
is probably about time for me
to say goodbye but i'll see you on the
way out collab
okay yeah yep oh i'll be there
wow that went by really fast oh yeah we
have to do it again next time i'll sleep
over for real
and we will watch shrek together oh yes
the the shrek mm-hmm
oh my god you're really
i love excited oh it's so sweet but i
always used to watch
wrapking german do you want to watch
shrek in german i mean
chad if you want to watch shrek in
german with english
oh i love the donkey
yeah eddie murphy what that's that's not
that's not his name yes that's his name
it's the name of the donkey character
it's just a voice actor
no his name is eddie stop me me i'm not
meaning
that's what his name is it actually is
no
it's not of course it isn't
which means
oh well i could never be mad at you
i guess not all right i better show you
to the door
um can you you know do the thing one
thing
get me
oh yeah yeah yeah
yes i will help you and then i heard you
were going to read super chat i'm
reading
everybody everyone don't leave uh listen
to her super jets yes
you can go to champions for me one
yes just let me turn off the thing
really quick because
when people hear super chat reading they
get real
they get real excited and want to send
the super chat in the last minute
which is very sweet which is very oh my
god i'm so
zoomed out how did that happen wait hold
on
in exactly ten hours from now we have
a way out part two collab on my channel
this time it was first time on her
channel
and now it's on my channel so if you
want to watch the continuation yeah see
you in 10 hours
come watch it i can't zoom in it you
know
press shift okay and then zoom in
it's not working maybe it was cdrl ctrl
oh my god that scared me so much
too late dad k walk
hold on no
and then they send the stickers because
i always put you on nuts
stop stop it quick
roll up pull the bridge the castle of
the bridge and they send the super
stickers because they know what yeah
hold on let me see where's my kazoo
let me pull it out i'll find it here it
is
there we go all right here we go i love
it i love
it oh it looks exactly like oh my god
all right everyone get your glow sticks
out here we go
that's not it no i'm doing it from the
intro but it's fun we'll do it from the
[Music]
verse
oh
uh
okay
oh my god that was very passionate yeah
i
i i put my all into the instruments that
i play so
amazing i'm glad that you enjoyed it
i want to give you some money for that
no don't
don't do that don't do that i'll buy you
a penthouse
yeah and how sweet hell yeah oh my
goodness yeah just one that's not there
yeah
yeah okay it's time for you to get out
of my house only because i know that you
you need to get home yes so i will show
you out the door but until then
deadbeats i'm your more i hope you
remember me sign off kiara
i'll be dancing goodbye
thank you for having me i enjoyed it
yeah that was fun
uh the way out collab as kia as kiara
said is on
her channel tomorrow ten hours from now
yes ten hours
yes yes so go go to kiara's go to
kiara's channel
please it will be fun part two we just
last night we literally just got out of
the prison but apparently we still have
to like yep do more
yep we just played shawshank in the
middle now yep even though we're already
outside so i'm really curious as to what
happens next
yeah me too i'm excited to watch it all
unfold so please go check it out
everyone
whoa yeah anyway we'll catch you on the
flip side
bye see ya
that was pretty good super chat people
see you soon by the way
see you soon
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
so
has left the building and and it is time
to
to read some supers
it's time to read some supers dead beats
i wonder what i want i wonder what will
be the instrument of choice
oh that's right there's no more light
anymore oh it's faded away
what a shame because latoya is gone
let's see no more hashtag takamori let
me go ahead and throw out the tea
it's gone all right there we go ah
and then i'm gonna sleep but first
first i want to i want to thank my my
deadbeats let me throw the hang on
there's a pillow here
i want to throw it out really quick
why is this labeled as iced tea
[Music]
just cleaning up i'm just cleaning i'm
doing a little doing a little house
cleaning deadbeats just a moment
[Music]
we please have the kazoo out but i don't
really want to use the kazoo
let's use um we used harmonica last time
so how about the good old-fashioned
recorder
deadbeats does that sound okay i'm
definitely okay at playing the recorder
so we'll use that for the super chat
reading hold on let me ah
super chat time super chat reading
and we will be doing the ones also from
the minecraft stream that got destroyed
by the demons
yay all right
where's my recorder i found it not the
potato chips
stay over there all right
let's go down the list here we go
big ups too wyatt c luke
and girl jane rude
okay moby thank you so much for the akka
they say
nice icon movie i always appreciate it
and a big ups of v twisty thank you for
the aca super chats go burr
b toy ski that's the dude thank you big
ups to kinko sagan
flynn k walk lord revan
a sweaty olympia lunchbox
deadbeat cranston
skyraven hk elias
he won dragons
for the child
send off war
she sews the gandra
raron the lone wolf
resolute josh k
times 2.
goose rhys balls
kfp legal drone
thorium 220
spywee krama chaos
garrow arigato gozaimasu
calling cash quest
phonetics tentacled
riverside view with the hino tory cover
am i really going to sing at this stream
i'll do it at the end i'll sing it at
the end
okay how about that we'll save it for
big ups to near trill 98
rkzm 2012.
tentacles seven three three six gt
ragin you be you be
ya bye
clown clown cork
make it weird oh no v toys you can't do
that around these parts
big ups designers you must consume
math pudding sg
bun thank you for the akka super
here's hoping the four star deluxe
chicken coop was reasonably priced
i hope so too i hope so too sg bun
me as well
big of zoo no elena
demi urgos
tag thanks for the aqua spa don't vacuum
too deep you might get your brain that's
a great point storm tag i gotta say
thank you kindly
96 tax
you shallow hell hawk
i like that name in this accident hell
hulk
god i need something to drink hold on a
minute
just just another sip really just one
more sip to make it through where are
the ones
i left it on the kitchen table one
moment please
i got it
wow my desk it has so much stuff on it
since crystal tony left
all of her things around
it's fine we will we will just we will
soji later which means we will clean
later
anyway where was i what accent
moto account name
rafa it's a roving zero
kaijudo spartan
[Music]
wolfy 1012.
kingsley sang a.g
pavan sakharana
haneki duo zero thank you so much for
the aca spa
message received we got you dad thanks
duo zero
glad you got my back big ups tube
kazuna vulvarak
zach and tilla great apple
oh country gamer okusan man
thank you for the aka spock takamori
penthouse fun no no no no penthouse for
us
big ups too anime not
f i can't read this it's in russian but
thank you very much a privet
uh pick up soup pico
sweet gug camilla noah drake
a.g prom
drop the vault patrick chen kfp barista
thank you to everyone from kfp who came
to join us
sakura kimmy technical 7336
billy shinjikun slim stats
andrew perrin little prince
english kriegsman 404 error
small brain thank you for the akasupa
they say companion in quotation marks
i don't know what that means when you
say that and why you put it in quotation
marks but yes i do believe that i
use the word companion that is correct
and big ups decay brother aurelion small
kaio amber jack
key shooter cameron drafty
thank you very much for the akka spa but
the store is the penthouse suite y'all
earned no penthouse for us but thank you
i will use that for our vacation
let's see uh ramon lopez
it's a mystery mammal dude where's the
pizza sama i like i like your your
profile picture with
i think that's danny devito
big up to philip
pick up the coffee addict
moto account name that is a huge akka
spa
big loves to callipi and deadbeats from
sister fandom
nautical kfp contribution to homeymoon
thank you very much i appreciate it
arigato gozaimasu
tag thank you for the ah it's okay kelly
we know you just want to subconsciously
be an excellent provider for kiara it's
adorable
i don't know what you mean by that storm
tag but thank you kindly for the sweet
words of encouragement
and the lovely akka spy here's your tune
from my recorder to your ear holes
thank you big ups 2 dr chang kfp
sacrificial i can't read the rest of
this it's cut off
maybe i don't want to know what it says
thank you
she's so stagna
side rack
dra ringy thanks for them fours why am i
not moving
let me move my camera there we go now
we're cooking
big ups kfp cultured i can't read the
rest but maybe i don't want to
soseji bhuto
kfp deadbeat thank you very much for the
red
super here's a little something for your
honeymoon
i don't know what to say about that but
thank you very kindly for the akkas
sorry big ups decay
it's change one game
camera strategy generous
duo zero javier
yes yes yes tentacle seven
three three six demi
ergos pico
sky shield nine claw
tiger sure exorcism
i like that we're going to use that in
the future shrek shrek
shrek shaxter says black rose of storm
fans of fish erenius
sir fanny fancy maths
tentacle 7336
kaijudo spartan nemu
javier rodriguez v
toyski thank you very kindly for the
akka spa
but i don't necessarily appreciate the
green heart
vitoysky can't
big ups too i can't read this i think it
says helen de leof
lock kfp scrub instruction
big ups to sand javier ghost reaper 100
100. thank you very kindly
steven sunday she saw gaundra thank you
very much for the akka spa
it's almost the new year any new
resolutions or goals for 2021
ragdoll cats are very affectionate i
love ragdoll cats jesus
i love them
also i don't really make new year's
resolutions because i never really did
them in the past so
i just strive to be as good as i can
possibly be you know
instead of letting myself get let down
at the end of the year i just make a
a general a general promise to try a
little harder yeah
do something important big ups dark rod
dragon
nathan thank you very much for the
akaspa
official hinotory duet when how's the
homie moon planning going planning to
share spa day a hotel room a bed
uh funny face emoji i hope you both have
a great time
you deserve the rest especially you
callie you need to f wording sleep
i agree with that last part i do uh
because
tony and i will be sharing a hotel room
your uh your predictions were correct
about that
official hinator do what we want to do
we want to do a karaoke stream together
eventually so
probably at that time check it yeah
let's see big ups saying sang witness
reborn
navigated camera strategy
right kfp worker drone
betalex the kfp dumpster
big richie walk
nicodem
slick otter nin
mb737 thank you very much for the akka
spa no message
chad
thank you because to you be you be a bye
sand lord drag surprise
kevin lynn coffee powered robot
cyrat kfp worker drone lunchbox
serenity space thank you very much for
the akka spa hello cliff you love
watching as always
i'm getting a large model skeleton for
christmas this year i'm a med student it
makes sense to work
and felt you'd be the best to ask for a
name for it name to give it what do you
think
um let's see uh ghost rider
the mr bones and mr funny bones
oh it's a combination of funny men and
funny bones
yeah in memoration in in memoration
that's not a real word
deadbeats in commemoration in loving
memory of our funny man
who has since passed on yeah
name him funny man or mr funny bones
yeah or just just mr skrellington is
good
or mr skirlington if you feel fancy
best of luck to you serenity space do
your best
big ups 2 chulip z master 7-7
kevin lynn luke wilkins purple citizen
fried p k
navy boy
kayo amber kawaii kawaii kos kfp bell
polisher i think
the cheese gamer tone of bones or
tony bones cross star
kingdom sakura kemi shuzo
who says thank you for the crack i don't
know what you mean by that but thank you
pick up s17b32
pulmo murray dude wild nexus kfp eva
unit zero zero the return of tony bones
hey tony bones i'm sorry every time i
get
name is too good tony returns
i'm sorry
big ups to mari dude
sorry i already read these wild nexus
kfp every unit zero zero
jazz q v vgamer311
lord drac iskander relands
kenji jesse reason
duo zero thank you for the ah swerve yo
sanji sean i can't read
this name but the kanji for for child
and the
and the kanji for i think uh ruler is
there
like not as in the the instrument for
measuring but like a king
says
but thank you big ups to
ryu 18.
otp what's that big ups to shiloh xyz
ordeal
razzie razzie project zero zero
seven kamchatka shrimp
pt brown one two one elephant
kfp ash collector slick otter
banuka
nice to see two best friends hanging out
together again thank you as always
makeups across star kingdom junkie kuma
arty chan sanji a-a-a-b-b-b-c
286 200 thank you for the awkward spa
again sakamori hype train
yeah huh big ups to luke
judgment cazzy 39 thank you for the akka
spa
murray hype
there's hate headtaker21 gonna join you
on this one ghost rider enjoy the stream
people thank you
thanks for joining ghostrider i always
worry about ghostwriter getting a bit
lonely
uh in the pre-chat with the supers but
that's very kind of you
let's see ghost rider how many one two
three
four five six seven eight
interrupted by bloop the shark 9 10 11
12 13
14 15 16 17 18 19 oh my god
ghost rider
that's so kind i bet if you add all
those up that actually is like
a spot
thank you as always ghost rider porigari
any recommendations on hotels with no
way to cool i'm good but thank you
i'm going to go ahead and read the
minecraft supers as well
big ups to king ko sagan ah yes this is
when the stream crashed
jt mations steadfast waiter
kinco sagan 404 error zachary moody
luke killer 11 relens
nigero twerp knight
s404 awesome raptor 21
rough times zealand gold dart the
graveyard
oh my god and
and malachite jessica
malachite whack
eric pj davis typhon kfp legal drone
palace elite flynn pierce
ciron oblitery 2
azn for rife punished
nimu 9-0 404 error
noms whack zachary moody thank you for
the akaspa
hi cali i always love seeing your vids
and your songs miss reaper thank you
very much zachary moody here's your tune
on my recorder
reading the chat operator o20 says what
the hell is this the best recorder
concert you've ever heard sir
my ears lol that's right they feel great
don't they
next up let's see
big ups too dr chang kfp sacrificial
something or another
space guy rye bunny bear fish
you stuffy joe
hidden in the truth kiwi dude seal it
gold
saralex frodo
matthew mcchesney artie chan stuffy joe
shadow demon kokonaka
el swoos space guy rai
miso x and g
da o4 kransu
kfp legal drone kenjiro beat sparta
prowess
kyle of bones thanks kyle of bones i
really appreciate the akka super
i read this message i'm glad you're
playing minecraft don't say you're bad
at games
i just naturally attract death to me
that is true kyle of bones thank you
i appreciate it make ups too fubai ky
kyo amber zealot gold acosta's glade
choppin stuffy gel blue line 48
soy so skander loaded
poor porpoise furudo
bincho the great sean r
armed with wings exponent tie
claro big bouncy bob
lalo mars
big bouncy pop times three more
singing a rick roll may you rest in
peace
his name is boing boing bob
some big upstream phonetics jag bone
thinos maximum turtle
oh there's two more one two for big
bouncy bob because the waiter
darth griffius
kailyn sanders kenjiro beat blue sparks
5'4 oh here's another red block thank
you very much blue sparks
[Music]
i hope you enjoyed your tune blue sparks
54l big obstacle fgh
magic fish shadow demon s c
k thank you very much for the aqua super
here i have a red super chat instead
hopefully this will
fill in for those red blocks you need
i'm good i'm good
thank you kindly though
i'm definitely going to wake up the
neighboring demons but it's fine it's
worth it i want to give you the good
tunes
big ups to kenjiro beat lieutenant
colonel dagura chaff
a waste of company resources in time i
don't know about that one waiter
pick up some jag bone caleb lip
toshi thank you very much wow your first
super i'm honored
big ups to luna palace elite cyber dance
mari dude
cyber dance and then i'm going to
quickly read
some of these hold on blue sparks 540
nicodem
kenjiro beat the last airbender you she
blew sparks and
howie howie i think that was when i i
went i went to get the ping pong
when i got the tasty curry pick up
senando blue sparks
exponent thai thank you very much
and heart c now back to the ones
sakuna demon seal sierra fumey ky blue
sparks by for o kinko
sagan korantz andy luke damon seal from
a ky rectangle
sweaty lumpia alex mh nico
cappeller
kikeru violet s fixer darth griffius
insufficiently anonymous claro
lieutenant colonel de guricha
jumpe iori ace detective you're the man
kelly
lucitan stuffy joe fixer
loop the shark jay kim
slick otter darth griffius
zero aziz reijan kinko sagan
small potato 210 hikami
jake jacob eledron
exponent thai unstoppable phoenix bloop
the shark
okay and ghost a writer one two three
four five six seven eight nine
ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen oh
my gosh
thank you very much tori sugarino
it's like every stream he's here in the
beginning for every single how does he
do it
that's all now i'm gonna very quickly do
a little acapella of hinatori but i'm
probably going to mess it up a lot
because i'm really just not very good at
this song
but i feel bad not doing it so i'm going
to go ahead and try
for all of you and then we're going to
close out this thing because i'm very
sleepy
i'm so sleepy
just a bit of reverb yay
here we go hinotori
[Music]
m
this isn't going to work well i should
get the kazoo and said
there's no time for that
no where were we hold on let's see
if
[Music]
i've been trying to find my destiny i
need to sit up so that
my lungs have room there but they
keep pushing and pulling me astray
if i go wrong what awaits me in the dark
could you tell me please where i need to
go
break it down with the recorder
[Music]
tell me
is this the third verse i think it is
[Music]
blazing flames show me the path to
luminance and in the next life too
i promise i will find you
that's as high as your boy goes
i really want to expand my range but i
just didn't know
it's fine for now i think yeah here we
go that was
i mean i don't mean here we go i mean
here we did it
he natori acapella ah
i'm sleepy
we did it and we read the many super
chats yay
hooray
[Music]
hello i'm gonna fall asleep
because it's a busy day busy day
tomorrow
two collabs wow and i gotta do some
lyric riding
and i gotta wake up early because
there's something else i have to do
anyway thank you everyone for coming to
this big sleeper room
that was something else something else
all right some interesting things happen
[Music]
we had some good conversation and i had
some drankies hold on
but i'm i'm more delirious from being
tired than anything so
i'm gonna eat this tasty chocolate
i really miss this outro i mean i love
dj joe's stuff
and his awesome remix but i also really
miss
this song and envision a place where
everybody's chatting
i know that it's morning time for many
of you so i hope you have a lovely day
take care of yourself for those of you
who are also going to sleep
have some sweet dreams and we'll see you
for a way out
yeah yeah yeah it's at a good time it's
at a prime time for everyone
yeah yeah so that'll be good um
you guys can come and enjoy at a time
that works for more people like this
and it'll be on kusafi's channel check
it don't come here it won't be on my
channel you won't find it there
yeah but look forward to the many things
happening soon
i gotta i gotta go sleep so i can be
ready to do some more work
tomorrow let's enjoy the weekend okay
everyone
i'll catch you on the flip side i hope
you remember me
peace out
[Music]
a song
oh
ah peace
psych priests
you