[Music]
you
do
[Music]
oh
bye
okay hello
[Music]
are you guys excited for the chess match
of rematch
of the century
today we'll be putting our big brains to
the test
with a strictly strategic
game that we have both practice for
right kiara we practice
ah oh yes hello
one more time sorry okay
sorry i had the desktop
like low but not but i'm sorry
[Music]
since cynthia just said um we totally
practiced
i wrote on my twitter last night before
after my last stream i wrote i'm going
to practice chess
now and um after that i have to say i
i binge watched netflix for like five
hours and
uh i woke up uh 30 minutes ago
and played two chess games and still won
okay
yeah i played two quick ones on
chess.com
because uh apparently it's a better
place to play chess apparently
yeah okay so right after i woke up with
my littlest brain cells i
played two chess games and that's about
it
that's more practice than i got because
i i watched like one of those i watched
two videos where i was like
this is how to do some tricks to trap
your enemy and then
the other one was like beginning
beginner tricks for for
chess yeah that's how much i practice
i also someone sent me one video and i
thought it was a serious one it was like
also something about how to do a certain
move to capture
uh the king and but it ended up with
everything
uh being bombed and exploding so that
was not going to help
yeah it's not like you can just flip the
table like a
you know actual chess if you get mad
hold on here i i just need to connect
something really quick
it's important
hell yeah okay that seems familiar i
feel like that happened before
hey team teammates i am
nasty how you guys doing
um it's my it's my actually only my
second time
on this channel i think the first time
was uh
the big collab right i think since then
i've never collab with her on her
channel
last time was uh on my channel did you
all watch the first chess match welcome
back
did you all watch the first time
[Laughter]
welcome back thank you
okay are you ready
i was born ready to play tennis
yes we might we might i think we'll do
we'll see how long this game goes
chess is a game where each
we went to last time you won right
you get to say cheat mate when that
happens so maybe
we want to um like if we only play one
game now
then even if i win it will turn out to
be a draw
so we should play at least uh two games
maybe
yeah that's a good point that is true
yes
uh you know kiara i'll let you go first
this time
oh thank you welcome
i was first in my practice as well by
the way you kind of you played with kuda
so
yeah you get some practice yeah
i feel like it was practice sort of
sounds like going over the basics again
so it's helpful for me
yep yeah you played two games too though
he said what oh i i'm so confused
because at this time i'm looking on my
switch and not on the screen this is
so weird for me i haven't played uh i
don't
really play much in my off time
do you yeah what do i
yeah do you play and you're off time uh
yeah
i i played lake for eight hours straight
yesterday
what i was playing a game on the switch
that i bought
uh that's what i did with all of my time
hey do you always play so much in your
off time uh
no not usual usually i just like sleep
or read
i felt like playing it i feel like
playing something nice and relaxing
[Music]
what did you play uh rune factory four i
think you like it
have you played it you got roon factory
i heard so much about
it yeah it's really good
[Music]
i didn't know you like those kind of
games ah
i wanted some well it has farming and i
wanted to play harvest moon but
uh i i got the new like story of seasons
and it was not exactly what i thought it
would be so it's like kind of
disappointing because
the some harvest moon games like you can
actually explore and stuff
but uh there's not really too much
exploration but in room factory
you can you can go like a lot of places
yeah yeah i actually
uh i don't know if you have seen but
i've been playing uh
sakuna ah ruins on my channel
and it's it's also about farming but
it's like such
such a good farming um no it's
it's about rice farming yeah and it's so
so well made
i really love the style and like some of
the characters like they look so
cute and interesting yeah
it's on the switch i would recommend
that yeah it's on the switch on steam
and i think one other thing
oh you're going for it you're going for
it now
i don't know if it's a good
[Laughter]
i idea know either i have no idea but
actually
oh okay
hurry back horsey
going back to safety
wait um
come on kiara what did you learn out of
two two chest matches on stress.com
where i basically asked uh for
uh hints every other tune
uh i'll tell you one of the tips that i
learned there's like an
acronym it said swat but with an o
and it was like wait what do you stand
for you guys you guys know it's like
uh something weakness opportunity
[Music]
well you guys know what it is they'll
tell you hold on
[Laughter]
it's like it's like a swat analysis yeah
yeah yeah
no no not special weapons you guys know
what it stands for
um strength weakness opportunity and
threat you have to
analyze your strengths of the move
you're gonna make the weaknesses of the
move you're gonna make
what opportunities the move will make
and
how how you can threat or be threatened
i'm always trying to do that
ah i'm always trying
uh well
no you thought it was to be that easy
huh open it i didn't look
did you analyze your weaknesses huh
um no i guess i didn't
this is okay this is okay
[Music]
this is okay ah
if you guys didn't know kiara's doing a
talk show i said
you are already you're already gonna get
that well i don't know what's the time
[Laughter]
i'm trying to distract you
take me take me now
yes do it why why oh i see
i'm not gonna fall for that i'm going
back home
okay it's actually even better that you
noticed because i wanted you to retreat
which wait amelia watson okay i fell
into a trap
about the about the thing that i'm doing
the talk show um yeah i'm i'm doing it
i think uh well i guess for
um thursday yeah for american views i
think
is it first day yeah what no it's
supposed to be like at least friday for
america
wait what i'll tell you right now don't
worry i'll tell you oh no
it is it is friday i think for american
viewers
because it's saturday for me
friday oh yeah i think i was thinking of
something else
ah what do i do i mean
yeah i'm looking forward to that i was
um i was preparing
a lot of things uh some of those things
that i've prepared i will
introduce tomorrow in my announcement
stream already because i do have an
announcement stream tomorrow which
uh amelia is also trying to prepare
something for me but but not the whole
thing right just like a little bit
the whole thing okay
okay okay i can do it i mean it might be
like a rough draft
but uh wait can i go backwards to the
pond
no hahaha goddammit god damn it
i'll not let you go that easily though
um
i think wait i don't know am i
[Music]
this is okay it's okay this is okay
what a coward you are that's what that
was my plan anyways because then if i
took your bishop then i'd lose it to the
queen but i guess that's kind of a good
trade
see as always we're only doing pro moves
wait what i cannot place this piece here
what
oh oh wait there i was in the wrong line
from you no
no no okay i i'm sorry
wait that's the the queen right okay
[Music]
you have barely moved any pawns do you
think that is a wise choice
um i mean i've killed more of your puns
so it's not too bad i guess
yeah that's true
um lane
use your brain kiara somewhere in your
head there is indeed a brain you just
have to use it
you can do it
[Music]
uh
do it i do not
are you are you kidding me there's 32
000 people watching this
[Laughter]
are you kidding me it's okay it's not a
lot of pressure you
you can do it just just use that bird
the big bird brain of yours
prehistoric dodo brain
prehistoric excuse me i have a very
developed big
bird brain okay ah develop
[Music]
quite developed indeed
i'm gonna be easy on me um
you know i'm not you're you're too
good in this perspective
like obviously ah
going for flattery i see
why you sh are you sure you want to go
there oh why not
are you sure about that okay okay well
are you sure about that
are you sure about dad stop
[Music]
okay she was not sure about it
apparently
oh no okay i i i i don't have
i see i don't have as many tools as you
have so i gotta start uh
going on my attack um
however how how will i attack
how how will i
attack you amelia
emma are you looking forward to my talk
show yeah
yeah actually um that was uh
something you know uh i thought would be
a good idea anyways and i think it
really suits you
thank you it's not actually originally
it's not really supposed to be
a talk show it's more like um it's just
supposed to be an interview
but i guess you could call it a talk
show because i mean
we're gonna do a lot of talking yeah
my first guess is going to be maddie oh
wait wait no don't do that no why not
because i don't like it when you do that
ahoy no
no no no
[Music]
no i wanted to show how smart i am today
uh well maybe maybe uh next game maybe
next game will do better
okay but it's not over yet you think
this is over that's not no no
it's not open
better watch yourself
um
sorry my brain was thinking
it's okay you have to think obviously
with such a strong
opponent as me of course you have to
think a little bit stronger than usual
i hope your brain is okay it's going
into overtime
[Music]
i would like uh your king and my queen
to have a special relationship
um i guess i have to do a move on that
yeah that makes sense
i love how people are saying that was a
good move but that was like
the most obvious most basic move and i
was still about to miss it i was still
about to
like not even realize that i can see
that
you learn the patterns the more you play
indeed indeed
no actually i think there's no no
problem
here i think
yeah whatever i think
oh
well i mean i can take you but do i want
to do that
[Music]
because you're gonna take me with that
[Laughter]
[Music]
one
well
[Music]
uh this is a hard one
you can you can
um
oh
[Music]
if you take my horse i'm going to take
your horse and horse
and then that host just sounded like a
i don't know scottish accent or whatever
for a house
house okay yeah post
house what's uh
how how's your accent practice going
it's not going pretty good
if i say so myself
it sounds amazing i'm scottish that's my
origin
much scottish very scottish
you're about as much scottish as you are
british
my dear amelia watson
so a lot
no it's okay though i mean um
[Music]
maybe maybe it's better that you're not
british
maybe it's better for all of us
[Laughter]
i don't know what i'm trying to say i
actually really like i like british um
accents very much ah yeah they're pretty
cool
like just like mine
what are you ma you're you're pretty
defensive today you're like
you're most of your uh uh
[Music]
tools i don't know how to call them most
of you are
uh figures they're still in the back
yeah they're so defensive uh
yeah i don't know i didn't choose to be
this way it just happened
i was just reacting to your moves why
are you born this way
me too ah i see
you do
what what do you see tell me
um are you on the right track baby
i'm on the right track baby i was born
this way
[Music]
jared trapped my queen
yeah that was it was that easy
[Music]
it was that easy god damn it
gotta do something i gotta do something
i have to do something
to do something what do i do what do i
do
[Music]
no turning on tips apparently you can do
that in this game you're not allowed to
even though i would never be able to tap
but you can't do that
oh you wouldn't see it yeah
but i think if i turn on tips for me
wouldn't it turn it on for you as well
ah i don't know actually maybe
i know gooda was using it and i saw like
a little thingy that appeared but i
never
i never like saw and like do any tips i
guess
ah
i feel like the chad is uh trying to
tell you something
and not me something
take bishop with rook like who is that
about
because i don't think i can do that can
i do that take a bishop with a rook
that's cheating you're in chat
but the whole time saying that i'm just
trying to you know communicate
with the people i don't wanna you wanna
ignore all the all the viewers
how can i do that i don't even
see it but a rook is uh
oh no wait that's a pawn wait what's a
rook again
i don't know the english names of the of
the
what's a rook
the castle
every time you'll take my rook yeah but
then you would be able to kill my queen
with your horse oh yeah
that is true
it was an accident
there's it was a happy accident
why you shouldn't rely on chat
oh wait a second
wait a second if i move my rook one up
and now well i mean if you will take
them then you
i don't think it'll be a checkmate but
but
you cannot move yourself from a
checkmate into a check can you
however
ah but wait but but if you
if you just take it with the queen then
i'll take your
queen and then
then is this
oh wait a second if you do that
i think like if even if you take my
queen i think i have a solution
it might be a checkmate because i
because you've already caught me in like
two different
uh areas hmm
[Music]
i'll try i mean what do i have to lose
and i'm already
so close to losing yeah
[Music]
um i mean i i i did i did a lot of the
pre-work a little i did a lot of the
preparing for that okay
one more one and one more okay okay okay
why is there 40 000 people watching this
this chest is worldwide it's worldwide
not really like um i i played uh
chess with russia the other day uh
i replayed 51 board games but um she
doesn't know chess and most japanese
people don't know how to play chess
ah you know
it's not one of these basic and i think
in every other country
chess is just everyone knows how to play
chess
no matter if you're bad or good at it
but yeah
yeah i guess independent they have
something to replace that
for example i guess yeah
okay i will i i i will not
i will not look at the chat
but you know i just i just can't help it
because
i love interacting with my viewers so
much
understandable understand i'll give you
a pass this time
oh wait it's my turn yeah it's my turn
oh sorry sorry
what did you move i guess that's pawn
hey there you go
me too but i'm are you aware
that this basically means um you lost
against the chat
well i mean there's so many it's
combined brain power it's like
if you tried to build a house by
yourself versus like you know
building a house with 10 other people
sure yeah chat is like one
entity in if there's if there's a group
of 10 people spamming one thing
they'll be like ah this must be right
and then they spam it too
yeah that's totally wrong that's true
that is indeed
a thing
do i want to take your pawn am i risking
something here
no not really
yeah that's okay that's a good trade
i don't trust that
oh wait
i didn't know oh but you said i don't
trust that as if i had something in
uh in in mind but i didn't but now i
realized i could have if you would have
taken the part i could have taken your
horse
you gotta do it quick kiara on the farm
calculations yes you very much
calculation much thinking
big brain oh wait
no that's okay okay everything is under
control
[Music]
okay
i love your hicks so much
some people think that it might be a
sign of like something serious but i
think it's just because they swallow air
you swallow air yeah you know how like
when you drink soda the carbonation
makes you uh like actually like swallow
swallow air like
like for real i don't know probably
what an interesting woman she is hmm
air tastes good
i wouldn't agree on that uh fried
chicken tastes much better than
air although i guess you could try to
fry air because everything tastes better
when it's fried what
fried air that would just be that would
just be
crispy stuff yeah oh that's actually
good stuff
you know how when you fry something you
like to eat the crumbles
of like what's left over from the fry
fried mess yeah yeah yeah
oh wait did you just move the horse
yeah huh
see interesting
i think that's called a bishop is it a
bishop it's about i don't remember those
eh no no i took your did not take your
bishop
i think it is i don't know you still
have two horses on the field
you sure
[Music]
well i mean that doesn't
do that much so for now but um
i'm on it i'm on it trust me
[Music]
what could be your next move uh
it's probably you would probably
move someone from the first row next
um
i'm unpredictable you know
what i'll do next
sometimes i just move stuff randomly
just for fun
wait can i do something with that um
does the horse jump over
uh like for example if i'm here
uh or like i don't know can i if
something is in between whatever i want
to take
does it jump over it i'm pretty sure
interesting interesting very interesting
what on the way to
uh hell
is that the lyrics
what are you planning take a pawn
take a king wait i got dizzy from the
bopping
i'm getting dizzy
[Music]
what are you why are you going there
no no no no no no
what if i just go here
yep that works
ah how will you get out of this huh
uh i i i
i um
[Music]
you have to give me one no
no i would never
i would never sacrifice my people
well you have no choice mom
that must be i mean i could just go back
but
i don't want to go back i've come so far
oh wait oh no if i move oh no
no
amelia that's just rude
look i no give you anything i don't want
to give you my horse on my bishop
[Music]
no i refuse i refuse but at least i'm
gonna
i'm gonna take something with me
but i don't i wanna keep the bishop
but oh faint
aren't you forced to move if i do this
aren't you forced to move your king if i
do this because
i am checking your king no i don't know
and this is how i keep my bishop oh
but lose my horse okay i don't know if i
was worth it
bye bye wait uh
bye bye bye bye
bye bye at least i saw
i saw what i could do in the future
yeah no no not too bad you didn't see
this one coming huh
when you when you realize your mistakes
just as you're doing them
that hurts the most you should double
check your moves before you do it
i think i know though what you're what
you're doing i mean i know what you're
doing i know that you're using your time
traveling skills
ah you go back every time you do a wrong
move
you go back every time i know you do how
come you won the last game then i gave
you that one huh
no i won that fair and that's not
exactly square but i want a parent
triangle or something
no no
oh thank god you went the wrong route oh
my god i thought you could take my queen
there oh my god
[Music]
god what
i mean would you say you're the type who
likes to be in control
um of whatever
yeah no i wouldn't say that maybe
you want to be i want to be controlled
no no no okay i'm in control
you want to control hey
there you go chad there you go
wait wait what are you doing what are
you doing just looking around
i'm just browsing
[Music]
oh yeah so i mean i have to we said that
i have to talk show coming up do you
have anything
cool coming up ah no
oh that's okay too
oh yeah i actually had an idea today oh
uh for christmas i was i'm gonna do a
10-hour you like stream
you know how like people just put on
like a u-log thingy
what's a u-lock you'll you'll vlog it's
like a
it's like a uh fireplace with a
crackling
vlog like a chat stream
yeah but now i'm not gonna say anything
it's just gonna be silent for ten hours
and people are gonna chat with each
other oh that's pretty much what
i'm doing every time before my stream
because i take i take my stream slots
like
10 or 15 hours early and everyone's just
chilling and hanging out there
yeah it sounds similar yeah um yeah okay
okay
i also have some idea for uh christmas
but
i don't uh or like the the days uh
coming up to christmas
what huh what
why would you do that oh god
[Music]
no
now why won't you do such a thing i'm
hungry
or okay i'll i'll give you i'll give you
that one okay i'll
i'll give you that one but okay we'll
have to get rid of you
uh eventually i'll have to get rid of
you eventually
why oh wait i'm not gonna go there oh
hell no
oh no will i i'll just go here
okay it was delicious
i will not let you go that easy that's
for sure
you cannot escape
but wait wait wait i shouldn't i
shouldn't
uh get ahead of myself but you either
escape here or you even escape
here uh oh yeah that's okay okay so
saying you'll escape here take you with
my king and if you escape up here i'll
take you
with my queen yep that sounds about
right
oops it i'm not here where am i where am
i
oh oh wait what ah here
oh wait wait
here here here here
then if you go up here i'll take you
there but what if you just don't do
anything at all what if you just stay
there
well am i safe up here it looks like
looks like i'm safe can't really
currently do anything there yeah it's
pretty safe
please don't kill me
i won't kill you but i will secure my
protection
how just in here how how did
how in what way did you secure your
protection
and don't worry about it i can't tell
you that's top secrets
[Music]
by the way i was thinking of hiring you
again
on minecraft for some construction work
ah
could you do you want to help me out
soon like uh i want to do like
automatic frying pan
uh-huh like in the back of my restroom
did you see i was starting to play my
my restaurant yes
[Music]
do you know how to do those do you know
how to do those uh automatic
frying things where you put in a raw
chicken and it
uh well you get it like um
like
i can't think with two brains i need
another brain i really need another
brain god damn it
i guess you could put like a like a
hopper on top of a um
smoker and then yeah you could have it
so that
when the chickens die where however they
die it
the helper grabs it so i guess
my my chickens they don't die they they
go to a better place let's
let's say it that way okay oh yeah a
better place when they go to my tummy
um yeah we could put like a hopper on a
smoker or something or like uh
yeah a hopper and a minecart that
collects it and then drops it in a
smoker or something i don't know
sounds good i'm sure your chat knows how
to do it and you guys
for that i will listen to you just this
once
i could put you in check but i won't
lose too much
if i do that yeah it seems kind of
pointless
hmm well i'm thinking too much in this
move okay sorry
um i will i will um
[Music]
i will just stay i will just stay there
but i will make a move
to also strengthen my defense i think
with this boy
okay yeah
[Music]
that's okay that is um
goddammit no no nothing
no
you have to give me one
way your sacrifice is kiara hmm
no no wait oh my god but i can't i can't
i can't i can't let you do that
no that no no no because
because then you have two of your units
down there
you could try to do something really bad
and we don't want that to happen
so instead of you instead of me moving
away
i should try to do something to stop you
which i guess must be this move
yeah i mean yeah yep okay
no don't go there amen why not
i mean okay if you wanna
[Music]
yep that sounds good to me oh wait
oh yeah yeah okay okay
[Music]
i thought you could take my horse for a
second i cannot see
the the difference between white and
black fields apparently
i think they're like cookies so it's
like uh one's a like a
sugar cookie and the other one's like a
chocolate cookie
oh cookies
i haven't eaten breakfast what do you
what do you usually eat for breakfast i
mean uh well today i had the kiara
breakfast
um have breakfast yeah i have chicken no
no no nutella waffles with nutella
i also almost like usually i eat like a
croissant or something with nutella
um yeah but you move something what did
you
ah okay
so you move just one field
[Music]
i i spy
with my little eye
but you i'm not really in danger here
the only thing you can take is my pawn
that's okay did you make the waffles
yourself
ah no it's just um the toaster ones
oh do you know how to make waffles yeah
with like a waffle iron i've done that
before in like pinky
yeah yeah yeah but it's always such a
mess to clean it up
yeah because you squish it or you put it
down and then like all the the batter
comes out it's i don't know if it's
worth it
every time every time i want to move
something
i want to move my body
[Music]
you know i like how people always were
like no no chest no
chest please don't do this there's still
40 000 people watching so so much for
i don't know do you blame jess it's so
painful me me me me
they like the pain
[Music]
would you like to help me
um well oh
wait i just saw something ah
i just saw some ah i mean it could be
easily resolved i guess
but let's try let's try it
yeah well i hope you enjoyed playing
with your queen
that was pretty fun huh i'll just i just
go back
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah yeah i'll just go back never mind
i like keeping my queen don't wanna
don't wanna lose my queen
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
it hurts it hurts
oh yeah i should do that i should do the
lucia strategy
i learned something from her when i
collab with her
every time she was about to lose uh for
some reason she started to
to like or suddenly be in pain she was
like
[Laughter]
so
maybe i should try that to get out of
the situation
how would that help
i don't know i can't play anymore my
finger i got a cramp in my finger
well yeah then then i would not lose at
least
i wouldn't lose
um in the game of life for giving up
kiara you can do it
i just swallowed what i'm surprised what
you said
because that sounded so cool i just
swallowed my own um
spit
let's do something how about
this
well you'll just take me then yeah do it
it seems like a good idea
no i would never do such a thing
but
[Music]
i want to do something smart
i don't wanna i don't wanna do it too
much with my queen because it's um
one of the best units
yeah so if you mess up i really suck
okay whatever what oops only one okay
i want to win this i want to go
in the smart corner i want to be the
smart girl by the way you already like
me bottom left on purpose did you do
that on purpose
what do you mean did you
i'm on the screen bottom left did you do
it
no i'm just usually on the right side on
my stream
ah i see
[Music]
uh
yeah oh you're finally gonna move your
horse out of the corner
maybe finally
get it out of my stall okay
either you pay rent or you
die okay i was just gonna say leave but
if you wanna
make that brutal okay
sure
i mean what are you trying to do with
that horse
what are you trying to do
bye bye horsey bye bye
oh are you gonna
wait no no no no you will not pick my
queen oh no oh no
[Music]
no i don't want you to take my queen
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait hold
on
i'll just go here i'm safe here right
i'm safe no i'm not safe
but i'm safe here i should be safe here
yep please don't take me
no no
no my queen died
i will never forgive you
[Music]
this is it
this is the end
whoops
i will not let you do this to me
you're not gonna you're not gonna do
this with two horses horses suck
that's true that it's not gonna be that
easy okay it's not gonna it's not gonna
be that easy
oh
okay
this works so um well i guess you get
oh you get one either way
okay yeah that is true i got one horse
of you
i don't really mind i guess that's fine
if you want to make the trade
acting tough huh check
acting tough i see i see i see
oh no i can't go why not keep on
thinking i can go there
[Music]
wait what
are you moving a queen now huh
i will i will take your queen
that is my goal i don't even want your
king i will take your queen
because you took my queen okay
[Music]
i don't know just generally it seems
like i'm losing generally
and that's what i thought last game but
you you got me there at the end
thank you for it for saying it as if it
was
my my my doing
[Music]
i like the pain i drink your tears
they're not tasty they're just salty and
i thought
i thought ame is not salty
you're not salty right you don't like
salt right
uh i remember when i was a kid when i
was really young uh
my friend cried and i licked her tears
what what you answered me
what what no salty
so you cried for something that made you
sad but then
it cheered you up because it was so
tasty uh
why wasn't me crying but yeah oh what
so you you drank someone else's dude
when i was a kid i wouldn't do that
today
yeah sure sure you did just talk about
doing it today
but yeah no you wouldn't do that today
you're not
you're totally not someone who does one
thing again that you did in the past and
you're
now threatening to do against your tears
give them to me
oh my god uh but actually my tears don't
taste like salt
huh they taste like gravy
the
i guess so
please be nice to me please be nice to
me
[Music]
i wanna win i want to win
i think i'm the thing i wish i could
look into her head but
whenever i take off your hat maybe i
could look into your brain
oh yeah through my head hole
oh oh wait oh god i wasn't thinking
about that
what is that something you are such an
interesting
person amen uh you're so
there's like you're just like full of
like
like interesting
no no no no no no
i mean i guess i guess you have a bunch
of holes but um
oh dear let's not take it there
no
you you looted me
oh dear what's the chat gonna think
about us we're
professional chess players okay i don't
know what you guys are thinking about
but def
i'm not i'm not thinking about what
you're thinking about
not at all i would never i would never
lose ammo
[Music]
oh i forgot about that
he distracted me kiara
[Laughter]
oh well sometimes you have to make
sacrifices
to be able to move forward
beautiful well sad beautiful oh god [\h__\h]
no a man no a man no
no no
[Music]
no i'm mad no
i'm mad
[Applause]
oh wait what the hell bye-bye yeah
so now i'm happy i'm happy now
everything's cool
i have your queen you have my queen
yeah i like trying different things so
for once i'll try your queen
okay amen i mean if you want it that way
wait who's going well this is going well
yeah i kind of like gave up i guess my
brain stopped working
this is nice what happens i i was really
focused but then i got distracted and
now i just
i'm just doing whatever sure sure
i'll eliminate you amen
i am good terminator
did you ever watch that movie i didn't
but there's like apparently uh
uh someone playing
in that movie who i obviously have
connections to because i'm obviously
australian but yeah
you know what i'm talking about
people here don't understand my my hints
suck oh only my own people understand
these hints i'll i'll shut up now
i i get it i think i get it okay okay
well you are one of my people so of
course you understand
huh yeah yeah i'm kfp employee
headshot
oh yeah right i made you shuffle uh that
is interesting because uh recently i've
also hired hachama for
uh also working in the kitchen so you
you two will work together for a while
is that okay
uh what the perfect what a perfect
pairing
and ame working in my kitchen that is
only only good is gonna come out of that
obviously
we'll balance each other out okay
uh
okay let's see if i can still uh get a
win somehow we
we both lost a lot of our people
yeah i threw let's see what we can do
here
um first of all maybe
maybe i'll go here
wait i only have a horse a bishop and my
king that's gonna be difficult
wait i shouldn't leave this place i
should go here
every time i realize it like right after
i've done it no
this is very exhausting
[Laughter]
god damn it i i wonder still if i
wouldn't have done that if there if i
would have
won in some way i wonder if there's a
world if there's a timeline and
i would have won i think so
um
am i going on wait i don't have a chat i
have a horse and a king what what should
what can i even do yeah i can tell you
you probably want to move your pawns to
the other side but
i'm not gonna let ya so uh
good luck my palms to the other side oh
yeah
oh yeah that was that thing
that's true i i have more pawns than you
yeah but your face gonna come to the
other side check
yeah oh dear lord
oh you could go forward but okay
[Music]
what what the hell
huh nevermind
what what
oh
it's okay i can still win can i maybe
probably somehow i'm sure i'll mess up
again somehow
yeah i feel bad that that is a
possibility
could you stop like blocking my pawn
from moving forward there
i thought you're gonna tell me could you
stop this kissing
no i would never ask you to do that i
love your hicks
did you see that on my mario sunshine
stream i asked for someone to do a remix
with your hicks off the mario sunshine
song and the papa
and they did it i saw it
yeah is that yeah that's how i describe
it yeah
it was so good it was a little cursed
it was very cursed but also very good
that's what we want to see
well yeah up until now did anyone else
make like a song with your hicks before
uh i think so like a few i think there
was
a few oh
i think somebody made like the song that
i used for background music
somebody made like a hiccup version what
but is that is that i just want to make
sure that that is not like
it doesn't bother you that doesn't
bother you right
like if people do something with your
hicks does it not bother you
why would you bother me i don't know
maybe you feel like
embarrassed about it also ah um
there's nothing to be embarrassed about
but i don't know you know people have
some
i don't know issues with themselves some
some sometimes
ah yeah i hope it's just okay
for you what if uh
how'd you feel if people sampled you uh
but they put it to like a heavy metal or
something
i mean sure i'm not a
not a big fan of that genre but people
have been doing
uh a bunch of songs for me there's also
like one really
dramatic um piano
uh piano how would you call that like a
whole
whole dramatic um
playing like future piano play
about my my life it's
it's like really really beautiful like
an
orchestra like something you would hear
if you go to a piano concert it's so
beautiful would almost make you cry
it's amazing some people are doing some
amazing
music here
i'm thinking
i want to win please oh please
please please please please
[Music]
please
but i'm still not in danger how about i
move something else right now
that doesn't really help me but
i'm recycled there then
[Music]
huh
like the pawn is still so far away
from the other side of the field i don't
think he can actually
make it
[Music]
wait am i losing something again i do
this i don't oh wait
i can't go there i don't want to lose
something again i've lost so much it
hurts it just hurts you know
i'll do it i'll do it what do i have to
lose nothing
nice neck crack
i keep on cracking my neck like the
whole time
i've got some issues
you can only do that on the first move
forward twice
also you can't jump over it
okay can't i don't think pawns can jump
over anything
interesting move amelia watson
can i still win i is there any way
i can win this
i mean right now neither my horse
nor my king is in danger i think
so
i'll start operation
something
please
wait what's going on
uh-huh interesting move
[Music]
hmm
does not know what to do
mommy doesn't know what to do
what you moved what did you oh you moved
one backwards hmm
oh i guess i
could take your
oh isn't that a good move i feel like
my what is that
[Music]
i hope this is exciting and entertaining
to our
viewers i'm sure that i hope they know
they knew what they were in for
i think the best thing to do
is to do nothing
no wait i can't i mean
wait a second
eight second is this my chance
to shine is this my time to shine
oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god
oh god don't do anything stupid cannon
oh i see what you're doing but no no no
no
no no
no no no no
it cannot end like this no no
i've come so far
i need to do this somehow
[Laughter]
panic and
panic was okay of course i like that
you're rocking
back and forth
it's okay it'll be okay chiara you could
probably still win even if i take your
pawn
i don't think so
but if you want to be that positive okay
that's very very
very sweet of you thank you
[Music]
i can't do anything without pawn now
anyway because i can only move forward
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
you are so close to winning in it pains
me
no i can't god dammit
wait i think amazon or something is here
oh god can i can i get it yeah
okay
so did you guys know that on a friday
kiara's doing a talk show with mighty
and senpai
ahoy and it'll be like an interview
thing
and you guys should totally watch it and
this is definitely not a commercial
break or anything
but i'll be there i worked on something
for it too
and it'll be really cool
you guys don't want to miss it and i
can't reach out yet because
i have it covered so uh
i will work this out with my own brain i
think i did i
when i was playing as good as kind of
like practicing
how to kill the king sorry
sorry that's okay sorry welcome back
uh okay something something came
did you did you what did you discuss
um nothing
what did you did you talk about how to
win the game
maybe what that's okay i'm not reading
chat so
there's a chance i might slip up
[Music]
that's okay
what are you trying to do with that
horse huh i know
no i may not
i don't care anymore because
if you do that then at least
at least you make space for me to move
forward
if you say so
[Laughter]
cleaning up oh no
okay this is like there's absolutely no
way i can do this
there's no way
unless no there's no way i don't believe
in it but
i mean a woman's gotta try
bye-bye
yeah i clean up this one too sorry okay
i don't wanna
i don't want chad to tell me i just want
them uh what to do i i just
i don't want them to tell me what to do
but i want them to tell me if there is
any way i could win
there's no way right
there's no way right they're always the
same gd
yeah yeah your only chances were pretty
much like the
pawn i guess oh wait actually no
um yeah it's over
it's over it could be it'll be
kind of hard to trap you i think
um
yeah i mean at least
[Music]
there's not much i can do wrong now so
i just live my life freely like a bird
you know
live the last few years yeah just stop
yep
pain pickle well i think i'll just make
this easier for myself
no don't you
[Music]
you don't need to yeah but
it'll probably be faster because like
trying to trap you
with the horse and the tower it seems
it seems hard
yeah i would like to
i would like you to use all of that
brain power
but i guess it's also better for me if
you
end it up quickly yeah
um well the thing is though i can't put
myself in check anyway so
you have to do it you have to do it yeah
i'll try to be fast okay oh wait i can't
i am
could you could you maybe you throw
something ah
could you throw something oh we could i
guess there is a resign button but
[Music]
goddamn are you gonna choose the queen
of course you're gonna choose the queen
[Music]
yeah there's nothing there's nothing i
can do
there is nothing
yeah do you want um
maybe i should just resign just give me
your horse
no no
this horse is amazing move uh
move um to the bottom on the bottom
white one third
on the third the bottom from the end why
would i do such a thing ah
[Music]
okay move on
i will kill it i promise you i won't
kill me
okay i'm just kidding
okay i won't kill it i won't kill it i
can't driving anything
i'll fight to the bitter end
like a real warrior i'm only part-time
warrior so maybe that's why
i i didn't do such a good job but i'm
trying i'm trying
i'm going to stay there
do it check
check i'm checking oh i didn't even see
that i was actually just trying to do
something else
stop it don't do it
you're just making this longer what's
happening amen what's happening you're
just making it longer
what's happening on there
i was just doing whatever to end it fast
because you wanted me to end it fast i
should have killed your knight
yeah sure she's getting salty yeah but
it was i actually let you live
so that we could end it but you took my
horse even though you said you wouldn't
take it i didn't take it what it's right
there
hey the other horse that wasn't there
that was a long time ago
that was like three moves ago you've
only had one horse kiara
what what i had to
there was something here that you took
anyway no i didn't
that's why you still have the night
because i didn't kill it
but you took something because it was
like ah you were like i'm not gonna take
it
and i was like okay and then i did it
and then you took it i don't know
whatever it was
i said i was gonna but then i didn't
because i was being nice
of course you didn't
no
[Music]
oh no
okay
this is a really tough battle until
the end huh you're not gonna
make it easy for me huh well i was
trying to make it easy for you
to end
i only take positive endings
this is gonna be like last time where we
just follow each other
forever no don't worry i'm i'm not gonna
let that happen
as soon as i i only have my horse left
uh my
my king left then i will resign
is the game actually is the game uh
gonna
end if i only have my king left because
there's obviously no other chance to do
it i wonder
ah that's a
good question uh-huh
uh-huh you're going for it again yeah
cause it's it's hard to trap you with
the with the horse and the other one
oh
i see i see it just die
well i mean again i can't i can't
check myself so
well you're welcome to end it amen
you're welcome
i was trying to
i cannot believe it it's almost
50k people watching
these people love art this means this
means we're good at jazz because we're
entertaining
yeah we're pros honestly
oh okay
thank you well now we know it doesn't
end
[Music]
thank you for not dragging it out
thank you
hey get your hat out of here oh
stop it
well uh thank you
very much ame for this uh beautiful game
yep i will um next time
will there be a next time robert yeah
yeah why not we will practice more and
then
again and like before everyone leaves we
did say to play another quick game of
uno
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah oh wait i think i
it has been
oh so just like chess it has been years
for me to play uno so i
i don't really remember all the rules
but it is it like um
and you either uh put play the same
color of card or even
the next number the following number of
cards so yeah unless you have like a
wild card
or a reverse it's the same color yeah
that's a weird looking uno game well you
know it's like knockoff uno they can't
do the
we'll figure it out oh ah we have to
have pcs play
ew can you not play uno with two people
i guess not oh well let's try one play
one
yeah okay okay and thank you guys for
watching our chest thank you
remember thank you everyone if you want
more strategic plays to go
uh subscribe to kiara's channel too
thank you thank you thank you also
come to my come to my announcement
tomorrow there's oh my gosh
my announcement i mean i'm announcing so
such amazing things
you have no idea yeah it's really cool
you guys don't want to miss it i know
what it is and i'll just say it's very
exciting
really exciting
wait so okay uh so i
uh i could either like play a card that
is
uh pink right or a number five right is
that hard works
i think so it should tell you like which
is not available
oh wait i should play the same is it not
possible to play a six
i guess it's not by number no i guess
it's just bi-color
uh i mean uh same color and number oh
whatever the same number
wait so how did i forget the rules to
uno what the hell
what is the point of this like if you
want to end with one card or you want to
finish out your card yeah
yeah yeah yeah but at the end i wonder
if this game if this game does it too
but you're supposed to say uno once you
have one card yeah you're supposed to
just get rid of all your cards
and make the other players draw more
cards penalty five
cards wow
that was my only option wait
oh oh my god the the cpu
one was almost winning damn
uh okay there we go you didn't declare
what do you mean
where do i where do i you have to say
uno
i mean i knew it was soon and i just
didn't know i had like what is the game
listening to me or something
draw i wonder maybe there's a button you
have to draw a push when you
i could have won what really i didn't
even see that it was too fast yeah
i'm not gonna let you change in this
game you know
this came on it just called you uno
i guess that's similar like three
three letters that's pretty similar
big text why i was reading the chat i'm
listening to kiara i don't have that
color from orange to orange how smart am
i
wow good you're skipping
oh no color change
[Music]
which color are you missing missy
um i don't have any blue
i say reverse
reverse reverse
hey how come i didn't get to go oh cause
it reversed oh
there we go skip
oh my god oh my god
am i winning am i winning
finish whatever i got second place
i would have won if i had known at least
if you if if i hadn't lost you wouldn't
have won
because you wouldn't have known to press
the button
yay i never played this before how am i
supposed to know
it was also my first time to play it on
this one
thank you even though it was also
painful it was painful very much
i did notice quite the salt over there
amen
right now uh only once maybe maybe you
should take a bath or something you
you're very salty
i'm a little salty yeah but that's what
i
like about you toxic gamer
watson yeah salt tastes good too right
yeah actually i like salt i do like salt
a lot
so i would say maybe next month we do a
rematch
okay until then i promise you i
promised you i'm going to be practicing
so much maybe even with my viewers i
promise
you you will not win another time
if you win if you win another time
next time at the next rematch i promise
you
i'll do one um batsu gamer one
punishment game that you choose
okay okay okay we'll put it to a bet
okay
so i think i think
uh you should probably also practice but
i hope you don't i hope you forget about
it so
uh i think that'd be a good idea
actually what you're saying practice
against viewers so
i probably be like a chess member
members only you know i guess it doesn't
have to be members only because secondly
anybody could play
but yeah i'll try i'll try that too
i gave you a bad idea thank you
god damn it well let's see about that
you just woke up didn't you yeah going
back to sleep
no no
no i will uh i will do some things i
think
ah okay but thank you thank you for this
a wonderful opportunity and you
maybe will you be awake for my
announcement tomorrow
well i have to finish that thing so
probably yeah i'll start working on it
right now
okay but you can also sleep that doesn't
matter
okay thank you everybody enjoy this test
yeah it's very enjoyable
remember hi uh kiara has a special
announcement tomorrow and then
is that the day of the day okay on
friday
for some of you kiara is doing a talk
show with marine senpai
and it's like an interview thing you
guys uh you want to see it you're going
to speak some english too
right like translate a little bit
exactly i'm going to translate
all her answers so we're going to have
some deep talk deep conversation
yeah you guys don't want to miss it well
thank you kiara for playing chess with
me
thank you for the rematch
see you in the next one see you guys in
the next one thank you goodbye
[Music]
you