[Music]
Thank you for your continued support.
[Laughter] [Music] [
Music]
[Laughter] The
countdown will begin, so if you
eat then you'll be on time
[Music] Hey [Music]  [
Music]
[Music]
[Music] The
second half of the broadcast has started, so please wait.
OK
[Music]
Google
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter] I'm
here for an interview.
Sorry, that guy.
[Laughter]
[Music]
Thank you
[Laughter]
[Music] Thank you
[Music]
[Laughter] Let's do our best,
so Mr. Nedaruma fell
down. He was wearing pretty big shoes. Everyone
[Music]
It's about time for the competition.  It looks like we can start.
Okay, so after today's introduction, we
'll start. Okay, here we go. I
fell down on Daruma-san, but it's a
competition for everyone.
The goal is when the sign says ``Yes, Daruma-san.''  If
you head towards it and move while it shows you have fallen, you will die instantly. Yes, yes. The competition is for Daruma-san to run as close to the goal as possible by 321.
[Applause] It is
also important to act carefully so as not to die.
Yes, Harvest Yes, it's an important competition, and first of
all, everyone will have a preliminary round, and after that preliminary round, the top 15 will
compete in the finals
[music].
So, with that said, we'll
start with the preliminary round, in which everyone will participate.
Well, this year, it's a little bit like that.  I
'll tweet about the area, etc. Well, it's changed a bit.If
you
stop quickly and quickly, you'll be sliding around like this,
so you'll die
instantly.I
think the difficulty level has also increased a bit, but
last year,
this year...  Well, even on the system, it's
quite strict to make sure everything is done properly.
[Music]
Well, yeah, just for everyone.
Before we start the competition, I
'd like to say a few words about it starting,
but Ei-chan, the announcer.  Is
it okay if I say something like, Okay, it's starting. Is it okay if I just say a few words? Is it
okay if we start now?
Okay,
everyone, are you
ready? Ah, Eri.
Good.
[Music] I'm sure you're
canceling your entry or making an entry,
but
Fubuki says she wants to chat when you start, so I see.
Everyone's probably out of gold. I see.
[Music] [Music]  [
Applause] Are you
ready?
[Music]
I'd like to start. Yes, OK.
Mr. Daruma
[Music]
Somehow, a new one has been decided. [
Music] It's
pretty dead. [
Applause]
[Music]
[Music]  ]
Yes
[Music]
Yes and 12
Erm
Tomata
Event and
Toner
Azuki-san
[Music]
[Applause]
I guess we'll start with 1st place Do you
want to listen to the interview?
[Music] Nata-
san
[Music]
No, that was amazing. They must have been
practicing.
[Music] It
's broken.
[Laughs]
That's right.
Shiro is so harsh.
Shiro is amazing.
In the 15th final, even the last place got points. The
first
place person got one.  The number points are high, so aim for the top as much as possible,
but do your best to get as far as possible.Of
course, I think it's better to eat happily.I see,
since there's only one, and there's only one.Certainly,
there are people who want to eat.  There's that meat in the box in the back,
so I'm
calling you. I'm calling you. Star Match Comet.
Mr. Hoshimachi Daffodil. What did you do? It's something you
often see at sports day.
[Music] [
Laughter]
[Laughter]
This is crazy! That's
amazing,
Naka.
That's good. It seems like we're good friends. I wonder how
many points I should get. I
don't know. I'd like to
get in mpt3.
[Music] That's
right. I do
n't know what will happen, so I
might be disqualified.  Thank you very much
. Thank you very much.
Let's calm down.
[Music] I
really need you to move.
Good luck.
[Music]
Sorry.
Also, the letter "S" in the pelvic ship.
Maybe it's just me. No,
there must be a blue demon.
[Music]
Start Why are you there? [Music] But... [Music] [Applause] [Music] Try your best, try your best, try your best, try your best, it's starting Try your best, try your best - What's going to happen Tapping [Music] Come on
[Applause]
[Music]
That's not going,
that's not going  Hey
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter] It
was also 41. Ade
503.53.53
No, no, no,
so I
'm going to announce it. Yes, please.
[Music]
Oh yeah, some of the controls didn't work during the game, so I
was panicking, but it turned out okay. I'm glad I made it
to Abune's goal.
[Music]
[Laughter] You
did a great job, thank you. You
did a great job, thank you.
-1
[Music] I
was going to get first place, but
yesterday you
gave me an excuse.
Yes, thank you very much.
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Music] The
first place will tell you what's important, so do
n't worry. Lately,
I'm the winner of this game.
[Music]
[Applause] [Laughter]
[Applause]
[  [Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] That
must have been the place where he was being bullied [Music]
[Laughter] Let's get on with it
[Music] I'm
glad Button was there to help. Well, let's get back on track
here.  I
'm happy.
Can you hear me? Can you
hear me?
[Music] [
Music] [Music] I'm
back.
[Music]
So, Daruma-san is here.
Just the settings.
[Music]
The graphics in the settings have
processing priority.  If you change it to something like that, the lag
may be a little less.I also experienced lag earlier, so it
's the video setting.Thank
you for giving priority to graphics processing in the video setting.
[Music]
I think it would be better to lower the drawing distance a little.I'm already
at 6.
[Music]
[Music] I've
decided that it's probably going to
be another point.
[Music]
Take the apple and put the meat inside the cat.
Maybe you won't eat the meat after all.  That's all
I eat, so I
showed them the Nexte and they
asked me to put mine in the one with the bigger nose.
[Music] It's
cute.
[Music]
When we drink water, we all start from the top, and
from the beginning we make TNT.  The
boss is the
one from the top, and the two of them are playing under the festival,
so I'll
finish the water once that's done.
[Applause] I'm
nervous, so I'll definitely keep it at hand.
[Music]
Inside, I'm starting to think about quitting.
Now it's time to compete.  You don't have the courage.
[Music]
If you went up, there was an exit at the top, right? That's
right, come down. That's why Mermeru
woke up from there, senpai. It's scary. If you're really in a hurry, you wo
n't be able to do it. I see, you can't do anything.
Yeah,
but
basically everyone seems to
be able to mess up that much.I
think they must have lost the script.Maybe.I
have it.I don't have the DVD either.
[Music]I get
nervous when it's my turn.That's crazy.I'll see
you later on the white group's show.  I wonder how well the play has been transcribed now.
[Music]
[Music] That's
really all there is to it
. It's amazing.
[Music] The
left side is really hard to sleep on,
so the right side is full. When
everyone is together, it's
kind of weird.  There's
no water here.
[Music]
It's about time.
Enter from the left. To
collect, enter from the right.
Don't worry, you can go to the right.
[Music] [Music]
[Music]
Subaru Cap
I'm sorry.
[Music]
OkOkOk Is the
rain okay? We're
practicing
[Laughs] The
characters are okay too.
Wow, Matsu Muto is already
finished in red. He's a
red demon, isn't he?
[Music] I don't like it. [Music] He's
always serious.  Do it,
hey, die, die, die, do your best. I
want you to relax and have fun.
[Music] Having
fun is the best.
[Music]
Mel and the others should go here
[Music] It's the
wrong infection channel.
Subaru: Please tell me what you're going to do. I've
fallen here. It's
streaming. It's streaming.
[Music]
Streaming
[Laughter]
[Music] I'd
like it to be broadcast. The
other teams are really practicing relays.  Ade,
and Chiara-chan and Ame-chan are barely doing it either. It's too
bad. Just a little more. Please tell me if it's okay. I do
n't want to go around. It
makes me nervous. [
Music]
[Music]
[Applause]
Everyone is now delay relay
practice practice
[Music] -
Shall we do it like a man?
[Music]
[Applause]
[Applause] It's just
practice.
This is good.  It's a
shame
[Music]
Okay, here we go
[Laughter
] [Music]
[Music] [Music]
[Music]
It's about to start right at the end,
so it's okay. Well then, that's
good. It's
moving and swimming, but it's amazing
[Music]
On the
contrary, stop being so nervous
[Applause]
Freeze Power
[Music]
[Applause] [
Music] [
Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
No mistakes
[Music]
Ok,
let's go support the yellow one
[Music]
Interview  It seems like it's
going
well. I guess it's okay to include a voice. That's why I'm here.
What's going on? What's going on?
What's
going on? Is there anything you can
hear? It's probably
because of the frame.
[Music]
Thank you, thank you
[Music]  I do
n't think you can hear me, but
yeah, it's too scary
Running straight until it's scary
[Music] Yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah,
when you can't
run, you just sleep. It would be bad if you took a detour, you
idiot. I
think it would be better if you took it. It's
scary, scary. It
's not normal.
[Music] That's
scary.
Stick to the wall.
Do your
best. Let's eat when the countdown starts.
[Music]
Ah, it
certainly feels like there's no sound, but the
operation sounds are so accurate that I can almost hear them.
Even when I go to bed, it's a bit too dark.
Maybe there's just no BGM.
On the contrary, everyone has started. Eh,
hasn't it started? There
doesn't seem to be any sound. I
forgot about Peko-chan's BGM. Maybe
it's the sound of the studio.  No, I
forgot.
[Music]
[Music] I
can hear your voice. It's so
deep.
[Music] I think it's
Nina's number 3, but it
's a nice cat. This one
might be a hit. Everyone's here
[Music]
Mental Physical Pan  Shon, now 2 Peko What's
going on? [Music] [Music] It's not good at all, this is it. It's
just a cat. I
can't
do my best. I want you to
do your best. Yeah, do your best, do your best. Do your best. I'll support you.
When does it start?  It's a rough
guide to when it starts, right? This is the time when I'm most nervous. It's when I'm waiting. Don't send me messages. Kill me. It's tough. [Music] That's it. Congratulations. [Music] Which campaign is this here?
[Music]
Announcing the number of subscribers to the channel I wonder if
it's because it's so funny that they're still stopping it
[Music] Good luck! [Music]
[Applause] I'm
going to do this.  The
other one is finished. Bottom
Boss
[Music]
[Music] Ah,
here it comes, here it comes
[Music]
Hey, don't shout out to me. [
Music]
Let's try to be nice. I'm calm. [
[Laughter]
[  [Music]
[Applause]
[Music
] [Music]
[Music] [
Applause] [
Music]
[Music]
[Music] [Applause]
[Music] The
team has separated properly. It's a
difficult situation here. Delicious
Matsuri Senpai is a bit of an enemy.  It's
OK to lie,
I'm being shot.
I'm Matsui-senpai, it's almost over.
Nice, nice
. Alright, one more one will come down and two more will
come down. Thank you
for starting.
[Music]
Let's go. OK, I have to
run. Let's
blow it up.  I have to
do it!
[Music]
Do your best,
Uncle Creeper. It's the
last frame of Creeper.
[Music]
I'm really getting wet. It's pretty stinging. It's
raining so much from above.
No, but the movement was really good. It's
actually number 1.  This one
actually ranks number one,
but
it's the best.
[Music]
That's true.
[Laughs] I ca
n't forgive you.
[Music]
[Laughs]
[Music] I
think it was that one.
Those green guys killed me
[Music]
Well, I'll give you a little time
as a present [Music] [Laughter] The result was
unexpected. Congratulations, thank you.
[Music]
Thank you
Thank you!  In Begola, the
red group's
interview was also bad. I heard it was about the
red haired one. I did
n't like it because they had an enemy. That
's right, all three of them were really good. They were
faster than any of the cheeses. Seriously, they were the
fastest and did it.
It was really crazy, it was amazing.
[Music]
Okay, I'll go back to the next one. Wait a minute, then I'll say it. I wish I could go back.
Guys, the
interview is over, can I come back? Now, let's
talk about the main topic.
[Music]
Yeah,
[Applause]
[Music]
But we've been doing our best so far, so
no matter what our limits are, we just have to do this.
Please,
this is what we can do.
Where will the announcement be made?
So, thank you for the replay video
[Music]
Thank you
Do you feel like
you've got a complete plot twist? [Music] Most likely people will say that they're being eaten by that creeper that's being eaten.
[Music] I was
thinking, ``The
left side is faster.'' Everybody just walk straight.
Hey, let's just walk outside. It's no good. All we
can do is practice and cut this.
[Music]
Go ahead, it's dangerous. Do you have any tools
left over?
It's pretty good.
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
And I'm really looking forward to seeing how it turns out.
Yes, the point distribution is 30 points for 1st place and
20 points for 2nd place.Let's
have everyone prepare a little.
[Music] I'm
really nervous, aren't I?
[Music] [Music]
[Music]
Me  Please enter after completing the distance
[Applause]
[Music] [Music]
[Laughter]
[Music]
Subaru-senpai wants to use the camera
halfway, so I
understand your hard work
[Music]
Thank you.
The third runner
is the red-haired Crazy Ren Rental Physical Fashion.
And then
there's the picture of the red team, Reine of the white team, and Hear of the kei group.
[Music]
And the golden group is Ozora Subaru.  [Applause] I'm looking forward to it.
[Music] Are you
lined up properly?
[Music]
I'm sorry, but I'll say it first. It's
okay, it's okay, it's okay
. I think it's okay for this to be the last event in the second year of the selection.  But what about the red team?
[Applause]
[Laughter]
What do you mean? Ah,
okay, what's wrong with the character? It's the first one. It seems like in the
chat or something, that character is going to
run twice. Hey, I was called up.
Yellow team orders.
Don't waste Chiara Heart.  Pecola
OK OKOK
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughing]
[Music]
How about how about it, I'm
practicing Shaka Shakasha Shaka Shaka Shakasha.
[Music]
Yeah,
yeah, do your best. It's okay. I'm confident.
Don't wait.
What else?
[Applause] Hey, I'm about to
puke. It's
okay, are you okay? Let's
sabotage the other person.
[Music] I
think so.
[Laughter]
[Applause]
There's a lot of meat, so there's
no
way there's a lot of meat. What do you mean
? Just cheer me on. You can do it. It's a quilt.
[Music]
Yes, so do your best.
Shiro and everyone else.
[Music]
[Music] It
's the last event.  Please tell me how you feel now.
Mental Musical Punsion
[Applause]
[Music]
[Music] I
'm feeling like I don't really know what's going on.
So, how do you feel about Akihara? I
feel like I've practiced too much and gotten worse.
But
[Music] It's
okay.
[Music]
That's right.
Just do your best. I feel like
throwing up, but no matter what the outcome is, I
want to have fun and have fun with everyone in front of me. Yay
[Music]
[Applause]
[  [Music]
What do you think of Pekona, the leader of Ng?
The first half was really good, as the Yellow and Yellow Mob subjugation were pretty exciting. It's
easy for Yellow to win, everyone.
[Laughs]
[Music] [
Music] I'm
sorry.  Could you please enter again
? I'm really sorry.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Well, maybe
Subaru was too strong-willed and ended up reaching that point.
So, we're doing a rehearsal. It's exciting. [
Music]
[Music]  ] The
sports day venue got too excited
[Music] I
pressed the
other button to enter.
[Music]
Please line up Please be
quiet.
Quiet. Name
Hey, this
is good.
Thank you.
[Music]
What's going on? Are you okay?  Wait a minute and post the latest one.Would you
please?
[Music]
Thank you
Thank you, it's okay.Yes, thank you.  I
think so.
[Applause]
[Music]
It's okay for cats to enter. Yes, it looks like it's okay. I'd like to check with the management,
but they
haven't entered it.
[Music]
Let's have them do it.
[Applause]
[Music] I'm
going to go to the last two years of selection.
Let's start [Music] [Music] It's okay, it's okay, it's okay [Music] It's good, isn't it? [Music] [Applause] [
Music] [Applause]
[Music]
[  Music]
[Applause
]
[Music] [Music]
[Applause]
[Applause] [Music]
[Applause] Let's go to track and field.  ]
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] I
get the impression that you practiced really well.
[Music] It's a very
passionate
interview. Oh,
most of the time I
'm crying. I'm
happy.
[  [Music]
[Music]
Congratulations
!
[Music]
And now you're the NEET who finished in the same place.
How was it?
Some of you were like that too.
Until the very end, we didn't give up and lined up together to reach the goal.
[Music]
Hello, congratulations, congratulations. Please
look forward to the final score. [Music] Yellow team, ok, I'd like to go listen to it. Let's go for the last one, yellow
group.
Everyone
[Music]
Thank you very much
[Music] I
think it's amazing that we were able to catch up and finish in the same place.
[Music]
Everyone was passing the baton.
Everyone ran really well.
Well, for the last time, I've already given it my all and I'm done.
Thank you very much.
[Music]
Thank you.
Okay, so this is more than just an interview. Now that the
results have been announced,
all the planes are finished, so I
'd like to hold the closing ceremony.  Yes, I think so.
[Applause]
So,
to all of you, yes, the
first half of the members.First of all,
everyone, let's gather together.Let's
have a closing ceremony.Yes,
please, please, yes, that horse
was there.
]
Yes,
Mr. Subaru Ozora, the sports day executive committee member, is
on the contestant channel.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much. I feel
lonely. That's right.
[Music] I
don't feel like it's over in a blink of an eye.
But this year it's been
really, really smooth.
[Music] I
think it was a pretty great match.
Thank you for all the games. As expected,
everyone worked hard. There were
also times when I was really worried.  I'm sorry, but
thank you very much.
[Music]
[Laughter]
So now that we're all here, I'd
like to hold the closing ceremony here.
[Music]
[Laughter]
So,
everyone at the closing ceremony.  I wonder if your voice has been heard? This
position
[Music]
Now we
will have the closing ceremony.
[Music]
So, first of all, I would like to
ask Mr. Subaru Ozora to give his correct greeting.
Thank you.
Everyone
had fun today.
[Music]
[  [Music] I
think it's because of the preparation. It was a
great sports day. Subaru had fun too.
Thank you very much. Thank you for your hard work.
That's it.
Thank you for your greetings. Thank
you. Now for the final specific presentation
[Music]
Hey
[  [Music]
Well, let's start with the announcement of the last digit. First of all, how to
put the red hair on the bottom is doing everything. If it's going to be all
out, then it's
all out.
Sorry, let's go. The
last digit of the red hair, white group, TN group.
[Music] Well then, it's not up to me. [Music] We
might win, so
let's do something about it.
[Laughter]
[Music]
With the Red Team, we
ended up with a twist on the bike.
[Music]
[  [Music]
[Applause]
[Music]
Thank you very much
- You're
welcome.
That concludes the Live Sports Day 2022.
[Music] Well
then, let's
all gather here.
Please take a slow look at this tier here or here.  But they're lined up nicely
right now, so let's just
keep it like this. If we get together, we'll take
a picture.
[Music]
Yay.
[Applause]
Even if we don't, we're all
Mckin-keen at heart, so that's what we're talking about.
But seriously, the yellow color was really exciting.  [
Music]
[Applause]
Let's put this to good use next time, next year.
[Music]
But I don't know where I should be. It's reflected. All I
have to do is face forward.
Look forward. A little higher up, maybe a little higher up.
Red
Last time, it was from the Red Team
[Music]
Thank you very much.
Thank you
[Music] In
the morning, we
'll have a morning assembly at the dais.
Cool.
Tiara's English is cool.
By the way, everyone used the rest room. Please
use it
[Music]
Hey
.  [Laughter]
[Music]
That's not a suspicious person
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
Yes, the
latter one, please take charge of that camera.
Thank you very much
[Music]
Thank you