[Music]
yeah yeah
hey
[Music]
yeah yeah
he
[Music]
Bobby
Z hey you made it
[Music]
welcome hello hello I am CL beu
sparkling Jam of H life English Advent
but maybe you already knew that because
did you get did you get my
invitation did you get did you get my
invitation that I attached to a rock and
threw out your window to my birthday
sleepover party did you get
it did you get the invitation
J I hope you did well you're here so you
must have
huh it was you oopsies sorry I will not
be responsible for any uh damages or
anything but welcome welcome to my
birthday
party welcome welcome I I I uh mom saki
sent the set set up this this room for
us and and she left the house uh so we
could just have the the whole house to
ourselves uh and we can just party by
ourselves uh in the sleepover she left
us she left the snacks and and
everything yeah Mom that Homeless
party I hope I hope you brought uh comfy
clothes and snacks well I have snacks
for you and stuff like that but yeah
it'll be a good time tonight we're going
to no sleeping though we're not we're
not sleeping we're staying up late yeah
we're staying up late tonight uh
but but do you guys do you guys have
your
invitation you want to know you know
what we're doing today right you have
you have your
[Music]
invitation boom ah that I threw out your
window oh yeah so we're going to have a
big big big party
today uh now is welcome uh welcome uh
thank you for coming I was afraid that
no one was going to come to my birthday
party uh but you are here so uh I I
appreciate it uh that that you that you
came uh thank you thank you very much I
wasn't I wasn't scared that nobody was
going to show up or anything I prepared
all these snacks and and uh stuff so
thank you for
coming uh and today we are doing uh
question mark question mark question
mark karaoke for the first 2 hours of
the stream I will explain what that is
in like a second but uh after that we
are watching a movie with Advent uh
Space Jam original Space Jam by the way
I said original didn't I uh original
Space Jam so the regular one I haven't
seen it
before I haven't seen it before uh so no
spoilers I think some of Avan has not
seen it before either so that will be
fun yeah yeah yeah um so that will be in
2 hours from now uh if p.m. after 2
hours after that after the movies finish
we're doing some game nights uh with
friends so I bought all of the
jackbox packs you guys are going to have
to tell me cuz I I had no time I was so
busy I did not look at which ones were
good so you need to tell me which which
ones are good so I can I can host the
good ones yeah tell me which ones are
nice I bought literally all of them so
we'll have some fun with with uh jackbox
games at and and then at the end of the
night we're going to have a
peble party
a purle Pepple party we're going to hang
out
um what is it my manager gave me
something already from you guys I
haven't opened it um I will probably do
it at the pebble
party
time yeah uh or if we have
time during if I finish karaoke early I
don't know if we'll finish early though
we have a lot of scks but thank you
thank you for thank you for the the the
present though we're I'm going to look
at it uh later probably at the pebble
Party part but yeah yeah um oh yeah do
you like do you like my my Mom's party
setup she set this up for
me do you like it isn't it
cute look at
that thanks mom also
I did not ask for a for a picture of
Kyla but it's there thanks
Mom H but thank you for the background
by by resu I appreciate it it looks
great I love it it feels so it feels so
party e e
yes okay but we have we have stuff to do
today thank you for all the birthday
wishes thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you now the reason why I
was so busy is because of this um we are
doing karaoke but we are not just doing
regular karaoke we are doing duet uh
with my Senpai and we are singing their
original songs so I had to learn many
and many senpai's original songs so we
are going to do duet together uh they
pre-recorded uh their parts but I will
be singing my parts alongside of them
right now and it's all senpai original
songs all Originals um so I had to learn
a lot uh I will do my best to uh honor
Senpai and and and do my
best
yeah all of them um whoever gave it to
me not not all of them it is uh e n n i
d I wanted to invite all of JP too but
if I invited all of JP then the stream
would have lasted 8 hours on karaoke
alone but so it is just Ian and ID right
now yeah uh yeah I'm a
[Music]
little but I will do my best hold on
let's
Cal it's my birthday I don't need to be
nervous I can do whatever I want it's my
birthday I can throw I can throw rocks
at people or whatever is mine don't make
people
okay happy birthday thank you thank you
for the birthday
[Music]
wishes I have I brought I brought you
guys I brought you guys with
me where where's the other where's the
other ones where's the other ones
[Music]
H Pebbles yeah I I brought I brought
Pebbles uh with me welcome Pebbles to my
party if you don't see your Pebble here
today that's okay because every stream I
do a pebble of the day so if you if you
are not here today that's okay because
you posted your Pebble and I will have a
lot of days that I will stream so so you
are you will probably show up one of
these days so thank you for submitting
your Pebbles I like a lot of them have
like party hats and our dresser parties
and stuff so yeah thank you I brought
you guys with me but for now go
away you can come back later but but but
for
now it's Senai
time it's jum by time okay is my Reverb
on I don't even know what am I
doing what what today is my
[Music]
birthday what what am I doing oh yeah
uh Reverb is not on okay good that's a
good thing but now I will turn it on
okay EO EO EO
EO
okay who shall we start
with which some
[Music]
Pai I I hope I named them I did okay
uh which
one I
know ah
yay Ena let's start with Ena it's only
Senpai songs by the way way it's only
Senpai
songa let's start with Ena
okay I hope the volume is okay please do
not get on my butt for volume because I
have to balance everybody's volumes at a
different level um but you can yell at
me if it's bad but I took notes I
prepared so I know I think okay
[Music]
oh wait that is a
spoiler I got sh up hold
[Music]
on I'm already singing I'm so sorry
samai
[Music]
it's okay I'm not nervous now
uh in not was around here I
[Music]
think
fore
[Music]
for
Fore for
[Music]
foree
foree foree
[Music]
[Applause]
for
[Music]
fore
momy
yay thanks
Ena thank you for singing Ena I love you
please play Monster Hunter with me of
course people let us play Monster Hunter
together yay let's
play yay thank you in thank you thank
you
w
w w you are beautiful I love your song
your song is so nice it's so nice to
sing some of our Senpai songs are really
really
hard I appreciate a song cuz it's soft
and gentle and nice and fun to
sing thank
you for your amazing amazing song thank
you I love
you wow
bye-bye okay who is
next oh I know so I go like e and i e
and I
oh let's do another
[Music]
F Boo Boo
Boo this this person is the only person
who sent a video which is
great this will be
fun here we
go hello
happy birthday to my favorite cutest
Hard Rock
be Jo
joj do you like jazz I do like jazz this
song is a bit sexy so let out your sexy
side okay okay okay me first me
first as the city lights come alive
Shadows off the night help me spin my
wayo got my target there in my
he canun and but he can't
be is I make my smoo as the dressy
Groove while the
musain play the musical with aink in my
hand been work in a plan and it's going
good it's going good okay okay chears
chears to all your secrets your
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah don't you from
me let's go I can see through your
[Music]
eyes you're mine I can see through your
eyes in the
dark night
[Music]
super let's
go in my we every word he said ready for
replay then I SLI and he knew my hand
took off and he ran thought he could
Escape te to all your secret your
desires what are you doing
to late CU I won't stop don't you what
don't you hide for me let go
thinking the
line how far you may run
to I can see your
eyes
the night
super
power
okay let's go I can see through your
eyes
see the
super power get to my
head baby you're
mine what this point run but you can't
hide I'm yours yes I
[Music]
yes baby you're
M always one step behind I forgot to
learn this part
[Music]
I'll take my time to your
M trumpet sound make some trumpet
[Music]
sound wait that's air horn
oh that was good that was good thank
you that was
fun happy birthday people thank you
thank you so much for inviting me I you
have the most uh Bas Bas be Joe Joe Joe
joest um birthday
ever love you love you
to thank you oh she run away I can still
see
you oh okay well she's gone now thank
you
Z that was so fun I was I was so
distracted by her that I that oopsies oh
well I love her song it's so
catchy go listen to her song I loved it
I love learning it it was so it's so fun
toar and thank you for the video you
were the only one who sent in a video um
even though I didn't ask for a video you
sent it anyway and I was like
wow she's
great okay who's next uh I
did I
did I need a drink I got to excite IG
who's okay n
n who do I want next
[Music]
ah who do I want you know what I know
who I
want
Hello hello Connie
[Music]
hello let me set
up hey thank you for being here crony
hey thank you nice clock I like your
clock it's very big um you you look
beautiful
today please please hold on a minute
while I set up um your
thing okay call
ready
Connie ah
okay every day every heart Le Lula don't
you hear the ringing
[Music]
La
Lae foree
[Music]
[Applause]
the time flows cruy unchanging in
humanity reach the point of no
[Music]
return okay
fore
[Music]
speee foree
life and death at every Tech Humanity
clings to the Past Nostalgia will they
ever escape from the change of time only
the clock will
[Music]
tell
for every
[Music]
heart don't you hear the ringing
yay thanks
[Music]
Connie thank you you're so cool you're
the best
hello I have control of you ha
yay thanks
Conny nice L
goodbye thank you for singing
me her song is so beautiful that was uh
that was Daydream by Oral crony I am
singing only senpai's original song so I
am whoever I am singing with it's their
original original song yeah so that's
crony's original song it's called
Daydream it's really
good really good oh G song yeah go check
it out she has nice voice it's
beautiful
okay moving
on who next
[Music]
maybe ID okay maybe ID maybe ID
now
hello
[Music]
hello you want to
sing okay we can sing together
when I will do my best
I like Mo's original song a lot
too I like all of the original songs a
lot all of them all of
them
[Music]
okay let us sing for you where is
it
wait I think 50 was good for her
hopefully you're action and your work a
little less so sorry for cutting you off
mon Senpai I'm so sorry I'm so
sorry I oil balances is is hard for me
I'm so toxic yes I am the toxic one for
cutting her off never
match little last still hold on
yeah this is fine let's start
over your action and yours will match on
trash and that's
[Music]
Sur let me feel that I'm not good enough
I give you my best but you're not
[Music]
impressed it falls aart you broke my
heart you're spreading more lies and
lies the lies I had it enough got it out
I am begging
no it's you the one who spread the words
that I am fake it's you the one who stab
me right in the B now you say I'm I
don't even really care anyway it's you
things but then I took the blame it's
you who miss the run and do hit and run
you made my days Liv hell now I don't
care it's you that's true I'm very
[Music]
toxic
W can hear y can hear y can hear
y [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] oh my head Falls
theart you broke my heart they spreading
more life and and I had it enough got it
out I beging no
more it's you the one who tried to make
me go insane it's you stop and feel
ashamed I think you're lame it's all in
vain I better just ignore it anyway if
you the want who turn my world upside
down it's you who break the rules and
pull me under the going away cuz you
can't stay now go to hell now tell
me you made me question my
reality now I have the last learn all I
need to know it's you the one who make
me feel that I am weak you word to so
hard make me black and blue I know the
truth but you deny who car about it
anyway it's you the one who spread the
light and then you it's you the one who
defeat and never regret I have to war
you you know this
karmic get
you screw this screw this SC this
I don't care I don't
care toxic it's
me I'm
toxic right I'm roxic right I'm so I'm
so toxic or maybe they're she's talking
about you
maybe maybe
Roxy yeah always have been
thank you
moai you're so beautiful I love your
song thank you for letting me rock out
with you yeah yeah beautiful beautiful M
Senai thank you so
much rock out what a
banger has has volume been okay for for
everyone so
far is everything good again I have to
like adjust everyone at different level
yes okay good volum is perfect
[Music]
okay okay e
n n who's
next let's keep the hype
up hello
[Music]
hello it's not
coming I wanted to but we had we had
decided it
before her music video came out but I
wanted I wanted to sing comed it's so
good it's so cool but we're going to
sing another cool one
though come hi hi hia you're in okay I
will do my
best oh go she's in she's watching oh I
better not be up her song just kidding I
will have
fun no pressure okay Kiara volume
was
that I need to hiccup hold on I need to
burp I don't know I'm muting for
this okay now I Dr water
no she muted why why didn't you just let
us hear oh what a
shame
oh oh the horror what a shame okay
[Music]
well wait not
ready
okay
[Music]
ready yeah k i r a i don't want to stop
it yet Eng relax Yeah Boy soon this I
you are new B all here now got me love
I'm knock down down down there's
something special about you when I see
you I know
[Music]
it's a you baby then I'm done yeah yeah
feel you love it I just can't resist you
your eyes are like a spell that I can't
break through and that should scare me
but I don't know baby you're captivating
me and in the end you let me go that's
just what we do love hate all the same
if you know play that game I'm up up I
can't fight the feeling and I won't try
love all the same if you know play that
game BBE you decide if you want me to
shout it out right now it's just a game
I can't complain I do the same do you do
you say you do feel the same like a
flame I know I'll never be the same do
you do you just game don't ever let
you're stop falling you got it cuz
Love's just like a tox the way pain is
so common your problem I can't solve it
I'm just a in love know that there more
than a crush so you can't save me I'm in
2D and I love the rush yeah I just can't
resist you your eyes are like a spell
that I can't break through and that you
scare me but I don't know baby you
captivating me and in the end you let me
go just what we do love hate all the
same if you know play the game I'm up
inside I can fight the feeling and I
will try hate all the same if you know
play the game baby you decide if you
want me and shout it out now
game stay do do you
you sp me like a flame no I never be the
same oh Z do you in the end just okay k
i a r a got me breathless oh yeah I'm by
you night and day how can something so
wrong be making me feel so right me down
down take me up just like you do I'm
always coming back to
you's Go game can't complain home do you
do you say you do feel like
me
like never be the
same you you in the end just just a game
we play
hat do
do love is just a game we play Love hat
and betray you
you
game
yeah uh-uh
I love I love do you I love it I I you
so
good good job that was great thank you K
thank you for singing with me thank you
thank
you I love CA
too go listen to all her songs her songs
are BS you can dance to them maybe you
won't dance as well as kiaha but you can
still I'll still dance to them anyway
thank you so much for singing with me
amazing amazing song so fun to
sing what time is it I can I can keep
track of
time for specific reasons and we should
be fine for one more maybe at least
another one yeah okay uh
[Music]
H what do I
want
okay hi Ali what are you doing here nice
outfit you you seem dressed up for a
party wow
hone
[Music]
hello okay
um Ollie is here hi
Ollie let St together
[Music]
happy
birthday doly I'm so excited to sing
this with you yeah all right so you
think the first line again was it you no
no it was you
[Music]
are you ready
good job you did such a great job thank
you this song is actually really hard
even for Mommy so doing our best shall
we let's
go for
[Music]
crazy
all I czy party
[Music]
night are you ready
all right people baby this will be the a
take a very deep
breath hey
night night stay up on my
johnyy yeah heyy night CRA night up on
[Music]
[Applause]
CRA happy birthday B boo thank you best
best best song for a
party
yay yay thank you Arie Mama thank you
Mama thank you
Mama you come here you come closer mama
you have a big hat
[Music]
mama you sing so
good A lot of these Senpai songs were so
hard for me to sing or learn because
they have RS you know my R problem
you'll see it in another song too that
that like there's a r the the Japanese R
there's there's some some some there's
another there's another one in there
somewhere with the with the
[Music]
with thank you a mama
I can roll my AR it's my birthday it's a
day it's a whistle day
too it's a it's a it's a it's a it's all
those days yeah real oh de de de
de there we go I know the trick now
thanks
Callie do I do it now
[Music]
now I do it now right do I do I do the
thing the the
thing Papa wait do we do we do
it the thing yes okay think about a
time hold on I have um
I've come to make an announcement coek
bizu is a beeping beeping no not that
one not that announcement not not not
that announcement hold on it uh the
other one
[Music]
uh this better be the first
one
H H oh
[Music]
ha I have come to make an announcement
conu has birthday merch well
surprise surprise everyone
hello we have we have birthday
merch and I am going to do my best to
promote it but I it should be pretty
easy though because everything is kind
of pretty cool so I don't think it'll be
hard to to hype this one up because look
at that art from Mo Mama M Mama did that
art look how cute it's it's sleepover
themed ha would you have guessed
it sleep look I think yeah wow it's so
on theme wow fluffy fluffy them okay
items so we
have boom bab Bo's birthday celebration
March 2024
wow amazing look at that cute picture of
iy bioo bi is so
iy but it's not time to e yet we just
began okay and then and
then we have these lovely items we have
a sleepy th tapestry a squishy Pebble
plushy look at that you know you wanted
it you wanted it I knew it that was like
the first thing that I wanted to do
you're welcome it's there squishy Pebble
plushy yes for
you there you go you can eat yourselves
please eat yourselves H and then we have
a people beu beu my name is bizu bizu
Motif t-shirt and we also have a ah
smiling mug um I wanted to call it ah
mug but uh I don't don't think ah mug
would have worked so we have a smiling
be mug we have a voice pack and and set
bonus postcard da da da okay and then
and
Thena this illustration was illustrated
by m mama mom mama and I also put a
special message on it and I will be
autographing them
yes limited
autographing We Will We Will autograph I
will autograph sign them for you uh
limitedly so you probably get it ASAP
because don't use my signature to forge
uh legal documents thank you have a nice
don't buy it for that buy it for the
cute uh art and yes okay anyway
boom sleepy time tapestry you can hang
me on your wall and you can watch me
sleep well I have an eye open but
yeah am I selling this good it's cute
isn't it it's so cute it's so it's so
cute look at the PJs that Mo mama do me
in and I have I have the the plushy and
then you can get the plushy and we can
match
yes my my plushy is a little bit bigger
than yours actually know it might be the
same size cuz I'm pretty small so that
might be too scale uh uh but yes look at
the amazing drawing by Mo Mama thank you
Mo mama you are the
best
amazing tapestry you can hang it on your
wall yeah po Pap and
then here it is the pebble plused it's
in
Japanese
I I hold
on well JP Nikki you can read
[Music]
this oh I found the English one okay
okay okay okay
ah that did not
happen we have a palm siiz squishy
plushy it's squishy you can squish it if
it's on your palm so you can put on your
desk or on your bed or wherever you can
it's perfect for yeting because it's
it's Palm size so it's like pebble is a
perfect but ye the plushy yes I will eat
it
um but yeah pebbles look it's you
I'm so excited about this one it's it's
you and and it will have googly eyes it
will it will have googly eyes on it
yeah oh also sales start uh on the hour
so like in 7 minutes by the way uh uh
Manan is is working on the links and
stuff so uh 7 Minutes uh the this the S
St yeah thank you m thank thank you um
but yes plushy look at how look at how
how how plushy it is and it got googly
eyes it has it has a embroidered gem on
it and and it's very cute and I'm very
excited for this one yes there we
go MAA here you
go and
then B Motif t-shirt you can get a
t-shirt to repr present beu it's got a
moai with flaps on it who else is a moai
with flaps me it has a little little
little embroidered moai moai flap it's
so cute and then on the back you got my
wings because wings are
cool yeah look at the look at my wing
it's on the t-shirt it's on the back you
can be kind of edgy with it I mean kind
of I mean Wings on the back are a pretty
edgy thing I guess of t-shirts so yeah
you can be edgy it's cool
represent people wear
it can we fly I uh uh maybe I haven't
tested it but maybe you can fly um
you'll have to get it and find out and
then let me know if you can fly uh with
it
yes hey thanks everybody you guys are
better at selling this than I am just
kidding
and then the ah mug it's a smiling beu
mug we all know what
the why my cute mug yes very cute cute
mug um I chose all of these thingies so
like it like feel like a sleepover thing
with a plushy and then a mug uh so you
can have ice cold water with you at 3:00
in the morning keep your beeble mug next
to you in bed
uh so when you are thirsty you can just
drink the water from it and it'll be
perfect yes cuz who doesn't love water
from a mug at 3:00 a.m.
yes yeah isn't it cute it look I can
match the face
ah we're like twins now ah yeah and it
has little little designs on it um and
stuff isn't it cute yeah you could put I
mean you don't have to put water in it
you could put like what Baja
Blast hot chocolate yeah hot chocolate
where is
coffee
um yeah yeah yeah yeah
um what whatever you want you can you
can whatever drink yes the mug it's
great isn't it cute it's so
cute I'm doing amazing by the
way uh oh situation voice pack midnight
gaming this hasn't happened yet this is
this is for when the stream is over and
we get to hang out um because the
sleepover party is not over yet so this
hasn't happen yet this is this is you
know late night gaming with you after to
the party yeah yeah yeah yeah it'll be
[Music]
fun yes cute cute video game time maybe
with beo what's going to happen who
knows it hasn't happened yet but you
guys should maybe check it out yeah it
it it it'll be pretty nice to hang out
with you guys yeah that that I'm excited
and then and then and then and
then that's the that yay I did it I did
it all by
myself um bu by so we have two bundal
sales limited edition and complete set
yes limited edition and complete set a
limited edition will have the the
autograph on it uh don't for B Boo's
signature uh but yes that will be there
um don't write Ransom notes and be was
handwriting uh anyway so yeah that that
get that as soon as possible cuz a lot
of people want to use my handwriting for
ransom notes um and you know the stuff
is pretty good too right yeah uh and
then the regular set is also a set uh
and then you can have the individual
sales of the items and then individual
sales of the voice pack too
Japanese D I mention I also will speak
to you in Japanese later as well
yes the voice pack has has Japanese so I
will speak to you in both and both
English and uh Japanese oh thank you
thank you
Manan where where is it did I save
[Music]
it yes I did but I don't know where it
is uh
oh T here is a Japanese version for uh
DP so you can read it too yay we can all
read uh 1 minute can I have the link in
the pin can I pin the link the the the
good luck everyone we're going to we're
going to pin the link and then we'll
come back here and sing some
more yeah yeah the sales start in in 1
[Music]
minute put the put the link in the pin
maybe oh oh oh oh okay thank you thank
you thank you thank you thank you thank
you okay
go okay go I'll be be here I'll be here
if you want
um there you go okay so that is my merch
do you like
it what do you mean 404 not
found hold
[Music]
on I'll put this over here
good luck
everyone oh use the second one the
second link
work the second I'll pin the second link
so you are not confused
[Music]
uh
okay and then I will pin this one there
we go that link should work but yeah I
hope you like it I'm very especially
excited for the pebble plushy and I know
that a lot of you were excited all of
you were asking for a pebble plushy of
course it was going to be the first
thing I made
yeah so
enjoy
okay I'm going to go back to singing now
cuz we got we still got some Senpai
songs to
do where do I put
[Music]
this I'll just put it in the
corner
yay I'm a
professional yay
I hope I I totally sold it I mean
obviously Pebble plushy just speaks for
itself so yeah I did great okay
congratulations if you if you got my
merch congrats first ever birthday merch
that's pretty
special
okay I'm going back to singing what do
we on Ian now
also the schedule might get scheduled
off whenever
because you know things happen and I did
not test how much time I was going to
need so plus or minus if I'm late to my
own stream whatever it's my stream so
also Space Jam is not that long anyway I
have buffer so don't worry about it
[Music]
oh the other links are in the
description thank you
man the other the other links are
in
the description check the links in the
description of the one Pinn is not
working
[Music]
yes okay anyway back to singing
now oh I know who I
want hey
hak yes hello welcome we're going back
to singing
now do you like my merch hak
Bello yeah your merch is so cool I want
all of it thank you hakos b i KN see
Haka B likes it so obviously it's cool
yes h
B let's sing
together let me not hum your song while
I'm setting this up to spoil what song
you are going to sing in about a minute
[Music]
uh
okay h Bells is at a good
volume
hopefully my Reverb should be
back
okay
uh
Hey chaos the end of ends a steel rose
trapped in a cave of
ice this
is hako Bells hey yo what's up did on my
soul witness
me yeah it's like she's here it's like
she's she's
here wow anyway let's
see wait wait my my background
my okay okay okay
[Music]
okay now listen now time for something
new it's going get
crazy they want a revolution we'll give
it to them take a stand out my wish is
[Music]
your ride run away to get all this place
was
[Music]
run
away R run away I won't stay in my own
lane
till R run
away night
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm SC a loser too bad I've heard it all
before
all I need tell
my that makes your heart Bo start up the
party we going
[Music]
get will keep you on your feet
you run away always keep you guessing my
[Music]
into the
night ladies and gentlemen yeah yeah
yeah let's turn these streets into a
[Applause]
[Music]
r run away got to get
[Applause]
[Music]
to the night
[Applause]
witness thank you H
Bell witness
her
woo thank you H Bell
you are great my sis thank
you I love your song it's so cetty it's
fun to sing run away but it's all
ours I I'm kind of mad at you because
it's it's literally all ours and I don't
like that but it was still fun to learn
so bye
[Music]
H thank
you for your song nice
[Music]
okay who's next I know I know who I want
to
sing
welcome is
hello I will do my best to is some you
are so amazing I will do my best to try
to make you
proud cuz your songs are so
good I will become as I will try to
become as strong as you one day yes this
nuts
okay boom and then Vol you
okay you
[Music]
that I'll restart it over I don't want
you to get it cut off okay here we go
[Music]
is that too loud that might be a little
too loud oh that's a little loud okay
hold on hold on hold
[Music]
on how
this still loud oh that's pretty loud
okay how
this okay that's pretty good
[Music]
better
okay still loud really wa really okay
I'll do like 15 it's already okay I'm
starting over I think this will be good
[Music]
hopefully
you why is he
[Music]
quiet this is not the first
time is that is she still quiet
voice quiet races too low
oh yeah it's together how should
I fix it's it's on one
track
um you know what we'll just
I'll just get drowned out just a little
bit okay it's
fine I just don't my
[Music]
that window
hopefully you won't
[Music]
see this is not the first
time yeah
she maybe maybe I can get many CH to
help ah I many time do you know how to
equalize
[Music]
music hold
on
[Music]
uh okay I will sing the other songs
first Manan will do Manny Tan's best
we'll come back Tois we'll come back
toai we'll come back get some help okay
fine I'll say your song then I'll fine
I'll sing your song sure why not why not
you're here I'll just sing your song
[Music]
then
Kyla Kyla okay fine your turn then if
you're here you'll get some help okay
[Music]
um did you know that I we both died she
died and I died learning this song I'm
in plane you have
[Music]
go
up
feeling
L this
[Music]
frustrated caught in Twist of this
life
[Music]
complexity
forevering roller Coter inity my soul is
graving for it's getting hard to
suffocating in the grip of my Shattered
Dreams Chasing Rainbows drowning in
shadowed Moon beams tears streaming down
I'm searching for reason
why I'm
breaking free from these
chain no matter how hard it get I got to
keep on moving
you
can take my
life away I just W to be free please set
me free Let
Me
Be
Me Yeah Final Boss music who's playing
[Music]
in
this of
[Music]
inconsistency I'm the
emotional storm that is approaching
longing
for Simplicity
[Music]
myself in the forever I'm dring in the
oce of my un frustration and the
Darkness lost my way this love keep
going suffocating in the grip of my
Shattered Dreams Chasing Rainbows
drowning in shattered Moon
beams Me Myself and die
[Applause]
[Music]
I'm
breaking free from these
CH no matter how hard it gets I got to
keep on
[Music]
moving you
can take my
life away I just want to be free please
set me free let me
be
me Set Me
Free tears dreaming down I'm searching
for But Me Myself and
[Applause]
happy birthday p
[Music]
okay I already lost how long can you
hold your thing for also she said she
had a birthday message for
me hold on I got to download it see I
didn't open it Kyla I didn't open
it so I'm want to open it now thank you
for singing with me by
way
ah open later for be your birthday okay
it's later
now okay I'm packing my stuff right now
because I'll be living for my family's
vacation soon uhhuh yeah it's just
unfortunate perfect timing that your
birthday in your time zone yeah how
unfortunate but it's okay I guess I this
tce to
say have a great birthday my
grandpa what do you mean
grandpaa okay what should I say I don't
know just don't die sleep
well you you too I guess we never know
what kind of sickness that was Spa right
like at I'm tired I'm fine I'm a rock
what about you watch out for
yourself I guess just get good and get
some help oh yeah and one more thing
before I go
what what
what that's it what do you mean one more
thing what do you mean you can't do what
do you mean one more
thing get some help Kyla get get some
help days were the birthday message I
guess okay well that was
um back seat by KY
Kos one more thing what I thought you
want a plane I thought you had 5 minutes
it's like been 5
minutes happy birthday wait it's my
birthday well they for visiting what
what is that oh she she left on me okay
well I'm going to take a drink of water
she hadn't said anything by the time I
drank anything she she's gone she's
gone
okay what's one more
thing h
thanks Kyla
Kyla have have a a safe trip
okay who
[Music]
name oh let's do this
one
uh Hey
Callie you want to sing together and
then play Monster Hunter later please
[Music]
please I did not touch Monster Hunter at
all that's how like committed I was to
learning all these songs and preparing I
didn't not touch mon at all for like the
past two days I was I felt hurt and pain
I wanted to play but let's say let's say
OKC's here too loud welcome oh pressure
oh it's f fine it's fine it's fine it's
fine I'll do my
best M it's my birthday everything I do
is perfect today right
[Music]
yeah okay let's sing Carie my wife
no
[Music]
pressure I have so many things open
woohoo happy birthday boo thank
[Music]
you
stand man up say the and swe when the
gets rough and not until the last
emtional Still rocking back with every
surv we out of this world St connect cuz
when you chips down your CS out the
queen on
[Music]
enough to Fascinate us
can't
[Music]
and why should I be trying for a dream
ding every day is around for again you
know doesn't Su steady flow Still Still
thrill keep your eyes in your baby
[Music]
fellas what's that stop feeling sorry
just act I still don't care may lay it
down a million times get when I get my
sh night
[Music]
Tombstone shoot across the sky with the
bad
guys enough it's all right we got a
couple fights you know
yeah come on
[Music]
everybody
i'ms my
[Music]
us
can't happy birthday B thank you how
dare you you knew my problem with r
words and you still chose a song that
had r in it like what the
be how do you even say
[Music]
that you
you die die
[Music]
how dare
you oh I see that smile nice
[Music]
smile I I could not I practiced that so
many times but I
could it for the end thank you that's
such a cool song and I like rapping in
Japanese it's fun please let's sing more
Japanese WRA together so I get better at
it yeah yay thank you kie okay now play
Monster hunting with me thank you nice
nice good good good
song what time do I have oh we're we're
good we're we're we're
on we're on time we're on we're on we're
on good time wow okay cool
um thanks Skye thanks moli thank you my
wife you're at a spot F she said it
was my C on my RAB fire you hear that
hear that take it take that ho
ho okay um um um um okay
um uh who haven't I
done oh ID now okay
I want to do my best your song Cobalt
was the hardest song for me to learn
um because you are just that op I guess
but I feel like learning your song
helped me make a b better singer so so I
will do my best no guarantees though cuz
this was was really hard for me to learn
it I but I
I I my best
[Music]
okay yes it's a gift she's she's GIF GIF
she's dancing on my table or on my couch
it's fine you can stay
[Music]
there
oh Manny might have pulled through too
with the resu thing thank you
[Music]
m f fun fun fact Mar Tan's profile
picture on Discord is a moai statue with
like an apron that says best mom on it
and I do it for
her because that's what I feel
[Music]
like
um okay
[Music]
uh okay there's
Copo but yes I was drinking thank you
you have a great year this year and be a
better Rock I will be a better Rock and
let's see together okay BR together okay
okay
okay okay okay okay yeah
[Music]
help help okay your turn but help me
please come on okay okay
[Music]
wow
help what did you
say what
please go
[Music]
awayy for
okay bye oh
bye
okay thanks
[Music]
coo yes thank coobo that was fun why
listen to her song it's so catchy and
she just came out with it help help help
her by listening to it it's Cy it's fine
okay bye coobo bye thank you thank
[Music]
you it's really good
yeah the way she singing this so CL
[Music]
yeah
anyway yeah she's
[Music]
cool e n have i n am I missing I am
oh yeah let's do this
one hello hello F
hello
hello hi F thank you for the thank you
for the redirect by the way I'm late uh
uh thank you for the r hi s please I
hope you had a fun time on F's uh stream
yes
o um I been like an hourly for that but
whatever thank f
not ready not ready not ready I'm not
ready I'm not ready
[Music]
please
ready this is
a a preview as I drink water before we
sing
together okay
rainbow in
[Music]
the Gree
it's just
a fairy tale so it'll melt the away like
a
lollipop hiding a flying whe wondering
when I'll wake up oh
gu let me stay here
[Music]
R Ringle
roses and Laing up and down I want to
stay here forever ring ring
roses
and up and
[Music]
what it
was just my dream the golden sunlight
shows it's time to wake up waiting
quietly shutting my eyes and I S oh guy
what let we stay here
[Music]
yay thanks FAA I sold her I told her
this before uh when we did a collab or
first coll her song is my favorite song
of H life live and it's still true it's
still true it's so cute it is perfect
for her voice and has best like feeling
it and I'm happy that I get to
finally sing with her yes that that was
the thought yes that was the thought ah
sold what do you mean sold what what did
I say I told her what do you mean sold I
said told
to t t don't tell me I getting my other
letters mixed up too I said I said told
did did I say sold oh I told her that
that that that her song is my favorite
[Music]
yeah let's see man did you cook
thank you
fa oh you're the best man I love fa okay
bye-bye oh I I need to pick it up a bit
okay it it's it's fine it's fine the I
have I have I have
um buffer I have buffer time
because Space Jam is not that long okay
okay let's try
again that's
[Music]
loud let me just test the voice make it
stop what to get
tell me what's this
EMP hold on I have I have another
version it works but it's a little bit
clippy but hold on I have a that was the
even louder version
maybe the louder wor
[Music]
better can't see okay I will do my best
I'm so sorry
we are doing our best despite the Scuf
your voice is
[Music]
amazing light reflection on my window
hopefully you won't see
me I put the face that has been we out
just
today this is not the first time one one
by the gr to to me I can't seem to make
it St
my oh my tell me should I just start to
let you go
baby everywhere I go memories within me
still remain so strong but I can't go on
WE
M to get B tell me what's this EMP that
keep hold me for moving on
[Music]
me
goating m
so surely is it for me is it for you
tell
me light reflection on my
window hopefully you won't see me
I put the face has been BN out just
today
again the clock to
me to make it
[Music]
stop everywhere I go memories s in me
still remain so strong but I can't go
on TR of the past get by tell me what's
this emptiness hry H moving on
everywhere I go all the voice surrounds
me still remain so loud and I can't go
on Li Melodies so praise
surely is it for me is it for you tell
[Music]
me all I ever wanted was to
singe I forget how high this
[Music]
[Applause]
was everyone where I go memories within
me still remain so strong but I can't go
on repeating Melodies of the to
together tell me what's this EMP that
keep holding me from moving on
everywhere I go
over me still remain so loud and it
can't go
is it for me is it for
you is it for me is it for you I can
hear it any time you
[Music]
I am so
sorry she's too
powerful Mr Senai on a different stream
I am going to fix you know what in
between streams I am going to fix the
the the thing myself the audio
balancing and then and then and then we
will sing at the end of the night just
you all me together okay
yeah yeah yeah we'll we'll we'll fix
than I can't see so I I was laughing too
hard thank you thank you f i I will uh
we'll we'll we'll do another we'll do a
Encore duet uh
when what I'm sorry it's okay I if you
didn't fail
me you content but if Ru somebody gets
mad at me I am totally blaming
you okay yeah but we'll we'll do another
uh Encore
uh when I in between stream so I will
fix it okay uh we are done
okay oh I I can make it I can make it in
time an Senai hello hello an Senai hello
hello
[Music]
hellooo um
what is
it where is
it h is
[Music]
I break down Everlasting knife okay cool
I'll never break down Everlasting night
yeah
[Music]
I
oh
oh uhoh
[Music]
I'll never break down Everlasting night
he he he hey I still laughing from the
other older
[Music]
ah ah ah ah I can do this ah ah ah
ah foree
[Music]
okay I got the
ending I'll never break down Everlasting
night Everlasting
[Music]
KN I am so
sorry are you was also super hard to
learn
but I'm still kind of flustered from the
from the oh I'm so sorry I'm getting
blinked but I will do an encore of that
I will do an encore of that at the end
at the anything that I mess up I'm going
to do an encore of it at the at the
other stream the 1:00 a.m. to the
midnight stream when I when I'm calm
again feel the bathroom I
go here this this one this one we can I
can do this
one without without
without without laughing um yes we're
going to Encore that one
m
m m yes okay we have you did your I'm so
sorry I'm going to do I'm going to do
I'm going to do do a a Encore of that
one again we're going to sing that one
again and re that my song again
because your song is so Good by the way
I love it though I love it so much I
love how it sounds give it more reals
everybody go see it it's so good it it
sounds like so cool I
like yeah it's so cool but it's hard to
learn because it's like it's like a
different a different like style then I
think yeah
we're moving now thank you H thank you
sen you have another stream in two
minutes it's okay I have buffer time I
have
buffer
um okay
volume moment
[Music]
wait for you just finish say thank
youa happy birthday Biv B by boo thank
you song Let's
[Music]
[Applause]
Go for
[Music]
know mama
foree
[Music]
I
fore
[Music]
for say ah ah
mama
[Music]
yay I always do my best to try not to
cry when I sing that one because M your
song is too
powerful I love you thank you for
singing with me and be emotional on my
birthday
you're the best thank you thank you for
singing with
me uh one more song and
then we will hop over
to next
uh next we'll hop over to to
uh space
j then we will slam and welcome to J I
know the song that's all I know
oh you're
big
Yi okay
[Music]
it it's good enough maybe a little bit
higher so take I
answer clap your hand Give Me Love need
you love I need you love let me know if
you love me I'll move on all my love
give me love give me love need you love
I need you love let me know you love me
I'll move on with all my love
[Music]
I forgot
oh I got it
[Music]
and
answer leave it up give it up get it up
to get it up
hands up pick me up pick me up take you
take you up jum
jump start it up and down leave it up it
get it up get it hands off hands off
pick me off pick me off take you off
take you off jump off jump off start it
off
[Music]
me tell
for and answer
you give
[Music]
me give me love me love need you
love let me know you love me I'll move
on with all my love give me love give me
love need you love I need you love let
me love you love me I'll move on with
all my love give me love give me love
happy birthday people thank you I love
you thank you thank you thank you
than go I let's also play Monster Hunter
together let's also play Monster Hunter
together
[Music]
okay karaoke please listen to all of the
original songs they they will do it
better Justice than I ever
could but um it is time for movie we are
going to be watching Space Jam it is not
over yet the the bble Tano bble is only
just begun uh but I think I
need I I think it's time you know to
change into like something
something
comfortable
yay let's watch space j together yes I
have
pgs this is this is the rest of the
night is comfy comfy time so I hope you
enjoyed Senai karaoke I'm going to
redirect you to the next part of the
Stream let's go together thank you for
waiting for me we still have lots to
do happy birthday people
[Music]
l