[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
assistant
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you foreign
[Music]
flower
[Laughter]
it looks cute Baba Kiara again
[Applause]
I didn't know we were playing Among Us
I think we are down because it's kind of
it feels it feels like I'm intruding on
a niji Ian girls collab did someone get
sick and I had to come in
[Laughter]
[Music]
I have a bone to pick with all of you I
sent you all a tick tock this morning in
our group chat oh yeah
aha Nina This Is Us
yeah I didn't even watch sorry yeah
[Music]
okay my parents did the same thing they
sent me like tick tocks and it takes me
like five days to watch them I don't
even have tick tock
so yeah
wow sorry guys out zoomering everybody
I've never like been on Tick Tock it's
only when people send me like Tick Tock
links yeah yeah yeah
okay thank you girls
I feel amazing send me YouTube shorts
how is everybody else doing huh welcome
to this welcome we organized Nina put it
together yes
even though Nina is not streaming
I honestly just want to hang out with
the girlies I'll should we introduce
ourselves
yeah yeah where do we start from
I think we start with you okay we're not
opening my Tick Tock for admitting
because
I was the first to admit it it made it
easier for the others to admit it it's
true oh okay I know I'm not afraid to
disappoint Nina ever we're gonna do a
voice voice like uh volume check as well
while doing this and my view is already
telling me Nina is low so I'm raising
her don't worry don't worry I've never
had anyone tell me that before
I guess from Whole Life English uh I am
intruding today on this lovely cute
collab with these girls I'm so happy I
put a lot of cuteness into the thumbnail
I think it kind of looks like a purikura
thumbnail
[Music]
the gross I look like yeah insect every
time I take pretty cool
we took put
[Laughter]
yes the time I asked roseme and rainbow
to take a break with me and they said
later
yeah
everyone under the bus today
it's just we said we'll come back and
then we forgot or something I have one
question girls are you playing uh Uno
with controller now or with keyboard and
mouse
yeah that's how I think I used to play
and now I don't know how to jump but the
jump in button is for a keyboard do you
guys know I think it's w yeah it's gonna
say it on the screen it's gonna be like
press yeah W or e or something yeah okay
you can win a lot playing with
controller uh no I don't think so tilt
controllers
maybe try changing the Boston keyboard
hey that is no that cannot possibly be
the reason no no no anyway I'm gonna
throw the the button of itself
introduction over to Rosemary
okay
um okay wait I'm nervous
um hi everyone I'm rosami
um
Rosemary The Rock to me I am also the
rock if there were an actor who would
play me in real life it would be the
rock I believe that 100
me too before
I mean I have don't you remember showing
me your underwear
you guys wanted exactly okay here it is
missed out on a precious moment that
sounds worse than it is
I think you like being beat red I was
just taking the back I was like whoa
you know I told that um story actually
on my stream before yes very detailed
I feel like that's all you'll ever think
about now
no she's never gonna show you her
underwear again oh no yeah you better
have ingrained it in your memory
every little ruffle Every Little River
yes
memory
[Laughter]
it was really cute it was really cute
we go to the next Angel
um
how is the volume for everybody so far
you guys yeah
us who's quiet who's loud tell us yeah
for the streamers we will fix it volume
good okay resume a little low okay
I up you I had you a little down
actually so
I can audio good nice nice nice
nice
who gets
okay probably did yeah I gave her the
yeah I give it to you Puma oh okay
I'm almost
like
an actor were to play me it would be
Jack Black
we made that a thing huh
you are not Pomo what because your
reactive images is blonde right now I
thought I was meeting uh oh yeah
silver-haired girl today what the hell
oh I am I'm I'm you know I'm a silver
fox you know uh more foxy than the other
foxes the actual fox that's here oh yeah
that looks more like a cat as long as
that makes you happy
I'm looking at the screen and I think
we're all a bunch of little gray people
except the actual silver fox
I'm Gray
yeah you don't have a profile picture
I was not on board I did not understand
you're catching my jokes when they flop
thanks by the way for buying me Uno oh
yeah
did you see my message with it no no
oh come about me Uno even though I had
it on my Xbox
you have Uno
for real though
and Nina we had to buy it a second time
just say this really quietly I feel like
every few months I buy Uno again and
again on both my Steam account and I
genuinely feel like I've bought Uno's
seven times already yeah I don't
understand where my Uno game is going
why am I playing now
I see what you're doing it's like it's
they're making it realistic you know in
real life like when you use like your
deck of cards like you have to keep
buying it right so like you're just
making it realistic you're like right
one behind the couch yeah yeah you'll
forget at the park keep buying it
[Laughter]
you call me a grandma too
I think he's doing it on purpose he's
trying to rob me of my money
John Uno
okay
you can't just buy it once you know
wait an introduction one get it yeah get
it because Uno is one one yeah yeah
that's about it do you understand wow
well next by dosa one
I'm so sorry everyone
okay is it my turn yes yes
hi honey
okay if you want a real tone change hi
honey I am Nina kosaka of niji Sanji
Ian's third wave etherea and I must be
in luck today hello everybody it's a
pleasure to be here with you
um I am excited I organize this collab
because I want to hang out with the cute
girls I already opened up some wine I'm
having a nice glass and I'm ready for
all the embarrassing botsus and all the
fun times yeah
oh my God I have I haven't heard that's
like debut Nina I know
the voice is too powerful
[Music]
the whole atmosphere changed
it's fine it's fine I guess I can stay a
little cute but I would have a list of
batsu games on the bats of wheel I'm not
showing it on screen but there is
um the famous good old baby voice the
grandmother is the robot voice like I am
robot let's talk like this did you
demonstrating the other two voices oh
yeah the first two human baby boys
Uno in the park
robot voice yes and British accent and
singing while talking and then yeah
after every sentence
let's go
that's it oh that's it yeah
I know
he's Flawless and everything she does
well suck this game clearly she just
told us
no uh we will see who has the most cards
left after at that point when the game
is over oh my God
after each round will have to do a bats
game
[Music]
yes no matter how long you I want you
girls to be committed okay oh yeah okay
it's about drive it's about power
what is that uh you when you have a
seven you switch cards with the person
of your choice zero it goes it's the
whole board right yeah oh okay okay
just
crashed maybe you can get back in I feel
like that happened before
it's a box I think we should remake it I
think we should yeah yeah yeah maybe we
waited in the lobby for two hours
yeah okay okay
either
dude was there a game audio settings
yeah you can put it up or down I think
it's like elevator music yeah it's like
funky like background music
a routing issue let me fix it system
my chat is saying Nina Auto loss give
her a botsu oh
[Laughter]
I'm Not Afraid oh
I'm Not Afraid hit me hit me oh okay for
real all right all right girl he really
wants that bad too my wheel is spinning
it's gonna be oh wonderful a British
accent
why British accent is Pang in it what
absolutely pink oh my gosh the British
slang who knows no way boy
it's like a hot like if you see a hot
lady walking by you can say ooh Peng or
if that's a pain
sounds like you're saying
in it
in love
I am trying to join your game
let me reinvite you no I think it should
it's loading
a white bird
Nina I'm already in your lobby
I'm going to reinvite you again
and now it's stuck on my screen
talking when we get into the game
so I don't know if you really like being
better she can be British all the time
be British all the time don't let don't
let Society tell you whether you should
be British or not
I want to hear British Nina
I love British
oh wait I did yeah
me
morning let us play come on I want to
play I wanna play a game
play play
loading and it's still loading so slow
oh wait I think I'm in
here let's go nice time
don't crash don't crash don't crash game
[Music]
Nina
reconnecting try try like getting back
in some maybe or or someone else can
make the lobby
hi yeah you make the lobby I I couldn't
even hear you on Discord oh is that your
internet no I don't think so I have oh I
have really good internet
Lobby
why do I want now it's been a British
accent oh my God I had the best hand too
I was ready to go all out are we
quitting I guess yeah I just told me it
did the bot just close to me
they'll quit okay me too
I was totally gonna win this one
wait Nina are you making the room again
please one of you make the room yeah
because I got another invite from you
for me okay classic
it's not you
so we're doing the jump in the 7-0
and that's it oh yeah I think that
sounds good for now we can change rooms
later too okay I know there's like a
Teemo we can do like two V2s
okay I invite you guys
invite friend
uh we're not friends we're just
co-workers wait I can see you guys oh
invite the game but since we are not
co-workers are we friends
absolutely
I'm friends with everyone except
that's true how can you how can
a friend of Pomo because everybody is
pomu
she got you there Nina
um
[Music]
she banned you what yep I know I timed
you out
and you went into the chat and said
everybody spam
you emitting the details
damn why did you do that would you like
to object
yes objection oh I said homu is very
cute today please spam so it covers my
text and she doesn't see it
so yes I said please stop but
we're playing a different game now
Nina are you gonna join the game yeah
wait it's it's like black screening me
I'm sorry
I was betraying you you know the worst
part too is the only reason I didn't
check Uno is because I played Uno like
two or three months ago and everything
was fine yeah but things changed
[Music]
yeah it'll be soft it's like you
Nina
I will I will everything up for you
now thank you
you'll get it you'll get there Coco you
can do it okay though just in case can
you guys buy the game on switch Yeah
okay it's just okay I have a feeling we
might have to do the switch Uno oh my
God I I don't even I haven't I don't
have my switch like set up to my PC no
that would take like two minutes but
oh yeah we can also play a Mario Party
no
listen I am a big fan of Mario party so
yeah
oh yeah but just because the the
downloading thing but yeah should be fun
but let's let's try this come on Ubisoft
PC version let's go come on come on come
on it's it should be loading now I
believe you check this board real quick
um
I see I'm just buying a Uno on the
switch right now
I don't even know if mine is set up
either
oh my God no yeah should I go set it up
she's playing Uno Nina
what I don't understand is previously it
opened Uno and now it's not even opening
yeah actually maybe Monopoly would work
right
let's do one player though
all right
I love Monopoly wait I only played a lot
I played it for the first time like a
few weeks ago
I will play Monopoly review but I only
have it on the switch
I just bought Uno on the switch
[Laughter]
do you need to buy like Monopoly if one
person is control well it might be
different on the switch it might work
the only reason we do one person on on
PC is because everybody else crashes
every time
hold on I since y'all three are
streaming give me two minutes I don't
know why I'm just gonna reset my PC
sometimes that works you know sometimes
when things don't work so yeah right
back have you tried resetting your PC
genuinely okay
I was gonna suggest that but you know
okay right back simultaneously I'm also
setting up my switch as we speak oh you
know what I should do that too she's a
multitasking girl not really but
these uh desperate times call for
desperate measures
people people Monopoly
[Music]
what's up
yeah okay I already have Uno on switch
interestingly and I have Monopoly on
switch so I'm ready for whatever like
bring it on baby
[Music]
and Kirsten does the encourse apply to
ninja Sanji too it does
I think it is a widespread virus I think
I think I know what the cause is though
oh can I just say it
yeah that all of us little shits do not
test the games before could that be
could that be the cause it's like this
game so many times I don't know I've
played this game yeah but then again
but then again it's not really yeah you
know you know but then again the Ian
curse also happens so often that should
be a lesson to us to also test
everything then because if the encourse
keeps on reappearing and we should also
test things I'm also a culprit though
back operation that I organized huh
I just you know if anybody has any
concerns complaints or anything direct
them to me okay I should have checked
the game and I didn't so please
for this one we can blame them
I swear from now on I will triple check
every game even the ones that I played
like the date
Nina
yeah yeah how how long have you been in
niji sanjian
uh too long
sometimes I don't install a game until
15 minutes
maybe sometimes in my early days but I
stopped doing that I I installed at
least a day before because you know what
part of the difference between you and I
is that you are what the people call a
professional yeah no
[Laughter]
okay I'm inviting you
[Music]
invite me invite okay don't get too
excited yeah the case is no longer we've
broken the curse you don't believe you
don't believe
yeah look at her she's like it's stalled
the game early what's what's next wait
before the scream starts
oh
man okay okay looking promising it's
gonna switch up the order again
you're still there you're still there
though yeah oh no yeah
she's banned how about this how about
this I can just react to the robot and
pretend it's me playing
and after the boxes if the robot loses I
just don't want to keep delaying this I
have Uno on switch ready to go yeah I
can download it right now if you want
I seriously need it yeah where I just
like pretend to be the robot and if the
robot loses I do the batsu we could do
that while we wait for the game to
download on the switch yeah let's do
that we can like play something else or
play it on the switch it's up to you
guys
whatever you guys want I just don't want
to make people wait you know I have two
Uno's open right now
I'm the multitasker let's go
I'm excited
I'm playing with the robot no I I know
you made me skip my turn
oh sorry
what are they gonna change it to no you
fool it's my turn it is I the AI green
come on
oh
yeah
does everybody have to pay for Uno and
then download it or is it just uh I
think so I have I'm downloading it right
now okay okay my switch is all set up
no
oh Chihuahua left oh probably inactivity
because I just
I'm not much of a
multitasker it's just a normal one right
it's like a Ultimate Edition
oh okay I have to
and okay well I'll hide this for a
moment my second Uno he's not gonna see
it this is the second who knows
what is going on hey you just get my
turn
come on Nina bot is too strong I know
all right I was like you know what the
bot can play because then I'd win
finally had to add friends again
I could finally have a victory
I forgot how to add friends
um
[Music]
thank you okay it's been a long time
since I added new Switch friends I don't
I forgot
it's a new time oh yeah oh I'll add you
guys let me grab my I think uh only one
of us has to add you right because uh
yeah I guess because somebody makes a la
room
so it's easier for you okay
wait you know am I friends with you or
yeah we are are you asking this question
again wait why is my Uno download so
slow on the switch why what is happening
the womb really
[Music]
mine's not even well
nine minutes nine minutes it's gonna be
faster than that
for all the Kiara fans this is something
new right
I think it's fine this is exciting
just imagine that because of scuff we
moved the stream to one hour later but
here you see the behind the scenes now
yeah we we're so we all got together so
early too we were ready yeah what
happened
yeah oh I can put in the wrong oh oh oh
sorry I'm putting in the friend code for
Nina
people in my chat are asking if you
verified your game files did you try it
out I'm already friends with you
foreign
that's why we shouldn't play UNO anymore
we should move on to something even
better which is Monopoly Monopoly I'm
telling you nothing I I say you play
Monopoly because if y'all want to I
don't mind I have eight minutes
promo what you can't say no it's three
versus one sorry I'm fine with whatever
I'm gaming sorry and I'm eating my bread
okay with her to be fair but I I don't
know what's happening
[Music]
it's fun
this is the only Uno now this is the oh
or Monopoly Monopoly
Monopoly
all by yourself
roseme's here too how dare you insult
her like that no no how can you be
playing all by yourself you can even
just pursued me no no no that was a real
bad that was around
uh question if you're getting Monopoly
on
switch right yeah or on yeah okay yeah
wait so do I have to buy it too yeah oh
then I would have to download it it
might still take some time we should do
the thing that's faster
what for me but we are so okay wait I
just need to confirm it's Monopoly for
Nintendo switch
49.99 yeah no but no no go for Uno
because they're already downloading Uno
right we can just play it on the PC and
have one person like control it like we
did when Pullman and I played recently
no no I don't mind buying it I just
wanted to complain about the price
you know
two girls here downloading Uno at this
very moment yeah so let's just wait for
that let's just wait for that let's just
wait okay
okay I just want everybody to understand
I will complain but I'll still do it
let's do Monopoly another time
okay so in this Uno downloading waiting
time
[Laughter]
oh really
yeah
what
oh yeah yeah that's good that's good
that wasn't that good what's the
percentage
what
they'll be getting so so heated so
excited I'm not even playing I'm alone
why did you do that I don't know
I was gonna ask you a question Kiara
since you're here um how are you
enjoying Metroid oh yeah oh my God I
finished it yesterday I love Metroid
Prime I am so happy I'm so happy what
did you play the game
um I I recommend it but it was like um I
had a lot of fun with it in the middle
and up until the end when at the end the
match the the fission metroids were
absolutely tilting me and and the last
two boss fights were also absolutely
tilting me but besides that it was a lot
of fun
understandable yeah yeah did you play
the whole thing
I play Metroid Prime like over a decade
I didn't play the remastered I didn't
play yet oh well yeah I also just
remember like playing the game when I
was a child but I didn't really play it
I was just like on the screen running
around in the very place where you spawn
when you start the game because it was
too scary I wouldn't go any further yeah
I thought it was awesome honestly I was
like oh my God like it was a bit scary I
do agree but I was like this is so cool
I think your impression now would be
very different though you should play
old games that you played million years
ago you should play them now and see how
they changed for you oh yeah I used to
be like that as a kid if like if the
game was too scary at the beginning I
just couldn't play it oh yeah yeah me
too
the remastered there's one as many games
that I like Oh onekin I thought was
really scary when I was young was um
Final Fantasy VII I don't like their
dream but the the overarching like theme
of the game was so scary to me you know
I know Stephanie Rod was scary but he
was cool okay I saw something so cursed
today about Final Fantasy VII that I
can't believe is real
wasn't there recently a remake of Final
Fantasy VII yeah
um yeah yeah I saw a clip where the main
character what is his name Cloud
he gets seduced by her hand massage
person
and I'm like this cannot be from the
actual game ride because he's moaning
he's moaning and
is this the kind of game final fantasy
is I was so confused like I thought this
was fan made like yeah it's so ya bit I
think so what
what what
kind of processing yeah I don't even
remember I remembered I think that
District that area no it's real it's
real it is real it's like you get the
choice apparently between free massages
one where he's like you know I don't
know suffering having a bad experience
but anyway one of them is being like
kind of seduced from a pretty young lady
you know in a kimono and yeah oh he's
like can you log into the thingy he's
moaning sorry yeah
what is happening uh switchy oh
my gosh
Nina you did it I know imagine this one
crashes
Uno on the switch
but yeah oh my God Kiara that's so I'm
so sorry for interrupting that that is
such a oh I feel like
imagine oh I don't know I was so funny
oh there goes Rose in me now I'm
actually playing by myself
[Laughter]
it was Kiara would have had her win
he would have been able to batsu all of
us baby girl
okay now they're just bullying me I'm
good I'm leaving my download's almost
done
okay imitation wait what
hello
is downloading Rainbow Six Siege while I
was playing Uno
it's like your download has not been
completed like what download wait a
second you just have to log into the
Ubisoft account as well in this switch
version just one second
yeah give me a sec let me just get sorry
chats I guess
none of us are playing with Nelson
keyboards so we're yeah
scaling shoes
controller gaming we were on the same
level with the keyboard right
now we're on the same level of a
controller
I I I'm using Joy emails
because when I play Mario Kart with the
wheel I always have to move my body to
move the wheel walk into Ubisoft yeah
maybe we got aim assist now with them
the controller hey
yeah it takes ages to put it put it in
man uh wait what was that oh wait I
don't remember my email
oh welcome back Kiana home alive let's
go yes okay do you oh Ubisoft connect so
you have to connect with that right or
do you have to or you have to I think
just do it just.com what I'm in I'm in
let me oh wait why am I already logged
okay this is weird but I'm already in
apparently do you have anything else on
switch maybe maybe I previously locked
onto like another Ubisoft game okay
invalid email or thank you
I'm appointment
I'm I'm Zelda
oh here I have a profile picture yes yes
okay so let me set up my uh catch a card
then give me a second yum yum yum yum
girls
yes baby talk to me it's like early in
the day for you girls I suppose why did
you eat so far
oh I had chili
account
why but you don't log into the same one
Fruit Loops
I had anpan wait I'm Palm where the hell
are you guys yeah like
yeah
I have a grocery store that has an Pan
based grocery store
um
how many meals do you have today
actually it's like uh 9 p.m here but I
only had breakfast today
[Music]
listen
hello this is April the 1st so I'm
making the following Pizza did you see
that one from Little Caesars the the
advertisement that they're doing
crust why is it fake right I thought it
was real until people told me it's fake
and so I decided because it's fake on
the side I'll just make it myself fine
I'll do it myself yeah what's your name
one time probably made a durian Pizza by
the way yeah I know like what are you
are you crazy I had Dorian though when I
was recently in Indonesia and I I
expected it to be really really yeah bye
but they prepared Frozen durian for me
so I ate it in a still kind of Frozen
State and it was like it was acceptable
because of that
I heard it tastes really good I'm having
problems oh what's your problem baby
well it won't let me make a new account
because the email is already in use but
it won't let me log in with that email
what
I don't know it's the same email right
that you logged into the Ubisoft on PC
with right
I'm joining through your thing oh wait
no no it's telling me to connect to
Ubisoft try it with me try it with the
Uplay account that you connect or do a
password reset
oh maybe yeah what I did is I actually
just retyped like whenever you can type
your email I just type the same email
that I had on my yeah
computer yeah that's what I'm doing but
it says yeah I promise not I'm never
gonna have another Uno collab
it's okay I'm having fun yeah we're just
chilling when my Jen first debuted we
had an UNO collab and then one person
kept crashing and then we had another
Uno collab and a completely different
person kept crafts
oh my God why
okay so can I ask um because every time
I tell people who are in N A about corn
on Pizza they're like yeah that's so
weird but I heard it's like a North uh
European thing
corn corn
in all of Europe and and Japan but also
tuna when I say tuna and pizza as well I
get the same reaction from n a oh
they're like one tuna Pizza I guess it's
more the tuna thing actually listen
Kiara people in an a freak out over
pineapple on Pizza I know like they're
not ready for the for the tuna but tuna
is actually even that's not even that
like crazy because even in Italy where
the pizza comes from uh even there
yeah it's really good thing there yeah
please try
I feel like if they make it really well
it can be really good otherwise it might
be a bit like weird but if they make you
really well then it's like yeah bad yeah
I have this like um I have this like
mental uh I don't know what to call it
like a mental block so I used to work at
a breakfast restaurant you know that
serves like two eggs and bacon and I
remember one time somebody ordered a
fish omelette it was like an omelette
with salmon the restaurant smelled like
fish
like I remember bringing the plate to
the old man and it just stank like oh my
God that's the first time I ever hear
about a fish omelette yeah yeah it was a
fish omelette interesting I mean salmon
is great and all but
yeah I don't think I've ever had like a
fish on my before either what was the
old guy right
yeah you get Peculiar tastes with age
Maybe
oh my God
oh I mean that's still somewhat
acceptable I think yeah yeah I feel like
I mean I can see it maybe it's good
[Music]
is she dying yeah absolutely what's
happening tell us we can help you I mean
person
okay for our collab Kiara set like
everything up did I yeah you're like
okay Nina I'm this oh here do this click
this for today you're like okay server
for this this I'm like oh girl
that's the only things that I learned
from Ami anyway
you're not online Rosie homo can you
invite me uh it won't let me there's no
invite for me
I see you on my friends list
no it's not what it looks like
stop AI Luna
how do we get out of this game is that a
new Sanji member
how do I reach the Cog wheel press the
plus button on your controller
oh plus okay thank you
what is happening
we're turning it off and on again
yeah it is a Luna
oh my gosh that was so stressful Nina
how could you do this to us when I
invite somebody the invite button and
the unlock and spirit Lobby is the same
button
it's in the same face so I just like fat
fingered it oh have you do you not know
how to play on a switch Nina
oh no okay I'm back in the group Nina
I I like yeah my fingers most of me when
you get an invite it will tell you on
the top left I'm not getting an invite
are you sure
okay okay let me let me see and
so we should this is six minutes until
the stream starts girl so we should
really like get this going now yeah
you're right you're right
we move the stream back in an hour yeah
it's been one hour the friends list on
Uno
um
like how do you check the friends list
on Uno on the switch you don't need to
check a friend's list don't know because
it's just the switch front list
[Music]
yeah but I like either I make the lobby
or I get invited right so yeah how do I
because Nina said joint off of me but I
don't have any invite
oh it just pops up on the top left and
then you have to press the home button
and they don't have it I'm not getting
it in by it oh wait Rosie click the
little house and then go to the top left
to the Friends
post play I lost I'm out again a little
house
at the bottom
or you know what Rosie you start the
game okay but I only have you I I don't
know who do I have I think I might help
you I don't have Kiara on my switch
only the person who make of the room
needs the people yeah yeah yeah
and then you can invite everyone else
maybe yeah that sounds good
oh I'm so glad we're making it on time
four minutes we start the stream isn't
that exciting I mean and we're not sure
yet I mean four minutes but we still
have like loading screen time like maybe
five minutes that could give us some
extra drill then we need to do the
introductions oh yeah
oh my God still got time don't worry
don't worry it's okay and then and then
and then you know things often don't
work right away in Ian collab so then we
have the Ian curse extra time like maybe
30 minutes
so it'll be fine it's fine we could just
talk during that time I think people
will enjoy us just hanging out yeah down
the street
and my chat looks so excited for the
stream they're just like wow
yeah it's so sweet yeah
[Laughter]
that's okay okay I'm inviting
I'm inviting it
[Music]
is Nina as as not the the roommaker able
to invite me I feed you Rose you're on
Uno yeah you let me join off of you
okay I don't see a way to invite anybody
yeah well let me give me a friend called
please
oh my God
he roasted me on like my friend's list I
see Rose yeah that's the same thing I
see you on my list but I don't see on
Uno
[Laughter]
[Music]
we can push back the screen
you want me to do you want me to send
you mine or no I sent you mine now I'm
faster okay typing apparently
skills a skill issue
all right okay this will be it this will
be the solution for all our problems
okay I won't let you guys down one and a
half maybe at this moment you got this
oh yeah believe in yourself okay all
right I sent the friend request now I'm
going back to Uno okay crazy what has
happened no no he was never meant to
play this game apparently I promise I
will never for as long as I live make
another Uno collab
why is it searching oh wait get me out
of here
I think I've been
someone's game I have accepted
get out of there get out of there okay
hold on I'm just gonna force close there
we go the real friends is the troubles
we got into along the way huh
the troubles as friends
yes
I am awaiting my invite with open wide
arms okay you'll get a really big fat
juicy invite it's gonna be coming in
okay okay
you can't miss it once it happens yep
will I see it is coming
yeah you'll know you'll you'll hear it
smell it feel it smell it
finally there's a big question going
around who gave kiwawa the kiss on her
cheek on the thumbnail
what was it oh she had the small little
lips
one little lips on her cheek I was
sleeping I don't remember who did it you
know
it may have been promo and it looks like
it's like call it like a what is it
called like um lip gloss I'll take the
the DNA from it and I'll test it and
I'll see who the father is
so on your thumbnail I'm on the other
side of you so it's not me it has to be
Rosie or boom who do you think
um well the only way I can find out
maybe is they if everybody gives me a
kiss and we'll compare the the stamps of
the kiss
[Music]
all right who's going first okay
Rosie you go first
and that is the kiss
mom will you go first
um
I don't see Rosemary or Nina
because I don't think this is meant
no what do you mean you don't see them
yeah I'll show you but I invited you
there's no way what no I I promise you
how is that look at this look I just see
what there's no way to scroll down oh my
God and maybe delete the other friends
maybe there's a maximum of friends they
could display
get rid of them
would that help let's try that okay
[Music]
what yes Are You Gonna Kiss Me bomb kiss
you know what when your mom like licks
alive off of you your face
[Music]
no no that was nice
yeah
it's got to be a little slobbery you
know
[Laughter]
like when the dog is like biting on a
chew toy
kiss all right sorry I didn't hear
okay wait so does Nina have the game
open
I'm about to reopen it to okay maybe try
checking again after that I'm back on
the game let me know if you can see me
okay I'm gonna I'm gonna close I'm gonna
close the lobby and reach her eye okay
all right so weird
oh my God please Uno just let us in let
us play your game
I love how it says classic Uno because
this is just classic Uno
[Laughter]
oh I was gonna say don't delete Nina and
we'll see me delete all the others that
are in there
[Laughter]
still
Osaka
friendly dude friendship ended this is
like a roller coaster such a roller
coaster emotional damage I know
friend deleted Rosemary if she
what
okay I think I see your code Nina um
roseme can you put yours in too do you
girls have a physical copy of Uno at
home like right now
we can all role play like we're there
with each other
yeah
I draw okay
I have a lobby but I can't I can't see
Rosemary in the lobby I'm not on the
game right I'm like giving my friend
code yeah yeah okay thank you okay now
I'm searching Rosemary since I have
everyone like recently added at the top
I'll try and remake it
let me know
I invite I did
okay I'll go and leave
okay unable to join me okay well you
know we should have
actually okay if anybody asks
we can just say this was pre-april fools
to play the game April fools
you think it's realistic that we're
walking into the game no it was all
meant to be yes okay that doesn't mean I
sent you a friend request a real joke
this will continue until midnight in
every country so that's really April 1st
and that's when we say haha we're never
gonna play the game
spend nine hours with you girls so yeah
yeah okay okay I accept until 5am I'm
gonna dig out after three hours
oh
wait was that a happy or it was not a
bad I don't know
no I'm not on it right now I don't think
that has anything to do with it let's
just showing my friends for some reason
then then the last person to try will be
me with the superior European you Uno
and switch I agree save us Kiara I'm
gonna remove you and re-out you I
already did that I removed you and
reacted you okay okay put my check again
right now maybe
maybe no
should I restart Uno oh yeah let me try
restarting it okay I
forgot to accept your friends list
I didn't realize you all so unfriended
me that's how it works
[Laughter]
mutual friend
this is all just warm up
oh my God my head is still confused
right now I have no clue what is going
on wasn't me I said I'm sending you a
friend request right now just in case I
am sending you a friend request too okay
you unfriended me too
okay okay
I'm making a Lobby okay okay I'm ready
I'm ready making the lobby
great this is true
okay I'm entering the lobby
oh gosh okay Moment of Truth okay I'm
entering the game the game is being
entered right now I'm in okay let me
know if you can see me oh God
before
okay okay
foreign
I can't believe there's 7 000 people
watching this one
we should just play like Among Us okay
not among us but something else
into pieces this is my last resort
please give me um I think I'm missing no
do I have everybody as a friend no I
think so girl you update your Nintendo
switch no wait what that's okay software
that literally just takes a second yeah
I didn't have any update I don't okay
okay okay I'm gonna invite did you
accidentally press the update okay oh
wait wait wait wait I see Pomo and I see
Kiara I did not see it
I'm walking in I'm not getting a check
again I don't think the logging in does
anything
it does maybe
[Music]
I love this so much I'm enjoying every
second of it
okay I feel like I've seen this before
but in Japan when we're going to meet
with Kiara right we were four girls and
cattle was alone and rosamy's like I
don't know I'm just I
mean I'm like why are you nervous he's
the world beating us
amazing okay
I was very nervous Nina you know my
whole thing is freaking I was freaking
it
yeah we only need Nina in this room now
wait yeah can you see me no
you don't see me you're in she's Mina
Cena
okay okay Nina I did not see you okay
wait I'm gonna try to join off of piadas
okay because everyone else is here like
everyone else is in the lobby yeah
[Laughter]
off of your profile listen I'm friends
with everybody right now right yeah all
right I can't make it let me make the
room and see how if it works when I make
the room this will be so funny please
please please please please
[Laughter]
you know like that episode of Fairly
OddParents when he's he's on the
escalator and he's like when do we get
to the ride and he's like and there's
parents they're like this is the ride
I could run my accident
oh one second one second it's not how
you do it
how do you make a room
someone wake me up
save me take two I thought I had to take
two all right all right don't worry
don't worry we haven't even tried yet
Nina also boosted our server
well that was gonna be overdue anyway
for you girls
forty dollars I ever spent yeah
we can we can hear each other going to
despair in higher quality that's true
yeah that's awesome
I have to ask how high is the highest
you can see
how high the highest is what I can see
oh I've done some like Vocaloid covers
where they go really high oh yeah so
pretty high but I don't know what key
why
I was just wondering because there's
this like rock song called dream on oh
to me I'll sing it in my non-archived
screen
oh my God all the all the classic rock
fans are gonna be so happy
I think it's a fun song it is yeah oh is
it Aerosmith
I've heard of Aerosmith before like a
different song though I think
and I don't know what was it Iris
[Laughter]
forever to touch you know what the hell
oh
I've already seen that one yeah okay
girls one set one second when you girls
created the lobby how did you do it
okay uh you hit the planet and then you
click um you know where you're at click
there
but they just keep it as free for all at
the top
what that immediately sent me into uh oh
no okay now it works all right I think I
was in a different thing then okay
today's rules
on you do the three first guys okay
score limit
I can't stop thinking about when you're
singing in a rush oh my God okay I'm
gonna do this so I've known roseme for
over a year now right
okay
a Russian song called
and then I look at Rosemary and she's
singing the song in Russian with me
but it's because she was reading the
Japanese
words
but I was like sneaking out I'm like are
you I was excuse me crushing
like I felt so betrayed oh my God that's
so funny and at some point you just
accepted it and I just kept on singing
like you and you were like okay
you look like a big smile on her face
she kept going
um
[Laughter]
here I'm gonna print screen for you
the only friend that I can invite is
Pomeranian
the others are all whole life members
it was like randoms like who's on your
list and then you can't divide this is
sick because I don't know but I I am
Googling right now
Uno switch friends not showing up um
what if we do We join online and then we
have a passcode can we oh
test to test it yeah test it
I'm trying it right away yeah oh wait no
no it's putting me in a random match
oh
yeah
[Music]
guys this has been one of the most
collabs of all time someone on my
someone in my chat said is it because
your online status is hidden
hole is that oh oh my God tech support
who said that where are you Jay
well no because some people other people
can invite me oh that's true the thing
is like a few of us can invite a few of
us but not all of us right
that's true
friends
how to fix Nintendo switch can't join
front lobby
um is there a way to make it so anybody
can invite some people why is it like
this okay okay here's a new idea what if
you just all join online at the same
time
surely that can't be that many people
playing right no I will I will now
delete all my uh friends one second
except for you girls no no
[Music]
no no no
at them eventually
give me just a moment please if this is
a good idea but I feel like that would
work I'll do it out of solidarity okay
who am I dating
I'm a lot of friends
oh my God was walking the street right
now yes it'll be fine
oh interesting for work friends it gives
me the option to block them as well why
not for the other
that's a little dramatic yeah okay okay
but because I see in my friend list
y'all are online
um and and if I delete everybody else I
mean come on come on then the game has
no other option than to show me look it
has to show everyone right yeah the
issues that the list is too small to
like show everyone I did there's no way
to scroll down I did have a scroll I did
have a scroller but yeah it only went a
little bit I oh see everybody except
roseme still
so that's like it's weird right
then roseme let's get our laundry do you
have a problem with me do you want to
talk about you don't talk about it
what's up Rosemary
listen Nina you you saying that Russian
song and I really wanted to sing it I
really wanted to sing it that's how I
was singing it with you but yeah Drama
Oh My Gosh wait why did you say I need
my look really cute in my jacket roseme
and I'm glad that you're wearing it and
it's your jacket
knows what's up how to fix this let me
know I'm looking good chat okay
unlock the lobby but then what if it's
like a random player that isn't off I
got an advice from you again should I
accept it I'm in the middle of deleting
all my friends
[Laughter]
I think we should try the technique with
like only a few friends on the list and
if that doesn't work then maybe we
should try something else yeah I think
so too we are already all friends from
Ubisoft connect right okay yeah yeah I I
have your new self-connect right you
know
yes yeah okay yeah we do yeah we're all
all friends on both switch yeah it will
be self-connect
um okay okay I will continue oh God I
got so many friends over the course of
like three years man I ran around it's
over it's over
you're fired and you're fired
oh my God
and you're fired the lead friend we're
witnessing we're witnessing
Mass deletion oh my gosh on on air this
is it's very easy I think this they
still love you yeah I want to start from
scratch because I feel like maybe some
things went wrong here and there you
know yeah I almost restart also it's
kind of nice restarting from scratch
because they will give you all these
like butterfly feelings that you had in
the beginning that are now gone
a fresh friendship is something nice but
also an old friendship is also something
nice oh wow
someone said kfp layoffs no
[Music]
no it's I'm playing a game of deleting
people this is the game today
kfp we've called you into this meeting
to tell you
I'm almost done I have uh one two three
four left okay
delete
delete okay I'm waiting no is there a
dad side where's Nina
oh she's deafened oh why maybe she went
maybe she couldn't stand us anymore
she's finally done with us she's just
like I organize this collab I can take
it out
I hope this didn't kill her motivation
for organizing collabs because she told
me I really want to organize more
collapse now even when I'm not the one
streaming yeah
okay
and it's done you're my only okay now
okay okay oh my God okay oh my gosh
I'll restart the game though
um close Okay this is promising don't
get your hopes up I know I have a big
windows for this this is gonna work
believe me pressing My Fingers
um
[Music]
please
warning right before playing you will
not be able to play it with your friends
because we will not show them in your
friend
oh what happened
hi welcome back I have deleted all my
friends I'm not now gonna try my best to
make it happen so I believe I believe
this is it I believe all your past
friends don't count we are your new
friends you're like a cult we are
grabbing you away uh welcome back you
will now enjoy a greater experience when
playing Uno as a member of the Ubisoft
connect
thank you this is
sounding a bit cozy now
they don't let you play unless you yeah
you guys get that message too though
yeah I mean I don't think so yeah I got
the message because no I didn't I didn't
because I was already locked into Louisa
somehow okay maybe I just didn't read I
can't read
I can't read I'm nine centimeters tall
and I never learned how to read
Moment of Truth
okay
she laughs at your joke and all these
shows both still
sorry for laughing
did it get worse and now it only shows
because all uh all the others are ghosts
dead
well I'm sorry for laughing interesting
okay guys
maybe we should play something else or
just chat I don't know
[Music]
Monopoly Monopoly we can play Monopoly
you're like only problem is since we
counted at each other on switch if we
play Monopoly on switch wouldn't that
also give us the same exact problem no
no no no no no Monopoly will be fine
that's the thing that's what I'm
thinking right we would have to like
have a single person play it or we can
play something like maybe like Pummel
party Monopoly is different give me a
second no it's also by Ubisoft it's the
same thing it's the same thing on the
game can you try to see if you can
invite all of us yeah I'm opening it
right now let me see if it even tells me
to log into Ubisoft um
yeah yeah if you can well people people
how would it we don't I don't have it
installed so you know I don't have it
either she invited us we would have to I
think it'll be soft good it's a good
thing that we um you know delayed the
stream by two hours
I'm losing it you guys
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
their actions have consequences
well it doesn't count me too long to
Ubisoft that's a good thing already
I think you only need to log into like
Ubisoft once on the switch and then it
like transfers over it because I think I
was logged in from like Just Dance and
it like went over to Uno but then again
I don't think I could even see you girls
to invite you if you don't have the game
download but I'll I'll check I'll check
I'll check I'll check
I will tell you though it's totally
working
yeah this looks I look for the trailer
it looks way better than the Monopoly on
the PC oh there it is there's no in I
can't invite I guess because I have no
friends who have Monopoly right now okay
so I'm gonna go buy Monopoly it's gonna
work though oh my God even if it doesn't
work now one day I believe we will play
Monopoly together
which one what I've never organized
I've been through it this is it this is
the final Uno and we never got to play
what happened because you didn't have
Uno working and then it worked
so am I buying Monopoly or what no wait
it might take me a long time to download
on the switch though I thought it could
be bigger than Uno but last time I
played Monopoly was it on PC or was it
on switch guys do you know I think the
switchboard looks super cute yeah and I
think it was on the PCM does not work
it's it's real it crashes every time
same server though
on switch okay
you confirm your token first I don't
know if we're gonna get one guy but
confirm your token to see if that I can
add AI
what's my name what's my name oh no say
my name say my name I love that song
otherwise I know we could play garlic
foam
oh it's kind of fun yeah yeah wait I am
are we doing Monopoly I don't know I
don't know if it's worth it because if
you all buy it and download it and it
doesn't work then we spend a number of
hours
yeah that's a stream of the hopes of
some time playing a game
again I just want to apologize I did not
check the game because
two months ago and everything worked
this is fun this time
he's like wait do you can we play
scribbleo do you guys know what that is
scribbling
wait I'm gonna do a poll I'm gonna do a
poll do you guys want us to uh try
Monopoly or or play garlic phone now
is it like in terms of you know I think
I'm checking let me check
it's even free guys it's free
oh wait no sure
let me take a look really quickly at my
games please
I had issues with Monopoly when I played
it was a collab
never I didn't have issues inviting
girls I didn't have issues with
connection either I think I mean maybe
at the very end somebody disconnected oh
yeah yeah Monopoly is a bit famous for
having
um silver issues at least on the PC I
don't know on the switch
and I feel like it's this well it's the
same as you're really sorry okay oh well
garlic phone seems fun
yeah I think like
fall maybe like Pummel party stuff like
that
yeah
I put it
I put up with uh some stuff in them
they're saying play garlic phone now
garlic
I love garlic I just love garlic
baguettes
um
okay so what do you mean it's called
garlic bone what do you mean it's not
it's not garlic it's garlic foam
Tiara uh there is a game can you double
check on your end there's this game
called unrail it's super cute
and on switch it's super fun it's super
easy to play we just build a train
together like train tracks together
and I don't think I'll build a train
again no no no no it's a tiny it's like
a tiger yeah a tiny spot it should be
like maybe under a gig it's a super like
if anything
I cannot play unrealed
garlic phone is fine
[Laughter]
okay I wrote you the reason yeah no
worries have you um
uh have you uh played Terraria okay oh
oh my God Terraria
new things
yeah yeah
okay I'll start the garlic foam Lobby
because uh that way you girls won't
accidentally show it on your screen
oh okay okay it's been a while it's been
a while I love garlic foam garlic phone
I will have to change to a beautiful
thumbnail later but I'll just change the
logo that's it yeah
there we go I'm having a lot of fun I I
know I know folks are like stuff didn't
work but this is fun for me this is the
best like huge delay I've ever had
[Laughter]
London I know I know realistically if
you're really looking forward to Uno and
you don't get Uno yeah it's
disappointing but this is an adventure
this is a ride
German ads
you guys hear the German ad no no no
but I kind of want to now
Deutschland
speak
besides English
oh yeah Russian French what about you do
you speak something
um
English and Japanese no Japanese right
yeah just a little oh sure what about
what's that means
the language of the earth
well she speaks a lot of languages but a
little bit oh like she understands
Spanish really really well
the Russian right I mean we know that
yeah
um yeah Japanese oh I took a bit of
Italian
[Music]
s oh I just saw your room Nina okay hold
on one second
okay I am
so cute that's like real life what the
chicken it's just because I don't have a
phoenix
yeah yeah okay chicken
we are getting together how is it
possible that a free game is letting us
play together versus a 50 Euro or do you
have some game
this is so easy is there any music on
this site I don't hear anything I don't
think so I know yeah
okay okay yeah yeah bring your own music
[Laughter]
do you
[Music]
thank you for reciting my music
I don't have Mike I need stupid music my
ad blocker doesn't work
your what doesn't work my ad blocker
doesn't work but it's okay I'm just
cutting off the sides
yeah I always I always like uh on on
websites sometimes um when I'm streaming
like the the wheel website that spins
the wheel I have to like cut out all the
sides or gyozo because it just has like
15 different ads I'm like I'm sorry I'm
not trying to advertise anything
okay
[Music]
are we gonna like do some uh are we just
gonna do normal first I suppose
whatever y'all prefer yeah
okay my pen my pen I have a pen I have a
tablet
s
oh my God
[Music]
oh no
actually you know what was really scrub
like I I somebody was uh giving me a
prompt of Yago tea bagging and then what
what I wrote Because I didn't know what
tea bagging is is
the supermarket at the counter putting
stuff into a bag a tea he put a tea into
a bag that's what it don't worry no
that's genius what are you talking about
oh my God I keep getting ads on on
garlic food is this normal yeah me too
me too a video in the beginning of the
middle of the screen is it really in the
beginning yeah
but just I don't have an ad maybe my ad
blocker is superior
okay I'm in I'm in
um gave me like a whole video one and a
half hours it felt like two hours to me
all right ready I'm ready oh
do we need some introductions first
oh my God okay let's go
should I do a zombie Jam like a small
bgm
went on
my audio stuck
oh
[Music]
how about this one this is perfect are
we starting is it starting
uh I can start yeah let's start it all
right what are you doing this game again
write a sentence write a sentence
I don't think you can hear it yet uh
uh
[Music]
um
I sent in my prompt already
okay yeah I'm good I'm good
I'm so sorry
it's okay okay I wasn't including myself
okay
[Music]
oh it's been a while since I drew
something me too wait I know me too did
you change any time settings
so badly okay uh
how to draw I don't remember how to draw
that's it's cute it's very cute
I'm having the time oh my God okay
whatever stick man I'm a stickman I'll
show you my most beautiful Stickman
oh this is perfect perfect oh
why am I oh my God
I don't think they know we'll know what
this even is let me decorate it maybe we
have so much time we have too much time
we have to make a faster round later
yeah it's gonna go no no I'm not gonna
have enough time it's gonna go quick at
the end oh my God
does it look more like what it should be
no oh no it's happening oh my God this
I'm already stressed out and we just
started how does it even look like I
don't even ever wear it oh my God I
don't even know what it looks like
how's that everybody
I'm hungry
I'm getting hungry
you want to snap hungry too I want a
snack
I eat as a fairy I want to eat baby I
want to eat the ferry yes
and stuff oh my gosh bony
[Laughter]
let's see your thighs first and then we
can compare
Nina spies
how is this everybody
second do you like it do you like my art
I like it but I like it oh my God
is it better now
that's uh that is Nina
[Laughter]
um
I think that's a close team just in case
this is so good what is this
oh
[Laughter]
this is this is so good whoever Drew
this what is this thank you
you must be a man it is
I know it's one of you well it has to be
one of these I think I know which one
you got
oh okay okay
how do I draw a skull
prep it
is whenever I put my mouse on the guard
take phone it like gets really laggy for
some reason and don't put your mouse
there yeah
with your imagination draw with your
head
don't you have a tablet
I guess that wouldn't change it defeat
the purpose
for the references don't worry it's
anyway
no it's not it's beautiful
I think
I'm having a hard time okay guys I
apologize for my drawings but I am
drawing out like two frames right now is
your computer laggy it's only like the
garden phone like window I don't know
why
down
[Music]
oh yeah sorry not sorry oh my God that
yeah that is so accurate here let me
help them out a little bit otherwise
it's too difficult
um
okay I did my best I think this is my
masterpiece
I think this is
I'm looking forward to seeing it well
oh my God I can't I can't
it's gonna be so obvious that somebody
is using a mouse and keyboard no I mean
yeah
you're right
there we go here here that's well final
context what is happening
okay
how much more time
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah that means we get more rounds are
you girls ready
wait are you actually roseme because I
know you're having issues
okay okay
you didn't get to throttle did you okay
okay two drawings good
foreign
[Laughter]
that's roasted pizza slices yeah those
are Doritos
really old Doritos we girls playing you
notes you know you know
[Music]
[Laughter]
we're just gonna skip to the next one
okay no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no
wait wait wait wait wait wait don't go
to the next one yet I want to say I want
to point out in the one that Paul module
the shape of the faces looks like uh
like a bird where the nose would be the
butt the mouth would be the wing
[Music]
it's free
we're
always
so cute
someone has to provide high quality art
here you know hey I'm drawing at two
frames maybe maybe
phone okay I couldn't put in my entire
prompt it was gonna be
it's like you know when you ride a bike
and you have the little bike wheels that
help you ride the bike you can't brag
about riding the bike like the tricycle
basically more unicycling here take it
back well I can't ride a bike wow
it was gonna be with their with their
babies Kiara and and right but I've been
out of space
[Laughter]
I guess it's realistic I'm 174. he's
nine Nina's shopping for her
I thought this was a family trying to
eat me or like
[Laughter]
because you skull face
oh my God she's been shopping for a
really long time
they're not age fine like her wine maybe
we can play a a mode that we have never
played before
you join the let me rejoin it what's
what's interesting
completely start writing and keep
drawing Until the End okay complete the
sketch start with basic lines and see
the other players interpretation that
could be cute
okay yeah we can try
I'm open for anything just one sentence
to ask questions and have fun with the
others drawings
wait which which one is that
Icebreaker compliment sandwich sandwich
oh compliment is you start to complete
the sketch start with some basics
in this room
[Music]
start writing and keep drawing Until the
End finally I'm fine with any of them
animation is fun too but with four
people We're not gonna get a really good
animation yeah I'm thinking that too
unless they give us yeah we're four
people oh my God
I swear this game's doing it on purpose
Let's do let's do uh the speed run all
right all right let's go speed run I'm
ready I'm ready girl okay all right
you're going down
[Music]
I know it has to happen but I never
think about it I know right oh gosh um
um give me a prompt come on
I don't know I don't know
it's gonna be faster
isn't that a realistic prompt that I
came home
what is this from this is starting the
same way okay
um
okay
that's exactly what I'm saying
I still like this
that's my garlic film like
excited for this
oh my mouth is watering I'm getting
hungrier by the minute
yummy oh boy
wow I mean this just turns me on this is
kind of my Kink here
beautiful it's seducing me thank you who
am I I was gonna say you're making me
hungry because I thought you were
genuinely hungry oh my God I am also
genuinely hungry
oh yes okay done I even got done earlier
oh
this one's very easy
okay oh
boobies sank down
what we'll let them guess she's a bone
she's literally bones
[Music]
I have to draw quickly this is gonna end
what does this mean what what is this
what undo okay you know what I have an
idea I'm very confused too I feel like
some people here are not taking the game
seriously
[Music]
it's too bad at art
keep good
or something
true thank you for the advice oh my God
what is happening I forgot about that
about what I forgot about the boobs
thanks for telling me reminding me yeah
of course of course oh man I feel bad
she's got other ears
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh that's it oh so fast all right all
right
Kiara cooking corn Pizza
[Music]
what
what is my pink
yeah please explain to the class
I don't know what I think I heard
service
but Samus is not my cake
yeah what is your well making the corn
cob Pizza
we can vote I vote we spin the wheel for
rosami to do a Boston I vote too okay if
I deserve back to you deserve a bad
super your past drawing too Nina
are you joining us it's gonna be
majority and roseme will have to do the
botsu of your spinning choice I think I
accidentally closed it but we can just
choose one for her randomly
Point your finger she just left
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
being a bad girl she deserves punishment
yeah yeah it wasn't me this is your this
oh she's back she's back welcome back do
not stand for the Slender
for your daily punishment honey the art
is beautiful though I mean now that you
told me it was Salmon's and not me
holding like a veggie wrap or so that's
what I thought
she wrapped oh
this is clearly sadness what do you mean
now yeah but why did you censor my eyes
yeah I'm pretty sure she does yeah okay
that's her gun in her head
should be a little more gun like maybe
that should have been some pew pew pew
coming out of that yeah you can see it
looks like a like a gun like a cannon
what do you is giving me more Mario tube
than like you know hand Cannon
oh yeah oh yeah
it's good it's beautiful though but it's
not my king
but it could be if you think about it
long enough
like okay Kiara tell me this like tell
me you you see status and you're like
okay she's not cute I mean I have to say
I got some fan art of me as Samus and
that was like mind-blowing and always
you see now you're starting to get away
from I get it I get it all right let's
go next
accent oh yes
interesting
[Laughter]
butt crack I'm sorry I really ruined
this one why do you keep giving me a hat
rabbit ears
it reminds me of something something
that looks like a hat that looks exactly
like that some characters some game
character looks like you have a small
alien on your head or something not game
character anime character wasn't it
character who has a hat like that but
different color
is that green green my butt crack
a green light oh is that this of my butt
crack on the bottom I thought
I fought my mouth and then the eyes are
my questions
have you guys ever watched
yeah but I haven't watched all of it but
like I watched quite a bit of it
it's my favorite animal
well okay recommend it to me so somebody
who's not watched back in monogatari how
would you recommend it to me how would
you sell it to me if you want
um a long really intricate story and a
lot of cute girls lives
oh yeah like that I know the story is
just absolutely mind-blowing but uh this
is just like overload you have to focus
when you watch it but it's so good it's
so worth it
I have Kiara's chat open is that the one
with the tooth brushing scene yes yes
um
there's some funny fan servers in in the
anime but there's also a lot of like
really serious plots as well
um
it's really good there's a lot of
reading
yes there is a lot of reading
titles are of oh okay
yeah yeah
at Big recommend okay let's look at that
I'm just thinking uh
oh sorry I ran out of time we found time
[Music]
[Laughter]
some people don't take this seriously
yeah
[Music]
I'm not serious but
um
like Kiana I didn't have the time
I'm too busy laughing so I don't have
time to like who's the extra person
there's a ghost
who's the extra person
[Music]
you're in the middle yeah maybe I
commanded the I don't even say that face
I know
[Music]
you know shaking that ass
more more
what is happening
have you guys seen her she's she's
literally wasting away she's so decrepit
she's she's older I'm only
800 and something can you not yeah
what's this I'm not that old
older YouTubers than 800 yeah true right
100 yeah but like it doesn't reflect in
her beauty anyway like she looks very
young exactly
I am
cool you know I'm just it's a artistic
representation of your soul okay it's
true you cannot critique you cannot
critique stuff like this you know like
there's Beauty in everything you know
yeah I am I say no promo I like the
shape of the left boob
I know right
and in the first one she didn't have
boobies she only had ass so it's an
improvement
maybe like her old butt went up and then
she grew a new one oh
do we have like a recovering skill on
your trade on your book butt
this is when you cut it off does it
regrow you like unhappy atmosphere that
we have created in this collaboration
yes
should we go back to trying to play Uno
no but I I will not I will I will have
this I love Pomer but I have to say Nina
is beautiful she doesn't look like this
your body still looks good it's just
your face maybe like you know what I'll
give you some sunscreen Nina you'll
still hang this on the fridge right
[Music]
[Laughter]
pay back pay back next time you draw
something or we give promo about this
game now because she has done bad
ger game will be
um
well because related you have to learn
how it is to be a real grandma you will
talk in a grandma voice
she will learn what it means to be old
now
listen I gave you a compliment Nina I
said I think my face is saggy but not
with the rest looks good
almost the same sunscreen
you need to change I'm sorry you need to
change that sunscreen oh no it's only a
matter of time
[Music]
I have some candies in my bucket oh
okay why do you sound legit
I'm a method act you're out of your face
from this
I want to very quickly like say this
because I know there might be a lot of
new fans watching uh we like please
don't think for a second that you know
they're bullying me or I'm bullying them
we're that close like it's please do you
have a gun to your head right now
[Laughter]
when they say I'm old and saggy and and
stupid I old and stupid end thank you
twice
blink blink blink I'm going off script I
mean smelly
I am contractually obligated to say that
we are the bestest of friends oh no
yeah please I know because I feel like
we we have we banter really really hard
yeah we did I just want to make sure
that you know folks that are tuning in
don't feel like oh are they actually
like being mean to each other are they
like I would not be inviting people that
I think are mean to me to a
collaboration with me
a lot of the people yeah after you hear
that Rose to me
you'll hear this
I am very timid if I'm like saying stuff
like that well it's not like I like you
guys ready I don't like it
is
I'm very I can say lots of stuff like
um oh
uh like what like what can you say I
like green tea I like green tea can you
say I love you to these two girls
um these three girls these three girls
grandma that you love her before she
dies
[Music]
well it's it's been I guess like a
yeah my breath it's my final look like a
pretty cool collab I guess you know oh
my god wow
I feel like if ever really grows old
Rosemary will be not will not be
visiting her in her old also I mean all
I mean
no nobody's gonna visit pomu
oh
[Laughter]
you know what there will be no need for
visitation because all YouTubers end up
in the same old people home oh my god oh
it sounds like hell
we'll talk about you know the good old
days when we're really old yeah you
you've already done that yeah
okay Rosie you have two more people to
love say it
no I
I mean like I mean maybe not but like
I'm maybe maybe having a good I mean a
good time with you know
guys
you guys okay she is
okay I love I love green tea I love
Crepes
um what who is that they're not here
green tea and Crips are not here yeah
why can't you say it two things that are
not even alive but you don't say it to
us where it really matters they don't
judge me okay they don't care if I'm
saying it or not it's not embarrassing
okay I mean I'm just judging you for
your underwear but I was I was I said it
was good and cute
yeah
I can show you my underwear though but
there isn't much
take that offer yeah yeah you can
you know freedom for the you know
times
oh
wait there's Pom-Pom oh my God oh my God
pink okay have you seen those underwear
with like where the butt crack is it's a
heart
oh yeah yeah I mean an open heart
wait what hey you have that wait do you
mean
though I'm like okay I not right now but
I used to have underwear like that and
then it had a little like heart charm I
think it was
sorry sorry can you just tell me is the
heart the Open Heart above the butt
crack or
it's like the top of the butt crack okay
okay okay okay okay
wouldn't there be like a draft and then
you'd feel cold I don't know
[Music]
they wore it backwards boxers were they
no
no let's play another game
okay okay let's play okay ice breaker
yeah I don't think I haven't played that
one before what's Icebreaker I don't
know we'll see I'm writing the sentence
Oh my God uh oh no everything's gonna be
about underwear
[Music]
try really hard not to make it about
underwear all right okay uh challenge
impossible level
um
here we go I got it I got a decent one
there you go
um
but but but but but but
like one tea right
I don't know
oh
wait what
my God Panic ensues
oh yeah that makes sense that makes
sense okay that
thanks brother for real this like a good
artist I feel like
uh you girls you have like really great
artists in your fan Community yeah such
good art can they draw this too
foreign
[Music]
okay
I want this to be real in the future I
want to see what it is it's you
[Music]
and what color should it be
I kind of feel like drawing Puma with a
hat now instead of the headband you know
if I do this I don't want to like get us
banned if I like
the table triage
I also feel like I'm gonna reveal some
things about my character that people
don't know oh that's good we wanna know
more new stuff so you know how I have
the markers
you don't have the markings on my face
um
in other places
did you is there is there some way to
prove it yeah like where
will we find out no that is top high
knowledge If your manager has a problem
with this I promise you I will appall I
will write like a written apology for
this
I just don't know how to like write this
otherwise
wait what don't worry about it
is
an ash goodbye we call it in German we
call it the ashkavite uh is it on top of
your burnt
it might be on top of your butt what the
huh what the is that what the
is who wrote this I have the batsuit
what
what we're just drawing a normal
what is
what
who wrote this are you okay okay what am
I ah
ah is it a joke yeah use your use your
use your fun jokey
um
what is this
okay I'm just gonna draw this literally
because I'm so confused by everything
yeah me too I'm just gonna draw this all
literally
all right I'm getting serious now yeah
I'm drawing oh wait I have to
go there we go oh yeah guys oh yeah
oh no lines
hey I'm having wine
I said lines where is it from maybe
maybe
she does
oh
no space for face
[Music]
how to draw this
oh okay ribbon cute ribbon um
I think the booty needs to be you know
more like this
oh
yeah
but who is this yeah bye yeah bye yeah
bye I guess it's me I guess it's me
oh
there's a lot of
a lot going on here yeah that's not a
crazy crazy round
it's a very sensual round that's for
sure
[Music]
is it not strange feelings and emotions
okay
okay I'm sorry it's a good pot
it's not good everybody chat says it's
fine
I swear if I had a tablet
like I feel like you're meant to draw
this with your mouth right that's like
no I agree
ment
oh my goodness who wrote this okay I'm
sorry who wrote this proud
well if you're saying it like that I
feel like I have an idea I don't mean me
I think that means this right that's
like you know another way of saying that
go ahead I'm learning so much English
today
like so worth it my vocabulary is
expanding can you give us an example of
what you've learned
um
yeah so first I thought Twin Peaks maybe
a mountain
but I think that probably means
this yeah it's a mountain it's one of
them yeah
I know so much about climbing now
because I just watched a video about
climbing oh really one of the twins
sometimes smaller than the other you
know I should go hiking yeah we should
go hiking together one day yeah sure
we're totally gonna do that add that to
the list yeah yeah yeah yeah
now our list has two things
and it's I need some safety do you say
do you wait safety somewhere at the top
is someone at the top to save you yeah
probably I Think Jesus Christ
[Laughter]
is Jesus up there yeah yeah I don't see
anybody else who's gonna be at the top
to save you
here here's some nice armpits for you
guys to enjoy nice I'm gonna love some
armpits I don't know why people love
armpits so much I'm gonna oh my
apartment I love armpits no wow so happy
it's cool to love armpits again armpits
it's never gone out of style just like
the shoulders okay I'm not old armpits
are sexy and so are ankles ankles are
sexy oh yeah ankles can be cute
ah do you guys notice
um this like the YouTuber or I don't
know if he's really a YouTuber but she
made like videos you know in Victorian
only fans where where you get like ankle
pictures but it was a joke yeah
and a lot of people signed up for it
actually
what really but for real yeah y'all not
think armpits are kind of sexy I'm a
Touhou fan
I have a lot of armpits there
yeah there's a little character designs
with yeah wait why is this my prompt
why did I get my own prom I got my own
prom too
or maybe because there's like not enough
people oh maybe or we compare did
everybody draw everything maybe maybe I
think maybe maybe that's what Icebreaker
means
oh yeah
yeah you're gonna need to do another
grammar round This was
um
laughing grandma
okay
such a lovely young lady right now
oh my God is it me is it not a young
lady
oh
I don't know what my prompt even was
like I don't know what I was trying to
accomplish with that I'm so sorry
wait wait I started trying to like be
cute and I'm like oh this is not cute
um
um sensor
censor yes
[Music]
she's Conquering the world
so much
[Music]
you said
no I
know it's a joke
I mean maybe I mean are you safe
to be your grandmother huh I just sit on
this thing I think she would be a good
grandma that's honesty
was just everybody
[Music]
all I heard was
hello yeah hello yeah I'm really busy
working on this phone yeah sorry
we need to come up with the prompts man
I know we did
these props I just I just want to say I
I am ready to write like my apology if I
need
[Music]
bring it let's see it let's see it oh
God hold on
uh-huh under aware yeah that could feel
confused
what is it
um
[Laughter]
I just need to see koalas again yeah
it's so good I'm downloading this yeah
it's so detailed oh my God got up I'm
just gonna put that on our fridge
I'll send you a better one promo oh
my God
at first I thought it was like a bot
prompt because I didn't understand what
it meant at all
you've never been told that the joke is
under there
under the tree under there under the
tree
the joke is under there you want me to
answer where yeah
[Laughter]
okay for anybody who doesn't know this
is like old trivia roseme is the first
one to have fallen for that joke really
no is she really no no no no no I fell
for a dog I underwear I knew that you
guys are talking about underwear but up
dog
a dog is My Kryptonite I don't think I
but like yesterday I got I think I fell
for these not stroke twice oh no twice
twice so for even um
[Music]
it's not my fault they're also childish
and what are you doing bullying
bacon cookies
came from my chat I'm sorry
I don't know I was trying to make
something interesting and that always
the same but it looks like she's it
looks like she's like sleeping yeah
no time
[Music]
why do you have bigger boobs as an old
lady
you know no no no no smaller because
they're sagging exactly but at some
point Pomo decided that now it's enough
she doesn't want to get called Flat
anymore so she can you know
is a great candidate
become the person you want to be to get
them augmented Canada for what for
restock Monday
[Laughter]
like is that one you put like Silicon
yeah yeah
you're a great candidate for that too no
oh me I was stacking everybody
today
is justice as well it's true yeah see
which I'm not I wouldn't no not at all
not at all exactly no so uh Kiara we
have this one co-worker who's pretty
flat and she always says medium is
premium premium and it's like honey
you're not medium oh my
words
true you know medium that is like such a
cope wow she's gotten a buff though
right like she's dead she did she got it
look at you though
mine's foam
[Laughter]
but I don't think it came from me
for me right for me oh no I don't know
I remember squish from Nina oh
[Music]
that was a good squeeze from Nina
that reminds me uh Kiara ages ago me and
Rosie were in a hotel room no it's a
mirror and I you know I did you compare
a bra because it hurts so I just like
him you know I only have a few like you
know firm years left I want to live them
there's not a lot of firmy years left
genuine question when do the firm years
end yeah uh
soon
really oh no that's stressful
honestly like I'd say anytime after like
26 27 The Firm years are about to end
what really not soon
can you do something about it you can
break out I think working out helps yeah
you like chess chess workouts but you
know the bigger you are the more
inevitable no way you're just bragging
at this point it's just so hard exactly
that's what she did oh my God
when she was naked
okay so Kiana we went for food and I was
eating and I dropped something on my
boobs and rosemary has like really big
Benzie so I'd be like oh my God
my big breast caught the sauce that I
dropped
what's freak out she would she'd be like
how could you say that
oh my God look at
it's like an anime
and we're at the hotel I think it was
wearing like a tank top and I I forgot
what we were doing but I think I was
doing my makeup and I was like I shook
and something and Rosie's like
he turned to the side and she looked and
she went oh my God
the realization it's
did you girls ever go to an Onsen
together I want to go oh I've been
before I wanna go if Rosemary would you
feel comfortable going to a nonsense
with us I mean like maybe yeah
like
[Music]
phobia but I did go to an Onsen with
Cali in Japan and it took me so much
courage to like get in there with her
thankfully we went to like we went to a
resort that had like several different
onsets there and there was one that was
supposedly like not so popular because
Cali scouted them all out for me because
she doesn't really mind at all and I
said we could go to this one this one's
always pretty empty so we went there and
the moment we entered you know there
were like two old Japanese ladies there
they probably feared the Gaijin so they
left the moment they saw us thankfully
so that I felt a bit more comfortable
about that and then well you know even
even Justice Cali I felt really nervous
looking at her but you know oh my God
it's oh it's rough it's rough it's rough
but I'm glad I got over it and went with
her but I also one one time only I went
alone to a big big big public one which
was a big mistake because that one was
so crowded oh and I felt like everybody
was looking at me because I was the only
Gaijin the only Foreigner
I I and I was like I didn't know where
to look because at every corner since it
was so crowded that I recorded it was a
naked lady I didn't want them to think I
was looking at them I didn't know what
to look it was so awkward
your feet okay it's so funny because I
went to an Onsen right the whole thing
is you're not supposed to stare like
you're supposed to be respectful enough
I'm not scared at any of the Japanese
grandmothers they sure as heck did not
get them
[Music]
but just because you were just
overwhelmingly you know you sound like
you were pretty oh yeah they're like
she's a model I'm telling you if you
need someone to go with you I'll go with
you I can scan before before I'm good
and if I need to get into a place
I'll get into a fist
he's also like private one oh God guys
guys it gets worse though it gets like I
mean worse in terms of uh
comfortableness so I've been told that
in Korea they have and also like
something like an Onsen but there the
old ladies will start to wash you
[Music]
apparently so I'm like really scared
that's like next level Onsen Next Level
wait just random grannies just started
washing you apparently I mean that maybe
not randomly but like it's it's pretty
common apparently oh I just have a
granny washu are they naked too
maybe that's like a volunteer service
you know how like when old people don't
have a job anymore they're bored maybe
they sign up to be like a volunteer
bathroom okay that's just that's just uh
exaggerated it's a service but you know
oh okay yeah it's like a massage service
like a random Granny's where they would
just come up to you like scrubbing your
back yeah I mean they are strangers
there's a lot of cultures where it's
like you know like a lot of cultures are
very communal
right and you're all by yourself I feel
like the grandmas would be like hey like
you know we can wash we can help yeah I
get that I think with the community
they're not it turns out they're not
naked okay so that's good that's good
but but maybe maybe somehow maybe them
being naked would make it fairer to me
like would make me feel more comfortable
because you're the only one naked yeah
right maybe they should be naked
make it equal make it fair okay I'm not
gonna push for this but I will say when
we if we are in Japan at the same time
ever
nonsense I won't push for this I won't
like but if anything no give me the sign
and I find like 12. I genuinely refuse
you know what okay I'll go to the water
park
there's a water park
um no it's not a water park it's an
amusement park and hot springs together
I thought there's a ferris wheel in
Japan where you can sing karaoke in the
fair oh my God
ending okay
I don't know it but I want to do that
yeah sing Inuyasha and the prayers
look how specific that is
I'm excited one day one day I will make
it a reality but not the onset no thank
you you can go with the niji girls I
won't I won't go I will not go
you can imagine me being there
this is what prompted it I could bring a
Chihuahua cardboard cut out oh yeah who
did that
oh
where they are now oh it wasn't me so
say so
wait what do you mean
[Laughter]
what it's meant to me what is wrong with
you guys you guys were like where's we
still stay so but this is what it was
meant to be I've been betrayed I thought
I thought I was getting the joke for
once
what no yours is perfect thank you this
is happening okay
I don't care I tweeted it everyone's
timeline needs to be cursed
are in the same way people Rock Nina
looks like it looks like a torpedo like
don't worry about it but remember the
evil like rocks that are like crazy yeah
they're evil volcanoes that erupt milk
yeah yeah yeah so and now is this the
new information that we have now where
your markings are you are the markings
yes allegedly oh illegal information
it's also like like Kiara's yes what
does it look like that what what do you
mean what do you mean what do you mean
that's what a body looks like
which part is confusing you
this is really realistic actually I'm
quite proud of this one it's actually
really good no no yours is a good Kiara
I meant Nina's oh okay on my fridge I'm
gonna print this
it's amazing well Nina might need to go
to a doctor yeah Nina I have no idea
what is happening you know what she
already told us this is what happens
later on apparently this rests sag when
you have big ones okay
something you girls don't know
[Music]
flat is Justice all right all right
girls let's move on from the topic okay
let's see Rose it means
it was sweet very sweet
[Laughter]
I finished the blanket
mission of life completely cute
[Laughter]
wow
I like Grandma Puma very much
oh
have you gotta have you heard like any
stories about bulma's Grandma no she has
a grandma
you do
she has a grandma
tell me yeah what stories are there why
do you girls know her grandma Stars she
tells her Grandma's stories
my grandma is a little crazy
um you know some okay so I'll tell the
story that people quote the most
probably the one time I was at my mom's
house and we were eating dinner and we
were just having a nice time and it got
quiet my grandma just says something
unprompted no no reason Bruno Rhyme or
Reason why she said this oh
but she just says you know
if you come up behind me
you better fight me or me
and and we were like Grandma oh my god
wow that is a feisty grandma
yeah every she's gotten into fights at
the old people's home her roommate had
to move out
she's my ocean
my great grandma would like flirt with
every like guy she would see it should
be like she's unable to move and she'd
be like flirting with all the guys and
they'd be like 20 years younger than him
and she was so popular with the grandpa
a lion what is that called
a cougar
every year that we get older it's one
year that we are closer to being cougars
girls
what what's that again
it's when an older woman likes a younger
ah but what if you just don't want the
younger guys what if you just like women
yeah
yeah it's still a cougar oh oh is it
yeah I don't know though
um I just wonder like if I'm really
really old what could be my pickup line
like hey boy I'll add you to my will
um
you are too eager to say that
yeah
you know really hot girls come to a
funeral you want to come to my funeral
what
oh my God
that is really confusing yeah
yes what oh I'm I'm sorry in advance
it's okay
I don't think I could even I don't I
don't know any any pickup lines
[Music]
I lost my phone number can I have yours
that's a universal one yeah when
somebody wrote what a borrow my teeth
that is so gross
you don't know any pickup lines try them
try them
try some pick up lines on us oh grandmas
have candy okay I have this famous one
that I came up with that I never brought
it back because it's so bad
hey hey girl are you a pizza cause your
mods are really cute
you're what
I said what because he wants a really
cute cute Fox matzah
mozzarella mozzarella mozzarella really
cute maybe change it not Mozzarelli
mozzarella cute oh this mozzarella
what's a mean
um
the whole thing is you're saying because
you're really cute but yeah adding the
mozzarella in it yeah are you a pizza
like are you a cheese pizza yeah
I don't love it but I'm also old and
cranky and stinky and stinky yeah I got
like I got one
baby are you a side quest because I want
to grind you real man
no no
no I mean sorry
I just got that from the chat
about the grinding post
what don't you know how it is you have
the grand experience it really sucks man
you have to grind so hard for some games
man to get to you know a certain point
go to this one area and kill 30 lions
and want them here and kill 50 salons
give me some proper quests lead me
through the game properly
I wanted to be done properly all right
anyway my God oh my God it's coming up
with some hey crazy are you what's that
guy's name Jason Krueger
[Music]
the what what's the mouse guy's name
Jason Krueger Michael Krueger
right now
[Music]
am I Jason Voorhees because I want you
to wear me like a hockey mask
no I walk to where you like a hockey I
don't know
I'm crying
where does it come from
thank you Jason corgis because
I don't play the games at all I am so
bad with the scary games yeah me too I
can't not play scary games
the plague right there at the Scorch
yeah but again like you know before we
had you know similarities in terms of uh
free sizes and now we have similarities
in terms of interest when it comes to
games
scary games and not so scary games
I just named the three that Marilyn
Monroe has and I'm like those three same
as Marilyn Monroe
um
you wouldn't understand it's for people
who have hips and breasts you wouldn't
get it
no I have no body I just have but I'm
literally a stick figure I don't even
have a wolf yeah you're right I have one
for you most of me okay are you are you
Samus because I want to glump you like a
Metroid
that's what it felt like to me I don't
know
it's just like that's literally a glop
s when they just I thought that was like
an action in metrics no
thank you uh yes
what is it it's like a like a over
enthusiastic hug a hug yeah yeah all
right
apparently it is a Run and Jump hog but
for me it felt more like you know like
glomp you know lump I would rather be um
running hugs than that
technically like covering my whole body
in that Metroid
you know I'm gonna be a metric for you
girl
you're the only Metro that I will not
shoot down then
oh my God everybody what are some good
pickup lines hold on someone just sent
me this one
are you a fossil sample because I'm an
impatient paleontologist and I want to
date you badly oh my gosh really good
because you're old they test and you
want to find out what that where when
that that fossil is oh yeah wow that's
good
I'm getting Indiana Jones Vibes I like
it
oh oh that maybe that is a reference
what is NSP
that's paleontology joke has layers is
that a is that a joke because because
layers you know you have to like there's
layers to fossils I don't know she's
cooking she's cooking I'm not cooking
kitchen's on fire it's on fire oh she's
burning it down oh God blow it out Kiara
Pamela I have a good time
I have to ask you I was told to ask you
from the chat oh what is your type and
why is it me
I mean I just genuinely want to know
this is not supposed to be a pickup line
oh so uh I want to add really quickly
when we met up in Japan wasn't there and
Kiara kept asking about Pomo and she
kept being like hey what about Momo what
do you know this about the moon um
[Music]
actually
so my my next month's members only
wallpaper
I will reveal something now I'm sorry
it's not related to the other girls but
I got a hoverboard with Bobo I'm
remembering no I I I commissioned your
artist to draw me my members wallpaper
and there's a little reference to you in
there either
I can't wait oh my God oh my God
I love you mama
oh my gosh I can't wait to see it
okay
um anyway so we play the game again
[Music]
I have to use the restroom oh okay okay
I've been getting too much excitement
and too much wine
should we get should we think of a
actually kit chat tell me tell me a good
point for the next round a good one yeah
I like the drawings that came from the
granny Puma one those are just so cute
okay okay
that's so cute the first one for them
memberships thank you
[Music]
oh I like
um
[Music]
maybe nothing that's related to oh
that's interesting
that's an interesting one I will choose
this one
I like that one
that will come out as an interesting
piece of art you have to think about
what will give you the best results and
the best confusion to the next person
who sees it
okay yes
[Music]
I don't know oh I like that one actually
okay hold on I'm gonna write that one
down at least
advice
cannot get advice from chant
can you girls can't explain me something
I've been seeing a lot of the like now
no I don't know what is that where did
it come from like normal yeah
where did that come from I think no no
but why is it just recently that it's
become so popular
here Australian saying oh no no
because I I saw it I think where I
started seeing it is do you guys know
new jeans
oh yeah I know I know it I know like one
side yeah
all the members are fluent in English
and one of them is from Australia and
she always says Nara and and then they
make a joke about it that's what I'm the
one from and then I saw it everywhere
else too
yeah we have a couple Australians yeah
so they say Gnar oh I think that's yeah
that's why I got popular with it because
you have like so many Australia
now I wanna learn a proper British or or
something else accent because I think
it's really beautiful
what did I miss ah we're talking about
Noir thanks explain more to me but not
really what do you mean what do you mean
not really no like what's more oh nor
like Norm yeah why do we always say it
the same way or he's like no more
actually or when I was in Japan the
other day I I was walking by like a
store which the name I took a photo
actually it was literally nor
it's a hair and makeup I will upload the
picture on Twitter
I'll upload them all right no actually
no no no no no
[Music]
yeah yeah
what we write s
what smelly why did I do what
the collapse chat oh that's when I was
typing up your script
you already forgot
which okay
well if you if you want to go to the
north hair and makeup place I posted a
picture now you will find it easily
honest it's on Twitter on Twitter
[Music]
too
I think it looks a little
I mean that sign is pretty beat up
I guess so it's kind of cheap they have
to re-renovate it yeah
oh no maybe now with all the new uh
customers incoming they will have the
the songs surrender things that their
popularity yes get your horror and your
makeup done yeah
more like normal rounds or so because I
got a good prompt now I think I need a
second one okay prepare it I need a
second one too
share some with me okay um I like this
one just take the one that's already
written there and then replace the words
with our names
[Music]
yeah yeah
that is uh
why
I made it even better okay I'm ready
Freddy my name's not even Freddie
[Music]
the only one who didn't attempt this in
the pretty stream possibly I heard you
laughing what's going on
between I'm gone
does that means
oh
my God
[Music]
I'll figure it out and and that to me
and that to me you will don't let me
down now
um
don't let me down
how do I
oh I'll do this I'll do this okay
here is the head
all right all right I mean I'm just
being realistic here because I don't
think I could really do it
okay okay this is words
bring up some questions like what is
this
ask questions just create good art you
know
all right well you're the one saying
that so I'm expecting big things now
[Music]
give her a little t-shirt
s well he's always naked let's make them
let's wear some clothes yeah give them
some clothes
otherwise this is going to get age
restricted so we don't want that yes
Nina Drew her full-on breasts on streams
I don't know what you're talking about
all the Twin Peaks she did yeah
oh shoot
Bob
I'm gonna Tick Tock time is running out
okay I think that's good
what are you gonna cook after stream
um you
oh
what oh
my this is so cute oh my God what is the
name of that Trend
um
oh
wait is this not as cute as I thought it
was is this maybe
I think so Rosie really
I think so
it's so cute oh
okay hold on hmm
okay
why is it so detailed okay
oh my God this I got this I'll do my
best I'll do my best I'll do my best
hurry up you don't have a lot of time no
it's still fine
yeah we got plenty of time I just
started
[Applause]
oh God
oh my God
okay okay
total the whole dream job I'm getting to
the to the point where it gets funny
oh yeah it's so funny
foreign
you guys get it right chat do they
really I think though
this is good
okay maybe it's not good maybe it's not
good
veiny so done with their
[Laughter]
no
you love us
take it back
[Laughter]
are you attended it come on oh no no I'm
honestly really honest all the time
that's my European genes that I can't
hold back so I wish I wish I could maybe
maybe I should be Cinderella maybe it
will help oh
right
okay
my homework early
yeah no filter no filter at all
sometimes good though
for the people in the back
I will always speak the truth whenever I
can alright are you ladies ready no
yeah
show me what's your problems
[Music]
okay you think that will make me happy
really Chihuahua working at niasanji
daycare
what's wrong with us
this is just too stressful I'm gonna
like get a high attack at some point
please
[Music]
looks special oh okay
don't worry about this if you don't know
yeah there we go
anticipated confusion great finana's
been erased
[Music]
doing the worm on the Dance Floor
[Applause]
planking by herself for big strong sexy
abs
oh my God who cut open my womb
yeah that ain't happening I'm not doing
the wall the worm and I'm not doing
planks both is unrealistic
[Music]
is so cool
I like how your breasts are touching the
floor before your feet my words there's
no floor there is
I thought she was like Superman flying
through here
could be dying Victorian childhood
I mean bankruptcy
in case you don't know every time I'm
sick that's what Nina calls me
I have to tell you ages ago Rosalie and
I went on a trip and uh she was like on
another co-worker's couch right Millie
uh I almost said Millie parfait millipar
face couch and she was just like oh
looked like that dime like Victorian oh
she was like oh
I was on the floor
both of these arm and like caressing
Rose in his arm while Rosie was on
Millie's couch like dying
oh
it's dramatic
that shows you who the real ones are man
who are there when you're dying right
are you dying Victorian child
I was laughing I'll be honest
I was like not feeling I was like oh my
God I feel so bad and you know it's like
haha you look like a dying Victorian
[Music]
I did ask like do you want some tea some
water some Advil
who we're taking care of and you were
still kind of like oh I I did you know I
did the air conditioner was on she was
listening to her favorite music
I'm really really caring like that too
yeah
you keep caring and still make fun of
your friends
you know accidental Renaissance
you say kind to a mirror passed oh
no
until we're doing anything in like a
karaoke and roseme is feeling like a
little sick you're gonna love it
you want to see here why does everyone
want to see me in pain
he really does look like a dying
Victorian time
[Music]
I hope that will not happen I hope
everyone will be Genki and at their
bestest yeah
okay can you tell me like when we go to
karaoke until five in the morning which
we will what are some of the songs you
plan to sing
[Music]
I mean realistically I'll probably sing
some you know idle J-pop songs and some
little K-pop songs
like what tell us
do you know hello projects
yes
yeah I love Brown project and and oh I
guess I might you know when it comes to
uh like English songs I might sing some
um
[Laughter]
and maybe some Fergie oh
delicious I don't know
[Music]
um
and maybe uh I'll sing
um Leaving on a Jet Plane by crabs
viewers are crying now they're book
bursting out in tears
it's it's a song that you know it has a
lot of history because when I left Japan
after like a one year stay which is when
I joined Hollow uh at the end we did
like a a karaoke me and Kelly did one
that was like a farewell cuddocket and
one of the songs I sang where I started
crying while singing it was a song
Leaving on a Jet Plane I don't know when
I'll be back again yeah and so since
then it's kind of like a PTSD song Oh no
you've been crying in Japan singing that
song yeah yeah but you'll be back in
Japan exactly a circle
yeah what would you guys sing
what's your go-to karaoke song to
impress people
I've known I am known for my Yokai Thai
so deity because I do the dance
[Music]
dance
I know a little bit of that I never
learned like all of it entirely oh you
can teach me
teach yourself difficult it's really
good Rosemary's really good at singing
one of marine song songs
the talking parts and that was it you
did it so well
[Music]
I know that Nina keeps on talking about
you know trying to improve her singing
skills so I'm curious
in karaoke I typically will sing a lot
of like English like Dad Rock like
Nickelback stuff like that uh but my
favorite Japanese singers when I was
growing up was gact
um
stuff like that so I think like kind of
like I guess the dad rock version
oh wow wow that is awesome though yeah
but only old women love gack
[Music]
do you have any young cool cute friends
that love gact
on I don't know only old women love
visual K and gact and all that stuff
come on
[Applause]
you're still popular yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
I don't really know how many Zoomers
either right yeah
usually my go-to is like old anime
openings so I could talk I'm like hold
um Inuyasha openings
we're talking like old Gintama opening
a bug take has like one of my favorite
uh openings uh endings from holic like
I'll usually do anime openings and
endings
oh oh I want
you girls remind me if I wanna I like
when we get there there's a
Mariah holic
um opening where there's a lot of
moaning
I get so committed to it um
okay what about you what about you
um
please
why are you always asking me about them
I'm hungry
I sing I sing like a bunch of like chica
Idol songs that I can't sing normally
because they're there's no karaoke's of
them that exist are they on the karaoke
machines
time sometimes the more popular groups
are look at you the dads too
maybe
and I like to sing macro song together
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
last round and then end it because
there's hungry people
[Music]
for the other round what do you prefer
oh that was fine too I don't care yeah
I feel I feel as we keep drawing I don't
think I'm gonna draw any better because
I've had a little bit of wine
of course that makes it better at the
point of the Guard tick phone
I I I'd be okay to talk if everyone else
is cool people want the zatsu in my chat
probably because we stopped talking when
we draw yeah that's true
like a free draw mode or something that
you could just like uh yeah I have a
question
let's let's imagine a different timeline
where kiwawa gets into a ninja-sanji Ian
generation not to replace someone just
as an additional member which generation
would kiwawa be in
Plaza light
oh
because you were early on and off in me
too not not in terms of time but where
would you like fit in I can see you like
getting along while the theory also yeah
I was gonna say ethereum yeah because we
have a lot of uh yeah we have a lot of
singers
and honestly I could use another
extrovert
everyone in like etherea there's just
like so like extroverted like even like
um
I wonder
of course I would want to be in Las
Vegas
[Music]
I just feel like early on yeah I feel
like it would because uh uh myth debuted
I think before lazulite right yeah yeah
so that's yeah like well you'd be in the
first job Senpai I know
do you guys have like a like a quite the
Senpai cool high like I don't know thing
going on or not at all
not that much I feel I feel like some
people call us Senpai but we normally
yeah yeah like of it for example Ike
calls me Nina Senpai but I'm two months
a senpai to him and for example I have
zero respect for Pomo as my Senpai
art like for example me and Rosie have
two months between debuts and obviously
I didn't trust her like I'll ask her for
advice on stuff but in a lot of times
like I might have really unique things
happen in my stream that rosenie might
not be able to give me advice on because
she hasn't dealt with that as a senpai I
think in like uh for holo live you guys
have a much more obvious like Senpai
kohai culture
yeah yeah also because there's so much
time in between yeah that's what I was
thinking I think a lot of us we all kind
of grew together because we were all so
short in between debuts
who's the most reliable
you did my freak I told Pomo I didn't I
couldn't find anybody for my outro and
she made me my outro despite having just
debuted and being busy what Anita Pomo
has been one of my most reliable senpais
since the start genuinely oh that's so
sweet yep homo what's your statement to
that
[Music]
you know I just
oh oh
growling I love her a lot and she always
will like give me her advice give me her
stuff
good good Senpai you wear the Senpai
title very well
and she'll always I feel like everyone's
so busy and everyone kind of like for
example I don't I never joined any scary
game collabs I will not force myself to
do a scary game but I feel like Pomo as
Senpai will always go out of her way
to try and like make sure she's
interacting with everybody she's joining
everyone's collabs she's there for
everybody oh I feel she really really
goes out of her way to do that kind of
stuff
not making lies about me I'm lying she's
she's using your reputation trouble with
the Australian word
the Australian one
she's a Gnar it sounds like nice ignore
yeah she's an ore what what but doesn't
that just mean no
yeah I feel like for my senpies
personally a lot of them are pretty
introverted and like kind of you know in
their own little bubble and I feel poem
was been consistently the Senpai that's
tried our hardest to get out of the
bubble and to try and help us and to
like even if she's like kind of shy and
not feeling it she's always like trying
oh
[Music]
yeah like for I feel like for last night
in the city it's a bit of like a weird
like because you were like we we all
joined at the same time differently but
I don't think I don't think it means
Senpai yeah the most reliable in Ian in
general I'm not really the type of
person to like reach out first like if I
have like a problem I'll try to like
usually like fix it myself I feel like
one person who's very like Tech oriented
would be like that's what I was gonna
say oh yeah but I don't know I guess
there's like a few people who are like
if you have an issue with this here's
this fix yeah yeah yeah there's a few
members I think who um don't use Discord
very often so like they just it does not
they just don't like answers often oh
there's not there's a couple of people
that are very active on the Discord so
if we have a problem they're really
quick to answer yeah yeah
right so one of our one of our
co-workers Kiara his name is Shu he like
until I went on a trip to Japan with
like him and other people I didn't
really get to interact with him a lot
but he has always helped me with
different stuff that went wrong like he
he wouldn't be stupid he's like oh I see
that Nina and scarla have a problem and
he'll jump in to help us
wow I always tell them like I feel as a
co-worker he's wonderful you know
because sometimes the closer you are to
people the more you kind of help each
other out but having a co-worker that
you're not really close with you don't
share jokes with you don't you know but
they still help you when they know they
can help
[Music]
yeah sometimes you don't even like have
to like say anything they'll just be
like here's the fix for this if you ever
have this one yeah
[Music]
I think like the the answer would be
probably um I mean nowadays
I'm not really receiving much help just
because I'm a pro no
oh yeah yeah but definitely in the early
days I would always get help from Ahmed
I think
um I'm trying to also be reliable and
help out like plan some projects and
also tell people like give them advice
like I think I give I give someone like
thumbnail advice like I gave I give
crony from what advice can you give me
thumbnails
well I mean I wouldn't say my thumb is a
really really special
I think you're a little one is so cute
thank you I was motivated
motivation so I wonder I hope oh yeah
okay the Advent calendar yeah yeah I
hope people can see me as someone
reliable
um it's nice to be relied on right
feels nice so I will be more reliable
I want to be reliable
I'm gonna be that Senpai because I have
to be I'm from
the Virgin gotta be yeah good senpai
you know you you don't you shouldn't
pressure yourself that much yes you're
the first gen but I think every other
person that comes into the company you
know we're all for
eign you can do your best to help
everybody but at the same time like
don't don't put that pressure on you oh
no it's not a pressure it's it's a
pleasure not a pressure you mispronounce
that word lady
English practice
[Laughter]
that was very old
[Music]
no that was
kind of words
and trying to get better at English for
my whole life now
another thing too is like sometimes you
want to be a really good Senpai but a
lot of people can be pretty independent
and that's okay now right yeah I think
in our uh Ian there's like most people
are always very moving very
independently that's what it feels like
to me yeah
I know so often I'll be like I want to
ask about something in my chat will be
like you should ask so and so and I'm
like I don't want to bother them
[Music]
I'm sure they wouldn't my day would be
happy probably just get get a message
from you
[Music]
um
we definitely I feel like everyone's
always so independent the only times I
ever ask for help is usually for like
music I'll ask for help we have a lot of
people who know music and Ian too you
have so many like talented like Petra oh
my God
so much stuff on her own damn it's just
like a production company yeah I know
she's cracked I wish I had so many
skills I wish though you just have
different skills yeah
yeah I guess so um
where do we go for dinner if we go for
dinner
where do you want to go wait we're going
for dinner
I need to fix my hair yeah
[Music]
are you good at grilling can you yeah
um
they Grill it for you anyway but I think
the curling yourself is more fun
it's not so difficult
I don't mind helping to grill but I'm
always really happy when somebody else
grows
I know I used to always be the one who
lets others grow but like with like
non-hono friends in the past but every
every time I went grilling with whole
life en members I'm I end up being the
griller a lot of the time
look at me in the eyes do you want to
grill I think that I would probably do
you want to grill over I would probably
over Grill things sometimes
yeah I don't mind it like overground a
little bit but the thing is I've been to
I've been to yakanika so many times that
I I have like some knowledge for example
after like a little bit of grilling you
should always ask the tanions and the
the staff to change your grill because
it will change the taste if there's too
much I feel like every time I went
they've always done it like they know
when to do it sometimes they do it for
you but sometimes they don't notice so
you're gonna be like
[Music]
um
Ohio
oh good morning oh it's already very
legendary but I guess good morning yeah
if you want I will grill for you
I will give stop secret money to grill
for you no that's the thing though
that's the thing about yakiniko we
should all be grilling there shouldn't
only be one person and there should be
many people really I cannot Grill I
cannot grip that's okay like I'm happy
if you guys can grill grill recently
I'll practice let's put something on top
of the grill and then you take it off
after a few seconds
I know but I'm super annoying when to
take it off and I'll and then I feel
like it was like fumbling
drop I'm gonna drop the meat yeah
but pretty a lot of Yakiniku places
though the staff can cook for you and
especially if we tell them that we're
beginners I can pull the Baka guys but
it's about like it's about doing it
yourself but I cannot that's how happy
when other people can do it
okay
I actually uh but when staff do it I
feel like kind of embarrassed when they
they Grill it you know how they think is
best and then oftentimes it like is
still way too red for my personal
preference wait yeah
um I've I've been trying
everything actually yeah read that a
little bit really we didn't Grill
anything
no no we didn't Grill it but I think
like you said like one of the meats was
like
right oh maybe
um
your steak Kiana oh no no
what's the order what's the order
it's rare medium rare no no it's blue oh
blue is a thing
yeah
okay wait wait what the tank is blue
it's just like really really raw I guess
real the size of the steak
I've never heard does it come from a
blue cow or yes light
I'm green we're a medium
does that even cooked is it like cooked
or where medium rare medium medium well
okay I would probably prefer a medium
don't take the medium well don't say it
don't say it I mean
because I don't want people to judge me
but no it's fine though it's fine over
the years I've been I've started to
enjoy a medium very much uh and and
medium is premium as we've heard but in
a different sense in your defense yeah
again this is I'm just gonna say this
very broadly I have heard from people
who own Korean barbecues that you should
be well cooking a lot of your Korean
barbecue Meats oh really because
typically like it's better to just well
cook them just to be on the safer side
oh
a lot of you know since you're not
getting a steak at a steakhouse
yeah I think that's okay as long as it's
not bleeding I think I'm good
yes I'm I'm kind of the same way I don't
like it if it looks if my plate turns
red I'm like
like medium rare medium rare has like
they have a lot of blood right so that's
the ketchup okay but I have had raw like
really good quality of course raw beef
before
and the capers
it's really good it can be really good
but I would prefer to just grill it
you girls have any like vegetarians or
vegans well then you like rounds
I don't know that I know if anything we
do I don't know if they've ever yeah I
have met like I think I'm one of the
people who's met one of the most members
and I don't think anyone's been veggie
some some people don't like fish
at one time he got an Uber Eats and it
was just a chicken finger with tartare
sauce that's it
vegetarian and to give it more I always
forget I always offer her yeah I'm
vegetarian
I've met Mika like three times and we
always have this problem I feel so bad
oh I wonder then if you remember my
preferences for drinks
you don't drink alcohol
[Music]
[Applause]
I kept ordering drinks for both me and
Olivia oh my God I would never want to
go at New York it's taking a little bit
but she wasn't drinking as much as
YouTube yeah
and you and you you guys are going off
and Kiara and I were not drinking the
most sober karaoke that's what we'll do
well you know gotta stay sober too not
accidentally say something and then get
bonked by my company
now be careful go be careful
have to have control over myself my body
remember to drink a house is good though
it's like some like mocktail or
something oh yeah mocktails are fine
I just remembered the place where we
were at they had a limited amount of
pizzas
new pizza is a day like we're like okay
wait do you still have the pizza they're
like yes and we were so happy we're like
oh my God yeah but it wasn't even that
great I feel like everything else was
better than the pizza
but it was just like we were so
surprised because it was late in the
evening really late and if it's so
limited they said what like five per day
I think it was like 10 per day ten but
we were like no way they still have the
pizza but they did what's wrong with
them why nobody ordered the pizza I
don't know we'll have the pizza yeah
yeah it's so unpopular what you learned
the reason why
I
[Music]
was enjoying the other food a lot like
the pizza is all right sorry you weren't
even there and we'll keep on talking
about this day no that's okay let's
let's include her when we go to Japan
the four of us it's planned it's already
happening I want to go to shimokito zawa
to Thrift Store oh
okay okay okay
I mean you know it's kind of rough on
old people you know
you'll have to like
you go on a Monday we go on a Monday
afternoon there's not a lot of people we
go to La foreign
[Music]
when it's crowded oh I I think about the
things I would do to these people
oh my God please don't beat me on Monday
to come in with boxing gloves
um don't worry it wasn't me I'm never
gonna beat you up
[Laughter]
she'll beat you up and desert you no
because she had never gone before it
wasn't so bad actually how was it
it was mildly crowded but not so bad but
there's always so many aggressive people
around aggressive like yeah they like
try to offer you or to try to get you to
go places or offer you had the story
people yeah but that's way I think
that's way stronger in other places like
uh
shinjukuya yeah
I think it's not that bad not that bad
and for these kind of things
um
I mean I did get offered every once in a
while someone comes and say hey would
you like to join this model agency
I'm glad so my Senpai told me at the
airport she's like people will approach
you Nina and they're gonna try to
interview you you have to say no you
cannot and he thought she did because I
would have been like yeah of course I
want an interview yeah I didn't realize
that like you know my voice my
oh oh I did once
um like many many years ago when I was
in in Texas
when I joined this company oh did once
go ahead and like went for like the
interview and then and then I think they
took some pictures too possibly
Polaroids no no no I don't think it was
Polaroids but yeah I went ahead and I
mean it wasn't too bad like they had a
nice decent nice like office in a good
location and it wasn't too bad but
generally I wouldn't really recommend
because you never know when you're
getting yourself into yeah and it was
fun no it wasn't two sauce
I think it was fine but I went like
through a lot of
um like self-initiated uh interviews and
stuff as well like to you know do stuff
wanted to get jobs like in that industry
but yeah the self uh uh what did I say
self-initiated ones are definitely
[Music]
like look into the company yeah not
someone on the street yeah
wow
[Music]
oh it really wasn't that's scary no no
no it was really fun it was yeah okay
it wasn't that fussy is that you had a
good time yeah but if you need me just
tell me I can bark at people like a like
a little dog
chihuahuas I mean
[Music]
I feel like you are you wouldn't be that
intimidating what was it me oh I can
yeah
really surprised just the barking
that's the intimidating thing
they don't call me Bros me for nothing
I know you've met her and she seems so
shy but when she has like something to
defend she gets like fired up
her arms expand three times
[Laughter]
who are you gonna call
when you're in Japan do you have a
favorite neighborhood or a favorite and
like please don't say like your favorite
favorite spot because I don't want
people to oh
but do you have like a favorite
stuff that you like to do
and like
a place I used to have a favorite like
area but not So Much Anymore these days
they're like
um I feel like
I like a lot of places I wouldn't say I
have a favorite one but things to do I
just I mean I just always like going to
Colorado and
shopping but not shopping also stresses
me out at the same time yeah too much
shopping yeah but I do want to do like a
bit more sightseeing because when I
lived in Japan I didn't do much
sightseeing it just kind of like I mean
certain I know a lot of places in Tokyo
and Osaka but
I want to see like different corners of
Japan that would be nice but there's one
place that I used to always go to that I
always like when I'm in Japan with
someone who's there for the first time I
always bring them there it's called
enoshima you know oh my God I'm gonna be
going there for the first time next week
it's one of my dream places to go to I
just never had that week you're going to
Japan no right yes
I'm going to Japan next week
[Laughter]
um
if it makes you feel any better I too
was surprised she said it I too was like
wait what you said it yeah I've already
talked about it on stream before oh then
let me if you already plan to go to
enoshima let me tell you so so there's
this I mean energy man this is like a
bigger place but the one thing that you
really need to go to the park is that it
is it no no no it's an island like a
little island but you walk over to it
over a bridge and then it's like this is
just a lot of walking ah you probably
saw it in an anime didn't you
[Laughter]
look me at the eyes and tell me you'd
never take a trip based off something
you saw in an anime okay I I used to
play this game called love
plusima and I just really wanted to
always go
oh my God with my anime girlfriend
are you bringing your anime girlfriend
are you bringing her
because apparently I think recently it
wasn't in an anime again it shows up
quite a bit but there will be Senpai
right
what bunny girl Senpai I think uh
apparently also in bocce it wasn't Bocce
recently
um
are you prepared be prepared you have to
like walk up and down so many stairs
there are escalators but remember that
part yeah there's a lot of walking
because you're really exhausted make
sure to like walk around the whole
island you can easily do it and even
like half a day what do you like what do
you like in on the island tell us like
everything what's what's what's the tea
there's a secret spot that I showed um
you know people before as well
um but when I went there the other time
when it was bad weather it wasn't even
it was really underwhelming
but there's like once you go up the like
beginning path where all the shops are
you will know it when you get there then
if you go to the right and then for like
I have like a secret path uh yeah and
then you go without getting all the
secrets yeah there's a secret path that
leads it to like a little Shore
um yeah and in summer there's a lot of
people there but
um during like colder days not so much
but it's like a really serene
scene for me like I don't know you sit
there and then you look at the water and
just just I don't know it's just very I
don't know I've just been wanting to go
to the beach recently yeah
um what's up what I want to go to the
beach too but it's not like more warm
enough for the beach yet right I will
just say uh
Japanese people will probably agree with
me but kanagama beaches are definitely
not the pretty beaches in Japan
was the prefecture where enoshima is in
I mean there's a lot of surfers there
but it's not really like especially in
the cinema you don't go I mean some
people still go there to swim but it's
not that important
I just want to watch the video okay okay
yeah for that it's fine for watching is
fun or or surfing if you suddenly take
up a surface hobby I've surfed before I
want to serve I want to learn how to
serve me too later on in my life maybe
one day I want to move to Portugal have
a lemon tree and wow
wow
surfing fairy
well not like well okay so not I
couldn't do like big waves but there's
like a really thin board you can get and
like you ride on like the the really
thin part of the water with it I don't
remember what it's called
surfing
a long ways I've never actually done
like those big big ways you know look at
skimboarding yeah skimboard skimboarding
boogie board boogie board wakeboard no
big boogie boards were two or two thick
but that's the same boarding was like
yeah yeah yeah that was look that looks
more like what I
would do but screen recording
[Music]
oh
yo can you do a flip
yeah yeah
you're showing your screen just in case
so I completely forgot that this was
still
you know what's the worst part I saw us
talking on your channel and I felt like
I should have been like hey we should
make you should make yourself like big
screen to talk to us
huh
what I thought you should like make
yourself like big camera to talk to us
like you know the big like
talking camera
what does she mean like
anyway yeah
yeah I am still hungry yeah I think
oh man all right wait guys what what
restaurant are we going to what where
are we meeting
we caught on such a tangent
I just want to say thank you so much for
joining me I had so much fun I'm so
sorry the game didn't work if you want
to do more collabs I will make a better
point to research the game anything that
is not Uno anything that is not Uno I am
down for it yeah I will look for co-op
games for us okay
like say that she's planning something
big and I don't really think you are you
really planning something big
like a baby
[Music]
collab a big one then he was like say
that a long time ago
I think we were talking about maybe
doing something but we just got busy
yeah it never continued from there
saying we should have a crap game
I never played that before I'm afraid
we'll be too toxic oh my God
friendships are broken if we ever played
crab game
like you would never want to be oh yeah
I go feral I go first go bad
and but you know what uh I I wanna I
wanna play yeah we should continue on an
idea I want something bigger you know
big what do you want to play
I don't know I have many ideas well we
can talk about it behind the scenes many
unions but yeah I want to see if we can
get some I mean I would love to like
always have you girls to myself but I
want to see if someone and girls want to
join to yeah it's been nice though thank
you for accepting me like decent and
opening up to me and you taking me in
like you know I'm I belong here it is
really nice to be so welcomed with open
arms thank you I told my audience after
Alaska lab we like we started talking an
hour before the collab and then we
collabed and then we kept talking and
the only reason we stopped was because
we were both okay so we're like we gotta
eat and it's once again honestly yeah
the thing that stops us once again the
food the hunger always food that
prevents the further
I only had breakfast and now it's almost
midnight so I I need food oh my God
what are you making tonight by the way
did you say no I'm not sure I have two
two recipes left with ingredients from
you know the hello beef yeah
so it's some chicken or some fish
because I I've been wanting to eat more
fish because it turned out really well
last time
wait what kind of good for you too and
hake
oh if I ever I can wear you my recipe I
literally just take a salmon I put like
a foil around it I put lemon tomato
garlic garlic garlic and then you just
put the foil in you put it in the oven
yes
[Music]
okay hungry sounds very intense right
now
thank you girls for having me bye-bye
thank you thanks for having me thank you
for having me too thank you for having
me
lots of underwear and yeah
you can have worse things happening for
you guys even though we never ended up
playing Uno honestly the whole like one
and a half hours of figuring out how to
play Uno were really precious to me
oh I'm glad we failed I'm happy we
didn't make it
people I'm glad we opted to make it
together yeah I just have to say I love
that what we got to the
um switch part of Uno it didn't work for
different people so it wasn't just
really the problem yeah no no no
problem we are all the problem we know
who the real problem is now
sanjian's first wave
oh hey don't pick up my granny don't
pick up my granny I went to the servers
and I deleted your names
now I have to send all those friend
invites again to my home
it's fun it's fun it's fun one by one
step by step yeah thanks for watching
guys
I love you
[Music]
guys
talk a little bit I don't know okay you
guys are here after am I doing I don't
know okay oh okay
[Music]
all right
muted
[Music]
foreign