[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
oh
push hey
hello
why are there so many people on ah
because whatama is making a house for
sniffer I saw that and she started so
late and cut Ella is Anna and who else
[Music]
I wonder if she knows the song oh wait
you don't see the screen what's going on
oh there it is
there it is
no
the Luna encounter and rust yeah I
really gotta get her on the holotalk uh
sometime in
right now it's July oh August
in August I don't think I have time on
uh for holotalk until August
um
oh wait ah what's going on where does it
go where does my game go here underneath
that and then
is this okay
I think I think it's more or less
fitting in but I want to make it bigger
for me
[Music]
no
mama
because you know I don't I don't really
want to do hollow talk while I'm in
Japan because I got all my late I got a
million layers set up on OBS and the
thing is like with streamlabs obs
you can
um like log in to your account
and then it has everything set up but
with normal OBS it doesn't have that
you have to there's no login you have to
download the software and then put all
your layers in there is no logging in I
honestly think like I switched in the
very beginning when I debuted
I was using that's my energy drink by
the way I was using oh you heard the
Miranda
I was using streamlabs OBS in the
beginning and Cali was using it too and
the other girls were using normal
obvious as far as I know and then
sometimes uh I stopped using OBS
streamlabs because
um even though OBS looks more I know
like more Technical and not so pretty
for
you know
beginner streamers I guess
um
I realized the OBS is better for some
reasons yeah
yum yum yum I I got the same one as last
time because it's so yummy ah yeah Noble
I got used to normal OBS but yeah the
other one was more streamer friendly but
in hindsight at some point there was
just like drama about streamlabs OBS I
think so and hence that I'm happy I
changed
no I just I just started drinking it I
just took one sip I don't normally drink
uh energy drink
I'm going to go super
yeah
um
uh yeah what was I saying what
what yeah okay okay I'm tensioning
already I haven't even freaking begun
properly I'm already dancing like an
insane person I didn't finish the tunnel
right because I ran out of time and my
pickaxes are dying right that's my
problem
I have four pickaxes and they're all
dying
so we'll have to find a solution for
that first
because I don't have one I think
um because home is so far
I also we need bgm one second and and
game sound one second once one second
one second
you keep on sinking down that's fun
I think that is the game audio
or actually yeah um
[Music]
ah wait let's do
look like this and like this and then
hey
today we're using this old uh oh thanks
Albedo this old
nostalgic bgm
yesterday I was stocking some
Japanese
kfp chickens
and
I I I wonder like on Twitter I was
stalking them on Twitter
oh wait my fov is crazy
and and and I I was a bit confused I'm
not gonna lie I was a bit confused
I I want to ask
why why did you remove your my ocean
mark from your profile
and why do you only write about a
certain other girl now
but you still seem to like me because
you bought my limited uh birthday
merchandise
[Music]
do something I don't know
I'm not gonna say the name because I
don't wanna like no publicly call out
someone but I'm just worried if I did
something wrong sounds
foreign
[Music]
to begin with and and then compared to
when you use them but then you remove
them because then I notice
um
foreign
[Laughter]
oh well well
I shouldn't
kill much but it just stood out to me so
much to me because that person was
always
like writing at me
and now suddenly wow this is so cute
[Music]
this is so cute this is automatically
generated and they built
like uh
a stable or
something for the for the animals even
with water
that is so sweet
that looks nicer than
Some Farms that actual players built on
on the Hello Minecraft server because
everything's just for the sake of you
know
wait how do I get back out
everything's just for for the sake of
you know having it
exist and not for visuals
anyway what do we do doing today so the
snap oh [\h__\h] uh
too strong I got like Hulk Hands
too strong I want to finish my tunnel
and then I want to
go find a sniffer a new it was a door oh
it Blends in so much a new
um animal
this house is so big I want to look at
that too
are they stuck in there or like nobody's
inside I guess because how could you
look
open the door
oh
um
I
have a problem
how am I gonna go about fixing my
pickaxes we could make like golden ones
and so on probably where's the nether
chest
um
um wait where's another chest foreign
yes
is there something useful in here yeah
I've got nine diamonds I got iron
there's nothing in those okay but we can
make some things maybe
crafting table
we need to make an anvil
yeah
uh we need to make first uh cool iron
is also streaming Minecraft and she's a
bit busy right now but we have a promise
to meet up later to do some stuff
together maybe the maybe she will
have a little bit love the tunnel if I'm
taking too long but normally she's
planning to join when I do the sniffer
uh search
anyway which one should we efficiency
five efficiency five
okay let's fix one of the the fivers
okay thank God
oh oh
my God
Wrecking Ball and then what's this one
I'm carrying also five okay
you can't I can't fix it fully
oh also I'm lacking the levels okay okay
so this is where it stops for now I
wonder if these two will be enough to
finish the tunnel it has to be tots
foreign
yeah yeah but then I have to find
certain things too
get the the experience point and that
takes ages look I didn't
that takes a while this is better use
the rest of the iron on pickaxes for
exclusive yeah yeah
I think for now we'll leave it at that
and um
um later if we really need more
then I go back and I'm I'm I make some
iron pickaxes and we'll see how far we
get with that yeah
yeah I can't go back to go to an XP farm
I also ran out of fireworks
to fly
um
yeah
yeah I'm I'm a little bit [\h__\h]
worst case Kyla will always come to my
rescue also I'm planning on giving this
to Kyla as a present as a thank you
because she's farming it right now
anyway and I got it by accident and I
don't even I don't even care for it
that will actually be
surprisingly a present that she needs
and will be happy about I think don't
you think oh wait I didn't run out of
fireworks but still still I don't want
to go back
on
um
let's put some stuff away
[Music]
yeah yeah
one potato away too so I don't
accidentally break them yeah
[Music]
let's put some stuff away I don't need
all these letters
uh yeah whatever
where's my chocolate bars
my sorting system makes no sense please
don't question it I just want to put
things away
she's not helping me to fly
no no I don't need help flying I know
how to fly
okay guys I think I'm ready to go back
into into the tunnel
um
I don't know
remember
but I can't make torches can I because I
don't have um
what it takes to make torches
I have the sticks but I don't have
charcoal charcoal charcoal
thank you
tender in case it breaks through that
foreign
did you say flint and Tinder it's flint
and steel
top trees
yeah whatever
wait what do you mean still from from
the still from the village where do they
have charcoal
charcoal
[Music]
oh no it will be there demise but that's
not even that many
oh
give me free torches let's go
life-changing
give me give me is are they inside too
man
if I ever get torches again I will
surely light this place up again
hold the four torches on one here here
torches
[Music]
this is the first time I think that I
see four people logged in at this time I
mean yeah
I think like some right now it's like 11
p.m GST I know a lot of girls will end
their stream around the time but not
start their stream
foreign
[Music]
she does
a princess shouldn't be up so late
should she
doesn't she have like
protectors to tell her
to take care of herself
you have a bed we are somewhere
probably
princesses can do whatever
true have you seen Disney movies
it ain't true
they wish they could
do
who put the flower there that skilled it
they put flowers in the dress so
cute
you guys you know it would probably be
best for you guys if you never leave
again
because with the lights gone it's too
dangerous
like I'm honestly just worried
laughs
no not you guys
[Laughter]
I don't know maybe it applies to you
guys too did somebody go in here to
sleep now I wonder no
survival sleep
look down yes
24.
foreign
did I get it I think I did
I think it's fast as you just I don't
have time
it's as fast as you make it from
charcoal
but for that I would need to make
charcoal first
this is fine and and yes
we're just reusing materials it's it's
good for the environment
not good for the village because they
will die
it's good for the environment for the
greater good
okay well 34. hmm I guess okay while I'm
in the Never
I could have some charcoal production
going here and this is just for now how
about that
basically just burning
I literally just pushed myself back on
my rolling chair and hurt my my shin
that's how shocked I was
I pushed myself physically away from the
PC
because
so wait it's um
wood burn
ING with wood right that's that works
right
if I burn wood with wood then I get
charcoal right
like logs yeah
okay I don't want to use the the cherry
blossom wood
it's too pretty
burn wood with any fuel
yeah well that will be wood
how do I make the furnace again Stone
Maybe
[Music]
okay eight stone I don't think I have
Stones right now I'll guess some of the
houses might be made out of stone
hmm
eight Cobblestone okay
hi hi hi hi hi hi
we are Minecrafting so I watched the
video on what is new in this update so
that I actually know everything and I am
enlightened
I want a sniffer
and after the sniffer on another stream
I wanna do some archeology
looks interesting am I in the things you
get from it or not like
overwhelmingly amazing most of the time
they're just normal objects
a little launchers but but it looks fun
to go with a pencil uh
the brush
over the sand and find
some stuff but first it's not on any
sand you have to find specific uh
uh like ruins in
some sand Terrain
yeah suspicious sick so how can sand
pieces I guess okay okay it's suspicious
because it doesn't look like a normal
Sand Mountain
but rather you see that something is
hidden underneath of course
yeah but still I think it's funny to
call it suspicious
[Music]
in case you guys don't know because some
people didn't seem to know the sniffer
is like this chunky big animal new
animal that doesn't exist in real life
um that
can first of all you get it from an egg
yeah funky looking egg
and then you
Hatchet
and then
you out comes this big big sniffer mob
and it's very slow but it Snips around
in like a 20 block radius or something
like that I don't know
and we will find like uh seats for
flowers new flowers there's two new
flower types one is basically like a
bloom scene from totk the the glowy
glowy flowers
and another one is just a funky looking
big tall flower
yeah
ah
I for them
the new signs that you can create
[Music]
those are interesting too
so which house should I still do
the wait maybe from the one that nobody
is using
I shall steal the Stone from
sorry
[Music]
Omega
eight uh okay I don't need the weird
ones
I can replace this
why do I have one piece of fence
okay
taking this Wheels apart I don't wanna
lately lost yet
right and then completely destroyed yet
right
that was one piece too much
the explosion wasn't my fault
Ah that's where I got the
fence from okay okay so we made a
furnace
and
uh we burn
and we burn
there we go that should be okay for now
I think it is
[Music]
foreign
a lot of money from Pepsi for that song
and I feel like it's a direct answer to
new jeans Coca-Cola song
what do you think gets more money
a a K-pop Idol group that gets sponsored
by Pepsi or bicolon I would say Cola
especially because that was that was
really obviously like they even sang
about Cola in the lyrics but for the
Pepsi song I don't think they did they
were just wearing Pepsi outfits all the
time yeah Cola pays more I guess
but I don't I don't even really like the
Coca-Cola song from new jeans that much
I know I don't know
did I forget something I hope not
all right
what's with the charcoal with the
furnace I I I left it there on purpose
I'm waiting for it to create what I need
she had Pepsi noodles what the [\h__\h] is
wrong with her
sometimes this lady makes me question
all of her life choices
she's such a dork such a weirdo
a Korean teacher told me about certain
Korean noodles today that I'm fascinated
by the idea of them
there's no noodles called Nam Yong
which are cold noodles okay
noodles buckwheat noodles served with a
cold soup okay okay okay sounds yummy
and normal right but it's not normal
the soup must be frozen apparently
like okay not so Frozen that they're not
it's not liquid
but my teacher told me
and showed me a picture it's like the
the top it has like some
some Icy
uh little pieces basically
um
cold sober for the summer yeah basically
like that but the Korean version and
they make it like real cold they put
they make it so cold that the surface
the top has like broken icy pieces and
my teacher said if it's not
um if it doesn't have these icy pieces
then she will
think that this is not proper Nam Yung
now I'm really curious that would be
great to eat in the hot hot hot hot hot
summer
right
um
Stingray
I want to eat it
she told me about a place where I can
eat it in Austria
curious
very cold noodles
very very very cold
I feel like Koreans are just so extreme
with their food
it's either super hot or super cold
or super spicy or not spicy at all
there's only extremes
[Laughter]
I mean
for Japanese food they also like it
super hot in terms of temperature I've
noticed like Ramen is scorching hot I
still cannot forget the story that Chloe
told on her stream before
that makes me genuinely worry about
myself because I feel like that could
happen to me too
she's Japanese but I feel like
it happened to me too do you guys know
the story I'll tell you it's not even my
own story but I think it's a good story
so I'll tell you
um I'm story recycling other people's
stories
basically she went to I saw it in the
clip she went to a ramen restaurant yeah
like a typical ramen restaurant not
ichiran just a typical one where you sit
on the counter seat
you still see the other people
and oh
and you eat ramen there and it's very
typical
um and she orders a Ramen and you know
they usually come out very very very
very scorching hot
and she is
maybe you remember what it means
not being able to really consume food
when it's scorching hot
so she waits to eat it but you know I
told you guys before that Japanese
people say
ah
Japanese people say
um that if you leave the ramen like that
for too long the noodles will uh
eventually nobiru
they will like be soggy and
here we go we're continuing
no more torches though
you'll get soggy and and you know it's
not good if it gets soggy and long or
whatever directly translated the noodles
get longer but I think what they mean is
they get soggy and I don't know
I personally don't really
care that much because for me it's
katanai can't be helped
because I'm also negot and I need a long
time to eat ramen because I'm I also
cannot
I cannot slurp ramen noodles
I can slurp when there's nothing in my
mouth but when I have noodles in my
mouth I can't slurp
so um
so Chloe orders the ramen arrives in
scorching hot she's nakeda she can't eat
it so she waits okay she waits a little
bit for it to cool down and the ramen
Place owner
scolds her tells her to
start eating already because otherwise
the noodles will
um you know
become
soggy I guess and she's like yeah but
it's too hot I can't
and and they're like no we don't care
you have to eat it like they get
actually upset about I don't think this
would happen anywhere like normally I
would hope that you know you're paying
customer so you can just eat it however
you want but this person really cared
about the way their Ramen is being eaten
because it's for them supposed to be
consumed a certain way which I
understand too but still like okay some
people will not be able to burn their
tongue okay
yeah I I really felt for her when I
heard the story and then you know she
gets really stressed out because they
really like pressure her and get angry
at her so what does she do
now this I don't think I would have
thought of doing because that feels
scandalous to me I feel as a tourist I
cannot afford doing that
normally in Japanese restaurants you get
free ice cold water always right away in
the beginning so she takes the cup of
ice cold water and pours it into the
ramen
which obviously to me is even worse than
the Soggy noodles because
it will make the
soup tastes completely different but in
that moment
of bread I suppose which I I totally
understand
if the ramen placed on it would get
angry at me I also would feeling bad
ah
okay what do I do what do I do they're
mad at me what do I do foreign
[Music]
Place owner guy gets really angry
apparently I guess he saw that he should
have done it when he wasn't looking
and he kicks her out of the restaurant
tells her to leave
dad I find quite drastic because she
paid for her Ramen and did not get to
eat it
and she's like confused you know but she
she's just like okay
and leaves
she doesn't make a fuss or anything she
just leaves
oh no refund no no
let's kick her out because he's pissed
I feel bad for her I I mean I can see it
their point of view but
I'm kind of surprised to hear about such
a story in Japan where
they're like
you know
I don't know they I feel like the
customer service is great in Japan
they're always so nice and so polite and
they have a hard time speaking their
actual Minds speaking their actual
feelings out loud
so usually such situations don't happen
but it really made me wonder
it really made me wonder like this could
happen to me
so more more and more I feel like I
cannot go to any other Ramen place than
ichiron
because there you can eat without being
looked at nobody knows what you're doing
with your food
actually
oh God
I have a story about
how much you feel you can feel
private
privacy and it's such an idiot but I
wonder if
I'm I'm dressing in public is illegal
right but I'm
um
what if
what if you're not
what if you're not undressing the outer
layer of but an inner layer that is not
visible like nobody sees you under you
know what
[Music]
um okay so a friend of mine
[Laughter]
is
in the in the really hot summer goes to
an ichiran
and you must imagine it's it's not like
completely closed up cabins but like
your back isn't closed off but the front
and the sides
you know
there's like walls and fences or
whatever
so the purses oh the person sitting next
to you
usually won't really like see you unless
they bend over
and you know make an effort to see you
you know what I mean
yeah it's a booth
yeah and your back look behind you these
are the ichirons are usually very like
narrow
so
um behind your seat behind your back
immediately there's a wall
there's not much space you know it's
really narrow rooms
um
so
my friend sits down and it's it's late
uh actually
um so there's not many customers anyway
there's no one tour my friends left
they're I think may have been someone
once on her right or one more seat empty
and then someone to ride on the next to
the empty scene
yeah yeah
and
um
yeah so my my friend wasn't wearing a
normal bra
my friend was wearing a bra but it's a
special bra it's one of those sticky
bras with no straps
foreign
[Music]
yeah it's kind of like
um sticky it just sticks to the skin
and it's nice to wear when you wear
something like backless or shoulder
lasts because then if you wear a normal
bra you will see the bra straps you know
and it doesn't look nice
yeah
yeah yeah
not pasties I guess but like they're
smaller ones and bigger ones this was
just normal big ones not the ones that
are just supposed to cover the nipple
arenos
no but the whole boob you know yeah
yeah
no it's girls talk when girls talk we
talk about things very clearly in
details
yeah no it's not support although it's
not really supportive upwards I guess
but um you can
kind of create cleavage with these as
well if you
stick it on your boobie a certain way
then you can create some middle cleavage
but you can't like
push it upwards I guess if that's what
you mean no
but anyway that's not what this is about
it
[Music]
so it was it was quite empty in the
restaurant it's very hot she's she's
wearing a it's called a nubura and
Japanese
I don't know why I don't know what it
stands for the new for like maybe no
yeah
and she notices
um
that because of the sweat
I know it's because it's a cool it's
coincidence that it's another sweat
story she notices we got the sweat like
the the bra just won't stick anymore and
it's like it keeps on like getting off
like trying like it escapes her boobs
foreign
but it doesn't stick it's like so sweaty
and heal and and at that point she's
just like I want to take it off I want
to take it off
and it gets hotter when she's eating the
hot Ramen you know
ah so
what does she do
she maybe
um
[Music]
she she she puts her hand under her top
which is kind of loose you know and
nobody's looking anywhere she checks a
million times if somebody's looking
and and quickly
rips I say Rip but I'm sure it didn't
like hurt or anything because it was
just so loose anyway rips It Off
and quickly just hides it in in her bag
thus nothing was exposed
but definitely something was freed
have I learned of this one it's my
friend's story
okay
so so would you say this is
length what do you call I don't say
anything wrong right right it's like a
yeah
like a trick yeah
she was just you know and then in the
pinch
painted
foreign
how do you call like the acts of well
indecency or whatever what you call it
when you're like
getting naked outside this
an illegal term for it
a public indecency public exposure
indecent well public indecency I feel
like I heard that word before
could this be careful categorized as
such
uh
no okay thank God okay but that happened
in an incident and for for somebody to
be able to do that at an ichiran
doesn't that tell you how incredibly
safe
and private
you have so much privacy
it's amazing that's why I introduced it
to gura
for eating anxiety
um
I know
foreign
no that's exactly the takeaway that's
why I told you
that's why I love eating them because
you can you can eat your Ramen if you
want you can pour the the ice cold water
into your Ramen if you really wanna I
mean I wouldn't but if you really want
to you could
or you can take off your sticky bra
you know
when she did it she also like really
leaned forward so you know that she
would really 100 be covered by the
fences you know
and even if there were like security
cameras I don't think there was any
angle where they could
catch such a thing because
that's that means no it's impossible I
don't think
they could capture it somehow because
the shirt stayed down
the hand went underneath
and yeah
guys I'm just doing girls talk here okay
just just
let me do my girls talk okay
this is nothing different from the girls
talk streams that you guys enjoy so much
okay
don't judge me
it was hot imagine you having something
stick to your body and you notice it's
it's a weird feeling it says my friend
um
it's a really weird feeling to have it's
just like slowly
going off of your body you know letting
go of your skin and you feel the the the
the sticky
plastic whatever it is
you feel it's like wet and blood okay
[Music]
yeah nice turn to the world
you're welcome but then back to the Nam
young Nam young would be really great in
such a hot summer I guess
surprised that it has to be like I see
that the top is Frozen that's really
interesting but I wanted to give it a
try
huh
cold noodles yeah Korean cold noodles
actually you know Grandma
lives in Japan right and she's been
living in Japan for a long time and and
she really likes
food I would say she's a Christian ball
it's no money
because
[Music]
in English
she really likes food she's really thin
but she really likes food she eats all
kinds of food she just she does food
experiments by eating all kinds of food
she likes spicy food especially but I
think she would eat anything
hmm
yeah and um when I was in Japan the last
time
it was
coincidentally also very hot
hahaha
and um I felt like eating something cold
you know
for lunch
one of the foods that in Japan
here
uh wait Minecraft Holo Ian never wanted
to say Holo Ian never that's interesting
two free
one eight
in my tunnel
I am still digging
um what's this thing oh yeah one of the
foods I really like to eat in Japan in
the hot summer is
um
which I wonder what it translates to
in English cold chilled noodles
no
Suka
[Music]
um
foreign
Japanese 7-Eleven they have a
hiashichuka
as like Bento kind of style that I like
so much but we went to a restaurant I
wanted I wanted to eat
and Jen ma never had here sugar before
I'm like what this is for the summer you
have to try it it's it's so good
Ness
you know
you knew more Japanese food in the
native but she's not she's not a native
but you know Ian staff they're I think I
don't know any of them is Japanese but
they all live in Japan you know for a
long time speak fluent Japanese fluent
English maybe never I thought yeah
yeah yeah yeah there's this one specific
um Chinese food restaurant
Shane in Japan that's called I guess
that I used to eat the yes sugar
a lot at and their child is umai too
very good
yeah
um so I brought her to a hidakaya so
that we could eat here sugar
and you know I told you she's she's a
gourmet she's a cushion but she likes
everything
somehow surprisingly
she wasn't
depressed by the hia shuko
what is
hahaha
yeah
yeah at least you tried yeah she helped
me finish my food because like we shared
one portion of cold chilled noodles they
come with um veggies oh
did I arrive what is
[Music]
let's go I connected it I just have to
place the the ice
let's go
now I have to place
the ice but if you want you can help me
but no need
oh let's go I thought it would take much
longer because it took so long last time
what's this portal for again this was
for the missile right I didn't
realized it was
up here
yes
I didn't bring the ice though did I
did I
uh
let's meet at Ian
and quarter
never portal
yeah yeah I am so I'll go to my home
I'll grab the eyes she can grab some ice
too and then we place the ice and then
we can finish faster
oh
nice
I have a gift for you
I think I have enough eyes most guys
maybe maybe she has some
she was opening her a shulker full of
ice
hmm
yo I can't believe I made it okay let me
go to ice although
yeah okay my chocolate boxes are
um
at the thing
um I think the connection is perfect we
uh actually managed to connect
did I make this like recently
and now here's the Mesa
and then what's the other portal
ah is that where I started and then I
got out and then I flew even further so
that part that that portal doesn't lead
to anywhere special does it
I think I understand now
to make sure it's new terrain yeah yeah
okay so that's just newly loaded terrain
that maybe you can also use for finding
other things that just need new terrain
new newly loaded Terrain
um
my mail
long tunnel
what was I just talking about before I
saw Kayla's message
the ice might be inside the chocolate
even so I gotta pick up Kyla anyway
I'm surprised you didn't like it so much
to me
okay
to me it's the perfect summer food but I
also kind of prefer the convenience
store version surprisingly
I
there we go
hey what what's going on
what is this
I don't remember building this
what's that
I have to end them kill them maybe
eventually oh
some of that somebody else must have
built that I don't remember building
that
um interesting we're gonna get in VC
with Kylie I suppose let me just finish
my salami
um
is she here
[Music]
she just flew up
busy in one minute
hmm
why is she flown away why is she fly
away is she getting a present for me
what's going on
just because she heard I have a person
for her but I only have one
it's something she likes but
matama is reading a combo
let's see if Waterman reads this too
she'll slowly read it out like
see if what what
it might really be in energy
[Music]
got it
I think I remembered the part where I
took all the ice where what order
I think I remember that though
did that
oh my God
wow
autumn
but just wait if I type that now because
Kyla will be confused
just reading it
huh oh yeah that's uh is it mine
it's not something Shooters brought
right okay
[Music]
I'm in Japanese Museum
open it
okay it's not it's not from her
okay let me
let me get them oh wait this means I
have to switch to testimonial oh
hello oh wait wait
yeah
I know I cannot
you can't connect
is your connection dead
no but hold on it's okay
uh finally
double bgm probably let me fix the
monitor only there we go okay
hello Kyla hello
what is this
what is what the surfer
bottom it wants to join
with it
oh no she can't speak English though can
you speak nihongo Kayla
uh I'm nihongo JoJo oh that doesn't
sound good
please just speak English yeah but also
we're gonna do our own thing but I don't
want to say no too
nice icon
I mean it's okay
no
push there you are
she thinks I invited her oh
Minecraft gone it's okay take your time
because I don't know what to do with
this situation right now that I created
um
it I I will explain to her what we're
doing because like I think she's she's
doing her own thing
on her side
[Applause]
I confused like I think I made her think
that I want her to join the voice chat
but
um she's doing her own thing you know
ah ah
I'm going to explode my brain is
exploding I I try to be a social person
always but now I'm exploding
hi
[Laughter]
so fun
I am
I am uh
oh God
what did I do
she wants to look for sniffer I thought
she already has the sniffer and is
making a house with a sniffer
she's I don't mean she's an FK okay
she's AFK
okay
[Music]
ah
it's okay
I think a socially awkward situation
then I normally only make things so that
they're not awkward
okay I will
um translate between Kyla and vatama
we'll do it I will do no worries
see she knows where it is I'm pretty
sure
I don't I can't I can't this is the one
situation that finally conquers me and
kills me
um Kyla where did you go
I've
I'm playing with the animals
outside the floor itself no in front of
the fourth floor
[Music]
Club hello
she says she she's always small I
already have her on maximum
foreign
[Music]
okay
but she's much louder than you wait
maybe I make you more quieter
[Music]
how about oh I think I got it
this is maximum guys
is it fine now guys I think so
good good okay better okay okay okay
okay
stand back
foreign
[Laughter]
oh now it's first time
uh I mean first time talking in PC yeah
and not really not really the whole ID
cop last year
oh
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
come on
foreign
[Music]
we will be in the same team
August
oh yes yes August August
um
coming soon
thank you
yeah
[Music]
Kyla
maybe maybe I need blue eyes do you have
some blue eyes
I have some but not so many oh blue eyes
blue I mean I can I can take that first
hold on okay
maybe I have what is Senpai doing right
now she is making a house for a sniffer
oh in the new server right
there
yes yes
okay okay okay
[Music]
I will take it
little little little
how many uh uh one Chalker one box one
box
stuck
who's in this car
[Music]
she wants a full shulker box uh the uh I
I want to ask uh the the Redstone is the
the dust or the black one
oh by the way I found some more blue
eyes from my side so no need I think
oh really yeah sure I think it's okay is
it enough maybe I have a lot of cactus
but just um blue eyes not so much but
I'll mix it
okay I mean I mean I can just bring some
yeah okay okay I'm I'm in the tunnel you
can just I think you already know where
the tunnel is right yeah yeah okay you
can find me somewhere in the tunnel okay
okay
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
yes
Venus god wow
Venus because
it wasn't Venus like a like a you know
sensual goddess
true anymore wow
we'll see
she is yes
I know I know
foreign
yes
love and beauty goddess Venus
oh no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no
no no no no no no no no no no hi Ella
can you bring me some torches too okay
maybe two stacks okay hold on I have a
present though for you you will like it
I promise I need to craft it first hold
on hold on okay
um
I don't know yet
oh yeah
[Laughter]
I made a joke Japanese jerk
yes
that will make a house that is like uh
like a forest for the sniffer so I said
oh Mori okay
thank you
money
what time is Empire
Genki
yeah
powerful
yes yes
[Music]
Papa
foreign
[Music]
a song about stress
Empire
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
hey
oh come on how much can I know and I
don't have to uh
[Music]
Kyla what's your favorite type of bra
what bro bro no Bruh Bruh Bruh
why certain topic
don't question it don't question it just
go along
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
I prefer non-wired Brads but the problem
is you know my friend told me when you
sweat sweating then it doesn't stick to
your boobies anymore and then it can
fall off yeah yeah oh really yeah to
happen to my friend yeah yeah yeah
not me not me
okay not personal experience yeah no I
wouldn't know anything about that no no
oh yes she is
oh yes
uh
is there something you want to ask about
the messenger I will translate it
[Laughter]
actually you know what what time is is
one of my oceans oh really what foreign
you sent her a DM before about it
and and I also mentioned that in my
devil stream actually oh you did I don't
remember you uh
um
panicking right now who is Kyla Ochi
what am I and
uh uh um
nice choice nice choice
I love her
rubber duck I'm running out of ice and
maybe I should go to get on I I can take
some ice hold on hold on hold on eyes
eyes
[Music]
eyes eyes torch I don't know is that
enough guys I don't know uh
got it
oh
wow
how about you how about you me okay
but I I first got to know whole life
through Focus Empire
foreign
[Laughter]
actually your voice is pretty similar
the color of her voice is the type of
.
can you do any impersonations of
whole life members
not really I think
um
I'm really bad at like impersonating
actually yeah
say it low say it in the low voice
um
base for it yeah
it was pretty good
I can't stop laughing oh my God
minor foreign
[Music]
McDonald's
[Laughter]
[Music]
needle need or not
because
foreign
[Music]
I can do better than that
what do you think Kyla of my pickled
impersonation
um you need to
sound higher I think
yeah yeah
[Laughter]
you know she's just chilling sometimes
she's just chilling you know her voice
is chilling
[Music]
well you can go that high your voice oh
I can go much higher much much higher
oh how how about we test the r right now
with watamation pie
that's actually good because I I wasn't
sure how to give an example because I
can roll ours normally but not in like a
Japanese way you know Japanese songs
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
can't do that
so
thank you thank you
foreign
I can't do that that specific uh rolling
I can't do that
like in a very German way I can say
but that's not it I understood
understandable yeah yeah yeah that's
different yeah that's different
the tip of the tongue is
how do you do it
tell me
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
I'm on my way I'm on my way thank you
[Music]
thank you you deliver first to me and
then to one of my Senpai okay okay
um
foreign
[Music]
worldwide traveler Kyla a worldwide
Travelers
you know Kyla first I wanted a camel
Bernard changed to sniffer but if I
would have gotten a camel I would have
named it Camilla
oh I love a lot of people say that the
camel cannot be brought home
I think okay but this is difficult to
bring at home I would say because of the
distance oh
okay
oh Camilla Camilla
hey what's what's camel again in
Japanese
[Music]
yeah I forgot caramel camel I Used to
Know It foreign
Camilla
I know it's not good to translate your
jokes but I'm doing it or to explain
your jokes but I'm just doing it so
everybody understands what's going on
it's okay I'm here by the way where are
you oh which side of the tunnel I'm
going back to the from the beginning of
the tunnel I'm just entered the another
portal okay okay you can maybe I should
have taken the boat you can maybe wait
at the
stairs yeah
do I have the book I have to poop okay
wait wait I'm on my way
I'm on my way
one piece
is
Marshall
okay
[Music]
I said three stacks of Lights
I mean just I mean just
think just take whatever how many do you
need just take it okay thank you that's
enough
okay
Overkill the kind of the the queen of
Overkill
okay bye-bye I will go to next place
next station
hi
um
[Music]
nice I'm coming
Redstone how much Redstone a full
shulker box right yeah wow nice Sasuke
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
yes
no no no Kyle if you don't know Japanese
how were you like listening to water my
streams Clips or
Clips but sometimes just just watch like
it's okay no don't and I if don't
understand then it's okay oh
oh okay it's just I don't know it's just
like comfy yeah yeah and you get like
maybe a general idea of what's going on
just by looking at the screen Maybe
foreign
[Music]
I am here
oh
hello Uber Kyla arrived
for you ah
thank you
my gift for Kyla I still have a gift for
you too Kyla
Arigato what's going on
for you
thank you
[Music]
Full House cool house
thank you
[Music]
no no no you're not third Wheeling it's
okay it just seems very familiar to the
situation I had with Guru and okayu
Senpai where I was just translating for
them
deja vu no no no no this is different no
it's different
thank you so much
[Music]
very cool outfit
oh
[Music]
thank you
I I don't even know how to go out but
it's okay I'll find my way out uh
okay it's okay okay
I think
I'm going back to the tunnel right now
everybody gets what they need
it
um
foreign
[Music]
anymore
I almost died
I I've almost died oh but it's okay from
embarrassment or
excitement and from from nervousness
but see I mean it was
um kind of weird how this came together
but you got some time to talk to about
the mission by nice too a little chat
yeah but I just kind of hinted at what
I'm saying by now that maybe maybe now
is a good time because you're coming
back to me so we'll probably be talking
to each other yeah yeah yeah yeah
wait wait I forgot where to go that way
that way okay okay and just try to get
to the end of the tunnel eventually you
will see me but I'm just placing blocks
right now I hope this
actually it might not be enough
oh it's not enough yeah I mean I can
just grind some blue eyes again
somewhere here some some normal pack
dies is fine too
yeah a mix usually is what I've been
using just mix of pectins
wait I will try to find Ian server got a
lot of eyes too yeah yeah
where should I go eyes I baby
eyes eyes
I need some fun in the future maybe for
the future yeah but oh this tunnel
yeah definitely not enough oopsie doodly
Doom
I could fly around outside of the tunnel
too to find somewhere ice
okay okay wait
probably I can find some I
I
need to get present for Kyla
when I get out of the tunnel don't make
me forget guys
did someone spoiler you what I have for
you I hope not
did they tell you did your chat tell you
about what what I have for you oh no no
no okay good don't tell her nah
please don't tell her
there is no ice here where can I get
eyes
yeah I could turn back the bgm right
guys I'll turn it back on
we have no idea to this
you have no more
no more ice
in the I don't know
um no no no no I I use I kind of use a
lot of ice back then for why
for for the road too yeah from for the
tunnel ah you also made the road yeah
and then that's just the leftover yeah
Iceberg by Omi I know there's many
Iceberg biomes and only Ian forever I
flew by so many of them
I think even on the way from the first
on the last that one portal that I made
do I have fireworks no
okay I will go fly too I'll I'll go find
some myself Kyla
yeah I'm still trying to find it too
it's okay
[Music]
does this count as shaped eyes for the
bingo card
Kayla are you trying to to fill out the
bingo card yeah the Bingo right yeah
yeah we have to eat shaved ice yeah the
shaved ice
yeah yeah a lot yeah but it's just like
too sweet and
you just have to eat one bite and then
you can give the rest
true right
because in in Austria we don't have
shaved ice normally but I guess maybe I
mean you can make it by yourself but
don't you need like a shaved ice machine
I'm not gonna use my my cheese grinder
and shave ice with my cheese grinder
oh
or
um what about
um
what do you call the
not gelato
but like a certain type of
ice that's more ice cream that's more
close to like
um
what is
sorbet yeah sorbet okay can we say
sorbet is shaved ice
not really
not really I think is it not kind of
shaved ice Japanese one but
I mean if you say that's
but it's okay I'm going to Japan next
week so I'll eat shaved ice enjoy
[Music]
shaved eyes
actually I ate shaved ice maybe one time
in my life at a Japanese Summer Festival
next time if you come to Indonesia again
probably you can try to find the few
thighs but I'm guessing you guys have
like your own version of it like a
little bit
yeah I think it's different I think it's
different how what's the difference
um
it's like
more like the Indonesian traditional
eyes we have like a lot of
we we got like uh the toppings the
toppings right we got like uh coconut
uh syrup
um um
beans like what black beans black beans
I don't know I
I
usually don't eat sweets so
guys I am right all right right it's
true yeah that's the one you said you
don't want to eat this
[Music]
okay guys
copy this these coordinates 278
1102 24 700 just so that I don't get
lost write it down guys write it down
I'm grinding some ice right now okay me
too
where my wings
Wings don't go hot wings
what a red bins Jackfruit avocado all
fruits
or sweet or sweet where am I where am I
where my hot wings
what
I lost my elytra
well let's go there's no way I wouldn't
bring it it's in my house really oh come
on my chest probably I'm so sorry
hi today
it's in my home and I'm on the other
side you know where I started the tunnel
on the other other side
it's in my shoulder at home
[Music]
Magicka I thought it was here
ah
Kyla how long do you plan on streaming
today
not that long I think I still have like
I don't know like
I eat a whole idea gonna be very busy in
August
so we have like a lot of homework right
now homework
yeah oh I think I know why
yeah yeah right yeah right
yeah yeah
thank you so yeah I don't know how long
can I stream tonight
you have to set priorities
yeah I know thank you for replying
you're welcome
it's my pleasure hello
how long will you stream me
um another
five out four or five hours
because but not all of it will be
Minecraft because I have to read super
chats too um
oh tomorrow
[Music]
oh my God we have to watch it
I am so excited me too yeah we're not in
the moving in pretty ah
I want to sing
what time was it for me I think it was
like maybe around it's
um 10 p.m GST so it's 3 P.M for me okay
okay I will be awake guys
you will be watching too of course worse
of course
finally my fear is to watch that too
definitely second gen
hey that's so long for second gen ID to
do 3DW
[Music]
delayed
um
it's finally time
yeah
wait actually if you you're removing one
ice pack okay you know what yeah I will
do something else I because it doesn't
make sense if we both do the same thing
yeah but I have to do the Torches anyway
so I will torches and then wait for your
arrival
oh by the way why are you putting
torches and uh nether like um
because because it's so dark in the
tunnel especially when you have shaders
on
you question my
my methods huh
I just wanna know like what's for but
okay it makes sense
guys you made me forget the Kyla gift
again what the hell
I forgot to pick it up again I will pick
it up next time and come back
time
and I need no torches
you walk without torches you're not
scared of the dark
my torches is the lava all over the
nether yeah you died did you thank you
did you lose your things
no no no it's just the the way to go
back
yeah oh
because it's too far away already
let's not look in his eyes
ah guys do you remember when I made the
portal uh and then I saw this like big
uh
Fortress never Fortress was that a
fortress or was it a Bastion
where you want to go explore that let's
go no I was I just I just found a really
big one and you know they were like oh
my God that's that's really good it's
really rare
and I was wondering because today in the
video that I watched about the new
update I saw that there's
um these
um trimmings yeah the trim is right and
Bastion and Fortress but where is the
difference between a Bastion and the
Fortress The Fortress one is kind of
radish in color kind of red the Boston
kind of black oh and I chat says I found
a fortress oh okay
is Bastion even more rare or
same
you can say Bastion is more dangerous
did I ever see a Bastion
Fortress huevos skeletons and Blazers
and what about best what do you find in
the Bastion
is Brut piglin
[Music]
brute penguins
yeah I'm gonna brute first
question is dangerous really
yeah yeah of course of course of course
oh yeah
speaking of things
I wasn't looking oh what happened I got
I got jump scared by a piglet I get jump
scared so easily you know
it's okay Minecraft do that a lot of
times she
should go this way
this way because I need to pick up the
I did not
soil myself
I found one very close to my mess up by
all me never go oh really
really I don't remember that
so you go to the Bastion for what what
do you trims only for the trains but
what about before the trims why would
you go
no no uh the before I just like passed
through it and then I I thought like I
have no knowledge about that and then I
just died I just then lost there and
then nice and then I've never gone there
again after that oh it's but I need to
get involved
uh no no actually they offer
uh a lot of
valuable things too inside the bathroom
yeah
they have never worked fashion a lot of
gold
another dungeon followed him
some never ride really yeah some neither
but it's not worth it it's not worth it
that was before now you go there for
Trims and never read smithing template
um
[Music]
I see oh and a pig step music disc yeah
true true true true
I see
a great night
[Music]
I don't care about the trims but you
know what I want to do another time I
want to do some archeology
yeah yeah the pottery right yeah yeah
yeah when pottery and just like dusting
with the brush dusting the suspicious
sand yeah
true true
that's exciting did you try it yeah
did you try the archaeology did you try
it already yeah yeah I got some but not
all of it
but the you know the sniffer egg uh you
find it in warm water right
was it really is like just desert
wait what do you find in the warm water
what was it
something new you find in the warm water
I saw
really yeah the warm emotion
um
no I guess it was something else
real warm ocean no that I guess that's
archeology
okay I'm confused
there's many many things yeah many many
things in this new oven yeah
oh yeah and the Bastion right
um Minecraft
update the requirements for having
natural tools and equipments right now
so we need to go to Bastion to if we
want to have like neither armor and
equipments tools right now yeah I saw
myself why
and so much more complicated
it
but with that updates diamond is more
valuable yeah
I have to go digging for diamonds yeah
yeah
I have this and let's take the potato
how's it going how much ice did you find
I got I I wait I crafted it already to
blue eyes but it's only four Stacks blue
eyes and my biggest is almost dying
um
is also fine like a mix
okay okay okay
[Music]
so should we meet again at the portal
okay
oh
what is the coordinate of the portal
vitamin I don't know
I actually have the notes but too lazy
to open it's okay don't you know it by
heart already how to get there
I got it guys I got it
[Music]
did you not see guys are you not
watching this dream
mobile users
um your eyes too small
um
we're building a tree
she didn't want help did she I feel like
I already offered fauna to help with her
big tree
don't you say no you know
what happened the winds
what happened
it's okay it's okay it's just the wind
nice the wind like flowing through all
the rooms and then the door went like
boom ah yeah yeah
[Music]
happen all the time yeah
I'll kill you
Personal Agenda
little piglets
so Kyle did you achieve what you wanted
to achieve today
should I have no goals but kinda yeah
kinda
my goal is this right now is just like
getting
as many Nethers as possible
before August so yeah
uh yeah you've been doing it for a while
right oh man
getting stronger and stronger
this
is so long without eyes oh my God
I'm coming back I'm coming back
oh
but it's not a lot and I don't think
it's enough probably I'm gonna fix my
pickaxe first and then that's okay I'll
pick up my elytra and then I go find
some more ice if I need it
um but I don't know I think I think in
theory once I have the ice the tunnel is
finished quickly and then I can go find
the egg but I don't know how long you
want to stay with me no pressure it's
okay it's still 12 right now it's fine
you guys have to look at the screen more
closely
brought the gift
of course I did
uh
you guys got the coordinate for FFF I
don't know
yeah I should go there too I think
because I have to probably
um repair my elytra
Maybe
why are you going for your pickaxe yeah
I still have your pickaxes
I repaired one fully I replied both
fully but then I already forgot about
that you forgot
short term memory Kyle yeah I got
distracted a lot yeah
poor Kyla
all the stress from streaming so much
she doesn't even notice that she's
losing her memory
slowly every day
She's forgetting more and more
you you want to fix your ally trace it
maybe maybe I mean I can just fix it for
you it's okay
[Music]
it's your way of fixing uh an elytra by
giving me a new one
I'm here oh me too almost
almost almost almost almost almost
almost
[Music]
aren't there piglens in the boat here
before that did somebody removed them
did you remove piglets
no you I would have been Maybe
or was it at the beginning
I'll kill them now no yes
no don't let the intrusive thoughts
[Music]
they must die they are not paying to use
the tunnel
it's only free for whole life members
no they can't even defend them
okay I guess they kind of did
now it's angry
get off but they don't get off the build
interesting
um oh
oh sugoi
this is perfect
oh you're putting in even more Kyla here
is something for you look at look at the
inside of the chocolate box yay
oh
you got it like you got you got it when
you stream mine
um no I mean I wasn't purposefully
looking for it but yeah it was found in
the creation of this tunnel randomly
oh very lucky
[Music]
sweet I can give you this one back too
thank you yes thank you now if you want
you can follow me if you want I'm just
gonna quickly finish though
I don't know if that's enough though I
mean if that's not enough
you can find some ice again what is that
all the time I see something there and I
don't know what it is when I'm
driving by with my boat
I know it's so rare
and I don't need it
usually like I tried uh I think sometime
two one or two years ago I did strip
mining with my mom
she joined our en Minecraft server and
then she showed me how to do strip
mining and we tried to get some never
right but yeah I don't really need it so
if I find more I can give it to you
it's fine it's
it's fine
with one in here okay
we can ride the same boat
me where did the boat go ah did you get
the boat
no
I'm wait I haven't I'm blind
oh wait
okay
[Music]
roll roll
is this this one is really short this
path
it's just okay one short one and then
another long one
okay okay
then where where is the eyes again oh
this one yeah and this one is long ah
wait okay okay
this is the last one like the last
tunnel oh for now for now who knows
maybe in the future when Minecraft adds
even more new biomies then I have to
find them and I have to go really far
okay
this one is the long one yeah if you
want actually we can do um I I've been
doing a right row pack nice left row
blue eyes
for example
you can do right row if you want
okay
and if you need more let me know I can
give you money right here there bad
times
[Music]
oh oh okay
let's see who's faster
no don't do that
I'm done
teamwork
if you ever need help building something
you can ask me for help too of course I
can try to help
I don't like building so much but I can
try
this is considered as building though
building
[Music]
what did you do
are you freezing
it's fine it's fine what'd you do
it's fine
all good
did you place one in the wrong spot no
no everything's good because I do not do
but I have silk touch
you made a hole of lava no no no no no
all good be careful
nah it's fine
[Music]
I had to fill some holes that were
showing lava so yeah maybe sometimes
when you accidentally dig too deep
I'll find some lava not good not good
snitched on
that is the problem when both of us are
streaming then
yeah somebody yeah somebody's trying to
hide a secret
I need more eyes more come here
now stay don't run away right away don't
run away one
two three four there you go
make it I'll make it until the end
Kyla when should we play Diablo again
I'm so busy like I don't think I can
play it the whole month
and that's a good question yeah
maybe in August all very busy right yeah
but August yeah
ah it's okay it's okay
we'll find a way if anyone finds a way
it will be you guys
you're the one who
is like the most capable of squeezing a
million things into one day no yes yes
not really I just
um I think if you're saying that I'm
good at squeezing not really probably
I'm good at um eliminating
eliminating other things
sleeping oh yeah but you see I I
wouldn't do that I I don't think I could
function on long term yeah I think I
would be very very exhausted and burnt
out yeah don't do that don't do that you
don't feel burnt out or anything right
no no no because because for me
streaming is like relaxing no for me
yeah for me streaming is just when
I want to have fun it's playing games
it's talking I mean I get that too but I
think even then even when streaming is
fun for you you should always know your
own limits and give your body some time
to rest I know yeah I know sometimes you
feel yourself that you're fine but
eventually your body will tell you yo
I'm not okay yeah but just give me I
don't know I don't know why but every
single time when
um I feel very tired whenever I touch
Grassroots because yeah let's just like
exhausting yeah
but yeah I mean every single time I told
uh my fears about like okay guys
tomorrow I'll be touching grass and then
probably I will still stream but maybe
I'll just go like for one or two hours
and then whenever I start streaming
right it's gonna be like going hours and
hours and hours and hours it's like I
don't know streaming charge my energy
somehow
oh that sounds good
if you don't like touching grass how are
you gonna do the barbecue thing in bingo
I mean I can do that in games no that's
so late if you're trying to solve
everything and get your games
you have to do a real barbecue
what where where you would barbecue
stimulator or something like that well
how do you do barbecue in which game I
don't know not yet not yet oh no no no
no
barbecue rough you can do barbecue and
wraps
all right that gives me another reason
to play raft less
no
[Music]
real barbecue it's yummy it's good it's
like you're just eating food
oh are you really like a food enjoyer
like you're kind of picky of food I'm
picking yeah
okay okay
got it
yeah because I just eat food for
surviving
I don't care about the taste anyway
actually
I ran out of blue eyes but I'm just
gonna use
I think
I mean I can grind again
no we'll just use pack test it's fun
it's still fast
my eyes are feeling dizzy
because I'm trying to
keep up okay I'm faster I'm faster
this is like we're already competing
against each other and all right all
right no don't say that
oh but Kyla we're in the same team right
yeah have you seen no no yeah we are not
competing yeah we're not competing we're
in a team
and there is no Lava behind right I just
no no no no no no no no backwards and no
everything's clean and safe
but you know I was looking at the teams
and I thought I have kind of nice oh
wait here there you go I thought the
teams the other team the the team that's
not us is kind of uh
overpowered strong
but
I think you're the the only really
strong one in our team Kyla no no no no
no don't say that you are you're strong
our tree our Dream our teamwork
our older uh members decided now because
I don't think I saw a full member list
um
on progress on processed oh okay yay
uh
I guess it doesn't matter
is it so there's still like some open
spots in the teams yeah still
um
fail I think if you need more of
probably some more Ian would also maybe
put it or more Japanese members too yeah
we are we're we're doing it right now we
are contacting them okay okay
no worries just get us someone good in
our team
to win right yeah and we're gonna win
who's really cracked at Minecraft crony
this chronic participating
um not yet get crony
gouda is already participating so but
she's in the other team
I have to find my newfound sister I feel
so sad
okay
[Music]
okay then
now what
you look like a Pokemon Kyla this is
nice okay
let's uh did you bring a boat
yeah okay let's go back to the very
beginning a very nice place to start and
then I just leave my things at the at my
home
okay and then we can fly to find the
sniffer but so the sniffer we don't have
to go to a newly loaded terrain I think
we need to yeah I think we need to go to
the newer chunk but don't they all like
spawn everywhere in the in the deserts
new ones hey to go to the new one okay
then in the end after I get my elytra we
have to maybe go back here
because this is newly loaded here is
newly loaded yeah yeah sure sure
okay but then how do I bring I know
never mind that's the good thing I just
get the egg and then
but wait how do we get the egg where was
the egg again
where you're wearing the leather uh the
eggs we need to brush right do you have
brush no brush no brush I have some
brush oh really for you my first brush
oh thank you how do you make the brush
um copper Fender sticks
[Music]
okay let's go
okay I I got my elytra
and we come back here and then we fly to
some desert and then
and then we find egg
okay come here okay
let's go
but we're in the never we don't have to
sleep guys
yeah we're gonna explode if we sleep
here spamming
and never it doesn't matter
no repairs needed uh I don't think so
maybe for the maybe for the Elijah I'll
check
I can fix it warm ocean that's what I
was thinking something in the warm ocean
you can find the egg in the warm ocean
no huh
from
the
no no not dancer um
Beach
yes I think if I'm can somebody look it
up because we're unsure
this way
but I mean desert also in the warm ocean
do like close by
that's found in warm ocean yeah yeah
yeah in the sand in the warm ocean yeah
that's that's what I mean yeah yeah yeah
okay I was right and
foreign
so I think the egg yeah the egg is
definitely only in newer terrain I would
say
okay where is my elytra
oh I put this here
found it durability 121.
[Music]
I wonder if it's enough
looking what I have
I have nothing interesting
nah this is interesting see
no and this one is netherade eggs Yes
mine I made it so yeah so you you have a
nice refugees yeah from when I got never
right with my mom oh wait oh
look in uh this this chest this shelter
for you okay
ah all right
are you are you really okay with that I
mean yes
isn't it too much I didn't know I still
had some take a ticket
isn't it too much oh wait oh wait
what happened
I can help you I'm so happy I can help
you
isn't it too much
I don't know no yeah I mean I mean you
can use it like I don't need it I don't
know I don't need it I'm upgrading your
no I mean I don't need it I'm not I
don't really care about these trims they
look cool but I don't care about them
I mean I mean you can you can upgrade
your what uh
oh the diamond diamond stuff is fine I'm
happy with diamond pickaxes I don't need
never ride pickaxes and stuff take it
take it take it I I I already
shut it I took
oh you took it okay good yeah
but can we go to fauna fancy fish farm
yeah okay because my things are breaking
okay okay yeah
yeah do we fly or do we yeah you know
exactly where it is
yeah no yeah yeah yeah
yes yeah yes yes yes
yes but I I always first I go with the
train
I don't know how to go to fly uh there
at first I go with the train and then I
fly okay I'm very confident you ask
yourself
okay let's take the uh inferior Subway
of the
and server is there some card for you
too
it's okay I can walk no no it's a really
long pass Kyla okay I will fly
oh okay um
well I hope you don't Bonk your head
whenever there's um
a wall
that's been very unfortunate
but now you're so fine
so far
okay
I don't even see uh oh there you are did
you Bonk your head no I'm fine really
are you sure are you sure it's fine
yeah died out in the tunnel doing
exactly what you did ah ouch
it's okay yeah but it's okay I'm fine I
told you
he will show
what is this anyway what is that here
for should I get rid of this
am I going to the right place have you
never gone to fauna's fancy fish farm
with the subway
never okay okay now you will find out ah
for Enderman
is it really close
yes but I think the subway now is a loop
so you need to know where to get off
oh really yeah I mean it's time I just
keep going no I just keep oh
but then there's a connection yeah
once we get to PPP I know how to get to
FFF
okay
what direction is this maybe next time
you no I can't because this Subway it
makes many turns so I don't know which
direction it is when I fly
[Laughter]
remember the coordinates but I don't
know
it's okay I mean I mean I have the
coordinates if you want of FFF
yeah I just I just need to open the
notes oh oh well I'm almost there hi hi
follow me
this is so slow
it's okay you can enjoy the
the view the view of beautiful trimmed
Kyla
I think we're almost there oh yeah oh
really oh yeah this feels like we're
almost there
is this Subway slower than it used to be
because like damn
we should speed it up I'm gonna call I'm
a I'm a construction Watson construction
oh it's here yes yes yes yes
[Music]
positive and then we go up here
and once we're outside I know that it's
behind PPP
where are you oh here okay
follow
[Applause]
it's okay it's okay
somewhere here yeah this this big tower
that's ever ah oh yeah that's super
close yes I see I see ice
okay
[Music]
okay got it I I a golfer so I guess
there's two swords we can move to it
hello fishies are you here fishies uh
where are they
we just need to wait
I wait wait uh what am I
you're fine what is what is this dirt
going on here
yeah probably Andy move for dirt
what's Andy doing up here I don't know
is this okay foreign
these are so scary
ah I'm scary
augmented and now I do the pickaxe
um
I should have
should have brought
my other pickaxes too
oh well
is there an end of trust here
yeah maybe I put it in the in the chest
I'm going to die
oh
okay
your turn
okay hold on oh yes okay
okay I can give you back your your
pickaxe the second one
I'll put it in the in the chest above
you okay okay
no game mode
oh
really oh ah
how about now
there should be
wait no now it's like triple or double
back double bgm
isn't there double bgm now guys
yeah uh
uh good I'll just turn it off
hey you didn't hear double really
okay yeah maybe it's not double
my routing confuses me
[Music]
after me
whoa what the fish was sucking the life
from me
it went to soccer convention
do you know do you know salt do you know
Saucon
um
not really
you never heard of sarcon
I'm reading the live chat
Chad you ruined it
Ted kind of helps me to understand oh
wait I still had the funny fish Falcon
sorry I didn't give it back but I need
it anyway oh
did you see the pickaxe it's in the
chest
oh
[Music]
oh what she was already saying it what
yeah because because when when you when
when you ask it like repetitively and
then I was like oh
um um
um
I tried
you know when someone asks you
repetitively about something
[Music]
and I just I just I just I don't know I
want to share my experiences with other
people
.com
there it is there they are you are they
all like arrive at once
so it's last year so not as sassy as the
suspicious scent that we will be for
sure
suspicious gravel Yes actually you know
how to differentiate that because
my eyes
cannot see it
the suspicious oh
because we need to like differentiate it
uh-huh
if we because if we break the sand the
suspicious sand it's gone yeah yeah we
need to differentiate it like using our
eyes
but for me I usually just have three
and I only after my mouse cursor and
then let the F3 well I would probably do
it like that too yeah but it's like
slower actually if you can differentiate
it with your yeah your eyes yeah it's
faster
okay I'm done with amending everything
I'm a little bit more I think hold on
anymore
maybe we need to sleep
that's a lot of phantom we just went to
sleep
you want some
Kyla are you trying to sleep I'm trying
to protect
using too I'm trying to swing my sword
but I'm scared that I will accidentally
hit you no no it's okay I'm I'm a
part-time Warrior my official lawyer
says I'm a part-time Warrior I'll take
care of us
oh okay come here come here oh you
little [\h__\h] they got stuck
Kyla was that you
no of course not I I did not think you
you is there any chance perhaps that you
make yourself so strong with all the
never right and all that and the million
items because you are actually bad at
combat at fighting actually actually
right oh actually right you know what I
have my Thorns armor so if you hit me
you gotta damaged
so you're saying that I damaged you yes
oh my God
okay okay okay but it would be funny if
you're actually like if that's when why
you're doing
um all these all this effort to become
stronger in Minecraft
I mean after all I'm just a blacksmith
it just makes sense
I may not needed but it's just my job
right so yeah
ah
it's so fast
come here come here
you'll be dropping a lot of good stuff
we should pick it up and probably fell
into the ocean oh there it is
I got some Phantom membrane
nice oh yummy yummy okay now we go now
that we're safe yeah we need to go back
to
uh I don't know we need to go back to
the tunnel first right yeah we need to
get to the your chunks I mean we can fly
on our way back but I always get lost
when I fly
it's okay we can have the coordinates
all right what was that
yeah do you have them
yeah coordinates hold on let me open let
me open my notes first
uh coordinate MC cordon and okay e n
Surfer
it's uh
foreign
is this this one the minus two one two
maybe
44. remember yeah I think I think I
think so minus two one two forty four
okay I follow you
where are you let me let me put back all
of these fish first okay
[Music]
okay okay
let's go we go to I think it's first of
all this way
we go we need to go that way though
really okay
oh yeah
flying
paper I'm not a penguin by the way
oh yeah right oh yeah true
my fingers don't blow so fast okay just
goes straight okay
No Pain still there I don't know I don't
see you
um
you're good you're good I think I found
some stuff
yeah okay that is that is that
um
this way okay
it wasn't completely straight
where are you
no I'm I'm on my way okay I arrived at
the portal
okay
should I bring something what are we
doing we just need the brush so we can
get an egg so I need yeah yeah we need
to go to the tunnel first
and then just fly whenever to wherever
we can find the warm ocean right okie
dokie
okay
oh it's burning a lot of burning Forest
oh maybe that's my my trail that I left
behind by accident
let's see
I was an accident
yeah good evening
you played Hulk here before right yeah
wow look here did you play my character
Kiana yeah why you saw how Kiana leaves
behind a fire Trail right yeah the trail
yeah that's right so maybe the forest
fire that you saw was because
[Music]
got it
my character I think I said this if she
doesn't know who who my character is
my character Kiara you know right yeah
my character Kiara say Kiara
where is the city or that one city okay
just to make sure that we're talking
about the same thing which city you mean
our village
I don't think you can call this a city
the Ian city right the it's not it's not
worth being called a city it's a village
just a village Kyla
don't say that wait can you give me like
the coordinates of the portal like
another portal
wait what is oh this is not someone's
house right maybe because it's burning
hold on hold on hold on burning
this is literal burning this is really
oh no
it's uh it's on fire I don't know
why how soon is on fire why what is
okay
um 361 should I write it down
361 and the Z
minus 500. okay
okay
you guys always want me to sing Spanish
right I found this song today
from Katy Perry with some dude which
they sing in Spanish I think the the
boom boom boom girl that song
but he raps in Spanish so fast it will
take me five years to learn the song oh
yeah Daddy Yankee
I'm here hello
hello
[Music]
let me write this down under my camera
what happened
okay let's go
let's go into the dark
[Music]
what time is it over there
almost one it's okay oh so early it's
like good morning time good morning
good morning USA
did you know did you know that in Polish
TV
all the TV programs or almost all of
them my my teacher told me
um they're like you know dubbed but it's
like
dubbed by like everything is done by the
same person
like one guy one guy does all the voices
oh really yeah and apps are what
eh
for the ads or for everything for TV
shows everything oh movies one one
person does like older voices and they
will speak over like they're the
original track will be there too really
quietly the original for example English
track and then one guy reads over it
like really like like monotone like like
this
yeah really yeah my ah my Korean teacher
told me because she lives in Poland too
and in many other countries
and she told me polish TV is really
weird because there is no like proper
dubbing like in other countries TV Maybe
yeah but I mean if that one guy does all
of the dubbing probably I mean
that guy gonna have like a lot of
experience and it's gonna be like
goodness
in in like German speaking countries our
dubs there's like different people for
different characters of course and then
they also they're like actors right they
will pronounce things like like actually
with feelings and my teacher told me
that in Polish TV they just rated
monotone and proudly for women
characters there's a woman voice sir who
voices everything and for guys there's
just one person who voices all the guys
in that one show or whatever so it's
like all the same it's like predictable
but woman is awesome okay never mind I
was just corrected for women it's also
all one guy oh really oh my God that
just made it work
oh my God can you guys not like hire one
more person
that one guy moment that one but
apparently I'm not wrong so what my
teacher told me was was right okay I'm
glad that I'm not lying and spreading
misinformation
[Laughter]
imagine in the movie there's a lady and
and a guy flirting with each other
having a really sweet time and then it's
just the same guy talking to each other
in the voiceover I love you you are so
beautiful oh my God I love you too
you're even more beautiful I will love
you forever oh my God will you marry me
yes I will marry you oh my god oh I'm so
happy oh we should we should have babies
and make children and like oh I'm so
ready oh oh yeah wow that is very very
bad
crony Behavior no
because crony loves herself
oh you know what I owe this I owed us a
village some torches let me know I
stole torches
it's okay it's not okay they're gonna
die because of me
it's not okay
no no
[Music]
um
writing down the coordinates okay we're
good nice more coordinates for the
coordinate folder beautiful okay
all good okay I love when I'm wet you
should honestly you should publish your
your
notes yeah all right so that people know
right yeah
because often I'm like looking for
something and I'm like hmm why did I not
write down the coordinates
yeah I regret coordinates yeah where we
want to go ah anywhere any direction as
long as we can come back
according it's secured but there's no
wait no we need we need warm warmly not
that way maybe which which way
we can go that way
okay I will just follow you
I'm just trying to find some I don't see
you
just go straight it's gonna be fine wow
there's so much Sakura here
I found the best Sakura bayomi
oh this is so cute it's loading so slow
Kyla please go slow
I'm I'm going around too it's so true
sad polish oh my God how many Polish
people are in my chat right now because
I saw so many people who said yeah
that's right that's right I can't
believe there's so many any Polish
people in my live chat maybe not
quite a lot
happened I don't know I know I'm okay
I think I have so many because I always
stream at European Time
one I'm here oh
this guy here oh hello
yeah
is this not a warm ocean
hi I don't think this is so Worm but
there's Turtles
yeah doesn't that mean it's warm I don't
know
this is just
normal plain ocean
um
I lost you
[Music]
I'm I think I'm still close here but we
can just go around this ocean and
probably there's a warm one
okay
would it saying warm water
warm water
I can't even see from here
don't you want to sleep first bad time
no I don't I didn't bring a bed
I can give you a pad
oh no that's ice again
what's your graphic card
oh I heard that you just change it right
yeah no not yet I have it but I have to
still
um I have to
build it yeah ah I see I see so not
right now it's still the old one yeah
yeah
mine is still 38 DTI 30 40 TTI
38 DTI 3080 oh I'm getting a 40 18.
this is eyes this is cold one I'm
breaking
what happened I think I'm just I like to
scream oh it's in my free time I like to
scream
it's okay it's my hobby you know it's
okay
[Laughter]
whatever I don't care about this crying
obsidian
uh
[Laughter]
can I tell you a story yeah I don't know
if you know the story one time one time
I was playing Minecraft like maybe two
years ago and
um I was just chilling just just
building something and I found really
randomly uh uh oh I was found I was
found by some drowns
and the first round that found me he was
throwing a
he was throwing tridents at me and I'm
like I've never seen a trident drowned
before that was my first time first time
okay and then I kill him
the first round I ever see I killed him
and he dropped a trident oh so it's like
first try so I called it the first
Trident first Trident first try try it
you still have it right now yes I still
have it
but the reason why this was so special
and funny is because gooda the the girl
who has a trident as her weapon
um she was looking for tridents in
Minecraft and she was she was farming
them for hours and hours and hours
they're just very lucky yeah I just
found the first try without looking for
it and she looked for it so many hours
and didn't find it for a long long time
[Music]
did you find some warm ocean yet I'm not
but I'm brushing some suspicious
grateful right now
uh-huh
a cold ocean okay I'll go look now I
thought maybe
I'm not flying straight though but as
long as you have the coordinates
it's good yeah it's okay that's just
normal ocean there's cold ocean ocean
and warm ocean
cheers graph
species oceans
[Music]
breath full aggression
suspicious grapple River
oh pottery
Kyla got distracted
by suspicious gravel
because it's very suspicious I need to
check it it's raining now
the sky is so sad
pieces
some ice here
there's blue ice packed eyes
you wanna take it but you have finished
it you want to change it again you know
I'm just I don't I just was thinking
because it looks nice nice Spike
okay I go look for
warm warm ocean
maybe here
[Music]
it's scary
kind loads in so slowly oh yeah you need
to go back
it's not loaded I'm loading so much
terrain oh God where where is Home Kyla
it'll be fine
I don't know where I am
it's okay I got the cord in it
I mean I can go to your place no
what no no go go elsewhere because here
there's nothing we don't need this area
Beach cold why is it all cold I don't
even know where I came from
um Kyla can you tell me the coordinates
uh the accordion is what the the portal
yeah closer to where we came from
okay
um
twists
thank you
you're welcome
perfect I am going in the right
direction
ouch oh yeah let's go
ocean
River
[Music]
I found this the cherry blossom by Omi
again
nice it's so pretty
uh I'll fly I'll go ouch oh you're not
planning to um build something using
that I don't know I I maybe I thought
maybe I add some cherry blossom
materials to my villager
um Farm venue
where you know Phoenix done the one I
built I thought maybe
I can make it look cuter more aesthetic
and maybe maybe I build a new house who
knows
a new house that I don't use
okay I'm going this direction now
because Savannah sounds warm
yeah true true so funny okay remember
oh [\h__\h]
oh she's still trying to find
oh
whoa Nanny what did you find
wait
Forest what do you mean first I'm in the
water
oh there's a lot of dirt though
I guess I should
carry this instead
what's this wrong grapple or sand are
you even looking for a warm ocean now
yeah yeah but uh hold on
because last time I found a sniffers in
this kind of place so maybe I'm gonna
check this
okay
I'm going completely different direction
now
it's okay
if I find it you come to me or I
honestly I mean I think I can probably
uh brush off the egg alone but you know
if you want you can come to me
let me get some bamboo while I'm here
[Music]
Kyla has learned to ignore my screams
yeah it's okay
this one
there should be a suspicious Sun here
right suspicious Sun
's piece is sad
so it's fine you can you make is it true
that you can make um blocks out of the
bamboo now
ah I don't know I feel like I heard
something like that
yes yes you can okay oh really yeah
and I just found the bamboo forest so
I'm just gonna bring a lot of bamboo
but it looks the same was that the thing
it looks the same as
normal one
or
[Music]
it looks different okay okay
I guess that was just about the signs
maybe
um
signs just can't be pink for example
I don't know what I'm talking about
no suspicious sad
ah maybe it's because you don't have
your good luck charm Kyla yes
yes good luck doco I'm here I'm here
I'm here good I am your personal luck
shooter
Oh that's oh wait that's all the toys
like this no you sure about that okay
then adios
Amigos
foreign
[Music]
okay I have enough bamboo
I go look for warm ocean again
did you guys uh start talking to my chat
for a moment did you guys watch I
thought
I found warm let's go is that good
enough
check check I mean am I looking for
something specific
in the uh like a monument or so yeah you
need to find Monument or okay
okay
Monument
okay well I was saying guys did you
watch formal stream yesterday because I
called in to her stream
the birthday right yeah I I saw I saw
the what is that the poem yeah you saw
my people
yeah on Twitter I I read it
good one a good one thank you I figured
out that I have a talent for it
yeah yeah you do this ocean was really
tiny what the hell yeah
why is this ocean so small
where where where do I go
this way
why does the ocean become a river I
thought the rivers become ocean right
now baby I need to go to your place 1500
okay uh and two twenty four thousand two
hundred
should I write it down
no no it's fine
what is this ocean
this is not a real ocean this is a plot
no this is a lake
if many rivers
flow into a close
body of water then that's a lake
I think
ouch it's baby ocean
oh yeah this is the look warmer yeah oh
yeah where are you did you already find
me
not really a close close by I'm so long
I think this is I think this is the
bamboo yeah I think this is the bamboo
that you saw should
thank you guys Minecraft geology thank
you thank you I am more logical than
Minecraft
geologically because I'm trying to find
Monument maybe there's nothing here Kyla
I just want to follow you can you please
carry me
oh okay
um wait
uh
uh oh yeah probably this is the bamboo
that
you saw before okay two uh one uh 1500.
and 24 200.
okay okay
yeah princess carry me please I just
want to turn off my brain and follow you
is that too much to ask
thank you blank thank you
I mean probably we can just go by boat
probably so that we can go together yeah
but you know the problem here is I found
the lukewarm ocean but it's basically
just a lake because it it doesn't turn
into a big ocean it's just a lake even
though it's cold lukewarm ocean
so small and everything around it is
jungle and rivers
okay and I cannot I don't I seem to
always come back to it when I fly around
okay uh
1500 the Z
uh yeah XXX is 1500.
and then the Z the 24 300 200.
two four three right yeah
[Music]
oh my God my breath I can't hold my
breath
two two four two four three two four
three
here's my leg Lake wow
I adopt this Lake
you are another
yeah
we're like so far away already on the
service yeah there's still much much
unexplored Terrain in our first
Minecraft
endless endless yeah
oh
two four three okay close close close
close
okay
I am starting to get
a little bit crazy from my bgm
this is like a very big jungle there
should be a type of jungle here by the
way but yeah what what kind of jungle
this jungle yeah
there's like a monument Temple monument
in the job oh you think so yeah because
it's so big so probably if we
can find it
hmm
you can go look for it have you already
gotten the trims from the jungle yeah
yeah
but I mean it's gonna be good if we can
find enough I'm
[Music]
nearby
I'm once
162 245. like Wawa is real
[Music]
in existing
in Canada
[Music]
to be here where are you
I mean
I am
I am somewhere you have to find me let's
let's play let's play hide and seek in
the forest
oh hi hi
I go hide in the forest and you try to
find me
ouch
what the [\h__\h]
what was that
why did you hurt me Carla
oh no it's the burbs again
Kyla don't worry I will protect you
let's start already what
yes bye-bye share willpower
okay I I you want to live
here
and there's oh my God there's there's a
little cat jungle cat
CH it no sorry I'm getting I'm getting a
little bit crazy from my energy drink I
think even though I only drank three
sips
you fly I follow
we sleep we sleep okay but I have no bed
I can log out though
I hear monster I hear monsters okay
that's okay
okay Kyla I will close my eyes and you
will fly and find me
the the right ocean because I I need to
find it
it's it's your job
I want to give you this nah that's just
one piece oh
one piece plenty Pottery shirt thank you
I'm not sure yet how I will use this but
I will try
yeah you need you need four of that the
same one okay four what yeah for what
four shards for short make what uh the
the pot for the pot I thought you need
drinks
uh this is like the
it got the pattern something like that
oh ah this is the one on the pattern
[Music]
um
okay let's go I don't know um
where should we go
go with confidence
and determination
you know what just go with both
okay options
yeah
adios
[Music]
um
Kyla we should
um sing like a pirate song
no no no no I look up uh what do you
call those those ocean ocean sounds guys
what do you call that again
see shanty
ones
[Music]
no way what's a copyright free see
shanty
um
a lot oh see shanty
um there is nothing
hmm
there is nothing here
what do we do with a drunken angel
I won't see Shanty lyrics
lyrics
whoa okay but how does the
Melody go
maybe maybe now that I can write poems I
can create my own sea shanty
even better nice
what do we do okay
what do we do
nothing here
no concealer
nope what will we do with the drunken
sailor what will we do with the drunken
sailor early in the morning way hanging
up she Rises way hanging up she Rises
when you hanging up she Rises early in
the morning shave his belly with a rusty
razor okay okay I can come up with this
this is really early in the morning
I'll write my own right now while you're
while you're rowing row row rowing the
boat I'll registered
what do I do with
no
I don't think there's like a way to go
to this
warm ocean
and walk Island piano
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
guys give me a good line
um
everything the same completely new line
guys
you need to be drunk to write good
shanties but oh well I don't drink
alcohol
[Music]
um
nothing
cannot do we need to fall
okay and you guys I don't like your
ideas neutering
[Music]
laughs
I want
neutering
load faster first
uh
[Music]
okay here I have a couple of lines okay
you can join me anytime
um ocean how far to go to the war um
ocean how far to go to the warm motion
oh I didn't think about the last the
ending
ah I can't wait much longer I can wait
much longer
will travel further will travel further
Kyle and Kiana will travel further
photo
[Music]
why won't you to rain load faster why
won't new terrain load faster why won't
you to rain learn faster
you want to go check if there is like
three or no no okay stays focused guys
yes it's very focused yes no we don't
have time to be distracted
I want you to reload faster
um
that's a ruined
why does new terrain not load faster
um
is it a graphics card thing or a server
thing no that's the server thing because
this is like already Far Far Away wow
what is this on our left side that's a
um ruin but it's in the wood this is
this one right this one got us peaches
gravel for the shards if you want to
check but it's not it doesn't have an
egg right no but I'll take a I'll take a
screenshot for the coordinates okay
okay good all good yes I got it okay
why doesn't the terrain load faster at
this sort of thing
um
what do I finish that with
[Music]
I'll bunk into a mountain I want to find
the sniffer and go I want to find a
sniffer angle I want to find the sniffer
Echo and then make scrambled and goes
what you you want
make scrambled eggs with any egg of
course yeah we went too long I think
okay Carry Me
carry me okay
okay I found that I know Kyla why is it
so hard to find the warm ocean when you
need it of course of course it's hard
maybe I'll just follow you fly
wow the forest is on fire it's okay fire
in the forest wine
I see
Beach as the ocean but no oh I see I see
something cool
I see sheep but no
how to how to get out of the water when
I eat I'm in the water it's okay it's
just double space and right click okay
I knew that I just I just got a little
bit nervous
it's okay let's
see does the warm ocean always come with
um the fancy flowers and stuff
the lukewarm is yeah yeah the the color
of the water is all different
it's kind of greenish
can say yeah I noticed
oh no I lost you
hey oh no
I'm in 700 x
700 and that 22 uh
22 yeah okay I'm here I'm here I'm here
[Music]
okay let's go
why can I not find it
[Music]
and is it even guaranteed that I find an
egg
it's kind of hard actually but oh no
that's okay I'm lucky I'm lucky yeah
yeah I believe in you it's fine
oh really sure
this is a big ocean I think we have
finally found the Atlantic
I say I see a more deep ocean a monument
or something no no Monument
but something glowing
hmm
[Music]
no where is she you lost me again
yeah did you get distracted again
no it's really hard to follow someone
you
hmm
I am in 708
I've been trying my best
708 and
24 100.
okay
I'm at a village
I feel like we've been here before
Village
hmm
maybe you can go to the village and
sleep first probably I can
yes but first I take the beautiful
terracotta wait I don't have the bed
with me nice
oh I have your bed hey
that's okay
it's okay beautiful well it's it's so
beautiful it's orange and and yellow and
these are my colors you know
my my favorite
there's so many enemies here oh my God
ah
okay you little [\h__\h] [\h__\h] yeah
700 24
000 750 and then 24
000 200.
why there is no Village here 756
wait wait
okay okay got it got it it's a
terracotta Village
[Music]
I can take some bad from here yeah take
a ticket
too
excuse the more oh you want to sleep
Yee I'll think about it okay no just one
second
I sleep now okay right why am I doing
this I have a whole mess up you're right
oh my God I'm so sorry I'll stop I'm
stopping it just looks so pretty I
thought I I need it I don't need it
where are you
I'm in the house oh
what happened I I dodged a skeleton in
my his Arrow hit this villager
not again you little [\h__\h] [\h__\h] you yeah
[Music]
okay Kyla
where is the egg
oh
trend
give me
ah
wrong okay follow me
go this way maybe
slowly slowly slowly slowly
slowly slowly slowly slowly slowly
oh oh this is such a beautiful beautiful
Valley oh my God
okay no ocean God
I will find a new ocean
a better ocean are you still there
I don't see otherwise okay I'll go this
way
um
now we need an air Shanty are there air
shanties
instead of sea shanties
we've never heard of such a thing but
you know what we we needed it
[Music]
I'm uncovering
every piece of our en server
nice I think I lost you again no but
it's okay okay you know what maybe we're
going different directions just go yeah
and then you see who finds it first yeah
yeah because like I mean for whatever
reason it doesn't make any sense if we
go to the same
Direction nice of an event yes wait is
this a warm one no no no no no no no no
no no yes I found I found
really
I said the same one as before no the new
one no no no no it's new
this is like a lot of jokes
lukewarm is not okay
it has to be warm
Temple or there is a jungle temple oh
well
I found I found something
is this what we're looking for
really
lukewarm is fine I found
um
I found
okay okay
good I'm good okay yeah yeah I escaped
thank God for my electric
I'm not gonna die here no
um
but I found I found what we're looking
for apparently
oh really I'm just gonna build myself a
base really quick or or put my bed here
and then I look for suspicious scent but
if there's ground ones throwing tridents
at me it's a little bit difficult
[Music]
I'm coming I'm coming okay I can tell
you uh one
1992 is where my bed is 1992. and 25 and
100.
okay
but okay 1992 is X
okay okay what if we get a trident again
that would be too funny
Good Year it was a good year
I just wanna go back back to 1999
it's a ride in my own neighborhood
I just wanna go back they hit me baby
one more time I wanna go back want to go
brush but first I need to kill
you I need to kill first destruction
25 I see Trident I see Trident coming at
me another another Trident really yeah
yeah
I don't see him but he sees me it's not
fair
you little [\h__\h] where are you
okay where is it here no
um I I gave it a coordinates of the bed
um but I'm like in the water ah
oh
all good
yes I will kill him and get a new
trident
okay
I got him
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh good I don't I don't think he dropped
the Trident but at least he's scared of
that and I almost did too
you're using your armor right no you're
using and I think I heard another
trident
there
I think maybe my maybe it was my
imagination
I saw any trident
um
there's many enemies
but and they keep on spawning too right
so it's good if I have you you can take
care of the enemies and not look at
suspicious sand look it's in the water
are you in the water yes no right but
right now I'm above water so you could
maybe see me there's like a light spot
in the in the ocean
on your bed
so I'm close to that relatively
just go in the water
I saw a chest somewhere here I think
oh yeah
water
mending fishing rods
let's go
don't you see me the actual coordinates
are 2069.
and the the sniffer ain't not gonna be
in the water right no but the sand isn't
I think in the water
oh the sand where the egg is underneath
as far as I know
okay yeah
he told me they told me two thousand it
will be yes yes egg isn't yeah okay good
2016 nine I can't open what
I need some water breathing potion
I know I can make a dollar one
just this one 2800
thing oh hi
hi
so my viewers said that it could be here
okay can you take care of the enemies
and I look for okay okay
for the um
a suspicious sand right suspicious and
exhibition ah suspicious suspicious
stand oh
what's inside wait I think my inventory
is full
um
I don't think there was anything in that
one was it can they be completely empty
what that wasn't brushing it's right
click
I did it wrong it's okay there's still
plenty of it yes that's nonsense okay
um
breathing breathing um um oh sand
sand
thank you
sandstone and
I will try to look at the others then
haven't checked the other not yet no
okay
do you have a door Kyla
a a breeding right um hold on
hold on
Maybe
let's craft some door
I'm too stupid for this
answer I don't think I think there was
like just a single suspicious sand here
you
know
oh and there's no respiration
I thought I can lend some but no
um
there was one Oh you mean the one I
broke oh
um the door a door
[Music]
and right click red red red click
shoot
I got I got an angler Pottery shirt
I'm gonna run out of food
I I have food I have food oh
um yeah yeah I don't have much left I'll
go find another suspicious and
is it always like at the bottom
this one big food thick food oh thank
you
oh thank you sticky sticky
thank you
oh do you have a water breathing potion
I I I don't bring it but what I can do
is actually maybe I can lend you my
helmet
this one this one yeah just just just
take my helmet first time
it will let you it will let you print it
I didn't pick up the recipe ah
what happened I almost died
wait no I get it now I get it get it get
it
you have it the potion really
[Music]
nice beautiful helmet it's fire
resistance guys
it's viruses
fire assistance potion
the water breeding I I don't
my my energy is still the netherite
set up guys
oh
yeah can there be a delicious sand here
too
actually should we bring another setup
well uh I will I will try to find some
wood my my breathing holds much longer
thank you thank you
I think it's 45 seconds right now
suspicious what I I go up first I go up
first
any of the structures should have some
okay nice
I'm going first
okay we do the squish Squatch with no
egg I don't think that's an egg ah is
that a pickaxe or something like that
pick it up
or is it where is it
Nani
oh yeah it was a wooden hole
what
don't give me useless things
I want the egg
suspicious sand
it's great Squad
it's so dark
that is
a shelter Pottery shard
okay
I want to do this during daytime
[Music]
shocker
on that one okay okay
oh the one that I just got from the
uh treasure map I see yeah I have two
potion I have two water potion you need
that
would be probably kind of useful yeah
and I can give you back to oh wait does
this not work because there's something
on top
wait what where's the oh here here
ah
hold the torch oh interesting
[Music]
okay that helps a lot yes
Kyle you're still here hi yay I got
another shard
okay
um
this one is the potion you can just have
it oh thank you let's go
do you want uh you can no you you use
one too no no it's fine it's fine I have
doors right now okay
foreign
I think I already found all the
suspicious sand in this little spot
maybe I know one more
one more
I heard that
I am
[Music]
it's brown Emerald emeralds
okay I think here maybe no more
okay I go here
I'm mostly looking at the on my
um
the letters here so if I'm missing
something guys or if I'm going back to
the same place let me know because it's
hard for me to notice
okay let's go back here this is so big
there must be more
should I like get rid of some of this so
maybe I can see more
[Music]
sad
okay
suspicious
[Music]
come on come on it's round it's round
it's not round
what was that
no is it just like that cards
that was cold great
wow exciting
uh
I want to open it
wait
thank you for the door
you're welcome
get rid of all this stupid
that's me me
it's me it's me okay
it's fine
I didn't know you could hear the other
person drowning
we can yeah
um
yeah that's a lot of treasure map
oh
there should be at least one I think but
one egg
one egg would be nice
species
I haven't brush it okay oh brush it yeah
okay I brush
but I don't think that looks like it's
pottery okay
[Music]
um
maybe down here
[Music]
oh you could probably
um when I was looking for
some kind of tree for the like Lush
caves
I used that some kind of mod or so that
made it stand out more you could
probably do that for the
what is this probably yeah something
like that
I'm using the shaders and people see
that it's very visible but problem just
blind
I'm blind too don't worry I don't even
know which ones did I go to before these
ones or these ones
maybe if the chest is
empty
I'm probably even here portion gone oh
already
[Music]
are you living your shelters there hey
yeah you're gonna forget no no why I
even remember surely okay Chad chat will
tell me right okay suspicious and
ghetto
that's it one two three this one is
already done and that was an ax wow
[Music]
it's so cool
is it just literally one layer iron
what do you mean
like
the first layer that we saw and then we
don't need to dig down
um
I mean sometimes underneath the cut
Sandstone underneath those there's often
suspicious sand I missed two what
where I came from
hmm was it here ah wait I think I saw
something
what do you mean I missed I missed too
right next to each other
but not here wasn't there uh
all of this are saying
oh
I found one but that's probably a
different one right
um
when I took the top off yeah okay this
is not an egg
what is
it
[Music]
um
Sands
how long does the breathing potion work
three minutes okay
I can give you some doors after that
suspicious sand
oh nope
I'm not even gonna finish that one
we need so many Maps iron okay I'll go
to Sans and I go here
maybe also under the chest
[Music]
my eyes are getting tired from looking
so closely
what
Sans
they have a cracked pattern on them too
really
yeah people see that all right
maybe I'm just blind come to me too
I
okay
I'll just remove every sand that is not
suspicious
isn't that the most genius strategy yeah
you can do that
I'll remove the whole ocean
if I have to
why not dolphins
did I hurt you
can dolphins attack you if you hurt them
no okay
oh God
oh
Kayla before
I I didn't even find the egg in the
ocean ah if I'm somewhere else but I
thought it could only be in the ocean
that's why people just saying it like I
was just too lucky for finding that
before it really yeah
because I watched the YouTube guide and
it said I have to look in the ocean warm
ocean
okay this is the first time I'm I've
been doing brushing underwater trying to
find the eggs like this
this is real Minecraft strategies
two places in the Google search wrong
motion rooms and some sand thing hmm
but it's weird that the egg would be
here because that animal normally it's
not in the ocean
why why would it be here it's so weird
I can't even blink
this is awesome
man
this is all the sun Islands think you
mean those eggs are so old
um
I guess so
really really ancient egg
no it's a species one
I found something suspicious but let me
breathe first
you can find it you want the doors
oh no no actually the helmet is like
really really helpful on its own
is this the one that I oversaw before
[Music]
and as maybe that is just
too dare what you guys can see it oh no
hold on which one I don't know which one
I have no problem I'm just blind
which one
not this one right that one Kyla do you
need glasses
fine but it's just I cannot see the
pattern
why did that break guys
was that suspicious this one okay this
one okay
it broke like like glass
oh I'm gonna die
what's this
ah an ax
I have a feeling there is no eggs we are
finding an ass together oh I was so fun
next yeah that looks that must have been
suspicious
um
no my church say there's like there are
like two I don't I cannot see it I'm
blind
it's very visible what it's very
don't let them make you feel bad about
your eyesight Kyla I am just as bad as
you with this
right side
this one
okay uh
[Music]
mine I feel like we looked at everything
guys if you see something let me know
suspicious sand is dark I'm not looking
at that I'm looking at the the words on
the screen
that should be simpler
just gonna get rid of the normal sand
again
genius stretch oh God I'm getting so
tired from this
not thing
anymore
our ruins guaranteed to have under
guaranteed to have the suspicious sand
but I guess not the
not the ink
what am I gonna do for my my scrambled
eggs now guys I guess so while I have to
rely on you guys too bad now hand over
the eggs guys hand them over
the chicken eggs
how is the percentage like how how much
how how
is the percentage of finding the sniffer
egg I guess slow
to tell me
life no 6.7 6.7 is oh
6.7 is the same one as the
real estate should not be that hard
new fresh egg let's go
drop rate oh yeah drop rate yeah drop
rate that's the word
I'm trying to find the words for that
yeah drop rate yeah
hmm
is that all maybe we have to find a new
one
you sure you check all of this already I
think so
this one done
maybe there's another warm ocean close
by
Where's My Shirt By the way
I'm gonna look for my shulker I've been
in front of your shelter though I hear I
think yeah
there's no more there are ruins on the
beach you can use those as well really
ruins on the beach
they can be there too
yeah you can check that one
ouch
it's okay
all good
I'll fly to find
uh the
beds again
okay which side
I don't know
I'm too stupid to fly
Kyla
I forgot how to fly I forgot
there we go I
where you are young where are the Beds
which side
it's really hard to fly here
cannot fly
oh wow
I found
corals
foreign
maybe there is another
um and it's what's really warm is
actually Maldives level warm ocean wow
but that is definitely not their
Direction where the beds are oh well
so
this looks like there could be another
uh Monument here
maybe really you've got another one I
think there could be another one because
this is so big
1992 I am
I just look around then I explore
hmm
this is still look one lukewarm look
warm I'm I'm not warm
is that a ship
oh could it be at the ship too
no I guess not but that's a really
intact ship not this one for sure
Atlantis
ocean Monument there
ship will have the trim I don't need the
trim
I need the sniffer
hmm
go on an adventure because we're oh yeah
I I think we can take off to go on an
adventure Bingo Square
oh yeah yeah true true for that I think
you know Minecraft is okay
okay maybe there are no there's no
Monument here after all
although
no that's just
really easy to see
yes barbecue you have to do in real life
check again in daylight
is there anything in the warm ocean
can we find the one I only see a lot of
corals
but originally I thought people said I
have to go to a warm ocean
oh oh I found uh
I found another like Temple thingy
Monument thingy
Monument
or ocean Monument or the same thing that
we were looking at before okay okay sure
uh where is uh coordinates uh 2 600 uh
uh and 25 200 uh
oh you should be here there's monsters
again maybe this one hello I'm here I'll
take care of it
I'll try then there's a trident really
it's okay I'll take care of he's not
he's not shooting
okay
all good oh
really I don't see you
I see you hi let's go let's try to find
it
wow this one is much prettier
he has so many chords
just go down bye
no stop
okay
suspicious sun will will find it here
we'll find it
fresh
I cannot go home if I don't find what I
need
yeah of course yeah yeah yeah
I wonder
also I don't know did you bring your bed
because I'm gonna place my bed here and
then maybe we can sleep
I'll just disconnect it's fine okay
you're so fast do you have like a
shortcut for disconnecting
no
okay
maybe maybe we should go by a system now
I am gonna observe the one where I have
the bed on top okay
so we don't have to look anymore
afterwards so hopefully
it almost ends normal sound
son
elytra takes damage when swimming oh
what wait what really
never heard of that before
oh Pottery shard
um I found one suspicious sand
ton
nah nothing
oh
nope
what is even that thing
gold
hmm
what happened that is dying but at least
this one's way closer to the surface so
we can go up quickly
good night good night everybody who's
sleeping
I wanna find it and then I'll go uh Read
Super chats but I cannot stop before
you're gonna Read Super chattel to Kaila
yeah wow
and I and I
I don't know how to say a lie in
English
like
[Music]
um
yeah what's the right word for it
cannot see it guys
um there is nothing more right
good girl I don't know that sounds kind
of weird
and I sounds better
and that's an actual adjective
diligent yes diligent I think is the
right word
is diligent I am
production
the legend the legend yeah you are the
legend yeah Legend
legendary Kyla
deadly and delicious
what
this all sounds so similar okay there
was literally only one suspicious sand
on this side what the hell
I am now
going to go away from my bed or I take
my bed
so that I know what I'm doing
I'm going to the middle part
okay
that's suspicious and
oh no
oh nothing
nothing
here's something
Pottery again
that was one and I just tried to broke
the I just tried to break the the the
the the grass
to see what's underneath
huh
why why does the the sand act so
suspicious
[Music]
nothing
have you even found a single one since
we came here
a suspicious scent um
yeah but like trash trash trash trash
and you know all those books well you
know are you just joking all of the all
of the ones I broke by accident have
eggs in them
probably
so okay you you are looking very
suspicious oh that is not an egg
this one how about this one
we'll see this one
this one
[Music]
more trash
who put so much trash into the ocean
magical Ben
it's like the sand right
like why it's yeah
good wait I will get rid of them here
no
hmm
species oh I mean okay I can actually
see the difference now okay I'll try to
go like this
in the future it's just like a little
bit darker mm-hmm
for the resort
wait there is no single Sun here
there's one too red yeah okay I've got
an iPhone okay
[Music]
I can see it now
real
um
yeah I just like one time you have to
look at it and then
you can see it clearly
you can what's the difference eh oh look
closely guys
it's sand but like a little bit darker
than the others
I can now confidently and quickly go
through all the sand
there's nothing here really
not single of it
hmm
fine I'll just leave the dirt here
um
how about this one this one is done
right you didn't find a single one where
you left the door
yeah I'll find out me or is this where I
already went yeah maybe maybe probably
because it looks like I already dug a
little bit around there
um
over here
it's not even a ruins I don't know maybe
this is also already touched we need a
system Kyla to check which one we
already checked
like putting putting a stone on top or
so
oh you want to put a
okay um
I'll just put on yes okay
torch on the roof that works too I think
this one's
check the output output torch okay this
one's kind of checked too I think
how about this one
let's see yeah that one looks maybe oh
this one is suspicious
Nani
oh I found one too I think that's one
really you can't
um brush normal sand anyway right so you
could also do a test with your brush
I guess
but it's gonna takes time
oh this is suspicious
no eggs no eggs
it's worth removing some of the
some of the blocks to see what's
underneath oh
the third island
what happened there
um
nope nope it's fine it's fine
oh man
um
the brush I think this one's done
this place maybe maybe under the corals
hmm
okay this one is me
don't worry check
um
I feel like this one's already empty now
sure
I'll do a double check
we don't need to
double check double check another layer
no ah double check double check
especially now that I have my third eye
same color but just darker
it's like in the middle a little bit
darker
Kyla where's your Minecraft third eye
come on
wait wait wait this one is feels like
it's different color but I took Sun
maybe I'm just
I don't know my eyes is open your bird I
Kayla
you have to first open your mind only
then can you open your food eye
yeah maybe it's because of the Shadow
[Music]
let's blame the Shader
we blame the cheater
and nothing here I think
you're here just make it harder or
really and better then
okay this is double checked so it gets a
second torch
let me double check this one
then one done that one
maybe since you checked this one maybe I
can try to fly
try to find another one yes please do
okay
let's go sorry Kyle I'm very unlucky
today otherwise we could already end it
it's my fault
my Phoenix Vlog is not existing today
I mean I think I don't know I should
have
the luck but I don't know where is the
lock
you put this oh you want to sleep I want
to sleep this is comfy chat is lucky
chat is lucky I'm not feeling kind of
bad you know I am so focused on the sand
I'm so sorry guys
it's 9 am stream still happening of
course because it's already scheduled
guys
I have I have a stream at 9am
that's in in how many hours
yes half an hours seven hours ah and you
want to sleep in between right
yeah and some sleep is what a week
no need for Sleep Need for Speed
oh wait this one looks did anyone check
this yeah let's find another one but
it's not double checked
there I feel like there's another one in
here there must be there must be
because I didn't uncover this
if the cut Sandstone goes so deep that
means that down there there could still
be suspicious sand right
really
oh
yeah
guys please help me to see the
ruins is this a ruins
this is a monument
oh no another Trident hold on try then
you need to wait go get him go get em
Kayla
okay
I sure
I think I found another one here but
it's just one like the only one what one
building only okay
I found one
see guys look compare this and this the
amount of dark pixels is more on this
one
again
[Music]
congratulations
[Applause]
okay amazing we can go home okay
the same place as the previous one right
yeah where I was still staying yeah hey
let's go oh
yeah
yes once I've opened my third eye it was
only a matter of time
yeah I guess we will fly back to the
portal coordinates yeah okay
let me brush brush
do I need this
and what uh what do you planned with
that egg by the way uh scrambled eggs
okay nice what I need two to breathe
well first of all I just want to hatch
this one okay and then we can talk about
finding
more eggs maybe if I'm really bored on
my private time I can try to find more I
feel like here we're done there's no way
they have a second egg
in the same ruin I feel like you have to
be
extremely lucky
um
okay
repeat nothing
unless
I don't even know which one was it uh
which one was there even
which one was it
this one
can look a little bit closer on this one
goes this one
oh wait you have you have a sniffer
right
uh
uh I
I gave that to me go to yours hey
that's okay I guess you didn't need it
for yourself
hey it's one
I can can I not secretly breathe with
someone else's sniffer
without them knowing
just go there but it's probably I mean I
mean you know and there there is a
sniffer in the
in front of the portal the new server
portal
I I think you can just
but then but then I need to get my
sniffer there but I want it to be close
to my house that's kind of annoying
yeah yeah it's different so I I'll just
find another egg and then yeah
I'll be fine once I have dinner and then
another egg
pieces nope
maybe braided and got multiple yeah I
mean in theory I'm happy with just one
sniffer but I guess two is good for good
measure
uh
I mean the ocean is still huge you can
yeah
oh yeah you're brushing on the one
single uh Monument thingy
and there are actually two but maybe
nope nope nope nope
I created a door with water
fascinating
I missed one which one
she wow oh that one
[Music]
cut sandstone
that is sand that is cut sandstone
that is also got sandstone
I think that's all in this place
nope
Emerald gun oh yeah probably ah it's
okay like guys okay
sand Sands and and can it really be
underneath there I feel like it's too
deep what are we talking about we talked
about Snappers it's a new Minecraft
animal
ah okay
yeah yeah torch flowers seeds will be
needed if you plan on breeding them
what about what do I need to make it uh
come to life
do I also need a torch flour seed
actually I forgot what was the thing
that makes the echo hatch
yeah I yeah I have no idea but I just
just time because uh yeah the Moss block
uh like kind of uh makes it faster
but you can also just place it on normal
anything I guess
okay
I'm at my home oh okay do you have on
the coordinates for your portal
let's go
um
[Music]
six eight
two four okay hmm
oh wow
so far
um which is that west or south or east
or
West
we just need to go to the negative X
which one is that
I think we are now
we are facing the
different okay
one I think
thank you
foreign
do you still have enough fireworks yeah
I think so
oh yeah
oh this is still this is like a big warm
ocean
[Music]
or we've been here before we've been
here before right
would be funny if we
are actually accidentally back at my
mess sound that I found
could this be
okay okay
we are going back yay finally yeah
um
I'm led to have you ever had Japanese
omurai Zoo before yeah
[Music]
I can make it for you with the sniffer
egg
we sleep
you're 68. I mean you're trying to find
the sniffer egg for I don't know how
many out just for almost yeah
it's very nice
[Music]
uh
what's the is that coordinate
two four seven nine six
okay
[Music]
I wonder maybe I'm happy I should make a
house for the sniffer out of the Sakura
materials oh yeah maybe I think visually
it doesn't really match so well but I
mean what did I get all those Sakura
materials for
I said I would build something with it
so
stream dead
or YouTube dead
Cali might love some oh the Sakura stuff
yeah I can I can give
yeah maybe I find her I'll find her
actual current home and then I'll Place
uh a sakura tree right at her house
I see there's some fighting going on
there wow yeah diet and Golem is like
protecting the village so well the egg
is safe
let's go
wait there is a flying bat here
oh yeah I put that here before
[Music]
hi I should give you back your helmet
yeah yeah
she'll love that in three months when
she sees it but recently hasn't cut uh
Kelly been playing Minecraft a bit more
often here
thank you it was very helpful
and then we can go back together
yeah let's go
[Music]
because I hope I hope I will not be
coming back here
so soon
what if I want to I have my eyes Road
ready anytime
yeah it's close by yeah it feels like
very close thank you for helping me
build the ice
thank you for inviting me I'm happy
maybe next time I play Minecraft again
at the weird hour I will ask you again
24 7.
thank you thank you so much for giving
me a chance to talk with what I missing
pie too
welcome it's it's currently in my my
profession to help
the members communicate with Japanese
members happy
I hope my never ride will find a good
place with you you're gonna make more
use of it than me
thank you professional wing woman
be like professional wing woman at your
service
that's one service holder Tony provides
professional wing woman
you know wingman
yeah I'm your wing woman oh he wouldn't
because
it was your second ocean ride so I can
help you with mikotu too I'm helping Ami
also with me coaching
not the only one
it's really great to have someone you
know that well you're extroverted right
you're extrovert right 100 yes no not
not 100 really no happy I feel like
um like you don't have any energy to
like go out oh all the time but that
might be depression
um
I even have like lack of motivation to
like get out of bed or eat or take a
shower you're good you're good now now
you're good
no but it's okay
what
what I I I I I'm I'm coping I'm coping
it's okay but I would really like people
everybody thinks I'm an ex I'm an expert
which way
I don't know but you're you're
controlling now yep everybody thinks I'm
an extrovert but I don't know I I
actually like when I am in a situation
with people the only reason why I'm so
open is because I hate awkward
situations more than anything so I just
always try to fill in the gaps with
conversation you know and communication
but in reality I I crave silence and uh
to be alone
like I that's why I always want to stay
in hotels alone not not share a room
ideally
um and I I like to travel alone too but
with traveling alone I I I'm a little
bit worried that some some nobody can
put sunscreen on my back
and okay it gets a little bit boring
traveling alone maybe maybe it's better
to travel with someone
um but only one person and then and then
I wish when we spent like four nights or
something somewhere or outside of my
country then I wish we could have
separate rooms because at least at night
I I like to have ah silence you know
it's it like extroverted by situation
and conditioned and if you say it like
that like well I don't know people can
say if they want to say they can say I'm
an extrovert but for me like it's not
the situation it's just I adapt to I see
yeah yeah situation when when because I
just don't want the other person to feel
awkward or weird so I try to make it
more comfortable for them
yeah yeah
got it wait if I hatch the egg
uh does it just walk somewhere or is it
automatically mine can I is it safe or
should I I should probably put it in the
fence or
I think you need to put it like in your
house no because it's gonna walk around
can you put it on a leash
yeah
um
it's kind of big
[Music]
build a farm for it yeah because I want
it to farm some area maybe I can put it
inside Phoenix
because Phoenix in his fence
I don't know it's it's kind of big
though yeah
big
and but how do you transport one can you
put it on a leash yeah please no boat
okay
so maybe I hatch it first here outside
and then I take it somewhere with a
leash when it's hatched but I make a
fence
first
can it go over
double blocks probably not just one
blocks maybe like like this
I wonder because the camel camels can go
up two blocks and even over fences and
everything oh really yeah
also because they have long legs
oh
so we cannot put French
on them no no for for sniffers it's fun
I think oh yeah if somebody said in the
chat and I think this makes sense
introvert doesn't mean uh that you're
shy necessary and thus extrovert doesn't
necessarily mean that you're yeah true
true I don't know
I think it's just like
the energy that you got when you are
like
alone or maybe with others like in
groups it's about like when
the time you recharge your energy
because I feel like whenever I'm in
group it feels like
my energy just
god well you know what the good thing is
that probably pretty much all of the
whole life members except Bales and only
are like that so you don't have to feel
bad about it actually only Santa is also
very introvert actually really okay yeah
you think she loses energy sometimes
like in terms of interacting okay then I
think bales
I can tell you who is extroverted
yeah
but you know like this is the only one
in ID though with Bales it's like uh
when was this we did some yeah we went
to dinner with this big group
and then you know in situations like
this she will afterwards be like I don't
want to go home yet I'm I'm lonely I'm
samishi and then she will make the other
people stay and go to karaoke or
wherever with her she wants to spend as
much time as possible with everyone she
gets lonely very easily
but sometimes I really appreciate you
have friends like that too even though
like Yeah because sometimes I feel like
yeah maybe it's a good time to like you
know go out too but well yeah
in Japan
I try to fill every day with meetings
and collabs because I want the stay to
be meaningful and not a waste of time
yeah but if I if I live in Japan then I
will not fail every day with meetings or
collaborations yeah don't forget name
tag I can name the egg too you're not
planning to put like doors eat not yet
not yet okay it's so slow anyway it
won't Escape
so slow it's a slow boy
yeah I I don't know did Bae ever say
she's not an extrovert because I I would
say she is like I think out of whole
life English she's the most extrovert
which is not a bad thing
that is the only one zeta also
say to the her viewers that yes
I think you know about that no no
yeah but but actually cool but actually
cool myself
I met her now several times and from
what I how I see her she seems maybe a
little bit shy towards some people
sometimes in the beginning when she
first meets someone she's shy but then
she's very extroverted to me
like one on one
um
I mean
yeah yeah but no like for example I let
her meet uh Callie together I brought
her to Cali
and you know she's always so loud and
active
oh no he's happy first yeah maybe but
but what I know and she took the test
it's showing introvert yeah so maybe
she's just in the middle I don't know
wait how do you do this again what
no she she definitely told me and Zeta
that she's actually introvert not not
because like right now because we're
like close already I mean Kobo also like
very talkative right now but yeah I mean
uh she took the test and she got
introvert so yeah
yeah yeah you guys should understand why
I'm calling the sniffer that name
okay
well I can't name it already can I
no I can't well you don't have to wait
with me Kyle I'm just waiting for this
thing to happen
yeah it's okay
I'll be just standing here
wait was it 10 minutes without the Moss
or with the Moss maybe I have a mask
will slipping gonna be like speed up the
process no no
no
the only thing that speeds it up is a
block of moss
wait uh there's not gonna be a creeper
here right if I stand here
um maybe there will it's safe right no
what okay fine I should sit on it for
immersion
you want me to hatch it for real
I'm looking for oh
I got most blocks
let me get the most Bluff
[Music]
and then underneath I can't read
um
is this better now
I will sit on it too oh sure I'll take a
photo of this uh huh oh [\h__\h] I'm so
ah shaders I should turn on my shaders
for pretty photos
soon I think tomorrow tomorrow I'm
building the new pc with all my new
things yeah
and then I don't I don't think I'm
playing any games anytime soon that will
actually you know show
the
specs yeah the not like the what it can
do
oh well
yeah looking cute ah do you want to come
inside and stand next to me on on the
sand block
yes
oh
cute picture
when I try less oh
oh look up
oh cute look at us
oh wait wait
um
maybe like this
hi
wow cute beautiful
uh to your record yes wow
wow it's too close
oh no
no oh no no no no
something happened though it's cracks oh
my God am I too heavy oh [\h__\h] I'm so
confused
uh
oh
my baby
let's go
come on Google
I believe in you you can do it come on
how long does it take when it uh cracks
once
I don't know another 10 minutes no
hopefully not
done
[Music]
I'll go out first before I cannot go out
when when will the
when will the sniffer and go ahead when
will the sniffer and go edge when will
the sniffer ever hatch I want to name it
well
it will find me plenty new things it
will find me plenty new things it will
find me plenty new things
such as some new flowers
okay it really takes a lot of time
20 minutes in total probably
20 minutes without the Moss block I
think and half the time with the Moss
block maybe or or was it 10 minutes and
then five minutes or so
but is it really 10 minutes before
before the crack at 10 minutes with moss
in total oh 10 minutes with the ice
and now it's on the Moss block so
soon TM
M it's almost 10 p.m over here
oh my God I can't believe tomorrow
later for the show because oh yeah I'll
never stream tomorrow guys what should
we do for members kind of what do you do
always for member streams
well
if you
if you ask them probably they will tell
you that I'm just scamming in my
membership stream but yeah
a lot of uh stories yeah yeah oh we do
love free talk free talk ah okay okay
yeah that's a lie what a lie I I guess
you you like a lot of members what they
do for their water for their member
streams is watch alongs alone yeah I
know right but and you don't do that no
no yeah yeah a lot of options are gone
for you
I've done like just once yeah once did
you follow me
um
almost
more and more one more one more
now go ahead
were you saying something
no no no no no yeah almost that but
before before that watch along right
before that watch along I prepared for
like I don't know I prepare for
a lot of sleep beforehand
oh and still almost
fall asleep I was like yeah yeah so much
oh my God
well I do a mix of games and some games
I play solo some games I play with the
viewers and then I sometimes
uh do some hand cam streams even
remembers and watch a long movie watch
Longs but I I think I never do like so
just talking strands uh I have I I I
have a talking stream
with membership no I'm sure they
appreciate that
I hope
I I have done it yeah once or twice and
also art stream yeah once or twice
um I need Ella's live stream they really
want me to sleep in this on the stream I
think for you like they would just be
happy that you're doing something good
for yourself you know yeah I got it I
got it
and and you know if you would do a
stream where like you just laugh out
loud
they would also probably love to hear
that just explain why you laugh out loud
I can laugh right now
wait ah it's almost 3 am right yeah but
no please are you okay Kyla
yeah
you scare me
[Laughter]
but honestly when I when I met you in
real life it didn't feel like you were
not laughing I feel like no because
because that's what I um okay that's
what I I think
I kind of forget but actually I
talk about this silent love thingy with
my fears when I mean whenever we meet
right we when I meet someone I mean the
visual is there right so when there's
something funny we just laugh yeah no
one no one is like focusing about hey
you got no sound in your love like
something like that you know because
it's there exactly but when yeah but
when we are streaming right it's gonna
be like why suddenly silent and then why
why you are not something like that
right so it's like very obvious and like
yeah and people start to ask but
whenever we meet someone like and it's
something funny we just laugh right so
we do really yeah we don't really look
at like oh this girl is like got no
sound and blah blah blah so yeah
hmm because official is there we know
like at least we know
who was the first thing inside it was
the first thing that's very cute
it's so hairy oh my God it's got a bit I
think it's gonna go bigger than that I
think
it's already sniffing I think but the
area is too small it's like let me sniff
more I want to sniff more
cute he's so cute
can I jump on it and then after no it
looks like I could
come to the world
oh my God
it's so cute we should take a picture
together
I'm always pressing the wrong buttons
it's so confusing here there you go
um
when I go closer again maybe
is there any like sniffers in the real
life though no no no no no this is
completely made up oh yeah okay okay
um one on one side I
um
sniffer chance
look at the camera
look look here
you're not giving the sniffers like name
tag I already gave it
oh Kyle can you go one step to the side
no yes yes
[Music]
it's really hard to think yeah
again maybe
um
it's so cute
come on look to the front yes yes um
um
it's sniffing my crotch
[Laughter]
don't don't that's embarrassing that's
why I don't like doggos
[Music]
know how to go out
um well oh well well well well
I was thinking just just quickly place a
block and hope he doesn't follow us
okay
oh okay I guess that works
that's really weird
that's really
hey we're dead end I'm happy I wonder
how long it takes until it grows up into
a big sniffer
it looks so weird where are the eyes
here
oh
somehow these things look like the eyes
it looks like a Pac-Man it does look
like Pac-Man from the front
oh
no no it doesn't want to show its face
oh my God it's Pac-Man nah 40 minutes
I want to see when it happens but
you put the double door oh it's going
you're not awake no we can safely go
inside yeah smart
yeah
the floppy ears oh it's like a like a
dog that hasn't been like brushed or
shaved in years because the the fur
looks like so
what's the word so
um
what is it
Shaggy method yeah it looks so matte but
I guess it's probably like supposed to
be more like leaves
I guess
okay
I think we can say goodbye and then read
super chats yeah
I will go back to the new server thank
you so much thank you too for everything
for helping with everything you're the
best
thank you thank you for inspiring me
I will talk to you again for another
Minecraft adventure
it's fun thank you
goodbye
adios Amiga
[Music]
oh it's crying don't cry
it's crying because it's in the rain oh
no
I need to go to the shelter soon with
with um flower flowers and everything
a big shelter I'll make it a big shout
out where it can always sniff if it
sniffed something
um I know for a while it can't sniff
that again but does it ever refresh
so it can sniff the same thing again
yeah okay like the frost yeah
I mean not at the same Bridge because it
will be annoying to get it up there
maybe
the last 10 I think it was 20. in the
video it said 20 blocks
okay so we just need to make a Terrain
that's like big enough maybe maybe the
size of like
half of this house or like uh two-thirds
of this house
is enough
you know but a little bit more than 20
blocks so just that it can move around
and sniff whatever block it once
and we'll make it look nice with Sakura
um
so next stream will be what whatama
Senpai did today
house building cover Google is is fine
now we'll do it another time
and
okay I'll do it
oh it's crying crying
oh okay I'm on it I'm on it I'm on it
I'm on it oh don't cry huh
oh my God it makes really cute sounds
actually
it sounds like somebody is having
stomach problems
bowel movements
go like I'm really hungry stomach
honestly I can relate because with the
energy drink I upset my stomach once
again and I already I had big tummy hurt
last night that lasted for the night and
partially today was weird really weird I
don't know where it came from
but I'm okay now
it's over two blocks to the entire room
higher than this
yeah yeah
okay
[Music]
what's going on
oh
yeah make him a proper Mansion yeah next
time next time
today we already wasted so much time
to find this little boy
alone just picking up the blocks
nice nice store system
somehow I never thought about doing that
with doors
um
ah
so I still don't know what to do for
members tomorrow
um
[Music]
I don't want to do another watch along
because I think the last one wasn't long
what should we do
I don't want to play tepic anymore I
think I'm done with Epic
genuinely
after last time
I think I'm actually just gonna leave it
behind
[Music]
yeah it triggered me
okay now it's got a roof
it won't get rained on anymore
or actually I could get rid of this
house once and for all and use the space
repurpose the space
for guba
and then move
my storage maybe on the ground
and also back into this house
um
because I mean I I think one of the
things I don't like is that it's two
stories and it's annoying to always go
up
but if I get rid of the actual old house
then I won't re resort to always using
it anymore
but it's kind of yeah it's kind of
historical isn't it it's got this
nostalgia
value to it yeah I agree
well this one too though
hmm
yeah okay we'll move it somewhere close
by and maybe up there
I'm hungry maybe it's time for another
salami
but we're gonna Read Super chats now
guys
oh
if you run rails we'll hop them one card
under the sniff up
um
oh maybe we can do that
basically a sniff upon but I mean
I don't need millions of those flowers
um
I'm fine with a with a couple
or do more
[Music]
I guess in the beginning when I want the
couple it takes too long
hmm
okay
I'll think about it did you make the pot
yet no
I mean don't you need four no I guess
just one four shards for one plot and it
can be different shards
well where did I put all the other
shards
in my Ender Chest
let me just put this here for now
[Music]
good stuff we were uh somewhat
productive we finished the ice Road I
just need to put some signs there
uh
so that people know
what goes where
[Music]
um
yeah and I'll wait
hold them
fancy stuff is in these
chocolate boxes
[Music]
mmm
oh yeah so we got a couple of Border
Pottery shards the member and the [\h__\h]
ton of these
cherry blossom stuff but we can get more
if we want to
oh more shards
um
I I actually I didn't care so much about
the shards uh
I actually was more happy about the fact
that you could make a big pot
with the brakes in the first place
um
because I had so many bricks and like
previously yeah I asked you when you
were doing with these bricks and you
guys said you can make them the floor
but
now
you can make big
but can you also put a flower in the big
pot too
um
yeah these are new need to put small
plants from oh you can do that okay wait
a second
um
that's so cool it's like a standing big
ass standing vase
um
hi baby
[Music]
how about Orange tulip
so basically this thing that I just made
you can make with the patterns on the
side
well I'm happy with just a plain one
wait maybe it kind of looks lame now
because the flowers so small it doesn't
look like it's making use of the big pot
um
you can put cherry tree sapling in
really
wait into the big pot or
all right let me get one
any sapling but Cherry looks best
[Music]
oh
how do you take one again
um ah like this wait
no wait how
I thought it was middle
ah
just one
ah well
um
ah like this okay
let's try this out
doesn't work like this no
okay so it does need the flower pot
but oh
yeah okay that looks amazing
oh
um
it looks so good
wow
cute
it's glowing because of the Shader
so nice
[Music]
nope um
I am
satisfied with that
very satisfied mm-hmm
[Music]
gray things go in here
when your sniff a grows up the flowers
it finds are big oh really like now it
finds only small things
I went
yeah
oh we have snort
angler shelter and plenty I don't know
what this means
how does that relate to what's on on in
front of on top of it
snored what the [\h__\h]
have you grown up yet
do I need to water you like a plant
because you do look like a plant
it sounds like he's suffering like his
whole existence is suffering he's like
why the [\h__\h] did you hatch me I'm an
ancient egg just let me Slumber me
living in this world is not meant to be
you know lady
it's just not meant to be
I'm suffering
what's up
I thought now that it's gonna grow up
even if it's just for the meantime I
want to give it a bit more space so
okay
oh baby
do you want some flowers to sniff here
hey
he's got such a big snood
coupon the sniffer yeah I mean she was
the one
eh
right didn't she answer ah didn't she
answer sniffing sniff
yeah or what can you do with an armpit
she had it coming let's be real
okay guys
I will read superchato oh wait
Nina is sending me
like you know her dates when she's
coming and like a restaurant she wants
to go to
um
Nina
oh man
when what did I tell you guys when my
new outfit would be revealed like middle
of middle of July or end of July what
did I say
Late July okay okay good I mean the
thing is it's it's ready but
um oh it's been ready for a couple days
now
I'll be honest but
I'm I I have to wait because
I'm I'm
kind of on
um wait waiting time for uh you know
those those like Graphics that always
uh come with the new outfits like to
announce new outfit
um
like apparently there's too much going
on so it takes longer than usual to make
the graphic
so now it looks like I will just
commission someone for I don't have to
pay for it but it looks like I have to
commission some non in-house person yeah
that's all we're waiting on
I mean I did request some small fixes
um but basically I'm waiting for the
crap
bye
you know hopefully actually if we if
we've asked someone external
it'll be faster than expected
is the graphing important kind of I
guess yeah I mean I would like to have
one I don't want to just make one by
myself because ah Brad graphic design
isn't my calling it may be my passion
but it's not my calling I always feel
very
um anxious when I when there's like
bigger important streams and I have to
make the thumbnail for it
I always feel like um I wanted to look
more special but it looks like [\h__\h]
so at least for in this occasion where
there's always professionally made
Graphics I would like to have a
professional make it
um
basement are you talking about my dandel
or what the reference to my dental
yeah they are there there must be like a
lot of new outfits
um being released right now I mean you
see it I think there's like a lot of new
outfits
ready to be released at the moment or or
recently released um
well
I guess and that's probably not the only
thing they do whoever's in charge of it
the team surely that's not the only
thing they're working on they probably
also make thumbnails for the official
Channel who knows and graphics for
whatever yeah they probably have a lot
of things yeah coyote is coming up
um
they're they're just the graphics
Department who work on many things at
once so I understand I understand it's
okay uh I just find it funny that that's
why we have to wait for my outfit it
seems like so unrelated
um
yeah
it's silly right
so I think for the first time in whole
life history
we not only me others maybe too I've
been told have to commission externally
I got I heard back from accents
um
about the pricing and everything
and I thought it would be like a
one-time 20K payment
but it's more like
um
[Music]
let me check again
like for what I need
I I asked kanodu which one he has
because apparently there is one two
three three different versions
um
and it seems like I can actually just go
with the cheapest one
the cheapest suit is
on one girl apparently four thousand two
hundred thirty Euro
the cheapest like motion capture
accents it's not a suit I think those
are the straps yeah
but that one works apparently and then
combine it with the meta gloves that are
6 000 Euro
the gloves are more expensive than the
whole body trick
gloves you know it's it's a thing with
motion capture gloves tend to be very
expensive for every motion capture
solution
so six thousand plus four thousand two
hundred which is already over a 10K 10
200 euro
and then we need software
and there's one that I need for
streaming
which is either 2500 per year
or 250 per month every month cancelable
and I don't think I'll be doing a stream
every
month and a whole year so I think I'll
just go for the monthly plan first
so 250 per month where I want to use it
for the streaming part and then for
other things
I think I need this too there's one
there's one software that I have which
is like the pro version which is
10 000 per year and there is no monthly
subscription you have to pay per year 10
000 per year
and the cheaper one which kanado told me
I only need the cheaper one
is three thousand
per year
so basically we we come down to uh it
was 10 250 plus three thousand so
thirteen thousand two hundred fifty
at 230. 14 230 plus if I want to stream
in that month it will be a number 250.
so
like fourteen thousand
but thirteen thousand around thirteen
thousand euro is like
um
for one year
so we can split it per month I guess
13 000 for a year of having this suit
with the software
and for every month I want to use it for
streaming and not for like YouTube
shorts or MV or whatever
we add a number 250.
about 1K a month right yeah it's like 1K
per month
now I can also write this off but I
don't know how much of this
could be written off how much of it is
taxes
but yeah if you calculated like that I
guess it's about roughly a little bit
more than you know 1.3 k a month hmm
hmm
[Music]
I
I think it's okay
[Music]
yeah no it's it's actually I think my my
tax lady will appreciate it if I have
more expenses she told me anyway like to
invest
at least so in so many thousand Euros
ideally
and I'm like I will never under normal
circumstances have this much expenses
this doesn't get me there and either but
uh I don't know
hmm
right off your new PC parts oh yeah I
will I will why are you buying this
yourself no I'm buying it
you know
mostly because I want to film for second
MV because I asked uh
yeah
there's no space in the studio to record
some motion for 15 minutes for pretty
much the whole summer
so now they're like offering me to ask
external Studios and I'm waiting to hear
back for how much it costs at external
Studios
and if it's not too expensive then I
might just use the external Studio but
this would give me the the freedom to
use it whenever I want you know at home
and I can do many projects
so I feel like yeah it might actually
pay off like in I I won't be held back
you know
I can do a lot of YouTube shorts I can
do tick tocks I can I can stream in 3D I
can you know
I can do 3D mvs
um I could do my own motion whenever I
want
no
the the most expensive like motion
capture suit that they have that's not
the velcro straps
you know the one we're looking at is 4
200 but they have one that's
this suit is 1000 but the system that
you need for is is for it is 13 000.
Euro
that's the best thing they have but
kanado said I don't need that
I trust Canada because he has a lot of
experience with it
um
and I think uh
wait I don't really watch code Miko I'm
trying to remember is she wearing the
whole suit when she does this
I feel like I only saw her wearing
straps
but code Mikko doesn't do like dancing
and stuff right so it's not so important
for her to have better quality
but Canada does dancing and for me I
look at his stuff and I think it looks
plenty good
um
oh she has the whole suit
oh okay okay
oh
this stuff looks excellent right you
know
so judging by that I think it's okay to
just get the the minimum and maybe maybe
the honestly I feel like if I spend so
much money they would probably be open
to you know after I tested if I feel
like this is not good enough
I'll either return it or get an upgraded
version if I really want to
I can't imagine them not letting me
return it
within a month or so if I don't
like it
um
no yeah I'll ask of course but
honestly with that amount of money
ah 1.3
per month huh
no
and I mean
when I'm done using it I can sell it
I guess
um
to another
upcoming YouTuber or so
maybe you can get a discount for
advertising
I'll ask
I will ask
oh yeah also like uh I asked how far how
fast it would arrive
and once you pay it arrives really fast
so
time wise it's not an issue
no I'm not gonna like ask to get it for
free but I mean oh there's cone would be
nice oh
[Music]
yeah I still have to think about it I'm
not 100 sure yet but I yeah
ah
yeah it would be cool to
have better home Freddy you know than
like the mocobee stuff
um
no
go with your heart
I'm not sure my heart is sending me
mixed signals
it just makes sense
yeah
yeah I'm gonna take my time I I first of
all I'm still waiting on the pricing for
external Studios which
um
I don't think I'm
allowed to disclose that so please stop
me if I'm about to disclose
such pricings
be like shut up shut up shut up right
now
shut up
um
last year didn't you say external screws
in Europe yeah yeah Europe yes we're
talking about Japanese Studios because
like basically I guess
like my my staff offered me
for the time where I am in Japan coming
soon uh to look for availability
in the studio in Japan during that time
but
honestly
at this point I don't know if I can make
it because the choreo is not done 100
yeah
and we could rush it like crazy but I'm
still having it being polished
and
I don't want to like force it to be
finished immediately
um just to also I need time to learn it
it's really difficult again it's really
difficult
it takes time to learn and I don't have
that time I have to stream I have to
travel and so honestly at this point I'm
I don't care
I mean I do but I don't
because trying to record it next week
would stress me the [\h__\h] out mm-hmm
yeah I need a bit more time to learn it
so ideally if I get the suit
then
um maybe I can record with an August
comfortably
yeah
learn learn the choreo in the first week
of August and then record middle of
August or so
so I want to help you setting up the
system
pretty much to set up I I
I've like it's velcro straps and you
know Wireless
sensors there
compared to the other stuff that I've
tried it can't be that difficult it's
surely also tutorials and you know I
don't think it's as complicated as
like camera setups new
it doesn't have cameras it's just the
straps basically what you need to learn
the software
I I think there's tutorials for that too
yeah
we'll surely not break my brain I've got
the other Home 3D to work before too
so this one I will make it work to
um
wait before I start reading super chats
let me check one more time if if my guba
has grown
you know still small
right
same size I think
oh
actually in the video that I watched
they said
um
dads there was a baby size but they
patched it out and now it just
immediately the size it should be so I
expected no baby size but is this the
baby baby size
or was there an even baby your size
before
small small Koopa house small small
grouper house
why small
this is baby
okay then I guess they didn't patch it
out or they patched it out and people
were like no
no whose eyes and then they brought it
back
I can't imagine that like that was my
reaction when I heard they patched it
out I'm like no
oh why would you do that why would you
take it away keep it small
you can see the big one at Louie's house
I have no freaking idea where Louie's
house is
it's okay we'll see it eventually
I think a few minutes are left okay I'll
attach it a bit more than
I guess
yeah yeah
[Music]
when are you going to renovate the
chicken you mean the coop
why it doesn't need renovating how the
chickens in there by the way I haven't
talked to them in a long time
he's doing
you're doing well
nice that's the usual room
is there eggs down here no
I guess this is broken
still is it broken
I don't know
I don't need eggs
I have you guys
that's enough eggs
small small guba
yeah maybe the it's just a minecart
that's stuck and if you move it it will
collect eggs again
thanks I thought you guys stopped it
from working because often oh yeah
probably
um super jump reading today yes
finally came back to us there's been
over a year have we been what why we
finally came back to us
ah it's hacking from the point of view
of them I was like what do you mean
did you come back to me
[Laughter]
oh I'm so sorry I didn't say hi for such
a long time but I always think of you
guys yes yes yes yes
would you put you
don't worry I got you you're safe in
there no one will harm you
except maybe the sniffer who knows maybe
you just never got a taste for chinking
I love them I love all my chickens
equally
even those over there
schnoofa
new version
five hours late we're ending two
actually I'm just waiting kind of for
this thing to grow up
oh
you know what's really cute I have many
tools for my cat's fur one of the tools
is like a a glove
a blue glove where the front
uh that you pet the cat with is
plastic and it has like Nubs
guys
yeah maybe you can imagine what it is
like what maybe you've seen it before
and like
advertisements or so online
yeah those are pretty good you pet the
cat and the Nubs on the plastic part
they kind of just make the
the really light first stick I feel like
it really only gets like the light fur
which is fine
um but yeah you just brush over the cat
and smoothie does not really like it but
smoothie generally doesn't like to be
jet gigantic
what the
holy [\h__\h]
huge
The Sounds changed too I think it's
gotten like a like a sucking vacuum
sniffer
oh
he's like a Rambo tooling
um break in castle walls
no it doesn't get any bigger than this
no no no it shouldn't pretty sure this
is it
damn damn girl
you're bigger than than the real Gooba
yeah I wanted to say the the glove yeah
this movie doesn't really like to be
here
groomed in any way generally
um but her fur usually never gets
Tangled so that's okay but I need to get
rid of all the like leftover fur you
know sometimes I have to force her and
and Chunky Monkey she's happy she likes
being brushed she likes being petted by
the glove she likes all of it and so
I've noticed
when I'm like somewhere in a different
room and I take out the glove uh like
the glove on its own makes no sound
unless you open the velcro because it
closes with a velcro around your wrist
so I opened the velcro and it could be
any velcro right but chunky monkey comes
running over
screaming like meow meow
it's really excited and flops down right
in front of me
it's about being brushed and then I
brush her and she's like purring and
purring and purring she wants to be
brushed forever even after I brush her
for like 30 minutes
she still wants to be brushed more it's
so cute and it's so good because she
needs to be brushed anyway like her for
gets Tangled easily
yeah it's so freaking cute I need to
record it at some time when I when I'm
ready yeah it's so cute
you don't take cats to a groomer
normally like
honestly
I I don't really understand people who
take cats too professional groomers I
mean if you want them to have some fancy
haircut for whatever reason
okay but normally
people don't really do that
hmm
maybe if you want to shave them for the
summer and give them some kind of lion
mane or so
but yeah I don't know
that's just I'm so unnecessary you don't
need to crush
brush or cut or you need to brush but
you don't need to cut or shave or
anything I think the only thing that
might be useful is for like really
really really
um
really oh
oh
thank you
that's your pod is that what I need
wow
um uh uh what was I saying oh yeah if
your cat has like crazy long fur
especially on on the butt chunkers had
this problem sometimes that almost she
hasn't had this problem in a long time
but sometimes she wouldn't have like
um kind of like a messy Toilet Time
and um
yeah uh her fur on her butt would get
really messy so I think it helps to
maybe shave
that part around there
mm-hmm
but besides that
I also don't cut my my cat's
Nails because they just use the
the scratch scratch
thingies and that's fine you know
no no
no
um I'm stalling let's go to my other uh
screen song
[Music]
where do we go we haven't been in the
office for a while for a long time
should we go to my office
[Music]
I'll take off my
my helmet and my sword
oh I wanted to say one thing in case are
there any like creators who like to make
tools or like you know fan art or
whatever
um it is now possible I want to make a
post about this too so that people more
people see it
um but it's not possible
oh
to uh we can attach not only like pngs
but yeah gifts
to us
but ideally if you guys make something
ideally please already send it uh maybe
on the Google drive or whatever uh
transparent
because like making it transparent on
our own I don't even know how to do that
there's no like
color uh key key filter
function for us for that so it has to
already be
uh yeah they can be transparent yeah
yeah like
um from my experience like I got some
transparent
um GIFs from
for example
I don't know how you make it but it's
possible um
yeah so you know what that was being
nice for I don't know maybe for like
a cute hat decoration or I don't know I
don't know
right now I can't think of anything but
sometimes I think of
things and I'm like oh I wish I wish we
could have ah like controller hands
controller hands
because I think
did I ever have animated animated
controller hands or only or like moving
arms you know like some of my assets
um
let me see
or like these ones
whoa wait this is transparent gift
now I should be able
now I just place it on OBS but now I
should be able to put it on my body
because before I could only
put like a PNG on me
let me try this so
and I can put the you know the the one
where I pet kotoni
I can put that one on myself directly
now too
so let's see
[Music]
um
hands
oh
that's the wrong one
[\h__\h] home
eh why is that
where is it
oh oh wait it might be because oh wait I
think I know why
I think the app version I'm using right
now is outdated
I need to get the new version
and then I can do the gifts but yeah
that will work
um so you know so please if you want to
make some assets like you know let me
give you some ideas so you know as we
said this one
what is this
um I might not want to show that one but
this one
stuff like this and
and this is not transparent but if it
were
I could put this attach it to me
directly
and then you know these hands
I don't have the transparent either I
think
floating out
and then
this one I can attach to my head so that
it moves with me I might actually do
that a lot yeah
foreign
[Music]
I wonder what else I have already
I feel like I had more juice
oh I guess I don't have many gifs saved
because I thought oh I can't use it
anyway
I think dakuma made a new one yeah the
one with holding the chicken that one is
so cute I want to use it
um
yeah cool stuff definitely
I'll make a post about it
like an example post fubuki always posts
those things and I think it uh gives it
visibility for creators
I'm excited
oh you know what I could also do like I
mean I already have twitching cat ears
but you could make twitching cat ears
for example
twitching cat ears or
or
um
but hands are just generally genius
oh Phoenix wings yeah moving moving
Wings whoo
or you could you could make a smoking
cigarette
oh
you know Black Box shooter the fire
we could make a similar version maybe in
my color a flame that moves a little bit
and I put it on top of my eye
and if I would get in trouble for that
though
or Super Saiyan Aura yeah for my whole
body
[Music]
machine gun yeah you could make a
machine gun hand that goes
I don't know how long GIF animations can
be
but that's probably like a
a certain like quality limit to it as
well I don't know
size are your size restricted I mean not
for us
it can be like high and B can be 5gb it
doesn't matter I don't think so
[Music]
um
yeah yeah I like you you can also do
something for the back like wings
because we can put it behind us we can
put it behind us and in front of us and
then if it's in front of us we have like
choices of different like parts for
example if I put it on my head I can
attach it to my bangs or I can attach it
to the base of my head
Etc depending on where I place it it
will like recognize more different
placements or like attachments to latch
onto
um
yeah yeah
so
that's how I was able to
differentiate between you know for the
hoodie the hood for uh
my tltk streams
depending on where I lasted onto
sometimes it would wobble way too much
or it would stay relatively in place and
move with my head not with my bangs or
so technology
I feel like this kind of Technology uh
Indie V tubers have had for
years now
but for us it's so new and so fresh and
so exciting you know it's revolutionary
yeah I've seen gifs on in dbtubers for a
long time
ah
[Music]
ensive
yeah yeah but it's cool like we're
getting more and more features I was
really happy about the the screen color
adjustment feature but I I hope they can
implement it for life to D2 because
right now it only works on 3D
and now we have the hands for 3D and I
noticed like depending on how
um
High the usage of the CPU of my phone is
the more laggy will the hands be but if
I when I use it today where the usage
was low
um it moved very smoothly
so that's the where it comes from the
lagginess
um
mitupa hands
I I didn't use it I just like saw it
when I turned on my PC and my phone I'm
like oh it moves so so smoothly
hmm
yeah
[Music]
oh by the way today in Korean lesson I
learned past tense
it's still very confusing to me
I think I need some time
to
get it in my hand
for example
to go
is kada going is Kyle or kamnida
um both are kind of polite
but if we have the yo form Kyle then we
can create the past tense with that kind
of
I think it was cut cut
s got this got shot
I don't [\h__\h] know
past tense got that's good got ah
soyo
um
audio
I don't know
like there's this
soil and
foreign maybe depending on what the
vowel is in the word
I think
um
brain horde
cut
um
cut soil
I got soil
wait yeah it's just that maybe
I guess the other one is a different
word
[Music]
um
I need some time but my the thing is my
next lesson is
not on the usual day next week because
I'll be in Japan so next lesson is soon
I have to understand it until next
lesson ideally I only have like two
lessons left jumping
big sleepy you should have drunken my
energy drink I still have so much left
over
uh okay let's let's read though
I feel like the energy drink kind of
hurts my throat I haven't I haven't been
drinking it it's like I took in total
maybe five or six sips tiny sips
and as you're drinking water most of the
time
[Music]
okay
by whom am I meant to be devoured of
course
um
situation
Pence
sometimes I am very hungry then you must
sacrifice yourself but I also need you
guys for customers
um
they could never sip that first tension
was what you mean the first tangent of
today or which which tangent
we're gonna read the projects for the
Birthday Countdown or for the waiting
yeah Birthday Countdown I think
what what was my was my um
my friends story
too much for you guys
it's just
I don't understand people's reactions
honestly
I think you guys are a little bit
exaggerating honestly
it was a lovely story Ryan
it's just you know
real life struggles you know
um
that was just another first aid in a
table discussion right there you go see
you are you are like
um sensitized or so
Justin thank you so much
oh
I made it one no it doesn't matter what
you guys made it weird
okay guys I'm gonna open up the screen
again so you guys can see what's going
on
um
mm-hmm
wow that's so big
come on girls
okay
I'll cut it like here
your eyes what do you mean
is it too bright well I don't think
there's dark mode on hololizer
uh yeah deal with it
wait I mean
I can maybe make it darker for you
guys are so obsessed with dark mode
it's unreal
uh
foreign
thank you you're welcome
maybe if you're in a dark room watching
my stream it might be yeah painful
I don't have to look at it
it's better okay
master
okay let's go yes I aim to please
is the music
too quiet or too loud or too annoying I
can change it actually I want to change
it because I got um attracted I wanted
to try
it open up
[Music]
oh
that's it that's exactly it no
this one's so cute it's not exactly in
my opinion Super Chat music I think is
more like chit chat music but wait you
don't hear it yet I know I know I know
hey
there you go
it's it's kind of cute
it's just piano
um
we might get sick of it soon but for now
we listen to this yeah Flora Inda or
Korean tea kin tip ah this is home of
chickenia because chip is home or house
thank you happy birthday attention face
on the pinky of Flora in that tip that
profile picture
I wonder if I've seen it before
that's me and my Sparks outfit maybe and
Elena I think
looks cute reminds me of Lily Allen
write some parts of this yeah
oh are you not the only one who thinks
so
it's from Apple yeah I recognize the
style even when it's this small
but I wonder if I've seen it before
might have been a while thank you happy
birthday to you too
thank you thank you for one two three
four four five six six pinkies wow
okay here we go
the Casper yeah
it's a whole house I know
um is it really that expensive I know I
won't get termites in my walls
surely
[Music]
um
oh where did they go oh wait did they go
golfing
oh my God guys I watched a little bit a
more I've been really slowly getting
into the newest season of handmaid's
tale and I have myself
the Marvel's Mrs maisel and
yeah really slowly I'm like at episode
two
really slow because I wanted to watch it
at a time where I'm not gonna fall
asleep while watching
and where I feel like actually getting
into it I started a little bit and I
realized
there's this new character who I
completely forgot but I guess he
appeared at the end of season four
but I don't think I realized this until
now
this dude character
after very close inspection
he's the same actor as Jess
E
from Gilmore Girls
but like so much more grown up
almost unrecognizable
I only recognize them because of his
voice
and then eventually the more I looked by
his eyebrows and everything but
damn he
looks
so different
and yeah Milo yeah
weirdly I feel like I think this is just
a like a styling thing
because in Gilmore Girls I feel like he
stands out so much and he definitely
looks like a main character
I don't know how to say this but in The
Marvelous this is maisel he just looks
like an unimportant character
because he's styled in a way that
like
any of the like background actors are
styled you know what I mean
so he doesn't stand out much
so weird
because I'm like why he used to have
such a big
like
important character Aura in Gilmore
Girls
[Music]
and now he just looks
hysteric
but I think it's a styling issue because
I put him in a suit and they uh like
slick back his hair with a [\h__\h] ton of
Wax
so generic so weird that's why I
couldn't recognize him
but at the same time it's kind of
interesting how different he can look so
that's cool
no I was excited because I realized holy
[\h__\h]
because the creators from The Marvelous
Mrs made a lot of the same creators from
Gilmore Girls and I just see so many
more and more characters actors that are
appearing that we're also in Gilmore
Girls
there's one another side character kind
of that works like a newspaper thing
he's not there from the first season on
but he's here now and he was also in
Gilmore Girls he was one of the love
interests from Lorelei
yeah
there's so many
dude I I think the the producer
was was also behind gamer girls she just
has this like I know these go-to actors
that she feels like she can trust
because she used them before
so she just uses the same actors again
and again
yeah but it works they they fit in
nicely
um
and now I'm like imagining a world where
the main character from Marvel's Mrs
maisel is that actress
would have been in gimmel girls
and I can see it
I could imagine her
being one of the main characters Lorelei
or Rory depending on the age also no she
would be a really good Lorelei I think
um but at that time I would say she was
too young for the role
Wes Anderson is also a director that
uses the same actors and actresses over
and over for his movies really I don't
know like who that is and what his
movies are
yeah
it's kind of I don't I get it but it's
kind of like please give other people a
chance
hmm
Tarantino too
huh
hmm
still planning on stopping at midnight
can you stay okay oh kind of we have an
hour
maybe a bit longer we we go a bit longer
anyway
um
[Music]
only attract those boys she attracts all
kinds of boys but then she is attracted
to the boys
she's attracted back at the boys who
want to mess with her relationships
[Music]
and like Sherry being overly obsessed ah
yeah you didn't include me when you were
about to marry Max
did he say that
what did he say that
um
[Music]
thank you for watching so much let's go
thank you don't be careful please don't
don't send too many super chatos okay
but I'm very very excited to read things
always gives me like a Gilmore Girls
flashback without me having to watch it
although I always like watching it hmm
thank you so much
I'm happy you're enjoying my my girly
show
but I you know honestly like I've heard
about like other men who enjoy it too so
don't get like immediately turned off by
the name or like the image it has okay I
think it's enjoyable by men too
you just have to open your heart and
your third eye
when's the next girls talk you mean we
basically had a girls talk today with me
Waterman Kaila
well I don't know we're all too busy
right now like I'm too busy I'm
traveling and all that so
I think in August maybe we can do
another one
um
it was too short it doesn't count
huh give me a break
Colin O'Brien was obsessed with gamble
girls in the day wow well there you go
really that's funny
[Music]
um
thank you sure nothing in total that's a
pinky at least thank you so much wait
one two three four five it might even be
a red one huh
[Music]
wow
and now Keith
[Music]
I love the keys
um
I know the words but I don't know how to
make the sentence let me okay
although I don't know how to say
please watch me
I'm gonna say I watched
it
uh
stroller
um
yeah yeah I can say that yeah I know how
to say is that
nice nice Korean
women
[Music]
happy birthday yo yo yo I hope your next
goals and dreams come true can you
believe it this is the first birthday
together and for me it has been an
emotional ride to be with you sorry for
not all being here all the time job and
dreams from my side keep me busy I love
you don't worry about it it's okay at
least you're still here keep me updated
that you still like me and I appreciate
that thank you for thinking of me
um
and I'm I'm happy if you're like you
know living your dream apparently
yeah
and doing your best at living life so
you gotta do what you gotta do my my
um
financial advisor made a joke that uh
would be better for me if there was
another pandemic I said you know I guess
that's right
but not only
not only no Financial but because you
guys could all just probably come back
to watch me every day again
[Music]
yeah honestly with the rising stupidity
of humanity
I'll probably get another pandemic
sooner rather than later
[Music]
somehow we're just
ignoring its existence now I don't know
I haven't heard any numbers in the in a
long time but it's not completely gone
right we just ignore it now so
but it's understandable we can't do
lockdowns for free [\h__\h] years right
that's just um
yeah
don't jinx them
if I look away it's not here exactly it
doesn't exist if I close my eyes
you have travel plans
yeah I think it's fine for a while but
you know you never know
this one was unexpected and came out of
nowhere and that can happen anytime so
it's rough but yeah
increasing in several places right now
really
hmm
but I kind of doubt that
any government except for the ones who
are like really serious about it that
immediately shut their borders
immediately like uh what was it who was
it
New Zealand Maybe
they would probably immediately close
down again if they got a new case like
sometimes we managed to get down to zero
right zero cases
Madagascar
if and then the one I heard about was
New Zealand I think yeah
yeah they were like really determined
[Music]
so I feel like they would probably close
down again no problem if it rises but
other countries I think will just ignore
it yeah
I only heard about New Zealand doing
this yeah me too and they they did it
they actually did it like it worked out
damn
and from what I heard the they also
weren't like [\h__\h] about it though
new zealanders
not gonna lie lockdown got me into Holo
uh can we do a poll
yeah I'll do one
did you
in some way
directly or indirectly get into Hollow
because of
clothing
yes no
for me
for me it's kind of also a yes I knew
about the existence before
yeah but I didn't really get into it
until the pandemic girl
oh no
anatava
[Music]
foreign
which one
I think I heard about Hulu in the past
when it was when I saw it was like a big
thing
didn't get into it until much later in
the pandemic
I mean not much later but yeah
is there Lane oh yeah that's that's
great a lot of people got into it for
the israeline oh
and once before your debut I got into
clips of home oh yeah very close
I was a trash taste people oh
someone I fall on Twitter talked about
Colonel player a lot at the start of
government then I I don't know maybe
maybe it's kind of related to put on
covet because maybe you wouldn't have
seen it otherwise or really cared about
it or and they maybe wouldn't have cared
about it either
started watching June 2021 because felt
my feet as a result of the pandemic boom
um
whole life saved my sanity one Hollywood
and Anime Studios shut down let's go
got into hell because I was stuck at
home in the random quote on the club up
here there you go see it I think there's
a lot of people that applies to
um
and I think most of the people who say
no
might be because they got into it like
recently like last year
or this year that's already kind of like
the end of the pandemic or after
or they knew it before
even before or after the pandemic yeah
[Music]
I got in because I was depressed and saw
a funny video a moment and just got me
hooked nice
I'm glad you made it here
[Music]
playing Doom so many of those
um
[Music]
animated streamers before found out
about her life after
I wasn't sure what it was but I showed
my bosses a clip of you
boss is what what kind of bosses
later on one of my bosses showed me
Corona eating my intense video then I
got recommended
what do you mean we need to learn this
like in terms of we need to learn how to
do live today
I guess because that would be useful for
I guess
your job in that case yeah
you saw an article about Guru
I saw Aspen gold once I saw an asthma
and gold clip yesterday of asthma and
gold I don't really
I just know he's a popular twitch
streamer but I saw him reacting to the
uh the what's his name d the
D DSL what's his name
yes
[Music]
the internet do something
what's done
please
tonight
that's it then right okay good yeah
um yeah I found asthma gold watching how
care did you see it
I'm not sure if it's the same clip
because I feel like they added something
to it maybe it's an edit of your clip
because I think at the end there were
some differences you saw it
um
was it completely your clip ah it was
your clip and they added something right
they gave him credit though okay good
hmm
there was I think some
some writing or so and it added
yep
oh no that was your Edition
oh okay okay I wasn't sure like if that
was if that was ruin the old Jane okay
[Music]
you got you into hold on no way really
did that actually get someone into
whole life that is surprising
ly
a membership
thank you I wonder how that reached you
don't be true thank you
hey
didn't reach the right person but good
try oh
will he get it you guys keep an eye on
it I'm gonna Read Super chats
thank you
[Music]
Patsy one uh 20 40 60. 80 100 orange
garden
it's nice how an orange carbon creates a
rental project because you get me to
read it
and happy infinity plus for your
birthday Kiana it's a little shocking to
see that it's already your first
birthday we're spending together the
time spent reviewing kfp has honestly
been some of the most enriching
experiences in my life but that is to
say it is because of you that we've all
come together
all these amazing supportive humble
loving kind and passionate people are
all here together because of you you're
amazing and I wish with all my heart
that you have the most wonderful
birthday today and every day I'll always
love and cherish you as my ocean and
support you in all your endeavors and
every one of your Phoenix lives and
thank you
keep on Shining as bright as you always
have since the day I first met you
because you inspired costumes by me to
be better person once again happy
birthday care much love
[Music]
for the sweet words
and for spending my birthday with me
once again
you are thus invited to my fourth
birthday
you got him nice let's go
congratulations welcome to the kfb club
he remembered manually no way didn't he
he did didn't he
I didn't remember manually on his own
it looks like he did it on his own
[Music]
he did it himself you guys failed
no you did not
you thought it was a bad time nice fine
I'll do it myself
[Music]
like once you guys send a certain amount
of super chats for uh memberships for a
specific person it just
it's been years to hit the action person
it's weird because it doesn't look like
there's so many
non-members in a chat
a go-getter attitude
you don't have the fingers to properly
aim oh man that's sad
more target practice Yeah
[Music]
let's go thank you for the generous
donation and you support always I'm glad
to have you around
I think you're sleeping right now but
hopefully you'll hear it afterwards mate
a name
for the pinky ah
are you awake
hello
[Music]
uh you know
not
me well I don't know this form yet
[Music]
I guess I could also say ELO
now
wait if there's oil how do I Sayo
[Music]
you know
because I guess I can just say the yield
form and then yeah add a question mark
in my head ah
[Applause]
[Music]
YouTube
every day name I'm so happy you're still
here thank you so much
yay thank you
I'm happy a male not nail man
what you say y'all
my Korean getting better
I will have to do some study streams
after I'm done with my lessons
hmm
what does it say happy birthday Ian's
first concert a new birthday this July
is a wonderful month I've been busy at
work and haven't been able to watch
stream in real time but you're here now
I'm enjoying your broadcast with an
archive I will support you Kiana
twinkle
over the table
what does it mean is it jingle
psycho oh
is it different from Diego I feel like I
heard hear Jacob
a lot
twinkle
what is this Korean I want to try rated
uh
[Music]
salad
I don't really know what that means
partially yes but
I know
but
I agree but I don't know I agree but I
don't understand
well done reading Korean let's go
[Music]
confusing me sometimes
just because it's the same leather just
uh flipped horizontally
sometimes my brain just reads it wrong
yeah but besides that hey and sometimes
I have like uncertainty for the s
if if I read it as s or [\h__\h]
I don't I don't know
oh well
thank you
soon
[Music]
it's you
feel like I always react to your name
like that it's you
okay now I'm drinking more energy drink
because I'm getting tired
and size was red
it's orange
what do you mean
ah where is it yeah let's say for your
birthday fauna offers you to give you
the power to turn kfb employees into
songbirds
oh it's so dark oh oh yeah the oranges
look like Reds
um as well as the power to turn them
back to normal but to drink everything
into songbirds turn them back to normal
it's being surrounded by songbirds
something you would like to experience
[Laughter]
if you guys would be turned into a song
birds
is that only like in terms of your
skills or also visually because I like
you guys visually
I I want you to be
fluffy timkins
fluffy fat timkins
yeah you're so round I like you being
round
[Music]
the songbirds are cute too I mean
we could try it for a day just for fun
and then switch back
but I like you guys the way you are
you guys like your the way you are too
long
I like being around
being round is nice you can roll around
it's actually like fast
as [\h__\h] way of jumbling down a mountain
or so just roll down
fast boy
travel you know you're shaped like a
friend yeah friendship
you want to be rounder sounds good
but plushy shape yeah yeah
um
but all birds are killed but you guys
are the cutest
thank you for the recipe happy birthday
and happy Fried Chicken day I hope no
tsumkin is harmed in the making of the
Stream
no I didn't even use an egg
I didn't even use an egg for the for the
dill
so no one was harmed yet
pretty vegan pretty vegetarian
pretty good
oh yeah yeah it was that's the thing
honestly honestly the reason why before
my debut I chose this date
I was looking for special dates that
would be funny
and I looked up if there's Fried Chicken
day and there was no International one I
only found a natural One National
American Fried Chicken day
so I purposefully
I purposefully set it as that day
yeah
immersion broken no no no not immersion
broken I explained at my debut that
phoenixes don't celebrate birthdays so I
don't really know when my actual
birthday was
uh but I have to choose one day you know
to celebrate it on one day of the year
doesn't matter which day it is right so
so I chose a day that just makes sense
I remember that part very well
get Lord
yeah National Fried Chicken day
I am Timeless oh God did I say that
I am Timeless did I say that
like that I am timeless
[Applause]
hola myth
and teaser trailer
[Music]
is this with boys
no
where's the voice one
oh God this is so nostalgic holy [\h__\h]
oh my God
isn't this crazy
I just won this one opposite
that's
where the powers of deaths join
come to the shark's side come to the
dark side
[Music]
I am death itself
timeless
God I am the only one only watch 50
microphone quality it stands out so much
oh my God
[Music]
I am Timeless and
I am I am timeless
[Music]
I am timeless
I gave them variations though okay I
don't know if this was really the best
one
I am timeless
oh
[Music]
I am Timeless oh my God I sound so much
more Austrian
Oh Mamma Mia it doesn't sound like me
right oh my God who is this
[Music]
really like purposefully changed my
voice that much this is still I would
say 60 of this is Mike the friends and
then
Iris what's Iris
sound like Iris sale that's me but like
also I think just gradually my voice
became a bit more chill and and that's
like maybe that that's maybe 25 and then
the rest is just me getting used to
talking on stream and my my German
accent disappearing a little bit more
and my intonation changing a little bit
so
yeah
I think all of this adds to me sounding
different
um
I think a lot of people just remember me
from my first couple of months or
whatever uh where I had this shitty
microphone and everything and I was more
like
and then they think oh I still sound
like that no I don't don't thank God I
don't oh God like
so painful
it's just so painful man
gone
a lot of people think you sound
high-pitched
oh there's something high-pitched
I can't like depending on like how
excited I am in the moment and
you know I have I think I just have a
lot of high-end UPS
UPS and lows highs and lows ups and
downs
when I talk I like to speak very clearly
too
and put a lot of emotion in my sentences
so yeah there's High moments but there's
also many low moments
um
no no I know I'm very low
don't pretend you weren't super cute but
I was
I was cringe as [\h__\h]
but maybe
two years later I will look back on me
now and also think I'm cringe
probably I will
I'll forever be cringe I'll just be
cringe forever
I was not no I'm so
cringe
although no last time where I re-watched
my debut stream
I came to the conclusion that
the uh
I had to say yo
now it was like
I don't think the things I said were
cringe much
but just don't
the combination of the mic and the voice
was cringe the way my voice sounded
through it was cringe makes me cringe
and the blood Echoes what the [\h__\h] man I
really don't understand how they could
let me do it like that
I Loki I want to say I love him
not blame but I feel like it could have
been better if everybody would have made
me aware of you know because we did we
did practice streams too
and we could have just said okay this
mic this mic is really not
not god let's get let's just borrow a
different one come on
come on I couldn't hear the echo when I
was streaming no
[Music]
um
I couldn't hear it it was creepy doll
[Music]
I'm not sure if the
Echo was only happening during that
stream or also during the rehearsal but
generally fix changing the microphone
would have fixed all my problems
saying
[Music]
oh you don't like this topic
why do you like past Wawa so much
she'll never be back
okay I just won't talk about anything
anymore
maybe maybe you just really want the
Super Chat to be read
[Music]
um
Timeless no she's not timeless
[Music]
um
uh why was I
oh bgm come back please you
mm-hmm
she's maybe Timeless in the way that
she's stuck in that time forever she's
not coming back
sweet though thank you for accepting me
the way I was back then and accepting me
the way I am now
thank you I love you guys thank you
thank you
[Music]
cook
don't unsubscribe
[Music]
that eel is like an Auntie or granny
kiss yes
[Music]
it's hot let me turn on my fan
is this a [\h__\h] human Austra is not
human
why it's so loud
this is okay guys you'll get used to it
[Music]
um
rainbow
if you had told me years ago that I
would be traveling around the world
experiencing new things meeting new
friends wearing a happy and Swinging
glow sticks around ruining my voice from
cheering all because of a vetiver I'd
have called you on Dust but then I met
you I found not only a funny
yeah
she turned up the fan
are you are you sure
my charismatic inspiring and
entertaining person was someone who is
uncommonly kind who inspires the Best in
Me
someone who made this me smile for the
first time in so long who made me pick
up a pencil
I taught someone how to pick up a pencil
[Music]
oh I taught him to draw to write and to
cook wow
teaching basic life
things functions just kidding I'm just
making jokes just joke just joke damn
damn I am capable of everything
[Music]
um where was I these gifts and a new
trajectory in my life are Priceless you
with your fancy words and I don't know
how I'm ever supposed to repay you for
them but I think my lucky stars every
day Lucky Star
foreign
[Music]
I buy sausage is that like Miss heard
lyrics
where do they say I buy sausage
what what which part
I never heard I buy sausage
I buy sausage ah I buy sausage
[Music]
ah now I can't unhear it thank you
I'm so proud of you For All You've
achieved and I'm so thankful that I've
been allowed to follow you on this
journey I want to wish you nothing but
happiness on a special day you deserve
the world kiwawa happiest birthday and
good I'm auto correcting you by the way
this is very wrongly typed good luck
next year oh and I mentioned rainbow
with my donation to my local animal
s and they help find new homes for
catching docos I hope that's okay of
course that's okay what the [\h__\h] sent
the whole Super Chat to them and nothing
to me
[Music]
happy birthday thank you that's so sweet
oh my God
oh my God that's like absolutely like
so cute I love that what a hero
I hope they have chickens at the animal
shelter
well actually I mean I guess it's better
for them to not be there because that
means they're ideally self safe
although I feel like chickens are less
safe in their environment than usually
in than an animal shelter because
normally they're you know
I don't really want to tell you guys
because
the world out there is really rough for
chickens
you guys may think you're suffering with
me but it's much worse for them
but I don't wanna
terrorize you
terrify you
with that fat
um
just don't just don't go and leave kfp
because I think you will be
torn apart
and not a very nice way
every single one of you
so be thankful
don't worry don't worry I'm on a mission
to save all the chickens in the world
and add them to kfp
so that they don't have to be
treated like [\h__\h] outside of kfb
I am on a mission being fried is better
of course of course because
well you're doing it
happily
and
more humane way
most of you are jumping into the fryer
on your own
when you're when you feel like it
you know when it's coming too kind of
[Music]
far
just just trust me you're happier here
than you are outside trust me thank you
Jara
Juan Carlos Rodriguez thank you
and of course Cruz thank you for the red
super chat happy birthday to my Kami
awesome thank you for all that you do I
know it's not always easy this year it's
extremely special to me because I got to
see you at a meet and greet and also I
cheered and lost my voice alongside a
lot of other Champions at la love you
boss no matter what happens I'll be
there supporting you keep on Shining
amazing funny
okay thank you
yeah I'm always so happy to meet you
guys in meet and greets I need to do
more
thank you thank you thank you so much
for coming to see me at this kind of
occasions yeah I appreciate it thank you
I know it might be a little bit
nerve-wracking to show me your face
but I show my face to you every day yo
look at me you're looking at me now
right so now you owe me something
I'd be too scared to meet you there's
nothing scary about that why would you
be scared what do you think I'm gonna do
to you eat you up hmm
that's not why you're scared right
[Music]
[Laughter]
that's so funny because that's kind of a
saying isn't it
like
like don't be scared of me I'm not gonna
eat you
because that's like obviously it's such
an obvious thing and and you know people
say that but I can't even say that
throughout my spaghetti it's okay
I also have those moments a bite I am
I guess it's more like that
I might bite you
um
I'm afraid of any comment about me from
from me comment about you from me I only
make positive comments about my chickens
if I make a comment
um
I wouldn't say anything
[Music]
yes I want to see you it would make it
more personal you know sometimes it
feels just a little bit unpersonal
that I always only see you guys in the
chat it's kind of lonely
you know
no
it feels like honestly it feels
so different you lost the raffle okay
well let's try it again
but it feels so different to talk to you
guys face to face more or less
hearing your praises and your story of
why you watch me Etc
from coming from your face
[Music]
is so different it hits so much harder
I hope we can do more of that
[Music]
um
I lost the raffle twice you'll get it
sometime we'll do more and more
you're disabled so you don't think
you'll ever be able to meet me in prison
but couldn't you do it from home
would you be able to do it from home
because we did meeting grades from home
last year
I'll do more of those because I can
do it whenever I guess but I I feel like
I need to combine it with uh
like I'll ask if I can do another one
for anniversary
yeah the zoom the zoom meet and greeting
that way I also usually have like
different or usually I say usually but
it only happened once
I mean know that right now actually
um
maybe an Anniversary
merchandise where's that friend
uh third anniversary merch
notes can I do a
meet and greet raffle again for this
please
and you also want to do in signatures
for anniversary uh I guess I was gonna
do them again yeah
for the ones who missed out this time
it's the signatures again to
oh
no no signatures for the album because
you just buy it normally there's like no
no merchandise thing going on
I don't think there will be but I mean
maybe at some point someday
what would be cool is if I could be at
an event
and be in person behind the scenes
and then we do meet and greets you know
like for example for dokumi
where I signed the cards on the same day
and you got back the same or the next
day
[Music]
then you could bring your CD or anything
else you want me to sign
and then you get it back
yo I was I was so stressed signing those
because I didn't have much time
I was rushing
that was a busy day
busy days
so much chaos
muchos muchos chaos
yeah I think I'll let you guys know in
the chat pre-chan I was dying
I need my small dress that you mean you
mean the the plastic
it don't sign the pluses give me
something else
oh yeah I was signing them while I
wasn't preaching can I get a guitar
sound oh I guess
my love kitty you disgusting
I need to one day sign hanayama's
boobie or butt cheek
[Music]
oh my God that's one of my bucket list
goals now
[Music]
Kyla rating me perfect timing
leap
Kyla thank you
hey yeah what's up we're reading Super
Chat what's up but tangenting talking a
lot in between
sleepy rate incoming
damn raid let's go I I I'm very happy
when I get rid of my whole life members
I really get worried and my whole life
members it doesn't happen so often
sleepy was she sleepy at the end oh man
I I'm so sorry guys for occupying her
for so long but I think
like because I asked her a couple days
ago if she has time
for playing a bit of a bit Minecraft
together with me not doesn't have to be
the whole time and she said yeah when
what are you gonna do when when
she didn't have a weekly schedule up so
I'm not sure if she was gonna play
Minecraft if it wasn't for me asking her
for that day
ah it's okay space waterfall it's okay
I'm glad you could be there
yeah I'm glad you've made another friend
me too me too
apparently yeah apparently I got raided
by Ollie like in pre-chats
I think didn't see it then
what do you mean sleepy Pema low rate
not Kyle what
you were just talking about her not
having a schedule yeah I was looking for
her schedule and then I didn't find one
I'm like eh does she not make a schedule
maybe it's just uh this week
during a geographer but I was distracted
I feel
[Music]
well okay I mean it's obvious that I
don't know this if you write me during
pre-chat
but that one yeah okay
I'll again
thank you so much
I hope you get some sleep now go go go
go
[Music]
I wonder when Kyla goes to bed I wonder
if in her mind
she kind of sends herself a chat message
that that
Minecraft brain rod
[Music]
like telling herself her body and her
mind communicating with each other
sending each other dead
[Laughter]
oh okay I understand okay I go to that
too okay
oh man
okay we need to get going guys uh thank
you Cruz
I read it all right did I yeah
and oh my God is that another rainbow oh
my God thank you fire the elements
[Music]
not a cult
happy birthday dear Tango here's a
rainbow for you wish you have a
wonderful birthday and all your birthday
wishes come true I'll keep supporting
you thank you so much
[Music]
I'm not gonna lie I've been
feeling a little bit more complicated
feelings towards the whole not occult
thing
because I've been watching like a lot of
uh or I've watched a lot of
cult related videos
and it just makes me feel more and more
um
like I don't even want to joke about it
there's some messed up [\h__\h] [\h__\h] out
there
um
but you know we're not serious about it
at all
[Music]
oh it's crazy [\h__\h] man no
no Bell no
crazy [\h__\h]
don't do what I say guys
don't do what I'd say
it's dark
um
this is a trick
no but do what I say when I say and some
when it's something that will help you
that's what the cult would say
[Music]
I can't tell the difference
but no no no no no no I don't want to
joke about this thank you for the
elements thank you
what a beautiful rainbow I'm glad you're
still around
thank you so much for the support
I hope to see you again thank you
forever
yes whatever you say mama
oh you guys can take off the tinfoil
hats now
never you comfy
if you don't take it off I'll put you in
the microwave with that
I've heard that's not a good combination
[Music]
no it's okay it's nice to have a hat I I
love hats you guys love hats it's
understandable
it's protecting you from the Sun
[Music]
I feel like it could get pretty hot I
don't know
how about your head is naked yeah
and I took off my diamond helmet
why'd you have to make me realize
I can't even look
thank you for the recipe did I say happy
birthday already happy birthday you
lovable Divine Exquisite warm sexy dorky
toxoplasmus infected big ass having yes
noodle art no gaming dancing cutie Idol
verbally always be my number one
mecoming ocean my attention I love you
too
[Music]
thank you
you already know you already know that I
know
it's not the first time
pointed it out
[Music]
no it's okay it's okay I will pretend I
didn't see anything I closed my eyes it
doesn't exist
thank you for the support now you're
always here you always
love me unconditionally
I appreciate that so much yes you
branded forever
[Music]
honeybunk
thank you for everything wow
John the bear thank you for the pinky as
a German I don't wish before her
birthday but I will be busy tomorrow
because my bachelor thesis is accepted
so I need to complete the right now
how can it be accepted before it's
completed damn happy birthday 18 years
old season
wait what
wasn't 18 years old season three be 38
like even more because 18 years old
season 1 is 18. 18 years old season 2
28.
18 years old am I what are you saying
let's okay we're not going okay wait you
mean because free did I start off with
18 we don't even know
if there's no particular
[Music]
and I thought the season is 10 years you
know
oh shut up
[Music]
poop and Marine goes by
I don't know
I am Timeless Plus for years
[Music]
[Applause]
um
[Music]
Club
and whatever
I'm waiting for an answer
from The Bachelor but no
UDA yet
I'm a good congratulations
congratulations
[Music]
yay
good for you good on you I'm proud of
you
of course
don't know what language I'm speaking
anymore
oh thank you sign painter thank you
foreign
could ask for and we have a lot to
celebrate congrats on your outstanding
performance
at the concert you sure make my Champion
heart skip beats every time I love it
spin
oh thank you I make you donkey donkey
very good let's just hope uh chickens
these chickens have a strong heart I
feel like you normally don't have a
strong heart chickens
just be careful with the Doki Doki
calm down
your heart is too weak yeah I think it's
too weak how how strong can a small
heart like that be
be careful please small small Champion
heart
[Music]
s
I love I love them
so much oh my God
[Music]
ah man
she's too funny man it's too funny
[Music]
laughs at the Turtle Man Poor turtle
anyway thank you so much next is mem
Feliz
oh my God is that birthday
well I know so I guess is here
is
wow
and wonderful and talented and sexy and
oh my God cute cute
thank you ma'am Marion
um
you're getting excited while riding on
huh hmm
[Music]
and yes
foreign excuse me
thank you ma'am you are cute too thank
question
[Music]
that hasn't been said before you know
how much I love you how much your
streams brighten my day how are you my
number one Aussie and will always be my
number one
about how fun your colors are how cute
you love us about how much I'm looking
forward to album and how happy I was
about how well you performed during the
Ian concert and how psyched I am for
volatility becoming official let's go
come on monkey think it's their birthday
happy birthday my best boss no need to
think you did so well this is perfectly
fine Super Chat I think you
I see no issue with that you did a good
job writing it hmm
one of the few people
in their name chicken
imagine shake it it's chicken
thank you for being here for such a long
time for always being so positive and
sweet to me wow thank you
JK hen
I thought he was a CPU
why
why is that new job title anyway I did
not give you this job title
so weird
you're not even like a living thing I
thought you were a monkey why are you
now a CPU
for a long time but
that was before I gave us
stopped it then why do you have it
[Music]
why
oh
they added a phoenix Emoji today because
excuse me
what
why would they do such a thing
what did this
I don't see it on YouTube
[Music]
Emoji pedia
they're planning September 20th oh my
God is there like a preview
Phoenix emoji
where do I see this
how do you know this
wait should I then officially change my
ocean mark
I could share I I could change it to
Phoenix but
we've had we've been using the chicken
for so long
is that allowed I'm sure it is oh I see
it and that looks kind of weird
[Music]
after the majest Majesty of Phoenix
in an emoji but when they tried
I tried
maybe they are adding this now because
they like ff16 so much they're like oh
my God we gotta we gotta make a phoenix
Emoji
there's also a mushroom in the lime
being added and some other stuff but the
mushroom and the lime I can see how
maybe that could be used as Oshi marks
for some YouTubers
and I guess we already had a chain
and now there's a breaking chain coming
up
thing
mark
your attached your chicken emoji I feel
like it's a little bit
embarrassing for me to have a chicken
posi Mark and I also felt like
embarrassing to put a chicken emoji in
your
in your now we're all used to it but in
the beginning I felt kind of bad for
making you guys do that
still everybody got used to it
[Music]
I mean no it's okay nothing's
embarrassing no no
[Music]
interesting though very interesting
thank you JK hey it's monkey
thank you so much
so let's keep late thanks for the pinky
another year for Kiana another year to
celebrate all her amazing
accomplishments she got her Idol outfit
participated in the first em concert has
tons of Amazing Friends and a fan base
that loves and supports her
let's go thank you
I think you even tried German huh
you even tried German you missed an a
but besides that not bad
I think this looks like you kind of
typed it yourself because otherwise the
G would probably be capitalized
so did you type it from memory
um
now I'm more proud of you if you did
type it from memory also even if there
is a little mistake also [\h__\h] capital is
capital capitalization I don't really a
lot of the time when I write dream and I
don't capitalize either
oh it's one of the few phrases you
remember well damn this is amazing
hmm
this is amazing
capitalism I do not capitalize on
capitalism
huh
German capitalism
something wrong there something is wrong
and it doesn't quite
[Music]
um
you do though your CEO says the CEO
[Music]
I don't really know what capitalism is I
don't really know
I don't really know
it many times
I don't really know what it is yeah
isn't it just like
capitalizing uh well I don't know
I don't know no one does
captain
you don't need to know
who cares we don't need to put a word on
everything
[Music]
happy first boss
they Buzz
[Laughter]
[Music]
I need to meet for some reason
there's a comma missing there
where's the two
all right I don't know why it's so funny
to me I'm sorry
I'm sorry I'm sorry emotion I'm sorry
I'm sorry second boss got impeached oh
[\h__\h] no
okay
character limit on Yo
every year I continue because this is
like entertained by your work in ways I
did not expect in the previous year
really
for musical streams to everything in
between is like a little treat I can't
get enough of hop hop you ever go up you
have a good one thank you
most of them will never help you with a
rise again
I'm actually surprised that you claim
you're being more entertained year by
year when year by year I'm playing less
and less ryza
I thought you'd like lose interest in me
if anything
but I still appreciate right wiser
oh they yeah they gave me a quote
for actually I'm married
tell me I'll give it a try but probably
just privately
I don't know if I'm even allowed to use
it privately maybe they just gave it to
me so that I play it on stream I don't
know
it came out of nowhere
no I can't play it on members
Chloe's
Nani
well motion I guess I'm losing you to
Chloe now goodbye it was nice having you
um I understand I just want to say I
understand
I don't agree but I do understand
I understand but I don't agree huh
yeah I think so
um
have fun I guess
and yeah people move on I guess
[Music]
it's probably asleep right now huh
I feel like I saw him and I guess not
emotion
[Music]
I'm not here to defend is probably
getting ready to watch Chloe again
[Music]
where
you can see
I don't think guys
are you sleeping probably
because I'm he's Motionless
foreign
everybody's going to sleep that's so
funny
okay okay
thank you for the Redtube happy birthday
you're the best if I had to describe why
I love Chihuahuas so much in 100
characters or less I'd say something
like come for the chicken themed
Minecraft as competes and stay because
you found an Aussie forever
[Music]
how dare you be so sweet
thank you
senior MC said things with the red super
chat oh boy
let's go happy birthday wow wow thank
you
oh oh
God I didn't turn off super chat today
huh I said I would I forgoto
[Music]
well it'll be turned off for members and
weekend streams
[Music]
if we make negative progress possibly
possibly not a little bit maybe
yeah weekend it has to be turned off
yeah
[Music]
well the rest of the dead and for always
being there when there's something
important and maybe also one there is
nothing important thank you
through the good times and the bad times
I you're here now too you're the best
thank you
Brandon thank you for the pinky you
don't need to read this out loud
and watching you has been so much fun
you never cease to be a fabulous
Entertainer thank you fabulous fabulous
fabulous
[Music]
someone said you like to have made for
the concert
oh that's you
wow thank you for admitting to it you
are going into my dark spot no just
kidding
that's a cute hat
and now I know you look so happy you
know in the front row it stood out to me
because I saw you so clearly
um
stood out to me
and
tap
more chickens faces in my mind
no it makes me so happy to see you guys
happily doing stuff like that he makes
me happy this is your first concert
wow
hey I took your first time
[Music]
bum
foreign
yeah the energy drink is um
doing its thing
[Music]
why are you like this why are you like
this
you love me like this so shut up
[Music]
okay calm down calm down
Skye thank you
[Music]
taxing to the sky
thank you for the recipe
[Music]
next to you keep having fun and 3D
birthday happy meals for real for real
or else
thank you thank you so much Skye
I love you thank you
bro wait Brandon that's the second one
oh my God an amazingly beautiful person
and the best ocean one could ever want
happy birthday oh you know what you got
yourself into you got yourself in a
little more
and now Keith
[Music]
thank you
oh there is a comma there it looks like
a DOT to me
makes a lot of sense now
I'm drunk on Red Bull yes
and my tummy feels like it wants to be
filled with pasta
because I ain't faster yesterday and
I've eat pasta again today because hello
beep canceled my hello beep box
so I have to make food on my own but I'm
I take this opportunity to make a low
effort food
yeah
so I just bought pasta pesto sauce
yes I've been drinking good because I'm
a bit tired now but I haven't been
drinking it so much the whole stream
just now at the end mostly
you can randomly cancel it but it said
something about they had some issues
like two days I think before it was
supposed to be delivered or so
they said like some notifications that
it doesn't it's never happened before I
think
the something with their stock
of ingredients or so went wrong I guess
like they had recipes out there that
were that they didn't have the
ingredients ordered for it or something
in the delivery chain went wrong
uh I guess so they couldn't fulfill the
recipes they could have I guess
giving me like a sub s
supplementary and a different recipe but
then
that would be weird too because who
knows if I would have liked that one I
don't know it's okay it's okay
substitute that's it substitute
yeah but alternative yeah I don't know I
am fine with
having simpler recipes this week or like
no recipes because I'm busy anyway look
I don't want to think too much about
cooking yeah
[Music]
It's Love Of Shadows thanks for the
pinky another video it might be I mean
it might be the middle or almost the end
of the work week and who knows what day
it will be by the time this actually
gets red
isn't it Friday today no it's first but
now it's Friday
at this time at least my mind is still
back L.A at La at the concert Collective
world
my mind doesn't miss the uh
what's going on am I having a stroke
I don't see any follow-up
what
what do you mean what you're confusing
me even more
shouldn't this isn't the end of it right
and you ran out of character
[Music]
and then did properly
it's just oh well oh well Evan I'm in
the middle of my super chat I ran out of
character limit
um well well I'll just end it right
there instead of changing it
stubborn chicken
oh
I I I I
uh you're losing me you're losing me
you're losing me partially because of
that and personal because of the Red
Bull
you JJ thank you
[Music]
that's like a cliffhanger
what are you not missing
it's like a cliffhanger
I will I will not be able I fill in the
gaps okay you will not miss the the uh
probably La itself
because of
the
shitty traffic or whatever
hot as [\h__\h] weather or something
foreign
maybe that's what you won't miss
we will never know the truth
sequel for us I mean Pirates here so you
could tell us
you got hit by a car
in L.A traffic
or you're probably typing out that story
right now
trial has expired by the full version
now
are you talking because like did you
tell me that because that's pyro
homeless story
what is that
was that a joke about why this Super
Chat got cut off traffic as well took my
friend ah okay it doesn't seem like that
actually happened driver goes wild took
my friend 40 minutes to pick me up at
LAX
airport well I don't know if that's long
depends on where they came from I guess
uh well I can imagine around the ex the
traffic is crazy
[Music]
you're the friend
now why did you guys all fly oh my God
fly with your wings though
[Music]
there's a l a uh road now on Mario plot
a Mario Kart
oh yeah I saw it
[Music]
Los Angeles
try out my card sometime oh
we could do a Mario Kart collab with
some girls where we test out the new
um
roads I don't think anybody really has
it on their radar right now because
everybody's like somewhere else with
their mind I think
we could do a little Mario Kart collab
racing on the new maps
new tracks
just for fun not a tournament
[Music]
busy and then I'm busy and you know
tweet about only right
yeah she in Japan
but I will
um not see her when I go to Japan
so sad
we are gonna miss each other
I'm so sad
[Music]
Ness
she can have all them in Taco she wants
so I don't want them
Guinea
sharing is caring girls
[Music]
yeah you've remembered tooth not many
people mentioned this in the super chats
I guess you guys don't care so much
about Fried Chicken after all huh
you should care more because we are all
about Fried Chicken but no that's not
true we're actually more about Burgers I
have to sign it that
I don't want us to be mainly about fried
chicken I want us to be mainly about
burgers with some fried chicken
but still you should still care about
this day
hmm
thanks to you I always have something to
look forward to this year's whole summer
ew album and fun games dreams GTA 4. I
love our busy bird but get some wild
deserves thank you I will I will
eventually
[Music]
August
but yeah there's many things to look
forward to
being personally looking forward to
Lena's pretty stream tomorrow
[Music]
yeah let's go
me too me too me too let's go let's go
oh my God I want to see dorky and Wayne
she's so dorky she's such a dork
y oh my God me to the twinsies Young
I have to go somewhere before
[Music]
member stream and before Elena's dream
too actually
[Music]
oh my God it's the best day of the year
oh my God
wait I'll try to read this in Australian
accent
have happy
have happy birthday to the Q tests
[Music]
how do I speak like Danielle from new
jeans
how do I speak like Danielle
[Music]
cuta sweetest most amazing person in the
world well
[Music]
um
uh
hope you have a one I don't know
wonderful birthday thank you I will
always be supporting you forever no
matter what you will always be my one
and only ocean
thank you for all your hard work and
everything yo does the bus it's
seriously so incredible how you I can't
I just I don't know I don't even know
where to start
I need to practice it
seriously so incredible how you always
find a way to make your Champions happy
no no valley girl doesn't make it more
Australian
incredible and Barrel Roll how your own
why why
sorry um this is the energy drink I'm so
sorry
you truly are the best I'll see any of
you any of us could ever ask fire
[Music]
you're an absolute best ever we love you
always Kiana I'm so sorry I I need to
um
[Music]
remember when it comes to Australian
accent
that stands out to me in comparison to
um British accent
the r r
water water extinct
[Music]
um
I just say make a lot and you can't add
mates to everything like a pickle
Brown
Bobby what go I am I'm
fine
oh my God I'm so sorry unknown I
absolutely butchered yours in the town
you're so nice to me and this is how I
treat you it's like unacceptable
[Music]
me please forgive me
I think I should end it I'm just I
although let's read this one because
then we are at the beginning beginning
of the stream yeah
how do you say I'm
alien and Aaron
sounds like it could be Australian
[Music]
[Laughter]
that sounds quite like it
wasn't bad that's a good accent let's go
what does unknown say about it
just laughing about it
how would you say unknown
a narrowing
just unknown mate no no
I'm so sorry
I'm losing all my Australian viewers
am I torturing them
I'm sorry
I love you
[Music]
maybe maybe love is torture
James McPhee
Reds and chat oh my God happy birthday
thank you you are our joy
die die die
[Music]
thank you so much
I think I saw you
unless I'm imagining it
[Music]
hello are you losing your mind watching
me yet hmm
if not then
are you immune or something how did you
reach immuneness immunity
teach me because I'm going insane
because of me
you want to watch seven deadly sins
the anime
I watched the first season of that I
think
and maybe
a new movie is out
you did what yeah what what what what
what what what
uh
I like the first season at least
isn't it too Shonen for you
no I like this one I like that
especially because what was her name
Elizabeth she's hot
just kidding but yeah she's hot
that's not the reason why I liked it
was good
it's your favorite
[Music]
people watched fairy tale though
no I like the characters you know they
were cute
um that that giant girl
was cute with her interactions with the
was it what the pillow dude or I don't
know it's been too long
yeah Diane Diane is cute and yeah the
the small dude is basically link I guess
because he's small a small Hero Let's
link
kind of Link
um
I don't know I don't remember the story
anymore but I think I enjoyed it very
much
oh and then oh my God I don't think she
was was she there in the first season
the uh the hot sexy lady who has that
name
yeah Marilyn I want to say because it's
like a male name and uh yeah it's a
special name Merlin
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
yep yeah
she's cool
[Music]
she's fine
um
Eminence and Shadow I think I maybe
heard of that once
I know what you mean boss I got you
thanks
always thanks Pig was annoying oh I
remember some annoying Pig yeah
why are you selling that I don't know
should I go I'm kicking me out of my own
channel
it's all gone
guess I'll go I'll see you tomorrow
remember stream I still don't know what
to do but I'll decide when I wakey wakey
snakey sneaky
snake I saw the super cute video about
snakes
and then this is the so-and-so snake and
this is a long boy and this is this but
when it's this and then send this and
then in this and then it's in this and
this part of the snake you call this and
this you call that and but all of the
cutest the cutest imaginable yeah
[Music]
oh the cutest words ever oh my God
it was so cute
it was really short though no broke
[Applause]
um
[Music]
that sounds like me saying for getting
spaghetti or spaghetto spaghetti
murder
oh man
it's all right
that's my fault
no never
oh no
I gotta go
okay I seriously
sorry I would like to publicly apologize
for me
goodbye
and in German we say Aviation
I
[Music]
am
GTA
on the weekend GTA on the weekend GTA
members
enjoy me while you can because next week
I'll be busy
I wanted to ask one thing
um if I do collab with Noel she said uh
I asked if you can do if you want to do
evening collab or like midday or like
you know noontime kind of uh what time
is good for you most of you guys
because she said anything Works anytime
works I don't know
Japanese evening oh that's the European
speaking
also I don't know if we're doing it on
her or on my channel but I guess like
you know I always feel bad like if it's
more mostly Japanese than
I feel like it should be on the other
channel but ASMR so I guess we just make
stupid sounds
[Music]
it could be on my channel maybe I don't
know
it's easier to have it on your channel
though so I don't have to set up
anything
is evening okay Japanese morning would
work but it's not morning too early
oh I don't mind either no
I think I'll be better at ASMR than
Subaru
yes
evening noon would be better hmm
maybe I'll do a poll
I don't know I don't know I don't even
know what time these times are in any or
so
did corvo delay is similar before
okay
I think Kobo could be really sweet in
there some more but she probably becomes
gremlin
foreign
[Music]
well if she tried if he wanted to I'm
sure
but I I like her being a gremlin
um
oh my God
she refuses to do it
in a healing way that's very good very
good very good Kobo keep on doing that
that's how it should be
okay and enjoying myself it doesn't my
eyes are tired I need to make some pasta
but only cook it the pasta and then put
on the sauce that's it
[Music]
oh and I saw PewDiePie and Martin
randomly I don't follow them but I saw
the baby somewhere in my timeline and
such a cute baby
it's so small and I'm like what she's
pregnant I didn't know
but the bubble is so small oh my God
yeah they have a baby now it just was
born just now like five seconds ago
[Music]
yeah they call them beer and uh so they
went for uh a name of PewDiePie
Heritage I guess
maybe if they get a second child they
give it an Italian name
it's nice but good luck with having
Japanese people understand how to write
that name because uh just they don't
even know how to pronounce that I've so
many times remember when I tried to
teach Nana kagura how to say uh
they don't they don't know how to
pronounce it
[Music]
should have thought of a name that they
will have an easier time writing and
pronouncing
they live in they live in table Yeah
they will say
[Music]
yorun but it's actually Bjorn Bjorn okay
it's this decent
they just ignore the dots I guess
laughs
[Music]
cute
cute damn
okay bye
[Music]
be for me what
um
[Music]
when is she coming
baby now
[Music]
she can't come in because the door
closed because of the
[Music]
she couldn't even come in oh I wonder if
they're like usually when I close the
door they're just like camping in front
of it
oh [\h__\h] the wind
[Music]
[Applause]
s
bubbles
[Music]
Raptor what the [\h__\h]