[Music]
I I was if I
could
got I want what I need
you
you like you
[Music]
super I don't even know
you see you me everyone
keep
my b
[Music]
i
i i don't even know what
to play me
[Music]
[Applause]
I don't even know what to do
this good your you
[Music]
around
[Applause]
[Music]
I don't I was if I
could perfect for you it'sing like it's
don't think
I
got
[Music]
I you I don't even know to
[Applause]
[Music]
I did
you i
[Music]
i o
k
hello how's it
going I'm
dying die die
[Music]
die I need you to balance out the
orange we have to mix our colors to be
yeah darker or lighter like a darker
urine what what what oh my God because
you're like orange you're both orange
actually you guys are like really really
dark
urine we just whose piss is
orange who
well I I think if you're radioactive
maybe speak up who who who wants to
confess I couldn't believe that
I would hear such a thing already like
one minute into the Stream So I really
thought you were mispronouncing
something record for
[Laughter]
this um yeah so we're back again with
Eden Eternal yippe
yppe um sh is feeling a little bit under
the weather right yeah I'm dying don't
die see you guys in heaven don't
die and and uh so yeah I think today
today will be a little bit of a shorter
stream
[Music]
right but we'll be we'll be efficient
anyway even with less uh we got to go
kill Charles
again okay it's okay it's been a while
so it'll feel like that's a
recap but before we do that um kfp is
inviting us to visit our Guild City so
while can I visit your city actually I
don't know if you
can um but if you can't I was thinking
you could visit Inkwell City if they
have one I heard kfp I I don't know how
to get to my own City I don't know
either yeah how do we get to the city is
it go to base when you open the guild
window press G oh I can go to your city
I'm going my base see a [\h__\h]
so you're going to Inkwell right yeah
I'm going to Inkwell oh I got a free
outfit oo I have arrived KY are you also
coming to the I go to base okay let's go
ink
willans wow so many people again by the
way I'm a Cheerleader today oh my God I
just
left got a cheerlead out so cute this
guy RP wait where I walked in and walked
out immediately no come back are you
scared don't be so terrified don't be so
nervous I passed backwards don't be so
socially awkward come on come on I'm
here I'm here I can't see you there's
too many people where are you what do
you look like oh my God
small I'm I'm up here actually I don't
know where I
am I'm on the plat I saw you I saw you
okay I'm here okay okay okay okay okay I
heard something about oh oh they're
already here you guys already made it
yeah they made the Statue so fast to as
well are they going to change when we
change outfits or do they have to be
remade also I'm stuck okay do they have
to be remade I wonder cuz like I'm not
I'm changing my outfit every single time
I log in yipp yipp
wow is there inal statues too shooting
you can I think you can go from like the
G menu and then find town maybe oh wait
did you go to ours or yours not I don't
know how how do I get to yours I
[Music]
don't
I wait are you where are you right now
I'm an Inkwell I don't know how I got
here mean I mean location not which
Guild the the the forest or Aven I'm in
Aven if that's what you're talking about
wait oh my God we even got a guild icon
now wow it's a
chicken I love that I'm just a Wandering
child in my own
Guild no but maybe inil has no City yet
do they oh we have a city apparently we
have
homes uh I don't I don't know if they
made a statue you got to enter so then
they can make one for you like I think
you have to be in I'm in I'm in the
thing I'm just ping around while
everyone follows me making sure I don't
kill myself inil show her the way show
her the way to the
Statue oh but it can't show me the way
cuz I'm running out away from that won't
work soon got a farm did you see you
open the guild announcements the kfp
made a
guide oh I'm reading the guide right now
the statues I remember Fame quick guide
oh wow you can like harvesting here I'll
link it thanks for the information
everyone Consulting guides containing
helpful and missable info
[Laughter]
wow oh please do a Guild quest to earn
10 Fame and then be promoted to employee
wow strict very strict you can't be
promoted unless you do
something wait there's icons for every
round rank
too oh the GRS got their own little
icons cute so cute they're in the
Box why are they in the box is that a a
shoe box oh a shoe
box per perfect perfect why are you guys
what can you guys calm
down calm down are you fighting each
other oh oh wait that's a boss oh oh I
didn't realize there's an enemy
[Music]
there okay well th those statues are
beautiful I hope you guys can remake
them every single day that I log in
okay that's so cute yeah
wow okay that was uh nice thank you guys
you worked so hard on making everything
even nicer thank you let's go
questing all right questing she already
needs to kill
Charles yeah for a third time cuz I hate
Charles heck yeah let's go we proba pick
up the
daily uh wait how do how do I get there
uh how do I not be homeless in the game
I forgot to rent a
house you can rent a
house yeah they said that we have a z
zero homeless population for
[Laughter]
Inkwell oh I need to be level 35 okay
I'm I'm mching off of you guys until
then we'll get there ah we should make a
group
again oh yeah a party
party party party thank you for the
invitation oh thank you all my healer
friends
okay let's meet at the
dungeon okay was it BR
root I have noidea yeah uh the
dungeon Branda
root why do I want to do a territory War
I would
die what territory are you fighting for
I I don't even
know where the heck are these people you
can get statues if you're like the top
four or a server I guess freaking
flexer [\h__\h] the one at Beluga Bay
right on my way Whata B
OHA that's D oh I was in the wetlands
oopsie it's okay we can have Gigi
teleport us I won't mess it up this time
I'm
running don't worry teleport away I I
have to run there
first don't don't worry I'm running
maybe I'll be there first before
you do I care about this
daily B
transform and then more
feel um North oh vile shark yeah yeah
okay uh it's like Nord shark but it's
not a VPN
is it even Nord shark
actually Nord I think you're mixing
shark
and you can be double secure oh yeah
you're so
secure why are you so fast Shori you're
so fast slow slow my little orange urine
oh what what move speed is your
Mount I have no idea you're
so
fast okay okay I'm going to summon
kiaha no no I'm
Su me I'll probably end up in the void
Vortex or something like that please be
careful okay now what if I summon you
again okay now I summon you
[Music]
again I'll end up in the black hole
please
okay we're good now hey maybe I can pick
up a
daily oh me too wait I can't I haven't
finished
this got to do the real Quest
first all right let's go this is been
vile shark vile shark Solo or
multiplayer for your quest uh I think we
can just do solo can't we hold solo yeah
SOLO okay we going oh oh right okay then
useless no
reason oh well no
reason um no
reason well well K can heal you too I
could I'm just going to watch I could I
could but however I will heal Kara as
well all right you heal me I heal her no
reason a healing uh what do you call a
long long long a healing trainer no
human cine yeah healing
cine
[Music]
yppe sorry I should have laugh seeing
you
die no no I'm not dying I have two
beautiful healers in this centipede
who's if you were in the human centered
which one do you want to be like which
position I guess the
front yeah to decide where to go yeah I
don't want be eating your [\h__\h]
you want the middle I I did watch that
movie and I remember there was a
Japanese guy and he speaks in like well
naturally Japanese and I was so proud of
myself if I could understand bits of it
wait those those jell when we kill all
of those Charles spawns right yeah you
get Charles we only need Charles to be
honest okay
okay well girls I need to announce
something
what's up yes I started watching
Breaking
Bad oh my God finally finally have you
guys watched it I've seen not I don't
know of course not of course not
what yeah I
I under a
rock wait gigy have you watched it I've
watched it I've also watched Saul
what letter call sa sa oh Saul I thought
you meant
saw no not s better CL all is um like
wait I saw it on nli part of the
universe it's part of the universe what
what universe is what who's the Breaking
Bad
Universe it is okay I I'm really not far
so maybe even asking that question would
be a spoiler
it's not really related it's about
another character ah he doesn't show up
until season 2 okay I'm like four
episodes in into season one or so and
I'm just like wondering how how are they
going to continue the story for Five
Seasons like they all
die I don't really know I mean yeah but
then it should end earlier like what I
can't really see the future it's
concerning I'm
excited I hope you're enjoying it I I
really enjoyed it the first few episodes
the first the only the first episode
actually I was like oh this is actually
I thought this would be more dramatic
but right now it's more
funny great but yeah after that it
immediately became really dist
disturbingly concerning and
worrying yeah I like Breaking Bad but I
think I prefer uh better call S over
Breaking Bad and then Breaking Bad was
just like I had to watch it in order to
watch Saul which was really really
good but I I I'm not saying that by the
way in a in a negative sense that it's
not funny or so it is still funny while
being depressing and that it's fine it's
good I'm not saying it's bad I just was
surprised it was as as depressing
already all I know about breaking bad is
this about like drugs probably and and
people be dying I what's the Saul
version who's Saul you have no idea
who's Saul not yet Saul is let I mean it
it has the same Vibes he's a side
character it's like lawyer stuff instead
of drug stuff oh so he does things
legally some yeah some law
drama I see I
see okay shall we go back to the
wetlands now that we did the or I think
go back to the wetlands okay
Wetlands I will be there soon do not
teleport
me what you don't want me
teleported not yet she wants to stop
running so fast her own legs or with her
own
Mount her own bunny rabbit cute yeah
it's so
cute oh yeah I like breaking bed now I
have two addictions Arcane and breaking
bed my enemy
[Music]
I can't get that out of my brain once
it's in there why why why did you have
to sing it sorry I want think about
it I sang it
like 30 times in my last Diablo stream
my chat is brainwashed I wake up to the
S silence and alive my turn
around
gy now that we can perhaps do English
song covers but only by putting them on
Spotify or whatever we should sing that
song why
me yeah let's do it let's let's pay for
the expensive license and LIC song
cover no just
kidding just kidding
what's the possibility should guys with
that cover with e of edgin yeah we like
just kidding and then a month later we
were just
kidding we never
kid my
head why why what the heck is demon
light cream where do I get this cream
yeah who up demon light creaming is that
a quest item does it say it's a quest
item main quest
Alice it level 32 throw it
[Music]
away are you joining a join how how are
you enjoying
Arcane um so I am currently holding back
to watch all the first couple of
episodes from the second season I want
to save it a little bit cuz I don't want
to end it too
soon but it's so good and it's like
really really
gay
and but it's so good agree yeah it's
beautiful it's a beautiful show and it
is beautiful it makes me want more which
feels like a
sin you can get more from playing League
of Legends mhm apparently not apparently
not KY there's no story there I've Been
Told
no no don't listen to them don't listen
to them need a
resist you can play League of Legends if
they put more story into their games
then okay then we can talk about it they
have this build water game that I heard
hold on let me look for it BW game
what game League of Legends here
how much is the game by the way how much
does it
cost 30 USD 30
only in this economy I mean and this for
real yeah here is all the ri Forge game
the game is free
geky Oh you mean League of Legends yeah
oh League of Legends is
free what a deal you have
invited into your chaos
you don't want to play it huh I don't
want to play it no what's your reason do
you not like those I got time for other
stuff I don't have time
for no no I don't know like I I I it's
it's complicated it's okay if you play
it I won't judge you you know I mean I'm
judging you but I just kind of want to
see like like I want to play the
characters that I saw in the show just
experience it once cuz like I need to
make that
connection but oh the attachment you
know they're making like a farming game
in League of Legends or something what
farming the yal one it's some it's some
relaxing cozy League of Legends
game where else can make demon light
cream is that not out yet I I don't
think it's out yet oh I need Darkness
Essence now oh who's emo in here besides
me yeah who
emo what go pet light cream wait how do
I get more demon
dust we got enough demon Essence I can't
tell I need Darkness Essence where that
too the game isn't holding us on our
hands anymore what the
spirits yeah they're green little guys
they look like saplings
essentially I'm killing them where where
where well well well if you press M and
like scroll down through monsters or
just check where I am at yeah I'm I'm
coming over it's not dropping do they
drop the other items too they Dro both
of them but I have not gotten a lot of
Darkness Essence yeah I haven't gotten a
single Darkness essence these Wetland
Spirits suck why she I got to make them
cry more a wetland Spirit oh am I
already
there do something
Tak
huh oh my
God okay was please give me my darkness
Essence I just want to be Emo
the essence of
[Music]
Darkness EG G so did you watch all the
episodes already for AR yeah I seen them
o I think I got spoiled a little bit on
Twitter No but it's kind of a thing that
I expected anyway to happen so yeah but
people should stop not everyone's
watching all the episodes yeah
well it's fine the next set isn't even
out yet I think people should lay off on
the spoilers until the next set of
episodes are out I know to be courteous
please get off of your mou or St a few
more steps away from me your big ass
feathers are constantly in my
screen and makes me jealous I want those
feathers you could just pluck it off of
them
[Music]
H good idea oh I got two five Darkness
Essence I feel like I'm partially
picking it up from Me Oh yay I got it
C
crafting
yippe Fusion right here
got why am I still fighting
this o more dark assassins I don't need
yeah I don't want anymore and we can
just throw him out of the inventory
that's
true why is this
like
clear okay I'm talking to
rocks what are they saying to you I
don't know I ski her dialogue did not
archive ski a
skippa okay Quest finish
next ah that's why you're talking to
rocks you're talking to
monuments yeah talking to the Pebbles
what's up
Pebble there's a big Pebble that's a
pebble when it grows
up yeah
oh
[Music]
cute let's see those monuments oh wow
wow it's got so much to
say I'm not listening I didn't read
it building volum
okay cool stuff oh I see I start I
clicked on another Quest where am I
headed o I should not be going wrong
Quest stay the right path giggy don't
get distracted lost I'm lost it's the
Zoomer
mind too easily
distracted my fingers are so weak my
hands are so weak oh I'm so excited for
this dungeon oh why yeah you'll see it
you'll see
it my hands
hurt why I've done so much gardening
today
oh I have are you growing like
vegetables or something no no no I just
I mowed my lawn and did the the edges I
trimmed the edges of my lawn but the
edges I did with like some shears
but it was so
exhausting and my hands are in
pain cuz I I kind of didn't trim the
edges so far because I didn't have the
the right equipment for it and so it was
it was a quite a quite a lot to
do beautiful garden yeah I wonder if you
can just replace your lawn with fake
grass no never no no I can't do that
it's got to be real grass not the
F no but my little golf
course I'm thinking next year I'll just
uh hire a gardener for the
really annoying stuff Argus oh there you
are can't click on that
there but it's a good workout I
definitely burned a lot of calories
today what's in your garden m not that
much yet because I I only have this
Garden since this
year but I had some strawberries but
like really a small
amount uh and I
had I planted tomatoes and uh bell
peppers but then I had none of it
because when it was actually actually
growing I was in Japan and then I I
couldn't have any of it no yeah and and
then I don't know a lot of my plants
also died because there was suddenly a
huge
rain uh attack from the
sky uh yeah trying to keep your garden
down yeah they're they are garden
keeping me they're Garden keeping
yeah but also I've been growing some
herbs I want to grow more herbs cuz it's
nice to have like fresh basil and fresh
parsley and stuff like that whenever you
need it so I need more of that I think
next year I'm really going to focus on
getting a sick Garden together but I
think I'm actually going to hire
professionals to like style my G make
them give you rose bushes rose bushes
why rose bushes out of all things you'll
be like the the Alice and Wonderland
Rose Garden yeah yeah I did want some
flower bushes but I I was thinking if
I'm going to plant any bushes then I
might as well plant like bushes that
carry
fruit oh that makes sense yeah I want
fruit I want more fruit you're living
the the harvest
Bush raspberry Su staining
ooh
yeah but I always got to be careful with
what I plan land because I'm always
checking if it's like cat safe even even
if they don't try to like nibble
anything I still want to be
careful make sure everything's cat
safe got to protect the kitties roses
have fruits rose hips rose hips I only
know rose hip tea wait you rose
hips rose
hips oh wait those are those really
edible
what's that in
German ha a i
s
oh never thought about eating those like
in uh in their not tea
form I'd be scared to eat anything like
raw that I
grow what even if it's just like veggies
and fruit
a little I mean like my parents grew
stuff but I fear like something came
inside it like a
bug n actually what's wrong with eating
a bug if you grow things yourself that's
like maybe the least concerned you got
to be about your food that rather than
like when you get it from the
supermarket or so who knows they must
have sprayed with a lot of pesticides
and [\h__\h] so if you grow it yourself you
can be I think less worried about that
stuff true but I could just buy it from
the
store it's so expensive and even I was
just so mad every time I buy like
strawberries or so it's just
always they die after one day in my
fridge even and most of them are really
bad quality anyway
weird my modified genetically modified
strawberry stay last a bit
what am I supposed to do with this I'm
clicking on it I don't know what to do
oh wait what do you want the magic key
there's like a stone a room okay so you
got to you got to press on that item and
then there should be like a fusion thing
click on that item again and like drag
it okay I was clicking on the on the
Rune nothing happens when I click on the
Rune but when I click on yeah it's
confusing when I don't want to pay
attention honestly and the indented can
you just do it piece where you get the
indented ancient piece I think you
should have gotten it by
default I
didn't just just keep pressing randomly
but you got to make the item boo why
can't they just give me
stuff okay maybe wait did you give me
what I
again no I do not want to track
you don't track all see a I got it
track okay okay
okay yippe can UNT track it oh shoot I
lost all my
tracking you face where do you get the
indented piece
uh when you click on collect magic key
it will leave you lead you to the uh NPC
it's like an NPC with
a green exclamation mark above them and
then if you choose the talking option he
gives you the wheel thank you sir you're
welcome beautiful antique collector
bass and
[Music]
kiaha immediately sharing my newly
acquired
knowledge not gatekeeping my knowledge
no Garden keeping here
mhm okay I found a SLO in my garden by
the way I almost cut it with my shears
you know that like
beer you should like leave a bunch of
beer around like open
for to access yeah yeah there's this
video I saw where someone left a a
container of beer and one slug showed up
and then more slugs showed up and then
before you know it the entire container
was full of slugs E I don't like beer
and I don't want I don't like beer with
slugs either like that just makes makes
it I I want my trunk slugs they're
funny really do they behave
differently yeah they party harder
H I have the
quest the Quest for the dungeon oh well
we have to talk to this thing
okay all right yeah I'm ready to for the
dungeon oh give me give me a bit it's
taking me across the map for another
stupid daily no it's a five player
dungeon does that mean we need two more
people you can still do a solo dungeon
yeah it even says choose single player
dungeon
still yeah it's saying go
solo we got to kill double door double
door yeah oh absolutely no reference is
intended right yeah we only believe in
single doors here
S no I left the slug what the heck is
this no slugs have been harmed in my
gardening
oh but you know if you have one slug you
have tons of slugs no no no I really
only saw one slug oh no that's because
they're underneath the the surface of
the dirt they're buried underneath every
time you step under grass they're like M
kiaha feet kiaha feet I'm that slug
can't wait for October Fest when all the
beer comes I have harmed slugs
before I did you pour salt on them or no
no wait was it really me or was it my
mom slugs have been in my presence
thrown into a fire place but I think it
was my mom well I did on video okay
there's video evidence of me doing it
too but because my mom did it
first oh you you learned her from her
huh from her
mistakes yeah I mean to be fair they do
look pretty gross I would just like
they're so gross and they were like I
swear everywhere I was camping in my
mom's Gard
Garden because I was making
a surviving in the wilderness
video uh yeah cuz her Garden is like the
Wilderness and on my camping area I was
like you know making everything nice I
had a fire I was making uh a chicken
soup
legitimately and uh yeah then there were
so many slugs and it was disgusting so I
had to get rid of some they were I swear
they were like in such a small area
there were like 50 of them oh my God
that was probably their home base and
you invaded their home no no no no no
that is my mom's home base and they
invaded my mom's
home but could have been the
Invader this is their land before you
guys plenty of slugs in this
world it's
fine wow they didn't pay rent yeah
they're not paying
rent well to be fair I don't think you
had any documents to make them pay
rent they ain't got nothing yeah did you
give them the paperwork maybe they would
have pay if you gave them the chance you
know maybe maybe they maybe I did them a
favor maybe like them being a slug is
their bad Incarnation after having a a
Bad Karma life and now that I wonder
what you
he no I didn't have a favor they're
reincarnating as a human again now to to
live an interesting life and then and
then they remember their slug memory
like
that's they're like I remember when I
was a
slug if only I could go back would you
still off me if I was a worm for real
for
real that actually is a legitimate
question
then the slug person reincarnated slug
person 30 years in life finally settling
down getting married and then getting a
midlife crisis wondering if their
partner would really love them even if
they were a slug so they ask the
question and open up about their
previous life I think I think I would
like not love someone if they were a
slug because they can't talk anymore I
think what I would do is they would be
my specimen and I would take multiple
pictures of them and just post it on
soci social media you would use them for
cloud is it really cloud though but then
it makes me wonder am I technically
taking like nude photography of them
yes they like it
probably if they didn't like being naked
they would become a snail and put a
house on their body also that would lead
me to if they didn't like being homeless
then they would be a snail putting a
house on their body so I think they they
don't own the property that my mom lives
in so I can I can burn it anyway enough
reasoning it could be like a light novel
title where it's like I was a garden
slug but a a phoenix evicted me from my
home and now I'm a human evicted me from
My Life by fire when a phoenix is at
your in front of you threatening you of
course it's going to be by
fire oh you in a you fighting I'm in the
dungeon bu are we wait oh okay I saw
people fighting something outside oh I'm
just sitting days I'm ready how do we
enter all I have is this rock oh you
still have to finish making the rock oh
no no no I see it it just says enter and
then five player and I'm like why okay
I'm inside you do have the quest that
says defeat double door yeah okay good
let's double
door I'm still a Bard going to be until
35 maybe I think that was what I needed
to
be right well I shall heal and then
magic boost other classes ice
Shield o Burning metal oh crap where
where did you go oh you're still right
here
oopsies BL 45 okay
oh got a little bit distracted
honestly you should just be like a a
tank Mage or a battle mage
GG I'm going I'm going no you should
choose in any case you should choose a
class that can tank AOE be like fight
with AOE while maybe like T for her
maybe GG I need to heal you stop running
away from the Healer don't worry don't
worry I'm so strong
killing destroying you think they're
tanky I
know to be fair you're
squishy but they they still they're
still so
tanky there are
mushrooms okay I want to change into
like a different class why were you
excited for this dungeon
CH oh that's because it took uh I took
inspiration from the name of it for
something
oh it's like Oh I like that word that's
a fancy word malice Palace what was that
ah sh I had to think of you in my member
stream uh on Sunday because I was
watching once again bakim monar um this
time we were watching the
secondar season we're like pretty close
to the end finally but the was it the
opening or the ending song I think the
ending song it was called
[Music]
shiii yeah it was a pretty good song Too
song about about I think um I don't know
something nice shiori yeah it was about
you about one shiori Nolla Yeah by to me
do you know Claris c l a r i
s yeah they made that song they sang
that song oh that one I see but yeah
they make many pretty song So Shi is
also a pretty song just like you are
pretty thank you now we have to wait for
a song called Kiara nah I would make
that
myself take it into my own
hands but you should cover with a
shieldy
song we'll have to see if I can sing it
when I'm not dying pretty in your
voice when I'm not dying oh God there's
a coming towards me uh don't worry he's
confused he's confused
he come
back I'm not using my staff why'd you
hesitate kinky it be funny using like an
axle this time I was using my
guitar H is that bad I don't know I
don't know the stat
difference I hope I do more damage now
oh wait oh you're a mage a mage I think
not I do want to be a mage heal yourself
I will wait uh I can be the
healer for a while if you want uh well I
had to level up myself stuff I'll do it
off screen I guess at this point I am
just considering uh preparing a tank
[Laughter]
class it's good to have all kinds of
things for when we
must it can be everything
mushrooms die transformed
mushro you will regret living here he's
living his best life he should have been
born a slug yeah he should have been
born a slug so he can get evicted
instead of
killed you didn't kill them right Smiles
at
you oh by the way I finished the the
did you like it I did but I had no idea
what they were saying most of the time
you game I I probably I don't know but
homicide vers the game where just like
creepy looking uh Creepy Pasta men and
they speak in a language that you can't
understand and you have to decipher what
they're trying to say for
context what is this game I had no idea
what the heck they said but they were
kind of cute you should start from the
beginning now that you have your Di AR
filled out and then fix your words if
any of them are out of context a lot of
them are out of
context it's like at one point they
would make sense for one situation but
the next uh situation is like it made no
sense I don't know what it
[Laughter]
is I like uh this dude named Mr
hood and then uh is he the one in the
beginning yeah but I didn't get on this
route I didn't even know you can get on
his route I don't think you can you can
it's just the like one choice that you
can easily Miss oh boo I want more
information on him he's healing what
the oh maybe he heals when you attack
him there's some characters who do that
do we actually have to think
now oh he D now don't
worry die die I remember one of the
words is like when you get the tool and
then you don't know it's tool so you
have like I don't know crowbar or ladder
yeah sense anywhere
else or like instrument it's like okay
instruments of
[Laughter]
torture what the hell costly out of Mana
now this is sucking up my
Mana uh hold up I need a buff you
where are you I need to buff
you oh you're good okay you're good now
oh cleric bubs
o I got B
bubs oh my God it's double door oh
my they really made him a wizard it's
double door audacity oh I think there's
something attacking me h M attack it
back fight backk you I'm healing you
guys
though double door you will die oh wait
I think if you lead him out he'll
actually like reset his health are you
trying to stop my
research
yes he just wanted to know about anime
girls dead what I wasn't even attention
so oh I'm s he I'm going to talk to
B okay me
too good job nice
dungeon yeah on to more good work
everyone good work indeed we are such
successful experienced Warriors making
good progress mhm
where is
Bez oh back in the main
place I'm
hungry you can eat like the mushrooms in
this area I hate
mushrooms I wish I lik them cuz they're
like growing in my garden against my
will I could what is it about it flavor
the texture both both but I do kind of
like mushroom sauce
oh the size like cream of mushroom I
don't like the texture either
yeah I wish I liked them would make life
easier ooh they got some nice
weapons I like seeing mushrooms grow in
someone's lawn like it's not meant to be
there natur staring at it it if you like
seeing that you should come visit
me oh and then can bring beer and get
all your slugs I want to see your cat
I'm coming over to see your quote
unquote cat no no for real everybody's
welcome though come over you coward you
want to see my cat well come see my cat
do it okay I'll let go there first and
then she can teleport me to your
area what am I going to link my soul
to I guess her bed this Quest wants us
to become level
33 got to do some other quests is this
guy selling Quest Books doing my
dailies are I able to trigger a quest
I'll I'll buy a book to get a quest hell
yeah okay reach level got to talk to
[\h__\h] Ro
23 there we go more mushrooms will be
killed
by my
hands we'll teach them a lesson grab all
these daily Quest I guess I wanted to
ask you girls a
question following question um this is
context uh yesterday uh I announced a a
cool
collaboration with a company yeah
they're going to do some cool stuff you
know and I was
wondering uh if you girls were to have a
collaboration with a company for example
like hi to they make like the PC cases
or V to make like knives and ramen and
stuff or anything really what what would
be something you want to put your name
on if you could make it if not just
these companies that I name just
anything in your mind what would you
want to
make like uh what type of sponsorship I
would want yeah essentially yeah I I
would want L to
close that's cute yeah yeah I think
that's in the realm of
possibility would you want to design
them no I don't need to design them I
would just like make a video on them
it's like give me clothes I'll make a
video Yeah would be nice if they would
actually like I don't know give the
outfit to you as as a life Tod outfit or
so cuz like Callie had something like
that before she got a a one piece
related outfit
so cute M yeah that'll be nice cute very
demure so
mindful want about you shoes because
shoe box oh shoes would be cool but I
don't know the question is so
broad it is but you got it's good to
have what about like boxing clothes for
G cuz you're boxing cloes oh yeah or
like any gloves who's looking to
fist yeah
but I do think it's it's good to like
work towards something and also
establish your own brand as a senpai I
want to tell you like for me with kfp
I've been like constantly like working
on this like image of having a fast food
chain and cooking Etc so I think if you
continue working towards something um
building up an image then eventually you
will get got game got no hey what got
game
G but yeah sure why not game why not got
are ging they love
sponsorships actually for me I think i'
I'd be stuck in Tech cuz I already have
like a bunch of tech videos
technically yeah I'm sure you could like
get something
maybe maybe like
a sponsorship for some motion capture
also or that that one a little different
yeah I
guess some I guess then you could get
the PC PC
sponsorship oh already already got one
oh hell
yeah even
better I would like keyboard caps M
that' be neat or keyboard nice
keyboard Go Get It Go Get It get those
gy key caps
what about a gem
keyboard
yes I would love those col if it's like
your it be funny General colors I love
that it'd be funny if your keyboard caps
were like the letters were flipped or
written properly or like it just like
not even the actual
letters that' be so evil all the letters
Doodles it's like what am I supposed to
do with this yeah I can't read this key
ke board people would just put them in
the right you know the right
[Laughter]
spot h i did the book quests but I'm
still not level 33 this will take a
while yeah it do taking me a while too I
do all these
dailies I'll buy another
book you should just sell shoe boxes
kill sell shoe boxes yeah without the
shoes just the shoe
boxes when I start reselling used shoe
boxes just from random
Brands they're totally you'll make them
special people will want the shoe boxes
because they're from you who wants a
shoe box that was in my home put a slug
in there why we back to slugs why are we
back to slugs we're giving them homes a
they can have homes what do you call
that re re um when you give someone
recycle no no no when you when you give
people homes re rehoming not rehoming
re what's the word help me chat re not
sure re rehabilitating slugs yes
oh oh you make them sound like drug
addicts though
maybe they are breaking bad yeah
Breaking Bad slug
Edition next
Quest
okay Wetland W Wonder Wetland
Exile okay got to manually turn the page
why can't you do it for me Quest
yeah rude
have you ever seen videos of snails
eating oh aren't they just like kind of
slugging around over the food doesn't
really look like they're eating I
they're like they use their little mouse
and they're like Yum Yum Yum Yum they're
so cute I don't know I see videos of
snails and I it makes me wish I had a
snail a a oh you know I jumped I owned a
rat the other day and it was such a
vivid dream actually
a what was your rat's name I didn't have
a name but I kept trying to keep it away
from my cats in my
dream I've always wanted a rat I just
don't like that their lifespans are so
small and it would really sad yeah I
think they only live like 2ish years and
they're really
smart small animals don't have big
lifespan
sadly unless you're like a a dog or a
cat I think yeah but if you want a snail
you could make you could easily get a
snail just pick it up outside and then
make it a little
terrarium wouldn't that be cute but what
if they're leaving their families like
they were just coming home from work
well then ask they have a loving wife we
where is your family I'll find it for
you is it inhumane to get a pet snail by
picking up a snail outside and forcing
it into your
home I think the oils on your skin would
hurt them too or maybe it's a different
thing well then pick them up to or so
and then put them in the terrarium that
you made for and then never use those
Chopsticks
again why why not I guess you could
clean
it what is this I'm choosing whatever
what's the correct way of getting a pet
snail would you have to buy it from a
breeder AER no go to a go to a French
restaurant save I think
be just scaring I think probably most of
them or do they
esaro do they
all menu can you like make any snail
your pet or is there like a a type
ofet why do you limit yourself so much
don't let you dreams be dreams I just
need to know what the humane way of
owning this now cuz you don't want to
get cancelled by the snail Society right
yeah
exactly yeah I I'll I'll prepare a snail
for
you I'll catch one in my garden wait
wait how long did they even last for
like lifespan wise the expiration date
probably less than the rat how long
snail live cuz I was thinking like
you're holding it for gii and then she
takes like a few years to show up two or
three years but 10 of it's large large
species snail how big is a large snail
have you seen the snail that like they
can hold in their arms large snail hold
arm here we
go is that photosho though do you like
snails if I send this will you be
disgusted by the snail send it send it
send
it oh is that real I've seen that
picture
before I think it's real oh that's so
he's kind kind like a bunny it's kind of
cute yeah they're cute let me send you
let find it the video that I was
watching where they're eating I'm like
like oh my God they're so cute or it is
though kind of a cute little snail but I
wonder how their minds are it's not like
they know you're the owner right they
just think of you as like oh the one who
feeds me but that's it but they're cute
to look at why does the why does the
face give me like spider Vibes though
just the face scares me you think you
could dress up a snail maybe maybe you
pain the shell honestly I feel like
that's possible that's true give it like
really cute make more attractive to
Predators right as long as we're
protecting
it brightly colored equals toxic no one
would want to eat it oh yeah yeah yeah
we are making their lives even longer by
protecting
it snail
with that huge snail oh my God if you
cook it that's so much
meat why they about cooking I am a chef
I have a cooking sponsorship I have to
think of
cooking no but ew can't e I'm going to I
do wonder what it tastes like what is
the texture of a really really large
snail e e e e e it's probably chewy m
M oh no this guy has
Health somebody I feel like you should
eat those big snails they're not they
don't oh but they're so big I would feel
bad for killing that right in front of
my face they look like they they would
be pretty rare too can you even
encounter them in the wilderness that
would be crazy imagine seeing such a
huge snail IRL randomly in a in a
garden I would
faint please leave me alone don't attack
me snail have
mercy I'm trying to find it but I found
this instead that's
cute I need to find
I what were you looking for I'm trying
to find the snails eating I don't know
where where the is a draw icon Vector
mage of a cat
snails yeah cute
it would take like six hours for it to
reach you I guess I'm not in danger then
when I encounter one if it takes so long
to reach me but who knows maybe the big
ones are faster than the small
ones they're definitely faster they got
to be faster they yeah they cover more
ground
exactly terrifying thought
that size snail is perhaps like the
accurate size if you want to have a like
a like a kind of relationship to your
snail like
SpongeBob Oh you mean Gary I found
it found what is that a snail was Gary a
snail they're eating look they're so
silly oh hold up I'll check in a
bit oh it has music okay muing it okay
yeah
oh it's kind of cute
cute they're just eating is that sped up
that's surely sped up right I think it's
sped up I don't think they eat that
bad they're really cute when they're
eating they look so happy yeah I
know people like Kiara wants to eat them
no don't worry I I I I don't even like
mushrooms how am I going to eat snails
oh true true it's kind of similar
probably in texture
or more disgusting I'll stay with uh I
like eating
snails you like eating snails have you
had yeah when I go to a French oh you
have yeah I made it really tiny it's
kind of like um the texture of what like
clams or tiny little I see they called
esar oh yeah they're like seafood but
snails ooh
oh muscles
yeah well with a lot of garlic anything
can taste good
huh and butter so much butter garlic
butter
M I do have that compound butter in my
fridge what if I combine it with the
slug in my
garden what's for dinner tonight kiaha I
think I'll make
cabonara o but like legitimate
carbonara not let's not legitimate when
you when you like add um like cream to
it you got to make it just with the um
the golden part of the eggs and uh lots
of cheese peino and uh
paragano yeah so I'm going to make it
the legitimate way cuz it actually
turned out pretty good last time I made
it and this time I have the better
cheese and
I'm I'm excited for kabara oh yeah the
bacon bacon is important I don't have
the bacon that
they ask you to use normally but I got a
good enough
bacon will you be posting pictures maybe
recently I haven't been posting pictures
because yeah I like your food photos
thank you yeah it makes you look at my
food and how I don't do
[\h__\h] yeah now makes me hungry I've I've
been taking taking a little break from
my like food subscription that sends me
the ingredients M those who shall not be
named
but but yeah now that I'm just cooking
things more on my own I'm not trying to
make them look too nice because they
usually just look nice when you have
lots of side
dishes then you can plate them up nicely
mhm but when I just cook
something like without the food
subscription I just make something
simple like the cabonara and then it
doesn't look very
special so yeah less pictures from the
wa
recently I think it's still special food
photos are beautiful a well I am doing a
cooking stream again soon finally for
the first time in a long time ooh yeah
am I
kchen whenever the things from my
sponsorship arrive ooh nice nice I'm
excited I love cooking
streams I I don't know they make me
nervous but I I want to do enough of
them that I'm not nervous anymore while
doing
them I will always be nervous for
cooking streams took me three hours to
make a stupid
hamburger
yeah I'm I think I'm nervous about the
logistics of streaming it yeah yeah
exactly that's probably the part that
makes me most nervous cuz I'm hey
there's this like level 90 dude in aen
wearing a pumpkin head nice pumpkin head
is he evil n oh he's a heroic boss he
will kill me uh-oh careful don't solo
careful oh yeah I remember smacking him
and then running away on accident Don't
Die scary pennis you're like level 71
you you could take
him careful you'll get one
shot I see but that makes it
tempting sheld oh where's the auction I
want to see cute
stuff cute clothes please oh wait I'm
already FR free what the heck I didn't
Noti this I kept on I kept on questing
for so long you are grinding I'm I'm so
oh mindlessly
grinding all right I'll finish this
little Quest though guys guys who are
around me can you just kill the the
enemies that spawn I'm just going to
kill the
stones cuz that's all I got to do thank
you next
Stone where I need more
Stones oh
here oh so
cute oh you can fight with a
kebab there's not a lot of items in the
auction though I don't think the player
base is like too
much yeah
it's not
huge
[Music]
wow that's kind of
neat all
right all right what the quest that you
got to do when you're 33 where did it go
I guess already thank you for thank you
for the money I would not be able to buy
this if
I whaty all spent I'm sorry forgive me
where where is the main
quest what did you guys do once you
reached level
33 I didn't even realize I was level 33
you said
so I just followed the quest I maybe I
have I have bought things for give me
people oh thank you thank you
Auntie look this stream is not sponsored
no no it's not you didn't Turnal
we're we're looking at you
Eden where's my head these are old well
but I only have one at a time oh you're
killing me you are killing
me
Wetlands daily
daily do where's
[Music]
Quest I hear this little
kitty your baby yeah oh wow good twirl
you so good nice trick where where's the
kitty at and leave my kitty
[Music]
alone our gu leader hey don't drive away
let me look at you
Flex nice motor
bike M oh here's the back
F level
90 wow our Guild leader level N9 how do
I unlock backpack maybe if I do
this maybe I'll go back to
the or I'll try entering the next region
maybe AA
volcano like give me more but how what
about the bank you need a bank lease to
unlock the slot oh my God the banks take
advantage of you in this game too A Bank
lease yeah to expand your uh your bank
stuff in the
game oh I got the
B guess I'll just keep expanding my
bags oh my God I appreciate it thank
you I got the main quest deep into the
valley I got to go to Soul Guardian me
too me too
why is that bringing
me I assum it's near the wetlands I
thought so too but it led me out of the
wetlands oh this is this a new area
actually yeah I think so oh new area
yipp The Valley Of
Kings that's like The Lion
King ah found poor
talk to Derek Derek
dook WF this is a
[Music]
forest
okay are we back to questing
girls yeah got talk
D Derek probably killed my family
no he didn't Derek is
Chill Derek's just trying to raise a
family of his own there are so
many daily quests in this area ignore
them
ignore I picked all of them up no just
do the
main when will you get to do these
dailies I don't know there's just a
tempting the way that they're right here
in front of
me you need to clean clean it up get rid
of it all right maybe that's the feeling
that I had yesterday when I was cleaning
everything I even used my Roomba again
do you guys have a
Roomba I do I don't I do not use it
I you should use it I need to use it
more
often my cats get upset you with it
really mine surprisingly don't care like
one of my cats she hates when I turn on
the vacuum she freaks out and runs away
into a corner but the Roomba she doesn't
mind cuz it's like not as
loud she's chilling the Roomba will make
me trip make you trip do you have a name
for your Roomba and then the Roomba is
there my Roomba it had a name I changed
it because I had to reset it up now it's
just wa
bot oh yeah not not so exting I hope
CeCe has a Roomba and it's called the
WBA the
WBA the WBA W I see I saw those tweets I
know what you're talking about oh giggy
can't have one she'll just ride it like
those cat memes says
herb is that true giggy
I no it's not true you can't be trusted
with we be
friends you can't be friends with a room
gigy no
not no no you can't they're great
friends yeah it doesn't CeCe is just
like a
Roomba why is she turning around you the
whole time like a cleaning robot yeah
just just like a
Roomba is she constantly bonking against
the wall yeah is she exactly what she
looks like is she having trouble getting
over the carpet the thick
carpet must be rough man she gets stuck
constantly on on edges and stuff and you
always have to reorient her say herb
says I she I guess you will stick 100
goggly eyes googly eyes on it only two
because it has a
face I should put I I haven't put any
eyes on my Roomba yet I should I should
I like when have costumes but I don't
have one for
mine yeah you can get them a ma outfit I
know that we talked last time we talked
about outfits for pets but if there's
room outfits I think I'm
in yeah I'm pretty sure there are might
be like an Etsy thing though
he Roomba outou that's
crazy maybe that's for people who aren't
allowed to have pets in their uh
Apartments cuz there's a lot of man I
want like a an Android some say like an
Android Butler instead of a
pet I already have a pet though they
don't they don't Butler for me all they
do is [\h__\h] on my
floor yeah what they actually [\h__\h] on
your floor one of them when they're
upset and they'll get enough attention
and oh my
God wait that's also the cat that tries
to be like dominate a dominant between
the two
sucking the other cat yeah yeah actually
it was he was the
sucker that cat is not like uh climb on
top of my smaller cat and bite him and
all that stuff to aert dominance a baby
he's a nasty cat seems pretty
nasty yeah his name is pepper why why
did he pepper why did pepper [\h__\h]
everywhere why did pepper become so
spicy I don't know he's just a big cat
how old is
pepper I think they're both like two
years now oh so young I would excuse the
[\h__\h] if he was
old no he's he's just a young Brad damn
he needs Brad
correction what are you guys talking
about in the guil
chat don't fight in Inkwell
no f are my ink Wells getting bullied
kfp are you bullying My Ink Wells not
sure what's going
on hey inkwells are good people what's
going on for killing the mobs that I
have to kill no problem I still got to
kill one more Scout though yes yes you
have to
please oh thank you Gigi for potentially
killing them I got it I got it
y we're working together ever see we
could be questing so much faster if we
were actually always on the same Quest
and not delayed by one
minute daily Quest daily
Quest I I had to come join the guild but
already play M noi Mai noi is still
going on yeah they're getting an update
too oh [\h__\h] pretty amazing though I
heard it was really good I couldn't get
into software update when it first came
out hard I I made a character but I I
don't know why what happened I was I
guess still too busy with my other
mmpg but it was pretty it was
cute I heard that you can just cook in
there you don't have to fight and you
can play music on there yeah you can
start like a
band
oh wait is this a I miss Maple Story
2 it's like actually it's so good
I want Maple Story 2 back wait so maple
story one exists but Maple Story 2 is
dead maple story for West oh yeah it's
dead for the West because we didn't pay
it enough they couldn't like it's
because to the greatest of the first one
no it was really good but I think it's
just like the grind when you get to end
game and then they weren't um go back it
wasn't really healthy and then the
player base just died a
R but it was so fun why didn't you save
it why didn't you do
anything so many you killed it you
killed maple story I I bought the $100
Founders pack was that not enough no you
should have bought the $1,000 found this
back I don't have 1,000 have $1,000
where guard he's not spawning I I see
him he just has him
nice actually questing together can't
believe it who's G hey he's dead now
don't worry about
him oh good
point I think you would lik story too me
was it 3D yeah 3D yeah 3D it's like a
little isometric I think it was so cute
wa let me look it up maybe I saw the
visuals before maple story too it it is
cute I like it that one
a I wonder what class you could have
done I think you could get two classes
as veins if that still existed I
wouldn't mind playing it
now it was so good it had so many
Community things and you could full edit
your home the only thing is that there's
like a lot of copyright stuff that
people just upload onto the game oh
okay why do they do
that no one's stopping them it's the
internet of course we have to collect
worm skin we're skinning the
worms no not the
worms it's okay I guess you didn't love
the worms enough we don't love them
enough yeah I would love you guys if you
were worms thank you I would keep you in
thear if you were worm so you'd love me
still of course in a in a way in a and
twisted way would you use would you take
photos of me and post me on the internet
would you use my worm body for Content
yeah I'd be like look at this dirty worm
so no please I have no autonomy as a
word well you could have crawled away
but you didn't when you had the
chance is it these crawl fast
enough is it any of
these they're all worms let's try do can
we skin for worm skin didn't I remember
get a
skin
okay crispy warm
skin give me
more are you also skinning the worms
girls yeah yeah I collected them all
though fin you finished already I I'm
not getting the drops okay now I'm
getting them now that you have it all
I'm getting
them it do be like that sometimes huh it
do it do
be one
more oh did Herb ride something who is
the Fus well oh he's probably an aen
again her asks would you still love me
if I did the worm worm I would love you
I would be impressed so much if you did
the worm there have been
many many people who have attempted the
worm so
far but or if you can like dance a it a
little can't she oh cuz I saw her moves
in VR chat for oh yeah I saw that too
was cute her VR chat scam with the new
model the she was wiggling less small
model she wiggle
yeah she says she
Wiggles is that your signature move herb
the wiggle the
wiggle full body
wiggle who up wiggling day
worm I'm
hungry I am too oh there's arms
here no F
worms I'll make um worms later worms in
the form of
Spaghetti O that's good my mama makes
this dish that I call worms I actually
don't know what it is NE to me I want a
photo of it the next time she makes it
you call it worm you just cut up beef
anyway and like gravy but I always call
it worms cuz it's brown
gravy I think so but like the gravy
sauce taste a little different than just
gravy what the what makes it look like
worms it's all
brown and just cut up beef that's all
brown and a lot of brown
gravy like worms are
off what am I doing here oh okay sounds
like a Michelin star restaurant dish I
need her to teach me the recipe she's
always like I'll teach you next year
I'll teach you next time you visit she
gay keeping the family recipe why she
hiding it I know she wants you to
continue relying on her for the worm
dish yeah yeah she wants to teach you it
yet she's scared that if you know it all
if you have all the knowledge you'll run
away you run off of maybe you'll even
sell a book with
it imagine what the Betrayal me who can
barely
[Laughter]
cook yeah ask yourself why can't you
bear like cook why can't you cook
because she's not teaching you yeah it's
her
fault she's not letting you into the
recipes of the family the gatekeeping is
real
mhm gatekeeping by your own mother let
her cook let her cook let her cook let
her cook let her
cook it must be said out
loud she already you need to have
courage courage to cook courage to say
it maybe you were having a dream of that
rat because of Ratatouille and cooking I
actually never watch ratat really NE you
both haven't yeah I haven't oh my God
you should maybe we should watch it
childhood I think I've actually besides
watching Shrek with Cali I don't think
I've ever been in a watch long with
anybody else so far in we should watch
would we be able to watch Ratatouille of
course we can watch anything oh wait
isn't that Disney but we can still watch
it as long as we don't like oh that's
true we can watch it and just like not
do a watch along I guess no no we can
still do a watch
watch uh can we not is it though I don't
know I don't know how it works oh well
oh well all I know is that we're
supposed to avoid like uh
jibi and probably maybe Disney too
honestly well
Disney and Jojo I just know we shouldn't
sing the songs but watching a movie
without showing the movies should be
fine I I don't know I got no clue have
changed I see I see
yeah no JoJo why no
JoJo uh I think I think someone watched
it and then they had to like stop
oh oh no well good that I'm not into
JoJo five ring flower cute Must
Destroy no flowers here oh oh it spawned
right away in the same
spot no
don't why why must you how would you
take her flower yeah right in front of
me right in front of me right in front
of her you would take her flower you are
an [\h__\h] go to the corner and think
about what you've done think about it
yes letting you guys follow me just for
you to obstruct me
next
Quest what quest are you girls on now
I'm killing mantises bloody
mantises I think I'm the one after that
I will wait I will do this
again I don't know here I will kill my
daily Quest okay where were you when
daily Quest was killed I was killing
bloody mantis
and shovel
[Music]
pinch oh will we get I actually don't
know what will happen will we get in 25
minutes an update an email kfp will we
get an email I made them sign up for the
sponsorship
emails oh there's like a like a every
day there'll be like a reveal I think of
one of the things in the lineup I think
I so the first one should be in 25
minutes I honestly don't know what
they're going to
reveal I'm excited too woohoo I'm
excited to
see I mean I've seen the the full lineup
I just don't know what they're showing
today but let me tell you there's some
exciting stuff coming up
mhm I want to see I want to I want to
know what they're revealing have you
signed up you need to enter your email
I will enter my
email so I can see what they are
releasing yeah you should I'll send you
I'll show you where you can sign up
later thank you I expect you to actually
sign up I will I'm I'm here I'm nosy I
want to see
[Laughter]
it uh defeat
Fay okay oh my tummy just went and made
a noise it went like
Hy gigy are you close to
Fay I am not close to Fay what the heck
I think she already killed Fay for me I
I killed F so face someone you summon
with like the item okay okay I did see
you just running past me Shi why how how
come you guys have already like have why
do we have delay again we want s I'll
wait on the next Quest no no no it's
fine it's
fine okay I'm
summoning okay this one we're about to
be like getting to the dungeon soon so I
wait in front all right that can be
our big thing to end on maybe okay okay
I think I need to drink some apple cider
vinegar
after oh no it's supposed to be healthy
for you I don't know if it helps a sore
throat though it might just burn away
the bacteria do you think you only have
a sore throat or something bigger like I
I currently only have a sore throat at
the moment it hurts drink hot tea with
honey oh I do but it's not hot anymore
it's just like room temperature tea with
up fous
fous I should and you should take fruit
candies I always have froat candies
right at my desk because especially in
the winter time when I read super chats
my throat is constantly
dying man we are abusing our throats
yeah can't be
helped it's our
job true I'm going to eat
loeng yes
yes yes eat it's good for
you
loeng can you like overdose on lenes or
like not death but like can you have too
much I think it probably does say on the
packaging uh that you
should maybe it depends cuz there's some
that you get from the pharmacy right I
feel like those uh some of those might
have like a tiny bit of like painkilling
something in there right I think I've
seen that before to
like get the swelling or whatever from
your throat gone I don't know yeah it
messes up your tummy but you won't die I
don't think you can overdose from throat
candies time to test that out
girl oh my quest is already finished
without me lifting a finger
nice
wow what a great freaking inventory
a this place is
beautiful talk to gray gray why did it
lead me there I clicked on
it apparently that's not where I had to
go lead us to
gray have you talked to gray already no
I'm running to right now okay
cool I just can't find zepherus
that's like the end of the quest or
something I think oh
okay yes I need to set up my humidifier
again but I don't know if it really ever
helped
me but got to bring out all the big guns
for the winter time I already noticed
like I have so much legum in my throat
again especially when I just wake up I
notice there's like m
all choking oh
yummy yeah I think that yesterday I'm
like damn I should get a humidifier near
my PC I'm cold again you should I have
like free humidifier so that I have one
in my bedroom and one in my office and
so on and air air purifiers as well I
have threee of those but I don't use
them
oo I was I was forced by my chat three
and a half years ago to buy air
purifiers because they thought or one
particular person thought that it would
help me I got one guide would did it
help no it didn't no I don't think so
but maybe it did but like0 point0 5%
impact in my life that I wouldn't
notice but they look nice I mean when
when somebody visits I could say oh look
you will have the best air in my home
because I have an air purifier in this
corner and in that corner and in this
corner too yeah they do look
cool I have one tiny air
purifier or like a humidifier and it's
of chawa and it comes out of his
brain like there a hole the top of his
head he lights up and all the the the
air comes out of it nice that's cute one
question uh I I didn't get a follow-up
Quest did you girls get one H I got one
what's it called for what
quest uh the follow-up quest after
uh uh I'm on like rotten 3 Quest right
now it's called rotten
3 ah rotten free main
party yeah single player dungeon okay it
does say party though right for me it
say yeah okay I guess so
all right I'm coming random
worms
Oh don't worry don't wor do not worry do
you have the quest uhoh do you have the
quest I do I do thank
you you didn't leave me talk I'm just
going to be a bar so I can level it up
okay let's go
yipp
into the dungeon
this dungeon looks like a worm I'm bar I
can't help look at the dungeon map it
looks like a
worm oh my God it's a worm would you
still love this dungeon if it was a worm
I don't know I can I only know it as a
worm it's a poison dungeon I think
ooh nice
[Music]
wee bugs are
cute you're cute in photos you're cute
you're cuter than any bug oh I'm glad oh
that's good it would be really worrying
if she wasn't than a
bug I've never seen a bug cuter than you
honestly there are pretty amazingly cute
bugs especially like um fluffy
um what are they called the little
fluffy worms I forgot the word for it
what think they talking about the fuzzy
ones yeah the ones before they become a
butterfly or Mo caterpillars fluffy
caterpillars are so
cute I think beetles are really cute
too yes they can be depending on some
Beetle yeah depending on the beetle
there's some some of them are really
cute yeah they can be a huge pest as
well I have I like them in photos I will
not go near one in person but I like
looking at stay away stay
away stupid
feels beet why is there a oh it's going
around in a circle I'm like why is there
a fork in the
path ooh dungeon with choices but it's
false I know it's an illusion of choice
delusion giant mths are really cute oh
yeah yeah I mean this bugs after the
fact that they're giant makes them a bit
terrifying though yeah I don't know I
don't really like flying bugs cuz they
scare me a I'm scared of butterflies a I
hate flying cockroaches oh God
thankfully I never had to deal with
them I used to like cockro roaches I
mean at least I I didn't really like
them but I thought they were kind of
like cute not as like as long as you
never encountered them right no no even
when I like saw them running around on
stre in your
home I never I never saw them in Austria
honestly but like I used to see them in
summer in Japan and I just thought well
there's no neon no reason to need no
reason to be so extremely
hysterically panicky about it is what I
thought but of course if you have it
suddenly in your home I would be panicky
too but outside is like whatever outside
it's not too bad but inside like if you
see them you got to kill them yeah they
are
pissed mhm Genie I already attacked
Genie gy what do you say once it was me
oh no wait was it after me someone kill
it
GG sorry sorry sorry wait kill Genie my
brethren Genie no
Genie goodbye good night Genie
no it's okay I got you Genie is dead
where were you when Genie was dead where
were you when Genie
die when Genie is
killed go next go
next bug que AB
I was outside the
dungeon I used to live in an apartment
and then it had cockroach problems the
month that I was live like the first
month I was there and it was so
terrifying and horrifying I woke up to
one crawling on me and it was the worst
day of my life
no okay I was like why is this happening
to me I just got here then what did you
do did you leave or I made so many
complaints um I just no longer slept in
that room and then I locked myself away
somewhere else until the problem was
fixed good good good for you I would
chase them around with a vacuum cleaner
though because I didn't know how else to
deal with them because I'm scared of
killing bugs because a what are they
what are they jump at me I can't handle
it I don't know I'm scared I don't I
can't kill a bug they're scary I'm used
to splattering their bodies on the
walls no the thought of buck guts give
me the
egg there's this one time where like uh
uh my parents home was infected by a
bunch of fruit flies and I had to go on
a killing spree and I had like 30 fruit
fly bodies by the end of that day oh my
God I also have a [\h__\h] ton of dead flies
uh well actually now the problem is
pretty much solved but the past weeks I
had a big fly infestation problem me
please AG gring this but I bought an uh
electric fly water which is so good it's
like a tennis racket and it kills all
the bugs it's so good oh it's very
helpful yeah they just fly into it so
dumb and it makes zappy sounds one more
fun zappy sounds zap zap zap yeah I like
the sound it makes when a fly runs into
it yeah oh yeah the sound of
death
beautiful thanks for waiting for us in
front of the
dungeon moving
on well gy you once had a cockroach
problem
I when I lived in Japan in the beginning
of my whole lifetime I had a rat problem
oh my God it was so like traumatizing
but then it became kind of a part of my
identity while I
was and then I was sad when I left that
house and went moved back to Austria
because no there was some weird
sentimental like connection at the end
of all of that with the rats yeah it's
weird it's a whole
thing is it ins kind of cute but no not
I I don't think they're cute or anything
but like first I was really terrified
and I wasn't feeling comfortable I
didn't want to sleep I kept on hearing
the noises the tippy tis and everything
but then basically I think the reason
why I became so attached to it it was
because at the time it was in the middle
of Corona and I was just kind of like in
a bad mental state I was just kind of
sad and alone and isolated and all that
and then um it came to the point where I
had to leave Austria
but chat made a character out of the
rats in my house and we named it cper
and they you know they just like role
played as it and they sent super chats
as that rat and I built this connection
to this Super Chat rat and connected it
to the real rats in my
home I thought this was like some
Stockholm story at first but I I didn't
expect no but for real it became so
wholesome that was the only reason why I
could bear it and I could see it also as
a funny thing whenever I came across the
rat and and and then I felt bad for like
attempting to kill it cuz like I first
got like professionals to come in trying
to solve the problem but somehow it
survived every single way CRA yeah
they're like persistent mutant rats or
so um and then I at some point I was
like okay they're not dying so I'm just
going to give up I feel bad
they they're probably already blind and
everything they're already suffering so
yeah maybe maybe they led a nice healthy
life after you were gone yeah I don't
know about that because after I was gone
the whole house was renovated so we
probably just move somewhere else you
know what what they yeah hope I hope I
hope they found a different place that
made them happy you yeah maybe they're
living at a mansion now or like some of
moved away hub
yeah yeah but I I I I don't know when I
was back in Austria those the Casp
Casper was the name of the Rat you know
and it just it just disappeared and it
was like man I miss Casper
now which is so weird because I should
be happy that the rats are
gone but somehow I it grew to me well
I'm sure Casper lives on as the
neighborhood ghost
yay no Casper's probably dead by now
let's be real well the
Casper that but I'm sure he died
happy you know the reason why I called
it Casper in the first place was because
I first was like embarrassed to even
admit that I had rats because it it made
me so uncomfortable and it seems kind of
like the place is dirty or so but it
wasn't dirty because of me it had
already a red
infestation when I moved in that's why I
got it so cheap but yeah so I was like
pretending that I had
ghosts whenever I heard a noise I was
like oh the ghost's in my ceiling and
eventually I said it out loud I think
like oh the rats and then it was like
okay the
rats yeah but we kept the Casper name
cuz Casper is a ghost name yeah that's
true that's true yeah yeah it's not your
fault it's always the apartment's fault
cuz they should have dealt with that
yeah but I got it through uh like
connections really cheap so you know it
it was kind of a emergency solution cuz
when I joined Holo I was living in like
a Japanese one room apartment that has
the finnest wall ever super cheap and
you can hear but even when I was
whispering like this the neighbors were
knocking on the wall when I was speaking
like this I swear to God they should get
over themselves
I was like how the [\h__\h] am I going to
stream here so I I I really needed a a
quick solution to this where I could
talk like a normal person so I got a
house that was really
lucky yeah temporary house that was so
stressful temporary home with
friends yeah the friends are the rats
yeah the friends that's the
rat the friend that is the rat yeah you
know I you ever just get a pet rat at
this point to to recall the days with
that rat I was like what you got a rat
in Casper would that be cute I was
thinking if I um if only I brought my
cats with me to Japan for that one year
then maybe the cats would have taken
care of the
Rat what if they were too lazy to hunt
it and they just become
they well my cats do try to hunt bugs
when they see them so I feel like they
would have tried hunting the rat Maybe
could they hunt slugs actually why are
we back to slugs why are we full
circling back to
slugs everything circles back to slugs
at some
point the world is a slug yeah y
yeah this makes me think of
man everything circles back it it really
does it came Circle back to the slug see
that's like good storytelling right
there they have the beginning and then
it's actually the ending but you didn't
know isn't that what they did with
berserk
actually not that I ever watched it I've
never seen it I want to see it but I'm
too lazy to see it I just feel like
there's a lot of Classics I need to
watch or read but I I'm
lazy yeah that's like dedicating time to
actually pay attention and
focus when I can be mindlessly playing
some other
game I feel like black and monari you
have to have so much Focus yes true
they're always talking that's true you
need a lot of focus but the good thing
is if you don't watch it in a watch
along like I do you can just pause it
and reread the subtitles and everything
just take your time with it relisten to
the dialogue whenever you feel like oh I
zoomed out oh my
God I can't I used to do that when I
first watched it I paused the anime so
many
times cuz I can there so much
to I consume I guess to take in
yeah and they have so much hidden
dialogue in in the scenes also in the
anime like they quickly switch and they
give you like half a second to read it
cuz they're not thinking you will read
it but if you're watching it you're just
there to listen to the Japanese ASMR
yeah no but I will stop it I will read
every
dialogue it's important to read
yes how will you see all the
secrets mhm you check the
Wikipedia or like the tropes page is
like oh TV TR
yeah I go on red and I'm like can
someone tell me all the Easter eggs in
every
episode they're flexing in the guilt
chat are they flexing you
got from what I don't know
gambling
gotcha turn away from from
Goa stop ging it's wrong for
you I don't want to hear that from
you everyone nobody can take you
seriously stop spending money on Roblox
it's not
right freaking Roblox yeah give the
money to Gigi so she can spend it on
Roblox so I can spend money on
Roblox no why let's
SP sponsorship I don't know Roblox
sponsor got to be Roblox do they sponsor
anybody at
all I don't know actually they don't
need to because all the kids are giving
them the money from their mother's
credit
card they don't need
sponsorships Roblox sponsors Roblox it's
her childhood I guess life is Roblox
can't relate I I didn't even grow up
with Roblox I started playing like two
years
ago maybe even a year
ago well what got you like into it and
what made you stay though there has to
be a reason you stayed is it the
community there I do not talk to anyone
when I open my
Roblox I don't it's the gcha the gacha
is what's making me stay I started with
Beast War simul
and I played so much of be swarm and it
made me so
unproductive be
swarm yeah the whole purpose of beeswarm
is that you have a bunch of bees and you
have to collect honey and then you have
to increase your hive or make your hive
larger so you can collect more honey and
that's it that's the entire
game sounds cute it is riveting how on
the graphic there's nothing else
Roblox oh I have this much inventory
what the
heck
yeah my inventory is so full my
inventory is so
disgusting
yeah I need a pack
mule but that's
inscription we're go kill a Cy in Ultra
Hall me too this is another dungeon
really we already at the next
dungeon I have I'm only at Cam's group
ambition number five defeat God that's
okay we can wait for you we'll kill
things so you can also level up
[Music]
okay I'm just leveling up my b anyway
can you kill
gador I don't I don't know who that is
you must have killed him already gor
gor the V
drop what is it what is it I need to
check my
emails did they also tweet it out I
wonder or is it just email only
gatekeeping my businesswoman kiawa wait
I think it's in my spam folder check
your spam
folders oh my [\h__\h] God I can't
believe what I just just found in my
spam
folder spam spam click here for hot
women now hey sexy I saw that you um
uh need
aot need hot woman or you want a
raffle you know when I was in Japan I
was setting up my my computer and I
think I was trying to download like some
song because I actually needed it for
work and it didn't provide it for me and
in the midst of downloading it from like
YouTube uh I think I accidentally
enabled something and ever since that I
would get notifications of hot woman in
your
area I was like did I just go to
you um in anything actually I would get
random popups out of nowhere like
notifications I had to go back to the
site that I accidentally allowed um
notifications from
you allowing viruses onto your computer
your work computer well at least it
wasn't my
computer their
computer
yeah someone's going to get that
computer what if I get that computer no
I'm sure they fix I fixed it I fixed it
it should have been fixed
theoretically but but you'll know if it
was my computer if it has a picture of
the Mei that's like shirtless
open should changed it though I told
them to I told them to change it if they
didn't it's their
fault shirtless Demitri what are you
doing here on my
[Laughter]
PC I feel like a indirect connection to
you shi because of your love for Demetri
it's like so close you know that Meme
with the cars passing by and you look
out of the the window and you're like
what the heck looking at the person in
the other car do you know that Meme yeah
that's what I the Umbrella Academy scene
that's what I feel like with with uh shy
because you love Dimitri but I love I
love like adelard and whoever oh are you
obsessed with
Ard maybe more what was her name sopus
sop is that maybe I like the most oh the
the green woman yeah the bare feet girl
the goddess yeah but in any case the
girls you
know yeah yeah I like sis but it's kind
of sad because she's technically just in
your head and she'll always be in your
head
yeah sad like this is some weird
relationship no she's real she's real to
me Petra Petra well
Petra I'm salty towards
Petra why did she kill someone like in
the game I was playing the the Ard route
right and the like all the uh students
that you can get um mhm like pretty much
every girl I talked to was open to
marrying uh the girl protagonist cuz I
was playing the female protagonist
except for the one that I was pursuing
Petra that she was the only one who was
like completely straight and I was like
what the heck
why are you breaking my heart you like
you don't I actually I hate it when the
routes are gender locked it's like come
on I just want to play my game yeah and
I was opening
my you need to like that I
can spacial
conversion yipp oh oh my [\h__\h] god is
this the
right yeah no it's okay it's okay I can
do it I can do it I I know how to do I
was already linked to the right one you
fool I didn't even realize it looked the
same to
me
good this I linked my soul what would
would do without
you I know you would be so
lost okay let's defeat
Kenny yay Kenny
where is Kenny always
being oh I remember this
place this is you definitely need a
Healer for this I will not be the healer
for this I a level of my stuff this is a
hard one I will try to heal them okay
okay uh what's which one's heal this
one a this wait why am I oh crap they
like me more I have so many memories
here
yeah it's a good dungeon use my as I try
to level up my stuff
skills isn't this dungeon reused for
something else though cuz I remember
using it in the like end game a
lot maybe like the acid spur why they
sleep me
so far only healed
shieldy it's because they keep coming
after why don't they get attracted to
Gigi me who is the one agroing them but
they come to you you're so delicious
looking look at you yes so I don't look
like a strong
[Laughter]
urine they're terrified of the strong
urine goodbye yeah too strong for
them thank you for the heals you're
welcome maybe I don't even need to
constantly heal maybe I'll just uh
attack in
between CH why you up
there that's so I don't have to go down
there magic
boost attack
we are strong I'm pulling more no no be
careful gigy for real I'm pulling them
gyin they can't hurt
me man if Gigi was a fire emblem
character I think she would die in
classic Mode pretty
fast you I'm like the one that's in the
middle and you have to come to me in
order to save me in like EX amount of
turns or I die oh no wait you have
fireemblem experience what the heck I
know of it I've played
some I haven't played through three
houses though I only know through
osmosis but I played some others I
really like free houses I need to finish
Awakening I'm just stuck on it I was not
a big fan of Awakening craw bin wait
that was the newest one right Awakening
no that's old engage is the newest one
ah engage that's the one that I mean
that wasn't yeah I finished that one I
like the game play not so much the
characters and the story
though free houses is where it's at for
me but I only played those two so I
guess I
shouldn't I'm sure there's better ones
for Fire Emblem fans I'm sure they're
going to say but this game was the best
but I want to self insert it's not the
same if I
can't stay Bo they're
like GG you're so
funny what do you mean is my
noises I I guess so you're like an
8 I can't focus I have it's okay oh [\h__\h]
that's a boss that's a boss come here
T oh oh that's not even Kenny what the
heck yeah
oh do we oh we only have to kill meant
to be extinct uhoh what if we have to
kill tmad again it's okay oh we might oh
no oh
shoot
you MP what is
this stop hitting
me good job hopefully Kenny at hopefully
only Kenny is necessary but that would
make no sense kind of
actually where even is Kenny I think in
the middle of this I remember this
dungeon good old time yourself
[Music]
Kenny there's one on this side and
there's one on the other side left side
of this circle oh healing please yes
don't worry I got you I got
you Kenny you better be over here
or we will be
mad this dungeon is so much more
difficult when you don't play it
solo I remember this was high level
stuff what the
heck it it was high level but Solo's
just like so different now I
guess man you need some
MP MP
Elemental Guardian
[Music]
Kenny I pulled
him all right he died
now I'm out of
MP AR I'm dying for some reason oh I'll
heal you it's okay I'm okay I'm
balancing oh whoa whoa oh he keeps
having a oh oh but he's dead oh
oh that's good what happened who do we
talk to going to
autop oh it doesn't say anything about
pulling everything you're pulling
everything I'm on the autop paath we
don't have to kill the the the
dinosaur yeah that should be like the
next
Quest that will be another
time is like killing Charles three times
again there's Excalibur over there wow
oh yeah that's another boss yeah there's
three bosses in this dungeon
[Music]
actually do you want us to kill them now
H oh Jesus Christ they all came for you
GG yeah the quest now says kill
T the dragon the
dinosaur I'm going to oh good God I for
your
mistake well uh I will I will we reset
the dungeon
cuz we had to kill might as well oh wait
let me let me talk to skirt really quick
okay I I I'll kite them away I'll kite
them away don't worry I keep on Aging
them back to me by healing myself and
you oh no you're running out of
[Laughter]
mp2 fight them don't fight them I paid
for okay we'll fight them but yeah we
might have to reer real sister
H okay I have to run back there I'm just
going to run back why why do they do
this why don't they give us all those
bosses as Quest goals right away oh no
oh it's fine I'll die wait do we get
like
exp problems are you already I don't
think so oh are you already back in the
dungeon girls yeah we're in the
beginning the dungeon I think you're
about to kill me I just want to go to
stir
um I guess I'll
die okay I'm still in combat okay hold
up let me let me have him kill me wait
should should we should we exit right
I'm going to
exit okay I will exit then no no you
should get the quest I'll help you where
are
you I killed myself you didn't accept
the quest yet oh okay yeah the Earth
Quest yeah cuz I I had to die for chii
since no
all right all
right do you are are you in the dungeon
again I yeah yeah we'll do it we'll do
it we get the quest I'm here what you
guys want some
healing yes please I'm
hurt
cure
cure thank you okay let's go
St I would heal you if you're not if you
wouldn't be running away
what they running to Ty GG so you run
this
way I mean I assume it loops
around yeah he he's closer to the
left full party wipe yay we did
it
ow what the heck KY stop
running we're in trouble here
I'm just going to run I'm going to run
please I'm following you st why are you
so
far uh which one do I want I think this
one looks
nice okay I can go to tmat now okay uh
shall we try to clear these mobs and
then exit normally
or I I mean we we'll see
uh are
you oh you want to die okay why she not
sorry I have killing oh is giggy
muted yeah
oh
okay you're fine don't be so
dramatic you're
fine uh oh her mother her mother
father wait
tell your mom I said hi can your mom
hear us well she's playing a video game
and
multitasking mommy sorry
[Music]
Mommy I've become all shall we go to the
entrance now yeah please
please oh I cannot teleport from here
that sucks
zooming why is she already te- posing in
the back I don't know today I just can't
my dominance yeah I can't see I'm
actually a Christmas
tree yeah I already put up my Christmas
tree is my tree have you ever seen a
goth Christmas
before yeah you guys are so
un UN unupdated about what's what's hype
and and and uh cool these
days okay so it has been
reset yeah H let's do
this uncultured there yeah yeah if I'm
I'm so uncultured that I can't even
remember these words
oh I can't wait for this attack I lik
it level
up was that me or was that ni
nice oh GG's not back yet I guess no
we're
inside oh okay I'll be I'll be in there
I'm using a useless class right now by
the way just letting you
know oh my God my inventory is full oh
[Music]
I want to level up all my
classes bless you bless you oh thank you
so
much maybe I should do this later what
what I doing
now no let me drop the item I like ous
class
[Music]
what class do I need to level up thanks
for the membership
yippee
okay this is going well so
[Music]
far maybe we could ignore Kenny maybe we
can go around Kenny yeah yeah we can
this time but there's a third boss I
think after killing Tiamat we have to
get the Quest for the third third one
too possibly well let's kill him first
but he's
wandering oh yeah there's
um the camela people mhm yeah he's like
just walks in a circle yeah we have to
go it's like all like on the opposite of
where we are
now let's go that way on our
[Music]
way Me guitar impression turkey man I
just like zoning out to this like I'm
not even
thinking that's the right way the MMO
grind yeah it's sweepy
sweepy
Kenny Kenny no not Kenny
TI yeah come here we're killing all your
dragons dinosaurs and then we'll kill
you next if you feel like it it's in
clockwise
no should be we get there uh should we
go towards him instead of because the
enem is already cleared at least if we
go that way partially and then he goes
around
again around the world around the world
oopsies I need to stop typing in chat by
accident around the world
where are
you ra
XD I'm so close oh that's not
him he must be bigger he must be more
Show Yourself T mat
I see oh he's right there he's right
there yeah yes
attack kill don't let him breathe no
longer oh no why are he always after me
stab his toes oh
shoot oh shy shy I heal you don't run
wait where's
yeah where is he running
hello what what's happening did he did
he just despawn what
yeah oh he's he's over there he's over
there why it reset he got team reset ah
we brought him too far in his
Circle that's so dumb we H he got he
should have a
better okay okay okay don't oh he's
always after me huh okay don't worry I
got you I got you to
gy
Y what is
this I don't know but I'll
greed no no no I want to pick up the oh
let's talk to St
again damn you st for making us do
this oh I like the required level
okay oh my
now we got to kill snap turtle gamra
snap turtle
gamra yeah I think she's inside yeah
right here wa I'm talking to her first
BRB okay we'll just kill the
mobs level
up okay TG I can't heal you just let you
know it's okay we'll go at one one at a
time healer's coming
[Music]
I am
here nice
nice I just like hearing the random
guitarist
right I'm doing a concert for you
guys well
well oh
the cat climbed up the pillar snap
turtle
camra count your
days okay okay I'm here I'm
here you will die to our
wand to our combined vtu
power oh man why is it always after
me I'm just a sister of the cloth we did
itah we did it we we have to reach level
38 now
whyo it's okay it will be the problem
of ourselves from the
future future us problem
yes okay we'll leave it at that I think
yeah that was a good
run thank you think we did like three
dungeons today yeah productive
day yeah thank you for for the Eden
eternals I saw you playing Eden again
this week
shy yeah for mambers oo how you want a
level you want to
grind I I can yeah I mean I'm going to
be going on a trip soon so during that I
don't know how much grind then I'll be
doing that's fine I think I'm also on a
little trip this next or next next week
so wee trip
buddies
Spa ooh a spa yeah oo sounds so good I'm
so excited yeah yeah so everybody take
care of yourselves J I hope you get well
soon thank I let you know if I didn't
die thank
you I need you we need you for our eaten
Eternal Endeavors don't die you just
want me for my healing that's all I am
to I want you for your sweet
body I see I see you would love me if I
turn into a worm I would I would let you
crawl on me I want to keep you in the
jar
okay thank you also for the viewers who
participated again today hope you're
having fun
everybody we'll see you soon for more
eat of the Chan I think I'll read a few
super chatos so goodbye girlies all okay
byebye have a nice goodbye
everyone than for guys
goodbye
okay
yeah yeah yeah yeah the girls wanted to
uh go a little bit shorter today cuz she
already throat hurt and gigy has some
stuff to do so no problemo we were still
really efficient and
now wait I was trying to download the
video so I can show it on
stream let's try to download it from
Twitter
ah
oopsie this
one cuz I haven't seen it
yet cuz I was streaming don't know about
you guys but oh she already ra thank you
I'm about to watch the
[Music]
video downloading now there it is okay
CH it might be loud for a second but
I'll pause it immediately the accounting
department these uniform sorry I forgot
how to pause for a moment was that very
[\h__\h]
[Laughter]
loud I warned you though I warned you I
tried to warn
you okay okay this is the second video
for the collaboration
ation that is going on with me and Vite
let's see what this one's all
[Music]
about let me put it behind myself there
we go okay here we
go Department these uniform expense
reports don't make sense how do they
lose so many office supplies but their
uniform budget keeps decreasing
she's
serving angel and devil
F taking the
crown cute pineapple steep stream SP
I tick ties who who gave they must have
like gone to the kfp Discord or
something to ask for things to write on
this uh
wall let me check over here first I
think the bottom left is probably that's
all covered with boxes never mind it's
all locked up up inside man I hate this
it's all the
same um I don't know what to do with
this mess just tell me the cost wait I
don't know what to do with this tell me
the C be
good
no he's Sing lyrics again what about
that was really smooth though
now we're getting somewhere I might have
not noticed if it wasn't your eyes only
do not upload being so recent kfp
n002 this is it this is exactly what
we're looking for stop stealing my
face wait hands off what this why are
there so many incidents what you find
office supplies and furniture out of the
pockets of this don't reveal this
doesn't make any sense I don't okay
anyway I'm uploading these files to you
now but I should
where all right that's my que wait what
are these voices got everything s time
to move where should we go next and wait
do you hear those female voices in the
background BS running out of room for
all this
J no that's not mean that's some extra
voice actors I think it's other vtubers
but I I can't tell it was kind of quiet
there so many in we're running out of
room for this supplies and furniture out
of the pockets of this this doesn't make
any sense I don't it's not me or is it
anyway I'm uploading these files to you
now but I
should all right that's my quue got
everything done time to move where
should we go next that's not me wait how
did I get these coupons anyway yeah out
of for all this J
but so what we're not we're not uh
finding out yet they're not showing
pictures yet of ah man I have to hold
back even
longer
[Music]
no I thought wait I thought we would
see it's in the email it's in the email
do I have the email now let's see
[Music]
uh where's where where didn't I sign up
with
this
spam no I don't have have
it show me that I signed up
[Music]
actually what if you sign up after the
first email was sent out do you still
get
it I checked spam let me sign up
again okay
the
apron did the apron get
shown I
don't yeah I'll have to live without the
email but uh what does it did they show
a picture I want to show the picture on
the screen can you send it to me on on
Twitter I don't know what they put in
there into the
email show it to me
kfp show it to
me I don't know what you're
seeing I checked the promotions
tab
bro it's not
there we can't it's
secret we're literally having all of our
internal information leaked right now
kfp this is a dire situation send it to
me okay I think I have something in
my oh whoa okay you sent me the whole
email thank you oh my God okay can I
show this whole
email is this
okay
ta let's take a look at this email
because I I didn't get the
email white Ramen I just don't get it
you know I'm in the accounting
department and it just doesn't make
sense office supplies are constantly
being lost but the uniform budget is
decreasing ah out of time I got to move
let me know where we're headed next uh
where did these coupons come from here's
a do here I found something's very awful
about this place and we need to get to
the bottom of
it it's a new apron the Kik key apron no
don't reveal my
plans for all the people who couldn't
get the apron back in the days because
it was one of the First Merch items ever
this one has two pockets
wow description a cheerful colorful
service apron in kfp colors with Tik
ties that happen to be adjustable oh
that's what you mean with
ties and many useful Pockets standard
issued to all kfb class HT members
optional smaller Kik key aprons
available for reclassified class seat oh
there's two sizes notable observations
multiple reports of pockets containing
items not previously stored
statistically significant increase in
reports of
compliments upon wearing testing
equipment shows only cotton blend
despite documented anomalies H bottom
left bottom left pocket consistently
most reliable for item retrieval
statistically significant increase in
ability to Surf upon where oh surf
surf notes team member C6 223 discovered
receipts containing weak old order
tickets carbon dating suggests tickets
from future shift schedule research
division team member represented with
the usual for not understanding how
carbon dating works I don't understand
what this what any of this means results
inconclusive carbon dating machine
manufacturer refused return and ref
refund of carbon dating machine I feel
like I'm reading uh fallout emails right
now I hacked into some computer and I'm
reading the emails for the
lore oh it's for
archaeology during initial test
deployment of kfb UN O2 team member C
8832 achieved previously unachievable
serving levels subsequent investigation
revealed uh the members tick ties had
automatically adjusted to configuration
optimal for service team member insists
they were taking the crown during Peak
serving impact but could not adequately
explain how they arrived at the
conclusion or the mythology behind it h
training department requests footage of
the incident but were denied upon
suspicious of uh suspicions of ulterior
motives
sus team member 4245 reached into pocket
for permanent marker retrieved fully
assembled and stocked office supply
cabinet that delayed an impendent uh
lunch service team member 4245 severely
reprimanded for causing impendence
during service and sent to the usual
room subsequent attempts to replicate
phenomenon produced only normal pen
never permanent markers and free expired
coupons for the defunct Phoenix Burgers
office supply cabinet was never found
after that service remains missing C
related regarding displacement of items
additional notes of aprons appear to
develop additional properties based on
length of service senior team members
report increased pocket capacity and
enhanced
confidence research division unable to
determine if confidence boost is
anomalous or simply the result of having
someone to hide hands during awkward
conversations
cute so yeah yeah yeah yeah the first
item has been revealed it's a new
apron but um I would say that's the
only item the only like merchandise
thing that I have in the form produced
before but yeah two pockets w
who
[Music]
yipp so we are going to get daily
updates yeah probably the the things
that I'm most excited for are probably
towards the end they're probably
gatekeeping them
damn it how many are there many yeah
there's going to be a whole novel
written by the end of
this so I hope you voted because once
again you can vote for the next item to
be
revealed uh I voted for it now that I
entered my email
again but it says one out of nine on the
video so
you uh one of the nine for this one yeah
so I think the math tells us there's
nine
items
nine so
many nine
products no way and we've only seen one
so far
no you have to vote go vote for my next
item to be revealed this was the O2
right I think I voted for o O3 last
time and it became O2 because you guys
voted mostly for O2
apparently I voted for O3 again I don't
even know what it
is don't look don't look ah you have to
reenter email every really
really maybe just for the sake of vote I
guess it won't make a difference you'll
just
yeah yeah just
re-enter the same
email I don't know where mine went it
just disappeared into the void okay
let's go
to here
maybe oh
small I'm going to read some super chats
but I'm really hungry so I I can't bear
it too long and
also kind of exhausted from today I have
a cut on like
the inside of my hand on the inside of
one of my fingers in the crease of a
finger
it
hurts I cut myself with grass can you
believe it I've never cut myself with
grass before but I like kind of yanked
it too
too
excitedly too much power in my
yank and it's cut in the crease
man
why yeah they were really long please
wear gloves I need to buy gardening
gloves I need to buy so much [\h__\h] I
bought uh gardening like uh Edge
trimming shears scissors
um and I I I I um let me show
you so normal
scissors let me use my pen
normal sensors just look like this right
and then there are smart people who
produced smart
shears for this kind of work where I
don't know it kind of like
is I don't know how to draw this but you
know what I
mean it's like
uh cuz you you must imagine you're
like uh squatting
here that's me squatting honestly most
of the time I was kneeling on the ground
because the grass is so low on the
ground so it's so much easier with a
scissor that's shaped like this yeah
where I don't know how to explain
this you don't you do know what I'm
talking about right okay good but I I
didn't get one of these why do they even
sell normal shaped ones in the first
place I don't understand because it was
so difficult with this one it was so
difficult and then I'm left-handed so
first of all I have to get into awkward
positions because of the unideal shape
and then I noticed
that the fact that it's a right-handed
scissor makes it even more difficult so
I I had to use both of my hands for most
of it until I I kind of got a bit of a
better feeling for it and then I was
able to kind of cut through it with one
hand H but yeah I was cramping up my
hands my hands were so weak after it but
I just wanted to get it done in one
go and it it felt good at least I got it
done and now it looks all clean and nice
and ready for my visitors
I I'm I'm trying to keep everything
really nice and clean and finish up some
last things I I ordered uh a lamp for
the bathroom cuz there's still an
exposed um light bulb over the mirror
that I recently finally put
up um I bought new sheets for the guest
bed now I need to check if I need to buy
like a futon or so because there's two
people visiting visting um or if one of
my I think I have an air mattress still
so I hope it works still but yeah new
sheets and I bought new Cutlery and I
bought more plates and stuff because I
noticed when it's not just me then I run
out of plates and Cutlery a little bit
sometimes
I'm such a panic cleaner well I still
have a lot of time but just ahead of
time I've been cleaning just for my own
satisfaction too I guess cuz uh feels so
nice now when it's clean and I most of
the time I don't have the motivation at
all to even get out of bed but I've been
catching those few rare moments where I
do have
motivation small amount of motivation to
do something and once I get started I
but once I get the ball rolling it's
rolling there's no better feeling than
making a nice place for you guys I
really hope they will
feel comfy and will feel like it's a
nice place to stay in I hope
[Music]
so I hope
so got to make
it
pretty going to cook for them maybe once
or twice
but I don't know I want to take them out
to nice restaurants if
[Music]
possible yeah it's going to be less
stressful for me
too but I don't know maybe we can even
do a cooking
stream I'm going to test out my setup
for V hopefully before they come I I
bought a new microphone
for cooking stream I don't want to use
that old one anymore it's like way too I
don't know the Acoustics of that I don't
like it so I bought a new one got to
test it out it's not like the most
expensive thing but it seemed pretty
good for what I want to
do yeah teach them how to make an
awesome dish yeah or they could teach me
we could do like a teaching exchange if
but
uh well
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah you kind of already
[Laughter]
knew
yeah yeah um panic
[Music]
you know you
know damn it damn it I keep on feeling
like I'm going to get baited in on
Twitter yesterday I was on Twitter
looking at replies and stuff and I see
like a few people asking questions about
shipping um and I was like literally
riding out my answers but they were
asking specific questions like one
person was asking if a specific type of
item can be shipped and I'm like taing
out the answer and then in the like at
the end of it I'm catching myself like
oh wait if I answer this I'm implying
I'm confirming the
implication that this will be part of
the lineup oh [\h__\h]
oops so I deleted my reply before I sent
it but I was so close to sending it and
that happened like twice to me yesterday
so but um generally what I can say is um
shipping is going to be available for
most places most European countries too
um and uh I also asked about uh South
Korea because it wasn't on the list that
they sent me and they said like oh yeah
it's a bit it might be a bit difficult
for some like particularly maybe one of
the items of the lineup but um even if
that one item can't be shipped the other
items in the lineup should be
okay so we'll see we'll see and you guys
got to check if if if you put things in
the shopping cart later on and it says
not no shipping available maybe it's
only because of one particular
item uh that might make it difficult but
uh the countries where it should just
be okay for
everything are quite a
[Music]
few so America obviously UK Canada
Australia Germany France Japan Italy
Spain Netherlands Belgium Sweden Norway
Denmark Finland Austria Poland Romania
Portugal Ireland Croatia Greece Bulgaria
Philippines Thailand Vietnam India Laos
and New Zealand so okay there's
obviously still places missing
but uh it can be looked
into
yeah and especially I know for he no
Switzerland ah maybe you have friends in
Germany or so that you can send to maybe
maybe
yeah but perhaps if you guys are like oh
man why no shipping to this country I
think cuz I asked about Korea and they
were like oh yeah um we can look into it
we can try we can see what we can do
they seem pretty open to extending their
shipping list if it's in possible in
terms of customs and so on so just uh
type them a message on Twitter Maybe and
be like
hey shipping to my country please and
maybe maybe they can look into it but
for Korea I already asked yeah so maybe
maybe maybe they're going to try cuz I
know there's some you know kfp in Korea
Garden Park
Honolulu yeah for you I asked for you
H yeah I hope everybody can get it I'm
just glad that most of seemingly most of
what what countries are
missing seemingly most of
Europe
yeah is available so no
Lam H why I wonder do you guys have
strict
Customs must be a reason why
yeah I don't think I heard
Hungary yeah Hungary doesn't seem to be
included either
H maybe you can ask
friend or again try to ask them on
Twitter yeah they need to research each
country and I think I think there's
possibility to add more countries onto
that list if you just show them that
there is
[Music]
demand Brazil has a lot of taxes on exp
well we do too in Europe honestly
especially in Austria I'm surprised like
where's the problem with other countries
I
[Music]
wonder but again it might just be a
matter of one specific item cuz I think
that list is um
about is for countries that really would
accept any of the items in the lineup I
think Italy yeah Italy is
okay let's go
[Music]
Italy geek Jack no we're not talking
about geek Jack we're talking about Vite
they're shipping separately this is not
this is not uh like whole life organized
merchandise
this is from Vite and they're shipping
from
America can't wait to see everything in
the collab I can't wait either I wonder
what they'll reveal
tomorrow I don't even I don't know I'm
also on my tippy
toes I'm excited so let's read a few
super chats so that uh I can then go and
cook some food cuz I'm so
hungry I'm so hungry
um my
drawing
um I'm so
[Music]
hungry why am I so
hungry your pot pie is in the oven pot
pie
chicken pot
pie pot pie alone sounds like you know
Stoner
pie so yeah yeah I want I was Wonder I
thought you guys would be really excited
cuz you guys have been recommending me
uh Breaking Bad for a long time I
started watching it really randomly cuz
I felt like watching something new I
haven't seen
before uh but I didn't I was not in the
mood of continuing Arcane I I have
commitment no not commitment I have I
have I think I'm scared when I really
like a show that's really also like a
good show then I don't want it to end so
I stall watching it so I started
breaking
bad it's really
good the GD right oh thank you Legend Of
Z okay the last one okay
[Music]
so I really don't understand so I I
don't understand how are they going to
make Five Seasons out of that it it
looked like they
had
like like I'm like so he just in where I
am he just revealed to his family that
he's got cancer he finally said so but
generally it seems like he wants to he
he was he was so clo obviously he's
going to go back to it cuz he needs the
money for the treatment I assume that's
why he's going to go back to it I
haven't seen him really getting back to
it but he seems very close to it um but
then how is he not going to get in
trouble for Five Seasons when they were
so in trouble already in the first three
episodes and his uh brother-in-law is
literally already like on his like back
sniffing sniffing basically how is this
going to go for Five Seasons I don't
understand how are they going
to is he going to be making drugs for
Five Seasons that's so sad too he was
like really close to to fixing his life
already just saying [\h__\h] that I'm not
doing that anymore because that led me
into this path
spiraling is is see watch and see but I
don't okay just ah I want to know I'm
just I'm worried about him he can't be
doing this for Five
Seasons it only gets worse
no
[Music]
no no he had a way out once he took care
of all the
bodies it felt so bad for him when you
know they were bonding in the in the
basement and he was making sandwich
and you know they were bonding and I
also felt like
okay this seems rather
genuine but then he insanely intelligent
genius moment when he yeah looks through
the trash through the plates and real
sorry for people who didn't watch it who
will not understand what I'm saying like
when he puts the puzzle pieces together
I'm like damn he a stroke of Genius
there like looking through that I did
find it weird when he fell down and the
break the the brake PLO the PLO break
the plate broke there you
go uh the
break what the plate
broke
the when the plate broke got to say it
slowly the plate broke and then the guy
gets up
but I'm like what are you going to do
you can't move but he there's this this
moment of
silence but we don't see him taking it
and it also doesn't really look like he
can reach it but I guess he did reach it
the plate broke what
the the PLO
break the blade broke the blade PLO what
that there it is again
[Music]
he could reach him with his foot yeah I
guess but then what did what did he get
up
for
weow such a sucker he he he had his
trust he could have gotten out without
dying but he had to but also at the same
time no but he did still want to kill
him didn't he cuz like I was giving him
the benefit of the doubt that at the
time when he took the the the piece of
the BL
plate he was maybe still planning on
killing him but then after that whole
conversation maybe then he feels bonded
enough and sorry
for um the guy what's his name
again you know that even if he still had
the plate in his pocket now he wouldn't
feel like killing him
anymore but he did seemed like he was
going to go for
it looking back on this when you finish
the series is going going to be
wild I wonder you guys have who who
watched the whole thing in the chat who
watched all of Breaking
Bad so many oh my
God so I'm literally just talking about
the first four
episodes is this funny to you
from your
POV
yeah couldn't get for the first season
it's really sad I was hoping it would
keep the balance of being sad and like
concerning but also still funny but
right now it's not really
funny but that's fine I'm okay with it
it's
interesting better call solid is even
better all right good I have something
to watch afterwards afterwards too then
it gets funny again
okay Alo there's some humor sprinkled
okay good
good how but if if his brother is
already like susing him
now obviously he's going to find out
like
soon bro I I do think I saw pictures
before of Walter um bald in an
orange uh outfit so I think I saw it
before so I do think I know that he's
ending up in jail
eventually which is pretty obvious like
how can you avoid jail for Five Seasons
when you at that
point hazm suit no it looked like a
prison prison
suit guys all right all right I'm like
I'm giving you a big opening to spoil me
but you're not doing okay maybe maybe I
misremember you know but how I don't
even understand how he can't end up in
jail well okay let's leave with at that
stop talking to Chad okay but I'm
impatient I'm worried about him like I'm
already like I'm already like so
invested in his
well-being but also oh my God
he only got this one doctor telling him
that he's got really Advanced lung
cancer and he's going to die and then I
understand that you're like doing weird
[\h__\h] even though I wouldn't go for that
but I understand that you're like okay
whatever [\h__\h] my life but then later
when they're with the the whole family
and they're like you know what we're
going to we're going to take care of
this Walter we're going to get all the
best doctors but you know first thing to
do is to get a second opinion and in
that
moment they showed Walter's like face
and I was wondering if he was thinking
the same thing as I was thinking like oh
yeah right wait a second I should get a
second
opinion right wait what wait a second
what if I get a second opinion and then
it turns out I can't live and I've
spiraled down this [\h__\h] of
a Insanity that was absolutely not not
necessary because I only did that
because cuz I thought I was going to die
anyway in a couple
years really should have just gotten a
second opinion before immediately going
down that
path but
also there was this one moment
where uh who was it I I think um the guy
that he ended up
killing uh asked him uh why are you
doing this anyway or somebody asked him
why are you doing doing this anyway and
they're like uh basically putting the
words into his mouth like for money and
he's like yeah of course
that but not for money to uh leave
behind for your family or so was the
implication and he's like yeah yeah but
I don't even think that's what his fault
was when he started doing that he just
wanted to do like he felt like really
depressed and and lost and like
pointless
when he knew he had cancer and he was
going to die and he was living this
shitty life with all these jobs that
were treating him like
[\h__\h] and then he saw the glimpse into
the
other side that he has never seen before
and he was like [\h__\h] it like I'm going
to look into that because that looks
kind of fun with my knowledge and like
for him it doesn't it's not about the
money at all at least in in that first
like his decision to go there in the
first place is not for money I think
maybe later on because he needs to pay
for his treatment I suppose but at first
it's really just
about like how meaningless his life
seems to him in that moment and what's
the point of continuing this when I'm
dying anyway yeah I understand it I got
a good understanding don't worry don't
worry so he lied there when he was like
yeah yeah of course because of that
because he doesn't want to go into it he
doesn't want to he he cuz that's a good
reason to pretend that you're doing all
this [\h__\h] to leave good money behind for
your family after you're dead that's for
him a
more moral sounding reason
than his actual reason which there is no
real reason cuz he's
just you know
spiraling yeah he wants to justify it so
he takes an answer and he's like yep
let's go
that yeah I how do I have so much to say
after because it's it's it's captured me
it's got me in its
claws and I
can't I can't I can't wrap my mind
around how how does this go on for Five
Seasons I just don't understand he was
so close to finishing it they could have
finished it after five episodes and be
like
yeah he did some [\h__\h] that was crazy but
the bodies are taken care of there's no
evidence he's fine if he just stays away
from trouble now he will be living his
life
fine but we'll
see yeah the body is hit the
blor
if I love the moment though when he
blows up the car from the rich guy who's
always on his
phone I like that that that's that's
when you really felt like oh yeah he
gave up on that's like the most recent
thing I watched I think but he already
gave up
on like getting back on the good track
the good
path he just blew up that guy's car are
there is is the implication that there's
no cameras at the gas station because
bro would wouldn't that guy ask to check
the cameras or is he too dump to and to
just is he just thinking that just
happened like naturally and so he
wouldn't even think it's from a person
doing that so he doesn't even think
about checking the cameras
or 2008 oh okay yeah I thought that
might be the case that it this takes
place so long ago that there might not
be cameras everywhere
H but Walter was literally the only
person around like he was so focused on
the car explosion he doesn't even notice
the only other person walking around
getting into his car and driving off he
even walks away so slowly bro sorry I'm
like really
I I I haven't processed all of this yet
I'm processing it right now with you
guys so I need to talk about
it maybe you guys should be rewatching
it so that you remember what I'm talking
about or do you have all of this in in
your memory
still you need to rewatch
it here your rewatch yeah you actually
caught me rewatch oh let's go you're
starting now you make me want to let's
do
it but yeah I was need to watch Arcane
[\h__\h] you never watched it Now's the Time
Now's the Time I only spoiled you a
little bit the first couple of three
four
episodes and even then I think if you
really didn't watch something then
hearing something like that it's like
you you can't really make the connection
usually
although I I talked in quite detail
about
it you needed an excuse to start it
yay it was it was like um I was like
looking for Netflix and I was like I
don't want to re-watch everything that I
rewatched before I'm look I do want to
watch something new right
now all right and it was it was in my
Netflix
recommendations quite up there at the
moment so I was was like H all right I'm
actually feeling this right
now so yeah you watched it rewatched a
couple weeks ago oh perfect
timing I think he's great he's a great
actor
and it does feel a little bit like uh
Hell in a different
Universe the way he's uh playing him but
it's still different enough like it's
not completely
the same he has his own
quirks plenty of his
own what did I
say I forgot the word that I just
said
twerks quirks quirks not
twerks
[\h__\h] what's a twerk twerking wait is
twerking the thing that I do with my
butt what the [\h__\h] oh I'm so confused
I'm so
confused I'm so
confused
help I'm losing my
mind the words are all not feeling like
words anymore in my
[Music]
brain plate
plen [\h__\h] I'm not feeling so well
[Music]
today [\h__\h] my brain worms are eating my
brain
alive okay now I can do this I believe
in
myself hey I didn't even have to scroll
that far okay I'm gonna read the Zelda
super chats from the last Zelda stream
while I still have a a working brain
somewhat working
[Music]
brain what collabing with
SH I was in shock you know I I I don't
mind uh cursed conversations you know I
I have my own cursed conversations but
she only lived she only she only lived
up to her
um wait that's the wrong one lived up to
her
reputation by starting the stream with
urine
talk I did not expect that Mama
Mia okay okay let's go let's go let's
go I'm just so
so you should go full unhinged I think I
just did I think
I just did that for a
moment but also I think
they probably thought I was a bit weird
when I talked about getting emotionally
attached to the rats in my house and
being sad when I left them but they
don't understand only kfp
understands the feelings
And the
emotions that I and we went through I do
sound crazy when I tell that story I
know right I felt crazy I felt it I felt
the Judgment when I was telling the
story but yeah you had to be
there it was a rough
time and really the chat was all I had
and and the chat helped me feel more
comfortable and like work through
this uncomfortable living
situation which
overall it wasn't just a living
situation it was the whole like all of
it together coming together and I feel
like the rats were the embodiment of all
of the problems I
had and then somebody taking that
and making it into something more
positive by making it into a
character really influenced
[Music]
me that was like such
a psychology moment
man Casper is my
psychologist
yeah crazy stuff
man it's just not a good feeling when
the place that you're living in gives
you the heie
jeebies
and just just it's not like you really
don't want to be there but you have to
be there cuz that's where you
live yeah I was constantly on
edge like I was scared to go
downstairs but they could be anywhere
but even especially downstairs scared
me
just it really scared
me but toilet and kitchen was downstairs
and the kitchen's oh man oh
man ah
man
yeah no I didn't like it didn't like it
at all bgm please okay okay sorry did
you guys like the EUR be remix that I
played in the beginning I just found
that today it was but that's been out
since a month I didn't know there was a
EUR beat remix it's really good please
go find it on YouTube if you type in
Mirage remix
kiata or like EUR beat Mirage remix Kata
and you can find it it's really good
leave them a
comment so
good okay wait uh music
[Music]
okay here we go Che 47 D unknown D Moon
D Ro to thank
you
oh thank you thank you thank you oh
thank you D kfp beat
D oh I'm about the your tournament
probably already ended but I hope it
went well did it go
Welly let's go no don't tap her to your
to your
door I think you zero too every H thanks
for the pinky I have never played a
Nintendo game Pokemon om Mario 2 what
but I heard that switch 2 will be
released soon soon so I became
interested should I buy a switch or not
no just at this point if you don't have
one wait for the switch 2 because the
switch 2 will be downwards compatible or
whatever you call it it can play switch
switch 2 will be able to play switch one
games so at this point just
wait backwards yeah backwards
compatible yeah but I think switch is
like one of the or de best console
honestly it depends on your game taste I
guess but like I wouldn't want to
I I can live without a
PlayStation like when even when we're
talking about
streaming I think I would have an easier
time restricting myself to switch games
rather than restricting myself to
PlayStation games that's just I mean I
think that's very different for some
people because there's a lot of great
games on
PlayStation but my general tastes always
go towards switch games
but it's good to have
both switch light probably still good a
good buy well maybe before but now that
the switch 2 is coming closer
no I didn't even consider the switch
light would have been a nice option if
it was there from the beginning but I'm
not going to I'm not going to buy two
switches not one of those crazy
people not going to throw out my money
like
that waited seven years I can wait
another for switch Yeah for real it's
been so long well well uh GD thanks for
the red super chat oh
GD good day
GDA K today's my birthday fourth one to
celebrate with UK Fe so here's my
birthday tags greatly appreciate all
your hard work to give us smashing
contents C you boss hope you don't mind
if I request a birthday song thanks of
course not oh my
God I'm sorry it took me so
long happy birthday GD yay yay yay
yay happy birthday to you
in the
H happy birthday C
[Music]
you
congratulations
yeah I hope that you are healthy and
happy and that it will stay like that
and I hope that you will stay in kfp
forever
yeah I need
GD I need you to tell me what super
chats to read
haha no but definitely even without that
I need
you not going anywhere let's go I'm
happy to hear
that thanks
mate
yeah hope you are doing well and
enjoying your life making the most out
of it as you
should me arus thank you for the pinky
oh another birthday hi K it's my
birthday and want to say that is very
fun to hang here with you and the kfp
community your streams are always a fun
time and I like how much you interact
with everyone hope we can be here for
many more years yeah I hope so too thank
you I do try to always interact with my
community also like for example in the S
more PG yeah thank you so much for being
part of kfp of this lovely Community me
arus happy
birthday here for you Tobe happy
birthday to you happy birthday in your
shoe happy happy birthday in your pants
too happy birthday M
arus yay y
yay oh nice you're here now
too congratulations all the Valentine's
baby
o I
see spicy
Valentine's don't point it out like
that why must you calculate
their birth
creation
being what's wrong with
you m arcade D random
person
Rex
[Music]
Tracy angry
Cru
D thank you we cleared the game I'm so
sad up thanks for the red super chat
another Zelda game down for the gamer
had a lot of fun watching the series
thank you for the playr hour thank you
as well I had a lot of fun
too I really
[Music]
have developed a big love for Zelda
games ever since I started streaming in
Holo like I like Zelda games before but
it wasn't until gaming literally became
my job where I
really
like you know confront myself with so
many
games by also always completing them cuz
like before this I don't know I don't I
didn't I didn't really complete many
games there's nothing that
really kept me going that long and and
you know I wasn't such a good gamer also
back in the days and was often just
watching my brother and so
on yeah no tails off games are a bit
different H off games are the exception
I mean the first one Symphonia I was
still so young and I was just like
playing together with my brother because
Symphonia was multiplayer mhm at least
for the
battles um but then after
Symphonia the games I picked up I did
play alone and I did use usually finish
them yeah but other games but yeah I I
really have been having a good time with
Zelda gam specifically and next year
there's probably not going to be a new
one so I hope I want to at least uh Play
One older one and finish it probably
like aaren of time or
so that's my
mission look forward to it thank you Kaa
abs PL of fls of fancy dun J SW B dun
take it monkey than for the pinky off
topic not the usual monkey Cho but 51%
monkey Cho was also very cute oh wait
was this after the mimicry game then
again mimicry W was cute in general VOD
gang had a great time the stream was as
fun as I expected also congrats on
beating Zelda it was a nice cute series
indeed it was what I was only 51% monkey
to you don't even believe that right J C
Monkey we no I am when I do monkey I do
monkey good I do 100% monkey if not 500%
come on I'm more monkey than a monkey is
a
[Music]
monkey I'm
monkey that's not really it but I can do
I can do good
monkey
yeah M and eight thanks for two pinkies
congrats D this was a pretty fun game
and a bit surprising that it was such a
solid Zelda game after the initial
reveal it was nice seeing the series
used din Naidu and far again yeah and
the tri showing up yeah yeah true I've
heard that kind of positive uh critique
that people liked that the Triforce
actually mattered again glad you enjoyed
it this game was pretty similar with
past handheld titles like links
Awakening Oracle games finish cap Etc it
will probably be a while until New Elum
yeah as I just said so if you're ever in
the mood for a Nava there's always do or
Ocarina Maj yeah I think next year
definitely okarina or Majora or
[Music]
um the dark one uh the what's it called
again The Dark One Twi princess yeah one
of those threee is definitely maybe even
two if I can't if there's no other games
on my
list there's no other good games
for a long
series The edgy one the super edgy
one oh yeah maybe I'll wait a bit for TP
to get a switch Port switch to
Port yeah my are also
dark I
know but yeah was a good game I sad that
now it will be a long time until the
next one but we still have some to en
Joy thankfully thank you
m m d and spankenheimer
[Music]
Baba
agreed
um
huh I think I might actually leave it at
dad because the next one
has surprisingly many super chats it's
intimidating me
me and I need to eat I don't even feel
my Hunger that much anymore but I know
I'm hungry and I know that I'm sleepy
and
exhausted tomorrow is incription
right at like 5:00 p.m. or so no not 5
6:00 p.m. maybe no Diablo oh
Diablo oops
H 6 p.m Diablo
okay all right all
right sure that's fine I hope I can get
some work done before because I don't
know if I'm going to get the work that I
wanted to get
done
now tomorrow tomorrow
today Wawa had intrusive thoughts of
wanting to fix her
garden that took up all my
power yeah there's no deadline for what
I need to do it's just motion capture
stuff
yeah hope you won't be sore for tomorrow
I I definitely
feel uh the workout that I did in my
legs and also it was really bad for my
back cuz I was constantly like hunching
down and tensing up my
hands that was not ideal and that's why
I'm saying I think next time I need to
do uh trim
edging trim edging Edge
trimming I'm going to call a
professional and maybe I should call a
professional for my current brain
problems as
well I'm going to
go I'm going to call a professional M
now blade
blocken uh bingles dongus no
uh B binted bogus binted
B
binted Bingo bed no BOS
binted yeah BOS B don't don't gu light
me
okay goodbye
everybody going to go drink some Tai tea
I thought taiy and chaii was the same
but I looked it up and it says it's
definitely different thing but I must
have not drunken chai in a while because
I can't remember the difference so much
I guess chai is a little bit
more
[Music]
cinnamony it's kind of similarly it's
kind
of but I really like the ti
te you mean tea TI No I mean TI te
maybe In tha they say TI Thai but I say
TI in
[Music]
English I like both I like CH te and I
like Tai
te but currently I only have the
capabilities of making Tai tea so I'll
will continue making Tai
tea I like it I don't like milk in
anything else in any other tea
okay I just have to say that out loud I
know I wrote it on Twitter already but I
need to State this out loud I hate milk
teas generally okay I don't hate them
but I dislike
them but in TI tea it's
good but I put a lot of brown sugar in
it a lot of it Mak it really sweet I
normally never put sugar in my tea if
only I I usually just put honey in my
tea this was my formal statement toward
words tea
[Music]
ingredients yeah I've heard people
recommending me condensed milk for taii
tea interesting I might try it out if
you I know condensed milk is a like
sweet right so if you put condensed milk
in I guess you're not really adding any
sugar anymore
probably ni I said TIY not Titi
[Music]
I put I put my ti tea in the fridge so
now I'm going to have cold tii tea I'm
excited but I also like it warm I want
to drink it warm and cold at the same
time cuz you're hot and you're cold yes
and
you you're out anyway Amigos
see you tomorrow for Diablo when I'm
hopefully I have hopefully regained my
my brain capacities my brain cells I've
burnt them it's probably the grass fumes
not the kind of grass fumes that you
would
think or maybe it's exactly the grass
fumes you would think because you know
I'm straight edged so the only grass
fumes that I would be talking about is
real grass from my
garden so anyway I'll stop talking now
[Music]
goodbye don't forget to vote for
Vite let them know but make a good
choice okay
[Music]
okay don't say something that is likely
for me to say right now don't forget to
Vite for votes I hope I didn't say that
[Music]
1 a