[Music]
wow it's really coming down hard oh you
followed me
do you want to stay warm inside and I
don't know make more cookies or
something
well either way
you didn't end up doing anything with
that mop and bucket why not help me out
of making a Snowman
you'll know how to make one surely
let's see uh we're gonna need a carrot a
hat a scarf definitely some rocks to
make the eyes and the mouth
[Music]
could be worse I guess
that took a while
and well it's cold
I feel like something's missing though
[Music]
foreign
sorry if I boss you around too much
today it's been kind of busy and I was a
little on the edge
hahaha
see I actually have something for you
I was saving this to give someone today
and I think
you're the Long Island I gave it to
you've been so kind to me today after
all
Happy Valentine's Day pumpkin
now back to work
to make the perfect arms
foreign
[Music]